@zulahni Oh, honey. Don't force us to stage an intervention. Look at your life. Look at your choices. #sassygayfriend    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Re: ARG Tools 2.1: bad news, the HTML entity is actually "&mdash" (no "e"). #htmlisweird    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Confirmed. It's like magic! :)    
    
    
    College flashback: I just backed New Studio Album from Toad the Wet Sprocket! on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/17pShAZ     
    
    
    If you're wondering why I'm not tweeting so much this weekend, check my other account: @curtiscchen #wwcon13    
    
    
    #wwcon13 day 2 (@ Sheraton Portland Airport Hotel - @spg) http://4sq.com/15CQxkH     
    
    
    .@ninjahq "Scorekeeper XL," currently FREE on app store: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/scorekeeper-xl/id463243024?mt=8 …    
    
    
    "You call this archaeology?" #wwcon13 #nonsequitur http://instagram.com/p/cj4_8qGpk3/     
    
    
    I'll take Manhattan #wwcon13 #nobittersthough http://instagram.com/p/cknbNLmpoz/     
    
    
    Maybe it's just me, but emergency vehicles driving up & down the runway shooting off flares seems bad. #pdx    
    
    
    Last day of #wwcon13! (@ Sheraton Portland Airport Hotel - @spg) http://4sq.com/18WiWn2     
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Only movie I've ever seen where the Nazis are the heroes. THE NAZIS. #thatssomefuckedupshitrightthere    
    
    
    @kateleth I misread that tweet as "I'm a missing person..." and it confused and frightened me.    
    
    
    @mariancall Awesome! @DeeAnnSole and I look forward to seeing you there. :) #PAX    
    
    
    Hey @chiuki what do you think of this @kickstarter project? "Chineasy: The easiest way to learn Chinese" http://kck.st/1bZUaEJ     
    
    
    @chiuki Yeah, I wonder about that too. Some combinations always seemed rather arbitrary to me.    
    
    
    @snarke FYI, @DeeAnnSole & I have started BOARDWALK EMPIRE. Just 1.06 episodes a day (avg) & we'll be all set for S3 premiere! :)    
    
    
    Helpful infographic of the day (NSFW): Boobs per episode in HBO's #GameOfThrones , season 1 -  http://imgur.com/r/gameofthrones/I0tWqHN … via @imgur    
    
    
    @ninjahq "The Pointy End." Hell of a show.    
    
    
    @maryrobinette That's positively scandalous.    
    
    
    I'm often confused when I get a newsletter from "Tor" and can't tell from subject line whether that's @tordotcom or http://torproject.org     
    
    
    @bm0nies @mariafi @FlameIsLove @ghalidrim @snarke Or $4 in HD. :) What can @DeeAnnSole & I bring to share? Wine? Snacks?    
    
    
    (Great talk, but now I'm hungry AND horny.) Al Vernacchio: Sex needs a new metaphor. Here's one ... http://on.ted.com/dhGh  #TED    
    
    
    So this happened: "The Fatberg Saga, By John Scalzi and Paul Sabourin" http://ow.ly/nGDD1  #meanwhileontheinternet    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ninjahq and many happy returns of the day! Hope you've got big fun plans for tonight. :)    
    
    
    Here's the thing.    
    
    
    What a week.    
    
    
    @erikwecks @MeiLinMiranda @jtw78 @jgurley Sorry, can't make it this week, but hope to see you all again soon! @curtiscchen    
    
    
    @dresdencodak You've taken your first step into a larger world... @stargatecommand :)    
    
    
    Dear self, stop messing with e-mail and just GO TO SLEEP.    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "Money for Nothing": Read "Money for Nothing" at 512 Words or FewerTrue: the imag... http://bit.ly/14dcZwW     
    
    
    .@angelamwebber Oh, that's a known bug: should be "grimlock." BTW, have you guys talked to Hasbro about that Velociraptor Dinobot yet? ;)    
    
    
    Movie sign! #romeoplusjuliet http://instagram.com/p/c0Q8j_mpu-/     
    
    
    @Galumbits Nope... Do you have a lead?    
    
    
    So, Romeo+Juliet. Now talking about other Shakespeare adaptations. Great night with friends and cocktails.    
    
    
    And then there's EPIC TEATIME with Alan Rickman.    
    
    
    @Galumbits If you can drive up to the 'Couve, you're welcome to stop by our apartment and meet her! DM me for e-mail, directions, etc.    
    
    
    Today's lunch. #thisisnotaclue http://instagram.com/p/c1hxr-GprF/     
    
    
    Volcanoes in Portland area: Rocky Butte, youngest, 97,000 years old; Oregon City, oldest, 1.4 million. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Great Missoula Floods (from glacier in Montana) 15,000-18,000 years ago carved out the topography of the Portland area. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Mt. St. Helens is youngest volcano in region, ~300k yrs old (most active since 45k); cf. Rainier, 1 million, and Hood, 900k. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    This is Professor Scott Burns, BTW: teaches Geology at PSU, consults with City of Portland, Stanford class of 1970. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    The Oak Tree Restaurant in Woodland, WA is supposed to have the greatest cinnamon rolls in the world. #stanfordtour #geologicallyimportant    
    
    
    This guy knows from terroir: http://geology.pdx.edu/node/67  #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Kalama, WA was supposed to be a major port, never developed; but it was the birthplace of @PyramidBrew . #stanfordtour    
    
    
    If you're retired, you can take classes for free at PSU. #stanfordtour #respectifyoure65andusinggoddamntwitter    
    
    
    @Galumbits We won't be home until after 9pm on Tuesday; is that too late for you guys? We're on east side, 205 & Mill Plain.    
    
    
    Lunch! #stanfordtour (@ Forest Learning Center) http://4sq.com/19jtj8j     
    
    
    @Galumbits We're busy every weeknight next week, unfortunately. How about next Saturday, the 17th, after 7:00pm?    
    
    
    @Galumbits (We're also free weekday afternoons, but I'm guessing you're not.)    
    
    
    Sunday Sunday Sunday    
    
    
    Trek minus two hours! (@ Cathedral Park w/ @lauraehall @brianenigma) http://4sq.com/18nhnhh     
    
    
    "Freeze program!" #trekinthepark #train    
    
    
    Fuck yeah.    
    
    
    @bm0nies @mariafi @snarke @FlameIsLove @ghalidrim @DeeAnnSole Let's do it again soon! Is everyone free next month on Friday the 13th? :)    
    
    
    @mariafi @ghalidrim @snarke @FlameIsLove How about Friday the 6th then? @DeeAnnSole & I can host, if y'all are willing to drive. :)    
    
    
    DAMN IT FEEL GOOD TO BE A GANGSTA    
    
    
    Lunchtime video chat! pic.twitter.com/1TKksjWZEO    
    
    
    ATTN @thedoubleclicks : "Researchers Breed Glow-in-the-Dark Rabbits" http://youtu.be/h3Gz1ZsfJmc  #thewayiglow    
    
    
    Tell your friends who live elsewhere about the "Portlandia 'Walkabout' Experience" Sweepstakes: http://ow.ly/nUAkl     
    
    
    I *finally* own the Les Miserables "dream cast" recording in MP3 format. HOW DID I LIVE UNTIL TODAY?!? #theatergeek    
    
    
    @ellenjuhlin Honey, I still got the original Broadway cast recording on AUDIO CASSETTE and the concert performance on LASERDISC. :) #oldman    
    
    
    The @Kickstarter video for @viennateng 's new music project is totally worth <3 minutes of your time: http://kck.st/19fTKIp     
    
    
    Who will I see at the SFWA Readings in Portlandia tonight? http://www.sfwa.org/other-resources/for-readers/reading-series/sfwa-northwest-reading-series/ …    
    
    
    playing hooky (@ Cinetopia for Despicable Me 2) http://4sq.com/1dbamn8     
    
    
    Well, I guess it's time to get to work now.    
    
    
    I'm guessing @jonrog1 's Twitter account just got hacked. #happenstothebestofus    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "My Least Favorite Martian": Read "My Least Favorite Martian" at 512 Words or Few... http://bit.ly/16sZ78B     
    
    
    Photoset: hello-the-future: ilikeyourstuffs: continuants: mememolly: luckycatproject: Lucky Cats - LOLcats... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIssSp7-B     
    
    
    "Is Pon Farr like pudding?" "...It's SORT OF like pudding." #talkingtonontrekfans    
    
    
    Supplies! #namethatgame http://instagram.com/p/dGXuUGGpnm/     
    
    
    Just finished a game of Last Night on Earth: Timber Peak. Now starting Dungeon Roll. Why, it's almost like being at #GenCon! #notreally    
    
    
    @GoingLast Welcome to the Internet! ;)    
    
    
    @pdunwin @HellcowKeith ...that depends on the pudding. #HEYO    
    
    
    #SOON (@ Trek In The Park - @atomicarts) http://4sq.com/13HWx90     
    
    
    It's a pre-Trek in the Park picnic w/ @DeeAnnSole @ckwright @mariafi @ghalidrim @JadeE1024 @3hubcaps @snarke !    
    
    
    The cello is flying! @thedoubleclicks #teamaubrey http://instagram.com/p/dIwkawGpjs/     
    
    
    If not already, I suspect @NATEofBORG will henceforth be known as "scene-stealer" Scotty. #trekinthepark    
    
    
    I <3 @GailSimone . #thatisall    
    
    
    BTW, saw my first trailer for HOW TO TRAIN YOUR DRAGON 2 last Thursday. It was fine, but completely devoid of intentional comedy. #worrisome    
    
    
    @feliciaday "Floor dirty? No, floor clean!" #iapologizefornothing    
    
    
    I hate chewing.    
    
    
    @joshmillard Have fun! Great show this year. You probably already know to keep an eye out for @GarrettRWang :)    
    
    
    @Galumbits I'll e-mail you and cc: @DeeAnnSole :)    
    
    
    @ninjahq it's government island according to @PDXFire    
    
    
    @maryannjohanson Many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    I will ALWAYS push it to 30 for @TheDoubleclicks #podcasting    
    
    
    Heyyy @lessachu @ellenjuhlin :) MT @arielwaldman: Know awesome Bay Area women? Invite them to Science Hack Day: http://sciencehackday2013.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    this is going well    
    
    
    OF COURSE it's from Portland: "The Rum of Giant Robots" http://cheezburger.com/7734686208  via @feedly    
    
    
    GUYS I just realized "Top Gear" is an AUTOMOTIVE DOUBLE ENTENDRE now where's my goddamn GetGlue or Viggle or whatever the fuck thing    
    
    
    #latetotheparty #nothowitworks #toobigtotweet    
    
    
    @dinabugg @Galumbits <zoidberg>Hooray!</zoidberg>    
    
    
    @ninjahq @Galumbits Thanks! We're very happy with this result. :)    
    
    
    In other news, @DeeAnnSole still does not get how knock-knock jokes work. #loveyouwife    
    
    
    In related news, @DeeAnnSole just spelled "Squirtle" with a "D"--a letter which does not appear in either "squirt" or "turtle." #loveyouwife    
    
    
    ??? pic.twitter.com/xwluzlnfFR    
    
    
    @jmacfee yeah apparently we don't watch enough tv    
    
    
    LADIES PLEASE ONE AT A TIME pic.twitter.com/7Isz9FiazQ    
    
    
    Takenoko! with @AubreyCello (not pictured) pic.twitter.com/5jXeqnbTaW    
    
    
    @Molly23 is so weird sometimes.    
    
    
    The music for today's Google Doodle was one of the first pieces I ever learned to play on the piano. Beautiful. http://ow.ly/o9yWI     
    
    
    On the road again! California, here we come!    
    
    
    Almost at the border. (@ Suncrest Rest Area) http://4sq.com/12tVGuX     
    
    
    Welcome to California!    
    
    
    GOOD MORNING PALO ALTO, BRING US YOUR FINEST COFFEECAKES AND EGGS BENEDICT.    
    
    
    Breakfast! (at @Hobees Restaurant w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16WfkDw     
    
    
    Sure, Ned, I'll give you a dollar.    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "The End": Read "The End" at 512 Words or FewerThis is the last of my weekly flas... http://bit.ly/16WSsnh     
    
    
    @gailsimone ...and then an image of Bill Gates filled the screen, along with the text THINK ON YOUR SINS. A building in Cupertino exploded.    
    
    
    The 50+ Greatest Tweets about Ben Affleck's casting as Batman http://ow.ly/odSB1     
    
    
    (For the record, I thought @BenAffleck did just fine in DAREDEVIL.)    
    
    
    In-person Sci-Fi Book Club meeting! Discussing @loversdiction 's novel EVERY DAY with @aprilgirl2 @thebrianlynch @DeeAnnSole .    
    
    
    We are now watching DREDD. Long story. Don't ask.    
    
    
    Okay, now switching to EUROPA REPORT.    
    
    
    @anthonyha Aw, of course you're in PDX the same weekend we're down in the Bay Area. Hopefully we can meet up next time!    
    
    
    Good news, everyone! EUROPA REPORT did not suck. Slow to get started, but if you liked Landis novel MARS CROSSING, you'll probably enjoy.    
    
    
    @radven Could be! Palo Alto right now, Half Moon Bay tonight, SF tomorrow. You?    
    
    
    @radven We'll be back on Monday, if you're still around Portland!    
    
    
    P.S. @anthonyha @radven You MUST go see Trek in the Park this weekend! Ideally TODAY with @TheDoubleclicks ! :) http://ow.ly/oeuae     
    
    
    Hey, we gotta eat breakfast SOMEWHERE. (at @Hobees Restaurant w/ @aprilgirl2 @thebrianlynch) http://4sq.com/1dd1ikq     
    
    
    Wedding vows of the year: "I will never harm you, or, through inaction, allow you to come to harm." Congratulations Sunshine & Acorn!!!!    
    
    
    You don't have to go home but you can't stay here #weddingmusic https://vine.co/v/hexFuiIVq2Y     
    
    
    Wedding lights! It's possible we weren't supposed to push the buttons. But, c'mon, Gamers here. https://vine.co/v/hexQDruEUD6     
    
    
    The wedding cake is a 3-D crossword puzzle! (We got paper copies.) @ The Ritz-Carlton, Half Moon Bay http://instagram.com/p/dauDfSmpsS/     
    
    
    Solve time: <1 wedding reception. #thiswasaclue http://instagram.com/p/da-Q_BGpry/     
    
    
    I wonder if anyone has ever attempted to DJ a wedding using only Girl Talk tracks.    
    
    
    #ObThrillerDance https://vine.co/v/he2ZwK2dIX6     
    
    
    It's art I say! https://vine.co/v/he2m6w0I6tJ     
    
    
    @lahosken The words flow over the edges, this one "leftward:" JOB CHANGE    
    
    
    #ObHavaNagila https://vine.co/v/he2TnxDwIqL     
    
    
    There's a word for what happened here tonight: SWELLEGANT. Congratulations, Sunshine & Acorn! Thanks for an awesome wedding party!    
    
    
    @kwylie @mattcleinman YOU LIE! On Ceti Alpha V there was life!    
    
    
    OH: "There's an adult video store, they MIGHT have some stuff."    
    
    
    Now it's a REAL lunch meeting: @DeeAnnSole just drew a pie chart on the butcher paper table covering.    
    
    
    Oregon welcomes you!    
    
    
    Rainy days and Mondays always make me... less likely to tweet? I dunno. Lame pun/joke, pop culture/politics reference, ironic hashtag. DONE.    
    
    
    @snarke Did you know you can buy a kilo of 99.9% pure anhydrous caffeine powder for ~$30 (plus shipping)? Add some pep to any drink! :)    
    
    
    Just finished signing another one-year lease on our apartment. Expect to see our faces around Portlandia for at least that much longer!    
    
    
    #fandom Man Of Steel 2 Teaser Trailer - Ben Affleck / Bryan Cranston (FAN MADE): http://youtu.be/U4U4he3GgC4  via @youtube    
    
    
    @rmalena You have a very sensitive disposition. ;)    
    
    
    @jmacfee I KNOW RIGHT    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu Please define "helping out." :)    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu Sorry, bad timing--we'll still be in Make-a-Strip then. Sounds like fun though!    
    
    
    Well, I guess it's time to start packing for #PAX .    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu I'm your huckleberry. :)    
    
    
    @MayflowerPark We're arriving today. What time is check-in? 3:00pm? (can't find info on web site or in confirmation e-mail)    
    
    
    @mayflowerpark We're all set. Thanks for your help!    
    
    
    So who else is in town for #PAX ?    
    
    
    @notNksanymore @sin_plague Awesome! I think @littlelull is organizing some kind of Sea Monkey thing; are y'all in the loop on on that?    
    
    
    @notNksanymore OK, clearly you know more than I do. ;)    
    
    
    Okay WHO ELSE do I know here. (@ Triple Door - @thetripledoor w/ @bm0nies @zulahni) http://4sq.com/188X5Hm     
    
    
    @ninjahq @ftcup You chose... poorly. ;)    
    
    
    @ninjahq Yeah yeah. Like you're going to touch his mohawk or something. Dream on, K&R. :)    
    
    
    @jeffphi Monday morning maybe? We're here until Tuesday.    
    
    
    @erikwecks @jonathanhliu We might try to sneak in after Make-a-Strip, if there's room. Otherwise we'll look for you later!    
    
    
    @davidscotton Groovy. Are we going to try to do dinner sometime?    
    
    
    @davidscotton We're turning in early tonight. Check in tomorrow?    
    
    
    Attention, #PAX @GeekDads photo hunters: I can help you with at least one of the items today. :) http://ow.ly/omSqf     
    
    
    @rael doesn't know we're sitting behind him and to the left #pax    
    
    
    @mattcleinman You know us so well. :)    
    
    
    Snack & game break in WSCC room 304! #pax    
    
    
    Apparently I've played Borderlands enough that I can draw the vault symbol from memory. Now I have a… http://instagram.com/p/dqFooYmplq/     
    
    
    @davidscotton Maybe. @DeeAnnSole is playing an RPG now; I'm in a panel at Sheraton. Do you have dinner plans yet?    
    
    
    @davidscotton Check in with us when you're done with that? :)    
    
    
    @davidscotton Want to meet me downstairs in a few minutes? Wrapping up now.    
    
    
    @davidscotton bottom of escalator, near revolving doors?    
    
    
    @davidscotton On my way! Now    
    
    
    Day 1 of #PAX complete: included fun panels, walking expo hall, gaming, meeting @pigsquad, dinner with @davidscotton . Tomorrow: MOAR!    
    
    
    @zulahni @bm0nies @krissywrites @roscone That would be Team Meat, booth 125 (promo for new game Mew-Genics). You can go 2 at a time! #PAX    
    
    
    @zulahni LET'S MAKE THIS HAPPEN    
    
    
    I've bested Chapter 1 of The Room. Chapter 2 awaits! http://bit.ly/NyNpkE     
    
    
    @calamityjamie Hope you're having a great PAX! Any chance you'll have time this weekend to play a certain card game in person? :)    
    
    
    @calamityjamie Groovy. No rush, we're in town until Tuesday. Enjoy pin trading!    
    
    
    Seeing a lot of Superman shirts at #PAX this year. Wonder if we have Zack Snyder to thank for that.    
    
    
    Also, best #PAX cosplay so far today: PotatOS from Portal 2. (sorry, no pic)    
    
    
    @zulahni Looks like you're busy. Virtual hug! Wave!    
    
    
    Back in line for Acquisitions Inc. Also: snack time! #PAX    
    
    
    @ninjahq You're probably ahead of us. We're in the same column, at the front edge of the fire escape.    
    
    
    @ninjahq strike that, we're in col 4. You're definitely ahead :)    
    
    
    @ninjahq Do K&R have dinner plans?    
    
    
    @ninjahq Yes! Tell us where to meet you :)    
    
    
    I'm at Paramount Theatre - @stgpresents for MC Frontalot, The Doubleclicks and Hideo (Seattle, WA) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/1dDcUxk     
    
    
    @davidscotton Apparently not. :) Where are you sitting? Or are you one of the standing-up cool kids?    
    
    
    #teamaubrey #pax #thatisall    
    
    
    Also, how much do I love that @angelamwebber wrote an entire song about shutting down hecklers. #pax @TheDoubleclicks    
    
    
    @davidscotton heading out now, enjoy frontalot :)    
    
    
    Just finished The Room: Epilogue. Great little puzzle game, looking forward to the sequel later this year!    
    
    
    What the hell, calves. Stop it. We've got two more days of #PAX to get through.    
    
    
    Breakfast! With DeeAnn, Darla, Karin, Bryan, and our good friend coffee. (at @LolaSeattle w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/17A9Izc     
    
    
    ATTN @davidscotton :) MT @TheDoubleclicks: PAX! We're in Bandland at 11am today & there most of the day. Stop by! 4th floor of main hall.    
    
    
    MARCO (@ Expo Hall @ PAX w/ 10 others) http://4sq.com/1e4Gc5G     
    
    
    #whilesupplieslast “@PuzzledPint: Seattle puzzlers: find @sparCKL at #PAX and he just might give you an official PUZZLED PINT logo sticker!”    
    
    
    Sokobond! #pax #protip    
    
    
    @gfilpus shameless pandering    
    
    
    @rkhoo #mathishard    
    
    
    Boy it is humid in Seattle. #pax    
    
    
    Off to play the Pathfinder card game with @DeeAnnSole . What are y'all up to this fine evening? #PAX    
    
    
    Adventure is in the cards! (That one's free @mikeselinker ) #pax @ Washington State Convention Center http://instagram.com/p/dvpvBgGptt/     
    
    
    @angelamwebber Who are you and what have you done with Angela? ;) #ikidbecauseilove    
    
    
    It's dangerous to go alone! Take this COFFEE. #PAX    
    
    
    .@DeeAnnSole agrees :) “@jonathanhliu: Last day of a con, same old problem: still so many games, never enough time.” #PAX    
    
    
    Achievement unlocked! #PAX XP @ Washington State Convention Center http://instagram.com/p/dxOY6JmpkU/     
    
    
    Just played a student-made submarine game using holograms projected in translucent liquid tub. Fun demo! #pax    
    
    
    @mariancall Please stop doing that. I hear you don't have health insurance.    
    
    
    Someone is actually doing Freebird on the freeplay stage. Really? #PAX #really    
    
    
    Find a tabletop BEFORE checking out the tabletop game. #PAX #protip    
    
    
    Ticket To Ride with 5 players gets kind of cutthroat. #PAX http://instagram.com/p/dxlRFjmpv0/     
    
    
    Good night, #PAX . Good work. Sleep well. I'll most likely kill you in the morning.    
    
    
    @SyamaMishra She doesn't get eaten by the eels at this time.    
    
    
    @zulahni We're just leaving to meet some friends at a food place in Fremont. Want to come with?    
    
    
    @rkhoo Thank YOU. Day 4 was a challenge, but totally worth it.    
    
    
    @davidscotton It was great to see you at PAX! Sorry we didn't get to play a game together. We'll plan better next year. :)    
    
    
    @angelamwebber Converting between video formats is a can of worms which can eat your life. Do you have specific Qs? Feel free to e-mail me.    
    
    
    Today we are celebrating Jasper-cat's birthday by lounging around so he can sleep on us. It's a tough job, but somebody's gotta do it.    
    
    
    @Galumbits We're so glad she's fitting into your family. :) @DeeAnnSole    
    
    
    Mummies! (@ Oregon Museum of Science & Industry (OMSI) - @omsi) http://4sq.com/1cLboFx     
    
    
    @sequentialart Hey, will the gallery be open today before the 6pm reception? Just wondering if we can show up early. Thanks!    
    
    
    Out of the mouths of babes... pic.twitter.com/qlbI7lI1Yv    
    
    
    @ninjahq So how do you feel about this whole thing? @DeeAnnSole & I had a long talk about it on the way home from PAX.    
    
    
    @ninjahq @DeeAnnSole Fair enough, we'll talk in person sometime soon I'm sure. :)    
    
    
    No, I'm sorry, you can't just make Pepper's Ghost and call it a "hologram." Nice gimmick, but no. http://igg.me/p/441195/twtr/1844977 …    
    
    
    [blog] Be a Part of My 40th Birthday Project: TL;DR:  Tell me how we met!  :)Back in 2010, I ran a birthday ar... http://bit.ly/1dWdSoy     
    
    
    This will be the first of many tweets encouraging you to participate in My 40th Birthday Project :) http://ow.ly/oBP6m  #thanksinadvance    
    
    
    @wes_chu Thank you!    
    
    
    It takes a surprising amount of effort to make one's blog NOT look like total crap. #protip    
    
    
    @jmacfee You were #2 on the form (not counting my wife); @wes_chu was #1 on the blog. Time-wise, you beat him by a good 93 minutes. :)    
    
    
    @jmacfee ...but you got my e-mail 1st & @wes_chu responded to my later tweet. So you're both pretty, NOW GET BACK TO WRITING.    
    
    
    Just to be clear, I'm not fishing for compliments, I want an honest answer: How did we meet? http://ow.ly/oBVYY     
    
    
    Facebook on iOS: slow app, or SLOWEST FREAKIN' APP EVER?    
    
    
    Now playing: Monaco pic.twitter.com/gqy7gZBO6O    
    
    
    "Do you have control over your monkey?" "No." #monaco    
    
    
    "Okay, I'll try it again but this time I won't be an idiot." #monaco    
    
    
    @bananacave @snarke "What if my battery dies? You are responsible for showing proof of valid fare to TriMet ..." http://trimet.org/mobiletickets/faq.htm …    
    
    
    Hey, how did we meet? (That's right, I'm going to be nagging y'all about this for three more weeks. Get used to it!) http://snout.org/40survey     
    
    
    @bm0nies Okay, I'm gonna need an episode name here, for context.    
    
    
    @bm0nies First season TNG? That explains a lot. :)    
    
    
    I should look at the @GeekPortland calendar more often.    
    
    
    @Mastermindhunts No problem! Would you be willing to talk on our @teamsnout podcast about #rogueagent after it happens? Sounds very cool.    
    
    
    Just in case you missed the shameless self-promotion this morning, my story "Don't Fence Me In" is now in print: http://ow.ly/oItg5     
    
    
    I am torn between the desire to ask for what I want and the fear that I will be rejected. Must be Tuesday. #rimshot    
    
    
    @tereshkova2001 You are my people!    
    
    
    Yeah, I still don't really understand how about.me is supposed to work. Let's try clicking here! Hey, something changed! #infinitemonkeys    
    
    
    Photoset: thedoubleclicks: selfie cats! SO GOOD! TOTES ADORBS http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIsuiQ7XX     
    
    
    Emergency printing for @puzzledpint ! (at @FedExOffice Print & Ship Center) http://4sq.com/1e0oIss     
    
    
    Wow, that's... Okay. Wow. (beat) TWO? I mean, really: one, TWO? Wow. pic.twitter.com/KsUtz2lcpT    
    
    
    [blog] The Famine Teams: District 11, Agriculture: Jasper here!  This is part eleven in a twelve-part series, ... http://bit.ly/1ei9twa     
    
    
    I'm at Cinetopia for The World's End (Vancouver, WA) http://4sq.com/18V10qs     
    
    
    THE WORLD'S END did not disappoint. What can I say except I want @simonpegg @nickjfrost & @edgarwright to make more shows together?    
    
    
    Good news, everyone! http://ow.ly/oN7K5  #bettercallsaul    
    
    
    @gfilpus Thanks for volunteering to write some puzzles for @PuzzledPint ! When can we see your prototypes? :) #onlyhalfjoking    
    
    
    [blog] Haven't We Met?: I've ordered some rain for tomorrowPDX will be sunny but wetAnd out of nowhere you're ... http://bit.ly/1g4QiBN     
    
    
    Dear Twitter followers (and Facebook friends): How did we meet? http://snout.org/40survey     
    
    
    @littlelull Thank you! :)    
    
    
    @brittamarie Thank you! And yeah, we use paper lists too. They're still super effective.    
    
    
    @snarke DREAM BIG    
    
    
    Now playing: Last Night on Earth - Timber Peak #zombies http://instagram.com/p/eOj08kmpng/     
    
    
    OH: "A bag of dildos?" #nocontextforyou    
    
    
    Tired of Cards Against Humanity? Try playing "Taboo" (a.k.a. @TheEllenShow "Heads Up") w/ @CAH cards. It's unreasonably hilarious. #protip    
    
    
    @geekportland We'll be there tomorrow! What else should we look for?    
    
    
    To be fair, Hansel & Gretel never claimed to be *good* witch hunters; merely that they were specialists. #badmovies    
    
    
    #TNG https://vine.co/v/hnIAIal01HD     
    
    
    @littlelull Here's looking at you, kid. (with @DeeAnnSole ) pic.twitter.com/K0JeTz1ZM2    
    
    
    @thedoubleclicks I love you guys. Don't ever change.    
    
    
    [blog] The Famine Teams: District 12, Mining: Jasper here!  This is part twelve in a twelve-part series, looki... http://bit.ly/1f7quHu     
    
    
    OMG YOU GUYS @snarke MADE THE BEST VLOG EVER: http://youtu.be/AzwF_Z41LXU     
    
    
    @camillethegriep Thanks! I really enjoyed your story "Heart Made of Ground" too. I think Lucille & Betty would be BFFs in another world. :)    
    
    
    I'm at Cinetopia for Elysium (Vancouver, WA) http://4sq.com/157Adf3     
    
    
    @littlelull Many happy returns of the day! We'll see you downtown this evening. Don't wait up. :)    
    
    
    Les Miserables... with LIGHTSABERS! Star Wars/Les Miz epic mashup battle: http://youtu.be/e8PxrzAczOs  via @youtube    
    
    
    Um, yes. "once you have taken a bunch of people's money to do a thing, you have to actually do that thing" http://ow.ly/p4GPM     
    
    
    It's going to take a little time to get used to all this zooming. #iOS7    
    
    
    Mystery!    
    
    
    I appear to be on some kind of "hunt." (@ Funhouse Lounge) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1gMKoWi     
    
    
    I HAVE THE BEST FRIENDS EVER. THAT IS ALL.    
    
    
    So this is happening now. @ Papa Murphys http://instagram.com/p/eikby8mpqP/     
    
    
    Everyone else is in costume, now I am too. http://instagram.com/p/eitD7wmptZ/     
    
    
    Thank you, thank you, THANK YOU to everyone who was a part of today's surprise (to me) celebration. I am speechless with delight.    
    
    
    Nanny goat questions? @ Pacific Crest Community School http://instagram.com/p/ejLqwFGpnp/     
    
    
    @bm0nies Thank you! And no worries, I'm sure we'll see each other again soon. Drinks will be drunk. :)    
    
    
    @ObliviousWit Once you find your center, you are sure to win, dude.    
    
    
    @mattcleinman @rmalena You guys are unbelievable. Let's be best friends forever, okay? :)    
    
    
    Ten years ago, for my 30th birthday, I went to SpaceCamp (video: http://www.youtube.com/v/Ukm-XScoE_M?version=3&start=15&end=60&autoplay=1 … ). That was super cool... (1/5)    
    
    
    ...but what happened yesterday, for my 40th birthday, was even more amazing. My friends ran a Star Trek puzzle hunt just for me... (2/5)    
    
    
    ...including actors in full costume & custom-built electronics, culminating in an epic Starship Artemis mission on stage... (3/5)    
    
    
    ...and I am hugely fortunate to know awesome, creative, generous, crazy people who love making fun things! THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH. (5/5)    
    
    
    ...followed by one of @DeeAnnSole 's signature EndGame parties, with great food and drinks. BEST BIRTHDAY SURPRISE EVER... (4/5)    
    
    
    @ellenjuhlin Thanks! Looking forward to seeing you and your team next weekend at @TheFamineGame :)    
    
    
    @lauraehall Belay that, Helm, don't be a weirdo. ;)    
    
    
    [blog] Do You Speak Spanish?: You do?  Great!  Want to tell me what this voicemail (apparently a robo-call, al... http://bit.ly/15kfb7z     
    
    
    [blog] Puzzle Reciprocity: TL;DR: solve this video clue and get a tiny prize!*(Famine Game peeps: find Curtis ... http://bit.ly/15kAA0v     
    
    
    I think I have a happiness hangover. <3    
    
    
    My @stickermule shipment arrived today! http://instagram.com/p/en3xnNGppJ/     
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Look, I can't be a part of anything illegal.    
    
    
    @mariafi DO IT :)    
    
    
    For my party last Saturday, @DeeAnnSole got @HOTLIPSpizza , bao & dumplings from @stumplings , and cakes from http://larsonsbakery.net  !    
    
    
    Photo: tragedyseries: Friends, Readers, Rivals, I am overjoyed to announce some exciting developments that... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIsvwwDbN     
    
    
    NO, the question is, why do YOU have so FEW comm badges? #keepthischannelopen pic.twitter.com/1SYFNCy3yO    
    
    
    @adamd Come on up, we'll be happy to guide you through this foreign wilderness. :)    
    
    
    @jhelwig Your 21st-century "money" can be useful here: http://ow.ly/pbmHh  (shiny) or http://ow.ly/pbmJ6  (less shiny) #HTH    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma @civrot Aha! http://thatsaspicymeatball.com/post/46513917699/telnet-spaceclaw-net …    
    
    
    Help me get to 100 responses before October 1st! We're so close! http://snout.org/40survey     
    
    
    Oh dark thirty and we're prepping for infil.    
    
    
    Strapped in and ready to fly.    
    
    
    Welcome to Virginia! http://instagram.com/p/evmbWMmpu3/     
    
    
    Weekend read: get a FREE Kindle copy of weird Western anthology w/ "Don't Fence Me In" by @curtiscchen (that's me!) http://ow.ly/pg6Bm     
    
    
    Happy Birthday @mikeselinker and many happy returns of the day! Hope you've got fun plans for the weekend. We sure do. :)    
    
    
    Acquiring provisions for @thefaminegame (at @Walmart Supercenter) http://4sq.com/1h8xtxX     
    
    
    Starting tonight, I'm playing @TheFamineGame with an awesome group of people. Follow @teamsnout for event-related tweets, possibly NSFW.    
    
    
    .@thefaminegame begins! #faminegame (@ Artisphere w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/14PXXSm     
    
    
    @angelamwebber Yes and yes: http://www.geniesdivision.com/breakfast.php     
    
    
    Fueling up for #faminegame (@ Starbucks) http://4sq.com/1eOYwS4     
    
    
    Cornucopia! #faminegame http://instagram.com/p/ezjAyimpqX/     
    
    
    Thanks @thefaminegame for a great weekend! @teamsnout had a fantastic time and can't wait to do it again. :) http://4sq.com/17fPFUK     
    
    
    @lessachu @lahosken I think he meant "inconceivable!" ;) #faminegame    
    
    
    Friends! Please take a few minutes today to do my "how we first met" survey. It's for my birthday. :) http://snout.org/40survey     
    
    
    Tired but happy after 30 hours of @TheFamineGame , 14 hours of sleep, and lunch with Rich & Mike of Team Bloodshot. Tomorrow, I turn 40.    
    
    
    @wakjagner Nothing terribly exciting, but video games will probably be involved at some point. :) Thanks!    
    
    
    @littlelull @DeeAnnSole @alvyon Thanks! And Happy Anniversary to you two crazy kids!    
    
    
    @DeeAnnSole LOVE YOU WIFE :)    
    
    
    @geekamama Thank you!    
    
    
    @lahosken Thank you!    
    
    
    [blog] This is 40: The last ten days have been full of so much awesome, I can hardly believe it.  I'm forty ye... http://bit.ly/18Lp56C     
    
    
    @ninjahq Thank you!    
    
    
    @rmalena Thanks! And yeah, we can do a brief #faminegame show-and-tell at @PuzzledPint next Tuesday. :)    
    
    
    @civrot Thank you!    
    
    
    @brittamarie Thank you!    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu Thanks!    
    
    
    I am totally getting real important stuff done today. Ish.    
    
    
    [blog] Now Hear This: Eventually, somebody's going to figure out that these recorded messages are going to the... http://bit.ly/1caHE7w     
    
    
    Day Four: Phlegm    
    
    
    Pensive cat is pensive. pic.twitter.com/n6DrJh7Olf    
    
    
    how does twitter work again    
    
    
    I'm not ready to give up yet.    
    
    
    Schrödinger's Blog: An Open Letter to Speaker Boehner from a Game Designer - selinker: Hello, Speaker... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIswzu946     
    
    
    My favorite part of having multiple iPads is pretending to work like Captain Picard. http://ow.ly/i/3lBB9     
    
    
    Michelle Rodríguez as Wonder Woman would be a goddamn revelation, but it'll never happen. She would hate wearing the blue contact lenses.    
    
    
    Power outage!    
    
    
    Just reported our outage by phone to @ClarkPUD .    
    
    
    The power is back on!    
    
    
    Does the iOS "Remote" app not support screen rotation any more? That is the weakest of weak sauces.    
    
    
    Just emptied my @scottevest for washing. This is what was in the pockets. Not even 4 lbs! #semperparatus pic.twitter.com/Ubx7XvB7Dv    
    
    
    Looks like I'll be working on set this Wednesday!    
    
    
    @erikwecks @anniebellet @MeiLinMiranda @jgurley @jtw78 I'll be there!    
    
    
    Winter is coming and @TheDoubleclicks are ready: http://ow.ly/pEpay  #catsandnetflix    
    
    
    Off to work I go. pic.twitter.com/TnxoOc2gQH    
    
    
    Going radio silent now. Have a great day, everyone! pic.twitter.com/nGtT8xjQ6L    
    
    
    All done with a short day of perp-walking on #Grimm . Thanks to Paul & assorted other PAs who wrangled 6+ different groups of extras!    
    
    
    The only thing I hate more than wikis is CMSes. Seriously, they're all terrible. Just let me edit the goddamn files, okay?    
    
    
    I'm at Cinetopia for Gravity 3D (Vancouver, WA) http://4sq.com/GIhE5J     
    
    
    Projection problems #cinetopia pic.twitter.com/5N8nCdBQbU    
    
    
    GRAVITY was very good. Maybe a bit of a cheat, but go see it anyway. (See @neiltyson 's "Mysteries of #Gravity " tweets for nitpicking.)    
    
    
    Aaannnd I'm not planning to see any more movies in 3D. Got caught up in the GRAVITY hype, but the overall effect is still just distracting.    
    
    
    .@ninjahq You asked for it. This is all the visible stuff; I'll do a neater pic with everything laid out later: http://flic.kr/p/gxoVZi     
    
    
    @ninjahq It's one of these: http://angusnoble.com/indium/     
    
    
    @ninjahq Also this :) http://en.memory-alpha.org/wiki/Palm_beacon …    
    
    
    Tonight in games: Sokobond is mildly frustrating, Monster Loves You is charming, Plants vs Zombies 2 has goddamn pirates.    
    
    
    Couldn't decide on an @IgnitePortland idea so I submitted both: one musical ( http://ow.ly/pI5pd  ), one not ( http://ow.ly/pI5pe  ).    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma I only have mostly good things to say on both topics! :)    
    
    
    HAPPY BIRTHDAY @lahosken and many happy returns of the day! #thisisnotaclue    
    
    
    .@OMSI member night was great! Smaller crowds, not so many children. Sherlock Holmes exhibit was cool too. Loved the stamp/punch guidebook.    
    
    
    My dreams have been getting more complicated lately.    
    
    
    Last night, it was something about business travel, corporate shenanigans, and bad roommates.    
    
    
    The night before, it was being sworn in as a @PortlandPolice uniform and then going to a rural convenience store. #dreamjournal    
    
    
    I'm not sure what any of it means, except I guess I'm getting a good night's sleep?    
    
    
    FIGHT THE POWER - RT @CoreKnell: How to opt out of Google's new Shared Endorsement ads.  (Doublespeak of the month!) http://techcrunch.com/2013/10/11/google-to-start-employing-user-ratings-and-photos-in-shared-endoresments-ads/ …    
    
    
    "Many successful women suffer from impostor syndrome. Impostor syndrome is the feeling that you’re a..." http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIsxTQSjH     
    
    
    ?!?!? MT @pdxalerts: 2 men seen w/ molotov cocktail on railroad tracks near N Columbia & Peninsular. Train tracks now on fire. ~L    
    
    
    Movie night success! DROP DEAD GORGEOUS viewing complete. Also, everyone really wants to like "Agents of SHIELD"... but nobody does yet.    
    
    
    @ninjahq @IgnitePortland WHAT    
    
    
    "Why does it matter so much that I don't think you're funny?" MT @barbara_holm: 71 comments...People got really mad? http://www.portlandmercury.com/BlogtownPDX/archives/2013/10/12/my-least-favorite-piece-of-misogyny-this-week-comedy-bullies?section=41938 …    
    
    
    Is anybody else having to force-quit iTunes at least once a day since the last update? v11.1.1 on OS X 10.7.5 here. Just curious.    
    
    
    @Sminthian @ghalidrim Thanks for the info. Is either of you running a third-party streaming app (e.g., Connect360, Airfoil)?    
    
    
    @Alphastream please follow me so I can DM you :) #kthxbai    
    
    
    [blog] I'm Sure You're Shocked...: ...by the results of this online quiz I just took.  Procrastination!Your re... http://bit.ly/1bsIYiz     
    
    
    Puzzle makers tell all! RT @teamsnout: [podcast] SnoutCast #191: "Double Secret" Contributors Corby and Josh... http://bit.ly/19KhllC     
    
    
    Great advice: "know when to solo and when to follow" RT @zoecello: "Is Music the Key to Success?" http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/13/opinion/sunday/is-music-the-key-to-success.html?pagewanted=2&_r=1&pagewanted=all …    
    
    
    [blog] My 40th Birthday Survey Results: TL;DR: Despite an unfair advantage, my sister still wins.  :)Back in S... http://bit.ly/19S8Hl9     
    
    
    @homodachi It's actually very uplifting. John Cameron Mitchell's 2001 movie is great, but there's nothing like seeing Hedwig on stage.    
    
    
    Is there a show where someone says "'Mind briefing'? We just call that 'talking'"--or did I make that up in the dream I had last night?    
    
    
    I can't see the title CATCHING FIRE without thinking of https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Halt_and_Catch_Fire … .    
    
    
    Disney Princesses dress as pop culture characters for Halloween - Imgur http://ow.ly/pVGw9     
    
    
    @SunriseQueen Thanks! #dealwithit    
    
    
    "Fuck Off As A Service (FOAAS)" http://ow.ly/pVY4E     
    
    
    Last night's dream: Halloween night, a cappella singers in street give me shoes w/ plants for shoelaces. "Worst idea ever!" I shout... (1/2)    
    
    
    ...Earlier in dream, I rode a wheelchair through freeway traffic, passing Jonathan Frakes. He did not recognize me. (2/2)    
    
    
    Breakfast! (@ Beaterville Cafe - @elloportland) http://4sq.com/H8msBa     
    
    
    .@deeannsole 's weekend of games and pizza begins! (@ Lucky Labrador Beer Hall - @luckylabpdx w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/1cEcMKi     
    
    
    Now playing: Flapjacks & Sasquatches! pic.twitter.com/G6P7L2m81E    
    
    
    So this is happening now. Happy birthday weekend @DeeAnnSole :) pic.twitter.com/OL5sjwvvdP    
    
    
    .@deeannsole 's weekend of pizza & games continues--in the vault room! (@ Hopworks Urban Brewery - @hopworksbrewery) http://4sq.com/1bJ3vzp     
    
    
    Now playing: epic spell wars of the genderqueer wizards pic.twitter.com/Wbsx2UFJ8z    
    
    
    .@DeeAnnSole explains how to kill zombies pic.twitter.com/sbsp7bjR0d    
    
    
    OH: "I'm a helmet dude with no pants." #DungeonDefenders    
    
    
    Now: breakfast pizza. Later: MOAR GAMEZ @deeannsole :) (@ Lucca) http://4sq.com/17aavHW     
    
    
    Now playing: Last Night on Earth - escape in the truck pic.twitter.com/2tspwHrNI1    
    
    
    SPOILER ALERT: Amanda, the prom queen, did NOT escape in the truck. #LNOE @minitotoro @DeeAnnSole pic.twitter.com/ZQimPYrJrq    
    
    
    DO NOT EAT #RPGnight http://instagram.com/p/ftbfDSmptk/     
    
    
    And then @DeeAnnSole 's #DragonAge game turned into #Fiasco and we learned about a @ChuckNorris trucker movie. #RPGnight    
    
    
    I just brute-forced the solution to one-third of DEVICE 6, Chapter 4, and I feel pretty damn good about it. #puzzlehacker    
    
    
    A very happy birthday to @DeeAnnSole & many, many happy returns of the day. Thanks to everyone who helped us celebrate over the weekend!    
    
    
    #pathfinderACG #whatelseisnew @deeannsole http://instagram.com/p/fwfLRVmpqS/     
    
    
    Finished DEVICE 6 last night. Enjoyed everything except the WTF ending & F-U epilogue. Now I want to go watch The Prisoner again.    
    
    
    @angelamwebber You should assemble a team to "Escape from the Werewolf Village" :) http://realescapegame.com/regla01/     
    
    
    .@ericberlinct DEVICE 6 includes great puzzle interfaces, sound & imagery, but conclusion of narrative was not to my taste. #YMMV    
    
    
    Vancouver PD uniform just knocked on our door looking for the owner of a particular car (not ours), is now checking neighbors one by one.    
    
    
    [blog] My OryCon 35 Schedule: If you're anywhere near Portland, Oregon (the science fiction capital of America... http://bit.ly/1bWAlNl     
    
    
    It's official, I'll be presenting at @IgnitePortland 12 next month! Full line-up of thought-provoking speakers: http://ow.ly/q72gL     
    
    
    #oldiebutgoodie @DeeAnnSole 's @IgnitePortland 8 talk! "Travels with Our Cats" (2010) http://ow.ly/q6Yby     
    
    
    Took me ~7 hours yesterday to make slides for @IgnitePortland 12. Will take much longer to figure out what I'm actually going to say. #IP12    
    
    
    [blog] In Which I am a Professional Actor IN THE FUTURE: Shown above: the expurgated version of my paycheck fr... http://bit.ly/1c0OBVw     
    
    
    Hey Google Calendar, why isn't "respond to invitations forwarded from alternate email address" turned ON by default? http://ow.ly/q9bRM     
    
    
    @danielpeake @DavidJBodycombe We don't REQUIRE @PuzzledPint to be at different pubs; can discuss alternatives to location puzzle.    
    
    
    @civrot Did u mean "one of its draws?" If so, agreed, but we've repeated also. Localisation! :) @danielpeake @DavidJBodycombe @PuzzledPint    
    
    
    @civrot @danielpeake @DavidJBodycombe @PuzzledPint Let's move this to e-mail. Wait one.    
    
    
    Received our first box of snacks from @grazeusa . It's adorable! pic.twitter.com/BQJJXJ1nvv    
    
    
    Now playing: Fortune and Glory @ckwright @DeeAnnSole @jonathanhliu pic.twitter.com/Z5ljDXwge2    
    
    
    OH: "Snacks are irrelevant!" #trekmarathon #namethatepisode    
    
    
    What Star trek fans do with their free time. pic.twitter.com/3gqnYVRgpt    
    
    
    @ninjahq Yup!    
    
    
    Some cats like tortilla chips. It's a thing.    
    
    
    Cats are indifferent to Mirror Universe episodes. #trekmarathon http://instagram.com/p/f8W_yZmpkZ/     
    
    
    OH: "You don't usually give derogatory nicknames to things you like."    
    
    
    #trekmarathon now viewing TOS "Catspaw." Wow, it has been *years* since I've seen this show. #halloweenish    
    
    
    "Catspaw" was actually the second season premiere? Yikes. http://en.memory-alpha.org/wiki/Star_Trek:_The_Original_Series#Season_2 … http://en.memory-alpha.org/wiki/Star_Trek:_The_Original_Series#Season_2 …    
    
    
    "A cat is the most ruthless, most terrifying of animals." - Spock, who is apparently a dog person #trekmarathon    
    
    
    TNG "Genesis" is even more ridiculous than I remembered, and it's only act three. #trekmarathon    
    
    
    Kittens save the day! #trekmarathon    
    
    
    @snarke hey, check your email :)    
    
    
    In my mind I see the act-out sound effect from Don't Trust the Bitch in Apartment 23 as "shut the front door" #iamatwelveyearoldgirl    
    
    
    Our first 6-player game of #pathfinderACG ! @jonathanhliu @DeeAnnSole pic.twitter.com/qiIdzRq2DJ    
    
    
    Now what?    
    
    
    @JoshuaREnglish You'd think that, wouldn't you? Soon, my friend. SOON.    
    
    
    @ckwright @DeeAnnSole Nope, didn't make it out tonight, sorry. :)    
    
    
    So there was some kind of a sports thing tonight I guess?    
    
    
    Have submitted my @igniteportland slides for Nov.14th. Did 10+ hours of neuroscience research for one slide. Totally worth it, though.    
    
    
    Only in Portland can you go have a beer and talk earthquakes with DR. GOLDFINGER. No, really! http://ow.ly/qnGxv     
    
    
    Night driving through fog, listening to the PACIFIC RIM soundtrack. #MLIA    
    
    
    Aggressive panhandlers make me ANGRY    
    
    
    "The Tetanus Wall" #Portland pic.twitter.com/iogaLwdvfr    
    
    
    "Bros playing video games on a MAME console" would be a GREAT youtube series    
    
    
    "WASD is the devil!" - @DeeAnnSole "WASD is the best!" - @ghalidrim #nerddebates    
    
    
    King of the couch. pic.twitter.com/tmf0OGUn6T    
    
    
    @snarke Goodwill? I've seen electronics there, not sure if operational. Bring ipod to plug in and test? Maybe look for garage sales.    
    
    
    I just threw some money at @OKBJGM and you can too! http://igg.me/at/TheMiddlemanO2STK/x/1844977 …    
    
    
    http://wahealthplanfinder.org  is quite possibly the most confusing web site ever. But I'm now enrolled in Medicaid apparently? Thanks Obama! :)    
    
    
    2 Fast 2 Food: This Time It's Personal pic.twitter.com/OI5Ahb76eq    
    
    
    I'm surprised it took until season two for Don't Trust the Bitch in Apartment 23 to do a spit take. Or am I misremembering?    
    
    
    @3hubcaps Nope, sorry, we're at #OryCon all day. But you should totally do it! Tell Nancy and Liz I sent you. :)    
    
    
    Remind me to never ever rent a movie from iTunes ever again ever. Worst user experience of all time. Never again. In future, Amazon only.    
    
    
    @Nancy_Kelley Purchased rental on iTunes, wouldn't transfer to Apple TV; had to reset, switch to manual, and it's taking forever to sync...    
    
    
    @Nancy_Kelley ...when I did same w/ @AmazonVideo , purchase was reflected on all devices immediately, no hassle. iTunes loses a customer.    
    
    
    @Nancy_Kelley Fair enough. Diff'rent strokes for diff'rent folks. :)    
    
    
    For those just joining this complaint party: I give any new tech the benefit of a doubt until it annoys me too much. Then I salt the earth.    
    
    
    @wakjagner Yes, @AmazonVideo is great; has worked well on every device I've ever owned, IIRC. And if you're Prime, lots of good free TV.    
    
    
    Come to think of it, that's my policy with people too: benefit of a doubt until you get on my nerves, then YOU ARE DEAD TO ME. #hugs    
    
    
    Just call me "Daryl Zero."    
    
    
    Me: What's a synonym for "jerk?"
Internet: How about "schmuck?"
Me: PERFECT.    
    
    
    Super proud of my college friends (and future CTOs) @lessachu & http://fb.com/jeg  ! http://blog.hackbrightacademy.com/2013/11/women-watch-meet-20-technical-women-leaders-future-ctos/ … #runtheworld #gocardinal    
    
    
    "You proved...that you know where they live...but you didn't show up at their homes and schools and threaten them." http://ow.ly/qx1Wn     
    
    
    Just finished rehearsal for next Thursday's @igniteportland . Gonna be a great show, but get here EARLY! pic.twitter.com/o4kOuIDG9T    
    
    
    I just backed No Holds Barred Crosswords on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/13IwFgq     
    
    
    #nanowrimo write-in... with beer! (at @BurgervilleUsa) http://4sq.com/HAJqls     
    
    
    Shuttlepod One ready for deployment to @OryCon pic.twitter.com/SsoiDK31yV    
    
    
    Dear @dropbox , why does your iOS app suck so hard? I mean it. SO FREAKING HARD. Please to fix, yah? Love, me. #hateyou    
    
    
    Attention @orycon : Open Read & Crit signup sheets will be outside Madison Room in EMC by ~11am today. Thanks for your patience!    
    
    
    Ok that was a lot of tabasco #breakfast    
    
    
    The Internet is telling me I need to check out Bitstrips. How long can I resist?    
    
    
    @snarke Apparently you can talk to @kimvlcek if you want to know more :)    
    
    
    Fans have opinions pic.twitter.com/khLE1iEQBL    
    
    
    For reasons unknown I have the AIR FORCE ONE soundtrack stuck in my head    
    
    
    On the plane, waiting to take off. See you all in a couple of hours!    
    
    
    Great memories relived during our drive through Napa tonight. Gotta stop at some wineries before we fly out Monday.    
    
    
    I probably shouldn't sing my parody lyrics "It's a nice day for a Gay Wedding" out loud at any point today.

I'll just hum it to myself.    
    
    
    Haven't cried this much at a wedding in some time. Congrats to new husbands Chris & Doug (a.k.a. Chloe's dads)! pic.twitter.com/YPkgT91fgU    
    
    
    HAPPY BIRTHDAY @lessachu and many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    I'm at V. Sattui Winery (Saint Helena, CA) http://4sq.com/1dieKjf     
    
    
    "like a bad girl with a good tattoo" @vsattui1885 pic.twitter.com/dqZg8lmayI    
    
    
    Good news, everyone! The wine survived the flight!    
    
    
    @vsattui1885 We left with Gamay Rouge (of course), Angelica, and the "babymaker" Moscato Frizzante. :) Thanks to Kerry for a fun tasting!    
    
    
    @mariafi @snarke @3hubcaps What?!? FRIENDSHIP OVER. (Not really.)    
    
    
    FOOD TRICORDER! http://ow.ly/qKE5n  #omgwtfbbq    
    
    
    @civrot The theory (Raman spectroscopy) is good, but I remain dubious of actual day-to-day functioning. Also can only do surface scans.    
    
    
    @civrot Fair enough. I didn't watch the video. (I rarely watch crowdfunding "ask" videos--they're mostly pretty terrible.)    
    
    
    From @reddit /atheism: "I work in a restaurant [&] old couple from bible belt...left me this in place of tip..." http://ow.ly/qLBEX     
    
    
    "10 Things You Need to Know About @IgnitePortland 12" and #11: I'm speaking! :) http://ow.ly/qNvbR     
    
    
    Thanksalot for making me the closer, @IgnitePortland . I'll do my best to finish big. Some tough acts to follow: http://ow.ly/qNvgU     
    
    
    Just a few photos from the beautiful, beautiful wedding @DeeAnnSole and I attended on Sunday: http://adelineandgraceblog.com/2013/11/12/calistoga-ranch-wedding-photos-3/ …    
    
    
    Save the date, clever girl: http://themetapicture.com/when-the-husband-is-in-charge-of-the-wedding-invitation/ …    
    
    
    TONIGHT! 7:30pm (but arrive EARLY)! Watch @IgnitePortland 12 in-person at @HollywoodTheatr , or online at http://igniteportland.org  !    
    
    
    Sad to hear @cath_stevens won't be at @IgnitePortland tonight. Hope she shares her slides online later (hint, hint). Get well soon!    
    
    
    CORRECTION: @IgnitePortland #ip12 starts tonight at *7:00PM*. Early admission at 5pm w/ food donation! http://ow.ly/qPSm6     
    
    
    I'm going crazy. Just a little. It's okay. #ip12 #howdoyougettocarnegiehall    
    
    
    [blog] TONIGHT: I Sing the Ignite Portland Electric: Portland!  7:00PM!  Hollywood Theatre!I'm one of the spea... http://bit.ly/1ctFPPt     
    
    
    .@ninjahq Thanks! You can always watch online at http://igniteportland.org  :) @snarke @3hubcaps @rmalena #ip12    
    
    
    @snarke You rock. :) @DeeAnnSole & I will be there soon! We can play games while waiting! #ip12    
    
    
    @sandrawickham http://montypython.joolsc.net/downloads/sounds/NAUGHTY.WAV … ;)    
    
    
    @brittamarie Thanks! Glad you enjoyed it. :)    
    
    
    @AWeekOrAWeekend Thank you!    
    
    
    @snarke Thanks lady :)    
    
    
    @feedle Thank you!    
    
    
    .@rlhughesPNW The FIFTH verse rocks. The sixth verse, the original last verse--don't ever sing that. It's terrible. :) #QED #ip12    
    
    
    @tekniklr You are my people :)    
    
    
    @mattcleinman Geez. I thought we were friends man, now you can't even spell my Twitter name right. ;)    
    
    
    .@rmalena I stole all the best parts of that talk from other people. Like these guys: http://www.penny-arcade.com/comic/2004/08/04 … :) #ip12    
    
    
    @TheDoubleclicks @tekniklr That's me, the predictable superfan (which is also the name of my One Direction cover band). :) #rimshot    
    
    
    @mattcleinman thanks :)    
    
    
    .@cath_stevens @IgnitePortland Awesome, thanks! And re: slide 19, you can do that every month at @PuzzledPint :) http://image.slidesharecdn.com/igniteportlandtalk-catherinestevens4-131115004828-phpapp02/95/slide-19-638.jpg?1384498240 …    
    
    
    @cath_stevens Right, I forgot, you're a baby. ;) @PuzzledPint does hit some family-friendly places. Hope we're still around in 2015!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @doubleZY Thank you! Great to see you in person!    
    
    
    @mollyejohnson Be kind to your web-footed friends, for a duck may be somebody's mother. :)    
    
    
    .@mollyejohnson Anyway, I have a whole different set of feels re: Sousa b/c of Monty Python & high school marching band. :) Thanks again!    
    
    
    Um, did you really actually name your sunglasses company "CRAP Eyewear?" What?    
    
    
    I just backed Big Launch for Paul and Storm's New Album, BALL PIT on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/1bALB3k     
    
    
    #FF #IP12 Just a few of last night's awesome @IgnitePortland speakers: @johnnyfunk @lyzidiamond @kronda @gizm0_0 @E_Briannica @mysteryboxpdx    
    
    
    ICYMI here's the live recording of my @IgnitePortland #IP12 talk from last night: http://www.ustream.tv/recorded/40782603/highlight/435541 …    
    
    
    @kronda Thanks! As a former webmaster, I really enjoyed your talk. :)    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Well, some people actually *like* wang. #heyo    
    
    
    @lahosken @IgnitePortland No. :) Next question?    
    
    
    We're here and we love you @Molly23 ! :) #desertbus    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @angelamwebber and many happy return2 of the 6ay!    
    
    
    Some weeks I don't back any Kickstarters, and some weeks are above average. This week was an outlier.    
    
    
    @thefoodgeek but still not as many as @ghalidrim HE CRAZY :)    
    
    
    @tereshkova2001 @AgentsofSHIELD http://youtu.be/xCwLirQS2-o     
    
    
    I'm at Cinetopia for Thor: The Dark World (Vancouver, WA) http://4sq.com/17br7fU     
    
    
    Dear Internet, why are we not all watching Teen Beach Movie RIGHT NOW http://ow.ly/qTvl3  #removeonelettermakegreatestpunofalltime    
    
    
    Now playing: this fucking shit again. @CAH pic.twitter.com/I4zdF4fjg3    
    
    
    @caryy So would you say they're... GAME CHANGERS? Also, not yet. :)    
    
    
    OH: "It's not everyone who can thank their wife for suggesting bestiality." @CAH    
    
    
    Now playing: "Learn to Survive" scenario #LNOE #TimberPeak pic.twitter.com/5V2xSKySxN    
    
    
    R.I.P. Sheriff Anderson #LNOE #ZombieHero http://instagram.com/p/gza_dhmptp/     
    
    
    It's getting hot in heerrrre #LNOE pic.twitter.com/vxoHB0g069    
    
    
    Final result: so-called "heroes" won w/ 3 turns, 6 cards remaining. #LNOE #ZombiesWillReturn    
    
    
    @wakjagner Timber Peak (Flying Frog introduced the mechanic in Invasion From Outer Space)    
    
    
    Now playing: SKYLINE. Taking too many risks. Prolly gonna lose. I blame the wine. pic.twitter.com/T6JmWSwrPl    
    
    
    Hooray for @PuzzledPint ! RT @ghalidrim: @sparCKL @DeeAnnSole thanks for the puzzle kit,1 hour last night during dinner :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @angelamwebber We just started a new game of Red Dead Redemption. It is surprisingly difficult trying to NOT kill dudes all the time.    
    
    
    Pre-Thanksgiving feast by @deeannsole ! pic.twitter.com/QU9j085Ipf    
    
    
    @angelamwebber he's just thinking "wow that girl looks a lot like that Audrey chick from that band The Double Geek Girls on youtube" #duck    
    
    
    I have never worked so hard for one freaking star in my entire life. #PvZ2 pic.twitter.com/kR2EKBXg5F    
    
    
    @ClavisCryptica You might be able to talk @DeeAnnSole & me into it. :) What day? And where will we find 8 other team players?    
    
    
    Dear Twitter tech support: should I return this monitor for replacement? I've tried 2 different DVI cables already. http://ow.ly/i/3M61Q     
    
    
    @ClavisCryptica We can do Dec.6th, 7th, or 8th. Does one of those dates work for you? If so, time preference? cc: @DeeAnnSole    
    
    
    @ClavisCryptica @DeeAnnSole CORRECTION: *not* Dec.8th. Sorry for the narrow window! :P Would love to play with you guys if possible.    
    
    
    Perhaps you mean... a full BATTERY of cold remedies? pic.twitter.com/xo6nEo2q4t    
    
    
    Yeah, so I just wasted 23 minutes of my life on this: #DrWhoDoodle #notproud https://g.co/doodle/5cgy5t     
    
    
    @TheDoubleclicks @DeeAnnSole is way ahead of you :)    
    
    
    ICYMI here are videos of last week's awesome @IgnitePortland #IP12 talks: https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLfwE4lxvXUNkXj8Wy8N8vaAU_ivItsSeu … (I'm #16)    
    
    
    Yo dawg? RT @TheDoubleclicks: I heard you guys like tote bags. http://thedoubleclicks.bandcamp.com/merch  pic.twitter.com/S4S7I9KcmT    
    
    
    @littlelull @mariafi To be fair, *Facebook* is terrible at Facebook also. (I just cross-post everything from Twitter, because I'm lazy.)    
    
    
    @MaryRobinette I do not think that word means what you think it means?    
    
    
    @MaryRobinette IF YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN. #thatswhatshesaid #etc    
    
    
    NOW I HAVE A PINTEREST ACCOUNT HO HO HO    
    
    
    I mean srsly wtf is all this i dont even #pinterest pic.twitter.com/ncTXRRT0kn    
    
    
    @ClavisCryptica @DeeAnnSole Oh well. Have fun! We'll look forward to reading all about it on your blog. :)    
    
    
    So I guess some new medical TV show aired today? With an ensemble cast of old white dudes? Sounds kinda boring if you ask me. #troll    
    
    
    My first win in the #lordsofwaterdeep app. Take that, Easy AI! http://instagram.com/p/hE9Rbxmpk7/     
    
    
    Defending steamy dungeons. #saturdaynightsallrightforfighting pic.twitter.com/OJihPvtiGr    
    
    
    helpful cat likes to play video games pic.twitter.com/VSOxY7bnOg    
    
    
    More beer!    
    
    
    Let's go to the mall...today! pic.twitter.com/Gbx42jMdxO    
    
    
    Every time I hear the ARROW voiceover, I wish for a show where Dig tells Ollie, "Yeah, you 'somethin' else' all right, white boy." #fanfic    
    
    
    Tough to be a minority in a minority. I'm not into Doctor Who, I don't dig Night Vale. No, I don't need convincing. I'm just different, OK?    
    
    
    @snarke Say it loud! Say it proud! I DON'T CARE ABOUT NIGHT VALE! :) #DesertBluffs4Lyfe #troll    
    
    
    @TheDoubleclicks You are wise beyond your years. But we knew that.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @lessachu And that's okay! We don't all have to like the same things. BTW, YOU ARE NOW DEAD TO ME. ;)    
    
    
    Marvel may rule the multiplex, but DC owns the airwaves. 74% through ARROW season 1 on Netflix and still Diggin' it so far. PUN INTENDED.    
    
    
    And look... I want to like #AgentsofSHIELD as much as the rest of y'all, but they gotta meet us halfway on this. I'm just not feelin' it.    
    
    
    Regardless, @clarkgregg is still my homeboy. I've been #TeamCoulson ever since he fronted QUO VADIMUS on Sports Night.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @tereshkova2001 and many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    Despite plot holes, I will always have a soft spot for STARGATE CONTINUUM b/c they shot on location in Arctic Circle & aboard nuclear sub.    
    
    
    @ghalidrim You chose...poorly.    
    
    
    This week, I have 3 writing projects and 3 upcoming puzzle events demanding my attention. When did I ever find the time for a day job?    
    
    
    @snarke @ninjahq @rmalena @clarkgregg @ftcup (in Slavic accent) I have DVDs. You want DVDs? We talk. Make good deal. No vigorish.    
    
    
    Honestly, I just love finding any excuse to say the word "vigorish."    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma ARROW got much more interesting after Ollie accumulated a Scooby gang. Especially Felicity Smoak. Smart chicks are hot.    
    
    
    If you're curious about the fMRI in my #IP12 talk: RT @teamsnout: [podcast] SnoutCast #197: Think, Think, Think ... http://bit.ly/1aQ3X0j     
    
    
        
    
    
    @lostluck personally I prefer thankmaryann #heyo    
    
    
    I love that I can search for "andromeda" in my e-mail inbox and get results from three or four different conversations. #spaaace    
    
    
    [blog] Yet Another Honorable Mention: It's my second from Writers of the Future, but who's counting?"Bounty Ca... http://bit.ly/1bpBU9N     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving, humans! #notreally http://instagram.com/p/hRbXkUmppZ/     
    
    
    @danielpeake Sorry to hear that. Hope your next gig arrives quickly and is even more awesome!    
    
    
    Arf! http://ow.ly/i/3RVNf     
    
    
    Now playing: Dread Curse #Friendsgiving pic.twitter.com/exgaCL8WZB    
    
    
    The turkey is on the table. THE TURKEY IS ON THE TABLE. #Friendsgiving pic.twitter.com/NKrYMpR9l0    
    
    
    I think we might have enough food at this point. #friendsgiving pic.twitter.com/IVuWdmbDQ7    
    
    
    Apparently this is called "Watergate Salad." #friendsgiving pic.twitter.com/qYdQuqt14h    
    
    
    @Galumbits We refilled the wine bottle with water after we emptied it :)    
    
    
    No, the lyrics to Safety Dance are NOT "everybody take off your pants" #Friendsgiving #mondegreen    
    
    
    Photo: ruckawriter: spaceexp: Robert Curbeam on EVA outside the ISS Just… damn. The high frontier http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIs-lN69p     
    
    
    Reaching for the salt cellar pic.twitter.com/EB2rWkNaWH    
    
    
    OH: "There was too much Seaman in your ear."    
    
    
    I just backed JoCo Cruise Crazy 4 Animated Video on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/1h4GjlJ     
    
    
    Now playing: Tsuro pic.twitter.com/DimeXEarfL    
    
    
    Now playing: Last Night on Earth. Rachelle and Becky meet someone in the bank! http://instagram.com/p/hUxaLmGphh/     
    
    
    It's been a long day of begging for leftovers and licking feet. #corgi pic.twitter.com/UDDKZvXyxj    
    
    
    I APOLOGIZE FOR NOTHING pic.twitter.com/PLyu4PDjvC    
    
    
    Now playing: Epic Spell Wars of the Battle Wizards: Duel at Mt. Skullzfyre! http://instagram.com/p/hU_5liGpjY/     
    
    
    @littlelull @bm0nies See also: http://www.ebaumsworld.com/video/watch/280889/ …    
    
    
    @littlelull @bm0nies It's just an old SNL bit. Only mildly NSFW. :)    
    
    
    FREE TO GOOD PERSON: 1 extra ticket to #nerdnightout w/@TheDoubleclicks @JosephScrimshaw @superguitarbros 9pm tonight. Who wants it?    
    
    
    @mariafi @3hubcaps @minitotoro @ckwright I'm leaving now with a +1 (no @deeannsole #sadface), I say we just show up & decide on the spot    
    
    
    waiting (@ Russell Street Bar-B-Que) http://4sq.com/1fUy5Lz     
    
    
    @Alphastream It's yours!  I'll look for you at the door.    
    
    
    @ckwright @minitotoro @3hubcaps @mariafi @DeeAnnSole @ghalidrim @snarke 5 on our way now!    
    
    
    I'm at Secret Society - @thesecrtsociety for Super Guitar Bros and The Doubleclicks (Portland, OR) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/1c4jBly     
    
    
    Heard news of @RealPaulWalker 's passing during dinner tonight. He was 19 days older than I am. My heart goes out to his family & friends.    
    
    
    Trapped in bed, can't get up #lazysunday pic.twitter.com/5KY27yb0Xg    
    
    
    I'm just saying, Jennifer Lawrence and Emily Blunt have a head start on Vulcan eyebrows for the next Trek movie. JUST SAYING.    
    
    
    Now playing: The Perfect Heist pic.twitter.com/5dYxYalSLd    
    
    
    Now playing: La Boca pic.twitter.com/p79i41l4gc    
    
    
    @ghalidrim @zulahni DO TELL.    
    
    
    @zulahni Wait, what language are you coding in right now? (For calibration purposes.)    
    
    
    @zulahni If you pick Python, http://www.pythonchallenge.com/  is a fun intro. Drupal==evil PHP, Rails==hip Ruby, Perl==old bearded fat guy.    
    
    
    .@brittamarie Beefcake. BEEFCAKE! #beefcake :)    
    
    
    Agonizing over re-writing various e-mails to people. It's what I do.    
    
    
    If I got paid for doing @PuzzledPint , well, I wouldn't have to work for you, Deke.    
    
    
    Presented without comment. #diylolcat pic.twitter.com/ZAKkAepgkj    
    
    
    MT @PuzzledPint: [PDX] Find us TONIGHT at @OMSI After Dark! We'll be in the Theory Cafe after 5pm, with puzzles: https://www.omsi.edu/afterdark     
    
    
    C'mon guys they're not THAT bitter pic.twitter.com/Fm7mWcf6hb    
    
    
    OH: "...hipster office supplies..." #pdx    
    
    
    @musicvstheater KIDS THESE DAYS    
    
    
    This is the saddest thing and it happened in my city today :( http://www.katu.com/news/local/Vancouver-woman-unknowingly-live-tweets-husbands-fatal-crash-234520581.html …    
    
    
    No thank you, boxer briefs. Thanks, but no thanks. pic.twitter.com/gv3Yhjp5nt    
    
    
    YOU PLAY OR YOU GO AWAY (see also, sequel: CATCHING IRE) #igotamillionofem http://instagram.com/p/hjv5IWmplx/     
    
    
    @thefoodgeek Yo. What up? :)    
    
    
    [blog] Important Data Visualization of the Day: Because I know you've been wondering:That is all. http://bit.ly/1d37Mht     
    
    
    @thefoodgeek "Maker? I didn't even KNOW 'er!" #rimshot #crickets #iapologizefornothing    
    
    
    Tonight's double feature: OLYMPUS HAS FALLEN and WHITE HOUSE DOWN. Which one gets your vote?    
    
    
    Ashley Judd as First Lady? Yes, please. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    I wonder how many "package" jokes actual Secret Service agents make when no one's listening in on comms. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Yes. OF COURSE Gerard Butler is shirtless in this movie. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    You're here too, Angela Bassett? Cool. Hope you get to kick some ass later. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Also, WHY did they not just make a whole movie about Melissa Leo's SECDEF character. Give me crazy backstory! #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Y'know, in real life I'm sure a cruise missile would have taken care of this problem long before it reached DC. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    No, Mr. President, "find your son" is not really one of the Secretary of Defense's actual job functions. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Curse your sudden but inevitable betrayal! #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Seriously? Worst. President. Ever. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    And also, you never thought to build a backdoor kill code into your super-secret nuclear failsafe system? Weaksauce. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Dylan McDermott==Bill. Bill Clay. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Helicopters now. Did they lift EVERY action beat in this movie from Die Hard? #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    "Well, we're going to need some more FBI guys, I guess." #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    The Judean People's Front? The People's Front of Judea? #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    I apologize for my earlier tweet. Only MOST of this movie was lifted from Die Hard. The rest came from Terminator 2. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    And now the climactic "follow tech support instructions by phone" scene! #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Although, to be fair, props for using an actual, fairly secure password there. #olympushasfallen    
    
    
    Next up: #whitehousedown . PG-13, but includes "a brief sexual image?" Oh, behave.    
    
    
    Guys, I will be VERY disappointed if THAT was the "brief sexual image." Thermal imaging? And missionary position? Come on. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    James Woods with a gun? Never a good idea. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    @splunge2000 HEYOOO    
    
    
    If your point man can't remember a locker combination w/o writing it on his arm, your infiltration plan may need work. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Okay, so apparently this one is the young, hip, funny "Die Hard in a White House" movie. Or trying to be. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    I really just want Jake Weber to get exasperated and say "Allison!" to someone. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    So... Would that be a "hard Castle," then? #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Oh yeah, Channing Tatum, you work those laugh lines, baby. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    "Yes, we do need to get out of this elevator. And don't call me Shaft." #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Why do German action movie directors care so much about the 25th Amendment? Discuss. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Not without my daughter!!! #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Ah, yes, the old share-your-feelings-while-bandaging-a-broken-glass-wound scene. So cliche. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    OK, that traffic camera bit was pretty good. #whitehousedown    
    
    
    Jesus, how many presidents are you people going to swear in today? #whitehousedown    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hashtag literal ticking clock  #whitehousedown    
    
    
    "Tour's over." AWESOMESAUCE  #whitehousedown    
    
    
    For the record, #olympushasfallen : when an 11-year-old girl is smarter & braver than POTUS in your movie, #whitehousedown wins.    
    
    
    Who's been walking in our snow? http://instagram.com/p/hmPW0NmpnC/     
    
    
    Breakfast! (@ Podnah's Pit BBQ - @podnahsbbq w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/1eXVpVp     
    
    
    Heading up to Seattle for @PuzzleBreak tonight--our first official "room escape game." Wish us luck!    
    
    
    So this also happened tonight. (Not the "grand champion" part.) #pinball pic.twitter.com/Vn7XZ5t17a    
    
    
    @dmmiller We had a great time. LMK if you guys beat our 40-minute escape record! :)    
    
    
    @dmmiller I'm not surprised at all. ;) Who was on your team?    
    
    
        
    
    
    How did you ever survive holiday shopping before the Internet? Discuss.    
    
    
    Just spent the last of my birthday iTunes gift balance on ARROW season 2. Because ARROW.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @jmacfee and many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    You will probably *not* see me running through downtown tonight shouting "MERRY CHRISTMAS @WIEDENKENNEDY !!!" *Probably* not. #nopromises    
    
    
    @littlelull May the odds be ever in your favor! Wait, what kind of job is this?    
    
    
    This Commercial Totally Nails the Double Standard for Men and Women http://ow.ly/28I5ra     
    
    
    @BrianEnigma @lauraehall YEARS OF PSYCHOTHERAPY WILL BE REQUIRED TO EXPUNGE THAT IMAGE    
    
    
    Really, Stanford Engineering? You didn't get the GLEE joke? #nudeerections http://frametastic.com  pic.twitter.com/gO4ejFxM8p    
    
    
    Coffee in progress. http://instagram.com/p/ht6MQDGphV/     
    
    
    @geekamama OH, BEHAVE.    
    
    
    @lauraehall @BrianEnigma ...since when?    
    
    
    Big fire, little fire https://vine.co/v/hQDg7wJEqpW     
    
    
    I wish my high school classmate Terri Chung had been talking to Anderson Cooper about something happier: http://ow.ly/rCfku     
    
    
    I'm sorry, Etsy, I really can't justify spending $3 on one goddamn pencil.    
    
    
    Seattle gamers: indie movie needs extras for crowd scenes next week (Tue-Sat)! Details at http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/jrralls/rpgs-are-evil-dark-dungeons-the-movie/posts/689878 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    12 Days of Holiday Bullshit FAQ - cah: What is this bullshit? Last month, in a desperate bid for money and... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIs10xAsRf     
    
    
    @aliceandstuff man it's so loud in here    
    
    
    WELL I GUESS I'M NOT GOING TO SLEEP ANYTIME SOON http://ow.ly/rGZk7     
    
    
    I emerged safely from The Crypt, though I fear this is only the beginning of my trials. #TheRoomTwo https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/the-room-two/id667362389?ls=1&mt=8 …    
    
    
    #ICYMI RT @curtiscchen: Sold! My #jakeandandy novelette "Somebody's Daughter" will be published by http://leadingedgemagazine.com  in early 2014.    
    
    
    Come on, @AgentsofSHIELD , where's your "Out of Gas?" Or even your "Man on the Street?" Show me the money!    
    
    
    @ghalidrim @mcabain not like you had any ACTUAL work you needed to do today right :)    
    
    
    So revision 6 of the Sole-Chen holiday newsletter was the final. (Yes, we edit alot.) Printing now, mailing out with cards #SOON    
    
    
    When it comes to writing holiday greeting cards, @DeeAnnSole and I are an unstoppable whirlwind of comedy. Comedy, I tells ya!    
    
    
    .@Coffee_Villa @DeeAnnSole There was dueling strikethrough humor. Also "suburban excitement." And I may have drawn a grumpycat cartoon.    
    
    
    If you must watch A GOOD DAY TO DIE HARD, I highly recommend selecting the "descriptive audio" soundtrack on the DVD.    
    
    
    Yeah, no, "Google Drive" is still the worst product name ever. #genericbrandinternet    
    
    
    .@lahosken WELL THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE USED IT FOR DOCS THEN. You know what? I'm just going back to calling it "Writely." #grumpycat    
    
    
    @jmacfee Pretty sneaky, sis.    
    
    
    Three hours? But I thought hobbits were (wait for it...) _short_! AHAHAHAHAHA #unfollow    
    
    
    It's not a real party until the fire alarm goes off.    
    
    
    @brittamarie Was I carrying a cardboard box? :)    
    
    
    .@brittamarie (You might also see me on #Grimm tonight. But probably not.)    
    
    
    Tonight's holiday movie night double feature was Muppet Xmas Carol and Scrooged. With pizza, beer, and a dog wearing a scarf. Portland!    
    
    
    @mariafi Or you could listen to a recording of Patrick Stewart's one-man-show performance. If you think you can handle that much awesome.    
    
    
    Not to spoil #TheRoomTwo for anybody, but it is quite clearly the wrath of... someone. http://instagram.com/p/h5QECtmpp9/     
    
    
    @mariafi I see what you did there.    
    
    
    @rmalena Is the answer http://goo.gl/pt099X  ? I'm guessing based on clues 1, 2, 4, and 6. And knowing you, obvs. :) #lazy #backsolving    
    
    
    @rmalena better hope they're not on twitter ;)    
    
    
    Y'all will be happy to know that this year's Sole-Chen holiday newsletter does not mention poop at all. We do talk about biting, though.    
    
    
    @rmalena kids these days    
    
    
    ThinkGeek Fucks Up Big Time - elfstaranymore: I was really, really excited when I saw the announcement that... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIs11EepyJ     
    
    
    @Galumbits Oh no. What happened?    
    
    
    @Galumbits so sorry to hear this :(    
    
    
    [blog] Ten Books That Have Touched Me: In no particular order.  Also note that this is not an exhaustive list;... http://bit.ly/1kLx7PH     
    
    
    Apparently some cats like pizza crust. https://vine.co/v/h2VTgne2eaq     
    
    
    And now, revisiting a heartwarming holiday classic. #chefsdothat pic.twitter.com/Voil8iHATl    
    
    
    Archived screen: http://ow.ly/i/42duv  MT @J_Bloodworth: pub just fired head chef but forgot he runs their twitter: http://twitter.com/ploughpub     
    
    
    ISOLINEAR POST-ITS. ARE YOU FREAKING KIDDING ME. MAKE THIS HAPPEN NOW PLZ KTHXBAI http://datastickies.com/  #trekgasm    
    
    
        
    
    
    Watching LOVE ACTUALLY for the first time in years, and holy shit that IS Andrew "Walking Dead" Lincoln! #everyonessoyoung    
    
    
    I just backed Periscope Studio: Maiden Voyage on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/HXC8bq     
    
    
    WHAT. WHAT. WHAT. RT @tordotcom: WOAH. Joseph Gordon-Levitt confirms he will direct and star in #Sandman movie. http://www.tor.com/blogs/2013/12/joseph-gordon-levitt-sandman-movie …    
    
    
    .@geekamama @irwando Especially since there's no reason you can't drink and solve AT THE SAME TIME. ;) @PuzzledPint    
    
    
    @JosephScrimshaw @angelamwebber NEAR? FAR? WHEREVER YOU ARE! YOU'LL NEVER ESCAPE THIS DAMNED SONG. #reallynotok    
    
    
    .@bigbadchang Happy Birthday Roomie and many happy returns of the day! #vpxii    
    
    
    never underestimate the power of rhythm guitar    
    
    
    @snarke me, listening to the JOSIE AND THE PUSSYCATS soundtrack (yes that one SHUT UP OKAY) #iama12yearoldgirl    
    
    
        
    
    
    Okay, Internet: best 27" IPS LED monitor on sale for <$600? GO.    
    
    
    @DeeAnnSole @ghalidrim @mariafi I heard a rumor that *somebody* is organizing a #LNOE play date for this Saturday :)    
    
    
    Now on @slideshare, my @IgnitePortland 12 talk: "The Battle Hymn of the Republic" #ip12 http://www.slideshare.net/sparCKL/the-battle-hymn-of-the-republic …    
    
    
    Every time I listen to the LOVE ACTUALLY soundtrack I think Otis Redding is singing "Mayonnaise" instead of "May your days..." #mondegreen    
    
    
    I'm at @KigginsTheatre for Christmas Carol Radio Show (Vancouver, WA) http://4sq.com/J94uzy     
    
    
    Xmas decor in progress pic.twitter.com/K7bfwtEbC5    
    
    
    THIS IS HAPPENING NOW & YES THAT IS @clarkgregg . THAT IS ALL. #xmas pic.twitter.com/5Y1n1vHh50    
    
    
    Trapped under animal. Send help. pic.twitter.com/7E3lt5fWg4    
    
    
    “When “Life Hacking” Is Really White Privilege” by @jendziura https://medium.com/get-bullish/a5e5f4e9132f …    
    
    
    #GoogleCrossword solved in 0:14:50
https://g.co/doodle/2m9q44     
    
    
    @ninjahq OBVS :)    
    
    
    @ninjahq I'm still upset about "KTS" >:(    
    
    
    @ninjahq I'm guessing DDE==Dwight D. Eisenhower? #crosswordsmadebyoldwhitedudes    
    
    
    @dmmiller OH YOU FANCY HUH ;)    
    
    
    @aliceandstuff Have you seen @OrphanBlack ? It's pretty awesome.    
    
    
    #thebook #soon RT @curtiscchen: [512words] I don't think I ever made a formal announcement about this... http://bit.ly/1c70MSv     
    
    
    @mariafi @ghalidrim We're late! But we'll be there soon.    
    
    
    Round 5: Heroes doing well despite Lights Out in the Manor House. #nowplaying #LNOE pic.twitter.com/MPLkYk7ocy    
    
    
    Hellooooo zombies! pic.twitter.com/EGKJyoJxEg    
    
    
    Happy holidays, humans! pic.twitter.com/pGpRTxrbVa    
    
    
    Hey, do you smell something... burning? #LNOE http://instagram.com/p/iNSMkampkt/     
    
    
    @ninjahq 2 different games :)    
    
    
    @ninjahq Hi. Have you met @DeeAnnSole ? ;)    
    
    
    Well, ARROW did a pretty good job of setting up their second season arc. Hope they can deliver. Also, how cute is Kid Flash?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ghalidrim and many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    Weird dreams last night, incl. me saying "I believe a strict constructionist interpretation will support this legal argument"...(1/2)    
    
    
    ...into some device at a theme park hotel. Also morphing elevators and pantsless high schol reunions. My brain dreams weird things. (2/2)    
    
    
    Now playing: Flash Point - Dangerous Waters! pic.twitter.com/kHULsFDqtz    
    
    
    For various reasons, I find it hilarious that I'm getting spam from JDate.    
    
    
    Long story. Tell you later. #trekmas pic.twitter.com/EmSYJ4vQ6H    
    
    
    SantaWatch 2013 gift exchange: Wound up with genuine Mississippi puzzle & 2 tiny Cylons. @DeeAnnSole got Rail Baron game & political comics!    
    
    
    Also, it's true, @AubreyCello makes a killer mac and cheese. And @DeeAnnSole has created several deadly varieties of fudge & pralines.    
    
    
    Now playing: Tokaido pic.twitter.com/R1C8INAdz1    
    
    
    Action shot of the boys from earlier tonight. #foodrobot pic.twitter.com/xoYbLuofwU    
    
    
    Tiny Cylons will solve this puzzle without your help, human. Thanks to @hellcowKeith & @jennschiffer… http://instagram.com/p/iVpxTvmpis/     
    
    
    Sorry, that should have been @jennnbaker in previous tweet! Damn you soft keyboard lacking tactile feedback. #needhaptics    
    
    
    [blog] I'm Made Out of Meat: That title is, of course, an homage to Terry Bisson's classic short story "They'r... http://bit.ly/19hgJ7s     
    
    
    #XmasMovieThon begins! (@ Cinetopia for Frozen (2013)) http://4sq.com/JrkbCl     
    
    
    @jonathanhliu I was just about to say "pics or it didn't happen" but now I'm all like "CAN'T UNSEE"    
    
    
    #XmasMovieThon continues. BTW, FROZEN was great! #iama12yearoldgirl (@ Cinetopia for American Hustle w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/1bqycam     
    
    
    #XmasMovieThon #forreal (@ Regal Vancouver Plaza 10 - @regalmovies for Ender's Game) http://4sq.com/1czrBAD     
    
    
    #XmasMovieThon IV: this time it's Ben Stiller (@ Cinetopia) http://4sq.com/JsjLM4     
    
    
    #XmasMovieThon concludes with dungeons and/or dragon(s)! (@ Cinetopia for The Hobbit: The Desolation of Smaug) http://4sq.com/1brexaf     
    
    
    You guys, @lynnemthomas is live-tweeting Star Trek: The Motion Picture and it is totally awesome. #FYI #trekmas    
    
    
    Just watched Fast Times at Ridgemont High for the first time ever. So that happened.    
    
    
    @srj68 It was totally '80s! And now I guess I know what people are talking about w/r/t Phoebe Cates in a red bikini.    
    
    
    Listening to Frozen soundtrack outtakes. Enjoying the Lopezes' commentary & SO GLAD that prophecy crap did not end up in the final film.    
    
    
    @homodachi The song was adorable, but I hate storylines that hinge on arbitrary prophecies. Always better to write to character.    
    
    
    @kronda Don't forget Bradley Cooper played #Face in the ill-fated 2010 A-Team remake. Not exactly a superhero, but y'know. ;)    
    
    
    May 16th is my favorite. RT @scottjames: New York Times: 2013, the year in pictures. Worth your time. http://www.nytimes.com/projects/2013/year-in-pictures/?hp …    
    
    
    http://steamcommunity.com/groups/sea_monkeys … RT @zulahni: Hey, Seamonkeys! We have a steam group. Did you know? (I did, but it seems a lot of you aren’t there)    
    
    
    Now playing: Relic Expedition http://instagram.com/p/ic1cJNmpr0/     
    
    
    Hey America, have you hacked your science oven lately? http://madebynathan.com/2013/07/10/raspberry-pi-powered-microwave/ …    
    
    
    Now playing: Flash Point - Dangerous Waters (submarine map) pic.twitter.com/VJhXj5uMqi    
    
    
    BUT WHAT WAS IN THE SANDWICH? “@PortlandPolice: Central officers use a sandwich to peacefully resolve standoff... http://bit.ly/19spCYT  ”    
    
    
    Playing pro keys on rock band 3 is like learning to sight read all over again    
    
    
    21st century yule log https://vine.co/v/h92qT5vFHai     
    
    
    Now playing: #ForbiddenDesert pic.twitter.com/ibfwGpdX9z    
    
    
        
    
    
    @snoogans yup, made by the same folks, with some interesting new mechanics    
    
    
    @ellenjuhlin hmm, I've never played Amazing Labyrinth. Do you know if the iOS app version is any good?    
    
    
    @DeeAnnSole @mariafi For the record, I'm 2/3 through BROKEN KINGDOMS, and KINGDOM OF GODS is on my TBR shelf. :) #slowreader    
    
    
    If you like wine or just want to see how to run a @kickstarter check out my friend Alder's @vinography book project: http://kck.st/IAzFDy     
    
    
    Am I really going to watch http://ow.ly/s8gAP  just because @sfosternyc is in it? Maybe. Probably. OK YES #ohgodwhathaveibecome    
    
    
    @ellenjuhlin tru dat #boardgames4lyfe :)    
    
    
    Juxtaposition #pathfinderACG pic.twitter.com/UkGIojnTiV    
    
    
    Via @BrianEnigma , here's the @PortlandPolice scanner livestream mixed with an ambient music underscore: http://youarelistening.to/portland     
    
    
    @ninjahq yeah, she distracts you from your adventuring with her huge... tracts of land    
    
    
    @GailSimone You are terrible and I love you.    
    
    
    WHO LEFT THIS HAZMAT HERE #flashpoint #dangerouswaters pic.twitter.com/379xHxVAvL    
    
    
    [blog] Two Zero One Three Out: DeeAnn, Jasper, Tye, and I hope you're all enjoying your winter holidays!  Here... http://bit.ly/1d5znNt     
    
    
    Success! The boys are enjoying their Xmas gift! #onecatoneheatingpad http://instagram.com/p/imhY9HGpq2/     
    
    
    This is one of the toughest blog posts I've ever written. But I need to write this down. You'll see why tomorrow.    
    
    
    Now playing: Heartland pic.twitter.com/j3jERRTkUS    
    
    
    Now playing: Notre Dame pic.twitter.com/MUUyCxOoM0    
    
    
    @ObliviousWit Many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    Today's blog post (WARNING: SADNESS) - "I Miss My Friends" http://hotsheet.snout.org/2014/01/i-miss-my-friends.html … #theIinMEAT @igalko @wurmouroboros    
    
    
    I should really remember to quit and restart Chrome like, once every month or so.    
    
    
    In which a title is revealed! RT @curtiscchen: #512words Making Book: By Any Other Name: I'm terrible at coming up… http://goo.gl/fb/00qiQ     
    
    
    I should be sleeping    
    
    
    Our cats like to practice posing for avant garde short films pic.twitter.com/LipIU6KYBF    
    
    
    Our cats like to hunker down in their makeshift bed-fort pic.twitter.com/c4lXNkcbdu    
    
    
    Why I Don't Talk to My Wife Anymore - marcusaveryfamily: 2014 brings a new year and a lot of opportunity... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIs13Ollue     
    
    
    OK you guys this is my new favorite thing: a 4-year-old singing "Let it Go" http://observationdeck.io9.com/theres-a-4-year-old-singing-let-it-go-1494899509 …    
    
    
    I was going to stop watching TV but then there were cats sitting on me and now I might as well finish season 2 of The Newsroom.    
    
    
    @zulahni Oh, honey. Don't force us to stage an intervention. Look at your life. Look at your choices. #sassygayfriend    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Re: ARG Tools 2.1: bad news, the HTML entity is actually "&mdash" (no "e"). #htmlisweird    
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Confirmed. It's like magic! :)    
    
    
    College flashback: I just backed New Studio Album from Toad the Wet Sprocket! on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/17pShAZ     
    
    
    If you're wondering why I'm not tweeting so much this weekend, check my other account: @curtiscchen #wwcon13    
    
    
    #wwcon13 day 2 (@ Sheraton Portland Airport Hotel - @spg) http://4sq.com/15CQxkH     
    
    
    .@ninjahq "Scorekeeper XL," currently FREE on app store: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/scorekeeper-xl/id463243024?mt=8 …    
    
    
    "You call this archaeology?" #wwcon13 #nonsequitur http://instagram.com/p/cj4_8qGpk3/     
    
    
    I'll take Manhattan #wwcon13 #nobittersthough http://instagram.com/p/cknbNLmpoz/     
    
    
    Maybe it's just me, but emergency vehicles driving up & down the runway shooting off flares seems bad. #pdx    
    
    
    Last day of #wwcon13! (@ Sheraton Portland Airport Hotel - @spg) http://4sq.com/18WiWn2     
    
    
    @BrianEnigma Only movie I've ever seen where the Nazis are the heroes. THE NAZIS. #thatssomefuckedupshitrightthere    
    
    
    @kateleth I misread that tweet as "I'm a missing person..." and it confused and frightened me.    
    
    
    @mariancall Awesome! @DeeAnnSole and I look forward to seeing you there. :) #PAX    
    
    
    Hey @chiuki what do you think of this @kickstarter project? "Chineasy: The easiest way to learn Chinese" http://kck.st/1bZUaEJ     
    
    
    @chiuki Yeah, I wonder about that too. Some combinations always seemed rather arbitrary to me.    
    
    
    @snarke FYI, @DeeAnnSole & I have started BOARDWALK EMPIRE. Just 1.06 episodes a day (avg) & we'll be all set for S3 premiere! :)    
    
    
    Helpful infographic of the day (NSFW): Boobs per episode in HBO's #GameOfThrones , season 1 -  http://imgur.com/r/gameofthrones/I0tWqHN … via @imgur    
    
    
    @ninjahq "The Pointy End." Hell of a show.    
    
    
    @maryrobinette That's positively scandalous.    
    
    
    I'm often confused when I get a newsletter from "Tor" and can't tell from subject line whether that's @tordotcom or http://torproject.org     
    
    
    @bm0nies @mariafi @FlameIsLove @ghalidrim @snarke Or $4 in HD. :) What can @DeeAnnSole & I bring to share? Wine? Snacks?    
    
    
    (Great talk, but now I'm hungry AND horny.) Al Vernacchio: Sex needs a new metaphor. Here's one ... http://on.ted.com/dhGh  #TED    
    
    
    So this happened: "The Fatberg Saga, By John Scalzi and Paul Sabourin" http://ow.ly/nGDD1  #meanwhileontheinternet    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @ninjahq and many happy returns of the day! Hope you've got big fun plans for tonight. :)    
    
    
    Here's the thing.    
    
    
    What a week.    
    
    
    @erikwecks @MeiLinMiranda @jtw78 @jgurley Sorry, can't make it this week, but hope to see you all again soon! @curtiscchen    
    
    
    @dresdencodak You've taken your first step into a larger world... @stargatecommand :)    
    
    
    Dear self, stop messing with e-mail and just GO TO SLEEP.    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "Money for Nothing": Read "Money for Nothing" at 512 Words or FewerTrue: the imag... http://bit.ly/14dcZwW     
    
    
    .@angelamwebber Oh, that's a known bug: should be "grimlock." BTW, have you guys talked to Hasbro about that Velociraptor Dinobot yet? ;)    
    
    
    Movie sign! #romeoplusjuliet http://instagram.com/p/c0Q8j_mpu-/     
    
    
    @Galumbits Nope... Do you have a lead?    
    
    
    So, Romeo+Juliet. Now talking about other Shakespeare adaptations. Great night with friends and cocktails.    
    
    
    And then there's EPIC TEATIME with Alan Rickman.    
    
    
    @Galumbits If you can drive up to the 'Couve, you're welcome to stop by our apartment and meet her! DM me for e-mail, directions, etc.    
    
    
    Today's lunch. #thisisnotaclue http://instagram.com/p/c1hxr-GprF/     
    
    
    Volcanoes in Portland area: Rocky Butte, youngest, 97,000 years old; Oregon City, oldest, 1.4 million. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Great Missoula Floods (from glacier in Montana) 15,000-18,000 years ago carved out the topography of the Portland area. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Mt. St. Helens is youngest volcano in region, ~300k yrs old (most active since 45k); cf. Rainier, 1 million, and Hood, 900k. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    This is Professor Scott Burns, BTW: teaches Geology at PSU, consults with City of Portland, Stanford class of 1970. #stanfordtour    
    
    
    The Oak Tree Restaurant in Woodland, WA is supposed to have the greatest cinnamon rolls in the world. #stanfordtour #geologicallyimportant    
    
    
    This guy knows from terroir: http://geology.pdx.edu/node/67  #stanfordtour    
    
    
    Kalama, WA was supposed to be a major port, never developed; but it was the birthplace of @PyramidBrew . #stanfordtour    
    
    
    If you're retired, you can take classes for free at PSU. #stanfordtour #respectifyoure65andusinggoddamntwitter    
    
    
    @Galumbits We won't be home until after 9pm on Tuesday; is that too late for you guys? We're on east side, 205 & Mill Plain.    
    
    
    Lunch! #stanfordtour (@ Forest Learning Center) http://4sq.com/19jtj8j     
    
    
    @Galumbits We're busy every weeknight next week, unfortunately. How about next Saturday, the 17th, after 7:00pm?    
    
    
    @Galumbits (We're also free weekday afternoons, but I'm guessing you're not.)    
    
    
    Sunday Sunday Sunday    
    
    
    Trek minus two hours! (@ Cathedral Park w/ @lauraehall @brianenigma) http://4sq.com/18nhnhh     
    
    
    "Freeze program!" #trekinthepark #train    
    
    
    Fuck yeah.    
    
    
    @bm0nies @mariafi @snarke @FlameIsLove @ghalidrim @DeeAnnSole Let's do it again soon! Is everyone free next month on Friday the 13th? :)    
    
    
    @mariafi @ghalidrim @snarke @FlameIsLove How about Friday the 6th then? @DeeAnnSole & I can host, if y'all are willing to drive. :)    
    
    
    DAMN IT FEEL GOOD TO BE A GANGSTA    
    
    
    Lunchtime video chat! pic.twitter.com/1TKksjWZEO    
    
    
    ATTN @thedoubleclicks : "Researchers Breed Glow-in-the-Dark Rabbits" http://youtu.be/h3Gz1ZsfJmc  #thewayiglow    
    
    
    Tell your friends who live elsewhere about the "Portlandia 'Walkabout' Experience" Sweepstakes: http://ow.ly/nUAkl     
    
    
    I *finally* own the Les Miserables "dream cast" recording in MP3 format. HOW DID I LIVE UNTIL TODAY?!? #theatergeek    
    
    
    @ellenjuhlin Honey, I still got the original Broadway cast recording on AUDIO CASSETTE and the concert performance on LASERDISC. :) #oldman    
    
    
    The @Kickstarter video for @viennateng 's new music project is totally worth <3 minutes of your time: http://kck.st/19fTKIp     
    
    
    Who will I see at the SFWA Readings in Portlandia tonight? http://www.sfwa.org/other-resources/for-readers/reading-series/sfwa-northwest-reading-series/ …    
    
    
    playing hooky (@ Cinetopia for Despicable Me 2) http://4sq.com/1dbamn8     
    
    
    Well, I guess it's time to get to work now.    
    
    
    I'm guessing @jonrog1 's Twitter account just got hacked. #happenstothebestofus    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "My Least Favorite Martian": Read "My Least Favorite Martian" at 512 Words or Few... http://bit.ly/16sZ78B     
    
    
    Photoset: hello-the-future: ilikeyourstuffs: continuants: mememolly: luckycatproject: Lucky Cats - LOLcats... http://tmblr.co/Zp9xIssSp7-B     
    
    
    "Is Pon Farr like pudding?" "...It's SORT OF like pudding." #talkingtonontrekfans    
    
    
    Supplies! #namethatgame http://instagram.com/p/dGXuUGGpnm/     
    
    
    Just finished a game of Last Night on Earth: Timber Peak. Now starting Dungeon Roll. Why, it's almost like being at #GenCon! #notreally    
    
    
    @GoingLast Welcome to the Internet! ;)    
    
    
    @pdunwin @HellcowKeith ...that depends on the pudding. #HEYO    
    
    
    #SOON (@ Trek In The Park - @atomicarts) http://4sq.com/13HWx90     
    
    
    It's a pre-Trek in the Park picnic w/ @DeeAnnSole @ckwright @mariafi @ghalidrim @JadeE1024 @3hubcaps @snarke !    
    
    
    The cello is flying! @thedoubleclicks #teamaubrey http://instagram.com/p/dIwkawGpjs/     
    
    
    If not already, I suspect @NATEofBORG will henceforth be known as "scene-stealer" Scotty. #trekinthepark    
    
    
    I <3 @GailSimone . #thatisall    
    
    
    BTW, saw my first trailer for HOW TO TRAIN YOUR DRAGON 2 last Thursday. It was fine, but completely devoid of intentional comedy. #worrisome    
    
    
    @feliciaday "Floor dirty? No, floor clean!" #iapologizefornothing    
    
    
    I hate chewing.    
    
    
    @joshmillard Have fun! Great show this year. You probably already know to keep an eye out for @GarrettRWang :)    
    
    
    @Galumbits I'll e-mail you and cc: @DeeAnnSole :)    
    
    
    @ninjahq it's government island according to @PDXFire    
    
    
    @maryannjohanson Many happy returns of the day!    
    
    
    I will ALWAYS push it to 30 for @TheDoubleclicks #podcasting    
    
    
    Heyyy @lessachu @ellenjuhlin :) MT @arielwaldman: Know awesome Bay Area women? Invite them to Science Hack Day: http://sciencehackday2013.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    this is going well    
    
    
    OF COURSE it's from Portland: "The Rum of Giant Robots" http://cheezburger.com/7734686208  via @feedly    
    
    
    GUYS I just realized "Top Gear" is an AUTOMOTIVE DOUBLE ENTENDRE now where's my goddamn GetGlue or Viggle or whatever the fuck thing    
    
    
    #latetotheparty #nothowitworks #toobigtotweet    
    
    
    @dinabugg @Galumbits <zoidberg>Hooray!</zoidberg>    
    
    
    @ninjahq @Galumbits Thanks! We're very happy with this result. :)    
    
    
    In other news, @DeeAnnSole still does not get how knock-knock jokes work. #loveyouwife    
    
    
    In related news, @DeeAnnSole just spelled "Squirtle" with a "D"--a letter which does not appear in either "squirt" or "turtle." #loveyouwife    
    
    
    ??? pic.twitter.com/xwluzlnfFR    
    
    
    @jmacfee yeah apparently we don't watch enough tv    
    
    
    LADIES PLEASE ONE AT A TIME pic.twitter.com/7Isz9FiazQ    
    
    
    Takenoko! with @AubreyCello (not pictured) pic.twitter.com/5jXeqnbTaW    
    
    
    @Molly23 is so weird sometimes.    
    
    
    The music for today's Google Doodle was one of the first pieces I ever learned to play on the piano. Beautiful. http://ow.ly/o9yWI     
    
    
    On the road again! California, here we come!    
    
    
    Almost at the border. (@ Suncrest Rest Area) http://4sq.com/12tVGuX     
    
    
    Welcome to California!    
    
    
    GOOD MORNING PALO ALTO, BRING US YOUR FINEST COFFEECAKES AND EGGS BENEDICT.    
    
    
    Breakfast! (at @Hobees Restaurant w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16WfkDw     
    
    
    Sure, Ned, I'll give you a dollar.    
    
    
    [blog] Friday Flash Fiction: "The End": Read "The End" at 512 Words or FewerThis is the last of my weekly flas... http://bit.ly/16WSsnh     
    
    
    @gailsimone ...and then an image of Bill Gates filled the screen, along with the text THINK ON YOUR SINS. A building in Cupertino exploded.    
    
    
    The 50+ Greatest Tweets about Ben Affleck's casting as Batman http://ow.ly/odSB1     
    
    
    (For the record, I thought @BenAffleck did just fine in DAREDEVIL.)    
    
    
    In-person Sci-Fi Book Club meeting! Discussing @loversdiction 's novel EVERY DAY with @aprilgirl2 @thebrianlynch @DeeAnnSole .    
    
    
    We are now watching DREDD. Long story. Don't ask.    
    
    
    Okay, now switching to EUROPA REPORT.    
    
    
    @anthonyha Aw, of course you're in PDX the same weekend we're down in the Bay Area. Hopefully we can meet up next time!    
    
    
    Good news, everyone! EUROPA REPORT did not suck. Slow to get started, but if you liked Landis novel MARS CROSSING, you'll probably enjoy.    
    
    
    @radven Could be! Palo Alto right now, Half Moon Bay tonight, SF tomorrow. You?    
    
    
    @radven We'll be back on Monday, if you're still around Portland!    
    
    
    P.S. @anthonyha @radven You MUST go see Trek in the Park this weekend! Ideally TODAY with @TheDoubleclicks ! :) http://ow.ly/oeuae     
    
    
    Hey, we gotta eat breakfast SOMEWHERE. (at @Hobees Restaurant w/ @aprilgirl2 @thebrianlynch) http://4sq.com/1dd1ikq     
    
    
    Wedding vows of the year: "I will never harm you, or, through inaction, allow you to come to harm." Congratulations Sunshine & Acorn!!!!    
    
    
    You don't have to go home but you can't stay here #weddingmusic https://vine.co/v/hexFuiIVq2Y     
    
    
    Wedding lights! It's possible we weren't supposed to push the buttons. But, c'mon, Gamers here. https://vine.co/v/hexQDruEUD6     
    
    
    The wedding cake is a 3-D crossword puzzle! (We got paper copies.) @ The Ritz-Carlton, Half Moon Bay http://instagram.com/p/dauDfSmpsS/     
    
    
    Solve time: <1 wedding reception. #thiswasaclue http://instagram.com/p/da-Q_BGpry/     
    
    
    I wonder if anyone has ever attempted to DJ a wedding using only Girl Talk tracks.    
    
    
    #ObThrillerDance https://vine.co/v/he2ZwK2dIX6     
    
    
    It's art I say! https://vine.co/v/he2m6w0I6tJ     
    
    
    @lahosken The words flow over the edges, this one "leftward:" JOB CHANGE    
    
    
    #ObHavaNagila https://vine.co/v/he2TnxDwIqL     
    
    
    There's a word for what happened here tonight: SWELLEGANT. Congratulations, Sunshine & Acorn! Thanks for an awesome wedding party!    
    
    
    @kwylie @mattcleinman YOU LIE! On Ceti Alpha V there was life!    
    
    
    OH: "There's an adult video store, they MIGHT have some stuff."    
    
    
    Now it's a REAL lunch meeting: @DeeAnnSole just drew a pie chart on the butcher paper table covering.    
    
    
    Oregon welcomes you!    
    
    
    Rainy days and Mondays always make me... less likely to tweet? I dunno. Lame pun/joke, pop culture/politics reference, ironic hashtag. DONE.    
    
    
    @snarke Did you know you can buy a kilo of 99.9% pure anhydrous caffeine powder for ~$30 (plus shipping)? Add some pep to any drink! :)    
    
    
    Just finished signing another one-year lease on our apartment. Expect to see our faces around Portlandia for at least that much longer!    
    
    
    #fandom Man Of Steel 2 Teaser Trailer - Ben Affleck / Bryan Cranston (FAN MADE): http://youtu.be/U4U4he3GgC4  via @youtube    
    
    
    @rmalena You have a very sensitive disposition. ;)    
    
    
    @jmacfee I KNOW RIGHT    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu Please define "helping out." :)    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu Sorry, bad timing--we'll still be in Make-a-Strip then. Sounds like fun though!    
    
    
    Well, I guess it's time to start packing for #PAX .    
    
    
    @jonathanhliu I'm your huckleberry. :)    
    
    
    @MayflowerPark We're arriving today. What time is check-in? 3:00pm? (can't find info on web site or in confirmation e-mail)    
    
    
    @mayflowerpark We're all set. Thanks for your help!    
    
    
    So who else is in town for #PAX ?    
    
    
    @notNksanymore @sin_plague Awesome! I think @littlelull is organizing some kind of Sea Monkey thing; are y'all in the loop on on that?    
    
    
    @notNksanymore OK, clearly you know more than I do. ;)    
    
    
    Okay WHO ELSE do I know here. (@ Triple Door - @thetripledoor w/ @bm0nies @zulahni) http://4sq.com/188X5Hm     
    
    
    @ninjahq @ftcup You chose... poorly. ;)    
    
    
    @ninjahq Yeah yeah. Like you're going to touch his mohawk or something. Dream on, K&R. :)    
    
    
    @jeffphi Monday morning maybe? We're here until Tuesday.    
    
    
    @erikwecks @jonathanhliu We might try to sneak in after Make-a-Strip, if there's room. Otherwise we'll look for you later!    
    
    
    @davidscotton Groovy. Are we going to try to do dinner sometime?    
    
    
    @davidscotton We're turning in early tonight. Check in tomorrow?    
    
    
    Attention, #PAX @GeekDads photo hunters: I can help you with at least one of the items today. :) http://ow.ly/omSqf     
    
    
    @rael doesn't know we're sitting behind him and to the left #pax    
    
    
    @mattcleinman You know us so well. :)    
    
    
    Snack & game break in WSCC room 304! #pax    
    
    
    Apparently I've played Borderlands enough that I can draw the vault symbol from memory. Now I have a… http://instagram.com/p/dqFooYmplq/     
    
    
    @davidscotton Maybe. @DeeAnnSole is playing an RPG now; I'm in a panel at Sheraton. Do you have dinner plans yet?    
    
    
    @davidscotton Check in with us when you're done with that? :)    
    
    
    @davidscotton Want to meet me downstairs in a few minutes? Wrapping up now.    
    
    
    @davidscotton bottom of escalator, near revolving doors?    
    
    
    @davidscotton On my way! Now    
    
    
    Day 1 of #PAX complete: included fun panels, walking expo hall, gaming, meeting @pigsquad, dinner with @davidscotton . Tomorrow: MOAR!    
    
    
    @zulahni @bm0nies @krissywrites @roscone That would be Team Meat, booth 125 (promo for new game Mew-Genics). You can go 2 at a time! #PAX    
    
    
    @zulahni LET'S MAKE THIS HAPPEN    
    
    
    I've bested Chapter 1 of The Room. Chapter 2 awaits! http://bit.ly/NyNpkE     
    
    
    @calamityjamie Hope you're having a great PAX! Any chance you'll have time this weekend to play a certain card game in person? :)    
    
    
    @calamityjamie Groovy. No rush, we're in town until Tuesday. Enjoy pin trading!    
    
    
    Seeing a lot of Superman shirts at #PAX this year. Wonder if we have Zack Snyder to thank for that.    
    
    
    Also, best #PAX cosplay so far today: PotatOS from Portal 2. (sorry, no pic)    
    
    
    @zulahni Looks like you're busy. Virtual hug! Wave!    
    
    
    Back in line for Acquisitions Inc. Also: snack time! #PAX    
    
    
    @ninjahq You're probably ahead of us. We're in the same column, at the front edge of the fire escape.    
    
    
    