After quite some time working on different things: Running some  experiments on content extraction from web documents again...    
    
    
    might be interesting for @arifah77 RT @danielequercia: RT @LouWoodley: How are people using Twitter? (infographic) http://on.mash.to/p9XNMJ     
    
    
    Potentially interesting for all #essir participants: Recommended Reading for IR Research Students http://bit.ly/qoRfvj     
    
    
    Entertaining talk of Ricardo Baeza-Yates at #essir -- Someone please tell him why there are so many flower pictures in Koblenz    
    
    
    Just been to the "mainland games" in Rüsselsheim (Scottish highland games in Germany) -- Great!    
    
    
    Arrived at #ecir2010 http://bit.ly/33k765. Registration done. Today: Tutorials & Workshops.    
    
    
    Now opening of CIRSE (Workshop on Contextual Information Access, Seeking and Retrieval Evaluation).    
    
    
    Aim: Evaluation of contextual information access. Does Cranfield still apply    
    
    
    Acceptance rate was ~ 30%    
    
    
    Introduction of Stephen Robertson. (Slides' title: On queries and other messages)    
    
    
    Stephen starts his presentation    
    
    
    normal science: choose phenomena, gather data, formulate hypothese, make predictions, do new experiments, modify model, (restart process)    
    
    
    Critical experiments: setup where two models make different prediction. Sort out one, which does not comply with experiment outcome    
    
    
    Cranfield in the 50s/60s as critical experiment for information organisation theories    
    
    
    System is the part of the universe chosen for observation and measurement ( -- base for experiments)    
    
    
    Open systems (opposed to closed) interacts with its environment (that is the rest of the universe)    
    
    
    Interaction with environment: "something" passes the system boundary. We are interested in information, say transmitted by messages    
    
    
    Suggestions on how to study phenomena: find boundary, messages passing boundaries, message contents    
    
    
    Suggestion on evaluation: via output, outcome, involving environment outside the system (e.g. relevance is outside)    
    
    
    IR onion: boundaries of interest: system/user, boundaries in the mind of user    
    
    
    IR onion: (((((mechanism)interface)user model of system)user model of info seeking task)user problem ASK/model of larger task)    
    
    
    Orgins of the onion: intermediary (e.g. librarian): user <-> intermediary <-> system. Maybe then direct access to system    
    
    
    Pragmatic choice for boundaries: ability to observe and control with minimal disturbance of the system (all observations disturb system)    
    
    
    Lab settings: construct encapsulated scenarios    
    
    
    Nowadays: rich observables (system interior, interface). Missing the user's mind.    
    
    
    Missing: reference interviews between intermediary and user. today happens in user's mind    
    
    
    Indirect observables (relevance feedback)    
    
    
    Simple logging is very rich to capture user interaction. No user disturbance. extend with eye-tracking, questionaires    
    
    
    Scientific aim: make out-of-data predictions    
    
    
    So far: queries are central to the IR interface.    
    
    
    Approaches: query-free systems, systems to get more verbose queries    
    
    
    Views on queries: representation for information needs, ASKs    
    
    
    Alternative: query as speech act. Basic unit not the statement, but the speech act (e.g. "Thank you", "Fire!")    
    
    
    Questions are speech acts: they try to make something happen    
    
    
    Queries not necessarily as questions, formulation for search system different. Also commands are speech acts    
    
    
    Second alternative to interpret queries: as hypothesis. What kind of document has the answer to my info need, intent, ASK?    
    
    
    Query is hypothesis: if the results are good, the hypothesis was good    
    
    
    Queries as active probes  rather than passive descriptions    
    
    
    End of Stephen's talk, now questions and discussion    
    
    
    Next talk: Ralf Bierig: An Experiment and Analysis System Framework for the Evaluation of Contextual RelationShips    
    
    
    Work with Nick Belkin. Involving lots of implicit data. What goes on in people's mind during search    
    
    
    System will be presented as demo during reception tomorrow evening    
    
    
    PooDLE system http://bit.ly/3psAr personalised assistant to support contextual IR    
    
    
    Interaction events on a timeline, segmentation of event sequence. Aim: detect patterns, learn models on the data    
    
    
    Next talk: Ying-Hsang Liu: On Search Topic Variability in Interactive Information Retrieval    
    
    
    #cirse2010 proceedings will be online, URL following lateron #ecir2010    
    
    
    Searcher types: search novices, domain experts, search experts, medical librarians. Fields: search experience, domain knowledge    
    
    
    Comparison of two systems. One including MeSH keyterms, one without (only abstracts)    
    
    
    Next talk: Miriam Daoud: Contextual evaluation of mobile search    
    
    
    Evaluation setup: user studies to obtain queries and relevance judgements, then generate context for lab settings.    
    
    
    Next talk: Catherine Mulwa: A Proposal for the Evaluation of Adaptive Personalized Information Retrieval    
    
    
    Look at evaluation from the point of view of the adaptive hypermedia community    
    
    
    #ecir2010 #cirse2010 proceedings online: http://bit.ly/cjMaFC    
    
    
    Key note by Ian Ruthven: But Where Do We Go from Here?    
    
    
    IR as enabling technology: Other disciplines depend on IR technologies    
    
    
    Search is not a standalone activity. It is interwoven with other activities (e.g. writing a paper, developing an algorithm)    
    
    
    Danger of interfaces shrinking instead of growing. Google's simple interface is not best under all aspects!    
    
    
    Interface opportunities: cross-comparative studies (include existing systems), non-directed search, encourage people to search different    
    
    
    Emotional design to encourage users to search (differentely)    
    
    
    Reference to Don Norman (where did hear that name already? Tutorial at ECDL?)    
    
    
    Analyse social media. So far, models analyse what people do, not why?    
    
    
    How does the perception of a system influence a user's interaction with the system?    
    
    
    Nowadays most information about a person is not provided by himself/herself, but by others    
    
    
    IR is good in cooperations -- IR at the risk of losing its uniqueness? Don't forget core of the field!    
    
    
    Still too much of historic library scenario: people do search, walk away with information and then do another task    
    
    
    Again: IR research has focussed at lot on what works, not why?    
    
    
    User study on literature discovery: 41% of comments on the interaction (not information), 16% on intentions (what to do with information)    
    
    
    User study on literature discovery: 40% of comments about relevance    
    
    
    Not all information is equal: take a look at the source (human, who, media, machine-created)    
    
    
    Nice question: What role will technology play between information creation and information use?    
    
    
    Closing of #cirse2010 workshop. Nice presentations, two very interesting key notes.    
    
    
    #ecir2010 now attending tutorial on "Crowdsourcing for Relevance Evaluation" by Omar Alonso    
    
    
    Presenter working at microsoft on bing search engine and Twitter ;-) -- so real time search.    
    
    
    @domsom #cirse2010 was interesting -- lots of ideas for #relevanzer    
    
    
    Book on #crowdsourcing by Jeff Howe (recommend for our library?)    
    
    
    #crowdsourcing as a cheap, fast, easy-to-setup way to solve tasks    
    
    
    Focus on using Amazon mechanical turk for #crowdsourcing. Now applications (NLP,Translation, ...)    
    
    
    Amazon mechanical turk (AMT) seems to have performed good in TREC assessments -- better than professional assessors in one case    
    
    
    #ecir2010 looked at workers (turkers) so far, now shifting to requesters    
    
    
    #crowdsourcing tutorial: the coffee break is not yet ready for us :-)    
    
    
    Now doing real experiment on AMT online: photo of reality-tv star as result for query "idiot". Relevant or not    
    
    
    AMT experiment running: 5 opinions after few minutes (one from the workshop) : 2 relevant, 3 not relevant (1 from workshop)    
    
    
    Bow off to coffee break. very interesting tutorial so far.    
    
    
    #ecir2010 continuing tutorial on #crowdsourcing Now collecting results of idiot-query example    
    
    
    Next example: query classification task for AMT Showing how to get data into templates, List with headline query maps to $query in template    
    
    
    If there is no activity on an AMT experiment in the first hour, the experiment has a design flaw    
    
    
    Third experiment: relevance judgements on wikipedia. More data in a CSV-style list. Documents included in iframe    
    
    
    Swapping to "How to design an experiment on AMT"    
    
    
    UX is very important for AMT. Simple instructions, clear instructions, support users, good design, highlight key terms, provide all data    
    
    
    Qualification test can be uploaded only via API, but accessed lateron from dashboard during task construction    
    
    
    @elunca Great tutorial, thanks a lot    
    
    
    Opening speach of #ecir2010 statistics about submissions, organization. 44 / 208 papers, 28 / 73 posters accepted    
    
    
    First #ecir2010 keynote: Barry Smyth (UCD) on "Web Search Futures: Personal, Collaborative, Social"    
    
    
    Search as the Web's killer application    
    
    
    Overview: Key Challenges, Context in Web Search, Towards social search (HeyStack system)    
    
    
    50%  search failures. On average 8 hours in a month    
    
    
    Retrieval effectiveness rises with longer queries, but only till 3 terms, than drops again    
    
    
    Content Farms for SEO, gaming with search engines. Obtain top ranks but do not provide top quality. Generate contents for requested terms    
    
    
    Content farms: detect queried terms, calculate ad value of an article on related topics, hire free lance journalists to write the articles    
    
    
    Contexts in Search: User, Document, Task, Social    
    
    
    @domsom social context seen as a possible next step in development of search!    
    
    
    1 of 4 searches is trying to re-find something we found before, 2 of 3 searches is to find something our friends/colleagues found before    
    
    
    Search engines vs. Social networks. 500m queries vs. 750m shares, relevance vs. reputation    
    
    
    Social search engine: blurry expression, not clear what exactly it means    
    
    
    Example: Aardvark as social QA system    
    
    
    Collaborative IR: Remote or co-located / synch or asynch    
    
    
    Starting to introduce the HeyStaks system. Search utility: organise search activities in folders (staks); share staks; search, promote staks    
    
    
    HeyStaks Integration into browser to exploit standard search engines. http://www.heystaks.com/    
    
    
    HeyStaks: Relative high number of users producing staks, in other communities much lower.    
    
    
    Discussing model on how to promote a user's reputation in HeyStaks based on clicks in staks    
    
    
    Conclusions: web search is changing, context considered, collaboration of interest, relevance replaced/extended by reputation    
    
    
    End of Barry Smyth's keynote, now questions. I'll stop commenting to save notebook energy (no plugs arounds)    
    
    
    #ecir2010 first session with four talks: LM for time component in query, attitude in texts, IR in medicine, query log analysis    
    
    
    #ecir2010 full-papers-as-posters session during lunch break. Interesting work, might have deserved more attention    
    
    
    #ecir2010 great poster session last evening. Lots of interested people, positive feedback, new ideas    
    
    
    #ecir2010 bouncing ball game is a big success. People seem "unhappy" that the game is interrupted for the keynote :-)    
    
    
    #ecir2010 Udo Kruschwitz introducing Hinrich Schütze. Keynote on "Natural Language Processing in IR: Shallow or Deep?"    
    
    
    search in the real world is an interactive dialogue between searcher and expert. Search engines do not support this    
    
    
    several examples on shallow NLP in search engines: synonyms, snippets,...    
    
    
    Introduction of Powerset NLP Parser (by now bought by Mircosoft)    
    
    
    Examples for parsing real world questions for better results (opposing to standard web search)    
    
    
    So far the good examples, now some where Google performs as good or even better    
    
    
    Fixed-phrase queries can beat NLP in many cases. Dumb, high-precision queries close to an expected answer work well    
    
    
    Web search engines benefit from high redundancy of contents. This provides (all) possible semantically equivalent variations    
    
    
    But: web redundancy does not always help. Some example where fixed-phrase queries fail    
    
    
    Next NLP-Parser: Google / Michael Ringgaarg's Parser. Code example for the easy access to the parser. Very good efficiency    
    
    
    Ringgaard's Parser: High speed at the cost of lower accuracy    
    
    
    3. topic: Interactive NLP. Example: train a highly specialized NER for a specific task    
    
    
    Distinguishing "Barry Smith" via concordance lists and the context of verbs (Professor are "appointed" but not "traded" and don't "perform")    
    
    
    Visualization as key to get users accept the technique (Because it is even more work than relevance feedback)    
    
    
    Hinrich Schütze finishes  his #ecir2010 keynote, wishes more NLP in IR (with reference to SIGIR 2010 CfP topics)    
    
    
    #ecir2010 lunch poster on tag clouds and LM. Might be interesting for improving the document word cloud approach to help relevance decisions    
    
    
    #ecir2010 last day. waiting for keynote. been up too long last night discussing -- start to feel lack of sleep    
    
    
    #ecir2010 introduction of the KSJ award and its dedication.    
    
    
    Mirella Lapata can't be at #ecir2010 so the keynote has been registered and will be played back...    
    
    
    Description of content-based image retrieval, text-based image retrieval (annotations)  and the "Google-way" via text around pictures    
    
    
    Using human labelled images as training set to train an automatic annotator based on visual features    
    
    
    Use of latent variables as semantic concepts to model joint probability for features and annotations    
    
    
    Interesting idea for Image IR: annotate pictures with keywords, then form a caption out of those. Difficult but fascinating    
    
    
    #ecir2010 questions to the pre-recorded keynote? Questions are recorded and answers will be published online ... feels a bit weird    
    
    
    #ecir2010 next session on Personalization & Recommendation. Starting with Performance Prediction to Enhance Collaborative Filtering    
    
    
    #ecir2010 talk on "Personalizing Web Search with Folksonomy-based User and Document Profiles".    
    
    
    Central problem is how to obtain a user profile -- might be interesting for @domsom and relevanzer ... let's see    
    
    
    paper of current presentation(personalisation based on folksonomies) online http://bit.ly/aP5Ka9 @domsom #ecir2010    
    
    
    If I got it right: represent a user via his tags in delicious and model him as a document. Classical approach VSM and cosine for docs/users    
    
    
    Two new approaches now: VSM with scalar product (no length normalisation) and a BM25 based solution    
    
    
    @domsom social tagging profiles seem a good way to model a user's interest #ecir2010    
    
    
    NetSpeak http://netspeak.cc/ writing assistant. Search WWW for common phrases etc. System was a great demo at #ecir2010    
    
    
    last #ecir2010 session. Would be curious to get data of previous talk (Ralf Schenkel). Could compare my content extraction with spotsigs    
    
    
    last talk of #ecir2010 on spatial diversity. However, nice example on diversity in web search: SIGIR ("ours" vs. http://www.sigir.mil/ )    
    
    
    Interesting #ecir2010 talk by Mark Sanderson. Interesting considerations. Feels a bit like a keynote    
    
    
    Once again: Amazon Mechanical Turk to gather relevance decisions in IR. #ecir2010    
    
    
    A comment I expected: How to deal with the unknown bias in MTurk user evaluation. Tutorial by @elunca  said: doesn't matter #ecir2010    
    
    
    Now closing session #ecir2010 by Stefan Rüger    
    
    
    #ecir2010 now handing over to #ecir2011 in Dublin 18-21 April 2011. GC: Cathal Gurrin    
    
    
    #ecir2011 workshops in the Guiness Storehouse ;-) ought to be fun    
    
    
    Last thanks from Stefan. Then by #ecir2010 and Milton Keynes.    
    
    
    Did a few mTurk HITS after #ecir2010 crowdsourcing tutorial of @elunca It can actually be fun -- if the HITS are designed well!    
    
    
    Next week: ROBUST project meeting in Paris #ictrobust    
    
    
    Setting up new laptop -- why does no search engine provide good results for "which programs did I install last time?" ;-)    
    
    
    About to start my journey to Paris to meet with the folks of the ROBUST project. #ictrobust    
    
    
    Southampton people are presenting a first draft of the ROBUST community risk analysis dashboard -- looks good! #ictrobust    
    
    
    Listen how healthy is your online community -- cool work done by Polecat #ictrobust    
    
    
    Introducing the ROBUST project to the Virtual Center of Excellence on Online Communities and the User Advisory Board #ictrobust    
    
    
    Returning from a wonderful ROBUST meeting @TEMIS in Paris. Thanks to the local organizors. #ictrobust    
    
    
    Whisky, Whisky, Whisky! #cikm2011 promises to be a great event. [ Let's see if this get retweeted ;-) ]    
    
    
    Life is funny: Read a paper on document mixture-models of several languages, while next to me two bilingual kids spoke a German-English mix    
    
    
    Just finished the poster for #cikm2011 providing deeper understanding how ESA (Explicit Semantic Analysis) works    
    
    
    Leaving for CIKM in my beloved Glasgow #cikm2011 #ictrobust #glasgow    
    
    
    First hop to Amsterdam with KLM then off to Glasgow! #cikm2011    
    
    
    Arrived in #glasgow -- good scottish weather: it's raining only a little #cikm2011    
    
    
    Great event at the Auchentoshan distillery -- thanks to the organizors #cikm2011    
    
    
    Now breakfast, then off to the #detect workshop at #cikm    
    
    
    Keynote by @mattroweshow at #DETECT workshop: Using Behaviour Analysis to Detect Cultural Aspects in Social Media Systems #cikm2011    
    
    
    Behaviour Analysis keynote by @mattroweshow at #DETECT workshop #ictrobust    
    
    
    Christoph Kling now presenting on detecting cultural areas on flickr #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Second #detect keynote by Ralf Kreste on Recommendation on the Social Web: Diversification and ersonalization #cikm2011    
    
    
    Ralf Krestel giving a detailed analysis on tagging systems and tag usage in the detect workshop #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Ralf presents mixture of LM&LDA for tag recommendation. Wonder how it relates to the Epistemic model of Klaas Dellschaft #cikm2011 #detect    
    
    
    "Cultural Awareness in Social Media" presented by Tatjana Welzer #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Global communication without physical borders in social media motivates the need for cultural awareness! #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Giulia Boato presenting work on "Emotion Based Classification of Natural Images" #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    "Sentiment classification on images requires an understanding of cultural background" #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Ludger Martin talking about "Filtering Usability Data with Reference to Behavior" #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    #DETECT authors: Let me know if you have your slides online -- I'll link them on the workshop web site #cikm2011    
    
    
    "Classification of Tweets via compression rate" by Ko Fujimura #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Just learned a cultural difference: "wwwwwwwww" means "lol" in Japanese :-) #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    @ISWC2011 tweet compression rate is useful for hashtag harmonization. This might have solved your problem ;-) #iswc2011 #cikm2011 #detect    
    
    
    "Understanding Semantic Change of Words Over Centuries" by Derry Tanti Wijaya. Examples: awful, mouse #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Using google book ngrams dataset ( http://bit.ly/o7fAUi  ) to discover changes in word semantics. Nice idea! #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    Finishing #detect workshop with interesting plenary discussion. Nice contributions, very active audience #cikm2011    
    
    
    Thanks to all authors and contributors of #detect - You turned this into a great workshop! #cikm2011    
    
    
    @blogranger You're welcome. A workshop is living from its participants -- and we had a great audience. #detect #cikm2011    
    
    
    About to leave with @cckling and @nnaveed for the #cikm2011 conference welcome reception.    
    
    
    Cool we are on the Glasgow university news RT @CIKM2011: Computer scientists logon to Glasgow: http://www.gla.ac.uk/news/headline_215172_en.html … #cikm2011    
    
    
    Busy 1. day of #cikm2011: keynote by @karger, @nnaveed presents our paper, and I'll be around our ESA Poster with Benno&Maik    
    
    
    #cikm2011 starting very early today at 8:10 with the opening ceremony. Curious for the keynote!    
    
    
    Greetings from Glasgow to Bonn. Enjoy #iswc2011 ! Too bad I cannot be in two places at the same time #cikm2011    
    
    
    718 delegates at #cikm2011 -- largest CIKM ever    
    
    
    #cikm2011 @karger presents: high-speed, highly interesting keynote on managing information scraps    
    
    
    @kunegis corpus of information scraps http://bit.ly/rLBgDw  by @karger could be interesting for KONECT #cikm2011    
    
    
    dusty old algorithms + human intelligence + smart user interface = great information sharing application #cikm2011 @karger keynote    
    
    
    The microphone of the neighbour sessions seems to transmit to our audio system #lol #cikm2011 :-)    
    
    
    Interesting Session on sparse data and difficult queries. C. Zhai obtaining term senses by clustering on term-cooccurance matrix #cikm2011    
    
    
    Next: @nnaveed presenting our work with @kunegis @arifah77 on #interestingness and length normalization in #twitter retrieval #cikm2011    
    
    
    Exciting poster session. Lots of positive feedback on our Insights into ESA poster #cikm2011    
    
    
    Cool! Our billion triple challenge submission made it into the second round! Great work Mathias and Ansgar #iswc2011 #btc    
    
    
    @shangz most likely because CIKM had network problems today :-(    
    
    
    @idefixuni Hard to believe -- it did not feature our ESA poster ;-D    
    
    
    @fabradd Hi Falk! You're at #cikm2011 in Glasgow?    
    
    
    Physicians look at symptoms and guess, biomedicine could provide knowledge #cikm2011 keynote by Justin Zobel    
    
    
    One for @kunegis : Biologist describe the human metabolism as ... a network :-) #cikm2011 (but it is rather small ~50.000 nodes)    
    
    
    Saw 2 relevant demos: (a) local event detection on social media and (b) efficient retrieval of timeseries #cikm2011    
    
    
    Now @JeffD starting his talk with "you may ask me questions on Twitter" #cikm2011    
    
    
    Curious for the next #cikm2011 talk: "Keyword search over RDF graphs" --would also have fitted to #iswc2011    
    
    
    Funny title of next #cikm2011 talk: "Frequency-Aware Similarity Measures: Why Arnold Schwarzenegger Is Always a Duplicate"    
    
    
    Attending #cikm2011 session on Social Networks and Communities. Many relevant papers for #ictrobust    
    
    
    Find expert groups, infer user interest, evaluate influence and conformity. Will need to do some reading later! #cikm2011 #ictrobust    
    
    
    Paper on differences in twitter usage presented by @ruthygarcia #cikm2011    
    
    
    @kwelle yes, there is a pre-print at http://ruthygarcia.com/mycv.php     
    
    
    social search: is it "finding information through other people" OR "finding information with other people"? #cikm2011 panel    
    
    
    Seems a recurrent pattern: Systems should detect and tell what is missing in an environment (community, work group, expert network)    
    
    
    @kunegis @arifah77 had a nice lunch discussion and idea for future twitter work with @nnaveed today -- let's meet once we're back    
    
    
    Chance & Challenge: Merge social search and web search to avoid filter bubble phenomenon #cikm2011 #panel    
    
    
    Let's try: to what kind of questions can you get serious answers on social media? #cikm2011 panel    
    
    
    @renepickhardt you should check the twitter feed of #recsys. Industry track has interesting numbers for the GRAPHITY paper    
    
    
    Entertaining and inspiring discussions at the #cikm2011 panel. Thanks all    
    
    
    Kelvingrove gallery is simply a wonderful location for conference dinners: arts, culture & good food #cikm2011 #ecir2008    
    
    
    @kunegis spoke with a fan your slashdot zoo paper during the #cikm2011 conference dinner. His talk on link prediction is tomorrow.    
    
    
    @device_null Then anti-social search is an inverse one-class classification problem: you do not hat positive training examples    
    
    
    @seblimb Hey, didn't know you were on twitter!    
    
    
    @device_null That would turn interestingness into a static quality measure as in http://bit.ly/p1G53R  -- but the crowd might still find it    
    
    
    Steve Robertson on "Why recall matters" to oppose the fixation on precision@10 #cikm2011 industry track    
    
    
    Freebase identifies key values of entities on various web databases to describe an entity #cikm2011    
    
    
    Freebase API on Google API since last week #cikm2011    
    
    
    @arifah77 @kunegis Have seen this talk? @fabianabel : Slides about "Faceted Search on Twitter" are online: http://www.slideshare.net/persweb/leveraging-the-semantics-of-tweets-for-adaptive-faceted-search-on-twitter-9903104 …    
    
    
    Session on "Science, the Past, and the Future" starting with talk on plagiarism detection. Let's see what they're doing #cikm2011    
    
    
    Speaker says "plagiarism" and in come the experts from Weimar ;-) #cikm2011 #pan    
    
    
    Very nice analysis and great presentation of "Studying How the Past Is Remembered"  #cikm2011    
    
    
    The time dimension of text is a great resource for interesting information.  Adam Jatowt demonstrated that very nicely #cikm2011    
    
    
    Just checked the author disambiguation on MS Academic Search @ststaab exists twice at @unikold -- demo effect? #cikm2011    
    
    
    Presentation on "Citation count prediction". Let's see how it relates to discussion length prediction of @mattroweshow #ictrobust #cikm2011    
    
    
    Citation count prediction seems to benefit most from author and venue features, content less important ;-) #cikm2011    
    
    
    Another presentation by Adam Jatowt: this time on the future #cikm2011    
    
    
    @richardm_ which tool did you use for language detection on tweets? #curious    
    
    
    GREAT! If I got it right from remote: Our #SchemEx work with Mathias and @ascherpuokob won the #btc2011 @ #iswc2011 #WeST    
    
    
    @richardm_ Thanks! I'll check that out    
    
    
    Tough task: Hold someone else's presentation of ~34 slides loaded with formulas in a 12 minute session slot    
    
    
    Last day of #cikm2011 - going for the #smuc2011 workshop on search and mining user generated content    
    
    
    @giacomoinches I'm in the #smuc2011 workshop, but probably won't be around till the end. Maybe we can meet in the coffee break?    
    
    
    David Losada motivating a strong need of opinion mining and sentiment analysis for social media #smuc2011 #cikm2011    
    
    
    So, what OM&SA really lack seems to be discourse analysis: understand what is the final conclusion in a document is #smuc2011    
    
    
    BUT: when trying to understand what is considered interesting on Twitter we found that sentiments DID help: http://bit.ly/p1G53R  #smuc2011    
    
    
    My guess: there is not one sentiment flow approach that works for all kinds of documents. Twitter != Blogs != News articles #smuc2011    
    
    
    @denzil_correa Also: authors express sentiments differently in different media, e.g. in Twitter you can not elaborate much    
    
    
    @giacomoinches yeah -- sound fine. see you there!    
    
    
    @denzil_correa These are even more difficult. And I guess knowing the context of a document first would help here as well    
    
    
    @mattroweshow They also used author&content features, additionally some context (e.g. venue). I'll send you the paper by mail    
    
    
    An ontology on reputation in social networks. Does it integrate with #sioc ? #smuc2011    
    
    
    An ontology on reputation in social networks. Does it integrate with #sioc ontology? #smuc2011    
    
    
    Curious for how near duplicates in UGC relates to SMS spam #smuc2011    
    
    
    @arifah77 a test collection of SMS spam: http://www.dt.fee.unicamp.br/~tiago/smsspamcollection/ … might be useful for your work    
    
    
    Nice meeting @denzil_correa and @giacomoinches in person in the coffee break #cikm2011    
    
    
    keynote on Retrieval and Recommendation in Social Media by Joemon Jose #smuc2011    
    
    
    Combining parts of the datagraph linking users, items and tags for recommendations #smuc2011    
    
    
    For the combination users, items and tags I guess using something like TripleRank based on tensor analysis would work fine #smuc2011    
    
    
    Mapping tags to semantic concepts or POS entities to identify the category  of the tag. #smuc2011    
    
    
    Next #smuc2011 talk: Improving answer ranking in QA portals -- will be interesting also for #ictrobust    
    
    
    Features to measure answer quality: readability, formality, grammaticality, etc. Static and independent of query #smuc2011 #ictrobust    
    
    
    Finally someone noticed the talk slots of 40+20+20 min not summing up to a 110 min session. More time for talks and questions #smuc2011    
    
    
    @denzil_correa getting ready for his talk on "Mining Twitter Tweets to Tag Flickr Photos and YouTube Videos" #smuc2011 #cikm2011    
    
    
    #smuc2011 talk mentioned a social media platform for sharing YOUR sounds -- wonder if this will work out for long ;-) http://soundcloud.com/     
    
    
    Won't be around for the afternoon session any longer. Bye everyone, was a great conference and nice to meet you! #cikm2011 #smuc2011    
    
    
    Today we celebrated our victory at the Billion TRIPLE challenge with a TRIPLE distilled single malt scotch :-D #iswc2011 #btc2011    
    
    
    Interesting: Special Technical Community on Social networking (@stcsn)
http://bit.ly/uUWsKT     
    
    
    Van Halen on the radio and my daughters (3 and 6) "jump" in the kitchen :-) #LifeIsGreat    
    
    
    Just finished the LiveTweet prototype web frontend telling you how interesting a tweet is: http://bit.ly/tetMay  #ictrobust #WeST_Ko    
    
    
    SchemEX in the media #ictrobust RT @ststaab: RT @journalWebSem: Elsevier Announces Winners Semantic Web Challenge, http://bit.ly/tCXOdz     
    
    
    @kunegis will you tweet about the #trec2011 #microblog track? Keep us up to date    
    
    
    @kunegis what are the interesting results and take-home messages from #trec2011?    
    
    
    @mattroweshow Is there a CfP or workshop homepage for #msm2012 ?    
    
    
    Our LiveTweet (http://bit.ly/tetMay ) has been accepted as demo at #ecir2012. Well done @arifah77, @kunegis, @nnaveed #ictrobust    
    
    
    Presented #SchemEX today at the #ictrobust review meeting.    
    
    
    wow! don't manage to search the web because I'm stuck playing #pacman with the #google logo    
    
    
    @Kris10Vermoesen nice article about our #WebSci2011 paper. If you're interested I can also point to some follow up work.    
    
    
    @Kris10Vermoesen oh, and by the way: you might want to try out http://livetweet.west.uni-koblenz.de  - that's the theory turned into practice    
    
    
    Attending the RapidMiner workshop at @WeST_Ko    
    
    
    Sure sign you have been busy lately: Having to catch up readying your favourite web comics of the last 3 month    
    
    
    Brushing up my knowledge about the theory behind bayesian estimates for probability distributions -- feels good to do some math again ;-)    
    
    
    Talk on UX by @humanized at university of mainz    
    
    
    @isaach which data did you use for the tweet length plot? Made one for @trecmicroblog which had a different shape -- might post it later    
    
    
    Strange: my #google calender is not working any more under #chrome .. fine with #firefox    
    
    
    Freezing this morning. Will fire up some intensive computation on my notebook to defrost my hands ;-)    
    
    
    On the way to Ulm. Visiting Prof. Schweiggert and Hadi to plan the next steps of joint work.    
    
    
    Travelling to Düsseldorf to present #LiveTweet and the ideas behind it: http://livetweet.west.uni-koblenz.de/ 
#ictrobust    
    
    
    Returning from Düsseldorf. Nice audience for the talk about #LiveTweet. Thx to @kwelle and Isabella Peters for the invitation    
    
    
    @kwelle Das Sentiment Wörterbuch heißt ANEW : Affective Norms for English Words. Paper dazu ist von Bradley und Lang.    
    
    
    Leaving for project meeting in Dresden at SAP #ictrobust    
    
    
    Started #ictrobust meeting at SAP in Dresden. More and more things taking concrete shape in the analysis of online business communities    
    
    
    Busy project meeting: http://twitpic.com/8n8e4k  #ictrobust    
    
    
    Had quick demo and introduction of Apache Giraph by  @sscdotopen #ictrobust    
    
    
    Wonderful: my fellows from #ukob provided my with ice cream for the coffee break! Thx to @kunegis Felix & Julia !!! #ictrobust    
    
    
    Last day of #ictrobust meeting at SAP in Dresden. Agenda: small discussion groups and planning ahead    
    
    
    Don't manage to catch up the lack of sleep on the train coming back from #ictrobust meeting :-( Guess I'll do some paper reading instead    
    
    
    Bidding for #websci12 reviews. Many interesting submissions. A lot of twitter work. Hard to choose what I want to review...    
    
    
    @arifah77 working on new ideas about twitter analysis?    
    
    
    Just got a notification that our telco was canceled due to a Feb 29 bug in the web conference system :-D #feb29    
    
    
    Is there a method on the Twitter API to collect ALL the replies for a given tweet? Experience anyone? #twitterapi    
    
    
    Seems our team from @WeST_Ko won the @apps4de competition with the app LISA Congratulations! http://bit.ly/zkrLw3     
    
    
    If this doesn't proof the climate change: German radio reports about a drought in southern England (!) due to lack of rain!!!    
    
    
    On the road to Lyon for #WWW12 - loaded with stuff for our ROBUST booth. #ictrobust    
    
    
    Just set up the #ictRobust booth at #www2012 in Lyon    
    
    
    Had a great chat with Tomaz about web content extraction and boilerplate removal. Maybe an extension of my previous work ahead? #www2012    
    
    
    Now going to attend the #www2012 keynote by #TimBL.    
    
    
    Now a short intro by @ststaab on submissions and the technical program. #www2012    
    
    
    Start of the keynote by TimBL. Can't understand why I still see so many people checking their e-mail... #www2012    
    
    
    TimBL talking about web apps as a way to break through vendor locked systems. #www2012    
    
    
    Folks at the #www2012 keynote: Are you looking at the big video screen or at the "real" TimBL in front of out?    
    
    
    @Yves_Moreau Yeah, I am sitting in the middle and it is still far from the podium.    
    
    
    Attended an interesting session on semantic web search. Should try to position some #SchemEX followup here next year. #www2013    
    
    
    Hi @tomaz ! We meet for coffee at the #ictrobust booth once #www2012 sessions are over at 5:30?    
    
    
    @tomaz No prob. Let's meet at 18:00.    
    
    
    @tomaz @kohlschuetter I'm in -- what would be a good time? Coffee break/Lunch break?    
    
    
    Here is an article about the "CISPA" TimBL was talking about yesterday: http://bit.ly/IPfrif  @renepickhardt #www2012    
    
    
    For IBM's Watson having a selected corpus as knowledge base was better than having the entire web. #www2012    
    
    
    WWW 2013 in Brazil will feature a most influential paper award. Wonder how they'll evaluate this? #www2012 #www2013    
    
    
    Awards at #www2012 now announced by @ststaab and Michael    
    
    
    Neelie Kroes: Openness means transparency and choice #www2012    
    
    
    Now panel discussion on "web as human right" with Tim, Gilles and Neelie #www2012    
    
    
    TimBL: Google delivers you the principal eigenvector of what the world thinks about the words you have just typed in. #www2012    
    
    
    TimBL: imagine how you wish the world to be ... and then go geek and do it! #www2012 #panel    
    
    
    I'd love to see some of those #www2012 cartoons displayed during the social dinner online! They're REALLY great!!!    
    
    
    spoiler talk at #www2012 ... now we know that one of the most compassionate users on Yahoo Answers is a bot! #LeveragingUserContent    
    
    
    Talk about using flickr photos as basis for doing ecological field research #www2012 Reminds me of the work by @cckling    
    
    
    Another one of interest to @cckling : Discovery of geographical topics on twitter #www2012    
    
    
    One of the lessons learned from determining geographic topics: penalise too large regions #www2012    
    
    
    Going to chair the session on #webmining now. Interesting papers ahead! #www2012    
    
    
    Had a very interesting session on #webmining Great presentations and quite some good ideas #www2012    
    
    
    @tomaz Have a safe trip home and let's keep in touch about content extraction...    
    
    
    +1 RT @renepickhardt love the catoons by @Bouletcorp I heared he is supposed to upload all pictures of #www2012 on http://bouletcorp.com  ...    
    
    
    Leaving Lyon after a wonderful #www2012 conference. Heading on to Lugano for a visit to IR group there incl. @giacomoinches    
    
    
    Arrived in Lugano this evening - seems a very nice town -- and unlike Lyon I understand what the people say ;-)    
    
    
    Finished my #reviews for #ECAI2012 ... kind of last minute, given they are due by tomorrow    
    
    
    Been to the IR group in Lugano today. Great people doing excellent research! Also gave a presentation on our work on Twitter and SchemEX.    
    
    
    WebSci paper on Feature-Centric Sentiment Diversification of Online
Discussions with @nnaveed @ststaab http://dl.dropbox.com/u/20411070/Publications/2012-WebSci-Naveed-GSS.pdf … #ictrobust    
    
    
    As I was asked for it: the #ECIR2010 library for language identification of short query style text http://bit.ly/LangDetect     
    
    
    Good feedback question at @convergingmedia conference: is the web a web of words or more like a stream or ambience music    
    
    
    Looking currently at Twitters API... Need to collect data for a hands-on-session on web mining    
    
    
    Leaving for my second visit to Krakow. After the IIS conference in 2009 this time for the #ictrobust meeting at Software Mind.    
    
    
    Collecting twitter data of densely connected users. Need to implement Oauth to have more requests per hour.    
    
    
    Heading towards the social dinner in Krakow ... but before Software Mind promised a surprise ... Ho ho ho #ictrobust    
    
    
    Back in Germany after the #ictrobust meeting in wonderful Krakow    
    
    
    Submitted our WS-paper on recommendations for online dating websites using split-complex numbers with @kunegis and @gerdgroener #recsys2012    
    
    
    Leaving for Milan. We'll be at San Siro tonight ... and it's not for football ;-)    
    
    
    @mattroweshow been there last night for the #mdna concert. Was a great show!    
    
    
    That one's for @renepickhardt and the #typology guys : http://xkcd.com/1068/  ;-)    
    
    
    I'm reading a text on SEO: some people still believe web search engines  employ some kind of magic to come up with relevant results...    
    
    
    Findings of @westinstitute twitter analysis session @dagstuhl: the odds of retweeting this tweet are 7.4519706    
    
    
    What a week! 1 paper accepted, 1 paper submitted, 1 paper started, more then 30 papers read ... and I made a pirate hat!    
    
    
    @kunegis problem with this weather map: it is historic data :-(    
    
    
    What are the features one has to pay attention to when buying a pair of headphones?? Any suggestion?    
    
    
    Hey fellows in Koblenz... already got wet feet? ;-)    
    
    
    Great! which path do you take? Xkcd on Good Code http://pulsene.ws/FAgE    
    
    
    The highland games in Rüsselsheim become larger every year. Funny event http://yfrog.com/ny15zifj     
    
    
    Short summary of our #wole2012 paper on finding web documents to represent knowledge base entities: http://blog.west.uni-koblenz.de/2012-09-13/finding-web-documents-to-represent-entities-from-a-knowledge-base-a-novel-retrieval-task/ … #ictrobust @WeST_Ko    
    
    
    Just saw longest boat traffic jam on the river #rhine from #koblenz to #loreley    
    
    
    Working train is just too productive. Nearly wish to have a longer way ;-)    
    
    
    Took 3 children to get that experience: paper writing with a baby on the arm last night for our #btc2012 submission :-D    
    
    
    Wrote a short summary of our #btc2012 submission for the @WeST_Ko blog. Have a look: https://blog.west.uni-koblenz.de/2012-10-20/westbtc-2012-the-lodatio-retrieval-system/ … #iswc2012 #LODatio    
    
    
    Leaving for #iswc2012 in Boston. Going to present #lodatio -- our contribution to the #btc2012 
:-) #ictrobust @WeST_Ko    
    
    
    An unbeatable advantage of travelling by plane: nobody can knock on the door to interrupt you--I managed quite some work on the flight today    
    
    
    I guess an awful lot of people are offline while travelling to #iswc2012 ... hardly got any e-mails today ;-)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Effort should go in the direction of getting agents to work together in the semantic web (@jahendler #sw2022 #iswc2012)    
    
    
    7% of the data Google crawls contains machine readable information #sw2022 #iswc2012    
    
    
    Ari: I don't know how recognizing outliers saves me from being eaten by wolves ...  but evolution got humans good at it #sw2022 #iswc2012    
    
    
    @iFromm semantic data but not necessarily RDF. Maybe I should have said machine understandable (whatever that means)    
    
    
    #sw2022 static ontologies are a blocker for the read-write web---I think: composing a vocabulary from various sources you are quite flexible    
    
    
    #sw2022 @timberners_lee will give an improvised 10 min keynote (qualified by being a speaker that does not need to be introduced) #iswc2012    
    
    
    First #sw2022 talk after the coffee break on "Why the SW should become more imprecise" #iswc2012    
    
    
    #sw2022 : nowadays semantic web is strongly biased towards precision -- we need not to forget about recall #iswc2012    
    
    
    Next: @matthimm presenting our "vision" paper at #sw2022 on "linked know how" #iswc2012    
    
    
    @vrandezo Lets translate that in Twitter language ;-)
@matthimm @tgottron @ascherpuokob @gerdgroener
http://stko.geog.ucsb.edu/sw2022/sw2022_paper7.pdf … #sw2022    
    
    
    Got to the #wole2012 workshop now after the #mit tour. Sorry to have missed the beginning :-( #iswc2012    
    
    
    Next talk mentions "LOD Russia" in the title -- funny to have a national branding for LOD #wole2012    
    
    
    A "Math ontology" ... got to get my hands on this one :-D #wole2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    Next talk on extracting discourse graphs from wikipedia -- sounds interesting! #wole2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    @gatemezing not so far. was mentioned on the slides. Maybe in the paper  (http://ceur-ws.org/Vol-906/paper1.pdf …) -- haven't looked at it yet    
    
    
    @timse7 Prinzipiell gerne -- war aber nur die erste Hälfte da, danach anderer Workshop mit weiterem eigenen Paper.    
    
    
    #ECB appears in a talk at #wole2012 finally creating the missing link between my work and the one of my wife ;-) #iswc2012    
    
    
    Wondering why the authors didn't use ESA as purely text based approach for measuring semantic relatedness of terms #wole2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    current talk on turning keyword queries into SPARQL -- Seems a wonderful extension for our #btc2012 contribution #wole2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    Had some nice and interesting discussions in the aftermath of my presentation at  #wole2012 Thanks for the feedback! #iswc2012    
    
    
    Btw. for those interested in #ESA: If you want to understand how it really works, look at our CIKM'11 paper http://dl.dropbox.com/u/20411070/Publications/2011-CIKM-Gottron-AS.pdf … #wole2012    
    
    
    This morning: #cold2012 workshop on consuming linked data. Curious to see what is coming...  #iswc2012    
    
    
    #cold2012 21 submission, 11 accepted papers    
    
    
    There will be a paper on a QB4OLAP vocabulary. Particular looking forward to this one #cold2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    Next generation of Amsterdam's fire trucks are planned to be RDF fire trucks -- Pushing out all data in RDF #cold2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    What linked data might be good for: flexibly get the relevant data in a "black swan" scenario #cold2012 #iswc2012 @semanticfire    
    
    
    It really IS a small world. Got a message from an old friend I know from Glasgow times. She happens to be in Boston in the moment :-)    
    
    
    Next talk on what can be learned from federated DBs for distributed query processing on LOD #cold2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    Claim: using dictionary encoding and duplicate removal the entire LOD requires only 800GB storage space #cold2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    current talk at #cold2012: group RDF data characteristics into terms, triples, graph ...

I wonder: why not infer also a schema? #iswc2012    
    
    
    The thought just stroke me: #LOD is definitely lifting off, if we have to consider the problem of spam! #cold2012 #iswc2012    
    
    
    @mrowebot What exactly would we have to look for? Given the examples from Tom the spam would very subtle    
    
    
    so ...  there is spam in the BTC dataset. Looking forward to see this data. Anyone already got the URL? #cold2012    
    
    
    Spam in the BTC dataset: http://bit.ly/LD-spam  #cold2012    
    
    
    Ok, just got clarified. The spam dataset is an artificial dataset based on BTC which contains injected spam #cold2012    
    
    
    #cold2012 presenter made an app using semantic technology without hiding RDF from the user -- to show them there is nothing to be scared of.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    OLAP extension to QB vocabulary -- very interesting, but I cannot read anything from the back :-( #cold2012    
    
    
    Want a sneak preview of the @WeST_Ko #btc2012 submission? 
Live-demo: http://bit.ly/lodatio 
Poster: http://bit.ly/TzPvfP 
#iswc2012    
    
    
    #iswc2012 keynote. Idea: Represent not only data but also processes on the semantic web. Requires ontologies to have verbs    
    
    
    Interesting concept of an inheritance hierarchy for activities (ontology verbs) #iswc2012 #keynote    
    
    
    Collective intelligence activity design patterns must answer four questions: what is done, who is doing it, why and how? #iswc2012 #keynote    
    
    
    Decomposition of example communities into what,who, how and why "genes" (design patterns) #iswc2012 #keynote    
    
    
    Genes for collective intelligence...makes we wonder if you can do "genetic engineering" to create new forms of coll. intelligence #iswc2012    
    
    
        
    
    
    Italian football player Cassano made it into a #iswc2012 presentation!    
    
    
    Statistics about the availability of temporal information per pay-level-domain including the relevant properties! Nice work! #iswc2012    
    
    
    . @stcsn New logo looks good!    
    
    
    Getting ready for and looking forward to the Minute Madness :-) Usually a fun event #iswc2012    
    
    
        
    
    
    @cgueret true -- but on a large scale it is still hard to individually decide how the entire group is behaving. Don't you think?    
    
    
    @cgueret sure, but if I estimate 1000 people buying something, I myself can change that number by 1 item that I buy. That is what I meant    
    
    
    Again the question about spam in semantic data using http://schema.org  #iswc2012    
    
    
    Funny answer regarding http://schema.org  spam: "At Yandex we did not observe spam, but I know Google has problems with it" #iswc2012    
    
    
    #iswc2012 poster session about to come to an end. Last chance to get a guided tour of #lodatio at our poster. http://bit.ly/lodatio     
    
    
    Recap of the poster/demo session: extremely positive feedback on the #lodatio system - and one visitor wanted to hire our students #iswc2012    
    
    
    #lodatio managed to get in the round of the three #btc2012 finalists... what a surprise ;-) #iswc2012    
    
    
    #btc2012 finalists presentation of #lodatio on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/tgottron/lodatio-presentation … #iswc2012    
    
    
    That is a number: facebook has 60 petabyte of graph data #iswc2012 #panel #bigdata    
    
    
    My analogy: Google shows you HTML docs relevant to a query. SemWeb needs a search for RDF docs. Info stays in the docs #iswc2012    
    
    
    Attending the session on Instance matching .. which seems to have started early (?!?) #iswc2012    
    
    
    . @ascherpuokob Let me know if lightning stirkes ;-) #iswc2012    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Question "Who is familiar with Hadoop?" Hands rise. "Then I don't need to explain it!" And presenter really skips slide. Good one! #iswc2012    
    
    
    Now it is @brokenthoughts on stage: SPLODGE: Systematic Generation of SPARQL Benchmark Queries for Linked Open Data #iswc2012    
    
    
    Really nice talk by @brokenthoughts -- covered all the central ideas and the clean methodology of the paper #iswc2012    
    
    
    The upcoming session features a presentation on Semantic Sentiment Analysis of Twitter. Work by @hrsaif, @halani and Yulan  #ictrobust    
    
    
    After two days without coffee: today the coffee machine @westinstitute is back -- YEAH!    
    
    
    We've got open positions for PhD scholarships @WeST_Ko https://www.uni-koblenz-landau.de/campus-koblenz/fb4/west/Jobs …    
    
    
    This week: #WWW2013 submission, prep for #ictrobust review, financial audit, seminar talk, invited talk. Hope my head stops spinning now ;-)    
    
    
    Reviewer sighing: "We had to read also this additional 90 pages document."
Response by author: "Yes, but there were many pictures in it."    
    
    
    If always wanted to know how "stable" is your research group: The Research Group Truck Number https://blog.west.uni-koblenz.de/2012-12-20/the-research-group-truck-number/ … @WeST_Ko    
    
    
    Second day of juggling JSP, RDF, HTML, Servlets, Sparql and Web services for a nice #lod demonstrator    
    
    
    How do you actually call a brunch that stretches into dinner?    
    
    
    What do you use twitter for? Survey of @arifah77 Please participate, takes 2 minutes. http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/G9TVK25    
    
    
    Anyone knows an #IR model to capture globally the pairwise relevance relations in a group of three documents?    
    
    
    @alansaid you're welcome. Interesting topic and a different aspect of influence in social media    
    
    
    Writing paper on using the web to analyze readability of texts. News and kids literature are comparably difficult to comprehend.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Website for workshop on Metrics, Analysis and Tools for Online Community Management is online: http://bit.ly/mama-workshop  #ictrobust    
    
    
    I just donated my tweets to Science! Donate your tweets today! http://tweetsforscience.org  #Tweets4Science via @tweets4sci    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Leaving for #eswc2013 in Montpellier. Looking forward to an interesting conference and meeting some of the ROBUST folks (again). #ictrobust    
    
    
        
    
    
    Arrived at #eswc2013 this morning. Attending tutorial now on analysing and visualizing linked data with R    
    
    
    Yeah! Managed to get web access!!! Let's see how long it lasts #eswc2013    
    
    
    Introduction to adjacency lists (sic) in the tutorial on semantic data management in graph dbs at #eswc2013    
    
    
    Those #eswc2013 attendees working in the context of social networks: Have a look at http://stcsn.ieee.net/call-for-participation … or directly talk to me! @stcsn    
    
    
    The #eswc2013 keynotes better be good, interesting and fascinating. Otherwise people might easily dose off in these armchairs ;-)    
    
    
    "There must be more to a SW application than using a triple store" #eswc2013 keynote by Enrico    
    
    
    Current talk at #eswc2013 mentioning a community manager -- the concept of this role is spreading #ictrobust    
    
    
        
    
    
    Seen two very interesting talks at #eswc2013: one on SPARQL query pattern detection, one on predicate synonymity. Have to read the papers!    
    
    
    Next #eswc2013 talk on logical linked data compression. Curious to see how this fits with our entropy analysis over LOD schema information.    
    
    
    @lechatpito yep: will present the results on thursday in the second linked data session, last talk #eswc2013    
    
    
        
    
    
    Second #eswc2013 keynote on "End User Semantic Web Applications" by @karger    
    
    
    ... keynote starts with the conclusion. So in case people fall asleep during the talk at least they don't miss the important part #eswc2013    
    
    
    Interesting viewpoint: "An SW application is an application whose schema is expected to change" #eswc2013 keynote    
    
    
    #eswc2013 keynote by @karger demands: more Semantic WEB and less SEMANTIC Web. Give more powerful tools to the users.    
    
    
    Talk by  @mrowebot on topical specificity of online communitiess #eswc2013 interesting for #ictrobust    
    
    
    Wonderful CF-IFF: concept frequency - inverse forum frequency. A community-topic variation of TF-IDF #eswc2013    
    
    
    Next #eswc2013 on "Nanopublications" ... reminds me of the concept of MPU (minimum publishable unit)    
    
    
    Poster of #eswc2013 demo no. 1: "A Schema-Based Retrieval System for Linked Open Data at Web-scale " online: http://dl.dropboxusercontent.com/u/20411070/Posters/2013-ESWC-Demo-Lodatio.pdf …    
    
    
    #eswc2013 keynote: How can we integrate dynamic data (from any kind of sensors) into the Linked Data Cloud?    
    
    
        
    
    
    The slides of my #eswc2013 talk on Redundancy in schema information of LOD: http://www.slideshare.net/tgottron/eswc-2013-a-systematic-investigation-of-explicit-and-implicit-schema-information-on-the-linked-open-data-cloud …    
    
    
    @lechatpito Just to follow up on our chat before: PMI might be an idea for outlier detection. It's explained in the paper I presented    
    
    
    @AxelPolleres Might be a chance to get statistical evidence and support for formulating RDFS coming out of the data.    
    
    
    Our dear @miriam_fs is "a bit confused" when handing out the best poster awards ;-) #eswc2013    
    
    
    Leaving Montpellier. Good bye to all the #eswc2013 folks!    
    
    
    Funny random context at the REVEAL negotiation meeting: whenever we come to a conclusion, people in the neighbour room clap their hands :-)    
    
    
    Looking at #ecir 2011 program. Paper on Relevance assessment via croudsourcing by @elunca - I would be curious for a preprint    
    
    
    Many thanks to @elunca for letting me take a glimpse at his upcoming #ecir paper    
    
    
    Good question: how do you define the value of a community or the value of an individual to this  community? #ictrobust    
    
    
    Started the first evaluation based on #croudsourcing today -- looking forward to the results! #mturk    
    
    
    Reading about network models, information diffusion and traffic simulation to mashup a model for the value of a community :-D    
    
    
    Gosh! Why do i always have to run to catch my train or bus these days :’(    
    
    
        
    
    
    Finalizing the preparations for the final review meeting of ROBUST @ictROBUST --looks good!    
    
    
    Now, that it is an approach to detect trustworthiness in media: http://xkcd.com/1301/  @RevealEU    
    
    
    Heading off to Southampton for ROBUST project meeting.    
    
    
    Coffee, coffee, coffee! According to our twitter analysis noone is interested in this, but that is what I feel like ;-) #microblog    
    
    
    @darcybenoit what was the talk about? Who gave it?    
    
    
    Buon compleanno Italia #italy #birthday    
    
    
    @renepickhardt good example for external #influence on #twitter trends. We should look at such #events that are easy to measure    
    
    
    Just helped my uncle to install THE internet on his 10 year old pc :-D    
    
    
    back in office after kickoff meeting for EU FP7 project ROBUST #ictrobust    
    
    
    "Bad News Travel Fast: A Content-based Analysis of Interestingness on Twitter" accepted as full paper at #websci 2011    
    
    
    "Readability and the Web" paper written with Ludger Martin accepted at ITA-11 in Wrexham, Wales. #ita11    
    
    
    So far 41 answers to survey on twitter purposes of @arifah77 Please participate/retweet the link http://www.surveymonkey.com/s/G9TVK25    
    
    
    Leaving for Trento: representing ROBUST at the User Centric Media cluster meeting #ictrobust #ucm    
    
    
    Arrived at UCM meeting. Got strategic place near power outlet, coffee and cookies ;-)    
    
    
    Do online games reflect real world behaviour better than what happens in social networks?    
    
    
    Research and Development regarding Social Networks: what will be hot trends in the next years? #ucm    
    
    
    Back in Germany. Interesting discussions at UCM meeting. Pity I had no time to explore Trento :-(    
    
    
    twitter account auf #bcmz erstellt -- für die enkel ;-)    
    
    
    Fragen per NLP aus Text generieren = inverse QA ??? #bcmz    
    
    
    @domsom musste ja wohl sein -- nach heute morgen ;-) #bcmz    
    
    
    (Session E-Learning) Information Retrieval für E-Learning auf dem #bcmz    
    
    
    #bcmz Jon Kleinberg HITS: Hubs und Authorities in Netzwerken    
    
    
    Wieviele Dokumente gibt es eigentlich im Web?Letzte mir bekannte Aussagen von 2/2007: 15 bis 30 Milliarden http://tr.im/Gc6a    
    
    
    #bcmz PDF-Folien zum Barcamp Vortrag "Wie kann man Usability im Web (automatisch) messen" http://tr.im/GcrI    
    
    
    Message from my daughter: "Easter is great!" I guess it is for the chocolate eggs ;-)    
    
    
    Just arrived at #dagstuhl for the seminar on challenges in document mining.    
    
    
    In Frankfurt macht am Samstag (5.12.) der #apple Store auf! http://tr.im/Goxg    
    
    
    getting ready for first session on challenges in document mining. #dagstuhl    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hamish Cunningham: talk on the GATE family of NLP tools/application    
    
    
    Mímir: Attaching Sparql restrictions to named entity search: find all persons of a political party having said something in news articles    
    
    
    John Carrol: bootstrapping dictionaries for cross domain sentiment analysis    
    
    
    Presented our work on content quality and retweet odds ranking at #dagstuhl    
    
    
    Steven Burrows presented ideas on data mining of simulation results (of engineering data for bridges)    
    
    
    Had coffee and cake. .. now back to session. Massi talking on using search engines for NE    
    
    
    Massimiliano Ciaramita presented Piggyback: interesting approach for NER in queries based on search result snippets    
    
    
    Next is Michael Granitzer talking about feedback methods in visual document analysis    
    
    
    Norbert Fuhr giving last talk for today: framework for optimum document clustering - will be theoretic on what is a good clustering    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tim Gollub is preparing for his demo/talk on TIRA: a research assistant for empirical evaluations    
    
    
    @giacomoinches I'm at a Dagstuhl Seminar http://www.dagstuhl.de/de/programm/kalender/semhp/?semnr=11171    
    
    
    Andreas Henrich starts the day with a talk on multi-layer ranked visual faceted search    
    
    
    LFRP shows nice visual UI for combining facetted and key word search    
    
    
        
    
    
    Alexander presented http://www.goolap.info Nice work and insights on user search behaviour in this context    
    
    
    Next talking coming up after coffee break: retrievability of documents by Leif Azzopardi    
    
    
    What is the ease of retrieving a document and how does this influence our perception of information and the world? Interesting question!    
    
    
    Gerhard Heyer gives a talk on exploratory search and a bird's eye view on document collections    
    
    
    Gerhard Heyer: Change rate of word context as sign of interestingness in classical media    
    
    
    Now Harald Reiterer: Facet Streams and Search  Tokens. Seems to focus on user interaction with IR systems    
    
    
    Very nice presentations showing how to intuitively construct complex facet queries using tangible UI    
    
    
    Program for the afternoon and evening at the dagstuhl seminar: breakout working group sessions on specific topics    
    
    
    Continuing session on sentiment analysis in the break out working group    
    
    
    minimal String Edit Distance and maximum semantic distance: digital native vs. digital naive ;-)    
    
    
    Great thing about having people from #glasgow come to #dagstuhl : they bring #whisky -- many thanks Leif!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wolf Siberski gives a talk on understanding the intention of queries on structured data    
    
    
    Benno Stein talks about semi-supervised learning and exploiting unlabelled data    
    
    
    Benno presented some intersting results regarding the analysis of constraint clustering, co-training and structural correspondance learning    
    
    
    Peter Prettenhofer now goes into the details of a cross-lingual adaptation of structural correspondance learning    
    
    
    Short coffee break, now Arjen de Vries gives a talk on Search by Strategy    
    
    
    Arjen showed a way how to marry DB and IR that also allows to configure the search mechanisms -- experts only    
    
    
    Dennis Hoppe on Challenges in Patent Retrieval an Mining    
    
    
    Social event: trip to the town of Trier    
    
    
    Working group sessions after dinner. Dealing with optimum clustering framework and cluster labels    
    
    
    Last session at #dagstuhl : wrap up and conclusions    
    
    
        
    
    
    Leif summarizes working group results on research infrastructure    
    
    
    Jon presents the results of the sentiment working group -- orally and without slides! :-)    
    
    
    Stefan gives the last talk: working group results on what one could do when being able to read a 1,000,000 books    
    
    
    Norbert Fuhr concluded a great and productive seminar. Time to say bye to #dagstuhl    
    
    
    Leaving #dagstuhl taking home nice impressions and some good ideas. Thanks to the organizers    
    
    
    Using time on train to review papers  for the #tir workshop    
    
    
    Knew there will be fun in following: RT @ecb_europa_eu: We released an improved version of our mon. pol. game Economia http://bit.ly/iZEocJ    
    
    
    Example for an interesting tweet about NOT doing something RT @ecb_europa_eu: ECB keeps interest rates unchanged http://bit.ly/jwoyfX    
    
    
    Preparing presentation for Vision 2020 meeting in Brussels next week    
    
    
    Submitted #ECIR poster: language detection for query-style texts. http://kmi.open.ac.uk/events/ecir2010/    
    
    
    @domsom interesting #ECIR workshop for evaluating @relevanzer http://www.irit.fr/CIRSE/index.html    
    
    
    Scientific analysis of twitter: "A Few Chirps About Twitter" http://tr.im/HTgh    
    
    
    Leaving for the vision2020 meeting in Brussels    
    
    
    Arrived at EC for the expert consultation meeting "Vision2020 on networked media and beyond"    
    
    
    Our workshop #DETECT on detecting and exploiting cultural diversity on the social web has finally been accepted at #CIKM 2011    
    
    
        
    
    
    @craig_macdonald these newlines in tweets really can ruin your day when parsing large datasets :-)    
    
    
    Vision2020 meeting about to end. Will have to run to still catch my plane    
    
    
    Back in Germany    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries  that was really mean towards @craig_macdonald ;-)    
    
    
    TIR 2011 accepted our paper on "A Fast and Accurate Approach for Main Content Extraction based on Character Encoding"    
    
    
    DDR workshop at #ecir2011 - interesting topic but unlucky name. See wikipedia disambiguation http://bit.ly/eJKgGY    
    
    
        
    
    
    Boys with toys: attempts to come up  with a model to describe the clicks on URLs in tweets http://is.gd/JUaS0R    
    
    
    Gotcha! A "coffee" tweet for our twitter search system :-D RT @saadkamal: morning everyone! Time to grab some coffee..    
    
    
    @saadkamal sorry the twitter search system is not online yet. But my 2 favourite test queries are "coffee" and "beer" ;-)    
    
    
    phew! CfP Deadline CIRSE extended to 20/Jan http://tinyurl.com/yb55qoz -- more time for paper :-)    
    
    
    @saadkamal it's a research prototype estimating the "interestingness" of tweets.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @renepickhardt I agree on the relevance of coffee :-)    
    
    
    Leaving for vacation -- back in 2 weeks :-)    
    
    
    Back from vacation -- straight into ACM WebSci conference    
    
    
    Attending keynote of Mike at the #altmetrics workshop #websci11    
    
    
        
    
    
    Back at the #altmetrics workshop #websci11    
    
    
        
    
    
    UCount: Community driven metrics by @cdparra #altmetrics    
    
    
    Reputation of scientists seems not to be correlated with any classical impact index #altmetrics    
    
    
    Keynote #websci11 from Jaimee Teevan on the evolution of web contents    
    
    
        
    
    
    Aligning revisitation frequency and in page change frequency gives you the interesting parts of webdocs #websci11    
    
    
    #websci11 folks: remember to cast your vote for the best poster. The ballot box is at the help desk    
    
    
    @gingdottwit there might be some spare forms at the help desk. Check with ruth  @idefixuni    
    
    
    Next presentation by @kunegis of our paper on bad news travels fast and interestingness in the world of twitter #websci11    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kwelle happy to hear you liked the #websci11 poster session. I also enjoyed all the nice work presented there.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Interesting talk on the political news propagation on Twitter. Involves notion of node importance in the social network #websci11    
    
    
    Marcel presenting "The Effect of User Features on Churn in Social Networks" at #websci11 #ictrobust    
    
    
    "The effect of user features on churn in social networks" by DERI & OU wins best paper award at #websci11 #ictrobust    
    
    
    @kunegis RT @jasonpriem: A comprehensive directory of research data repositories http://datacite.org/repolist (via @EvoMRI,  @ReaderMeter)    
    
    
    One week left to submit a paper to the #detect workshop on cultural diversity in social media http://bit.ly/k8qOcd #cikm2011    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hey! Weimars PAN-10 Workshop on uncovering plagiarism at CLEF-2010 http://pan.webis.de/    
    
    
    About to start summer academy lecture on Web Retrieval #west #koblenz    
    
    
    Just gave a lecture in a tent -- weird :-)    
    
    
        
    
    
    About to board plane to Dublin. Then on to Galway -- ROBUST meeting. #ictrobust    
    
    
    Returning from an intense and productive #ictrobust meeting. Thanks to @deri for perfect organization.    
    
    
    @renepickhardt @nnaveed what are you two up to? #curious    
    
    
    @giacomoinches bad news: got invited to google+ but have to wait for them to extend the user test :-(    
    
    
    @Orpion Kwak et.al. discovered that already before (http://bit.ly/nJ4LAv ) . We looked into what people consider interesting #websci    
    
    
    Well done folks! Paper on microblog retrieval by @nnaveed @arifah77 @kunegis and myself accepted at #cikm2011 #ictrobust    
    
    
    presenting ROBUST at the User Centric Media Cluster #ictrobust #brussels #ucm #eu #fp7    
    
    
    