Financial crisis hurting new job seekers in Japan http://www.yomiuri.co.jp/dy/business/20081111TDY04303.htm    
    
    
    US Students May Seek More Loans as Savings Dwindle http://tinyurl.com/5jl7eh    
    
    
    UK MBA programs: Why the world is queueing up to sit the MBA http://www.independent.co.uk/news/a2333055.html …    
    
    
    This is probably not delicious. http://tinyurl.com/5valks    
    
    
    FT article on Harvard LLM Program http://tinyurl.com/5o6mga    
    
    
    FT article on Georgetown LLM Program http://tinyurl.com/6cwsw5    
    
    
    Where did all the people go from the collapsed financial institutions? http://blog.linkedin.com/2010/02/18/linkedin-analytics-financial/    
    
    
    Global Banks Poised to Cut 101,000 Jobs - Bloomberg via @BloombergNow http://bloom.bg/qI0cyA     
    
    
    Refugees From Meltdown Bang on Doors of Elite MBA Institutions  http://tinyurl.com/62qkp4    
    
    
    Economic mess provides travel hits and misses http://tinyurl.com/yo7q8m/c/a/2008/11/14/TRFU13RV63.DTL    
    
    
    Skeeter Jones, Canine-at-Law http://tinyurl.com/6asotz    
    
    
    MBA examiners call in the FBI in crackdown on cheats http://business.timesonline.co.uk/tol/business/management/mba/article4962442.ece    
    
    
    Stanford MBA students Fatal crash's cause remains mystery http://tinyurl.com/5rykmx    
    
    
    Using an MBA to find the silver lining http://business.timesonline.co.uk/tol/business/management/mba/article4962408.ece    
    
    
    Anderson's new MBA curriculum http://www.anderson.ucla.edu/x28616.xml     
    
    
    The US JD Scam: Hostile Witness - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/oyHr0Z .    
    
    
    deflation http://tinyurl.com/6oefgx    
    
    
    Japan's Economy in Recession http://tinyurl.com/5ans27    
    
    
    US Record Year For Foreign Student Enrollment http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/11/17/opendoors    
    
    
    US UNDERGRAD EARLY DECISION NUMBERS UP http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/11/18/ed    
    
    
    Wall Street Journal: The Top M.B.A. Programs if You're in a Hurry http://tinyurl.com/pfvd5m    
    
    
    Top Law Schools Based On Top Lawyers http://tinyurl.com/5awkfp    
    
    
    Nice advice: The Ten Biggest Lies of B-School - Forbes http://onforb.es/nSdVul     
    
    
    CEIBS: A Chinese B-school vies for Harvard status http://management.fortune.cnn.com/2011/08/10/a-chinese-b-school-vies-for-harvard-status/ … via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    UK Grad School: 'Can't Afford to Be Too Choosy' - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/opLCnk  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Understand the Revised-GRE http://gradschool.about.com/b/2011/08/03/understand-the-revised-gre.htm?r=twitter …    
    
    
    HBS Discusses Future of the MBA http://hbswk.hbs.edu/item/6053.html    
    
    
    Duke's Cheating Problem http://buswk.co/qdEYUc     
    
    
    MBA Pay: The $3.6 Million Degree - BusinessWeek http://buswk.co/iWV9TX  via @BW    
    
    
    MBA market index http://tinyurl.com/5u4lqh    
    
    
    Forbes Report on B-Schools http://tinyurl.com/5jaobm    
    
    
    Entrepreneurs at Oxford http://tinyurl.com/5jvo7h    
    
    
    U. of Chicago bracing for budget cuts http://tinyurl.com/6mcvyv    
    
    
    reading!    
    
    
    Adam Markus: The Role of Potential Employability in the Admissions Process http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/role-of-potential-employability-in.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Human Capital Contracts: Student Loans http://tinyurl.com/632vef    
    
    
    American graduate schools accepted 11% more international applicants in 2011 than they did in 2010: http://bit.ly/ptwJpN  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Verdict is in: Legal job market tightens http://tinyurl.com/68prun    
    
    
    No more subsidized federal loans for American graduate students: http://bit.ly/mSlS17  via @AddThis    
    
    
    MIT to Open Center on ‘Mobile Learning,’ With Google’s Backing http://tinyurl.com/3kb6xj2     
    
    
    Rational Response to Plagiarism http://chronicle.com/article/Toward-a-Rational-Response-to/128611/ …    
    
    
    GMAT Write Software http://tinyurl.com/57kjpb    
    
    
    Early Gen Xers are dumb: the test scores prove it http://tiny.cc/C2GFo    
    
    
    British MBAs Feel the Jobs Chill http://tiny.cc/0JleF    
    
    
    ETS to Introduce Evaluation System for Critical Personal Attributes http://tiny.cc/Cp8Zd    
    
    
    Number of GRE test takers declines in 2008 http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/12/08/gre    
    
    
    Net Impact's Guide to Green MBA Programs 2011 http://tinyurl.com/3h63xt3     
    
    
    In Finance now? Want to be in Finance after your MBA http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/in-finance-now-want-to-be-in-finance.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: MIT Sloan MBA Essays for Fall 2012 Admission http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/mit-sloan-mba-essays-for-fall-2012.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    More College Admissions Secrets lol! http://www.thedailybeast.com/blogs-and-stories/2010-03-14/more-college-admissions-secrets/    
    
    
    ‘Graduate Admissions Guru’ (ME!) Says Stay Away from MSU
http://www.thefire.org/index.php/article/10024.html    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: UCLA Anderson MBA Essays for Fall 2012 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/ucla-anderson-mba-essays-for-fall-2011.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Citibank Offering CitiAssist Global International Loan to NYU International Students   http://tiny.cc/2d2jC    
    
    
    Don't call it a zero interest rate policy, call it a sustainable interest rate policy :)    
    
    
    The Financial Crisis and The MBA Classroom http://www.csrwire.com/News/14083.html    
    
    
    Kellogg mistakenly some dinged students that they were accepted.  http://tinyurl.com/5yagn8    
    
    
    Kellogg mistakenly TELLS dinged students that they were accepted.    
    
    
    Taking a little break before returning to ESSAY LAND...    
    
    
    Know Your Audience: Three Things You Should Know Adcom Members. http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/know-your-audience-three-things-you.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    GMAT Explained in Japanese: 河野太一の GMAT OG12解説 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/search/label/Taichi%20Kono    
    
    
    Not a good time to go into the private jet leasing business http://tinyurl.com/8wcfn6    
    
    
    Japan factory output has biggest fall on record http://tinyurl.com/7cl6hy    
    
    
    M&A is on the way.    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: MBA & OTHER GRADUATE PROGRAM RECOMMENDATION ADVICE... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/mba-other-graduate-program.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Drinking Rockstar till the sun shines.    
    
    
    HAPPY NEW YEAR! NOW GET BACK TO WORK!    
    
    
    Highest Paid CEOs with MBAs http://images.businessweek.com/slideshows/20110830/highest-paid-ceos-with-mbas …    
    
    
    WSJ Blog on MBA Essay Questions: In Search of a Perfect M.B.A. Candidate http://on.wsj.com/obxoPk     
    
    
    If you don't believe in your goals and story, no one else will!  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/09/if-you-dont-believe-in-your-goals-and.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Take the MBA Search Survey! http://surveys.marketpointsinc.com/mba10a.asp    
    
    
    Cornell suicides raise concerns across Ivies http://thedp.com/article/cornell-suicides-raise-concerns-across-ivies    
    
    
    Adam's rude MBA essay question restatements #2: For HBS setbacks,  "What are three really fucked-up situations you have had to deal with?"    
    
    
    Adam's rude MBA essay question restatements #3: For Stanford Essay 1, "So what rocks your world?"    
    
    
    Adam's rude MBA essay question restatements #4: For Stanford Essay 2, "What the fuck do you want to do? Why are you bothering us?    
    
    
    Adam's rude MBA essay question restatements #5: For any essay involving a difficult human interaction, "When did some asshole fuck with you?    
    
    
    Adam's rude MBA essay question restatements #1 edited: For HBS accomplishments, "Give us three reasons why you are the shit!"    
    
    
    Rude MBA essay Qs #6:  Generic Goals Essay (CBS, Booth), "Make us believe you actually have clue about the future and that you love us."    
    
    
    Recession May Be a Time to Go Back to School  http://tinyurl.com/7rnuoy    
    
    
    Dirty Secrets of College Admissions http://tinyurl.com/7etgmo    
    
    
    Visiting INSEAD SIngapore campus on 20 September.  Really looking forward to my first visit. Two clients admitted to Singy for Jan 2012!    
    
    
    US Congress increases and reforms student financial aid http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/03/25/congress-gives-college-ai_n_513838.html    
    
    
    MBA Poker Championship begins on Friday http://tinyurl.com/ayc4qj    
    
    
    Most popular higher education Plagiarism Detection solution & Plagiarism Perfection solution provided by same company!  http://bit.ly/ple5g6     
    
    
    Decline in number of MBA applications. Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/mOCRB1     
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Decrease in total applications, but increase in applicant quality http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/09/decrease-in-total-applications-but.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Indian students deferring foreign education plans http://tinyurl.com/726cm7    
    
    
    GRE numbers drop for 1st time in 4 years http://tinyurl.com/b8jeco    
    
    
    Dartmouth to Cut Budget/ Stanford GSB cuts 49 non-faculty jobs
http://tinyurl.com/b5tj4k    
    
    
    Stanford GSB fires 12% of non-faculty staff http://tinyurl.com/av8h4z    
    
    
    The First MBA Presidency and the Business Academy http://www.counterpunch.org/davis01222009.html    
    
    
    BusinessWeek: Loan Crisis Hits the MBA World http://tinyurl.com/bhrox9    
    
    
    Which academics are hotties and which are notties http://tinyurl.com/czrywu    
    
    
    Rumor has that Stanford GSB and Wharton will merge.  See here for details: http://tinyurl.com/2ht3po    
    
    
    Stanford suspends $1.3 billion in construction projects as endowment plunges http://tinyurl.com/ae4pv4    
    
    
    FT: Funding an MBA  http://tinyurl.com/cpwjck    
    
    
    Making an application  http://tinyurl.com/amyf8w    
    
    
    College financial aid system facing stiff test http://tinyurl.com/d89tl8    
    
    
    RPI's President's compensation includes 36 acre vacation home http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/01/26/rpi    
    
    
    Stanford Seeks Wal-Mart’s CEO Scott as Visiting Professor http://tinyurl.com/b28k78    
    
    
    Falling University Endowments http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/01/27/endowments    
    
    
    MIT SLOAN GIVES IT ALL AWAY! http://tinyurl.com/c358j9    
    
    
    Tales of Crashing Endowments Reach a Crescendo http://www.typepad.com/services/trackback/6a00e5532b60e08833010537006948970c    
    
    
    Using Foucault to Deconstruct Rankings http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/02/03/rankings    
    
    
    Register Now for Free Online Graduate Admissions Summit http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2010/04/register-now-for-free-online-graduate.html    
    
    
    BW: MBA Job Outlook Dims http://tinyurl.com/cgers3    
    
    
    New Duke Policy Removes Protections for Students Accused of Sexual Misconduct http://www.thefire.org/article/11730.html    
    
    
    Bloomberg: Advanced Economies ‘in Depression,’ Worse May Come, IMF Says http://tinyurl.com/dyaxtv    
    
    
    Recruiting Drops at Business Schools  http://tinyurl.com/bvdo9s    
    
    
    Harvard Endowment will cut staff by about 25% http://tinyurl.com/apz5m4    
    
    
    End World MBA Tour Adcom Spam Now!    
    
    
    Carnival of College Admission http://tinyurl.com/c59lcp    
    
    
    Yale: 3 more murdered in New Haven http://www.yaledailynews.com/news/city-news/2010/04/12/three-more-murdered/    
    
    
    In recession, U.S. MBA students seek backup plan http://tinyurl.com/cqenyw    
    
    
    While I was insanely busy helping clients with 1st round appls to HBS, Wharton, CBS & LBS over the weekend,  Monday is pretty chill. :)    
    
    
    Businessweek article on why it is getting harder to get into top undergrad business schools such as Ross & McCombs http://buswk.co/rd7lNq     
    
    
    Bloomberg: Harvard Narcissists With MBAs Killed Wall Street: Kevin Hassett  http://tinyurl.com/bh9kyz    
    
    
    Bloomberg: Five Reasons for Japan’s Leaders to Get Drunk: William Pesek http://tinyurl.com/eyg7r    
    
    
    Harbus: Where the HBS Learning Model Falls Short http://tinyurl.com/afqoan    
    
    
    AddThis Social Bookmark Button
Wall Street? New MBAs say they can't get there from here http://tinyurl.com/d27gpd    
    
    
    For MBA Applicants, Final-Round Blues http://tinyurl.com/cynfk5    
    
    
    New Loan Program for International Students Created at the Request of the Graduate Management Admission Council  http://tinyurl.com/bjvzzb    
    
    
    MBAs: Uncle Sam Wants You http://tinyurl.com/dc2wgy    
    
    
    Not MBA related, but with all this bad news here is something twisted and fun: http://fuckyoupenguin.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    Student Lending Analytics Blog: Cornell MBA Program (Johnson School) Sees 30% Decline in International Applicants http://tinyurl.com/d7bpjy    
    
    
    Bloomberg: Want to Be Rich? It’s About Being Rude to People http://tinyurl.com/bah3x3    
    
    
    University of California, the waitlist from hell  http://tinyurl.com/y72o4gp    
    
    
    How To Properly Escape Capture Following Your Massive (or Relatively Massive) Financial Fraud: A Dealbreaker Guide http://tinyurl.com/9mhkfl    
    
    
    Flat applications to law schools http://tinyurl.com/dfcbnz    
    
    
    Dr. Doom: 6 months to US bank nationalization http://online.wsj.com/article/SB123517380343437079.html    
    
    
    More MBA programs taking GRE  http://tinyurl.com/cjmpo6    
    
    
    NY TIMES: Cover Letters http://tinyurl.com/cj5o2e    
    
    
    Thousands of video lectures from the world's top scholars FREE! http://academicearth.org/    
    
    
    Univ. of Texas Austin Ranks #1 Party School http://www.playboy.com/articles/top-party-schools-2010-top-10/index.html    
    
    
    Why Do Only Top MBA Programs Practice Grade Non-Disclosure? http://www.freakonomics.com/2011/10/12/why-do-only-top-mba-programs-practice-grade-non-disclosure/ … via @freakonomics    
    
    
    US Gov't Report Sees Increase In Campus Violence http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/04/16/govt-report-sees-increase_n_540699.html    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Why Choose Columbia Business School   #WhyCBS http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zQzdr1MFVFw&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    http://studentloanjustice.org/    
    
    
    Interest in business schools grows http://thedartmouth.com/2009/02/26/news/business/    
    
    
    Squeezed Out in India, Students Turn to United States Ivy League  for Undergraduate: http://nyti.ms/q1La7a     
    
    
    The Contrarian MBA Rankings of the Economist: Tuck is #1 http://www.economist.com/whichmba/full-time-mba-ranking …    
    
    
    Business education: Trouble in the middle | The Economist http://www.economist.com/node/21532269  via @theeconomist    
    
    
    MBA applicants in banking: Don't apologize for what you do, where you work, or what you want to do in the future http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/to-mba-applicants-in-financial-sector.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: MIT Sloan LGO Essay Questions for Fall 2012 Admissions http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/mit-sloan-lgo-essay-questions-for-fall.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Glad hard part of MBA R1 App. season is over.  Now can get back to blog writing. Maybe I will rediscover a normal sleeping pattern?    
    
    
    B-schools are in a 'green' building race http://tinyurl.com/daxnew    
    
    
    On April 28th at 9pm PST, I will be presenting a webinar titled "MBA Reapplication for Success." See http://www.aigac.org/summit/2010.    
    
    
    MBA: the letters that spell financial ruin http://tinyurl.com/b8sfn7    
    
    
    What Are the Odds of a Depression? http://www.hoover.org/pubaffairs/dailyreport/archive/40705647.html    
    
    
    My post on HBS MBA Application Interviews is up! http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/hbs-mba-application-interviews.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Wharton to be using behavoral questions again this year http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/wharton-to-be-using-behavoral-questions.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    A good argument for selecting alumni interviews?: Are we less likely to trust non-native speakers? http://post.ly/3gCOl     
    
    
    What English sounds like to those who don't speak it: http://post.ly/F5UU     
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Oh Joy! UC Berkeley Haas MBA Essays for Fall 2012 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/oh-joy-uc-berkeley-haas-mba-essays-for.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Stanford's budget cuts deepen http://tinyurl.com/cwnumb    
    
    
    Wharton MBA Interview Chat: No alumni interviews!  Will be using a number of behavioral questions  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/wharton-mba-interview-chat-10262011.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Three clients from three different countries invited for HBS interviews so far!    
    
    
    London Banking Jobs May Fall to 1998 Levels - Bloomberg http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2011-10-26/london-banking-jobs-may-decline-to-the-lowest-level-in-a-decade-cebr-says.html … via @BloombergNews    
    
    
    Who taught them greed is good? http://tinyurl.com/d5aanl    
    
    
    Bank of America withdraws job offers to foreign MBAs http://tinyurl.com/dm2ryh    
    
    
    Depression Dynamic Ensues as Markets Revisit 1930s http://tinyurl.com/denjdw    
    
    
    Revealed – the capitalist network that runs the world - physics-math - 19 October 2011 - New Scientist: http://bit.ly/sqjkQl  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Great list of potential employers: same link as last tweet - 19 October 2011 - New Scientist: http://bit.ly/sqjkQl  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Kellogg MBA Admission Interviews http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/10/kellogg-mba-admission-interviews.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Take the MBA Search Survey! http://tinyurl.com/dkegyz    
    
    
    Big Law to 2009 Graduates: See you in 2010! http://tinyurl.com/cmoqeg    
    
    
    Grade Inflation Seen Rising http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/03/12/grades    
    
    
    If it sounds too good to be true, it is.    
    
    
    INSEAD COOLNESS http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OwlQJ41Ano0    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Chicago Booth MBA  Interviews http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/11/chicago-booth-mba-interviews.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Stanford Institute for Innovation in Developing Economies receives $150 million gift http://www.stanford.edu/group/mba/blog/2011/11/stanford_launches_institute_to.html …    
    
    
    6 Booth invites, 5 CBS invites, 5 Wharton invites, and 3 INSEAD invites for clients worldwide! Hope more to follow!    
    
    
    Japan also has annoying helicopter parents hovering over university students http://www.yomiuri.co.jp/dy/features/language/T111031001854.htm …    
    
    
    View: Help Students Run the Numbers on Higher Education - Bloomberg http://bloom.bg/vHlVTv  via @BloombergView    
    
    
    So Wharton Adcom eliminates alumni interviews and then has insufficient hub interviews for international applicants. WTF!    
    
    
    Still waiting to see an actual Wharton R1 Interview report. Nothing on GMAT CLUB, ACCEPTED, OR CLEAR ADMIT YET.  Soon hopefully.    
    
    
    International graduate enrollments show 8% increase in US, biggest increase since 2006.  Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/rXPHB3  via @AddThis    
    
    
    2011 endowment returns near pre-recession levels | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/s6kZlm  via @AddThis    
    
    
    I commented on MBA Admissions 2.0: Technology Makes Inroads - Businessweek http://buswk.co/s1NTHE     
    
    
    European B-Schools Thrive in Down Times http://tinyurl.com/camjud    
    
    
    Is It Time to Retrain B-Schools? http://tinyurl.com/dzyfah    
    
    
    Why MBA bashing is unfair http://tinyurl.com/cp4bou    
    
    
    No Wharton 2011 applicant interview reports on clear admit, accepted, or GMAT Club yet.    
    
    
    My 2nd annual rant against Wharton Adcom. http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/11/wharton-has-insufficient-hub-interviews.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    2 Suicides at MIT Prompt Review of Student Life | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/vSfBPU  via @AddThis    
    
    
    The first public Wharton 2011 Interview Report is now up on the Clear Admit Wiki See http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/11/first-public-wharton-2011-interview.html …    
    
    
    Reminder: Take the MBA Search Survey! http://tinyurl.com/dkegyz    
    
    
    BBC: Business schools face test of faith http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/business/7941385.stm    
    
    
    Executive M.B.A. Programs Bulk Up Overseas http://tinyurl.com/c38dou    
    
    
    Survey on applicant B-School Decisions http://tinyurl.com/d6uowh    
    
    
    Three clients admitted so far to CBS! Congratulations to them all.    
    
    
    Homework and Jacuzzis as Dorms Move to McMansions in California: http://nyti.ms/uAxyoQ     
    
    
    Countries With the Most Students Studying in the United States http://chronicle.com/article/Interactive-Map-Countries/129702/ …    
    
    
    International Enrollments at U.S. Colleges Grow but Still Rely on China http://chronicle.com/article/International-Enrollments-at/129747/ …    
    
    
    Police shoot armed suspect at Haas School: http://bit.ly/sQoRFz  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Nomura starts European jobs cull -sources http://reut.rs/vWUVsG  via @reuters    
    
    
    Citigroup to Cut at Least 3,000 Jobs: http://nyti.ms/tE5dH3     
    
    
    Great article: Indian & Chinese MBA Applicants Face Much Higher Rejection Rates http://shar.es/ogE2f     
    
    
    Haas Japan Trip Party was a blast.  Just hope my head does not hurt in the morning!    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/edu    
    
    
    MBAs looking for work, BW's new feature, "The Hunt" http://tinyurl.com/cwla4v    
    
    
    Conde Nast Portfolio: What they Used to Teach You at Stanford Business School http://tinyurl.com/dy6daj    
    
    
    Degree of Uncertainty, MBAs Finding New Opportunities http://tinyurl.com/cfb22k    
    
    
    Wall Street Journal: Americans doing MBAs in Europe
http://online.wsj.com/article/SB123731998568560603.html    
    
    
    The Man Who Gutted the Ivy League http://tinyurl.com/d8sw5o    
    
    
    EconTalk: Taleb on the Financial Crisis http://tinyurl.com/ckjp9h    
    
    
    At Haas, they have a special way of counting words. My latest rant on stupid customer unfriendly admissions processes:  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/12/haas-mba-fall-2012-online-applications.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Eurozone's Next Problem: Foreign Investor Asset Liquidation, Could Hit $2T - Forbes http://onforb.es/tzNQUa     
    
    
    Jitters Over New GMAT http://on.wsj.com/udU1aQ  via @WSJ    
    
    
    ECONOMIST: Next Generation GMAT is coming! http://tinyurl.com/ddqpgy    
    
    
    WHARTON AND COLUMBIA BUSINESS SCHOOL TO MERGE http://tinyurl.com/d3n4g6    
    
    
    On the way to the INSEAD adcom event    
    
    
    At INSEAD event    
    
    
    Henrich Greve.  How Innovations Spread.  Singapore campus.    
    
    
    Explains case study    
    
    
    mini lecture o    
    
    
    Lecturing on what is a case.    
    
    
    Section 60    
    
    
    Q&    
    
    
    Lecture on innnovation    
    
    
    In taxi going to Chicago worldwide Tokyo event.  Beer with the Boothies!    
    
    
    Chicago Worldwide Tokyo was a blast.    
    
    
    Harvard Goes Web-Only With Course Catalog, Handbooks http://chronicle.com/wiredcampus/index.php?id=3694&utm_source=wc&utm_medium=en    
    
    
    Fall 2009 Client Results and Testimonials Updated http://adammarkus.com/results.html#FALL_2009_Client_Results_and_Testimonials    
    
    
    This One Sentence Sums Up Every 2012 Stock Market Outlook We've Read So Far http://www.businessinsider.com/nomuras-2012-equity-outlook-2011-12?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=moneygame … via @themoneygame    
    
    
    Cheating Goes Global as Essay Mills Multiply http://chronicle.com/free/v55/i28/28a00102.htm#cheating    
    
    
    Financial Aid Directors: In Their Own Words http://www.typepad.com/services/trackback/6a00e5532b60e0883301156fedb6be970b    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to CBS, Kellogg, and Stanford! More to follow!    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to Booth and INSEAD! More to follow!    
    
    
    Foreign Applications to U.S. Graduate Schools Slow (up 4%)   http://online.wsj.com/article/SB123906554985795469.html    
    
    
    Cornell Gets $350 Million Gift for Bid for NYC Science Campus. Beats Stanford! http://nyti.ms/t4xcDV     
    
    
    Wharton School Announces Launch of Custom Loan Program for International MBA Students http://tinyurl.com/d66slf    
    
    
    Yale Graduate School of Arts and Sciences more selective for Fall 2009 admission http://www.yaledailynews.com/articles/view/28584    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to HBS, Tuck, and CBS. More to follow!    
    
    
    Planned MIT Courses May Advance Front on Elite Open Education | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/vvqfxF  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Cornell and Technion's win in New York competition reflects desire to grow urban ties | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/seockp  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to Wharton!    
    
    
    The New International Economic Disorder - Mohamed A. El-Erian - Project Syndicate http://www.project-syndicate.org/commentary/elerian12/English … via @ProSyn #oped    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: The 2012  MBA Admission Season So Far http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/12/2012-mba-admission-season-so-far.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The Baseline Scenario http://baselinescenario.com/    
    
    
    NY TIMES: Crisis Altering Wall St. As Stars Begin to Scatter http://tinyurl.com/cy32e5    
    
    
    Time on Facebook Costs Students High Grades, Study Finds http://tinyurl.com/cw25g2    
    
    
    Patterns in Academic Persecution 
http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/04/14/rescue    
    
    
    Still amazed by the fact that I saw the Emperor and Empress of Japan drive past my apartment building this afternoon.    
    
    
    SLA Flash Survey Confirms Difficulty of Finding Private Loans For International Students http://tinyurl.com/d6gpl4    
    
    
    US News and World Report "Top 30" 2009 MBA Rankings: "Early Edition"  http://tinyurl.com/dy5cvn    
    
    
    UCB Campus helps graduating students cope with bleak job market http://tinyurl.com/cte5oy    
    
    
    How To Fix Business Schools http://tinyurl.com/clprva    
    
    
    Party School Rankings! Will not be suggesting clients use these.  http://tinyurl.com/dk4zuo    
    
    
    Why there will be very few non-native English speakers at Cambridge Judge: http://www.jbs.cam.ac.uk/mba/apply/requirements.html    
    
    
    Updated client results: http://adammarkus.com/results.html.  More to come!    
    
    
    With Jobs Tight, M.B.A.s Head for Home http://online.wsj.com/article/SB124026550135236597.html    
    
    
    My first blog post of 2012:  A graduate admissions consultant with 10 years of ... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/01/graduate-admissions-consultant-with-10.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Editing a 48 minute transcript is a real nightmare!    
    
    
    CBS Essays for 2011 up: The Elevator Pitch & the Speed Date http://bit.ly/bhpath    
    
    
    BW Changing MBA application article ( http://tiny.cc/s1p7k ) looks increasingly wrong as UCLA makes required audio/video essay optional.    
    
    
    MBA apps becoming shorter: UCLA and Columbia now shorter word count than HBS and Stanford.    
    
    
    Deans of Indian origin proliferate at top U.S. business schools | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/AEzJ8i  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Kindle bombs at B-schools http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/content/jun2010/bs20100610_200335.htm    
    
    
    Wal-Mart U. http://chronicle.com/article/Is-Wal-Mart-U-a-Good/65933/?sid=at&utm_source=at&utm_medium=en    
    
    
    Woman with MBA makes dog-running her business http://www.statesman.com/news/content/news/stories/local/04/27/0427dogrunner.html    
    
    
    Today's MBA grads create their own jobs by launching firms  http://www.usatoday.com/money/smallbusiness/2009-04-26-small-business-mbas_N.htm    
    
    
    Univ. of Georgia Marketing Professor kills 3 http://chronicle.com/news/article/6381/u-of-georgia-professor-sought-in-shooting-deaths-of-3    
    
    
    U.S. News Is Looking Into Possible Errors in 2010 Law School Rankings http://taxprof.typepad.com/taxprof_blog/2009/04/us-is-looking-.html    
    
    
    So You Want to Be a Professor  http://online.wsj.com/article/SB124054131801151501.html    
    
    
    UCLA LLM for new JDs: NO JOB, GET AN LLM! http://www.law.ucla.edu/home/News/Detail.aspx?recordid=2183    
    
    
    How much $ do US professors make? See http://chronicle.com/article/Chart-Average-Faculty/64500/    
    
    
    BusinessWeek: India's MBAs Face Dismal Job Market http://tinyurl.com/cq9pbo    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Adam's Global Top MBA Rankings 2012 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/01/adams-global-top-mba-rankings-2012.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Moody's Probes Colleges on Cash  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/06/16/moodys    
    
    
    UCLA MBA Applicants Rejected for Plagiarism http://buswk.co/wBL5Ur     
    
    
    My R2 clients have received invites from HBS, Wharton, Haas, Booth, UNC, and Georgetown. More to follow!    
    
    
    UCLA MBA Applicants Rejected for Plagiarism Totals 52 http://buswk.co/xNQt2Y     
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients accepted to MIT Sloan R1!    
    
    
    70% used UCLA audio Q: http://tinyurl.com/c8c4tq    
    
    
    Application processing at Harvard College http://tinyurl.com/ccm6e5    
    
    
    Kellogg to shrink two-year MBA program and increase 1 year program http://management.fortune.cnn.com/2012/02/06/northwestern-kellogg-to-shrink-two-year-mba-program/ … via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    Kellogg Overhaul Will Shrink MBA, Revise Curriculum http://buswk.co/x44iZj     
    
    
    R2 interview invite update: 3 clients invited to HBS and 3 invited to Booth. More to follow!    
    
    
    Law Schools acting pathetic in response to the lousy job market for lawyers: http://www.nytimes.com/2010/06/22/business/22law.html?hp    
    
    
    Chicago Man Rescuing Yale Business Ranking Prompts Anxiety - Businessweek http://buswk.co/xb5C6i  via @BW    
    
    
    Global Study Opportunities and GMAT Volume Expanding Worldwide http://www.marketwatch.com/story/global-study-opportunities-and-gmat-volume-expanding-worldwide-2012-02-15 …    
    
    
    At HBS Tokyo event. Waiting.    
    
    
    The most inefficient registration processes ever.  Logistics?    
    
    
    Waiting.    
    
    
    What is it you plan to do with your one wild and precious life? slides of HBS alumni    
    
    
    Facebook is too slow. Will blog later    
    
    
    Tokyo HBS Event presenter Andrew Erlich, NOT AN ADCOM (says he interviewed people): See http://bit.ly/bcyyQG    
    
    
    Japanese candidates: While HBS interviews maybe conducted by alumni, no one in Japan has been offered that option for a number of years.    
    
    
    Andrew mentioned that interviews could be conducted by alumni interviewers, as well as admissions (campus and hub).    
    
    
    However this interview information was general and not specific to Japan.    
    
    
    HBS does have a "small alumni interviewing network." See http://www.hbs.edu/mba/admissions/interview.html. I think these must be rare.    
    
    
    HBS TOKYO EVENT REPORT: http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2010/06/hbs-mba-admissions-tokyo-event-report.html    
    
    
    INSIDE HIGHER ED: 'The Student Loan Scam'  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/05/05/collinge    
    
    
    The new GMAT is coming in 2012 http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/content/jun2010/bs20100624_048037.htm    
    
    
    Another article on the new GMAT http://www.usatoday.com/news/education/2010-06-25-IHE-GMAT-changes25_ST_N.htm    
    
    
    Finding Applicants Who Plagiarize their Admissions Applications http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/06/23/essays    
    
    
    When Capitalism Meets Cannabis: On "legal marijuana" business http://www.nytimes.com/2010/06/27/business/27pot.html?pagewanted=1&src=busln    
    
    
    See previous tweet. Adam dares anyone to have MBA goals that involve legal marijuana in California, especially for UCLA, Haas and Stanford.    
    
    
    GMAC news on the new GMAT: http://gmac.mediaroom.com/index.php?s=67    
    
    
    IESE and MBS invade the US: http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/content/jun2010/bs20100617_473655.htm
Good luck!    
    
    
    Wall Street Journal on new GMAT http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748703615104575329202059488756.html    
    
    
    Study: Loan and scholarship recipients give less to alma mater | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/wWGfGI  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients invited to MIT Sloan interviews!    
    
    
    A total of 8 clients invited for Wharton R2!    
    
    
    Threatened Goldman Japan workers unionize | The Japan Times Online: http://bit.ly/AfQ2NW  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Accused spy for Russia tried to recruit fellow CBS MBAs http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/07/01/cynthia-murphy-accused-ru_n_631995.html    
    
    
    Harvard Business School? You'll Go Through Her First http://on.wsj.com/yNa6FK  via @WSJ    
    
    
    "The news this week about the MBA job outlook was once again overwhelmingly positive." http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2012-03-01/mba-jobs-outlook-cloudy-at-best …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: GRADUATE ADMISSIONS IS A LONELY ZERO SUM GAME http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/03/graduate-admissions-is-lonely-zero-sum.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Turnitin Partners with ProQuest to Aid Researchers | Education News http://shar.es/p1zKG     
    
    
    Adam is looking for a good German language teacher in Tokyo.  Write me at adammarkus@gmail.com if you know one.    
    
    
    Donald Trump calls Columbia U.'s President a total moron. lol  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/07/07/qt#231746    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to NYU and Michigan MBA programs!    
    
    
    GRE: For Institutions: GRE Comparison Tool: http://www.ets.org/gre/institutions/about/mba/comparison_tool …    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to Harvard's LL.M., Kellogg MBA, and MIchigan MBA!    
    
    
    Wall Street Is Hiring Again http://nymag.com/daily/intel/2010/07/wall_street_is_hiring_again.html    
    
    
    Take GMAT before 2012 http://bit.ly/d5do07    
    
    
    Study Finds Foreign Enrollments in US Slowing http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/07/09/foreign    
    
    
    Congratulations to my clients admitted to the Chicago Booth, Darden, and Stanford GSB MBA programs!    
    
    
    I worked with 5 LL.M. clients this year including my !st admitted to Yale.  1 or more admitted to Chicago, Columbia, Cornell, PENN & UCLA.    
    
    
    BBC News - Revealing Japan's low-tech belly http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/10543126    
    
    
    National Association for College Admission Counseling suggests SAT prep has a small, but significant impact http://tiny.cc/6byc7    
    
    
    Study: No Link Between Social-Networking Sites and Academic Performance http://chronicle.com/blogPost/Study-Finds-No-Link-Between/25541/    
    
    
    A hierarchy of failure worth following http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2010/07/a-hierarchy-of-failure.html    
    
    
    Academic fraud in China http://www.economist.com/blogs/asiaview/2010/07/academic_fraud_china    
    
    
    Policing Plagiarism Abroad  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/07/27/china    
    
    
    The new dean of Stanford's Graduate School of Business is Garth Saloner http://tinyurl.com/l28gs9    
    
    
    Wonder How Prospective MBAs Are Thinking About Student Loans? 
http://www.typepad.com/services/trackback/6a00e5532b60e0883301156fb2d267970c    
    
    
    In Global Recession, Global Ed Still Growing http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/05/29/international    
    
    
    Japan's Aoyama Gakuin Univ. uses iPhone to keep tab of students http://bit.ly/JMS5k    
    
    
    Job losses put squeeze on students in Silicon Valley http://tinyurl.com/nbf9vj    
    
    
    India's new MBA politicians http://tinyurl.com/mhxsjm    
    
    
    Shocking! Not! Corrupt admissions practices at the University of Illinois http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/06/01/illinois    
    
    
    Brookings Institution: Future of Student Financial Aid http://www.typepad.com/services/trackback/6a00e5532b60e08833011570b4d55d970b    
    
    
    Plagiarism Lines Blur for Students in Digital Age http://tinyurl.com/28yla9n    
    
    
    Undercover Investigation Finds Widespread Deception in Marketing by For-Profit Colleges http://tinyurl.com/2aqjuns    
    
    
    University of California Online Course Pilot Program http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/08/03/california    
    
    
    More unethical recruiting at for-profit colleges in US http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/08/03/gao    
    
    
    Shock??? Harvard Business School Won't Open Asian Campuses  http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748704905004575404960728487290.html    
    
    
    The number of GMATs taken in Asia last year was 34,449, compared with 21,376 in North America. See previous tweet for link.    
    
    
    Privatized Pathways for Foreign Students to US Colleges http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2010/08/04/pathways    
    
    
    FORBES: Jobs For New MBAs Are Back--But They're Different http://tinyurl.com/259jets    
    
    
    Harvard Study Suggests Twitter Users Are Self-Obsessed, Says Harvard's Own Tweet http://tinyurl.com/oo6pgd    
    
    
    More Americans Set Sights on M.B.A.'s in Asia http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052748703545604575407764037805500.html    
    
    
    A voluntary ethics oath at HBS that nearly 20% of the class take   http://bit.ly/EmBft    
    
    
    Re previous tweet: What about the other 80%?    
    
    
    Stanford Business School Partners With Star One Credit Union for Private Loans for International & US Students http://tinyurl.com/ort75x    
    
    
    10 Colleges NOT Worth Their Tuition http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/07/26/colleges-not-worth-their_n_659281.html#s120597    
    
    
    USC School of Engineering appears to have manipulated its US News Grad School Ranking http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/06/08/usc    
    
    
    Bloomberg: Global Investment Banks to Deepen Staff Cuts in Japan http://tinyurl.com/38dm9cn    
    
    
    Bill Gates Predicts Technology Will Make 'Place-Based' Colleges Less Important in 5 Years http://tinyurl.com/352xcoc    
    
    
    Colleges Extend Conditional Admissions to Pull In More International Students http://tinyurl.com/3aky2k2    
    
    
    Family looks for answers after son, a Chicago Booth MBA student, killed by Chicago cab http://tinyurl.com/29jbuns    
    
    
    Business School Applications Sputter http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/content/aug2010/bs20100812_392560.htm    
    
    
    No further tweets till 6/23    
    
    
    I finally finished my insanely long analysis of the HBS essays for the Class of 2015.  http://adam-markus.blogspot.jp/2012/06/hbs-admissions-essays-for-class-of-2015.html …    
    
    
    Done with my initial stab at the HBS Post Interview Reflection http://adam-markus.blogspot.jp/2012/06/hbs-mba-post-interview-reflection.html … as well as my post on interviews http://adam-markus.blogspot.jp/2012/06/hbs-admissions-interviews-for-class-of.html …    
    
    
    Someone should teach MBA admissions offices a course on the role of clear communication and the effective implementation of change.    
    
    
    HBS has now clarified the Post Interview Reflection. http://www.hbs.edu/mba/admissions/blog.html#post-2012-06-29 …. Unlimited length email-like thing, not a 400 word essay.    
    
    
    Financial Giants Are Moving Jobs Off Wall Street http://nyti.ms/QQJNHK     
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: My 2011-2012 Admissions Season in Retrospect http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/07/my-2011-2012-admissions-season-in.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    MBA Application Numbers Reach "Turning Point": App numbers going down overall http://tinyurl.com/2ul78fj    
    
    
    MBA Heavy Round One Volume Expected-  http://poetsandquants.com/2012/06/21/heavy-round-one-volume-expected/ … - I believe it completely!    
    
    
    Modernizing the Harvard MBA program - http://Boston.com  http://articles.boston.com/2012-07-15/business/32664293_1_innovation-center-harvard-business-school-associate-dean … via @ArchiveDigger    
    
    
    At CBS Tokyo event.    
    
    
    Mary Miller.    
    
    
    Prepare you for the changing world    
    
    
    Connecting theory to practice.  We have practitioners as well as researchers.  You learn from actual professioanals    
    
    
    Prepare for lifetime. Not just first post MBA job.    
    
    
    Global network.  1/3 international students. Lifetime network.    
    
    
    NYC    
    
    
    Faculty examples. Bringing real world into the classroom.    
    
    
    Differences. First year core. Option to wave out of classes.    
    
    
    2nd year flexible.    
    
    
    130 electives    Responsive to changes In the market.    
    
    
    PSi.  
Master classes. 
Identified as curricular innovations.    
    
    
    Can be a 2y peer advisor for psi.    
    
    
    Master classes.  Real live case. Not a hbs case!!    
    
    
    Electives outside CBS    
    
    
    No major required. 14 areas of focus.    
    
    
    Student clubs.  Very important.  100 clubs.    
    
    
    Career management center.  Advising. Coaching.  Execs in residence. Support you to manage career for lifetime    
    
    
    Network.  39k alumni.    
    
    
    Application    
    
    
    Look at80percent range. 
GPA. Need to see that you can succeed    
    
    
    Professional promise.  Resume. Recs.  Esssay 1.  Iview.    
    
    
    Explain if you cannot get a supervisor rec.  Do not get rec from someone who does not know you.    
    
    
    Essays. Chance to get to know you. Make it personal. Nothing generic please.  Tell me about you.    
    
    
    Let your passion come out. If don't know what you are going to do say that.    
    
    
    Personal characteristics.  Looking for participants not spectators.  I want peps who will get involved.    
    
    
    Personal characteristics. Test yourself in a safe environment.    
    
    
    If alll you do is work. You are boring and no one wants bores.    
    
    
    ED.   Bla bla. Standard line. Rd is 4/13!    
    
    
    You can apply rd anytime.    
    
    
    13 alumni presented themselves.    
    
    
    14!    
    
    
    2010 class profile much less finance peps.  Data out soon.  More entrpteneurial and social enterprise focus. No jobs in PE.    
    
    
    Mentioned elevator pitch in context of business plan competition.    
    
    
    Business plan comp levels. See on CBS YouTube site.    
    
    
    CBS has no international student no cosign loan. Only merit fellowships.  International financial needbased scholarships.    
    
    
    I asked what has changed since Meehan left.  A lot!  Was the answer. The new personality q reflects this change.    
    
    
    Curiously, Mary's face lit up and she smiled when I asked her this question. I guess the rest of the team is happy Meehan is gone.    
    
    
    End of my CBS tweetcast.    
    
    
    Which MBA program's application essay is most like a t-back? http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/07/brevity-is-soul-of-mba-application-in.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Yale Law to launch Ph.D. program for aspiring law professors | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/QCft6i     
    
    
    An audio interview with me on CareerEdge Japan: http://www.careeredgejapan.com/spotlight-interviews-audio--video.html …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Round1? Round 2? Apply when you are ready! http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/07/round1-round-2-apply-when-you-are-ready.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    New book on legal education and its discontents | Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/OmMOh5     
    
    
    The Economist's critique of The Jack Welch MBA http://bit.ly/KhI3l    
    
    
    The creative route to an MBA - http://FT.com  - Business Education http://on.ft.com/P9b4BU     
    
    
    North Park University encourages seminary students to pursue dual degrees | Inside Higher Ed: http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2012/08/07/north-park-university-encourages-seminary-students-pursue-dual-degrees#.UCDUMiH3Gsg.twitter …    
    
    
    STANFORD GSB Adcom: Don't worry about GMAT Integrated Reasoning http://www.stanford.edu/group/mba/blog/2012/08/why_you_shouldnt_worry_about_g.html …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Wharton MBA Essay Questions for Class of 2015 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/08/wharton-mba-essay-questions-for-class.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Wharton Interviews for the Class of 2015 http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/08/wharton-interviews-for-class-of-2015.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Emory misreported admissions data for more than a decade | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2012/08/20/emory-misreported-admissions-data-more-decade#.UDH26Fgfzmo.twitter …    
    
    
    I heard about this as a possibility a while ago, still surprising: UCLA's MBA Program Wants To Give Up State Funds http://n.pr/Ptc0Wy     
    
    
    MBA ROI CALCULATOR http://www.businessweek.com/interactive_reports/mba_roi_2011.html    
    
    
    Monex to launch ‘stock robot fund’ http://bit.ly/164bsx    
    
    
    Adam Markus:  Q&A with IMD's Associate Director of MBA Admissions... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/q-with-imds-associate-director-of-mba.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Dartmouth Tuck MBA Essay Questions for Academic Ye... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/dartmouth-tuck-mba-essay-questions-for.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Harvard Law School LL.M. Essay Questions for Fall 2013  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/harvard-law-school-llm-essay-questions.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Columbia Business School MBA Application Interviews. http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/columbia-business-school-mba_7.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Entrepreneurship as Disease http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2010/09/entrepreneurship_as_disease.html    
    
    
    NYU can refuse CPA's MBA http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/blogs/mba_admissions/archives/2010/09/nyus_rejection_of_cpas_mba_upheld.html    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: London Business School Fall 2013 MBA Application E... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/london-business-school-fall-2013-mba.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Chicago Booth 2012-2013 MBA Application Essays http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/chicago-booth-2012-2013-mba-application.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: MIT Sloan MBA Essays for Fall 2013 Admission http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/09/mit-sloan-mba-essays-for-fall-2013.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    A totally new version of my .com site has launched. http://www.adammarkus.com/     
    
    
    Business education: Europe is no longer the place to be | The Economist http://econ.st/Wl0hLf     
    
    
    NYU announces changes to its law school curriculum | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2012/10/18/nyu-announces-changes-its-law-school-curriculum#.UH_qxq37Juc.twitter …    
    
    
    Obama's New 'Pay as You Earn' Plan a Windfall for MBAs http://buswk.co/PLspbf  via @BW    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Wharton Group Interview Questions Now Made Public http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2012/11/wharton-group-interview-questions-now.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Exchange students live American nightmare http://bit.ly/Mk72b    
    
    
    Post MBA goals alert: Monitor Company files for Chapter 11; Deloitte to buy assets http://reut.rs/XlBjhJ  via @reuters    
    
    
    Busting the College Reputations http://bit.ly/itKMo    
    
    
    SEE THE ADMISSIONS BLOG CARNIVAL! http://bit.ly/38Odg    
    
    
    A MUST READ Admissions Director Q&A with MIT Sloan’s Rod Garcia  http://tinyurl.com/m7g642    
    
    
    University of California: Stop the new UC logo http://www.change.org/petitions/university-of-california-stop-the-new-uc-logo?share_id=KbIHLQbLJE&utm_campaign=action_box&utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=share_petition&utm_source=share_petition&utm_medium=twitter … via @change    
    
    
    FIRE's The State of Free Speech on Campus’ Series Exposes Repressive Policies at America's Top 25 Universities http://tinyurl.com/nqn4dx    
    
    
    REGISTER FOR CHICAGO & COLUMBIA MBA ADMISSIONS EVENTS NOW    
    
    
    Change in Repeat Policy for the TOEFL iBT® test: http://www.ets.org/toefl/important_update/ibt_repeat_policy …    
    
    
    CHICAGO BOOTH and MIT SLOAN both have their information sessions on 8/27 in Tokyo.    
    
    
    Victory for Freedom of Speech at Stanford: Student Graduates Despite Ed School Efforts to Revoke Admission http://tinyurl.com/m7t4ep    
    
    
    Great video on grade inflation at Harvard and other Ivy League Schools http://tinyurl.com/2785lxe    
    
    
    Vote for Kangaroo Mask #10 http://bit.ly/D8Jf6    
    
    
    Tulane sent incorrect information to 'U.S. News' for MBA  rankings | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2013/01/02/tulane-sent-incorrect-information-us-news-rankings#.UOhffLEL5f0.twitter …    
    
    
    So you Want to Get a PhD in the Humanities http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=obTNwPJvOI8&feature=player_embedded    
    
    
    Lobbying Showdown Over The Future Of Student Loans http://bit.ly/3EYNnx    
    
    
    Stanford MBA Program Information Session in Tokyo
Roppongi Academy Hills 
Sunday, September 06, 2009 3:00PM - 5:00PM    
    
    
    I need help analyzing the stats and basis of calculation for b-school rankings. Interested? Email me: adammarkus@gmail.com.    
    
    
    Bucknell's admission raises questions about how many colleges are reporting false data | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2013/01/28/bucknells-admission-raises-questions-about-how-many-colleges-are-reporting-false#.UQZOWLSGsnE.twitter …    
    
    
    Adam's Global 100 Top MBA Programs http://www.adammarkus.com/adams-global-top-mba-rankings-2013/ …    
    
    
    Dozens of MBA Applicants Tossed Over Plagiarism http://buswk.co/X90P8w  via @BW    
    
    
    Columbia B-school's Glenn Hubbard: Is an MBA worth it? http://management.fortune.cnn.com/2013/02/08/glenn-hubbard-columbia/ … via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    10 Books That Help Leaders Keep Their Skills Sharp http://www.businessinsider.com/top-ten-books-every-leader-should-read-2012-12?0=warroom-contributor … via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    India outclasses US in GMAT scores - The Times of India http://timesofindia.indiatimes.com/home/education/news/India-outclasses-US-in-GMAT-scores/articleshow/18522694.cms …    
    
    
    Wharton MBA Classes Go Bi-Coastal With Video http://twb.io/WeD80T  via @InformationWeek    
    
    
    The Kellogg Love Festival: MBA Essays for Fall 2010 http://bit.ly/WjehO    
    
    
    JPMorgan No. 1 Investment Bank Amid a Flurry of New Deals http://bloom.bg/VRfG7E  via @BloombergMrkts    
    
    
    Ross to Use Team-Based Interviews for MBA Admissions http://buswk.co/YRfx4m  via @BW    
    
    
    Americans Going to China http://bit.ly/19ZVVb    
    
    
    Just put up a blog post on a very cool MBA student venture http://bit.ly/17SDvH    
    
    
    Should Entrepreneurs Get an MBA? An Inside Perspective From an MBA Entrepreneur - Forbes http://onforb.es/10zdnG5     
    
    
    I support common-sense steps to reduce gun violence: http://at.wh.gov/k9AoL  #NowIsTheTime, pic.twitter.com/cvj17qaSqE    
    
    
    Adam is now an official The MBA Tour Partner http://www.thembatour.com/partners/northamerica.shtml    
    
    
    Gov. urges all Univ. of Illinois trustees to resign http://bit.ly/x286c    
    
    
    Carnival of College Admission New Edition http://bit.ly/oKsVJ    
    
    
    Jack Welch's Health Woes Delay Classes for New Online M.B.A. Program http://tinyurl.com/ng99pb    
    
    
    CAN YOU SAY OVERSTATED: Pablo Triana, The Coming B-School Collapse http://bit.ly/20rXqN    
    
    
    An interesting perspective on the MBA Ethics Oath http://bit.ly/4jEQrY    
    
    
    Fill out AIGAC's #MBA Search Survey by May 15 for a chance to win $100! ▸http://j.mp/AIGAC     
    
    
    Questions being raised about US News and World Report's School Ranking System http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/08/17/rankings    
    
    
    A Sign of the Times: Financial Aid Requests Rising http://tinyurl.com/q53jmo    
    
    
    http://blogs.wsj.com/atwork/2013/05/21/b-school-students-want-a-job-better-be-a-local/ …    
    
    
    MBA Hiring Is About to Go Into Overdrive http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-05-21/mba-hiring-about-to-go-into-overdrive … via @BW    
    
    
    First essay analysis for new MBA application season: http://www.adammarkus.com/columbia-mba-essays-for-january-and-august-2014-admission/ …    
    
    
    Stanford Essays: Same as last year! http://www.adammarkus.com/stanford-gsb-class-of-2016-essays-recs-just-announced/ …    
    
    
    25 YEARS OF PowerPoint! Zzzzzzzz.....  http://bit.ly/9tTwk    
    
    
    How to Score MBA Scholarships http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-06-05/how-to-score-mba-scholarships … via @BW    
    
    
    The Hot New MBA: Supply-Chain Management http://on.wsj.com/14xzQnh     
    
    
    Harvard MBA Graduates Get $50,000 For Taking Nonprofit Jobs http://huff.to/1b41ThJ  via @HuffPostImpact    
    
    
    At Columbia Business School Tokyo  admissions event    
    
    
    Waiting    
    
    
    There is a full house at the event.    
    
    
    More waiting    
    
    
    What makes CBS unique?  Theme. For a rapidly changing world.    
    
    
    Connecting theory to practice.    
    
    
    Faculty practical exp.    
    
    
    1/3 of faculty are practitioners    
    
    
    Core/flexibilty as a result of innovation.   Now can place into higher courses    
    
    
    Cluster system 65 diverse students.   Learning team comes out of cluster.  Cluster is also diverse.    
    
    
    Learning team is also diverse.    
    
    
    Program on social intelligence    Focus on soft skills    
    
    
    IBS. Ethics. Individual, business and society integrated into curr.    
    
    
    Master classes.  Practical exp.  On web.  Some students take 2 or 3    
    
    
    Master classes can become career opportunities    
    
    
    130 electives. Within CBS.  Plus can take 3 classses in other departments    
    
    
    Large number of areas of focus but optional. No majors on degree    
    
    
    Not a handholding kind of program.  Looking for students who are going to take initiative.    
    
    
    Meet other students outside your cluster through clubs    
    
    
    Career Management Center.  ACE advising coaching executive in residence    
    
    
    Exec in residence    
    
    
    38000 alums. 16 US and 38 int clubs.   Alum network value.    
    
    
    480 speakers last year    
    
    
    Spouses can participate in clubs.    
    
    
    Application.    
    
    
    Acad. Strength.  Undergrad record. GMAT in balence with undergrad record.  Broad range of scores.  Toefl. No min.   Target ranges.    
    
    
    Only look at highest score.  Verify after.  Share if score is moving up if below 80per range.    
    
    
    Want to see full info.  Professional recs. Someone who is senior knows you welll.  Do not worry about English ability of reommender.    
    
    
    Only those with less than a year of work should use a professor.  Family bus no parents please!   Explain if you have no supervisor.    
    
    
    Essay 1 is critial. Short term want a real plan.  What is it about our program that makes sense for you?   What the fit is.    
    
    
    Alum interviewers.     Personal characteristics: tone.  Stand out. What people are we admitting.  Who you are.    Tell us about you.    
    
    
    In the other essays.  Not right answers.  Be honest and focused on you.  Ways of showing you.    
    
    
    Apply earlier in the rolling start point rather than the deadline.    
    
    
    Get app in before Jan 6 is an advantage for regular decision. No difference in acceptance between ed and reg.  Stronger  aps.  In reg rnd    
    
    
    Intro alums. Diverse group of alums came.    
    
    
    No plan to increase class size.    
    
    
    Get in apps early.  More and more competitive.    
    
    
    Each app us read Twice and then by adcom.  Visit if possible    
    
    
    International students have priority for housing.  170 or so attended the event.    
    
    
    Booth And Columbia MBA Students Get The Highest Summer Pay http://www.businessinsider.com/top-mba-intern-salaries-2013-6 … via @tbi_warroom    
    
    
    UCLA Wins OK to Make MBA Program 'Self-Supporting' | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/quicktakes/2013/06/27/ucla-wins-ok-make-mba-program-self-supporting#.Ucxv5JeKGFo.twitter …    
    
    
    IN MEMORIAM: The INSEAD PDF Application is dead. It has been replaced by a standard online application.    
    
    
    Chicago’s Booth to Move EMBA Program to Hong Kong Detention Site http://www.businessweek.com/news/2013-07-12/chicago-s-booth-to-move-mba-program-to-hong-kong-detention-site … via @BW    
    
    
    Cornell Launches MBA Program at NYC Tech Campus http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-07-17/cornell-launches-mba-program-at-nyc-tech-campus … via @BW    
    
    
    Jennifer Aaker: The Seven Deadly Sins of Storytelling | Stanford Graduate School of Business http://www.gsb.stanford.edu/news/headlines/jennifer-aaker-seven-deadly-sins-storytelling#.Ue0c_t4HHV0.twitter …    
    
    
    How Swine Flu will impact US universities http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/08/21/h1n1    
    
    
    Getting ready to leave for The World MBA Fair in Tokyo    
    
    
    Just had a great conversation with IMD's MBA Marketing Manager.  I think I need to get this 55 minute conversation transcribed.    
    
    
    Why College Costs Rise, Even in a Recession http://bit.ly/wtDCJ    
    
    
    Platforms and Networks: A Compilation of the Web's Best Advice for Entrepr... http://platformsandnetworks.blogspot.com/2009/11/compilation-of-webs-best-advice-for.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    University of California Faculty walkouts planned http://bit.ly/3W6HGc    
    
    
    Wharton interview? read this: http://poetsandquants.com/2010/11/21/leak-of-whartons-interview-questions-raises-ethical-issues    
    
    
    2000 students at US university report swine flu symptoms http://bit.ly/HhW5k    
    
    
    If you are in Tokyo and interested in applying to NYU Stern, please http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/02/317.html    
    
    
    HOW TO GET INTO HBS AND STANFORD: 2 LEADING MBA ADMISSIONS CONSULTANTS SHARE THEIR EXPERTISE http://tinyurl.com/4aooh9c    
    
    
    ハーバードビジネススクールとスタンフォードGSB に入学する方法 http://lnkd.in/-ZeyyC    
    
    
    A New Dean for Stanford Business School http://bit.ly/MBbcG    
    
    
    Survey: ROI now top priority for US MBA applicants http://www.bizjournals.com/houston/stories/2009/09/07/daily33.html    
    
    
    International Branch Campuses on the Rise http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/09/03/branch    
    
    
    To the victors, the spoils: a post-Lehman scorecard http://www.reuters.com/article/mergersNews/idUSL951130920090911    
    
    
    The Game of Ghost Writing  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/09/11/ghostwrite    
    
    
    Yale Graduate Student Missing http://www.nytimes.com/2009/09/13/nyregion/13yale.html    
    
    
    Annie Le: Body found at Yale Lab http://bit.ly/7z2dn    
    
    
    Scoping out future leaders for HBS http://bit.ly/TKjLK    
    
    
    International grad enrollment is up, largely due to Indian students | Inside Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2013/11/05/international-grad-enrollment-largely-due-indian-students#.Unj6K3ftvsU.twitter …    
    
    
    Inaccurate calculations in US News & World Report College Rankings http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/09/14/usnews    
    
    
    Stanford University lays off 100s of staff because the endowment is taking a 30% hit!  http://tinyurl.com/pgt3v7    
    
    
    University of Illinois: President  and Chancellor blame each other for admissions scandal http://tinyurl.com/obrnm4    
    
    
    See previous tweet.  University of Il. makes me ill.    
    
    
    WALL STREET JOURNAL'S ACCELERATED MBA RANKINGS http://bit.ly/3guhrl    
    
    
    More Signs of Spread of H1N1 on Campuses http://bit.ly/2Kn5R7    
    
    
    Yale lab worker arrested in student's killing http://edition.cnn.com/2009/CRIME/09/17/yale.student.le/index.html    
    
    
    How Safe Is Your College?  http://bit.ly/3f8CfG    
    
    
    Will a Killing at Yale Affect Applications This Year? http://tinyurl.com/kj3ze5    
    
    
    When Less Is More  http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/09/23/essay    
    
    
    Carnival of College Admission is Back! http://bit.ly/14nCdf    
    
    
    After over three years of blogging on MBA admissions, I finally have written a full post on recommendations! See http://tinyurl.com/2ayughy    
    
    
    Stanford U. looking to sell $1 billion in assets http://www.reuters.com/article/domesticNews/idUSTRE59209320091003    
    
    
    I hope all my readers, friends, and everyone here in Japan are OK. My wife & my colleagues Vince and Steve and their families are fine.    
    
    
    NYU Japan Trek canceled. Assume others likely to follow.    
    
    
    I am now in  Fukuoka in Western Japan for purposes of safety and business continuity.  I hope to be able to return to Tokyo soon.    
    
    
    Help Japan: Make Donations! Invest in Japan's future! http://tinyurl.com/4kcm738    
    
    
    Wharton interviews are now 100% Behavioral. See http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2009/10/wharton-mba-admissions-interview.html    
    
    
    Harvard M.B.A. Indicator http://bit.ly/5GvGu    
    
    
    More international students attending US graduate school: http://tinyurl.com/3ns5vj5.  Business up 11% in '09-'10 and 4% in '10-'11    
    
    
    Network with professionals in Tokyo, drink with Adam, and contribute to earthquake victims on April 20th! http://tinyurl.com/3l5tyad    
    
    
    So you want to get into Stanford?  My audio presentation and the transcript are on my blog: http://tinyurl.com/3julkyk    
    
    
    Stanford Dean’s column: Robert L. Joss on his grandfather who delivered life lessons  http://tinyurl.com/yfewpen    
    
    
    My rant about Oxford MBA Programme's Extended deadline.  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/04/oxford-said-mba-extends-application.html    
    
    
    Harvard ignored warnings about investments http://tinyurl.com/ybqnckv    
    
    
    日本におけるTOEFL®テストスカラシッププログラム http://www.ets.org/toefl/scholarships/overview/japan/japanese    
    
    
    Adam on Admissions Officers http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2009/12/target-audience-american-mba-admissions.html    
    
    
    Harvard B-School Dean Jay Light Stepping Down http://www.businessweek.com/bschools/content/dec2009/bs2009122_689354.htm    
    
    
    UC BERKELEY CHANCELLOR'S HOUSE ATTACKED BY PROTESTERS http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2009/12/14/berkeley    
    
    
    Sustainability moves up the MBA curriculum http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/4dd89856-e84f-11de-8a02-00144feab49a.html?nclick_check=1    
    
    
    Harvard Swaps Are So Toxic http://www.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=20601087&sid=aHQ2Xh55jI.Q    
    
    
    My HBS essay and rec analysis for Fall 2012 is now up at http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/05/hbs-mba-program-class-of-2014-mba.html    
    
    
    University College London, "terrorism's Ivy League" http://tinyurl.com/yg2xf26    
    
    
    Kaplan acquires Manhattan GMAT http://www.beatthegmat.com/kaplan-acquires-manhattan-gmat-t50227.html    
    
    
    The costs and benefits of grad school http://blogs.reuters.com/felix-salmon/2010/01/07/the-costs-and-benefits-of-grad-school/    
    
    
    Harvard University Audited as Part of IRS Probe of Nonprofits http://www.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=20601087&sid=a99iobGRQye8&pos=9    
    
    
    Goldman Sachs Still Shines for MBAs Who Ignore ‘Hype’ http://www.bloomberg.com/apps/news?pid=20601109&sid=agFgbCvM44FA    
    
    
    Haitian Earthquake Relief. See http://www.hufh.org/
if you are a fan of "The Haitian" from Heroes.    
    
    
    For a full list or organizations see http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2010/01/12/haiti-earthquake-relief-h_n_421014.html    
    
    
    Harvard Business School Changes Its Class Profile: Finance down, Manufacturing and IT up http://tinyurl.com/3l3m8u7     
    
    
    Michigan State University Demands That Personal Opinions Stay Off Campus E-mail http://www.thefire.org/article/11512.html    
    
    
    FT: Doors of opportunity open again for MBAs http://tinyurl.com/4x7b7w4     
    
    
    Official GMAT APP for iPhone/iPad (Review) http://iphonehelp.in/2011/06/26/official-gmat-app-for-iphoneipad-review/ …    
    
    
    HBS MBA Program Sees Largest Female Percentage (39%) http://abcnews.go.com/Business/wireStory?id=13930748 …    
    
    
    HBS Class of 2013 data in Harvard Crimson http://www.thecrimson.com/article/2011/6/24/business-school-2013-women/ …    
    
    
    10 Really Stupid Things that MBA Applicants Do http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/10-really-stupid-things-that-mba.html …    
    
    
    Where men still dominate: Chicago's B schools | Consumer | Crain's Chicago Business http://www.chicagobusiness.com/article/20110705/NEWS07/110709971/where-men-still-dominate-chicagos-b-schools …    
    
    
    As Number One, China to Face Hour of Choice - Brookings Institution http://www.brookings.edu/opinions/2011/0630_china_bush.aspx …    
    
    
    Where is the Best Place to Invest $102,000 -- In Stocks, Bonds, or a College Degree? - Brookings Institution http://www.brookings.edu/papers/2011/0625_education_greenstone_looney.aspx …    
    
    
    WSJ.com - UNC Makes Risky Online Bet http://on.wsj.com/qHqJRa     
    
    
    A Farewell to Summer: The Pre-MBA Internship - BusinessWeek http://buswk.co/iZTGrk  via @BW    
    
    
    Wharton moving San Francisco campus http://www.bizjournals.com/philadelphia/morning_roundup/2011/06/wharton-moving-san-francisco-campus.html?ana=twt … via @Philabizjournal    
    
    
    Twitter Account of Adam Markus
http://adammarkus.com/
http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/
http://www.linkedin.com/in/adammarkus    
    
    
    初めまして。大学院留学のカウンセラーをしています。
私のブログでMBAやLLMといった海外大学院合格のための情報や意見などを公開しています.    
    
    
    Admissions Consulting for those who aspire to do great things! http://adammarkus.com.    
    
    
    Latest post: http://tinyurl.com/6ewcwe    
    
    
    Working! What do you expect?    
    
    
    Tired of trashing emails from low ranking programs that will be at The MBA Tour in Tokyo    
    
    
    Just read an article on how Law Schools game the rankings 
http://tinyurl.com/5jn3n5    
    
    
    Read Fall 2009 Fletcher Application Qs http://tinyurl.com/6faabq    
    
    
    International Graduate Applicants to the US increase a little http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/08/21/international    
    
    
    Challenging Work & Corporate Responsibility Lure MBA Grads http://tinyurl.com/5m5von    
    
    
    Application Levels RISE @ B-Schools  http://www.gmac.com/gmac/NewsandEvents/PressRoom/GMACSurveys/FactSheetApplicationTrendsSurvey.htm    
    
    
    Wharton's Interim Adcom Director http://tinyurl.com/6dvevf No big changes till a new one?    
    
    
    Your objective for all MBA Adcom events is to get as many free pens as you can.    
    
    
    How Important Are Standardized Tests?  http://tinyurl.com/6lyq2m    
    
    
    Should American Politics Be Abolished as a Field? http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/08/29/ampol    
    
    
    Good blog post on the academic labor market http://tinyurl.com/6fn3kb    
    
    
    UCLA Professor suspects cheating in racial admissions http://tinyurl.com/6f3qtv    
    
    
    Waiting for my YouTube video to upload so that I can post it to my blog.    
    
    
    Grad School Resume Template https://docs.google.com/document/d/1wLYKrhDvK_36xnVgV41xu7ETfjUJO0dIqW4K-DypIdo/edit?hl=en_US …    
    
    
    Published RESUMEtemp.doc on Scribd http://scr.bi/oOsonn #readcast    
    
    
    Reading "Resume Template for MBA, LL.M., & Other Grad School Appli..." on Scribd http://www.scribd.com/doc/59781852  #Readcast    
    
    
    Up to 80 MBAs at WVU May Be Sushttp://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/09/02/wvupect. Also some at a Carnegie Mellon!    
    
    
    GMAT Test Prep: A Primer - BusinessWeek http://buswk.co/nCkuei  via @BW    
    
    
    MIT event Tokyo    
    
    
    waiting    
    
    
    reading mit brochure    
    
    
    looking at Tim the masscot    
    
    
    video will start soon    
    
    
    quiz slide time    
    
    
    20000 in alum network    
    
    
    Angel navado    
    
    
    full house at event    
    
    
    Navado at MIT for ten yrs    
    
    
    10 Japanese in 2008 class    
    
    
    Navado conduucted interviews in Tokyo for 2008 class    
    
    
    fun video time    
    
    
    Anavedo@MIT.edu    
    
    
    1 year Master's in finance    
    
    
    mens et manus    
    
    
    courses to apply what you learn    
    
    
    expected to have ideas and execute them    
    
    
    take advantage of the whole school    
    
    
    .75 elective courses    
    
    
    1st sem 7 member diverse team    
    
    
    Get to know everyone    
    
    
    collaborative atmosphere emphasized    
    
    
    SIP IAP    
    
    
    Finance very strong    
    
    
    Change all the time    
    
    
    Challenge status quo not best practices are valued    
    
    
    sustainability    
    
    
    emphasizing experiential learning    
    
    
    student organized trips    
    
    
    want a diverse class    
    
    
    diverse undergrad majors.    
    
    
    increase in recruiting at MIT    
    
    
    MBA is transformative experience    
    
    
    apply when you are ready make the best app you can    
    
    
    thirty percent increase in apps    
    
    
    higher admit rate in first round    
    
    
    50percent taken from round    
    
    
    want to do is less important than what you have done    
    
    
    telll aspecific story    
    
    
    be specific discuss specific events    
    
    
    interviews by adcom who hAve read your file    
    
    
    reccomender should know you well    
    
    
    all pieces of app are important    
    
    
    can serve as a teaching or research assistant    
    
    
    sales pitch ....    
    
    
    16 alums    
    
    
    20 alums    
    
    
    MIT event over    
    
    
    Which US College Scores Best on the GMAT?  http://buswk.co/ndQw2V     
    
    
    The End of US Subsidized Student Loans? - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/onGy8i  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Keio and Essec Joint 2Y MBA http://www.yomiuri.co.jp/dy/national/20080907TDY02304.htm    
    
    
    MBA 4 FREE? http://tinyurl.com/6nfhcl    
    
    
    Cannot make it to Chicago HSB    
    
    
    because of rain cannot get to Chicago GSB event    
    
    
    getting dry    
    
    
    How UC is rigging the admissions process http://tinyurl.com/5qmr4d    
    
    
    UCLA's new admission policy rights a wrong http://tinyurl.com/6a3ejd    
    
    
    Wondering how big of a controversy UCLA's admissions policies will become    
    
    
    at MBA Tour    
    
    
    steve and I are waiting    
    
    
    People are networking    
    
    
    developing are pen collection strategy    
    
    
    the doors have opened    
    
    
    Twittering not effective at MBA Tour.  MBA TOUR BLOG POST will be up on Tuesday.    
    
    
    Undegrad Grade Inflation at US Schools: Easy A - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/nU5PaK  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Finance Job cuts continue in FT http://tinyurl.com/6by7x8/lead_story_cluster/newsletter///    
    
    
    International students most likely to finish PhDs in US http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/09/09/gaps    
    
    
    Just registered for the HBS Tokyo Event.  If you want to attend, you better register soon!    
    
    
    Michigan Ross Information Session on August 9th in Tokyo http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/michigan-ross-information-session-on.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: ON POST-MBA ENTREPRENEURIAL GOALS http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/on-post-mba-entrepreneurial-goals.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: HBS CLASS OF 2013 PROFILE http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/hbs-class-of-2013-profile.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Social-networking sites viewed by admissions officers http://tinyurl.com/5xvefg    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru by Adam Markus http://www.amazon.com/dp/B005D3NRA4/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_fG.iob0D9RRDG … via @amazon    
    
    
    In Japan Financial Crisis Is Just a Ripple http://tinyurl.com/43hhcs    
    
    
    Wondering about what HBS will be taking away from the massive leadership failure of their alum Pres. Bush    
    
    
    Is Yale Law School (Pres. Clinton) better at producing leaders than HBS (Pres. Bush)?    
    
    
    Wondering how to profit from the coming boom in financial regulation. SOX will be small compared to whats coming.    
    
    
    Our First President With an MBA http://tinyurl.com/4y5bsw    
    
    
    A list worth looking at: 50 Resources for MBA Applicants http://businessmajors.about.com/od/choosingaschool/a/50-Resources-For-Mba-Applicants.htm?r=twitter …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Stanford GSB Essay 1: What matters most to you, an... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/stanford-gsb-essay-1-what-matters-most.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Stanford GSB Essay 2: What do you want to do—REALL... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/stanford-gsb-essay-2-what-do-you-want.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    'Wall Street' No Longer Exists http://online.wsj.com/article/SB122212959612065505.html    
    
    
    David Brooks, The Establishment Lives! http://tinyurl.com/4w5u6s    
    
    
    Beyond a bailout, Wall Street needs new rules http://tinyurl.com/46o38s    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Stanford GSB MBA Essay 3 for Class of 2014 Admissi... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/stanford-gsb-mba-essay-3-for-class-of.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    What Can You Do With A JD? Be A Crappy CEO! http://tinyurl.com/4l6s86    
    
    
    Now my entire 5 post series on Stanford GSB Class of 2014 essays is up!  http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/stanford-gsb-mba-essay-questions-for.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Monster Launches Admissions.com for undergrads. I wonder if they plan on doing a grad site.    
    
    
    MBA Students Screwed, Given Comfort Reading Lists http://tinyurl.com/4t2yy4    
    
    
    LSAT-Free Law School Admissions Can Goose U.S. News Ranking http://tinyurl.com/3hrtdg    
    
    
    Michigan State University allows  Personal Statement Videos http://tinyurl.com/43ff22    
    
    
    Japan’s big banks put their megabucks to work in the West http://tinyurl.com/4p4aka    
    
    
    The King Is Dead http://tinyurl.com/5467jw    
    
    
    Creating the Anti-Rankings for Undergrad Education http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/09/26/collegespeaks    
    
    
    Stanford GSB Dean to step down at end of academic year http://tinyurl.com/3g6ua8    
    
    
    IMD of Switzerland tops Economist Intelligence Unit's 2008 MBA rankings http://tinyurl.com/3rzepz    
    
    
    Graduate schools consult Facebook http://www.dailyprincetonian.com/2008/09/26/21548/    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Word Count Later, Ideas and Stories First! http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/word-count-later-ideas-and-stories.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Bad news is good news for Japan http://www.yomiuri.co.jp/dy/business/20080929TDY07301.htm    
    
    
    at Tokyo HBS event    
    
    
        
    
    
    Mcneil hbs club    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hbs portrait project video    
    
    
    sorry standard hbs video    
    
    
    adcom spoke for a couple of minutes and a video    
    
    
    Not the case video. More holistic video    
    
    
    transformational experience : adcom speaking    
    
    
    what makes hbs unique    
    
    
    mission: leaders global and local    
    
    
    case merhod 100percent 500-600 in two years    
    
    
    analyze data and arrive at action plan    
    
    
    case based on questions.    
    
    
    presentation is going between video and adcom    
    
    
    passionate faculty    
    
    
    learning teams 6-7 diverse not people in your section of 90    
    
    
    diversity very key to case    
    
    
    real communities around diverse interests    
    
    
    .38 female .33 International .24 consulting background .42 humanities and social sciences    
    
    
    said nothing about age except re 0 experience entrants    
    
    
    Overview of program structure    
    
    
    Field study in second year.  Business plan contest also in 2nd year.    
    
    
    Discussion via video of what general management is.    
    
    
    Network  at hbs    
    
    
    alums on video discuss networking    
    
    
    Admissions:    
    
    
    A habit of leadership, different kinds of leaders    
    
    
    how have you lead and how is it unique to you    
    
    
    capacity for intellectual growth no minimums    
    
    
    gmats as low 550 were accepted    
    
    
    engaged community citizenship    
    
    
    willing to give to others    
    
    
    apply early    
    
    
    no preferabce for round one or two    
    
    
    essays now four show three areas in your essay    
    
    
        
    
    
    interviews    
    
    
    30 min    
    
    
    on or off campus telephone or small number of alum. You choose if invited    
    
    
    .5 receive fellowships and .75 receive loans    
    
    
    loan assistance for those in nonprof    
    
    
    final video. Adcom emphasized knowing exactlybwhybyou want to go to hbs at the end of her presentation    
    
    
    alum panel commences    
    
    
        
    
    
    adcom: some really enjoy manditory study team in first year but some don't    
    
    
    Adcom said no quota by age.  Typically evasive.    
    
    
        
    
    
    HBS Alum said to read Ahead of the Curve http://tinyurl.com/3ndkb3    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: GMAT and GRE at INSEAD http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/gmat-and-gre-at-insead.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    New-look GRE braces innovation http://www.business-standard.com/india/news/new-look-gre-braces-innovation/443365/ …  Sure, but MBA programs are still getting to few GRE scores for them to report data.    
    
    
    Wall Street Collapse May Result in More IT Applicants http://tinyurl.com/4oqxqp    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Kellogg 2012 MBA Application Essay Questions http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/kellogg-2012-mba-application-essay.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Just another reason to go to a highly ranked program: U. of Florida Jobless MBA grad begs for work  http://www.orlandosentinel.com/features/education/os-mba-begs-for-job-20110721,0,120760.story …    
    
    
    New Challenge to TOEFL: PEARSON TEST INCLUDES RECORDING SENT TO ADCOM http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/10/02/english    
    
    
    NYU Stern Professor alleges he was punished for confronting widespread student plagiarism- Inside High Ed: http://bit.ly/q3ZEzZ  via @addthis    
    
    
    Stern using plagiarism detection software in its classes http://tinyurl.com/434jtzc     
    
    
    Investment banking careers dim for MBA students http://money.cnn.com/news/newsfeeds/articles/apwire/3605459233ff96a2ae26ea50cf566a98.htm    
    
    
    UC undergrad admissions data now on Web http://tinyurl.com/4wrdfu    
    
    
    MUST READ ARTICLE: The Fall of America, Inc. http://www.newsweek.com/id/162401    
    
    
    Just watched the movie at  http://www.keatingeconomics.com/    
    
    
        
    
    
    LIBOR: THE GREASE THAT KEEPS THE WHEELS OF COMMERCE SPINNING http://tinyurl.com/4ba8cc    
    
    
    Crisis leads to opportunity    
    
    
    Dan Dresner on "Your bad idea of the day": US Postal Savings Bank http://danieldrezner.com/blog/?p=3979    
    
    
    What caused the financial crisis? http://tinyurl.com/3uflqq    
    
    
    The European collective response http://tinyurl.com/4ft9xw    
    
    
    Watching the TED spread: http://tinyurl.com/4ywka6    
    
    
    at LBS Tokyo Event    
    
    
    watching alums and applicants drink    
    
    
    the LBS event is posh. At the Grand Hyatt.    
    
    
    left the cocktail room. Now waiting  for the event to start.    
    
    
    adcom starts    
    
    
    motivations for pursuing n MBA    
    
    
    Lbs excellence    
    
    
    rank faculty research exceptional peers    
    
    
    rigorous admisssionsmakes for great peers    
    
    
    emphasizes need for a global view    
    
    
    value of network    
    
    
    London    
    
    
    global capital of the world    
    
    
    travel advantages    
    
    
    leadership bring in world leaders.  Leadership is vital. Become a global leader    
    
    
    clubs give the opportunity    
    
    
    Adcom speaker is totally polished.    
    
    
    careerr coaching from the beginning.  Strength of. Career services.    
    
    
    range of programs    
    
    
    MBA 15-21 months    
    
    
    After 1st semester decide on length    
    
    
    She is explaining the structure of the program.    
    
    
    many projects in the course    
    
    
    shF    
    
    
    shAdowing project 2nd year project    
    
    
    master of finance    
    
    
    Zoe and Tye are the adcoms. Both are very effective speakers.    
    
    
    Sloan fellow    
    
    
    linda    
    
    
    Sloan 8-20 years of experience.  For seasoned managers. 15 years of Exp on average.    
    
    
    structure of program    
    
    
    prepare for next career challenge    
    
    
    move to general or strategic management    
    
    
    Now discussing next steps to learn about LBS.    
    
    
    Application. Apply early.    
    
    
    18 alums and students    
    
    
    they are all introducing themselves. This will take a while.    
    
    
    alums emphasize international nature of the program.    
    
    
    alums still introducing themselves    
    
    
    Q&A can really suck.    
    
    
    I asked admissions if they provide any admissions data and they said no, but that there has been a significant increase in apps    
    
    
    leaving event    
    
    
    Commercial Paper Funding Facility (CPFF). Hope it works. http://www.federalreserve.gov/newsevents/press/monetary/20081007c.htm    
    
    
    PE RESEARCH CENTER AT LBS http://edition.cnn.com/2008/BUSINESS/10/07/execed.risks/    
    
    
    Free! Why $0.00 Is the Future of Business http://tinyurl.com/2okqbk    
    
    
    THE ROSE REPORT http://tinyurl.com/3vj3fu    
    
    
    at Tokyo Wharton Event    
    
    
    jacky zavitz    
    
    
    4 years in adcom and previously at career services    
    
    
    referencing Wharton website    
    
    
    aspire MBA facing new challenges given recent changes    
    
    
    a place where business knowledge is created    
    
    
    innovative learning : contrasting types of business schools  Wharton  in the middle    
    
    
    most faculty250 19 majors. Biggest school    
    
    
    different kinds of classes:    
    
    
    strongest in a number of areas not just finance    
    
    
    strength in analytical thinking    
    
    
    1st year structure  same as web    
    
    
    5-7 in first year learning teams    
    
    
    double major    
    
    
    Leadership. Various kinds of training    
    
    
    Engaged community crafting a diverse class 100 clubs    
    
    
    20 student conferences. PE    
    
    
        
    
    
    7328 applied 1190 admitted broad in terms of age 18-43    
    
    
    great data presentation emphasized breadth of those admitted    
    
    
    social impact    
    
    
    Philadelphia  perfectly located re east coast    
    
    
    she is trying to sell Philly. God bless her.    
    
    
    strength in global access    
    
    
    strength of international recruiting emphasized    
    
    
    value of the network    
    
    
    Lauder practical and intensive    
    
    
    financing 90per take loans.    
    
    
    admissions process    
    
    
    Academic performance. Degree and GMAT only. Must be able to handle the program.    
    
    
    Averages 111toefl 715gmat    
    
    
    professional development 0-20 years of experience    
    
    
    personal qualities really matter because most Applicants qualified in terms of academics and professional development    
    
    
    all interviews are the same    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    alums introducing themselves. Nine alum.    
    
    
    sorry 11 alum.    
    
    
    Event over    
    
    
    There are no capitalists in foxholes.  Milton Friedman and von Hayek must be spinning in their graves. Keynes is laughing.    
    
    
    3 Stanford GSB Students Die in Car Accident http://tinyurl.com/47bqrq    
    
    
    Impact of tablet computers on case studies The B-School Case Study Gets a Digital Makeover - BusinessWeek http://buswk.co/rbL4g8  via @BW    
    
    
    Business school applications rise as financial industry sheds jobs http://www.iht.com/articles/2008/10/14/business/redfin.php    
    
    
    Escape Route: Seeking Refuge in an MBA Program http://tinyurl.com/4rgg6g    
    
    
    Citibank Cuts Loan Program For Harvard Grad Students http://tinyurl.com/3vjwhf    
    
    
    Citigroup Curbs Foreign-Student Loans at Harvard, MIT http://tinyurl.com/4axq3a    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Ambition & Vision are Good: Thoughts on MBA Career Goals http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/07/ambition-vision-are-good-thoughts-on.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Graduate-Student Population Grows, So Does Its Reliance on Financial Aid http://chronicle.com/article/As-Graduate-Student-Population/128402/ …    
    
    
    As economy sputters, grad schools overflow http://tinyurl.com/2f7nc2/20081016/FREE/810169985/1057    
    
    
    Global banking reshaped http://tinyurl.com/4ameap/finance_crisis/oct/    
    
    
    MBA's: Outdated In Today's Changing Economy? http://www.cnbc.com/id/27215195    
    
    
    US reliving Tokyo's economic nightmare? http://tinyurl.com/4n28uz    
    
    
    Another New Front in the JD Rankings War: Paying Students to Apply http://tinyurl.com/6mt5da    
    
    
    Next Front in Rankings War: Paying Admitted Students to Retake the LSAT? http://tinyurl.com/6x6zh6    
    
    
    Kenyan MBA Boom http://tinyurl.com/5jxyry    
    
    
    Citi Loan Program Ends Nationwide http://tinyurl.com/59xm98    
    
    
    Top 5 Law School Rankings Scams of 2008 http://tinyurl.com/5qgegw    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yen Rises to Three-Year High on Bets Central Banks to Cut Rates http://tinyurl.com/6yu74t    
    
    
    Turning Japanese?  http://www.cfr.org/publication/17554/    
    
    
    The IELTS alternative http://tinyurl.com/27ppn2/www/story/10-22-2008/0004909162&EDATE=    
    
    
    Happy about the direction of the TED Spread http://tinyurl.com/4ywka6    
    
    
    Job search diagnostics http://tinyurl.com/5wmlvu    
    
    
    US Job Losses Accelerate http://tinyurl.com/6cuajw    
    
    
    World MBA Tour Tokyo November 6th preregister because otherwise you have to pay 500 yen    
    
    
    World MBA Tour Tokyo 11/6 Top European programs will be there, but participating US schools are not as highly ranked    
    
    
    Economic Crisis impact on US Universities http://www.insidehighered.com/views/2008/10/23/kneedler    
    
    
    Another view: Economic crisis impact on US Higher Ed  http://www.insidehighered.com/views/2008/10/23/seligman    
    
    
    Academic vs. Football Coach Salaries http://tinyurl.com/6atcjy    
    
    
    Credit Crisis Indicators: No Progress http://tinyurl.com/5tc4bg    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yale MBA dean to found Apple University http://tinyurl.com/59qlzu    
    
    
    Top Theorists Examine Rippling Economic Turbulence  http://tinyurl.com/56w2t3    
    
    
    Wiley Becomes Global Publisher of the Official GMAT Study Guides  http://tiny.cc/JyHv7    
    
    
    GMAT palm vein authentication http://tinyurl.com/62yt9u    
    
    
    The MBA Calls When the Economy Falls http://tinyurl.com/5rvxkq    
    
    
    Forté Forum:  MBA Value Proposition http://tinyurl.com/58bhr9    
    
    
    Happy Diwali!    
    
    
    With the Stock Market Sliding, Students Go to Cheaper Schools http://tech.mit.edu/V128/N51/collegecost.html    
    
    
    Students, schools adjust for struggling economy http://tinyurl.com/5juofx    
    
    
    GRE vs. GMAT (ETS vs GMAC) http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/10/28/bschool    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Four Reasons to Enroll in Your M.B.A. Program Now
http://tinyurl.com/57roka    
    
    
    In a taxi going to the Tokyo Duke event    
    
    
    at Duke event. Waiting    
    
    
    Karen Courtney adcom    
    
    
    title. Rethinking the boundaries    
    
    
        
    
    
    multi campus expansion    
    
    
    Fuqua bio    
    
    
    Risk takers at bus school    
    
    
        
    
    
    team player and leader brilliant and human analytical and global    
    
    
    Understand goals change    
    
    
    overview of entire school    
    
    
    global innovative visionary exciting GIVE    
    
    
    5 campuses opening    
    
    
    One MBA four Programs    
    
    
    general management MBA    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Comparison btw daytime and cross continent    
    
    
    On 6 week term basis.  Test out of core courses to take more electives    
    
    
    60percent faculty international    
    
    
    rigorous team oriented environment    
    
    
    good balence between academics and clubs/social    
    
    
    career resources are rich    
    
    
        
    
    
    create a diverse team    
    
    
    alumni network is strong    
    
    
    cross continent student speaking    
    
    
    MBA alums speaking    
    
    
    alums emphasize social networking value of the program    
    
    
        
    
    
    Emphasize small town environment    
    
    
        
    
    
    Essays: wroite from the heart. Answer question directly. Be human    
    
    
    be careful to customize your essays.    
    
    
    Make sure the recs get in on time    
    
    
    interview: encourage campus interview   or do an alum.   Comfortable interview.    
    
    
        
    
    
    many scholarships    
    
    
        
    
    
    Q&A    
    
    
    adcom consistently emphasized human relations skills.    
    
    
    alum: duke provides a flexible environment.    
    
    
    over!    
    
    
    Tightening Credit Squeezes International Students  http://tinyurl.com/59ux6b    
    
    
    Student Lending Analytics Blog http://tinyurl.com/6pgtgy    
    
    
    Visa Applications Soar for Indian Students Who Want to Study in U.S. http://chronicle.com/article/Visa-Applications-Soar-for/128466/ …    
    
    
    As Graduate-Student Population Grows, So Does  Reliance on Financial Aid http://chronicle.com/article/As-Graduate-Student-Population/128402/ …    
    
    
    Nomura, Daiwa to Cut Costs as Losses Build Overseas, Japan Economy Falters - Bloomberg http://bloom.bg/ohBlMA  via @BloombergNews    
    
    
    'The College Writing Toolkit' - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/nfjoM7  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Homer Simpson Must Be Fired From Nuke Plant: William Pesek - Bloomberg http://bloom.bg/oSSSUJ  via @BloombergView    
    
    
    Adam Markus: Graduate Admissions Guru: Dartmouth Tuck MBA Essay Questions for Academic Ye... http://adam-markus.blogspot.com/2011/08/dartmouth-tuck-mba-essay-questions-for.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Panel Sees Odds of U.S. Recession Rising - Bloomberg http://bloom.bg/nQMTRh  via @BloombergNews    
    
    
    U.S. business schools feel fallout from crisis http://www.reuters.com/article/domesticNews/idUSTRE4A403F20081105    
    
    
    MBA students lower their career projections http://tinyurl.com/5q93ea    
    
    
    Obama on Higher Ed http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/11/05/obama    
    
    
    WSJ: Financial Crisis Bodes Ill for MBA Programs http://tinyurl.com/5vtupb    
    
    
    Education level and career choice impact lifetime income. Is this a shock? http://chronicle.com/article/Education-Pays-but-So-Does/128526/ …    
    
    
    Good low GMAT score entry data here! GMAT: How Low is Too Low for Top B-Schools http://buswk.co/r7Bh8I     
    
    
    More Business Schools To Accept GRE Scores http://on.wsj.com/qQtMkd  via @WSJ    
    
    
        
    
    
    Debt, Dropouts and Degrees - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/n6DiJq  via @AddThis    
    
    
    High Cost of Study in U.S., Britain - Inside Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/qINlTr  via @AddThis    
    
    
    Yale's Robert Shiller making me more depressed: 
http://tinyurl.com/6jfrhf    
    
    
    Chicago Booth http://tinyurl.com/5r9d3a    
    
    
        
    
    
    Reasons to be economically cheerful http://tinyurl.com/6dwopv,0    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Business is good - for MBA admit offices http://tiny.cc/bc98L    
    
    
    More U.S. Help for Student Loan Providers http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2008/11/10/loans    
    
    
        
    
    
    