If you've been involved in an auto accident, you may have "hidden injuries" in your spine.  www.redapplewellness.net pic.twitter.com/eN5sPCg    
    
    
    Dept. of Justice raided the Gibson guitar factory, thus demonstrating just how out of whack the federal government's priorities are.    
    
    
    I'm doing research into non-drug treatments for peripheral neuropathy.    
    
    
    Medical vs. Chiropractic Treatments for Chronic Pain | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/1fVyEkxVl     
    
    
    I'm disgusted with the off-field behavior of the Steelers players.  Mr. Rooney, it's time to clean house.  Get rid of the bad seeds please.    
    
    
    @MyNameIsAlec I hope that "bitch" takes him to the cleaners.  I'm sick of these asshole football players acting like douches 24/7    
    
    
    Did you know the most common cause of headache is due to misalignment of the vertebrae in your neck?  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Helping Kids Recover From Sports Injuries | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/Fz2Bpkbb     
    
    
    Helping Kids Recover From Sports Injuries:  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/333 …    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Cholesterol Drug Scam, Wake Up America 13 http://youtu.be/gzoMn1ZzAPU?a    
    
    
    There are three kinds of people:   Those who can count...and those who can't.    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- eric clapton wonderful tonight live http://youtu.be/qneh8eJTcas?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Eric Clapton/Tears in heaven http://youtu.be/AscPOozwYA8?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Since 1773 http://youtu.be/8zsUNnFVMsE?a    
    
    
    I'm researching interesting new trends in detoxification.    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- After Midnight in STEREO - Eric Clapton 1987 version http://youtu.be/szRNqPBmqDw?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Eric Clapton & Friends - Crossroads http://youtu.be/iO2_LnlDdY4?a    
    
    
    Want to feel better and get a better night's sleep?   Stop watching the news and stop reading newspapers! http://bit.ly/a35ptK    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Eric Clapton & Friends - White Room http://youtu.be/rvnWuOjJDh4?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Eric Clapton & Mark Knopfler - White room [San Francisco -88 ~ HQ] http://youtu.be/Gn5qewPTURw?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Bill Burr - Muffins http://youtu.be/LnOg01N1u3w?a    
    
    
    I just got a new patient who told me she had been taking 20 (TWENTY) advil a day for her pain.  Yet her PCP wouldn't refer her to a chiro.    
    
    
    A Simple Solution To Feeling Better And Getting A Good Night's Sleep: http://EzineArticles.com/4129873    
    
    
    6 game suspension for Big Ben?  Oh well.  There goes the Steelers 2010 season.  Looking ahead to 2011.    
    
    
    The Steelers organization are smoking crack if they're even THINKING of trading away Ben.  A 28 year old 2-time superbowl winner???????    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Jeff Healey Band - Hoochie Coochie Man (Road House Soundtrack) 1989 http://youtu.be/o-IJsb_mTRo?a    
    
    
    Friday Haiku: Pittsburgh Pirates suck.  Big Ben Embarrasses Us.  I will drink beer now.    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Send in em Clahns (BIG BEN SONG in Pittsburghese) http://youtu.be/b63o_MgJ85k?a    
    
    
    I had new patient tell me she's taking 20 advil a day.  A DAY!!!!  And her PCP knows this and didn't try to stop her.  Wow.    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Beat it (Van Halen) - Luca Milieri - MCR® by Donato Begotti http://youtu.be/HjmejfM0WQI?a    
    
    
    @fractalaudio Hi Cliff - one of your customers here...Kevin Smith from Pittsburgh.  Hope all is well with you and yours!    
    
    
    If you're hurting and live in or around the Bethel Park area - give us a call.   412-212-8880.   We're here Monday... http://bit.ly/aWaNEL    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Israeli Air Force Strikes Rockets in Transit 28 Dec. 2008 http://youtu.be/qG0CzM_Frvc?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Gary Moore http://youtu.be/lWp-Mazmf88?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Pink Floyd Time http://youtu.be/uAtbrFUls4A?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Leona Lewis - X Factor - Over The Rainbow http://youtu.be/QLr1sBQ5gpE?a    
    
    
    I'm having a lot of fun teaching my 6 year old boy how to play baseball.    
    
    
    At Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic, we've implemented a brand new flexibility training program.   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    At Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic we just implemented a new flexibility program.  It's great for restoring... http://bit.ly/9gs8en    
    
    
    If you've got chronic headaches or migraines and you're taking medications for it, you're going down the wrong path.    
    
    
    Headaches are common but they're not normal.  It's like getting mugged in central park.  That's common but that's not normal either!    
    
    
    Since when is it improper to display the American flag in a school in America?  With all due respect - this is the U.S.A. not Mexico.    
    
    
    Happy Mother's Day from your friends at Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic!  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic has incorporated an awesome new flexibility program designed to eliminate chronic back pain!    
    
    
    Can't figure out why the Pirates would keep Brian Bass in the game that long.  He was obviously having a trainwreck day.    
    
    
    LET'S GO PENS!!!    
    
    
    Just got back from a vacation at Disney World.  Now it's time to get re-focused on health & healing.    
    
    
    @RocktronUSA I've been a big fan of Rocktron gear for over 20 years.  I'm currently using the Velocity 300 power amp.    
    
    
    Seriously, is there anything cooler than power tools?   I think not.    
    
    
    Ronnie James Dio:    Thank you for the music.   May you rest in peace.    
    
    
    If you've been dealing with chronic pain or headaches, chiropractic + rehab is the best solution.   Check out www.redapplewellness.net!    
    
    
    Is it a rule that it HAS to rain every Monday?    
    
    
    Would you say I have a *plethora* of pinatas?    
    
    
    Wishing my family, friends and patients a happy and healthy weekend.  And GO STEELERS!    
    
    
    Pirates beat the Phillies!  Woot!    
    
    
    I don't always drink beer.  But when I do - it's Dos Equis.  Stay thirsty my friends.    
    
    
    I actually got some work done on my book this weekend.  Tough to do when everyone's pulling you in all directions at once.    
    
    
    I'm here to help the people of Bethel Park get rid of their back and neck pain.  If you're hurting, give me a call. 412-212-8880.    
    
    
    @Melissa_Ott The most common cause of headache is stress on the nerves in your cervical (neck) spine due to misalignment of the vertebrae.    
    
    
    The Most Effective Solution For Chronic Back Pain Involves A Combination Of Chiropractic Adjustments: http://EzineArticles.com/4366952    
    
    
    Good news everyone! Kim Jong Il just registered to vote in Chicago!    
    
    
    We just got a new brain-based therapy device called "full body vibration".   Full body vibration is a technology... http://bit.ly/9QmWIK    
    
    
    I just tried my hand at being the head coach of my son's baseball team.  Everything worked out well and I didn't mess up too badly. LOL    
    
    
    Dennis Hopper - R.I.P.   "Now it's dark."  - Frank Booth    
    
    
    As 2011 winds down, I wanted to share my appreciation for this amazing and wonderful opportunity I've had to be a... http://fb.me/1qDNB1yUg     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/bC2rb4    
    
    
    Up early to do lawn & garden work before it gets too hot.  (Supposed to hit 90 today).  Then I'm going to relax and play my guitar! :)    
    
    
    Today, I once again re-confirmed my theory that it is impossible to go to Lowe's and spend less than $100.00.  :)    
    
    
    After a nice relaxing weekend with the family it's time to get productive!   Planning on writing an article & shooting new videos.    
    
    
    Just adjusted my last patient for 2011!   Hope you all have a very Happy New Year!    
    
    
    Tweaking and re-tweaking the website.  Everytime I think I have it where I want it, I change my mind.  LOL  Still... http://bit.ly/bZsSsX    
    
    
    After some pretty decent snowfall, I decided to keep my kids home from school.  We're going to have lunch & play Wii all day!  :)    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/bt55lQ    
    
    
    @tinayinzer Ooooh, looky at who got a Twitter account!  LOL    
    
    
    FYI:  The best way of avoiding the flu isn't a flu shot - it's optimizing your immune system via good nutrition.  Focus on raw whole foods!    
    
    
    @tinayinzer Say whatever's on your mind.  You've got 140 characters to tell the world what's going on.  :)    
    
    
    Heading out to take my dog for a walk on the trail.  His favorite time of the day!    
    
    
    Chiropractic is something that was intended to be utilized by the entire family.  It makes sense to keep your... http://fb.me/1BXA94JCB     
    
    
    Be the first kid on your block to like our Facebook fan page!  https://www.facebook.com/redapplewellness …    
    
    
    Take a few minutes to check out my blog for free health information!  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog.htm     
    
    
    Hey Tebow!  James Harrison's coming to Denver - AND he's bringing his checkbook.  Just saying.  :)    
    
    
    HERE WE GO STEELERS, HERE WE GO!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    @Antter95 I see somebody's been nipping at the hard stuff.  No, it's spelled PITTSBURGH STEELERS!  :)    
    
    
    Tebow is the most famous white Bronco since OJ's truck......    
    
    
    Physical Problems Require Physical Solutions: http://EzineArticles.com/4423040    
    
    
    Dear Media:   You can stop the Tebow frenzy now.  Thank you.    
    
    
    I'm taking the day off from work.  Taking the family to the Pittsburgh Zoo!    
    
    
    Brrrrr.  It's cold here in Pittsburgh!   I need to open a satellite office in Orlando, Florida!  :)    
    
    
    Did you know the cause of most headaches & migraines is in your NECK?  Misaligned vertebrae pinch nerves that go up into the head.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/dxJlhy    
    
    
    If you want to avoid getting a cold or the flu, clean up your diet, get a massage and get adjusted by a chiropractor.    
    
    
    Look to Neck Problems As the Source of Most Headaches & Migraines: http://EzineArticles.com/4472465    
    
    
    Give peas a chance.  http://www.peas.org/     
    
    
    47% pay no income tax.  Which are you more envious, the 1% that invest their money or the 47% that are just along for the ride?    
    
    
    The pro bowl looks like an elaborate, overblown game of flag football.  I mean - why even bother with it?  Total waste of everyone's time.    
    
    
    The longer I'm alive, and the more things I'm exposed to, the more I've grown to distrust and dislike the media.    
    
    
    @onlinerants Awesome job!  Congrats.  I admire your commitment and drive.    
    
    
    Fun in the sun today!   Went to the pool with the family.  Thank goodness I wore a bandana on my head.  Saved me from a scalp burn. :)    
    
    
    If you could *permanently* get rid of back pain through chiropractic & exercises, why in the world would you keep taking drugs?  Why?    
    
    
    Congratulations to the world champion New York Giants! The Steeler Nation salutes you!!!    
    
    
    There are four kinds of people in the world - those who are good at math, and those who aren't.    
    
    
    Hey everyone.  I haven't check in for a while.  Just thought I'd pop in and say hi.    
    
    
    played the song 'Cruise Missile (LP Version)' by Steve Morse Band on @myspace http://lnk.ms/YZv79     
    
    
    Thank you General Stanley McCrystal for your service to this country.  You have my admiration and respect.    
    
    
    Hey West Virginia!  Here's your chance to model yourselves after Illinois and sell a Senate seat.  Happy bidding!    
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/336 … http://fb.me/1CBbBYuhj     
    
    
    Just got back from taking my daughter shopping for baseball gear (uniform, bag, cleats, etc..).   Thank god she's not into hockey. LOL    
    
    
    There Is A Time And Place For All Healing Approaches: http://EzineArticles.com/6905159     
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/339 … http://fb.me/1Q4vPUhZD     
    
    
    Got pain in your neck, shoulders or back?  This may explain why:  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/339 …    
    
    
    FORWARD HEAD POSTURE CORRECTION http://aweber.com/t/8vcD4     
    
    
    Forward Head Posture Correction: http://EzineArticles.com/6914173     
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/342 … http://fb.me/KYkrCUkF     
    
    
    All About Vitamin D http://aweber.com/t/KYhre     
    
    
    All About Vitamin D: http://EzineArticles.com/6951659     
    
    
    We're all mature until someone pulls out the bubble wrap.  :)    
    
    
    @Mm_Mm_Pizza You guy's rock!  Best pizza in Bethel Park!!!!    
    
    
    Is Chiropractic A Good Choice For Back Pain?  www.redapplewellness.net/blog    
    
    
    http://fb.me/BYYTxYDO    
    
    
    Please visit my clinic's FB page and click the "like button".  https://www.facebook.com/redapplewellness …    
    
    
    Should We Train the Rectus Abdominis? | Robertson Training Systems http://fb.me/usi4Nu8v     
    
    
    Author Insights: Retinal Detachment Risk Associated With Use of Some Antibiotics http://fb.me/GvrU5Bbi     
    
    
    Hey all, I'm trying to create some buzz about my clinic. Please visit & "like" my Red Apple Wellness fan page. http://www.facebook.com/redapplewellness …    
    
    
    Is Chiropractic a Good Choice For Back Pain?: http://EzineArticles.com/4689945    
    
    
    It only takes a moment to be polite, be courteous to everyone today    
    
    
    I'd like to wish everyone a very happy and safe new year!    
    
    
    How To Use Ice Vs. Heat For Pain Control | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/16dd2W8oj     
    
    
    How To Use Ice Vs. Heat For Pain Control http://aweber.com/t/KncoI     
    
    
    Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic E-Newsletter:  April 29, 2012 http://aweber.com/t/DOykA     
    
    
    How To Use Ice Vs. Heat For Pain Control: http://EzineArticles.com/7027475     
    
    
    Don't Build Fitness Over Dysfunction | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/1urPg6nG9     
    
    
    Don't Build Fitness Over Dysfunction  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/348 …    
    
    
    Don't Build Fitness Over Dysfunction http://aweber.com/t/MguOk     
    
    
    Look For Uneven Pelvis As The Root Cause Of Lower Back Pain | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/1ZIPpgLcC     
    
    
    Look For Uneven Pelvis As The Root Cause of Chronic Lower Back Pain http://aweber.com/t/99n9a     
    
    
    The FDA Finally Acknowledged Statins Can Cause Diabetes and Memory Loss http://fb.me/1Yiw26Kib     
    
    
    Why Saturated Fats Are Heart-Healthy http://fb.me/1vhbe28ir     
    
    
    Americans consume 80 percent of world's pain pills as prescription drug abuse epidemic explodes http://fb.me/26CvO2KQa     
    
    
    I've read a LOT of health books, and this one is among the best out there.   I highly recommend you get a copy.... http://fb.me/1FatEZBRa     
    
    
    Diet Drinks:  Helpful or Harmful to Kick the Sugar Habit?  |  Dr. Mark Hyman http://fb.me/1KuEogR0b     
    
    
    Why You Should Choose CoQ10 & Your Dentist Over Statin Drugs http://fb.me/19V7iAFKN     
    
    
    10 Heart-Healthy Foods To Put on Your Grocery List http://fb.me/1QD7wEjtA     
    
    
    Why Grains Are Unhealthy | Mark's Daily Apple http://fb.me/1n7PG0UE3     
    
    
    Sugar Babies: How to Stop the Genocide of Our Children  |  Dr. Mark Hyman http://fb.me/1ZP0odruA     
    
    
    8 Ways to Avoid Colorectal Cancer http://fb.me/19OOOWcfD     
    
    
    Have you heard of MAS Correction yet?  Go to www.redapplewellness.net to get in the know!    
    
    
    The most effective treatment for low back pain is chiropractic adjustments combined with exercise.  http://redapplewellness.net .    
    
    
    It's truly amazing at how many health problems can be cleared out by going to a "Paleo" diet.  http://redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Kids back to school...now it's time for MY vacation. :)    
    
    
    More suicides have been committed with a knife and fork than by any other means.  Change your diet, and live longer.    
    
    
    I restore motion, alignment and strength for permanent relief of chronic pain syndromes. www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    @knitpurlgurl  I can help with the headaches.    
    
    
    @Hameed_Hemmat  Try using a little hydrogen peroxide in your ears.  I know it sounds weird - but it works!    
    
    
    I'm hanging out in my nice warm house...'cause it's cold and snowy out there.  Someday I'll move some place warm...maybe the Bahamas. :)    
    
    
    tough loss against the reds #Skyvi http://bit.ly/MAlexY     
    
    
    Have you ever noticed that nice peace of mind you feel after you clean & organize your house?  Or do you have to be OCD like me?  LOL    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kXbFzWnbIKg&feature=plcp … http://fb.me/2bwzeLPuK     
    
    
    What Do You Do When Your Back Hurts And The Medications Aren't Working http://fb.me/J0Nigcj3     
    
    
    What Do You Do When Your Back Hurts And The Medications Aren't Working http://fb.me/2qxZBvjIe     
    
    
    http://youtu.be/wTWsVcRt-9k     
    
    
    What Do You Do When You Have Thyroid Symptoms (But Your Labs Are All "Normal)? http://fb.me/1GwllvREN     
    
    
    Got disc problems?  http://tinyurl.com/9d743s5     
    
    
    Got disc problems? http://fb.me/22P2KY9pU     
    
    
    Is A Chiropractor Part of Your Healthcare Team?  http://aweber.com/b/23VhZ    
    
    
    Now accepting new patients.  If you are hurting and in the Bethel Park area give us a call. 412-212-8880    
    
    
    Been injured in a car accident?  Check out this video:  http://tinyurl.com/9zbqnxe     
    
    
    Been in an auto accident? http://fb.me/JaWEYR7U     
    
    
    Want free information about how to get rid of chronic pain? Go to www.redapplewellness.net  and sign up for our free newsletter!    
    
    
    Check out the new & improved website!   http://www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    If you've been hurt in a car accident, you need to check out this video:  http://tinyurl.com/9x99pls     
    
    
    Please check out my new website:  www.redapplewellness.net   Also, please sign up for my free e-mail club to receive great health info!    
    
    
    Want to find out how to get rid of back pain forever?  Visit my website www.redapplewellness.net and sign up for my free e-mail club!    
    
    
    Health does not come from a bottle of pills.  Health comes from lifestyle choices.  Eat well, move well, and get your spine aligned.    
    
    
    You are under the force of gravity 24/7.  If you have abnormal spinal alignment, gravity magnifies the stress placed on your joints.    
    
    
    You need to maintain your spine - just like you need to maintain your teeth, your car, your house, etc..   Maintain it or lose it.    
    
    
    Chronic back pain is typically either due to a movement problem or a motor control stability problem.    
    
    
    For all Obama voters: Early voting for all states has been moved to tonight at 11 pm at the main pier on the Outer Banks in North Carolina.    
    
    
    Restoring motion, alignment & strength is THE #1 best approach for neutralizing chronic, stubborn back pain.    
    
    
    I wanted to share a really cool experience with you.  This is actually pretty typical in my office (but I know... http://fb.me/2benO32nw     
    
    
    If you want to fix chronic lower back pain, one of the most important things is to improve the flexibility in your legs!    
    
    
    Why Most Doctors Miss The Mark With Chronic Pain Syndromes | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/Krzk8wws     
    
    
    Mastery is not a function of genius or talent. It is a function of time and intense focus applied to a particular field of knowledge.    
    
    
    @DennisDMZ Cranial-rectal inversion is a physical deformity affecting liberals.  Fortunately for them it's covered under Obamacare.    
    
    
    @chrisrockozfan Keeping it classy, 'eh Chris?    
    
    
    http://fb.me/DKXv9Pyo    
    
    
    Drug company whistleblower reveals why you cannot trust drug companies!  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog.htm    
    
    
    Go Steelers!  Beat the bolts.    
    
    
    @high_on_glitter I'm more right brain dominant.    
    
    
    Wow, the Steelers really look awful today....    
    
    
    The Red Skins really helped out the Steelers... moreso than the Steelers coaching staff,    
    
    
    My thoughts and most heart felt prayers go out to the families of the victims in CT.    
    
    
    How To Get Rid of Nagging Back Pain Forever With the Latest Breakthrough In Physical Medicine http://fb.me/DGVqDCIt    
    
    
    Dr. Alex Vasquez demonstrates how to make "green brownies"  which are made with organic, whole foods.... http://fb.me/JIHWndQR    
    
    
    Red Apple E-Zine January 2013 http://aweber.com/t/GxcAw     
    
    
    Acute vs. Chronic Back Pain (And What To Do About It) | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/CvScad7m     
    
    
    I would pay $5,000.00 to watch James Harrison tackle Roger Goodell.    
    
    
    Peripheral neuropathy is caused by 80% lifestyle (diet & exercise habits) and 20% genetics.  Change your lifestyle to get rid of PN forever.    
    
    
    Flu season is here.  Here's how to avoid the flu & stay healthy.  http://tinyurl.com/cx4hr2l     
    
    
    Tis the season to be healthy!  If you're feeling run down or have a nagging ache or pain, give us a call. 412-212-8880   - Dr. Kevin Smith    
    
    
    What You Need To Know About Omega 3 Fatty Acids | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/1zvqpbNQr     
    
    
    What You Need To Know About Omega 3 Fatty Acids http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/what-you-need-to-know-about-omega-3-fatty-acids/ … via @ksmithdc    
    
    
    RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog  via @ksmithdc    
    
    
    Who moved my cheese?    
    
    
    It's ironic that Pizza Hut (gluten city) are sponsoring Autism awareness.  That's like Pepsi sponsoring diabetes awareness.    
    
    
    Sweeeet! I earned $103.66 so far doing surveys. http://apps.facebook.com/291958277603640     
    
    
    Red Apple E-Zine April 2013 http://aweber.com/t/6VUkg     
    
    
    This rocks! I got $191.24 so far doing surveys. http://apps.facebook.com/163624457130621     
    
    
    Visit my blog:  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog     
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/?p=415  http://fb.me/EUxuR7XZ     
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/?p=417     
    
    
    http://www.redapplewellness.net/  http://fb.me/2zPkAjQFe     
    
    
    I took my 9 year old son (Daniel) to meet Pittsburgh Pirate Jason Grilli.  Grilli was one of the nicest people ever - and made my son's day!    
    
    
    Gary Moore:  R.I.P.  :(    
    
    
    Let's go Bucs!    
    
    
    Starling Marte is a beast.  With his help, the Pirates are going to snap their losing streak and make it to the playoffs this year!    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery: Google Reader is no longer available. To continue receiving Goog...    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery: Google Reader is no longer available. To continue receiving Goog...    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery: Google Reader is no longer available. To continue receiving Goog...    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery: Google Reader is no longer available. To continue receiving Goog...    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery: Google Reader is no longer available. To continue receiving Goog...    
    
    
    The bucs bats need to wake up.    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts no longer supports RSS delivery    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    Google Alerts RSS delivery is temporarily not available. To keep receiving Google Alerts in the meantime, you c...    
    
    
    11.5 Myths About Chiropractic Exposed!  http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog/archives/320    
    
    
    http://fb.me/GZtdVWgy    
    
    
    @GrillCheese49   Hope you feel better soon, Jason.    
    
    
    Andrew McCutchen for president!    
    
    
    Raise The Jolly Roger!    
    
    
    The problem with our healthcare system isn't about who's going to pay for treatment.   The problem is the treatments themselves.    
    
    
    People are led to believe that they can get a quick fix for the results of a lifetime of poor health choices.    
    
    
    At my sons baseball game.  Seems a bit chilly for an August evening.    
    
    
    It's amazing how much junk you accumulate over the years.  Time to clean out the garage!    
    
    
    Last night I went to see The Aristocrats play (in Pittsburgh).  Guthrie Govan's playing is mind bendingly awesome.  #GuthrieGovan    
    
    
    X-rays to Starling Marte indicate a contusion - no fracture (thank goodness).  Speedy recovery Starling!  Hope to see you back on the field!    
    
    
    Let's go Bucs!  Gimme # 71!    
    
    
    Russell Martin......BOOM!!!!!!!    
    
    
    If 80% of all disease is directly caused by diet, why don't we focus on diet as the cure?    
    
    
    MORE tattoo dos and don'ts, #3 glows! http://bit.ly/18CDJJM     
    
    
    The weirdest stuff out of Japan yet. You won't believe #4 http://bit.ly/1dFZMqj     
    
    
    Bruce Lipton - The Cell Membrane http://fb.me/2mlpFm7LG     
    
    
    Take a second look at these logo fails, I'm laughing so hard at #14. http://bit.ly/1dFZLT8     
    
    
    Disney's got a few new tricks up its sleeve. Pirates 5, Finding Dory, Maleficent- which do you want to see? http://bit.ly/1dFZNdF     
    
    
    The Most Common Cause of Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/bYQchrxkeYA  via @YouTube    
    
    
    How Climate Change May Affect West Nile Spread: According to the Mayo Clinic, taking a daily dose of <a href="... http://bit.ly/15O1BJN     
    
    
    A Guided Meditation On Calmness (VIDEO): ... returning refocused</a> and a little less anxious. Plus, <a href=... http://bit.ly/1eiixBa     
    
    
    The Best CrossFit Someecards: Cameron Diaz maintains those legendary biceps with a workout that includes Cross... http://bit.ly/13OBvsr     
    
    
    How We Can Teach Our Children Mindfulness: ... target="_hplink">decrease stress</a>, <a href="http://www.mayoc... http://bit.ly/1baDSuk     
    
    
    3 Ways To Ward Off Knee Pain: One of the most <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/walking/HQ01612 …" targe... http://bit.ly/13XVViR     
    
    
    Diabetes: Balancing your insulin, medication and exercise ...: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/insul ... http://bit.ly/1gfob2P     
    
    
    Exercise Linked With Decreased Symptoms Of Depression, Review ...: ... help alleviate symptoms of depression, ... http://bit.ly/1gjHhoi     
    
    
    High Blood Pressure In Childhood Could Signal Future Risk: But exercise also improves the strength of your hea... http://bit.ly/14bd4ph     
    
    
    Healthy Lifestyle Changes Could Lengthen Your Telomeres: ... releases endorphins in the brain and relaxes the ... http://bit.ly/1eXRR6A     
    
    
    Cold Sores Linked With Gene Mutation: Although its effects are probably still pretty small, according to Buka,... http://bit.ly/14gNoaS     
    
    
    Statin Use Linked To Cataracts, But Results Are Cloudy: Second, fish like salmon, sardines and albacore tuna a... http://bit.ly/19oDdiO     
    
    
    The Shocking Truth About 9 Foods You Thought Were Vegetarian: Shellac. <strong>What it is:</strong> <a href="h... http://bit.ly/18IJgxR     
    
    
    Superfoods Of The World: ... Mayo Clinic points out that having <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/chol ... http://bit.ly/1gPEHqu     
    
    
    TCA (Kreb's) Cycle Rap - Wilson Lam (Macklemore - Thrift Shop Parody) http://fb.me/2Fciu8mQs     
    
    
    How Chiropractic Adjustments Work http://fb.me/116XNfTA8     
    
    
    Facet Syndrome http://fb.me/39DMjA73S     
    
    
    Various Types of Pain http://fb.me/6kQrZVBuW     
    
    
    People With More Cavities Less Likely To Be Diagnosed With Head ...: Past research has shown that red wine may... http://bit.ly/18WiK4g     
    
    
    Depression Symptoms May Be Improved By Acupuncture Or ...: http://Health.com " target="_hplink">... http://bit.ly/18YyvaN     
    
    
    Welcome To Integrated Metabolic Solutions http://fb.me/1yYEFzKC0     
    
    
    Inflammation and Thyroid Problems http://fb.me/PP4Hlmk3     
    
    
    The Most Common Cause of Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/2ODXy1bRo     
    
    
    Secret #1 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/1vhUwmdli     
    
    
    Secret #2 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/M6ac8MVV     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #3 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/2nHESvQlc     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #4 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Prolactin http://fb.me/OVkXuZSW     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #5 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: Elevated Cortisol http://fb.me/1G7FTmcWJ     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #6 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: TPO Autoimmune Antibodies http://fb.me/6iOQsln4h     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #7 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Thyroglobulin Antibodies http://fb.me/16LLiv8pS     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #8 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms TSH Immunoglobulin http://fb.me/6jQB0Oyvd     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #9 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Autoimmue Attack Against T4 and T3 http://fb.me/2EuCcoXjO     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #10 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: Low Progesterone http://fb.me/6uoGKudMw     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #11 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Low Co Factors http://fb.me/V4GPOElo     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #12 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/3mJeOddPK     
    
    
    Gene Yale, Chicago-Area Apple Grower With 178 Varieties In His ...: has been linked with <a href="http://www.h... http://bit.ly/1fFA3h1     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #13 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Dysbiosis http://fb.me/2nxOyJDlw     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #14 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms 5'D Cytokines http://fb.me/3rOvHqv6Q     
    
    
    Do You Know How Much You Walk In A Day?: <a href="http://www.health.com/health/gallery/0,,20534367_4,00.html …" ... http://bit.ly/14M6sOq     
    
    
    'Feminist Makeup Tutorial' Parody Proves You Can Be A Strong ...: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/va ... http://bit.ly/1h64FGs     
    
    
    Bubonic Plague Still Kills Thousands: The Mayo Clinic reports that the last known <a href="http://www.mayoclin... http://bit.ly/17a8N6F     
    
    
    Sleep custom site - Mayo Clinic: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/sleep-custom-site/MY02525 …">Prescrip... http://bit.ly/19cmoa5     
    
    
    Healthy Breakfast Ideas: 17 Healthy, Autumn-Inspired Recipes ...: ... can also help <a href="http://www.health... http://bit.ly/18dJPCY     
    
    
    Runners: How to Prevent Low Back Pain - Spine-Health http://bit.ly/1bT6iZX     
    
    
    Too Much Stress In Midlife May Lead To Dementia In Older Age ...: ... target="_blank">good health</a>, <a href... http://bit.ly/18IgQZ0     
    
    
    7 Amazing Facts About Tomatoes: This dark leafy green is <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/vegetarian- …... http://bit.ly/18q1sPZ     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #15 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Underconversion due to High Cortisol http://fb.me/13LfjHQ8J     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #16 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Low Peripheral Serotonin http://fb.me/2EhdDUoJd     
    
    
    Kettlebell Training: What You Need To Know: By Joe Vennare for U.S. News Health. Did someone say kettleball? I... http://bit.ly/18slWYk     
    
    
    7 Amazing Facts About Tomatoes: Chia seeds are actually from the Salvia hispanica plant, and have been a part ... http://bit.ly/18q1sPZ     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #17 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms Underconversion dt Low Dopamine http://fb.me/1lpzZrvAb     
    
    
    Exercise Could Help Stroke, Heart Disease Patients Just As Well As ...: Characterized by <a href="http://www.m... http://bit.ly/18QixSd     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #18 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms High 5'D from Testosterone http://fb.me/2IEsDDmM6     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #19 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms TBG http://fb.me/2STLhjSZ0     
    
    
    Texting Linked With Sleep Problems For College Students: Your body temp <a href="http://www.health.com/health/ ... http://bit.ly/17xAGpw     
    
    
    Automobile Accident Injuries What You Need To Know http://fb.me/1OUyd2NbR     
    
    
    Work Comp Injuries What You Need To Know http://fb.me/2xZQhUqkn     
    
    
    Intro To Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic http://fb.me/1ywzsxHFo     
    
    
    Emotional memory affects behavior of persons with Alzheimer's ...: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/e ... http://bit.ly/1aRF9TD     
    
    
    Work-Life Balance Study Shows Personal Choice Is Key To A Good ...: Find a peaceful place near your office and... http://bit.ly/17CbUEz     
    
    
    11.5 Myths About Chiropractic Exposed: http://EzineArticles.com/5899632    
    
    
    The 3 Biggest Dating Dealbreakers For Those Over 50: ... itchiness in the area. According to the Mayo Clinic, ... http://bit.ly/192fwya     
    
    
    6 Famous Faces Touched By Breast Cancer This Year: "I take very good care of myself (mostly because I didn't m... http://bit.ly/1aWHbC5     
    
    
    Heart Problems And Stroke Risk Reduces With Better Sleep: What Not to Do at 3 A.M.</a> <a href="http://www.hea... http://bit.ly/19alGhD     
    
    
    Is Malibu High School's Campus Causing Cancer? Teachers Band ...: However, this type of environment <a href="h... http://bit.ly/17Q57at     
    
    
    Is Malibu High School's Campus Causing Cancer? Teachers Band ...: And a quarter of people say that <a href="ht... http://bit.ly/17Q57at     
    
    
    What To Do When You've Overeaten: Yoshida says that it can also be a great, natural reliever of gas (<a href="... http://bit.ly/19cDuH3     
    
    
    Health Postures Announces New TaskMate Go to Reduce Workers ... http://bit.ly/17SHRZq     
    
    
    AHA: Focus On Prevention, Not Just Treatment, Of Heart Disease: ... cholesterol</a> into the bloodstream, <a h... http://bit.ly/1csfiWm     
    
    
    AHA: Focus On Prevention, Not Just Treatment, Of Heart Disease: ... fruits and vegetables) <a href="http://www... http://bit.ly/1csfiWm     
    
    
    Flavored Water May Be Making Kids Hate Plain Water, Experts Warn: Try drinking it <a href="http://www.health.c... http://bit.ly/19h4nM7     
    
    
    8 Things People Would Rather Have Than Sex: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/hypothyroidism/DS00353 …" ... http://bit.ly/1b9LpX2     
    
    
    What Hair Loss Really Means For Your Health: For men with zinc deficiency, taking <a href="http://www.mayoclin... http://bit.ly/17VOJFE     
    
    
    Preventable Medical Errors: Third Cause of Death in the US http://fb.me/3byag2yt5     
    
    
    Snack Away A Slump: Five cups a day seems to <a href="http://www.health.com/health/article/0,,20409937,00.html …... http://bit.ly/19kvWUE     
    
    
    Pirates,  thank you for a wonderful year.  You battled hard and made the city proud!    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #20 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms | Bethel Park, PA http://fb.me/37HJ5pM3A     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #21 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/1EwXKNoDN     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #22 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/1Agrh0Zfp     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #23 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms http://fb.me/3kX4qnFBR     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #24 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms High Homocysteine http://fb.me/2IYeRsXnY     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #1 Why You Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/ST_Zc6IaMgE?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #1 Why You Have Back Pain http://fb.me/3apptHe1W     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #2 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/FLUKOFw53zk?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    6 Ways to UnDiet Your Thanksgiving: <a href="http://www.health.com/health/gallery/0,,20318484,00.html …">Make yo... http://bit.ly/1cAAZDE     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #2 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/6ue9HSzSc     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #3 Why You STILL Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/ytfmFIK6mkQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #3 Why You STILL Have Back Pain http://fb.me/1EIfcYEry     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #4 Why You STILL Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/sUQ7kL1h7_M?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #4 Why You STILL Have Back Pain http://fb.me/6n9F6psj3     
    
    
    Is Aircraft Noise Bad For Your Health?: ... <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/aerobic-exercise/EP00002 …... http://bit.ly/19nJugv     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #5 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/GoG-C8KVJLE?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #5 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/NT5S8yKA     
    
    
    Saltwater Bacteria In Florida Infects 31 Statewide With 10 Fatalities: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/heal ... http://bit.ly/19qFo77     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #6 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/Rmrws8zf9U4?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #6 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/12qhh4BXQ     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #7 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/V4MFW2Sk7zM?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #7 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/1CbK8Zwur     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #8 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/h2NOMVw8y-U?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #8 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/35M6tRtj2     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #9 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/1JZLIr7jY     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #9 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/EtgusO-zNsI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #10 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Scoliosis: http://youtu.be/eQVKLBRnvn8?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #10 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Scoliosis http://fb.me/6spJaVMJ0     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #11 Why You Still Have Back Pain: http://youtu.be/JE_hDHRRlK0?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #11 Why You Still Have Back Pain http://fb.me/6nME9Nurj     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    5 Surprising Uses For Pumpkin (None Of Which Are Lattes): Although its effects are probably still pretty small... http://bit.ly/19KW0bR     
    
    
    Irisin Molecule Could Help Explain Why Exercise Is Good For The ...: ... help alleviate symptoms of depression... http://bit.ly/1cq5Lg6     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #12 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Hip Problems: http://youtu.be/juw2BKYsjyI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #12 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Hip Problems http://fb.me/Yu7Otr5V     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #13 Why You Still Have Back Pain Vertebral Misalignment: http://youtu.be/kqccXl6_kbk?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Nd26jySHMUE …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #13 Why You Still Have Back Pain Vertebral Misalignment http://fb.me/2ou4HacvF     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UmZsg0sZegU …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #14 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Arthritis: http://youtu.be/ZqYtq-HzkfQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #14 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Arthritis http://fb.me/2JOiyIook     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FMXzUWCQyus …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #15 Why You Still Have Back Pain Pregnancy: http://youtu.be/opt9IbJ69yg?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #15 Why You Still Have Back Pain Pregnancy http://fb.me/Ya5oyPVm     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HDf0x_dA_JM …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #16 Why You Still Have Back Pain Asymmetries: http://youtu.be/smbuUtIwczU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #16 Why You Still Have Back Pain Asymmetries http://fb.me/1Ev8O9T7i     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #17 Why You Still Have Back Pain Spondylolisthesis: http://youtu.be/bpKOWyzvTnc?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2LS_3sTMBNs …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #17 Why You Still Have Back Pain Spondylolisthesis http://fb.me/MLqdp45n     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iyQpddzgkCM …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #18 Why You Still Have Back Pain Ergonomics: http://youtu.be/N_KwCjk-nPU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #18 Why You Still Have Back Pain Ergonomics http://fb.me/Ng6LmMNA     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X0PLfVHaIFI …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Hidden Secret #19 Why You Still Have Back Pain Abnormal Spinal Curves: http://youtu.be/dTV6mLU_hRQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #19 Why You Still Have Back Pain Abnormal Spinal Curves http://fb.me/MnRZUXYJ     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fJiOoYNrUjY …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #20 Why You Still Have Back Pain Short Leg: http://youtu.be/6Gx9vV0IYh8?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #20 Why You Still Have Back Pain Short Leg http://fb.me/MMpuWMux     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gG6g1nZWZnY …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dPy-K0d6DoU …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PPb1-Pd8v5Y …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-lZdPHMdFIg …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PyFRYRd-etY …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QyJ3kwZjeJE …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ldi1OilauVQ …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d-W4FWfONLs …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2oZFKqG_kyU …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AXM4pK57Y8A …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wHXmY76FcKk …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #7 Why You Still Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/ldi1OilauVQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #8 Why You Still Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/d-W4FWfONLs?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #3 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/PyFRYRd-etY?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #4 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/PPb1-Pd8v5Y?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #5 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/-lZdPHMdFIg?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #1 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/dPy-K0d6DoU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UKanQ6GrQ78 …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PbOHEUDbA8w …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xAE_45LQaJM …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5qVZQYK3Uu8 …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ke8uukroFs4 …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #15 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/UKanQ6GrQ78?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #11 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/xAE_45LQaJM?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #9 Why You Still Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/wHXmY76FcKk?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #10 Why You Still Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/AXM4pK57Y8A?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #6 Why You Still Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/2oZFKqG_kyU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #14 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/PbOHEUDbA8w?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5GE_a1SJyIs …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kd5OqrRx6_U …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mkCM6_Mv9eQ …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tis8-iL_xX8 …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sYIuqAY4L3c …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JD2qCePIHsQ …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EBFMBFADdkI …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=G1KEDgHw1YI …    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LtfSFCRW0SA …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #19 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/LtfSFCRW0SA?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #22 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/5GE_a1SJyIs?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #18 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/sYIuqAY4L3c?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #20 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/Tis8-iL_xX8?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #23 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/kd5OqrRx6_U?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #2 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/QyJ3kwZjeJE?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #16 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/EBFMBFADdkI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #21 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/mkCM6_Mv9eQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #12 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/5qVZQYK3Uu8?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #24 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/G1KEDgHw1YI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #13 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/Ke8uukroFs4?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #17 Why You STILL Have Low Thyroid Symptoms: http://youtu.be/JD2qCePIHsQ?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    Mindfulness-Based Stress Reduction Could Help Lower Blood ...: But exercise also improves the strength of your... http://bit.ly/1a0ULWd     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.redapplewellness.net     
    
    
    Just uploaded a video in YouTube. Check: http://www.integratedmetabolic.com     
    
    
    @Richie_Kotzen Caught your show with The Winery Dogs @ the Alter Bar in Pittsburgh.  Loved it!  Thanks for coming to the 'Burgh.    
    
    
    @mholland5001 Hi Mike,  thanks for digging my tweet about The Winery Dogs gig.  Please follow me back on Twitter! :)    
    
    
    I'm shooting more new videos to teach the world about chiropractic.    
    
    
    West Nile Virus In LA Claims Three Lives: According to the Mayo Clinic, taking a daily dose of <a href="http:/... http://bit.ly/1bU6eGr     
    
    
    How Playing Tetris Taught Me This Valuable Life Skill: ... of depression or bipolar disorder, and <a href="htt... http://bit.ly/19whWqo     
    
    
    Birth Control And Acne: What Going On (And Off) The Pill Does To ...: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/healt ... http://bit.ly/1cY45ut     
    
    
    http://Mercola.com  Introduces a New Product: Pure Power Protein Bars http://bit.ly/1d4DjR6     
    
    
    Have you ever noticed that in pharmacies, they sell stuff that causes disease in the front of the store and the cures in the back?    
    
    
    Congratulations to the St. Louis Cardinals on winning game two in the World Series.    
    
    
    Did you know asymmetries in your body can lead to back pain?  Check out my video to learn more.   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=smbuUtIwczU …    
    
    
    @Mal_Baaby I agree - having back pain isn't normal.  I have a lot of cool videos about back pain.  Check them out!    
    
    
    @TODAYshow #WhatWorksForMe   I'm a back pain expert and have a series of videos you may find useful.  http://www.youtube.com/user/ksmithdc/videos …    
    
    
    @TwistedCheer I'm a back pain expert and have a series of videos on the topic.  Check them out.  http://www.youtube.com/user/ksmithdc/videos …    
    
    
    Listed myself under #chiropractic interests on http://wefollow.com/ksmithdc     
    
    
    Going to a continuing education seminar this weekend - nutrigenomic therapies for musculoskeletal health.    
    
    
    Vancouver Tea Festival Brings Products, Demonstrations To Town: Researchers found that <a href="http://www.hea... http://bit.ly/1d9ptgd     
    
    
    Herpes Virus: Steroids, Statins, Painkillers, and Chemotherapy may ...: (2) http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/s ... http://bit.ly/19Id81i     
    
    
    Today I attended a continuing education seminar to learn the latest advancements in detoxification and in reducing inflammation.    
    
    
    Weight gain, the inability to loose weight (even with diet & exercise), low energy & depression all could be due to thyroid problems.    
    
    
    I have uploaded numerous videos to show how you can get rid of back pain.  http://www.youtube.com/user/ksmithdc     
    
    
    Simple Physical Activity Can Improve Heart Health: One of the most <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/w ... http://bit.ly/16HldFs     
    
    
    If you're suffering with chronic back or neck pain, you should be under the care of a chiropractor.  Get amazing results without pills.    
    
    
    Did you know medical doctors are the 3rd leading cause of death in the U.S. (right behind cancer & heart disease)?    
    
    
    I met a person who smokes, eats fast food, drinks sodas, and takes 6 prescription drugs per day.  But she's skeptical about chiropractic.    
    
    
    If health came from a bottle of pills, we would have been born with them.    
    
    
    Sheryl Crow, Olivia Newton-John And More Celebs On Finding Out ...: "I take very good care of myself (mostly b... http://bit.ly/1dPK6kC     
    
    
    Why Am I Injured? http://bit.ly/1cnOIuc     
    
    
    Put Some Evil Villains on Your Desktop http://bit.ly/1aEXcft     
    
    
    Water Temperature, Word Layout, and Fresh Caulk http://bit.ly/1drirnc     
    
    
    CreativeLIVE!!!! http://bit.ly/1aJL0fb     
    
    
    Paleo Lifestyle and Fitness Podcast, Episode 61 http://bit.ly/1aJL0ff     
    
    
    The Roundup http://bit.ly/19aWGqU     
    
    
    How to Create a $4,000 Per Month Muse in 5 Days (Plus: How to Get Me As Your Mentor) http://bit.ly/1cnoNTA     
    
    
        
    
    
    12 Indispensable Mindful Living Tools http://bit.ly/1aDTYsK     
    
    
    The Best Way to Save Your Time http://bit.ly/1aDHbIw     
    
    
    6 Common Turkish Get-up Technique Mistakes http://bit.ly/1co62zj     
    
    
    Rethinking Stress: It Could Save Your Life http://bit.ly/1dOCa37     
    
    
    Happy Halloween everybody!  Please be safe tonight.  And remember - all the Mallo Cups and Reese's Cups need to go to Mom & Dad.    
    
    
    The modern system of medicine is not health care - it's disease care.  The entire focus of what they do has nothing to do with wellness.    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #21 Why You Still Have Back Pain - Retrolisthesis: http://youtu.be/c8RzicV-8SU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #21 Why You STILL Have Back Pain.    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #22 Why You Still Have Back Pain Herniated Disc: http://youtu.be/B8CdlVbi8nI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #22 Why You STILL Have Back Pain    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #23 Why You Still Have Back Pain: Disc Degeneration: http://youtu.be/Xay5QDCllwI?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #24 Why You Still Have Back Pain: Stenosis: http://youtu.be/0LDeOB_Q_fA?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #25 Why You Still Have Back Pain: Fibromyalgia: http://youtu.be/moZrodZWgKo?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    9 Top Foods To Boost Your Brainpower http://bit.ly/1cnXmJr     
    
    
    Hidden Secret Why You STILL Have Back Pain
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xay5QDCllwI …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #24 Why You STILL Have Back Pain
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0LDeOB_Q_fA …    
    
    
    Hidden Secret #25 Why You STILL Have Back Pain
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=moZrodZWgKo …    
    
    
    Kraft To Remove Artificial Food Dye From 3 Mac & Cheese Products http://bit.ly/1aKREQJ     
    
    
    Testing the Ankle to Prevent Reinjury http://bit.ly/1csuEHm     
    
    
    Why I Read (+ a Dozen Book Recommendations) http://bit.ly/1aOIBjq     
    
    
    One of the most satisfying things about what I do occurs when my patients awaken to the fact that they can get healthy without meds.    
    
    
    The key to health is by practicing a wellness based lifestyle.  Eat right, move right, think right, sleep right.    
    
    
    Genetic Roulette—The Gamble of Our Lives http://bit.ly/19llWuD     
    
    
    Far too many people get bent out of shape over the outcome of a sporting event.  It's just sports, folks.    
    
    
    Aren't you sick and tired of seeing drug ad after drug ad on TV?  No, I'm not going to ask my doctor about XYX drug.  Enough already!    
    
    
    I just saw a TV commercial where they now say taking Lipitor can cause diabetes.  Now they'll sell me another drug for the diabetes!    
    
    
    Your body's fat cells store toxins.  This is why after you burn fat you can feel a little sick afterward.  So be sure to drink lots of water    
    
    
    Doing a 28 day detox will give you more energy, a clearer mind, a better night's sleep and get rid of chronic pain.    
    
    
    Tomorrow is election day!  So remember to get out there to vote early and vote often! :)    
    
    
    @JoeVennare My pleasure.    
    
    
    Heart Specialist Calls for Major Repositioning on Saturated Fat, as it’s NOT the Cause of Heart Disease http://bit.ly/1cF5buj     
    
    
    Ask the RD: All About Food Combining http://bit.ly/1aZN01l     
    
    
    My strength is outta control and I’m hardly trying http://bit.ly/1b0Ab8Q     
    
    
    Lyrical Learning, & Why We Learn Habits Wrong http://bit.ly/1cMqudi     
    
    
    Richie Kotzen: More Than A Fast Guitar Player http://shar.es/IQojU  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Just out of curiosity - has ANYONE in the history of mankind EVER redone their bathroom and stayed on budget? :)    
    
    
    Did you know diet soda can cause weight gain every bit as much as regular soda?  I stopped drinking Diet Pepsi and lost 40 pounds!    
    
    
    Big Pharma spends $1 billion dollars on direct to consumer advertisements in order to brainwash us to buy their pills.  It needs to end.    
    
    
    Helicopter Passenger Plunges To His Death, May Have Committed ... http://bit.ly/1cUJG8Y     
    
    
    4 Important Life Lessons from the Story of Eike Batista http://bit.ly/1b91EVP     
    
    
    Developing Selfless Compassion http://bit.ly/1cWNZ3y     
    
    
    @justinegeiszler Hi, please follow me back on Twitter.  Nice to meet you!    
    
    
    @PBKAppraiser  So long as we continue to prioritize profits over health and wellness, I fear what you're saying is true.    
    
    
    Two Exciting Alzheimer’s Advances: A Novel Early Detection Test Using Peanut Butter, and a Study Evaluating Co... http://bit.ly/1bcpXAy     
    
    
    The Biggest Medical Discovery of Our Lifetimes—Finding the Cure for Chronic Disease http://bit.ly/19J9iGe     
    
    
    Hay Fever Affects More Kids In The Southern US, Study Finds http://bit.ly/1d7MsaQ     
    
    
    Isolation vs. Movement Patterns http://bit.ly/19QxVRl     
    
    
    Winter Got You Feeling Dry and Itchy? Virtually All the Rescue Remedies Can Be Found in Your Kitchen http://bit.ly/1dfxRu6     
    
    
    It's been said before but it's worth repeating:  Your attitude determines your altitude.    
    
    
    Make It Your Job http://bit.ly/19WLm29     
    
    
    Dear Mark: Resistant Starch, Zinc Deficiency, and Something New http://bit.ly/1buECXK     
    
    
    Did you know chiropractic care is the most effective, fastest acting and safest treatment for back pain?    
    
    
    We're supposed to get snow.  Already?  Ugh.    
    
    
    Measles Reports in America: What Does It Mean? http://bit.ly/1bxAZAq     
    
    
    Why You Should Never Eat High Fructose Corn Syrup http://bit.ly/1ci4XbO     
    
    
    Circle of Iron http://bit.ly/1bqQKLo     
    
    
    Self-Discipline in 5 Sentences http://bit.ly/1a4MVuX     
    
    
    If you are taking a statin drug because you think high cholesterol is bad, you are grossly misinformed and your doctors are lying to you.    
    
    
    Common Insecticides May Be Linked to Kids' Behavior Problems http://bit.ly/1cqpXNC     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 1 http://bit.ly/1bFFsRF     
    
    
    What Exactly Is Cheese Powder, Anyway? (VIDEO) http://bit.ly/1eP26Mp     
    
    
    Being Your Best: The Key Mindset of Constant Improvement http://bit.ly/1cy8HWJ     
    
    
    Surprising Foods with More Sugar Than a Krispy Kreme Doughnut http://bit.ly/1bBFxHN     
    
    
    'Rethink Your Drink' Campaign Helps Battle Hawaii Teen Obesity http://bit.ly/1dCNyvA     
    
    
    The Promise of Adult Stem Cells in Disease Management, Anti-Aging, and Life Extension http://bit.ly/18Fnv3c     
    
    
    How To Eat Well and Feel Well for Thanksgiving and Christmas http://bit.ly/1dd50uu     
    
    
    How Creativity Works, & How to Do It http://bit.ly/1bUwhwT     
    
    
    No Country For Old Men http://bit.ly/17MdMbc     
    
    
    The Do-Anywhere Workout (VIDEO) http://bit.ly/1dkiuVw     
    
    
    Jealousy & Suffering http://bit.ly/17J00WS     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 2 http://bit.ly/1aBT5D9     
    
    
    Hugh Jackman Treated For Skin Cancer: What Is Basal Cell ... http://bit.ly/1fqN9Al     
    
    
    The Necessary Art of Subtraction http://bit.ly/1bY111J     
    
    
    How the Buteyko Breathing Method Can Improve Your Health and Fitness http://bit.ly/190sImh     
    
    
    Optimizing Your Life One Move at a Time http://bit.ly/1i7R1rW     
    
    
    What Nutritionists Serve at Thanksgiving http://bit.ly/1aMV2wq     
    
    
    When You Run Out of Ideas http://bit.ly/Ih6SF0     
    
    
    The Environmental Costs of Corn-Based Ethanol http://bit.ly/1jEe60X     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 3 http://bit.ly/1ewQw5X     
    
    
    Yes, Cigarettes ARE Making Your Skin Age Faster http://bit.ly/1iOTGVy     
    
    
    Peaking and Assessment as Preparation for the SFG http://bit.ly/1jFU4mN     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 4 http://bit.ly/IoEH7e     
    
    
    Why It's Not The End Of The World When You Go Overboard On ... http://bit.ly/1aVc7EL     
    
    
    Finding Focus http://bit.ly/1jFPAwx     
    
    
    Feeling Generally Dissatisfied and “Not Happy”? How to Nip Subclinical Depression in the Bud http://bit.ly/Ilof6X     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 5 http://bit.ly/1eD3H5k     
    
    
    How Alcohol Boosts Breast Cancer Risk in Young Women http://bit.ly/1brcPv9     
    
    
    How I Learned to Stop Procrastinating, & Love Letting Go http://bit.ly/1buP1GI     
    
    
    We Tried It: Lacey Stone's Booty Camp Class | Anna Almendrala http://bit.ly/1inOVEw     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 7 http://bit.ly/1jcbHgz     
    
    
    Hope everyone had a happy and healthy holiday weekend!   Now it's time to get back to work and be productive!    
    
    
    Ask the RD: Nutrition for Better Sleep and Gaining Weight on Paleo http://bit.ly/1isRGVh     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 8 http://bit.ly/1jhotdV     
    
    
    An excerpt from: Kettlebell Simple & Sinister http://bit.ly/1jhMhOy     
    
    
    Struggles with My Morning Internet Fast http://bit.ly/1eWndKo     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 9 http://bit.ly/1eWpgy6     
    
    
    Rick Warren, Daniel, Amen and Mark Hyman MD Huff Post Live http://bit.ly/1iCIDks     
    
    
    Eat This! Using Faith to Conquer Problems with Food http://bit.ly/1eZcVsN     
    
    
    Zoraida Sambolin Exiting CNN http://bit.ly/1bknIgM     
    
    
    Never Eat These FrankenFats http://bit.ly/1juaVM0     
    
    
    What’s Causing the Rise in ADHD? http://bit.ly/1cZac0D     
    
    
    Movement Principle # 10 http://bit.ly/1f3I91Y     
    
    
    Heart of the Matter—How We Got So Far Down the Wrong Track in Our Efforts to Prevent Heart Disease http://bit.ly/1d7JfI9     
    
    
    The Best Functional Exercises in the World http://bit.ly/1kni66q     
    
    
    5 Health Benefits Of Peppermint http://bit.ly/1knro29     
    
    
    Magnesium—The Missing Link to Better Health http://bit.ly/1bs8d6t     
    
    
    Dick Cavett: The Worst Thing To Say To Someone Who's Depressed ... http://bit.ly/1fhxJvX     
    
    
    How to Deal with Loneliness: 6 Essential Tips http://bit.ly/1dpHO85     
    
    
    16 Surprising Lessons from My First 50-Mile Ultramarathon http://bit.ly/1fkiq5t     
    
    
    8 Sickening Facts About Flame Retardants http://bit.ly/1bCnphw     
    
    
    FMS Featured on BT Winnipeg http://bit.ly/1kAnof0     
    
    
    Want More Tolerant Kids? Keep Them Away from the TV http://bit.ly/1ds60XB     
    
    
    13 Ways the Holidays Can Ruin Your Looks - ABC News http://bit.ly/JjV31j     
    
    
    Should You Run With A Cold? http://bit.ly/1funLHB     
    
    
    A Method to Find Balance http://bit.ly/1kGANCm     
    
    
    How Biological Farming Can Transform Your Food Supply for the Better http://bit.ly/1dChjwh     
    
    
    The Flu Shot: Helpful or Harmful http://bit.ly/1fz5xor     
    
    
    Unethical Journal Retraction Fuels Mistrust in GMO Science http://bit.ly/1bWcorj     
    
    
    The Importance of Primitive Patterns http://bit.ly/1jfUlSw     
    
    
    Build a Barbell Military Press on a Kettlebell Foundation http://bit.ly/1kf7kBU     
    
    
    Big Pharma & The AMA Continue To Lie To The Public About Vitamins & Supplements    
    
    
    Are Multivitamins Worthless?   Big Pharma Wants You To Believe So!
http://www.redapplewellness.net/blog.htm     
    
    
    Family Gatherings: The Ultimate Mindfulness Training Ground http://bit.ly/1khNaY0     
    
    
    Santa Does The Jolliest Parkour Ever http://bit.ly/1dPA0wA     
    
    
    Things Every Man Should Own http://bit.ly/1jmAbGC     
    
    
    Cell Phone Use Linked to Lower Grades, Anxiety, and Much Worse... http://bit.ly/1dQnjS8     
    
    
    The Calm Approach http://bit.ly/1cNtpAB     
    
    
    Western Movement http://bit.ly/1e70cmr     
    
    
    Plus Size Barbie On Modeling Site Sparks Debate Over Body Image ... http://bit.ly/1cOrLin     
    
    
    StrongFirst Roadwork http://bit.ly/1ctgPfe     
    
    
    3 Things You Should Do to Live with Inner Peace http://bit.ly/1cuVjGM     
    
    
    How to Help Fluoride Toxicity http://bit.ly/1cu1dIp     
    
    
    3 Stress-Busters That Will Help You Keep A Jolly Attitude This Holiday http://bit.ly/1e8OnfE     
    
    
    Essential Zen Habits of 2013 http://bit.ly/1jPGNNS     
    
    
    Fermenting Foods—One of the Easiest and Most Creative Aspects of Making Food from Scratch http://bit.ly/1lqkOIP     
    
    
    Ask the Readers: What Lessons Have You Learned in 2013? http://bit.ly/1d2wVaC     
    
    
    12 Changes for 2014 http://bit.ly/1k0wuqk     
    
    
    The Biggest Diet Mistake People Make After New Year's (VIDEO) http://bit.ly/1d4YeAW     
    
    
    The Way You Carry Your Strength Matters http://bit.ly/19Gt1TV     
    
    
    Psoriasis battle of CNN anchor Zain Verjee - http://CNN.com  http://bit.ly/1dbxOxz     
    
    
    Empowering Your HDL http://bit.ly/1d1bTP1     
    
    
    Can Food Affect Your Mood? http://bit.ly/1gpcWXP     
    
    
    You Probably Don't Have Bipolar Disorder (Or One Of These 7 Other ... http://bit.ly/1gtOdS9     
    
    
    How to Make This Year Your Best Year Ever http://bit.ly/1dfppcA     
    
    
    Stateless Mindset http://bit.ly/1di0bdt     
    
    
    I'm tired of Jeff Reed's off-field behavior and on-field incompetence.  It's time for him to go.    
    
    
    Good health habits leads to good health.  Poor health habits leads to poor health.  Eat clean, exercise & get your spine aligned!    
    
    
    Do you want to live a pain-free lifestyle with tons of energy?  Check out my blog for free health info!   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Did you know posture affects respiration, mood, energy, digestion, and the function of your nervous system?   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Chronic back & neck pain is due to problems related to motion, alignment & strength.  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    @Melissa_Ott If you're still hungry, it's an indication you're eating the wrong types of foods.  Focus on foods with high fiber.    
    
    
    I went into McDonalds to get a cup of coffee.  Saw a very obese woman order a McShamrock Shake & an apple pie. For BREAKFAST.  Wow.    
    
    
    Muscle relaxers & Ibuprofen are NOT the solution for back pain!   But that's what your M.D. will give you.    www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    You are either moving forward or backward.  Focus on constant and never ending improvement in everything you do.    
    
    
    The "Foundation of Health" = Diet, Exercise, Chiropractic & Stress Management.  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    How To Get Rid of Nagging Back Pain Forever With the Latest Breakthrough In Physical Medicine: http://EzineArticles.com/5256325    
    
    
    http://fb.me/O1yFJtf0    
    
    
    http://fb.me/TXaj4bms    
    
    
    Hoping the Steelers can get their mojo back after the shellacking Tom Brady & the Patriots put on them.    
    
    
    Sometimes it's worth it to farm out annoying projects to other people. :)    
    
    
    My 1,000th tweet!  Hurray!  I think I'll take the rest of the day off, eat steak and drink beer.    
    
    
    7.5 Facts About Headaches: http://EzineArticles.com/6070514    
    
    
    I believe the Bethel Park school board and the teachers owe me and my family (especially my kids) an apology.    
    
    
    Happy Easter!  Enjoy your holiday feast.  And don't forget to take your supplements & drink plenty of water.   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Hey - only two more weeks of Daddy Daycare (all thanks to the Bethel Park Teachers Union).    
    
    
    VIDEO: Fibromyalgia Solutions | Dr. Kevin Smith http://tmogul.com/tweet/binoz    
    
    
    Sodium Potassium Ratio: The best way for me to learn is to understand the logic behind a lesson. I need to comp.. http://bit.ly/72jZSo    
    
    
    In pain help.For the past four months l been losing weight,pain ...: ... that's causing the problem. http:/.. http://bit.ly/5E6IrN    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- How To Have More Energy | Dr. Kevin Smith | Bethel Park, PA http://bit.ly/67JiiK    
    
    
    VIDEO: How To Have More Energy http://tmogul.com/tweet/_f7bb    
    
    
    The fundamentals of health:  hydration, nutrition, exercise, spinal alignment, elimination & stress management.  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Hypnosis MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthhypnosisMY01020Hypnosisa. Guidelines for sites linking .. http://bit.ly/6nqzIz    
    
    
    Obama Hails 60th Senate Vote For Health Care - Health News Story ...: WASHINGTON -- Jubilant Democrats locked i.. http://bit.ly/6DuxNk    
    
    
    any post op gastric bypass patients with complications?: Here?s all about my surgeon? http://obesityhelp.com/mo.. http://bit.ly/5UQ3CK    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: jblevins.org ... http://bit.ly/7jCzWt    
    
    
    Top 50 healing herbs you can grow in your own garden | Health Informer: Medicine in the modern days certainly w.. http://bit.ly/4Z0fRE    
    
    
    Twitter / @flucoblog/fluco - Following http://bit.ly/4PePXW    
    
    
        
    
    
    How health lobbyists influenced reform bill -- chicagotribune.com: David Nexon had a big problem. An early vers.. http://bit.ly/8cN16E    
    
    
    Cyclothymic Disorder « LIVING IN STIGMA: Cyclothymia or cyclothymic disorder, is a chronic mood disorder that r.. http://bit.ly/6nD3D4    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: Gay Rights - Change.org · BY MICHAEL A. JONES... http://bit.ly/83SNTG    
    
    
    Lucia Chiropractic Clinic 的链接| Facebook http://bit.ly/5flnmq    
    
    
    The Official Website of Michele Bardsley » Blog Archive » 'Tis the ...: Commercials, newscasts, and signage.. http://bit.ly/5M8wup    
    
    
    Weil And Sea Salt: (http://www.prevention.com/cda/article/ask-dr-weil/ 35adafcc42a18110vgnvcm10000013281eac____.. http://bit.ly/6ewrBx    
    
    
    Dr Davis' Back & Wrist Pain Blog: Can Osteoporosis Be Prevented ... http://bit.ly/4NEbzG    
    
    
    2 Ways to Help Thinning Hair - Dr. Weil's Weekend Tip: If you want to improve your physical and mental fitn.. http://bit.ly/8C5Swc    
    
    
    Hepatitis: (December 17, 2008) Mayo Clinic. Toxic hepatitis. Available online at http://www .mayoclinic.com/hea.. http://bit.ly/8KOIx7    
    
    
    I'm ready for spring.  Who's with me?    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: History was made Friday, December 18, when Was.. http://bit.ly/5MTlb3    
    
    
    Six Until Me.: Living at the Joslin Clinic.: Last Friday, Chris and I (and BSparl) were at Joslin all day long... http://bit.ly/8xp1KC    
    
    
    Acupuncture - MayoClinic.com: National Center for Complementary and Alternative Medicine. http://nccam.nih.gov .. http://bit.ly/6YdhH0    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: By Evan Wolfson · Introduction. On the histori.. http://bit.ly/7ySy0O    
    
    
    Missoula Chiropractor-Transformation Chiropractic - Watch Video ... http://bit.ly/5QIu2g    
    
    
    [DOC] chiropractic billing ar-sa http://bit.ly/6pvVda    
    
    
    Paleo in a Nutshell Part 1: Food http://fb.me/XulRkT9a    
    
    
    KC-Blogs: Sodium Diet: On Thursday the doctor told me my sodium and chloride levels were well below normal, and.. http://bit.ly/84oeBl    
    
    
    Twitter Trackbacks for 11 Holiday Health Hazards to Avoid Health ...: First Tweet 2 hours ago. clarkmemorial Cl.. http://bit.ly/6iPfSs    
    
    
    Mayo Clinic - Mayo Announces Seasonal, H1N1 Vaccine Information: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.org/new.. http://bit.ly/6umkHv    
    
    
    Twitter Brooksie Ash Chiropractic and ADHDhttp http://bit.ly/7Euidk    
    
    
    Spas of Life - Healthy Living and Travel: Healthy Giving Ideas: Giving gifts to others is a fundamental activit.. http://bit.ly/89q1RX    
    
    
    Tay Moss - Ninja Priest: William Henry Moss: Here's my little guy, William Henry Moss. We'll call him &.. http://bit.ly/7Et0Kj    
    
    
    Links on "Fosston Chiropractic Clinic, P.A." | Facebook http://bit.ly/51wOGF    
    
    
    Turmeric Tea Recipe: (http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/art02833/turmeric-tea). Turmeric tea – milk & honey . thi.. http://bit.ly/6a9bHs    
    
    
    Executive Express Chiropractic-San Francisco CA 的链接| Facebook http://bit.ly/5zZAba    
    
    
    FOXNews.com - Senate Democrats Work to Advance Health Bill ...: Democratic senators worked toward making health.. http://bit.ly/5c0sOO    
    
    
    Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic:  Opening in Bethel Park, PA  12/29/09   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Oh, Susanica!: Back home with our two boys: Susanne + Monica = Susanica---Welcome! A bit about us...Monica (the.. http://bit.ly/5u2PFY    
    
    
    My new office will be open Tuesday, December 29.  It'll be located at 2409 South Park Rd. in Bethel Park (near the entrance to South Park).    
    
    
    Chiropractor, but no pain? | Chiropractor Search Results http://bit.ly/6cuO2l    
    
    
    Unhealthy Holiday Drinks - Dr Weil's Daily Health Tips - Natural ...: Dr. Weil's ground-breaking new pr.. http://bit.ly/8YmsNJ    
    
    
    Why the Day After Christmas Is The Worst Day For Your Heart: Related document httpwwwhealthcomhealthconditionar.. http://bit.ly/6BwB3C    
    
    
    sher's corner: Injured, ugh!: I think that I have tennis elbow. I have been experiencing pain in my elbow a.. http://bit.ly/7sI3q0    
    
    
    OneRiot.com - DE Pediatrician Charged With Sex Abuse: This revised and extended new edition retains the feature.. http://bit.ly/7kmA5q    
    
    
    Science-Based Medicine » Communicating with the Locked-In http://bit.ly/8i3B7h    
    
    
    Winter Issue of Discovery's Edge: http://discoverysedge.mayo.edu/de09-4-first-tuberculosis-dru g-spotlight... http://bit.ly/5QEmnH    
    
    
    Nutrition and Wellness Bytes: Mindful Eating: How to get started: When some people hear mindful eating, they mi.. http://bit.ly/4Lzvcg    
    
    
    9 Tips From Celebrity Chefs for Heart-Healthy Cooking - Healthy ...: Turn lean ground beef into delicious comfo.. http://bit.ly/6uDWsk    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: Pope's comments on homosexuality must not .. http://bit.ly/8Jx6sY    
    
    
    Links on "Platinum Chiropractic" | Facebook http://bit.ly/8rEmVN    
    
    
    Sea Salt Hypertension: (http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/qaa400277/sea-salt-flush) ... m.d., at the hypertension cen.. http://bit.ly/6oIHca    
    
    
    Red Hot Chili Peppers Nerves Study: (http://www.biography.com/articles/the-red-hot-chili-peppers-380598) ... fu.. http://bit.ly/92PVjr    
    
    
    ChiroOrg Blog – For Chiropractic and Chiropractors. » Clinical ... http://bit.ly/6Mat9y    
    
    
    walking - Jumptags from SaraAdams: Walking: The Best Exercise - Dr. Weil. Dr. Weil on walking. http://www.drwei.. http://bit.ly/5VENg0    
    
    
    Long-Acting Zyprexa Approved - US News and World Report: U.S. News and NCQA review over 700 health insurance pl.. http://bit.ly/8VgpDY    
    
    
    Heart Health Diet And Recipe: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com /health /heart-healthy-recipes /re0009.. http://bit.ly/4N7IFL    
    
    
    HawkeyeReport.com - Message Boards http://bit.ly/90AaFr    
    
    
    Executive Express Chiropractic-San Francisco CA 的链接| Facebook http://bit.ly/7j4fIV    
    
    
    Healthy diet: End the guesswork with these nutrition guidelines ...: You're trying to eat a healthy diet, b.. http://bit.ly/7lUyUa    
    
    
    Holidays Bring Stress, Pains to Many; Rivano Chiropractic Health ... http://bit.ly/4rRieG    
    
    
    Merry Christmas everybody!    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: I have been so saddened by Pope Benedict XVI&#.. http://bit.ly/5ypOpP    
    
    
    It always amazes me at the people who are scared of chiropractors - but not the surgeon.  You know - the guy with all the knives?    
    
    
    Women's Heart Attacks Just Like Men's Dr Weil's Weekly Bulletin: Conventional medical wisdom holds .. http://bit.ly/6YYaXc    
    
    
    Vital Votes Health Blog - Natural Health Articles by Dr. Mercola -: Vital Votes Health Blog - Natural Health Ar.. http://bit.ly/6XxDCH    
    
    
    White tongue - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/white-tongue/MY01011">.. http://bit.ly/8e49Si    
    
    
    Recipe With Thiamin B1: Recipes, tools and other helpful information; we do not share your e-mail address href=.. http://bit.ly/8mImaX    
    
    
    Back Pain Plan | News http://bit.ly/7Bx9So    
    
    
    any one out there has tried chiropractic for slip disc problem ... http://bit.ly/4rVW50    
    
    
    Plum Texan: The spirit: If you didn't believe in Christmas miracles before, perhaps you will now: Hello! I&.. http://bit.ly/5xmSaK    
    
    
    Broccoli Penne: (http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/rcp00171) ... Contributed by: dhanyaka dr. weil's optimum h.. http://bit.ly/6QPzkX    
    
    
    ChiroACCESS: MANTIS Database Overview http://bit.ly/8VWO4r    
    
    
    Rhythm method for natural family planning MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthrhythmmethodMY01003Rhy.. http://bit.ly/69d2bu    
    
    
    Science-Based Medicine » Multiple Sclerosis and Irrational Exuberance http://bit.ly/4r6rJs    
    
    
    Your San Francisco Chiropractor Has Some Injury Prevention Tips ... http://bit.ly/7BW0xe    
    
    
    treatments for influenza - Bloglines: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/bird-flu/DS00566/DSECTION=treatments-and.. http://bit.ly/4HkGzM    
    
    
    Possible $100 Million Grant Doesn't Settle UConn Hospital's Future ...: Two days after US Sen. Christop.. http://bit.ly/5iMdZH    
    
    
    Spinach Vitamin B: (http://www.vitaminsdiary.com/fruits-vegetables/spinach.htm) ... nuts, pork, potatoes, and s.. http://bit.ly/5gSDoa    
    
    
    Bloglines | People Subscribed To This Feed Also Read: Vital Votes Health Blog - Natural Health Articles by Dr. .. http://bit.ly/7iLNKL    
    
    
    Salt Pipe For Breathing Problems: (http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/qaa400600/using-a-salt-pipe-for-copd.html); The .. http://bit.ly/4Hfgn4    
    
    
    7.5 Facts About Headaches http://aweber.com/t/2NAEI    
    
    
    A look back at 2009's top nutrition topics - MayoClinic.com: Subscribe to receive the latest updates on hea.. http://bit.ly/6JtqGU    
    
    
    Middle East and Terrorism: A Year After the Gaza War: The ...: by Stephanie L. Freid. The rockets may have stop.. http://bit.ly/6gyeRk    
    
    
    Want to get FREE tips & ideas on how to feel better & get rid of chronic pain? Sign up for our newsletter!  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    mayoclinic.com Site Information and Statistics | Protrackr: Dmoz Title: MayoClinic. Dmoz Description: Clinical .. http://bit.ly/91ySxI    
    
    
    Libertarian Party: How Liberty Makes Health Care Virtually ... http://bit.ly/7UvaPP    
    
    
    overview for SatansLH http://bit.ly/8IGIN7    
    
    
    Dr Davis' Back & Wrist Pain Blog: Executive Express Chiropractic ... http://bit.ly/74PfWi    
    
    
    The Columbus Dispatch - Local/State | The Columbus Dispatch: Health News · Health Resource Center · Health Life.. http://bit.ly/8GROYq    
    
    
    Exercise More This Year: How to Make Regular Exercise a Part of ...: Finding the time for regular exercise can .. http://bit.ly/8B2rcT    
    
    
    Dr Davis' Back & Wrist Pain Blog: Forget Making New Year's ... http://bit.ly/6PUIwO    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: www.mohammadi.ca ... http://bit.ly/5RiUIa    
    
    
    HIPAAUpdate http://bit.ly/5vAHdp    
    
    
    BPD Friends » Bipolar ?!!?: A support site for anyone who suffers or knows of someone who suffers from BPD - Bo.. http://bit.ly/7fSv18    
    
    
    What It's Like To Be Pregnant And Diabetic: A Day Of Medical ...: Better Health is a network of healthcare .. http://bit.ly/8ZicIz    
    
    
    Bridal Lingerie Buying Guide: Article Source: http://www.articlesbase.com/health-articles/bridal- .... Health P.. http://bit.ly/5E51PT    
    
    
    San Francisco Spinal Decompression Guided Tour http://bit.ly/8Wcrbr    
    
    
    effects carbohydrate loading - Bloglines: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/carbohydrate-loading/MY00223. Carboh.. http://bit.ly/74QFu4    
    
    
    MOTHER HEALTH: Ladies Pay Attention: 6 Ways to Treat Bladder ...: Ladies Pay Attention: 6 Ways to Treat Bladder.. http://bit.ly/8lTnJi    
    
    
    See Corey Run: A Fitness & Nutrition Journal: The Subject is ...: Hello and welcome! If you're new here.. http://bit.ly/6sNZEB    
    
    
    Shopping for walking shoes? - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/health-tip/HT00.. http://bit.ly/8wPtwf    
    
    
    Permanent Weight Loss- The Ideal Resolution: Finally Keep the New ...: Almost every New Year, millions of peopl.. http://bit.ly/5gezM3    
    
    
    ACA - The American Chiropractic Association (ACA) - Representing ... http://bit.ly/8KTdxr    
    
    
    idahoagbell.org http://bit.ly/7ub37W    
    
    
    A torn scalp threatens baby's life, but doctors' ingenuity saves ...: Find tips, articles, information .. http://bit.ly/7Y9qSh    
    
    
    Pregnancy Over 40-Over 40 Motherhood: Antibiotics In Pregnancy: Of course you know to check with your doctor ab.. http://bit.ly/4TtX0L    
    
    
    Breast-feeding: Nobody said it would be this hard - MayoClinic.com: She co-edited the Mayo Clinic Guide to a He.. http://bit.ly/4Md55p    
    
    
    Healthy. Happy. Life.: New Year Soba Noodles, Soba Facts and a Recipe.: Looking for a healthy and delicious rec.. http://bit.ly/4Txd2M    
    
    
    Scientists Figure out the Cause of Brain Farts: If you want to use this article on your site please click here... http://bit.ly/4ZNCTO    
    
    
    raceOregon: So, what the hell is DHEA?*: Tyler Hamilton, Kenny Williams and now Tom Zirbel. Three names from di.. http://bit.ly/6BrTAO    
    
    
    Really Rainey: 50 ways to cut 500 calories a day!: Some of these are just plain silly or common sense, yet the .. http://bit.ly/4XDHmC    
    
    
    Twitter / Matthew Loop: Palmer Center for Chiropra ... http://bit.ly/6tWQb9    
    
    
    How to Get Nutrition Consulting Paid for by Insurance | eHow.com: ... diet therapy and modification is recogniz.. http://bit.ly/8CdcuN    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: Late on Wednesday, the Supreme Court in Pakist.. http://bit.ly/8ETz3y    
    
    
    Video How to measure blood pressure using an automatic monitor ...: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthhowtomeasur.. http://bit.ly/90NIXg    
    
    
    Byers Chiropractic's Friends - Wellsphere http://bit.ly/8CLBz4    
    
    
    Pandemic (H1N1) 2009 - Human Swine Flu - Department of Health ...: Human swine influenza (flu) information for .. http://bit.ly/65KffN    
    
    
    House passes legislation to delay Medicare fee cuts http://bit.ly/6ae7vm    
    
    
    HEALTH DEPOT EVERYTHING ABOUT YOUR HEALTH 25 DietBusting Foods You ...: httpcgipathfindercomcgibinmaildnpprivac.. http://bit.ly/6T7NYk    
    
    
    NeuroLogica Blog » Some Good News About Libel Laws http://bit.ly/4Rp3J0    
    
    
    The Practice of ScooterdudeWay httpwwwdrweilcom: httpwwwdrweilcom. Posted by Scooterdude at 629 AM ... Health A.. http://bit.ly/8LJRIv    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: She also addressed anti-gay activity in Iraq a.. http://bit.ly/7nH151    
    
    
    I'm moved into my new office.  Now I need to finish painting, cleaning & organizing.  I should be ready to re-open by next week.    
    
    
    Quigley's Cabinet: More scary paths: Being a visual and verbal chronologue of my peculiar life, foremost my.. http://bit.ly/4oVn2s    
    
    
    How to Do Bicep Curls Right: Article Source: http://www.articlesbase.com/health-articles/how-to-do-bicep- curls.. http://bit.ly/8BFT8u    
    
    
    When a Headache is Not Just a Headache http://bit.ly/5b4SpO    
    
    
    Gooseberry Lane: That French Diet Advice, Again: This Google Reader feed contains articles from over 40 differe.. http://bit.ly/4uZlTU    
    
    
    New Danger Associated With Drinking Ordinary Milk | Demas Web ID: Source : http://blogs.mercola.com/sites/vital.. http://bit.ly/5eCekl    
    
    
        
    
    
    Smoking cessation Creating a quitsmoking plan MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthsmokingcessationSK.. http://bit.ly/4uGA6M    
    
    
    Eye floaters MayoCliniccom: Spots and floaters American Optometric Association httpwwwaoaorgx4701xml Accessed S.. http://bit.ly/7YnWas    
    
    
    The Age-Proof Diet – Health.com | Best Diet Success: What you need: Food that makes you happy. A woman's ha.. http://bit.ly/76TIX2    
    
    
    Can Antidepressants Cause Weight Gain? « LIVING IN STIGMA: Can Antidepressants Cause Weight Gain? Posted by che.. http://bit.ly/4Wbe0R    
    
    
    The Dangers of Chiropractic http://bit.ly/8ZmlxQ    
    
    
    Meeting Medicare's Documentation Requirements http://bit.ly/6LZFYp    
    
    
        
    
    
    Medical billing code monopoly explains American Medical ...: As Democrats tout the American Medical Association.. http://bit.ly/6yz0JU    
    
    
    Managing Depression 101, Part 4: Diet and Supplements | My Online ...: Antidepressants and alcohol: What is the.. http://bit.ly/4xDiXD    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fatty Kathy's Weight Loss Journal: 2009 Ends with a Blue Moon: It only happens once in a blue moon. Decembe.. http://bit.ly/4F2AOJ    
    
    
    Search at blog directory Bloggernity.com using our blog search ... http://bit.ly/52vrV5    
    
    
    Chiropractors: Car Accident, staten island auto accident, staten ... http://bit.ly/89ajrm    
    
    
    Links on "ATSU Counseling Services - Arizona Campus" | Facebook: Learn and practice all 10! http://ww.. http://bit.ly/7Qmaas    
    
    
    Heart to Heart « Honey Magazine: Brittany Murphy's untimely, cardiac arrest-induced* death got us thinking .. http://tinyurl.com/ydaywqn    
    
    
    I'd like to wish all my MySpace friends a very happy, healthy and SAFE new year.   Please enjoy yourselves tonight and please don't drink an    
    
    
    Senate OK's Landmark Health Reform Bill - Health News Story - WGAL ...: The US Senate votes to approve a la.. http://bit.ly/8S71ho    
    
    
    Patient Education - Intute - Search results: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/preeclampsia/DS00583. This patien.. http://bit.ly/6GAeIp    
    
    
    I'd like to wish everybody a very happy, healthy, prosperous and safe New Year!  Let's make 2010 the best year... http://bit.ly/4yyr3d    
    
    
    I'd like to wish everybody a very happy, healthy, prosperous and safe New Year! Let's make 2010 the best year ever! Red Apple Wellness will    
    
    
    Mayo Clinic Drops Medicare Patients in Arizona as Obama Model ...: Mayo Clinic in Arizona to Stop Treating Some.. http://bit.ly/5diA8k    
    
    
    chirovoice.org http://bit.ly/8OnTVh    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: wrongdiagnosis.com/: [Discover] DrWeil.com - Official Website of.. http://bit.ly/62K2T6    
    
    
    Soy in Illinois prison diets prompts lawsuit over health effects ... http://bit.ly/5dySkB    
    
    
    Department of Health and Ageing - Information sheet 1 - How Aged ...: Minister for Indigenous Health, Rural and.. http://bit.ly/5vEq04    
    
    
    Chiropractic Articles for your Website>> ChiroHosting http://bit.ly/6f9K0o    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: www.fda.gov/search ...: [Discover] Wrong Diagnosis http://wrongd.. http://bit.ly/6CWXHd    
    
    
    Dr Davis' Back & Wrist Pain Blog: Happy New Year Everyone http://bit.ly/7raxlN    
    
    
    Health - Http Www Mayoclinic Com Health - JustAnswer: Here you can find questions containing - http www mayocli.. http://bit.ly/7oS0VZ    
    
    
    Commonsense & Wonder: And, then there are the $500 billion in cuts ...: Mayo Clinic in Arizona to Stop Trea.. http://bit.ly/4VeRv5    
    
    
    Roswell GA chiropractor: Passing of a chiropractic hero http://bit.ly/6Z5VDx    
    
    
    Challenge 21: Prosperous New Year!: Living Life Abundant said... One of my challenges this year is to focus on .. http://bit.ly/5925ab    
    
    
    I'm about 95% done with painting the new clinic.  We should be open on Monday, January 4, 2010!    www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Weight loss plan: In the interest of losing fat, or gaining it, there is one formula which generally rings true.. http://bit.ly/5xfNDA    
    
    
    RedTram News Search Engine | All news everywhere http://bit.ly/8Gh9BF    
    
    
    Obama Readying Immigration Overhaul Despite Political Risks ...: The punishing battle over healthcare is still .. http://bit.ly/4SDliO    
    
    
    Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic will be opening on January 4, 2009.  Call us for an appointment!  412-212-8880    
    
    
    www.painatlanta.com backlinks links backlink check http://bit.ly/7oSOU2    
    
    
    Women Wrinkle more than Men | Clipmarks: ... ;background-image: url(http://clipmarks.com/images/source-bg.gif);.. http://bit.ly/7i9xTr    
    
    
    Fatty Kathy's Weight Loss Journal: Honesty Helps and is Appreciated: I tried to leave this as a response to.. http://tinyurl.com/y8u2se7    
    
    
    Smart Tips on Hair Loss | A blog on Travelling: It is natural to lose hair and is part of the body's way to.. http://bit.ly/4PFM1X    
    
    
    The Mayo Clinic Diet and Journal « One Persons Journey through a ...: I am always trying to find ways to stay h.. http://bit.ly/8l7K4Q    
    
    
    vinpocetine: URL: http://www.espefa.com.pl/pl/oferta/szczegolowe/vinpocetine.html ... MayoClinic ... URL: http:.. http://bit.ly/6t9PgB    
    
    
    Links on "Shipley Chiropractic" | Facebook http://bit.ly/5XfBZc    
    
    
    2008 MAA-CBO Directory - Minnesota Dept. of Health: PDF format at: http://www.health.state.mn.us/refugee. Click.. http://bit.ly/7FCNjx    
    
    
    ED Bites: Saturday Smorgasbord: I don't usually do a smorgasbord on Saturday; however, this week had a numb.. http://bit.ly/8O1nEa    
    
    
    Clipmarks: EasyRSS: Clipmarks | Live Clips: Clipmarks - Backup daily marvelous clipmarks from clipmarks.com.

.. http://bit.ly/6eX8zH    
    
    
    WebMii - Three Girls: http://blogs.mercola.com/sites/vitalvotes/archive/2007/06/14/Three-Girls-Died ..... http:.. http://bit.ly/4PLbk3    
    
    
    tips | kenttrudo | My Bookmarks | | Mister Wong http://bit.ly/5WIIjY    
    
    
    YogaMD's Computer Relief iPhone App Now Available - The Perfect ... http://bit.ly/6HRTRo    
    
    
    Dr Davis' Back & Wrist Pain Blog: 10 Reasons You Should Consider ... http://bit.ly/6ZpqFc    
    
    
    ChiroOrg Blog – For Chiropractic and Chiropractors. » Become a ... http://bit.ly/5ZVX1T    
    
    
    Fitness tip: Include your friends - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/health-ti.. http://bit.ly/7Q09wy    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Great Fitness Experiment: Winning The War on The Last Ten Pounds: 2009 was a big year for me. Not only did .. http://bit.ly/8IZyDU    
    
    
    Search - NewsTimes http://bit.ly/6AtzQn    
    
    
    11 Holiday Health Hazards to Avoid - Health.com - Mixx: RT @goodhealth: Cookie overload, poisonous plants, and .. http://bit.ly/5gs2J1    
    
    
    Chronicle: Logo httpwwwnewscomcomcgibinprnh20090105MAYOLOGO ... information about research and education visit .. http://bit.ly/87vKem    
    
    
    Three New Reasons To Love Kristen Bell :: FITSNews: kristen bell m. We've always liked Forgetting Sarah Mar.. http://bit.ly/8QS5n8    
    
    
    Premature ovarian failure: Tests and diagnosis - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/hea.. http://bit.ly/8JhxTN    
    
    
    Spring can't get here fast enough!    
    
    
    By the way, it's 4 months until the start of baseball season & the Pirates are already 15 games out of 1st place. :)    
    
    
    Tarantula Hair Attack Pierces Owner's Eyes - ABC News: As one man recently found out in England, tarantulas.. http://bit.ly/6OjsIH    
    
    
    Core Esstentials for Your Workout - Momtrends: When I can't get to the gym or pilates studio I whip out a f.. http://bit.ly/7vFnZ6    
    
    
    Science-Based Medicine » The life cycle of translational research http://bit.ly/7Vqxq8    
    
    
    American Chiropractic Association: Chiropractic Profession ... http://bit.ly/7cArPi    
    
    
    Links on "Andrew Weil, M.D." | Facebook: Dr. Weil says: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/QAA63228 and. .. http://bit.ly/4BPfFp    
    
    
    Godlike Productions - Post New Thread: Default, Verdana, Tahoma, Ms Sans Serif ... WTF i checked -> wtf http.. http://bit.ly/5JcN6s    
    
    
    High Expectations? States Weigh Marijuana Reform - Health News ...: OLYMPIA, Wash. -- Washington is one of four.. http://bit.ly/66cgOh    
    
    
    Have a very happy and safe Memorial Day weekend!  Don't forget to eat right, drink plenty of water and take your vitamins & supplements.    
    
    
    Finding Wellness and Wellbeing - Office of Human Resources ...: http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/parenting-tips.. http://bit.ly/5BuOgc    
    
    
    ChiroOrg Blog – For Chiropractic and Chiropractors. » Chiro.Org ... http://bit.ly/70J0pD    
    
    
    DrWeil.com - Official Website of Andrew Weil, M.D.: Dr. Weil says: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/QAA400145 ..... http://bit.ly/52767M    
    
    
    Penicillin allergy MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthpenicillinallergyDS00620Penicillin allergya. .. http://bit.ly/4Su9xN    
    
    
    Forums - Yog-Sothoth for Lovecraft & Cthulhu - http://bit.ly/67CQyl    
    
    
    Afternoon Snack: Two Pieces of This Sushi Weigh in Under 75 ...: Glamour magazine: fashion, beauty, hair, makeu.. http://bit.ly/5KEYW7    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: REACT. IT'S TIME. CHILD TRAFFICKING The be.. http://bit.ly/4ZcdRH    
    
    
    Chiropractors: terrible neck and back pain, Staten Island ... http://bit.ly/7ZLoaa    
    
    
    Broccoli A Cure For: (http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/qaa400037); Wednesday, january 07, 2004 by mike adams, the.. http://bit.ly/4qpvcB    
    
    
    97 Reasons to Drop the Lighter - LIME: Still trying to think of a New Year's resolution? If you are a smoke.. http://bit.ly/7h4lmT    
    
    
    DepoProveracontraceptive injection MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthdepoproveraMY00995DepoProvera.. http://bit.ly/7kpFTJ    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hypertension And Sea Salt: ... in japan, salt consumption is higher. [48] hypertension(http://en.wikipedia. org.. http://bit.ly/5BAFH3    
    
    
    Spots Unknown, Under The Skin of San Francisco // current http://bit.ly/7kRyJg    
    
    
    FML: I was told by 'Seventeen' to add liquid highlighter to my ...: Health : Today, I was told by '.. http://bit.ly/6JRadZ    
    
    
    Paul Offit, Amy Wallace, and Conde Nast being sued by anti ... http://bit.ly/5uc2KP    
    
    
    Darla Shine's Happy Housewives Club Healthy Living » Blog Archive ...: Tunguska Mist Banner. Fight Back! Yo.. http://bit.ly/6fpZYJ    
    
    
    Heart Health Diet And Recipe: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com /health /heart-healthy-recipes /re0009.. http://bit.ly/7P9riJ    
    
    
    Horner syndrome: Causes - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/horner-syndrome/DS0.. http://bit.ly/4Pk6XR    
    
    
    「Balance Chiropractic & Wellness」についての投稿リンク | Facebook http://bit.ly/4V6QVp    
    
    
    Broccolis Calories Per Person: ... 2 per person. want more healthy nutrients per serving: calories 88.3 (with m.. http://bit.ly/5x7syH    
    
    
    Crohn's Disease Condition Center - Health.com: Health.com Exclusives. 10 Ways to Cut Chronic Pain With Food.. http://bit.ly/8qKugc    
    
    
    Alzheimer's Can a Mediterranean diet lower my risk MayoCliniccom: a hrefhttpwwwmayocliniccomhealthalzheimer.. http://bit.ly/77ETIf    
    
    
    » Rhinoplasty: It's Not Always For Aesthetics …also known as ...: According to Wikipedia, the “word rhinopl.. http://bit.ly/5zzWyQ    
    
    
    Senior Sem Power Point http://bit.ly/7W4szm    
    
    
    How to Save a Life: January is National Blood Donor month. Although there are many committed blood donors like .. http://bit.ly/7kCUo4    
    
    
    Holistic+Integrated+Medicine: Includes advice on health and nutrition, recipes, forums, and online sales. Based.. http://bit.ly/6ZoIhC    
    
    
    References for Chiropractic Manipulation http://bit.ly/7F0MTM    
    
    
        
    
    
    LBN E-Lert »: U.S. ECONOMY LOST 85000 JOBS IN DECEMBER; UNEMPLOYMENT STEADY AT 10%: The unemployment rate held .. http://bit.ly/7bknCy    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: www.iwantsixpackabs ... http://bit.ly/600FBx    
    
    
    Tobacco-Using State Workers May Face No Health Coverage - Health ...: NASHVILLE, Tenn. -- A new proposal at the.. http://bit.ly/4GeYzV    
    
    
    Warm Potato Slad Recipe: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com /health /potato-salad /nu00355 ">re.. http://bit.ly/69A10G    
    
    
    Quish Recipe: (http://www.epicurious.com/recipes/food/views/crustless-quiche-241749) ... <a href="http:.. http://bit.ly/4KDUlF    
    
    
    Chiropractic Treatment for Bipolar Disease | eHow.com http://bit.ly/4DI0pH    
    
    
    Try Weightlifting and Chiropractic For Back Pain. It Works For Me ... http://bit.ly/721rSD    
    
    
    FDA Approves Actemra for Treatment of Rheumatoid Arthritis ...: Yesterday, Genetech Inc (a subsidiary of the Ro.. http://bit.ly/5oOGXA    
    
    
    Chiropractic Collections // BlogCatalog Topic // BlogCatalog http://bit.ly/5AxqWG    
    
    
    Organic Salmon- AskKids.com: http://www.drweil.com/u/id/QAA400061. Smoked Salmon & Trout. Salmon, Trout, Gl.. http://bit.ly/6dh8zC    
    
    
    Recipes For Health Drinks: find articles on liquid health and refreshment, and recipes for great tasting drinks.. http://bit.ly/6LX6ZI    
    
    
    Constipation in children: Risk factors - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/cons.. http://bit.ly/8CBC1d    
    
    
    New Solutions for Fibromyalgia - Health.com - Health.com: Is the fat acceptance movement bad for our health? .... http://bit.ly/6X5sJB    
    
    
    The types of antidepressants used to treat... | Gather: Jan 09, 2010 Published in examiner.com To treat depress.. http://bit.ly/7aXvi9    
    
    
    ChiroOrg Blog – For Chiropractic and Chiropractors. » JAMA ... http://bit.ly/7Hboug    
    
    
    What Is Chiropractic http://bit.ly/7PyXLA    
    
    
    Is drinking echinacea tea when you're NOT sick bad for you ...: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/QAA293438 If.. http://bit.ly/77QEco    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: www.mayoclinic.com ...: [Discover] Eat Like Me http://www.self.c.. http://bit.ly/8m6AMQ    
    
    
    Interstitial lung disease: Coping and support - MayoClinic.com: Treatment of idiopathic pulmonary fibrosis. htt.. http://bit.ly/8z2w2g    
    
    
    New Chiropractic Blog Announced: Free Resources for Chiropractors ... http://bit.ly/8Qwf1B    
    
    
    ACA - The American Chiropractic Association (ACA) - Representing ... http://bit.ly/87elgE    
    
    
    Too cold in Pittsburgh.  I'm moving to the equator!    
    
    
    FOOD SNOB: welcome to the bake-a-long!: Victoria and I have started our Artisan Bread in Five Minutes a Day bak.. http://bit.ly/4TCKUV    
    
    
    Clarifying Your Weight loss Goal: Tips and information on <a href="http://www.health-care-tips.org/herb.. http://bit.ly/68127c    
    
    
    Internalization of Anger and Motivating Change: Anger is a Barrier ...: It is difficult to communicate with som.. http://bit.ly/7MTxEH    
    
    
    What Breastmilk Tastes Like Part 4 | Code Name Mama: 3How Does Milk Production Work httpwwwkellymomcombfsupplym.. http://bit.ly/5WdGGI    
    
    
        
    
    
    Anti Inflamatory Cookbook: (http://www.drweil.com//antiinflammatory-diet-makeover-part-2-cabinets.html). kick o.. http://bit.ly/4EOkC6    
    
    
        
    
    
    New Blood Test for Peanut Allergy More Accurate, Allergy Relief: Peanut allergy is one of the most common food .. http://bit.ly/68pZsK    
    
    
    Breaking Through the Fibromyalgia Sleep Problem New Solutions for ...: Healthcom Exclusives. 10 Ways to Cut Chr.. http://bit.ly/6iYPnF    
    
    
    ACA - The American Chiropractic Association (ACA) - Representing ... http://bit.ly/6a93GW    
    
    
    My daughter Katelyn is selling girlscout cookies.  Who wants some?   Shoot me an e-mail!    
    
    
    My daughter Katelyn is selling girlscout cookies.  Who wants some?  Shoot me an e-mail.    
    
    
    Thalamus Center - Early Childhood Psychological Development ...: Ireland Child Sexual Abuse - Commission of Inv.. http://bit.ly/7vBHCC    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hasil Pencarian Back Ampamp Neck Pain Blog | Blogging Stuffy Web ... http://bit.ly/4K3xV1    
    
    
    "dissociative identity disorder" - Professional Medical Resources: Your symptoms also are not explain.. http://bit.ly/6snGW7    
    
    
    Democrats may side-step conference committee on health care ...: As Congressional Democrats attempt to arrive a.. http://bit.ly/916uE0    
    
    
    what is candida overgrowth - Bloglines: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/id/ART02853. Are You Suffering From Candida.. http://bit.ly/7KR1Uy    
    
    
    American Beverage Association Blog » Blog Archive » New Year, New You?: At the beginning of each year, most of .. http://bit.ly/8sH2x8    
    
    
        
    
    
    Department of Health and Ageing - Medical Benefits Reviews Task Group: The Medicare Benefits Schedule (MBS) is .. http://bit.ly/7IsA6H    
    
    
    Acatoday.org http://bit.ly/6hB5un    
    
    
    Healthy Recipes - Food, Cooking & Recipes - Beliefnet Community: nnn123. Posts: 842. Tomato corn and basil .. http://bit.ly/8ZQ4JP    
    
    
    Essure MayoCliniccom: Greenberg J Hysteroscopic sterilization httpwwwuptodatecomhomeindexhtml Accessed Sept 29 .. http://bit.ly/5Cj3c0    
    
    
    bakebakebake: December Theme Winner And January Theme Announcement: December Theme Winner And January Theme Ann.. http://bit.ly/6CjdNf    
    
    
    St. John's Wort Not Helpful Treatment for Irritable Bowel Syndrome ...: Read more information on treatment .. http://bit.ly/7ezMac    
    
    
    Definition of Health « Geske Chiropractic http://bit.ly/6SZzMc    
    
    
    Want Vocal Variety in Your Speeches? Breathe!: Voice coach Kate Peters describes how to obtain vocal variety in.. http://bit.ly/7Tx1WH    
    
    
    Mayo Clinic Weight Loss Plan: They actually came out with one!! Fake "Mayo Clinic diets" have been go.. http://bit.ly/5wGt1F    
    
    
        
    
    
    Brotherhood of Bald People :: View topic - Great Tea Article On ...: http://www.drweil.com/drw/u/ART03092/My-Li.. http://bit.ly/6rjidm    
    
    
    Single Women Rule » Read it and win: Healthy Cooking Tips from the ...: By the weight-loss experts at Mayo Clin.. http://bit.ly/7ztc9F    
    
    
    Discover From Your Favorite Topic or Web Page: Tips http://bit.ly/7PuWBS    
    
    
    MayoCliniccom Heart Disease Risk Calculator Helps Users Understand ...: MayoCliniccom's Heart Disease Cente.. http://bit.ly/4DT24q    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Health Related Issues To Playing TalkBass Forums: httpwwwspinehealthcomconditioalnerveroots. The radial nerve e.. http://bit.ly/6reFpa    
    
    
    kitty.nu » I do not have an eating disorder.: kitty.nu: a semi-personal, semi-daily kind of blog.

kitty.nu - .. http://bit.ly/4X8CpH    
    
    
        
    
    
    Meaningful use of electronic health records http://bit.ly/5su4Ct    
    
    
        
    
    
    Finding the G-spot: Is it real? - CNN.com: More Health · Haiti earthquake could trigger possible medical 'p.. http://bit.ly/7zniLN    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just got some signage up at the new office. At least people can know what's inside now!  LOL   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Visible Mystery: Why trampolines are dangerous: Actually, an unenclosed trampoline is about the most dangerous .. http://bit.ly/5H2QLt    
    
    
    Acai Optimum Review - Get FREE Trial Now: Its high nutrients content provide you numerous health benefits.</.. http://bit.ly/5vZKs7    
    
    
    I went shopping for my back pain and here's what I got - This Mama ...: When we returned home from vacation.. http://bit.ly/7fCUBc    
    
    
    Diverticulitis: Symptoms - MayoClinic.com: <a href="http://www.mayoclinic.com/health/diverticulitis/DS0.. http://bit.ly/8Dj8EX    
    
    
    Peace, Love and READ! (collection of Books with bag): Dr. Weil's 8 week plan for optimal healing power by A.. http://bit.ly/4ZqDEO    
    
    
    Like patients in pain, Olympic athletes turn to doctors of ... http://bit.ly/7IgSRP    
    
    
    Well the new clinic is now open!   I've still got a million little things to do.   There is an infite number of... http://bit.ly/5zFsMj    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    The new Red Apple Wellness & Chiropractic clinic is finally open!  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    If health came from a bottle of pills, you would have been born with one in your hands.  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Well the new clinic is finally open!  I've still got some odds & ends to tie up.  But we're functional and accepting new patients!    
    
    
    Good health habits leads to good health. Bad health habits leads to poor health.  So eat right, exercise, drink water & get adjusted!    
    
    
    Did you know that chiropractic adjustments keep your joints moving well, corrects your posture and prevents arthritis?  redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Onward and upward!  I've got some more projects at the clinic (new outside sign & building out a consult room).    
    
    
    New solutions for fibromyalgia pain:  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    After taking a month off, I'm going to be back with more videos & educational articles.  Stay tuned! http://bit.ly/6AcKDr    
    
    
    Have you become a fan of Red Apple Wellness yet?  Go into Facebook and become a fan today.   Free health tips and great info!    
    
    
    For Bethel Park residents suffering with back pain, neck pain & headaches - I'll be back soon with more articles & videos - free info.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Quick reminder to everyone:  Make sure you're supplementing with 5,000 to 10,000 units of vitamin D per day.  ... http://bit.ly/chE7HW    
    
    
        
    
    
    Well, the snow's here.  But we're hunkered down with a cache of food.  Bring it! :)  (Watch the power go out now).    
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy Birthday America!    www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Glad to be back!  Myspace locked me out for a while. Hahahaha    
    
    
    I've about had it up to HERE with snow.  Literally.    
    
    
    Snow, snow everywhere!   Remember to use good lifting mechanics when shoveling out your driveways. http://bit.ly/btLvYm    
    
    
    The sun is shining, it's a beautiful day and the Pirates are 4 games over .500!  Woot!   www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Way to go Pittsburgh Pirates.  Time to raise the Jolly Roger!  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Wow is it warm out there!  I'm staying inside with a cold drink.  www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    Most chronic pain is caused by problems associated with motion, alignment or strength.    www.redapplewellness.net    
    
    
    MLB umpire Jerry Meals needs to be fired.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just say no to Obamacare.    
    
    
    If you've been involved in an auto accident, you may have "hidden injuries" in your spine.  www.redapplewellness.net pic.twitter.com/eN5sPCg    
    
    
    Dept. of Justice raided the Gibson guitar factory, thus demonstrating just how out of whack the federal government's priorities are.    
    
    
    I'm doing research into non-drug treatments for peripheral neuropathy.    
    
    
    Medical vs. Chiropractic Treatments for Chronic Pain | RED APPLE WELLNESS & CHIROPRACTIC http://fb.me/1fVyEkxVl     
    
    
    I'm disgusted with the off-field behavior of the Steelers players.  Mr. Rooney, it's time to clean house.  Get rid of the bad seeds please.    
    
    
    