@phylogenomics I'm mobile today, but heard you're having issues w docs vanishing. Cld you email me a verbose log file? 'Help>FAQ' 1/2    
    
    
    @phylogenomics may have system-specific issue, so if log doesn't help let's set up a call later Monday w engineer here in London 2/2    
    
    
    I like! RT @PLoS: Tim O'Reilly comments on the PLoS/Mendeley API Binary Battle "[make] science go faster" http://tinyurl.com/TimO-ReillyBinaryBattle …    
    
    
    Science app ideas from the crowd http://bit.ly/nRJ2rW  (join the PLoS/Mendeley API Binary Battle)    
    
    
    @MendeleySupport  I work for http://bit.ly/o6jEWw  and I want to add a button "Export to Mendelay".Do you have a 20x20px  or bigger image?    
    
    
    Hehe, "...dinos lived at least 500yrs ago" New blog via @phylogenomics on num of species article http://bit.ly/oa49AU     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt It's impossible to respect the "Legibility" and "Clearing Space" in an icon 20x20 px. See this example. http://bit.ly/o5hIZ1     
    
    
    What do people think of the feed tab on Spotify? Useful? Interesting? Items relevant to you?    
    
    
    Interesting. "Academic publishers make Murdoch look like a socialist" in the Gaurdian http://bit.ly/om8d58     
    
    
    I had more typos in my last tweet than my entire thesis. :/    
    
    
    Scholarly Kitchen at it again with their BS comebacks. This time against Guardian's Monbiot http://bit.ly/pGJQJf     
    
    
    .@drs1969 Safe to say the writers of both stories have an agenda. I'll leave it at that. No need to comment on blog    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt always nice to start off with a few sweeping personal slights too...    
    
    
    Was Monbiot's blog rhetoric or more? See this analysis on library STM costs http://bit.ly/k4Ljwo  Slides 5-8,12    
    
    
    How old is that in "blog years?" Congrats! RT @PLoS: Happy first birthday to PLoS Blogs - http://bit.ly/PLoSBlogsOneToday …    
    
    
    Amazeballs. Yesterday Mendeley users added half a million articles. Took us five months to get our first 500K. Total now 109M    
    
    
    Rumor is true. Hackday at Mendeley HQ in London on Sun. Speak w/ @mfenner @ianmulvany @jasonhoyt for more info #solo11    
    
    
    API stat. In 2 wks Mendeley will pass 1000 developers using the API launched 14 months ago. #solo11    
    
    
    .@IanMulvany Was the applause that publishers are killing off PDF in favor of HTML5? #solo11    
    
    
    Just open sourced the Twendeley app at the Mendeley/Science Online hackday #solo11 https://github.com/jjhoyt/Twendeley …    
    
    
    .@pixievondust You can try out Twendeley at http://bit.ly/ad5nKQ  or get the source code at https://github.com/jjhoyt/Twendeley …    
    
    
    Second app of the day now on Chrome extension store "Mendeley Context Search" http://bit.ly/nVJz1h  #solohack11    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt any interesting things being worked on?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt it's "only" using the page title? #solohack11    
    
    
    Updated Mendeley Context Chrome extension. Now shows Mendeley readership for PubMed articles  http://yfrog.com/ny8b3p     
    
    
    Cool! @mfenner tackles article-level metrics by extending the open sourced @PLoS API server http://bit.ly/pU3gpw     
    
    
    Off to Whitstable, England for final weekend  holiday outside London before the baby!    
    
    
    That's awesome for newsfeed updates! RT @IanMulvany: unofficial chrome extension for Mendeley is nice: https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dmjdlnefabajccabhbemdnodgelechkd …    
    
    
    +shagtastic judges panel RT @mendeleyAPI: Just 15 days left to enter the $16K Mendeley PLoS API contest http://bit.ly/e9EiYE     
    
    
    Looks Presidential RT @mendeleyAPI: Liking the blue feel of this third party Mendeley app for Android "Scholarley" http://bit.ly/pxFJFH     
    
    
    Excellent. iPhone crashed, had to do restore, nothing backed up (txts, phone nums, photos) since Nov 2010 apparently.  Boo-yah. Life restart    
    
    
    Huge $$$ prizes RT @mendeleyAPI: Last call to enter the PLoS & Mendeley apps for researchers contest! Blog http://bit.ly/pxhYwl     
    
    
    Any ideas why most academic publishers don't use unique names for downloaded PDFs? e.g. SDarticle.pdf instead of insertDOI.pdf    
    
    
    Reading Scholarly Kitchen is like running into that stodgy old professor in the hall who refuses to accept a new dogma posed in his field    
    
    
    Guide to using Mendeley on Android - blog http://www.mendeley.com/blog/tipstricks/android-on-mendeley-an-app-guide/ …    
    
    
    Groupon seemingly in trouble again with exec depart. & revenue revise. Also, see this prediction from last year http://bit.ly/rb3DMQ     
    
    
    Mayor Boris tells us to report bad roadworks. I like the bad example photo http://bit.ly/p5hwrX     
    
    
    Ha! "How about zero?" Scientist meets publisher to negotiate a paper deal #OA http://youtu.be/GMIY_4t-DR0     
    
    
    Open Access journals to account for 90% of articles by 2020 one analyst estimates http://bit.ly/mPvydD     
    
    
    Entrepreneurs near Seattle! Join Startup weekend EDU edition & pitch/build the next startup Sep 30th http://bit.ly/q2eLxO     
    
    
    Literally no time for twitter, so much going on and so little time to take a look :(    
    
    
    Fab! RT @Droideley: Droideley (#Mendeley #Android client) installed on 1000+ devices! Cool :)    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @mendeley_com Is there a way to get more API calls? Asking for a Binary Battle-Submission that'd like 2 perform 1 Mio requests ;)    
    
    
    In the past 7 yrs Apple stock has grown 5000%. Holy $(#@    
    
    
    Cool for scifi/dystopia/fantasy book fans. Flowchart guide to NPRs top 100 scfi books http://bit.ly/rbQ3ch     
    
    
    Great article on why scientists need to be more vocal in public & publish in open. Ans: Cuz the public is hurting http://bit.ly/p4W2As     
    
    
    Great article on #openscience & public trust - 'Social Media for Scientists Part 1: It’s Our Job' - http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/science-sushi/2011/09/27/social-media-for-scientists-part-1-its-our-job/ … @jasonHoyt @mrgunn    
    
    
    Princeton bans academics from handing over copyright to publishers. Promoting OpenAccess http://bit.ly/pdbhC9  #OA    
    
    
    The Princeton banning of handing over copyright has sent a shiver down my spine & a shock wave across academic publishing.    
    
    
    New group to collect Uni policies on #copyright & #OA for other Unis to model after Princeton precedent http://bit.ly/p7naDh     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt It's not quite new - Harvard, MIT, Duke, Uni of Kansas and others have similar policies - see http://roarmap.eprints.org/     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt banned how? Does Princeton retain?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt ah! I was thinking the Press, not Uni. Thanks for clarifying. Will/does Mendeley auto-tap/link to such repositories?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt a good shiver right?    
    
    
    Willing to pay $5/mo 4 streaming music, but not 4 something that improves your research (career)? #whatsWrongWithWorldToday    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt My career should pay me, not vice versa.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt ... with a highly uncertain dividend. Even stock market trading seems more rewarding. Or gambling.    
    
    
    .@egonwillighagen I was speaking in general terms abt investing in your career. Not abt Mendeley or similar tools cc @dominikb1888    
    
    
    Last day to enter the Mendeley/@PLoS Binary Battle apps contest! Winners announced Nov 30th http://bit.ly/hETJ55     
    
    
    Congrats to @plos on their refreshed website & mission statement! http://www.plos.org/     
    
    
    I think that's a 1st RT @Pewology: Whenever I end up on Mendeley.com, I keep expecting it to be a UNATCO website.    
    
    
    Founded http://Ologeez.org 2006. Last commit end '08. Joined competitor Mendeley 3mo later. Shutting down Ologeez Oct 7 2011    
    
    
    Hello World. No baby as of yet. Amazingly, I will actually tell you when he does arrive. It's not a secret. So, please stop asking. XO!    
    
    
    Apple could have saved $13B in lost market cap today by calling the iPhone 5 instead of 4S. Oops.    
    
    
    @jasonhoyt @mrgunn @enroweb is there a blog post of entries coming? I want to check out the competition! #binarybattle    
    
    
    Attn academics and students! RT @mrgunn: In London? Want to help Mendeley out? Join us for user testing next week: http://bit.ly/r0A3KG     
    
    
    New arrival! My son baby Elliot was born this morning in true Binary Battle style on 11-10-11! http://yfrog.com/o05j8wrj     
    
    
    Baby Elliot's first shot and breath of life  http://yfrog.com/h7ajrsquj     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Baby Elliott Hoyt? As in, yours?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt congratulations, nice DOB!! Hope mother and baby are well. Enjoy! ;)    
    
    
    Yesterday's @NewYorker cartoon "Turns out everyone here is self-published." The future of academic publishing? #OpenAccess Wk    
    
    
    The modern family  http://yfrog.com/h374ymxj     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt is he on Twitter yet? :)    
    
    
    Cool use of the Mendeley & @PLoS APIs in the openSNP project http://opensnp.org/snps/26324#mendeley … #personalGenomics    
    
    
    As a techie, I'm embarrassed to admit this: I just now replaced my iPhone 3G after 2.5 yrs. iPhone 4S baby.    
    
    
    Top 40 Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle . Day One http://bit.ly/rUdgGc     
    
    
    Day 2 of the Top 40 Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle http://bit.ly/s0JYgL     
    
    
    Wow! RT @axfelix: @mendeley_com @plos I'm blown away by results of the binary battle. This is more & better work than has been done in yrs    
    
    
    MT @axfelix: OMG it's a citation visualization that's actually useful for browsing. OMG. I'm going to go make coffee. http://vyzkumap.net/     
    
    
    Day 3 of Top Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle is now out! http://bit.ly/tswT7q     
    
    
    Day 4 of Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle. +full-list recap http://bit.ly/vtcZFO     
    
    
    If we can sequence a human genome for $100, why can't we openly publish for $100? http://openrepub.org/  via @OpenRePub    
    
    
    Ausgezeichnet! RT @delaiglesia: New blog post (German): Mendeley/PLoS API Binary Battle http://bit.ly/uPGI3P     
    
    
    The boy weighed in at 10lbs 12oz in his latest checkup. Three pounds in just 4 weeks since he was born! Mama has some good milk    
    
    
    Happy Birthday, Carl Sagan. I'm still inspired.    
    
    
    Siri. Please tweet ... Oh wait. Silly me for thinking an integrated Twitter with iOS 5 would work w/ you. Siri - "STFU, Jason."    
    
    
    Why in the H-E-double hockey sticks am I not at #Berlin9 ? I want to marry you.    
    
    
    #Berlin9 why wld I publish in a journal that didn't have the sense to secure the .com/org domain names b4 announcing itself? eLife?    
    
    
    The top 20 things. Ever. http://bit.ly/3n6rFh     
    
    
    .@PLoS & @Mendeley_com will be announcing the Binary Battle Top 10 apps to impact science in about one hour.    
    
    
    Announcing the Top 10+1 Apps in the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle http://bit.ly/s7uE8k     
    
    
    .@openSNPorg congrats! Great app and concept :)    
    
    
    Also check out the complete Binary Battle rundown w/ judges + the Top 10+1 apps on the dev portal http://bit.ly/twkfLB     
    
    
    Sh%t! Swearing more in life reduces pain tolerance when you stub your toe & shout f%&. Research says http://1.usa.gov/tPPWF6     
    
    
    More amazing apps almost in the Binary Battle Top 10 http://www.qrate.me  http://vocabulari.se  http://moodley.fidesol.org     
    
    
    Congrats to the 50 millionth DOI assignee from CrossRef! Oddly enough, it's a scanned paper from 1985 http://bit.ly/vR6vQl     
    
    
    Public voting now open to decide who should win the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle! http://bit.ly/u1WjHL     
    
    
    Hope they fire that "officer" RT @markasaurus: Everything I thought would never happen in this country http://bit.ly/sJ12gu     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt the shit that's happened here recently makes me want to mail my University of California diploma back to Sacramento    
    
    
    liked:  "(for those of you who missed it) PLoS One is launching a brand new altmetrics collection. Details and CFP..." http://mnd.ly/u39pbP     
    
    
    Heat-map of the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle voting across the world thus far http://yfrog.com/o02qep     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @mendeley_com What are you guys using to create that visualisation? Looks good.    
    
    
    The world needs both the "Microsofts" & "Apples." Tradeoff is backwards compatibility vs. innovation; diff need/diff times    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt when the world is moving from desktop to tablets, businesses to the cloud, don't see where backward compatibility would matter    
    
    
    Fair to say that Dropbox is just a fancy GUI for git repos?    
    
    
    Ironically, story behind pay wall RT @michael_nielsen: Paul Allen on the case for open science: http://on.wsj.com/vFPWx4     
    
    
    45 minutes until we announce the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle Apps for Science winners.  5PM GMT / 9AM PST    
    
    
    #oa openSNP wins PLoS/Mendeley Binary Battle http://bit.ly/vwmCZV  on PLoS BLog, and Mendeley blog http://bit.ly/siSrCj     
    
    
    @helgerausch Congrats for all the test-writing. I'm keeping an eye on the logs and server load right now :D    
    
    
    Devs of @totalimpactdev said of Binary Battle "You've inspired innovation that wasn't otherwise happening" Thx! let's keep inspiring!    
    
    
    Check out the interview with the Binary Battle Apps for Science winner, @openSNPorg http://bit.ly/unhn1w     
    
    
    Help the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle winner, @openSNPorg, win a grant to genotype people for free http://bit.ly/trV9gU     
    
    
    ZOMG. I'm babysitting Elliot tonight, by myself. Father/son party!    
    
    
    And spit up all over his outfit within 10 minutes of mama leaving. Party's started!    
    
    
    I want a pair of these. Sergey Brin was 2500 years behind. pic.twitter.com/TR6vnxX2    
    
    
    Happy belated fifth birthday, @PLoSone ! http://bit.ly/rUjqMV  cc @PLoS    
    
    
    Sad news all, I left Mendeley. What a great 3yrs! Good news, started project to disrupt another industry.    
    
    
    Postdoc truck http://upmic.wordpress.com/2012/01/03/postdoc-truck/ …    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt which industry? ;) You did an awesome job at Mendeley, THANKS!    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Good luck! Looking forward to see your future projects! Are you staying in London?    
    
    
    At Somerset House pic.twitter.com/jDG1RLwb    
    
    
    .@subcide Haven't seen Sherlock. Better question though, are his thoughts in anachronistic font?    
    
    
    Elsevier execs spanked  '...whose sole purpose it is to lobby governments into preventing Open Access' http://bjoern.brembs.net/comment-n819.html …    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Curious to hear what's next :-)    
    
    
    w/ RWA & SOPA, Elsevier+paywall publishers are only delaying their inevitable crash. Shareholders will be jumping ship soon    
    
    
    Now that I've left Mendeley I can freely state that AAP+Elsevier are the biggest threats to science existing today    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Why?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt eh? what? why? Lancet/Cell/Scopus/Research4Life (etc) chopped liver?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt What are you smoking and please can I have some?!    
    
    
    Commercial publishers: make vast profits, buy protective legislation, rinse, repeat. bit.ly/zBJpHK  by @brembs via @Klortho    
    
    
    Good article and written on my 35th b-day! RT @BoraZ: Does the journal really matter anymore?  http://bit.ly/z3DJDx     
    
    
    I always ask myself, "Have I failed enough to succeed yet?" 10 things entrepreneurs [SHOULD] fail at http://tcrn.ch/z9XJhu     
    
    
    praise in triplicate @jasonHoyt ditto @jasonpriem @researchremix thanks for the great work. (I still love the "change the world" photo)    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt happy birthday. :)    
    
    
    .@CameronNeylon Did someone say 'beer?' cc @mfenner @wjjessen    
    
    
    Elsevier+Execs made 14 'donations' to main #RWA Congress backers, Issa & Maloney, in 2011 http://bit.ly/xcsgq9     
    
    
    Time to vote them out. List of US Congress members taking contributions from Elsevier http://bit.ly/xNBZEC     
    
    
    .@subcide Even if the contributions totaled just $1, it still shows legislation can be bought by outsiders.    
    
    
    Great! RT @gfry: @jasonHoyt Jason, have you seen "Open Knowledge Saves Lives. #OpposeHR3699 ! http://bit.ly/wJ6oVF  #RWA    
    
    
    You don't get to destroy science just because it doesn't fit your biz model #RWA    
    
    
    And coding resumes.  return $awesome;    
    
    
    How Microsoft would redesign the BOX of Apple product. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=EUXnJraKM3k …    
    
    
    Do startups need 'Wartime CEOs?' - "Wartime CEO violates protocol in order to win." http://bit.ly/eqMuIl     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt startups in general?  I would say no.    
    
    
    First day on a brand new planet!    
    
    
    @jasonhoyt Hey jasonhoyt, I just mentioned you in my comment on "Tea Party Nation Sells Out to Newt Gingrich Based o....    
    
    
    Annoying @VirginAtlantic "pre-flight courtesy" call is actually a sales call, costing me mobile minutes + time.    
    
    
    Wow. @37signals sounds like they'd be fans of SOPA. Drop the hate of @curebit already. You both look foolish.    
    
    
    Adding some fuel RT @wilbanks: After years of activism, first true body blow to Elsevier comes from passive resistance http://bit.ly/zYS18t     
    
    
    Uk folk hows your lovefilm streaming experience? Seems jerky to me, not buffering, but jerky.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt cheers for info , whats film selection like on netflix?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt cheers for info , whats film selection like on netflix?    
    
    
    Ten Things You're Not Allowed to Say at Davos http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2011/01/ten_things_youre_not_allowed_t.html …    
    
    
    An equity analyst's take on the Elsevier boycott http://t.co/IYiJXzNqvia @stephen_curry cc:  @jasonhoyt    
    
    
    Elsevier is "committed to the broadest possible dissemination of published research." Until it hurts profit$ http://bit.ly/yZvsUl     
    
    
    Out now. I co-authored a chapter on usage metrics in science (avail from MIT Press)  http://yfrog.com/obezlmyj  #mendeley    
    
    
    More double speak from publishers to law makers abt OA as threat to viability of research. This time in UK parliament: http://bit.ly/ACkxej     
    
    
    Speaking today in San Francisco at Molecular Med Tri-Con. I talk data! Yum http://bit.ly/A7aRVL     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @BioMedCentral: 2012 Benjamin Franklin Award Finalists Named http://ow.ly/9kARH  #science #openaccess    
    
    
    Shouldn't have to be Indiana Jones to find a research paper http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/02/google-trained-minds-cant-deal-with-terrible-research-database-ui/253641/ …    
    
    
    I decided to perform a literature search using ONLY Mendeley. Got some awesome results - http://bit.ly/zPeZbd     
    
    
    … but it helps? RT @jasonHoyt: You shouldn't have to be Indiana Jones to find a research paper http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/02/google-trained-minds-cant-deal-with-terrible-research-database-ui/253641/ …    
    
    
    1 of my former PhD thesis advisors just shared a link to his latest genomics paper, which is behind a paywall. I felt like chastising him    
    
    
    And it will *only* cost me $20 to "rent" his paper for the day from Genome Research. Fabulous!    
    
    
    Work/Family balance lesson #32-When present, BE present. Partner gently reminded me this morn while I was working on the laptop, in bed    
    
    
    The always interesting @petermurrayrust & his synopsis on the scholarly pub debate held w Elsevier & others http://bit.ly/AbrVAS     
    
    
    .@invisiblecomma @petermurrayrust you can't copyright a fact, which is why the US takes a friendly legal stance on text mining, UK following    
    
    
    Fail already. SearchMe tried this RT @TheNextWeb: Oolone: A visual search engine designed by a London neuroscientist http://tnw.to/1DWzS     
    
    
    My academic goth friends will like this; Journal of Dracula Studies. For real. http://www.blooferland.com/drc/index.php?title=Journal_of_Dracula_Studies …    
    
    
    Amused that my GMail auto-detects mail from Google corporate as spam.    
    
    
    Great! RT @creativecommons: Announcing the Why Open Education Matters Video Competition! w/prizes up to $25,000: http://bit.ly/wE20uP  #OER    
    
    
    Good market intel RT @wilbanks: Challenges in big data. By some of the shiniest brains in big data. http://bit.ly/xn2D3w ”    
    
    
    congrats on a productive conversation! ;) RT @researchremix: New post: Talking text mining with Elsevier http://wp.me/p4g7f-fU     
    
    
    In the latest OA newsletter, @PeterSuber argues that non-#OA publishers knowingly distort the facts http://bit.ly/yIo0on     
    
    
    The 1953 double helix paper was never peer-reviewed at Nature.  Is there a new pub model in that fact? http://bit.ly/y1vQUn     
    
    
    Important RT @thePeerJ: 12 points to fight the misinformation campaign led by non-OA publishers against #OA & #FRPAA http://bit.ly/xsuKrm     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @David_Dobbs tried reading note about the 1953 paper you referred to. current pub model did not allow me: pic.twitter.com/9u4rqZp5    
    
    
    Visions of Terminator. This scares me. DARPA has developed the world's fastest robot cheetah: http://glpo.st/zYMMbj     
    
    
    It's concerning when academic publishers claim to advance science, but then oppose bills in congress that wld do such #FRPAA    
    
    
    The American Association of Publishers now promoting xenophobia argues @mbeisen http://bit.ly/Ajz1ev  #FRPAA    
    
    
    High availability name nodes now for Hadoop! This means more realtime big data apps http://bit.ly/yODmWH  ht @aglet    
    
    
    Wish #CSS multiple backgrounds could stack across different classes somehow. So if class A and B, apply both backgrounds.    
    
    
    Why will paywall publisher boycotts work now vs. 10 yrs ago? Social media. Power has shifted.  http://thecostofknowledge.com/     
    
    
    At the Imperial College waiting for the Ig Nobel Awards Tour Show with @jesperht.  Can't wait!  #ImprobResearch    
    
    
    Also good for inventing PCR RT @TelegraphSci: LSD could treat alcoholism because 'trips' make you reassess addiction http://bit.ly/A5cUR4     
    
    
    #SXSW. Showcasing every thing that you won't remember next year.    
    
    
    LOL at "back when social media gurus were simply called 'tools'." by @kn0thing http://alexisohanian.com/an-open-letter-to-kevin-rose …    
    
    
    Big FU to users to not be straight up that they will eventually shutdown. Why the marketing-speak at this point? Postereous sells to Twitter    
    
    
    Pork pie of politeness  http://instagr.am/p/IH8UpSEIhY/     
    
    
    AOL products headed by the CFO? Profit-led innovation == death http://nyti.ms/Aww4OD     
    
    
    .@subcide No clue why any tech/product person wld go to work for AOL.    
    
    
    Goldman Sachs director quits due 2 poor company values. Do the big 4 scholarly pub execs feel the same? http://nyti.ms/Az2sVf     
    
    
    Shocked! MT @invisiblecomma: FWIW, I asked Elsevier for access to extract & publish an index of articles/gene names, they said no.    
    
    
    I remember when Google founders' goal was 'get users to destination' as fast as possible. Their goal is now reversed. Cld be their undoing    
    
    
    "Talent Code" seems like a great book. Too bad Elsevier publishes it. Boycott hold fast! http://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/055380684X …    
    
    
    How can we make science journalism high-throughput, as every scholarly publication deserves translation for the masses?    
    
    
    .@mccormicktim Nice! Need to build the right incentives to enable a crowd sourced "wikipedia for science" #sciencejournalism    
    
    
    .@subcide @mccormicktim See earlier tweet for context  http://bit.ly/w9Q0tU     
    
    
    OK Google Minus (Plus), time to let people merge their Google Apps profile with their personal profiles. Huge use case    
    
    
    Once more 4 the late birds. How can we make science journalism high-throughput? Every scholarly publication needs translation for the masses    
    
    
    #Git. I can't live with you. I can't live without you.    
    
    
    .@prokopp What? And give up CLI goodness?! I currently use GitX when I feel a need to succumb to the gui & admit defeat #Git    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt hopefully not permanent.  Just need to convince the uk govt that I should stay :)    
    
    
    MT @thePeerJ: #reddit frontpage discovers Elsevier boycott: perspectives of educated non-scholars http://bit.ly/weJZM9  via @jasonpriem    
    
    
    High-throughput civilization discovery in PNAS; "anthropomics?" http://bit.ly/GHvWjg  cc @phylogenomics    
    
    
    Cool, the first user of openSNP has entered his penis length.    
    
    
    +1 to Elsevier for this Open Access copyright propaganda filled w/ inaccuracy. http://bit.ly/HcHble  via @SauropodMike    
    
    
    You couldn't make it up! A human genome paper is free at Nature ... but access to the corrections costs $64. http://phylogenomics.blogspot.co.uk/2012/03/natures-access-absurdity-human-genome.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Feed:+TheTreeOfLife+%28The+Tree+of+Life%29 …    
    
    
    We are scientists pic.twitter.com/pYRlumZo    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Excellent t-shirt!    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt cute :-)    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt He really needs a miniature toy pipetman. That would complete the look. Super cute!    
    
    
    How to raise a future sci.tech innovator? My dad watched star trek & NOVA. I simply followed. @rww http://rww.to/H8l6ln     
    
    
    Elsevier in trouble again? Author fees are $3K  for "Open Access" option, but is it actually OA? No says http://bit.ly/HhZtDM     
    
    
    .@invisiblecomma You're both an object model and an instance of that object.    
    
    
    Google Scholar's list of top publications (by h5-index) ranks arXiv ahead of Lancet, Cell, PNAS, JAMA, etc.
http://scholar.google.com/citations?view_op=top_venues …
Interesting    
    
    
    Required reading from Peter Thiel on lessons learned from the 90s tech scene. http://blakemasters.tumblr.com/post/20582845717/peter-thiels-cs183-startup-class-2-notes-essay …    
    
    
    Instagram nearly blew up on day 1 due a missing favicon img file. Good slides on scaling http://scr.bi/I97fZQ     
    
    
    Elsevier staff now resorting to irrelevant ad hominem attacks on Open Access supporters (see comments) http://bit.ly/Hwlzg3     
    
    
    Summary: If you have the talent, do something that matters. From The Atlantic, inventing a new future http://bit.ly/IyxE5N     
    
    
    Wld post-pub peer review mitigate this? RT @brembs Some brief responses to the Sage Bionetworks Congress http://feedly.com/k/JHuonI     
    
    
    Dreamed last night that I worked at Apple , SJ was alive & had me getting his lunch everyday in exchange for daily chats. Hmm    
    
    
    Coincidence? My son's first initial is equal to the hexadecimal representation of his birth date.  #proudDad    
    
    
    Now if I'd only not eaten that croissant last night I'd be having a nice breakfast right about now.    
    
    
    1am.  Miserable fail at getting my sleep patterns back to normal...    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt I fell asleep at 2pm :(    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt no, flew back from NZ today.    
    
    
    Have finally tamed the beast, which is AWS ec2. Until next time & goodnight my old foe.    
    
    
    I am still counting the grammatical errors on their site. Is that part of their "new lit format?" RE http://bit.ly/JX80It  @ivanoransky    
    
    
    Ah, I want. XD solar window charger for the devices. Sleek http://bit.ly/vFtmu2     
    
    
    Well done! RT @p_binfield: This is my last day at PLoS ONE. Just made a farewell blog post at: http://blogs.plos.org/everyone/2012/05/18/plos-one-a-personal-farewell/ …    
    
    
    It's Devo time pic.twitter.com/TWKfryZi    
    
    
    Real reason? Key players left NASA 4Industry RT @wired: OpenStack Launch Partner NASA Grounds Development http://bit.ly/JAa9K9     
    
    
    Hero RT @robinlloyd99: Tech entrepreneur secretly lives at AOL HQ for two months http://pulse.me/s/9EbqI     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @invisiblecomma It's like they can't wait to be made irrelevant.    
    
    
    So @p_binfield's 5yr-old drew our new @thePeerJ logo. FTW  http://yfrog.com/g04orxkj     
    
    
    @Villavelius @researchremix @mbeisen CC-BY is considered to work with data mining as pertaining to facts, as those are not held in copyright    
    
    
    Mind boggling & simplifying all in one. Every Black Hole Contains a New Universe http://goo.gl/fb/e4frv     
    
    
    My non-human greeting at #foocamp last night  http://yfrog.com/ocjwknoj     
    
    
    Why we need more 'PrePrints' 2 correct errors MT @ivanoransky: Climate paper put on hold after being published online http://bit.ly/MuHFRX     
    
    
    Nature, Ars Technica & Stephen Curry cover @thePeerJ launch: http://bit.ly/LQzpia  http://bit.ly/MGRdgg  http://bit.ly/LQzzWS     
    
    
    Thanks all for the well wishes on the @thePeerJ launch today! #OA cc @p_binfield    
    
    
    ! RT @timoreilly: Huffpo covers launch of open access journal @thePeerJ, in which I am an investor (@oatv) & board mem http://huff.to/K02IuL     
    
    
    .@subcide Thanks!    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Congrats on the launch!    
    
    
    .@prokopp @chris_koerner Cheers!    
    
    
    .@skonkiel +1 for opposite days.    
    
    
    The @thePeerJ monkey doing some outdoor experiments pic.twitter.com/oKblEJsZ    
    
    
    Science with the boy! Not a good ending for the worm tho pic.twitter.com/sYfRABPV    
    
    
    @Villavelius @daveyp @albrummer the cluetrain left about ten years ago, if your not on it by now you may never be.    
    
    
    UK Open Access Finch report proves committees cannot innovate nor take a stand for science http://bit.ly/Ndm4l4     
    
    
    Me too! MT @petermurrayrust: http://blogs.ch.cam.ac.uk/pmr/2012/06/21/scholpub-peerj-and-tim-oreilly/ … @thePeerJ & @timoreilly. Tim can transform #scholpub if he wants to, & I hope he does.    
    
    
    The youngest @thePeerJ member!  http://yfrog.com/z/odxjupp     
    
    
    'Big data' now sounds as quaint as 'Web 2.0' hmmm    
    
    
    .@caseybergman tho in academic publishing, a typewriter w/ Internet access cld be considered a 'disruptive tech' & be true ;)    
    
    
    Just had coffee with the soon-to-be father @ianmulvany and wishing him & fam the best!    
    
    
    Pizza+beer+ tech talks tonight in London at #HNLondon - I speak abt academic publishing disruption http://bit.ly/LHHJ2G     
    
    
    Great talk about a framework for disruption by @JasonHoyt #hnlondon academic publishers must be terrified of this. #PeerJ #ftw    
    
    
    A couple of thoughts as promised @hrishio @jasonHoyt http://post.ly/81KGt     
    
    
    Slides from last night's #HNLondon on disrupting academia. http://slidesha.re/MX7L1H  Video up later at http://vimeo.com/hnlondon     
    
    
    @thePeerJ kewl. too late for me, will catch the archive. talking of which, I archived Episode 14 ;-) http://vimeo.com/6315514     
    
    
    Me + @p_binfield talk Open Access & PeerJ w/@drkiki streaming live at 7ET tonight http://twit.tv/     
    
    
    On the Internetz live in 10 mins w @drkiki & @p_binfield. We chat abt Science + @thePeerJ ...Go to http://twit.tv     
    
    
    Pulp is my pre-show music lineup for this evening    
    
    
    @MikeTaylor curently 'do you remember the first time'    
    
    
    .@jokrausdu @thepeerj @drkiki @p_binfield I was referring to biz models (i.e. payments)    
    
    
    . @miketaylor @jasonHoyt @jokrausdu @thePeerJ @drkiki @p_binfield Off the air for me as well.  Was enjoying the conversation.    
    
    
    Installed the @altmetric 'donut' in my boy's baby book. #altmetrics pic.twitter.com/YWSGWHv4    
    
    
    My talk 'A framework for disruption' is now on Slideshare homepage under 'Hot on LinkedIn' http://slidesha.re/pU8AzP     
    
    
    I'm a dad, mother is doing really well, his name is Elio, he's a cutie, arrived last night. pic.twitter.com/SCnGpP3G    
    
    
    Apparently http://rightmove.co.uk  allows leasing agents to photoshop rental pics. #shouldBeIllegal    
    
    
    Five interviews w/ Americans, each earning 5x as much as the last. http://gqm.ag/L8umMN     
    
    
    When will Silicon Valley start disrupting the banking industry? Please oh please.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt http://simple.com  is trying to. There's definitely lots of industries that need to be disrupted.    
    
    
    keep going! “@openSNPorg: Thanks to all users we've reached 200 genotypings! http://opensnp.wordpress.com/2012/07/01/milestone-reached-200-genotypings-2/ …”    
    
    
    For those who weren't around on the wkend, @p_binfield & I talk abt PeerJ + Open Access w/ @drkiki http://bit.ly/MOvh3k     
    
    
    Dream come true. @thePeerJ is finally in the same podcast (min 30+) as the Higgs Boson as told by a Kiwi http://bit.ly/PiG3AK     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt one who shares a name with a family guy character no less :)    
    
    
    New Zealand's Sciblog discusses @thePeerJ, #OA, Finch Report & Higgs in latest podcast. OA starts 30min http://bit.ly/PiG3AK     
    
    
    Awesome, sorta: @ProfBrianCox says bank bailout costlier than UK science 'since Jesus' http://bbc.in/M4bq1U     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt That’s an awfully specific dream…;)    
    
    
    The cost of NOT publishing Open Access @MikeTaylor http://svpow.com/2012/07/09/what-does-it-cost-to-publish-a-paper-with-elsevier/ …    
    
    
    Slideshare staff is featuring my talk 'A Framework for Disruption - PeerJ' on the homepage http://www.slideshare.net/  #PeerJ    
    
    
    We've just announced @thePeerJ Academic Board on the blog http://bit.ly/Oxrswr  & the board is here http://bit.ly/OxrxQL     
    
    
    @APEERsurvey @katinalynn Our vision is as good as those who accept our invitation to join. More women than men declined unfortunately.    
    
    
    We've just announced @thePeerJ Academic Board on the blog http://bit.ly/Oxrswr  & the board is here http://bit.ly/OxrxQL     
    
    
    .@robstockman @NeilWithers @professor_dave Only first 12 auths need pay w/PeerJ & that's still < PlosOne. How is that costly exactly?    
    
    
    New job at PeerJ. Looking for THE systems engineer. Details http://peerj.com/careers/     
    
    
    Hey late night London devs! Fact 437- PeerJ pops for cont. integration. We're hiring http://PeerJ.com/careers/  via @thePeerJ    
    
    
    the UK REF looks like they will move to require OA for consideration for assessment   http://www.hefce.ac.uk/news/newsarchive/2012/statementonimplementingopenaccess/ …    
    
    
    the UK REF looks like they will move to require OA for consideration for assessment   http://www.hefce.ac.uk/news/newsarchive/2012/statementonimplementingopenaccess/ …    
    
    
    "Science funding is borked." New post at Enjoy the Disruption blog - http://bit.ly/MJT6WS     
    
    
    .@ThePeerJ co-founder @JasonHoyt seems to have a new blog. http://enjoythedisruption.com/  But "All content CC-BY-NC" -- why the NC clause?    
    
    
    .@ThePeerJ co-founder @JasonHoyt seems to have a new blog. http://enjoythedisruption.com/  But "All content CC-BY-NC" -- why the NC clause?    
    
    
    "Science funding is borked." New post at Enjoy the Disruption blog - http://bit.ly/MJT6WS     
    
    
    Makes things exciting! RT @thePeerJ: PeerJ tech fact - we deploy code multiple times every day. #continuous-integration #CI    
    
    
    These two are A+ RT @thePeerJ: Hacking away at PeerJ HQ pic.twitter.com/NcOsUcTD    
    
    
    "PhDs should be aware & train for alternative science related paths." It's not alt, it's mainstream http://bit.ly/LzhhX0     
    
    
    last tweet hat tip goes to @pgroth    
    
    
    Link: http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwPoL_eq     
    
    
    Last wk I said smaller grants cld help science http://bit.ly/MJT6WS , now some say for digital health too http://bit.ly/O4ixWi     
    
    
    Last wk I said smaller grants cld help science http://bit.ly/MJT6WS , now some say for digital health too http://bit.ly/O4ixWi     
    
    
    Startup dads (and moms). Asset or liability? - New post at Enjoy the Disruption http://bit.ly/OQCqwk     
    
    
    Does anyone have numbers on the ratio of stackoverflow readers:answerers? e.g. 95:5...    
    
    
    @codinghorror ?? RT @jasonHoyt: Does anyone have numbers on the ratio of stackoverflow readers:answerers? e.g. 95:5...    
    
    
    @codinghorror ?? RT @jasonHoyt: Does anyone have numbers on the ratio of stackoverflow readers:answerers? e.g. 95:5...    
    
    
    Twitter's latest API policies bring me to one conclusion, time for devs to leave for other platforms that appreciate them    
    
    
    Found Bug #1 with OSX Mountain Lion - activation code provided by Apple is invalid cc @AppStore    
    
    
    Found Bug #1 with OSX Mountain Lion - activation code provided by Apple is invalid cc @AppStore    
    
    
    Looking for Backend Software/Sys Engineer at PeerJ. Spread the love! Thx Hacker-Jobs 4 free listing http://bit.ly/OmExM2     
    
    
    Is it Read Only Friday? http://bit.ly/GUlO3z  cc @subcide    
    
    
    Where's the anti-olog/monopoly suit against Visa et al? RT @gigaom: iZettle says it’s ‘confused’ by Visa blockade http://dlvr.it/1x5J67     
    
    
    Off to SF to monkey around w @p_binfield for a week of unconferencing & promoting Open Access #scifoo    
    
    
    Off to SF to monkey around w @p_binfield for a week of unconferencing & promoting Open Access #scifoo    
    
    
    Bye bye Quora! You can turn it off, but still... RT @HackerNewsYC: Thanks to Quora, now you can’t read anonymously http://goo.gl/fb/Mzvmu     
    
    
    On the Google shuttle w @imrankhan & a blurry-eyed @p_binfield on route to Day2 of #scifoo pic.twitter.com/0u0cnOJ5    
    
    
    Checking out a two person submarine at the Googleplex pic.twitter.com/EH3Lve2p    
    
    
    We're hiring! UI Engineer in @thePeerJ's London office http://peerj.com/careers/     
    
    
    All your base b3long to us pic.twitter.com/PyjtOuv5    
    
    
    Video of my HackerNews talk now up. "Disrupting academic publishing w @thePeerJ" http://bit.ly/PY0uhj   -Slides http://slidesha.re/MX7L1H     
    
    
    Good luck in SV! Good RT @coderholic: 2 years of #HNLondon! http://bit.ly/OibDfp     
    
    
    Cited this guy in a talk last Feb & didn't realize that I lived near his old 17th c. home (now an ugly law office). pic.twitter.com/FLudaGbD    
    
    
    Heading to DC later today for a face2face with the team building elife. #excited. Thanks to @HHMINEWS for hosting.    
    
    
    Oracle giving devs one more reason to move away from MySQL. Sucks, but perhaps inevitable.    
    
    
    Wrt last tweet, this calls for a longer blog post on the business stupidity of Oracle's latest MySQL move.    
    
    
    How the original, more radical, vision of PubMed Central was derailed by traditional publishers http://bit.ly/Nbyb4O     
    
    
    How the original, more radical, vision of PubMed Central was derailed by traditional publishers http://bit.ly/Nbyb4O     
    
    
    Pro tip: Unless your name is Gates, Jobs, Page or Brin, put more than "Here's my CV. What's the salary?" in your cover letter    
    
    
    Science data archiving - Did Amazon Glacier just come up with the answer? $0.01/GB/month. Expect 3rd party-apps to use http://bit.ly/SMioWy     
    
    
    Question: if you were pushing a production update to your website, what time of day would you do it?    
    
    
    Question: if you were pushing a production update to your website, what time of day would you do it?    
    
    
    Question: if you were pushing a production update to your website, what time of day would you do it?    
    
    
    Question: if you were pushing a production update to your website, what time of day would you do it?    
    
    
    Family day at Reading Festival. pic.twitter.com/S3PfLfrd    
    
    
    Django Django at Reading. The baby is getting more attention than most bands. pic.twitter.com/t9nwBtie    
    
    
    MT @invisiblecomma: Want to improve the UI for a new version of HubMed's Citation Finder? Fork and start editing: http://bit.ly/NDHk0q     
    
    
    A misconception that raw research data must be massaged & curated kills motivation to make it available. Release it as is.    
    
    
    Mmmm, JSON. RT @IanMulvany: fuck XML. thank you, and goodnight.    
    
    
    Another good bouldering session with @seewahcheng tonight.  I need to work on my finger strength and he needs to work on his awkwardness. :)    
    
    
    So Nature's iPad/iPhone apps are trying to charge me to view open access articles (e.g. ENCODE).    
    
    
    Knowledge cartels. Boom http://www.indexoncensorship.org/2012/09/the-battle-for-open-access/ …    
    
    
    Update on Aaron Swartz. The guy who released most of JSTOR to the public. Legal troubles. http://flpbd.it/Qpfa9     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Jason - I have emailed you on an Open Access issue via business@peerj.com. Hope it has been passed onto you.    
    
    
    ZOMG RT @invisiblecomma: Both @Scopus and @ri_science are storing passwords in plain text and email them out when asked #security    
    
    
    The challenge for scholarly societies via @cameronNeylon http://bit.ly/UZ4dS4     
    
    
    Startup pitch contests. Worst idea, perhaps ever. http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwUQgApn     
    
    
    Startup pitch contests. Worst idea, perhaps ever. http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwUQgApn     
    
    
    The Self-Destruction of the 1 Percent http://flpbd.it/RG75p     
    
    
    Don’t monkey about, support #OAWeek and sign up with @thePeerJ now.    
    
    
    me too :D RT @stephenjjohnson: Still trying to win a mug from @thePeerJ for # OAWeek    
    
    
    .@JohnRHutchinson @MikeTaylor be thankful you and your manuscripts were not alpha testers :D    
    
    
    Foood 4 thought! Noam Chomsky on Where Artificial Intelligence [& systems biology] Went Wrong http://flpbd.it/rHUVX     
    
    
    No comment "Do intelligent people drink more?" http://flpbd.it/IZhtf     
    
    
    NPG digging its own grave in quest for short-term profits with CC-BY price hike. Via @rmounce http://bit.ly/Un2Q1L     
    
    
    At the Telegraph helping 200 awesome entrepreneurs bring ideas to fruition for London StartupWeekend! pic.twitter.com/rHp4aPAG    
    
    
    At the Telegraph helping 200 awesome entrepreneurs bring ideas to fruition for London StartupWeekend! pic.twitter.com/rHp4aPAG    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt before the rest of my team SmartWard arrived on Saturday morning I made cashpools.co it needs some work!    
    
    
    rt @p_binfield: Very excited to say that PeerJ will be taking submissions from Monday! http://blog.peerj.com/post/36654776923/call-for-papers …    
    
    
    rt @p_binfield: Very excited to say that PeerJ will be taking submissions from Monday! http://blog.peerj.com/post/36654776923/call-for-papers …    
    
    
    .@subcide that's what versioning (and managing user expectations) is for! RE http://bit.ly/SG5JH1     
    
    
    .@subcide that's what versioning (and managing user expectations) is for! RE http://bit.ly/SG5JH1     
    
    
    Extreme programming/mental challenge: Coding at 8am before coffee w/ a teething, loud one-year old next to you.    
    
    
    New on SV-POW!: Crowdsourcing a database of “predatory OA journals” http://svpow.com/2012/12/06/crowdsourcing-a-database-of-predatory-oa-journals/ … Comments please, @RickyPo @CameronNeylon @rmounce    
    
    
    I'd invest in any startup that finds a way to stop this illegal trade & killing http://m.guardian.co.uk/environment/2012/dec/12/malaysia-seizes-elephant-tusks …    
    
    
    Congrats to @IanMulvany & @eLife_sciences on the new site. You've raised the bar for publishing research.    
    
    
    top tip, when bringing a spare pare of trousers into work in case of wet cycle, don’t bring wife’s trousers (unless she is bigger than you).    
    
    
    As a father to 2 young boys, my heart goes out to the family of the Sandy Hook victims. I'll join the US in a moment of silence at 9:30 ET    
    
    
    I can see investors jumping on the #snowfall bandwagon, only to be raked over. The beauty is because it was first.    
    
    
    NIH budget to be cut by 8.2% due to fiscal cliff failure. Only 2 days left to save it. http://j.mp/W90oa2     
    
    
    Surprise! More security probs for Internet Explorer 8 users. http://flip.it/cqGOA     
    
    
    A bone to pick: not enough product-market fit - Building a startup ... http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwbBYNRI     
    
    
    My comment on why XMP for researchers & publishers -  http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwbGi-bW     
    
    
    Design by committee MT @MikeTaylor: the naming of "PubMed" and "PubMed Central" (two completely different things) is a total train-wreck.    
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor Oh, and don't forget the confusion over medline vs PubMed that most researchers have.    
    
    
    Someone just sent their resume into @thePeerJ as an info graphic and QR code. Awesome.    
    
    
    Ha. New #altmetrics paper by @researchremix at Nature's paywall here http://bit.ly/VT6mwH  or free here http://bit.ly/RHH72Q     
    
    
    And of course that free version is from a startup owned by a Nature sister company.    
    
    
    Putting real science into sci-fi RT @NathanFillion: My favorite Firefly fanboy rant to date.
http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/guest-blog/2013/01/10/saving-lives-in-serenity-can-a-fanboy-and-physics-change-a-movie/ …    
    
    
    Aaron Swartz found dead, but lives on with Open Access - http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwbaCi9I     
    
    
    WH petition to fire US Attorney who wanted Aaron Swartz in jail 35 yrs for downloading science articles http://wh.gov/Ex1n     
    
    
    http://nature.com  seems to be down.  Hmmmm    
    
    
    Twitter should stop forcing the use of their URL shortener until they can actually resolve links. Just sayin' cc @MikeTaylor    
    
    
    Twitter should stop forcing the use of their URL shortener until they can actually resolve links. Just sayin' cc @MikeTaylor    
    
    
    It pays to lobby RT @HarvardBiz: Aaron Swartz's "Crime" and the Business of Breaking the Law http://flip.it/qFWyz     
    
    
    Not too late to sign the White House petition to investigate the US attorney resp for Aaron Swartz http://wh.gov/Ex1n     
    
    
    And good news, 26K+ signatures on petition to remove US Attorney Carmen Ortiz, also resp for Aaron Swartz http://1.usa.gov/UVfNgo     
    
    
    Open Access & Editorial Quality event at Wellcome Trust Feb 6 http://bit.ly/VOcSE  Note: PeerJ not on panel :(    
    
    
    it is nothing short of obscene how richly rewarded publishers are for the very modest part they play in the scientific enterprise    
    
    
    Are academic publishers extracting value & wealth from scientists? http://bit.ly/VJJEL7     
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor Good ex of 2º revenue stream from reuse despite CC-BY is @plos.    
    
    
    When stealing isn't stealing - The most disturbing part of the Aaron Swartz story - http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwc1sxlD     
    
    
    When stealing isn't stealing - The most disturbing part of the Aaron Swartz story - http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwc1sxlD     
    
    
    From earlier: When stealing isn't stealing - The most disturbing part of the Aaron Swartz story - http://bit.ly/10F4cby     
    
    
    Meg Hillier, my local MP, actually did something about my UK Visa - Foreign entrepreneurship http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwcC1Z6i     
    
    
    I 'm angry. The UK Border Agency has held my passport hostage for 5 months. Way to support your entrepreneurs David Cameron.    
    
    
    Awful RT @hrishio: .@jasonHoyt mine for 3 months. No tracking system. No help line. Can't believe they can get away with it. #ukvisa    
    
    
    .@PatrickSocha @hrishio @ernestopriego I assume David Cameron et al don't really understand foreign investment opportunity    
    
    
    jQuery Blog » jQuery 1.9 final, jQuery 2.0 beta, Migrate final released http://buff.ly/VI21jt     
    
    
    Whodathunk the FB like button wld have a huge conspiracy of being evil?! Remember when FriendFeed first intro'd it? http://bit.ly/WPPneb     
    
    
    I 'm angry. The UK Border Agency has held my passport hostage for 5 months. Way to support your entrepreneurs David Cameron.    
    
    
    My partner is Welsh. Scared MT @JohnRunions: Welshman Paul Marshallsea becomes head of Wales' shark wrestling team!  http://bbc.in/13Vrskq     
    
    
    MIT tries to dampen the tone in investigation of #aaronsw tragedy by now calling it an "analysis" of its role http://nyti.ms/VI0iK8     
    
    
    Wrt last tweet - ie "investigation" suggests probable fault, "analysis" suggests no apology needed, but could improve.    
    
    
    The ensuing privacy debacle for FaceBook's new graph search, in images (actual graph searches) http://bit.ly/TiNEmA     
    
    
    I was halfway to work this morning before I realized I was wearing @codinghorror’s coat. Oops. pic.twitter.com/31RSPg9j    
    
    
    A "free" @virginatlantic return ticket costs $700 in taxes and fees, of which $458 is a carrier imposed fuel/insurance charge.    
    
    
    Death of Spock: Wrath of bathtime baby pic.twitter.com/bqQMZ8QB    
    
    
    .@IanMulvany yes, issue #1 they're using godaddy  :)    
    
    
    .@IanMulvany and http://impactstory.com  redirects to a kickstarter project.    
    
    
    I felt the same abt academic publishing "Fuck it, I'll Do This Alone." http://flip.it/9k6NR     
    
    
    It would be so much less contentious if CC-BY-NC licences for #openaccess were instead CC-BY-NS (No [re-]Sale), allowing datamining etc.    
    
    
    If a publisher goes bankrupt, what are the consequences for OA vs. paywall articles? @MikeTaylor answers http://bit.ly/TQFi66     
    
    
    If a publisher goes bankrupt, what are the consequences for OA vs. paywall articles? @MikeTaylor answers http://bit.ly/TQFi66     
    
    
    Heartbreaking to hear all the pithering in the #HoL inquirty, even from the Good Guys. No-one with guts to make the fundamental points.    
    
    
    Most people don't understand that an architect's primary duty is dealing with bureaucracy.    
    
    
    Considering Amazon's "aesthetics," I can't decide what its 4 pages of job listings for design/UX means. http://amzn.to/XdapDH     
    
    
    I noticed @pandoDaily 's redesigned site is easier to read if you shrink desktop browser  to phone width. Bad design on full    
    
    
    I'm considering diversifying/hedging my family's future by getting started w bitcoins. Problem #1: I have no idea what they are    
    
    
    I noticed @pandoDaily 's redesigned site is easier to read if you shrink desktop browser  to phone width. Bad design on full    
    
    
    I'm considering diversifying/hedging my family's future by getting started w bitcoins. Problem #1: I have no idea what they are    
    
    
    Why sauropods had long necks; and why giraffes have short necks https://peerj.com/articles/36/  via @thePeerJ    
    
    
    One more thing 21st c. publishing brings - How @thePeerJ's architecture keeps costs down for academics http://bit.ly/11QAe4Q     
    
    
    Whale teeth & treating wounds with cannabinoids are part of this week's new images + #OA articles on PeerJ https://peerj.com     
    
    
    Biology is in a slump - we need error logs to get out of it http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVweXYKPJ     
    
    
    Nice these researchers get $3M in prizes each, but all are well-off already. Young scientists wld be better http://bit.ly/Ym7Ore     
    
    
    .@simonbayly yes, not very inspiring to the young scientists (the prize's stated goal) if they have to wait a lifetime    
    
    
    Former PhD mentor today, "Rejected from Nature Thurs (3 mo. in review), scooped in PLOS Bio following Tues." Spot the problem    
    
    
    Former PhD mentor today, "Rejected from Nature Thurs (3 mo. in review), scooped in PLOS Bio following Tues." Spot the problem    
    
    
    Former PhD mentor today, "Rejected from Nature Thurs (3 mo. in review), scooped in PLOS Bio following Tues." Spot the problem    
    
    
    Former PhD mentor today, "Rejected from Nature Thurs (3 mo. in review), scooped in PLOS Bio following Tues." Spot the problem    
    
    
    I'm in Wales!    
    
    
    @subcide I'm going to head down to the biscuit factory tonight.    
    
    
    Asking publishers abt OA laws MT @brembs I think it's like asking the tobacco industry to chime in with their opinion on smoking bans    
    
    
    Asking publishers abt OA laws MT @brembs I think it's like asking the tobacco industry to chime in with their opinion on smoking bans    
    
    
    If US/UK public was clearly informed on who's helping shape OA policy (self interested publishers) then embargoes wldnt exist    
    
    
    Well done National Museum Wales in Cardiff on the natural history exhibit @amgueddfaCymru    
    
    
    Lots of misconceptions in this article on #openaccess that I couldn't resist responding to. Much still to be done. http://bit.ly/XtWIEp     
    
    
    Hey Google, get off your ass & help this guy w his copyright issue. "Your IP: does Google care? http://flip.it/p0Wao "    
    
    
    I agree. "Publishers, whose role is to disseminate information" are now blockades to research says @mbeisen http://bit.ly/VFZG8v     
    
    
    “@Protohedgehog: This plot of APC vs 'openness' by @rmounce is a much more informed overview of Gold OA #OAintheUK http://bit.ly/Yu5Mt7     
    
    
    Seems 2 grad students @Protohedgehog @rmounce are more knowledgeable abt Gold OA costs than RCUK & Finch Comm #OAintheUK    
    
    
    Pay once; don't think again w PeerJ MT @franknorman: Padgett highlights practical difficulties with APCs: purchasing proc & collab papers    
    
    
    It occurs to me that sites like Storify are the modern equivalents of revisionist history &  = good/bad for humanity    
    
    
    Awesome for babies RT @jjodx: AMAZING!!!: Scientists Uncover Invisible Motion in Video http://nyti.ms/13kIg5R     
    
    
    .@mbeisen @rravi plus their suits/hair are tacky & worn only by out-of-touch publishers & hipsters re:http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMp1211259 …    
    
    
    Groupon CEO fired, stock at 25% its IPO & here was my call 2+ yrs ago on Google's $6B offer, just sayin' http://bit.ly/15lVe1w     
    
    
    A breakup letter to scholarly publishers from @srp (steve pettifer) http://bit.ly/VR5GLr     
    
    
    Years on it, I still can't figure out how LinkedIn is useful to me or most other users; besides the spam requests    
    
    
    Hey @Twitter, make sure the @TweetDeck for Web is at least half as good (for tweeting) as the Air app before retiring Air.    
    
    
    With that LinkedIn rant over, here's a good slide deck from the LinkedIn data science team http://slidesha.re/ZfZM4b     
    
    
    "Pete & Jason are eating ramen noodles so you don't have to" - suggested slogan to authors from PeerJ editor @stephenjjohnson    
    
    
    If you are in the UK under no circumstances use @Morgan_Randall as a letting agent. So bad, I'm notifying the housing authority    
    
    
    Subscription publishers & their effective lobbying efforts (paid by subscriptions) against Open Access http://bit.ly/ZtgC19     
    
    
    Hope the Internet pushes Sun co-founder Khosla to do the right thing & allow access to Cali beach http://nydn.us/Z5lBmv     
    
    
    MT @thePeerJ: Interview w/ PeerJ AE Jen Wagner "What researcher wld choose a process other than PeerJ?" http://blog.peerj.com/post/45838032441/jennifer-wagner-interview …    
    
    
    Oh my. Had forgotten about Tapes n' Tapes until just now.    
    
    
    Why the invasion of Iraq was the single worst foreign policy decision in American history http://flip.it/P1yob     
    
    
    PeerJ: legit?    
    
    
    Another example of research hidden for months due to academic publishing norms http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwgvdebl     
    
    
    WaPo publishes info-map of country "friendliness toward foreigners." Surely the US is shld be divided into states http://wapo.st/WWmpyQ     
    
    
    Reason no.7 - monkeys RT @thePeerJ: Six reasons to submit your next article to PeerJ http://blog.peerj.com/post/46261563342/6-reasons-to-publish-with-peerj …    
    
    
    .@ScholarlyChickn PeerJ has stated since launch (http://bit.ly/YufcYV ) that it would work with institutions. What are you getting at?    
    
    
    CEO of T&F parent corp income £1.9M, CEO of PLOS £298K, CEO of PeerJ (me) £47K. I don't believe in obscene profiting off EDU    
    
    
    based on http://bit.ly/YEqCt6  via @rmounce    
    
    
    CEO of T&F parent corp income £1.9M, CEO of PLOS £298K, CEO of PeerJ (me) £47K. I don't believe in obscene profiting off EDU    
    
    
    CEO of T&F parent corp income £1.9M, CEO of PLOS £298K, CEO of PeerJ (me) £47K. I don't believe in obscene profiting off EDU    
    
    
    "CC-BY under attack from the International Assoc. of Scientific, Technical & Medical Publishers" aka not the future http://bit.ly/14wfXC9     
    
    
    <3 copy RT@David_Dobbs: Conservatives, feathers ruffled by twisted duck-dick research, demand US withdraw penis funds http://phenomena.nationalgeographic.com/2013/03/25/ducks-meet-the-culture-wars/ …    
    
    
    SSP now claims "non-OA articles are seen by the right audience." Nice euphemism for 'restricted to those who can afford it'    
    
    
    .@srp Exactly. Science spies & evil countries are forced to use only OA articles. As they could never afford subscription fees.    
    
    
    @LibSkrat Sorry, didn't mean to exclude! We covered Instit. Repos, but is there any thing in particular abt libraries? cc @p_binfield    
    
    
    .@researchremix @tjvision Congratulations on being first! #PeerJPreprints    
    
    
    MT @invisiblecomma: articles analysed in http://bit.ly/10zau7M  not in Google search results; low rank for multiple domains or dup content?    
    
    
    Opinion: MOOCs all the rage, but #openaccess has greater societal potential http://chronicle.com/article/The-Real-Digital-Change-Agent/137589/ …    
    
    
    Up early to take a full day of abuse from strangers :) it's going to be a long day...    
    
    
    My thoughts on Mendeley/Elsevier & why I left to start PeerJ - I joined Mendeley as head of R&D at the start... http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwiGtFGt     
    
    
    My thoughts on Mendeley/Elsevier & why I left to start PeerJ - I joined Mendeley as head of R&D at the start... http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwiGtFGt     
    
    
    My thoughts on Mendeley/Elsevier & why I left to start PeerJ - I joined Mendeley as head of R&D at the start... http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwiGtFGt     
    
    
    If someone said in plosone/PeerJ cover letter that want to publish if peer reviewers accept, but won't do revisions, wld paper be refused?    
    
    
    If someone said in plosone/PeerJ cover letter that want to publish if peer reviewers accept, but won't do revisions, wld paper be refused?    
    
    
    To Masters students at #EGU2013, if you're not going to publish your thesis, consider using @figshare! e.g. http://bit.ly/X5fUJk     
    
    
    FYI William Gunn is a great asset to Mendeley MT @mrgunn: I joined [Mendeley] to make #altmetrics a thing, & that work continues    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt It would seem that  "darling" is the word of the day for both of us. http://chronicle.com/article/In-Sale-to-Elsevier-Mendeley/138449/ …    
    
    
    @FakeElsevier @ColditzJB @wilbanks @skome We haven't gone anywhere. It's too soon to say that we can't do any good anymore.    
    
    
    On train London > Oxford for today's rigour & openness conf. I need some rigorous coffee.    
    
    
    I signed the Cost of Knowledge to boycott Elsevier #mendelete (sad day) pic.twitter.com/vsqTt4Qfnr    
    
    
    Inspiring MT @ethanwhite: Pace of science is changing. Our new preprint cites @researchremix's preprint frm last week http://bit.ly/17v9BTk     
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor @kaythaney Graham Taylor said 1st peer review 1665    
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor @kaythaney Some evidence suggests 1st peer-review much later (http://bit.ly/YQ6ySm ) & I cited that in Who killed the preprint    
    
    
    MT @MikeTaylor: New on SV-POW!: The evolution-or-revolution debate at the Oxford Union http://bit.ly/ZVhKju  #openOxford    
    
    
    Give 'em hell (& OA)! RT @CameronNeylon: At Committee room 6 UK Houses of Parliament #BIS committee hearing on #openaccess    
    
    
    And b4 PeerJ RT @MikeTaylor: #BISOA @CameronNeylon says high APCs estimated by Finch derive from systemic market failure    
    
    
    Mendeley's new overlord, Elsevier lobbying at #bisoa MT @RLUK_David: @wisealic says repositories should be for everything except articles    
    
    
    "Journal of negative embargoes?" @MikeTaylor @CameronNeylon #bisoa @peerjPrePrints #arxiv    
    
    
    Elsevier et al trying to convince #bisoa that they're too big to let fail. Hint: they're not. PLOS, ELife, PeerJ, F1000, etc    
    
    
    Elsevier's argument (link http://bit.ly/13anab7 ) to UK Parliament seems to be "but OA will jeopardize our biz model"  #bisoa    
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor @Stephen_Curry Microsoft, AT&T, etc made similar arguments to uphold their monopolies as well    
    
    
    Actual Elsevier arg to #bisoa "16. Green OA is not a biz model & therefore has no revenue stream associated with it" http://bit.ly/13anab7     
    
    
    The logic of pt. 17 in Elsevier's #bisoa evidence wld suggest http://arXiv.org  is harming physics w/ preprints http://bit.ly/13anab7     
    
    
    The real elephant in the room is "shld tax payers continue to subsidize 30K jobs at Elsevier, etc?" #bisoa    
    
    
    .@BioMickWatson Agree. And now that publishing is more efficient, we can move those tax-payer funded jobs to other areas    
    
    
    Amen RT @Villavelius: Low quality articles a threat to the scientific record? The threat is all the stuff that's not published    
    
    
    Cool new tool for #authors: Elsevier Journal Finder. Matches your abstract to best-fit journal http://goo.gl/tfqS2  #elsevier #beta    
    
    
        
    
    
    A decision tree on where to send your next manuscript via @MikeTaylor http://www.miketaylor.org.uk/tmp/journal-finder.html …    
    
    
    A decision tree on where to send your next manuscript via @MikeTaylor http://www.miketaylor.org.uk/tmp/journal-finder.html …    
    
    
    Fond memories of learning abt Lac Operon in college. Francois Jacob has died. http://bit.ly/12yKdKf  h/t @DeepFriedDNA    
    
    
    @simonbayly Ha. The work describing the open source code for the bio transistor is behind a paywall in Science http://bit.ly/15ATGnb     
    
    
    Baffling. Authors place Stanford study w/ Open Source bio transistors behind a paywall in Science http://bit.ly/11DpyRd     
    
    
    Surprise. Another bad show by Google. Bottom line, don't trust them with your data http://bit.ly/11y1v7G     
    
    
        
    
    
    Under my mattress RT @MikeTaylor: @jasonHoyt Where do you keep your email?    
    
    
    .@MikeTaylor I think it cld be time for some regulatory measures, e.g. required notice of acct cancellation for email/storage providers    
    
    
    I received this in the PeerJ mailbag pic.twitter.com/3fYvC63JoI    
    
    
    Thiel's "change the world" fellowships for 20yrolds incl Dropbox clone & selling your salary 4 equity. Hmm http://flip.it/qtFRh     
    
    
    Joy. The 18 month old has gotten into a "wake up at 5am routine" all week.    
    
    
    Joy. The 18 month old has gotten into a "wake up at 5am routine" all week.    
    
    
    .@datadryad will soon be introducing submission fees http://blog.datadryad.org/2013/04/29/submission-fees-to-be-introduced-in-september-2013/ … This is a good thing for the sustainability of the service    
    
    
    .@datadryad will soon be introducing submission fees http://blog.datadryad.org/2013/04/29/submission-fees-to-be-introduced-in-september-2013/ … This is a good thing for the sustainability of the service    
    
    
    The Economist print version name checks PeerJ & other usual suspects in Open Access http://econ.st/121pOLI     
    
    
    ... and now hosted at Github: https://github.com/beiko-lab/gengis …. GenGIS manuscript is submitted, hopefully coming soon to @thePeerJ preprints.    
    
    
    LinkedIn (LNKD) down 10% on day when markets every where are rocketing up. More proof the site is vapor?    
    
    
    Subtle. Facebook changes "Promote your post" to "Boost your post." Presumably boost seems less like selling to your friends?    
    
    
    I seem to recall Google claiming they'd only use their patents as a defense. Guess not http://bit.ly/16f25wV     
    
    
    .@DOAJplus Hi DOAJ - PeerJ has asked multiple times to be included, any progress? Already indexed in PMC cc @david_prosser    
    
    
    .@DOAJplus Hi DOAJ - PeerJ has asked multiple times to be included, any progress? Already indexed in PMC cc @david_prosser    
    
    
    I predict bioRxiv from CSHL press will flop (http://bit.ly/ZODlYs ) - few biologist preprint or comment & CSHL press lacks #oa credibility    
    
    
    I predict bioRxiv from CSHL press will flop (http://bit.ly/ZODlYs ) - few biologist preprint or comment & CSHL press lacks #oa credibility    
    
    
    For the record, I fully support biologists preprinting at #arxiv - I see no need for clones that fragment this space.    
    
    
    Elsevier CEO: "That is also open access, but it’s paid for by the librarian" http://www.nature.com/embor/journal/v4/n8/pdf/embor913.pdf … Dammit, that is NOT WHAT THE WORDS MEAN.    
    
    
    @EndoMetabPub True, tho output in line w expectations after large launch. Submissions ++ mo/mo as word spreads.    
    
    
    Academic publishing costs & the blind man's bluff http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwkaKb9t     
    
    
    Great experience w/ @TransferWise. Luv taking the middleman (the bank & FX traders) out of FX transfers.    
    
    
    Contemplating deleting my LinkedIn. Just spam...from them #2ndLinkedInhateTweetOfWeek    
    
    
    Oh well, our J Neurosci appeal failed. New rev also hung up about null result, even tho strongly supported by Bayes. Pub bias in action.    
    
    
    And like that, first outside pull request to the London #hack4ac  website repo ! http://bit.ly/10yYtOa     
    
    
    CHORUS: It’s actually spelled C-A-B-A-L http://bit.ly/181qesu     
    
    
    ResearchGate to nowhere? - I'm baffled by its $35M funding round http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwmjc0AA     
    
    
    Agree MT @beccarosen: Every single sentence in that Larry Page post can be narrowly interpreted to allow for the existence of PRISM.    
    
    
    A CHORUS of falsettos. @CameronNeylon dissects paywall publisher plan to shutdown PubMedCentral http://bit.ly/13qKSgz     
    
    
    "I’m a little baffled by the recent $35M funding round for ResearchGate" - @jasonhoyt http://enjoythedisruption.com/post/52304544394/researchgate-to-nowhere … You ain't the only one!    
    
    
    If the NSA program at the cost of civil liberties is so effective, why did Boston still happen?    
    
    
    Interesting that not a single story abt NSA leak above the fold on NYTimes.    
    
    
    There! RT @thePeerJ: Hack4ac - A London Hackday to celebrate CC-BY on July 6th http://bit.ly/14T40Sh     
    
    
    Ha! RT @skonkiel: The Scholarly Kitchen "shakes things up" by adding two more middle-aged white dudes to its homogeneous roster of authors    
    
    
    OA jnls have simpler & more transparent financial model says @MikeTaylor http://tinyurl.com/lddvcdp  Does this hold for non-APC funding sources?    
    
    
    OA jnls have simpler & more transparent financial model says @MikeTaylor http://tinyurl.com/lddvcdp  Does this hold for non-APC funding sources?    
    
    
    OA jnls have simpler & more transparent financial model says @MikeTaylor http://tinyurl.com/lddvcdp  Does this hold for non-APC funding sources?    
    
    
    OA jnls have simpler & more transparent financial model says @MikeTaylor http://tinyurl.com/lddvcdp  Does this hold for non-APC funding sources?    
    
    
    Yay. Github finally trimming some of its fat https://github.com/blog/1529-repository-next …    
    
    
    Go Pete! MT @jimtill: OA Now interview w/ @p_binfield of @thePeerJ http://bit.ly/19QA5Bf  #OpenAccess via @OpenAccessNow    
    
    
    Asking why funders don't demand full OA via @MikeTaylor http://svpow.com/2013/06/19/funders-have-all-the-power-in-oa-negotiations-so-why-arent-they-using-it …    
    
    
    #science “@BetaScience: Last night I gave the guest speech at graduation for my old high school. Here it is: https://www.facebook.com/morgan.langille/posts/10151437992746433 … #SRHS”    
    
    
    Cynic in me says, "Wow. Obama is really trumpeting climate change policy lately. Surely not to drown out domestic spying concerns!"    
    
    
    The @NewYorker suggesting mainstream journalists no longer a voice of opposition to gov't http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/johncassidy/2013/06/demonizing-edward-snowden-which-side-are-you-on.html … #snowden    
    
    
    A plug for my favorite London DJ in Wales (& our kids share blood). If you need a bespoke DJ at your next UK event http://www.epicstereo.co.uk/services.php     
    
    
    The Zuck wld've said "OA - It's happening, bitch" MT @p_binfield: My preso shld've been title "OA - It's Happening!" http://blog.peerj.com/post/53830570248/open-access-whats-happening …    
    
    
    Wonders if we can get more women involved in this hack event geared toward academics in London July 6 http://hack4ac.eventbrite.co.uk/     
    
    
    Wonders if we can get more women involved in this hack event geared toward academics in London July 6 http://hack4ac.eventbrite.co.uk/     
    
    
    @DrMagennis @essiepett Novices welcome. There will be informal offers to show you the ropes, perhaps a quick "bootcamp" & non-coders needed    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/f0MTtwCgxQ    
    
    
    Wonders if we can get more women involved in this hack event geared toward academics in London July 6 http://hack4ac.eventbrite.co.uk/     
    
    
    One week to go and nearly full capacity for #hack4ac already!!! http://hack4ac.eventbrite.co.uk/     
    
    
    Am I missing something with Medium? I see no value-add to using it over other blogging platforms.    
    
    
    Am I missing something with Medium? I see no value-add to using it over other blogging platforms.    
    
    
    Am I missing something with Medium? I see no value-add to using it over other blogging platforms.    
    
    
    Someone missed the memo on the benefits of Open Access http://andrewgelman.com/2013/07/02/19268/ …    
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Made my 1st comments on @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints last night. I actually do feel incentivized by the points system https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    I do meta-analyses myself so overall I like the paper. Just a couple of things I'd tweak @cjlortie's @PeerJPrePrints https://peerj.com/preprints/39/     
    
    
    Of all the US Independence days in my lifetime, today's is the most important. #restoreTheFourth #nsa http://www.restorethefourth.net     
    
    
    Science funding is borked: Part II http://bit.ly/18xPKFq     
    
    
    Anyone used Masonry / Isotope / Packery JS libraries in production before?  Any gotchas?  Any clearly better than the others?    
    
    
    Retraction of 19-year-old Nature paper reveals hidden cameras, lab break-in, evidence tampering http://bit.ly/12foUtf     
    
    
    Just at skillsMatter venue prepping tomorrow's #hack4ac w @IanMulvany. Freaking awesome venue! http://hack4ac.com     
    
    
    With @IanMulvany & today's #hack4ac geek prizes pic.twitter.com/mNtGb1GPPm    
    
    
    #hack4ac is about to kickoff pic.twitter.com/kL0QhfN1Mf    
    
    
    #hack4ac pitches on the wall up for voting pic.twitter.com/2O5wFrAK1S    
    
    
    About five main teams have formed at #hack4ac event. Teams off & very focused atm.    
    
    
    Shit, my alarm failed to go off again - still worth rocking over to #hack4ac? CC @rmounce @IanMulvany    
    
    
    @rmounce 12,16,29,31,57,74,77,82    
    
    
    ScienceGist a new tool at #hack4ac presenting pic.twitter.com/2rdmeZPUM6    
    
    
    Now "PLOS Author Contributions" built at #hack4ac (& uses @thePeerJ data) pic.twitter.com/wr6H5Nv21V    
    
    
    Reservoirdogs at #hack4ac classifying @thePeerJ papers based on methods pic.twitter.com/sIY2vfWixf    
    
    
    "figures to data" project at #hack4ac showing best figure ever pic.twitter.com/g7I9B5dKqx    
    
    
    "Figures > Data" project transforms figures from @PLOS @thePeerJ BMC @figshare into CSV files pic.twitter.com/pgwlam6GuU    
    
    
    And the #hack4ac delegates cooling off in the London heat w a pint pic.twitter.com/PjoOmGrMfQ    
    
    
    The giants of #hack4ac Daniel, Matt, & @petermurrayrust pic.twitter.com/eEcpc83BNe    
    
    
    Married last weekend yet still at makes @juretriglav the trooper of #hack4ac (on right) w @IanMulvany pic.twitter.com/w0keJ87nNI    
    
    
    Answering 25 tough interview questions, part 5 http://wp.me/pPtWk-P9     
    
    
    2 of hacking, 2 dozen of drinking. Perfect! RT @IanMulvany: Some pictures from #hack4ac http://www.flickr.com/photos/mulvanynet/sets/72157634547992581/ …    
    
    
    Just realized @thePeerJ has published more than 100 articles in its first 5 months.    
    
    
    1st annual @thePeerJ family BBQ! pic.twitter.com/6jlUHG7nEZ    
    
    
    The "Shazam of bioacoustics" paper discussed on NPR science https://peerj.com/articles/103/     
    
    
    Hey, look: manuscripts don't require authors! #PeerJ pic.twitter.com/aSmOJthCHO    
    
    
    US House has voted to allow NSA to continue the mass phone metadata collection of all citizens. Welcome the Surveillance State    
    
    
    US House has voted to allow NSA to continue the mass phone metadata collection of all citizens. Welcome the Surveillance State    
    
    
    Amash amendment loses 217: 205.    
    
    
    US House has voted to allow NSA to continue the mass phone metadata collection of all citizens. Welcome the Surveillance State    
    
    
    Lawmakers Who Upheld NSA Phone Spying Received 2x the Defense Industry Cash http://flip.it/C7VOu     
    
    
    Wrt last tweet, it's an outrage, but sadly not surprising    
    
    
    TGIF- the day starts with a 4 hour LEED meeting in a jobsite trailer.    
    
    
    TGIF- the day starts with a 4 hour LEED meeting in a jobsite trailer.    
    
    
    Putting together my Facebook advertising presentation for the @distilled  meetup on Thursday from The Spaniards Inn on Hampstead Heath #yeah    
    
    
    @rmounce @Mart_the_Thomps Doesn't look like that metagenomics paper has free access.    
    
    
    Most popular news in NZ today: "Woman steals ID to go partying", "How to get out of a parking ticket", and "How (not) to load a digger". #nz    
    
    
    So, PeerJ PrePrints? ;) MT @eperlste: @neurobongo @debivort ... attempt to hack PLOS ONE/PeerJ model (& sprinkle in arXiv)    
    
    
    Yep, not Open Access MT @rmounce: I am deeply unimpressed that ResearchGate & http://Academia.edu  *force* you to login to download PDFs    
    
    
    Yep, not Open Access MT @rmounce: I am deeply unimpressed that ResearchGate & http://Academia.edu  *force* you to login to download PDFs    
    
    
    Thx to @IanMulvany coming to babysit, the lady & I are going out for an overdue date night!    
    
    
    Elsevier allegedly deleting comments on its Open Access video if competitors mentioned e.g. PeerJ http://vimeo.com/72755742     
    
    
    Full conversation between Elsevier rep & commenters about Open Access comment removal https://twitter.com/Protohedgehog/status/369878772222160897 …    
    
    
    Alleged deletion of comments on new Elsevier video - is that innovating? Blogged http://bit.ly/1aqFcc8     
    
    
    For @MikeTaylor & other sauropod lovers pic.twitter.com/5EatEeRPdC    
    
    
    Question - Any anecdotes of authors NOT citing a source because it does not have a DOI (just a URL)? How common is this?    
    
    
    "Who Will Pay for Public Access to Research Data?" reprint (PDF) at http://www.sciencemag.org/content/341/6146/616.full.pdf?keytype=ref&siteid=sci&ijkey=.e2Ezowko%2FxF2 …    
    
    
    "Who Will Pay for Public Access to Research Data?" reprint (PDF) at http://www.sciencemag.org/content/341/6146/616.full.pdf?keytype=ref&siteid=sci&ijkey=.e2Ezowko%2FxF2 …    
    
    
    6yr old comment on O'Reilly Radar on Saas + GPL predicts the commoditization of services like Google http://oreil.ly/19FmHOg     
    
    
    Thank you VirginMedia for increasing my broadband by £4.25/mo this year. Only a 13% increase this year. Totally reasonable.    
    
    
    http://Peers.org , a grassroots org founded by...corporations? Nice tear down of the "movement" at http://bit.ly/1dYHLSB     
    
    
    @SonyUK Your SEN has been down/up all week. Your lack of communication in forums is apalling. Returning new Bravia ASAP    
    
    
    If it is less expensive, does that mean quality goes down? #openAccess http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwuIUVo8     
    
    
    Why aren't we doing more about the surveillance revelations? Post on EnjoyTheDisruption http://bit.ly/17RHbkN     
    
    
    Can someone fire this Pax brogrammer already? http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwufXkrL     
    
    
    Would it be unfair to summarise the new BIS #OpenAccess report as "We're not going to be your bitches any more, publishers"?    
    
    
    .@jasonHoyt well done. And good luck for the future.    
    
    
    Thoughts on ALPSP and future of society publishers - http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwv0Nbhc     
    
    
    Thoughts on ALPSP and future of society publishers - http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwv0Nbhc     
    
    
    Schmidt won't "pass judgment" because he benefits from it [spying] - Guardian http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/sep/13/eric-schmidt-google-nsa-surveillance …    
    
    
    No, not really. RT @LSEImpactBlog: Programming is becoming an essential tool to every field of research. http://j.mp/16e0Ppv     
    
    
    Slightly uncomfortable granting @papersapp modification rights to *every* file on my dropbox account in order to sync :/    
    
    
    Slightly uncomfortable granting @papersapp modification rights to *every* file on my dropbox account in order to sync :/    
    
    
    Oh dear. Misguided piece in @timeshighered re need for Impact Factors in #REF2014. http://bit.ly/18f6uj1  I've commented    
    
    
    Oh dear. Misguided piece in @timeshighered re need for Impact Factors in #REF2014. http://bit.ly/18f6uj1  I've commented    
    
    
    Definition of New England (in my mind) RT @David_Dobbs: One of my favorite trees, in driveway next door. http://instagram.com/p/eziuISTQyR/     
    
    
    One of my favorite trees, in driveway next door. #maples #autumn #vermont @ The Meadow http://instagram.com/p/eziuISTQyR/     
    
    
    One of my favorite trees, in driveway next door. #maples #autumn #vermont @ The Meadow http://instagram.com/p/eziuISTQyR/     
    
    
    WTF is up with Apple of late? - User testing fail http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVwwDna4B     
    
    
    Rightly so.  US scientists boycott Nasa conference over China ban http://flip.it/e6pHl     
    
    
    Arctic research halts for first time in decades due to shutdown, meanwhile Congress continues getting perks http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/10/09/congress-government-shutdown_n_4065432.html …    
    
    
    This is bad, really bad. Science has paywalled a retraction h/t @MikeTaylor http://www.sciencemag.org/content/342/6155/191.1.full …    
    
    
    This is bad, really bad. Science has paywalled a retraction h/t @MikeTaylor http://www.sciencemag.org/content/342/6155/191.1.full …    
    
    
    Finally removed the annoying virus on my Web experience, otherwise known as Google+    
    
    
    46 million yrs-old and it still makes me feel itchy http://bit.ly/WYJU7w  h/t @Protohedgehog    
    
    
    No, you & D.C. put the world at risk - House Speaker John Boehner: "We fought the good fight, we just didn't win." http://on.cnn.com/19RW4Zc     
    
    
    Indeed, biggest week yet for PeerJ MT @thePeerJ: For #OAWeek next week, we have a great selection of articles & all have open reviews!    
    
    
    Seriously loving the pink PeerJ Charlie for Breast Cancer Awareness Month pic.twitter.com/unhtw63U8I    
    
    
    Is this SSP's new Pres? "Who are you? What qualifies you to edit this? I would love to compare credentials ..." http://en.wikipedia.org/w/index.php?title=User_talk:Scholarly_kitchen …    
    
    
    I just answered, "What does Open Access mean to you?" https://peerj.com/answers/33/     
    
    
    Yes! Obamacare Program Released On 35 Floppy Disks http://www.theonion.com/articles/new-improved-obamacare-program-released-on-35-flop,34294/ …    
    
    
    Well deserved! RT @wilbanks: Third #SciASAP award goes to @EvoMRI for his work on making it easy to integrate OA content into Wikipedia.    
    
    
    Loving today's PeerJ featured image from the Farke et al Baby Dino study https://peerj.com     
    
    
    From now on I am blaming all PeerJ 'glitches' on Obamacare contractors & my dog    
    
    
    From now on I am blaming all PeerJ 'glitches' on Obamacare contractors & my dog    
    
    
    *switches phone to silent mode*    
    
    
    Apples says 200M devices running iOS7 just 5 days after release. How many happy users though?    
    
    
    "if you let me brush your teeth then I'll let him [plastic hippo] fart on your arm" - Partner negotiating w our 2yr old's demand for farts    
    
    
    BS. We did it at Mendeley MT @mrgunn: Anurag highlights the problem of signing restrictive licensing deals as reason no API #scielo15    
    
    
    Real reason - Google doesn't really like open re: lack of Google Scholar API cc @mrgunn #scielo15    
    
    
    Real reason - Google doesn't really like open re: lack of Google Scholar API cc @mrgunn #scielo15    
    
    
    Whatever this iPhone was doing before the 7.0.3 upgrade went wrong, it's doing 8GB less of it now    
    
    
    In the house for #OAEdin w @McDawg @joyoung (Edinburgh)    
    
    
    Really enjoyed #OAEdin in Edinburgh for #OAWeek Thx @McDawg @joysci and Jan!    
    
    
    Setback 4 research “@MikeTaylor: I see that the relaunched PaleoDB uses the super-restrictive CC By-NC-ND licence. http://paleobiodb.org/#/faq  ”    
    
    
    New blog post: Commenting on scientific papers, about the recently launched PubMed Commons and commenting in general http://blog.martinfenner.org/2013/10/25/commenting-on-scientific-papers/ …    
    
    
    Panel question discussed at #OAEdin "Shld PLOS lower its APC now that it makes $20-30M a year" I said yes. #OAWeek    
    
    
    My talk from #OAEdin RT @thePeerJ: PeerJ Blog - Changing the currency of science to solve our greatest challenges http://bit.ly/1dEey12     
    
    
    Is there a way to split a 300MB GeoJSON file into a folder of static GeoJSON tiles?    
    
    
    Is that a 60s lava lamp on the PeerJ front page or another @rdmpage project? pic.twitter.com/SqtJmvulhV    
    
    
    Cuz the paper itself is immortal?! RT @IanMulvany: why tag authors as deceased, when in the end they all are?    
    
    
    Reusable data - we're not there yet  RT @rmounce: PS if you missed my talk just now, the slides are here: http://www.slideshare.net/rossmounce/sharing-reusable-phylogenetic-data-were-not-there-yet … #tdwg    
    
    
    A tad larger than when at Mendeley! MT @prokopp: How Facebook de-duplicates [300 Petabytes] http://j.mp/1a4Np3g     
    
    
    CrunchBase responds to their attempted recall of its own CC-BY data & legal intimidation http://info.crunchbase.com/2013/11/05/crunchbase-people-and-the-eff/ … @creativecommons    
    
    
    Wow. Google+ can't even get the vanity url thing right. Forcing real names + 1990s email naming schema e.g. `fullname1995`    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    Start asking today! RT @BethSkw: Live Event - 'Ask Me Anything Journal Club' with the Dino Joe authors - PeerJ Blog http://blog.peerj.com/post/66681632429/ask-me-anything-event-dinojoe …    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    Agree RT @PeroMHC: true, change there will be slower. @mfenner @jasonHoyt @urbanevol    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does it seem like PeerJ is floundering a bit??    
    
    
    I've said it before & I'll say it again: biologists shouldn't buy into hype surrounding publisher-hosted preprint servers - just use #arXiv    
    
    
    So is a CC-BY-ND/NC/no-reuse preprint that #bioRxiv offers still allowed to be published in a peer-review journal that accepts preprints?    
    
    
    So is a CC-BY-ND/NC/no-reuse preprint that #bioRxiv offers still allowed to be published in a peer-review journal that accepts preprints?    
    
    
    Doing my Dr. Evil impression MT @thePeerJ: We've saved academia $1M so far, and counting... http://blog.peerj.com/post/66773028124/peerj-saves-academia-money …    
    
    
    Ecosystem boost RT @Mesosphere: We just released Elastic Apache Mesos - launch an @ApacheMesos cluster in 3 steps! https://elastic.mesosphere.io/     
    
    
    Wow. MT @nils_gilman: What happens when you deprive global underclass of possibility of revolutionary redemption?  https://books.google.com/ngrams/graph?content=revolution%2Cterrorism&year_start=1917&year_end=2008&corpus=15&smoothing=4&share=&direct_url=t1%3B%2Crevolution%3B%2Cc0%3B.t1%3B%2Cterrorism%3B%2Cc0 …    
    
    
    Drank EXACTLY 1.333 pints of Sierra Nevada on last night's "date night" with the wifey & woke up w/ headache. Getting old :/    
    
    
    Drank EXACTLY 1.333 pints of Sierra Nevada on last night's "date night" with the wifey & woke up w/ headache. Getting old :/    
    
    
    Animated Checkboxes and Radio Buttons with SVG http://buff.ly/1iUYNAP     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt I read your blog post on too many PhDs and was wondering if you could let me know where you got the graph? http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-life/are-there-too-many-phds/ …    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt I read your blog post on too many PhDs and was wondering if you could let me know where you got the graph? http://blog.mendeley.com/academic-life/are-there-too-many-phds/ …    
    
    
    @jasonhoyt Hi Jason. Wondered if we could discuss a talk about PeerJ at UCL next year? My details attached   http://ow.ly/qVMYP     
    
    
    10 Science things to be thankful for. @invisiblecomma & I involved w/ items 9 &10! #PeerJ #Mendeley http://bit.ly/1873Mtp     
    
    
    Don't know why, but I love seeing manuscripts with inexplicable ALL CAPS titles    
    
    
    No hell has not frozen over, but for once a balanced post on @scholarlykitchn wrt AcademicNetworks http://bit.ly/1bVRVEL     
    
    
    I like Pope Francis. But Time choosing him as Person of the Year ahead of Edward Snowden is ludicrous and cowardly. http://edition.cnn.com/2013/12/11/living/time-person-of-the-year/index.html …    
    
    
    Is Nobel Laureate Randy Scheckman being a hypocrite? Bullocks. - Whoa. Some serious debate flying around... http://tmblr.co/ZoHRVw10vtHRu     
    
    
    New post: "Is Nobel Laureate Randy Scheckman being a hypocrite? Bullocks" http://bit.ly/1fjKsy1     
    
    
    Sad that I will have to pull my first supervisor-less paper, because my fee waiver was rejected by Ecology and Evolution.    
    
    
    It's live! MT @thePeerJ: This month's PeerJ Journal Club on "Visual neuroscience & magic" starts now! https://peerj.com/ask/VisualNeuroscience/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    What a jolly holiday season courtesy of Elsevier! Lumps of coal to al & to all a goodnight! Takedowns http://bit.ly/JKEMC3     
    
    
    Geometric morphometric analysis of snout shape in extant ruminants (Ungulata, Artiodactyla) https://peerj.com/preprints/176/     
    
    
    Or 1st of 2014 in London! MT @thePeerJ: Last PrePrint of 2013! "Occurrence of twin embryos in the eastern bluebird" https://peerj.com/preprints/186v1/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for the Christmas card to us at PeerJ @joysci. Just back in office today.    
    
    
    @marksaurus come back and help build this http://www.wired.com/autopia/2014/01/skycycle/?cid=co16608294 …    
    
    
    We dig Irish accents RT @bkeeganMMU: Ive dropped [#Mendeley] Screencasts into a YT Channel... http://bit.ly/jluWS1 #econmsc    
    
    
    Wikify research with new Mendeley tag pages e.g. http://www.mendeley.com/tags/gene+therapy/    
    
    
    Science funding = military funding = worst analogy ever RE http://bit.ly/jfjxdL @stuartcantrill @sciencebase    
    
    
    .@sciencebase @stuartcantrill No access to helicopters doesn't block military progress. No access to research does block progress of science    
    
    
    Mendeley app update for iPad/iPhone: new is edit metadata, & open PDF in app while in other apps http://bit.ly/gwrJAE    
    
    
    I thought an article was #OA if @IanMulvany ordained it to be. cc @axfelix @mrgunn    
    
    
    +1 idea @mrgunn suggests microformats for #OpenAccess articles    
    
    
    .@axfelix RU talking 1st rule of fight club here, wrt making #OA demarcation obvious & explicit? cc @mrgunn @ianmulvany    
    
    
    If any Londoners think Shoreditch is gentrified, you haven't been to San Francisco in a while. #artisanaleverything    
    
    
    Early rise bird sings;Tea is made with milk de jour;Work brings chaos.    
    
    
    @AnnaEvely Thanks! Hope Mendeley & the music help The Cause. #savetheworld    
    
    
    gonna have to take the macbook pro to the hospital today as Mendeley iPad is crashing when I try to access documents...    
    
    
    Poll: Mendeley Search http://www.mendeley.com/research-papers/search/advanced/ or Goooooooogle Scholar? Pros & cons    
    
    
    Feel cultured now? RT @IanMulvany: Just back from giving a good Mendeley presentation at London Met!    
    
    
    liked:  "Is anyone doing work on alt-metrics for the arts? I'm interested in learning more about approaches to..." http://mnd.ly/kM29gl    
    
    
    Grimsvotn and I are now bitter enemies.    
    
    
    Tag page of the day "DNA Unzipping." Naughty http://www.mendeley.com/tags/dna+unzipping/    
    
    
    At mountain Goats London gig. Last seen in SF 3yrs ago. Guinness in hand. Makers Mark 3yrs ago    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt just bought tickets to Vancouver show next month. Hope it's a decent set! Darnielle is always incredibly enthusiastic.    
    
    
    Waiting for a succinct definition of what it means to pull a "Google fail" cc @subcide wrt google wallet/wave/buzz/etc    
    
    
    "To Google Fail" = Over-promise 10x100, Under-deliver 10x100 /cc @subcide    
    
    
    London-based hacker? Come hack4knowledge at Mendeley HQ June 11/12. Tix+info http://hack4knowledge.eventbrite.com/    
    
    
    Back from a lush week of Greek beaches, Mythos, & no Internetz. Ahhh.    
    
    
    Free tix still left for London's Hack4Knowledge weekend at Mendeley HQ http://bit.ly/lA7lmp (NYC is sold out)    
    
    
    Libs & Conservs brains really are different. Paper co-auth by Oscar winner Colin Firth http://mnd.ly/iVq0QT via @paperoftheday    
    
    
    Sneak peek of new deduplication feature in Mendeley. There's more & release is soon.  http://yfrog.com/edrzip    
    
    
    Finding suggests Mendeley was 3rd largest UK OpenURL referrer in April, beating Medline & Scopus http://bit.ly/k4uTGv    
    
    
    Yay! RT @plos: PLoS and Mendeley team up to bring you a rockin Binary Battle - $16,000 in prize money! http://tinyurl.com/BinaryBattle    
    
    
    Study suggests full bladders help us make better decisions http://bit.ly/lYnIuv    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt lol, awesome research.  Remove all toilets from the whitehouse?    
    
    
    Paper of the day: "Social rejection shares somatosensory representations with physical pain" http://mnd.ly/jt03rV    
    
    
    I, for one, welcome our new PLoS ONE overlords. RT @brembs: An oligarchy of Mega-Journals http://ff.im/-FeKc9    
    
    
    holy shit, that is one avalanche of inbound email, I wish I had one of those mountain safety rockets that could disperse it all.    
    
    
    Did you know?! Amazon has kindly offered $50 AWS credits to ALL valid Mendeley/PLoS API contest entrants http://bit.ly/hETJ55    
    
    
    Serious hackathon multi-continental coordination! Hack4Knowledge NYC-London schedule at Mendeley http://bit.ly/mdFXEA #h4k    
    
    
    @Droideley Hi all,

Thanks for contributing to Open Science! Just a note that we intend to release a new method to... http://post.ly/2AAgW    
    
    
    Score for citizen scientists. Google Earth now includes sea floor maps. What will the crowd discover? http://tcrn.ch/l9CYop    
    
    
    Send a tweet to @LoveMendeley & this bot goes wild at Mendeley HQ in London (pic) http://yfrog.com/h25ljbqj    
    
    
    .@rdmpage Good thought on XML for some titles. WRT link to paper, title-based dedup of 1bn refs is no easy feat. Stay tuned    
    
    
    .@rdmpage Thx for the ideas! Don't stop believing that we're taking academic discovery to the next level http://bit.ly/i0S6E0    
    
    
    You can't cultivate the innate geekery going on here. A viral Magnum ice-cream campaign has started at Mendeley London HQ    
    
    
    Happy coding! RT @rdmpage: Getting ready for #h4k (on the Isle of Cumbrae)    
    
    
    Watch Hack4Knowledge live streamed at Mendeley London http://bit.ly/kp7fYT and NYC http://bit.ly/lfqwu8 #h4k    
    
    
    Hack4Knowledge kicks off 2:30BST/9:30EDT. Join IRC channel hack4knowledge at http://webchat.freenode.net/ cc @McDawg #h4k    
    
    
    Just Found research http://www.mendeley.com/research-papers/search/?query=Successive+and+Targeted+DNA+Integrations … abt this page http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/21652525/ … using Mendeley Related Research for Chrome #h4k    
    
    
    Hack using Mendeley APIs & Chrome extension to find related research of Web page (pic)  http://yfrog.com/ke39jp #h4k    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt available?    
    
    
    Update on Mendeley Related Research Chrome extension. Now have Facebook & twitter sharing (pic)  http://yfrog.com/h0oiydp #h4k    
    
    
    Found research on Mendeley about "A longitudinal popula..." using Mendeley Related Research Chrome extension http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/19157689  #h4k    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt what url does it share?    
    
    
    Totally spent after a geektastic Hack4Knowledge weekend. Thx to all the external devs who hacked with us in LON & NYC! #h4k    
    
    
    Found research about "Living Bibliography..." using Mendeley Related for Chrome http://livingbib.organelas.com/     
    
    
    Neat mashup by @rathko - Wikipedia pageviews + Mendeley APIs to show trending topics & related research http://bit.ly/l1qJKf    
    
    
    .@ChemConnector @jasonpriem I think it just looks at what's trending on wikipedia, then adds relevant research articles    
    
    
    Mendeley recommendation engine now offers holiday suggestions!  http://yfrog.com/kfm8jp TY @subcide    
    
    
    .@ezyang come work for us and help improve our algos! #win http://www.mendeley.com/blog/jobs/    
    
    
    Leave tomorrow for the Edinburgh International Film Festival all weekend! http://www.edfilmfest.org.uk/    
    
    
    "Back door method to getting articles in PubMed" - Or just add it to Mendeley for it to be discovered http://bit.ly/jFEBUi    
    
    
    .@subcide starts new meme: "Celebrate Mendeley 1.0 dev preview by [insert activity 1.0]" http://bit.ly/19rD9i    
    
    
    A few weeks back I posed "What could you do w/ extracted keywords from 100yrs of research?"  Tag trends  http://bit.ly/my4iL7    
    
    
    And with @IanMulvany RT @IanMulvany: great brainstorming session with @jasonHoyt    
    
    
    Great! RT @williamjnixon: We are also seeing an increase in traffic to Enlighten from links in #Mendeley #googleanalytics #oai7    
    
    
    Dreaming of a world where copyright cannot be held by corporations, only individuals. Science would benefit.    
    
    
    There's a sign up on the convenience shop below the Mendeley office "Now less expensive BEARS"    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Do they have Polar? I heard those are more difficult to keep in stock.    
    
    
    Indicates academia under-represented on LinkedIn RT @mendeleyAPI: Data Insight mashup using Mendeley and LinkedIn APIs http://datainsightresults.wordpress.com/2011/06/26/team-15/ …    
    
    
    Congrats to Katherine High, grad student Hojun, & colleagues on their Nature paper. Related to my work w/zinc-fingers http://bit.ly/mCtXlT    
    
    
    The giant bladder in the humid London sky is about to burst open. 1, 2, 3...    
    
    
    Our @IanMulvany walked into Mendeley HQ wearing a phytological society t-shirt. My t-shirt says "Grok" #geektastic    
    
    
    .@techsoc All your citation data can be exported or pulled out of your local SQLite database. No lock-in w/ Mendeley    
    
    
    Visiting scholar @mgrani gives an update on his work at #Mendeley in near-duplicate detection + more... http://mnd.ly/iJmWfl    
    
    
    Just made my last frickin' tube commute into the office. Walking distance now. Ahhh    
    
    
    Just peed myself a lil' bit with excitement of Mendeley 1.0 almost here!!    
    
    
    2 minutes in heaven MT @cpf118: the official Mendeley tutorial videos now live on our YouTube channel http://bit.ly/p9JPMZ    
    
    
    Excited 2b joining the Mendeley Webinar for Life Scientists w/@mrgunn as host! Starts in 40 mins. Signup http://bit.ly/mVPwbM    
    
    
    Best #Mendeley feature of todays release:  Logging in now remembers the page you were on! http://mnd.ly/p5Dd6h    
    
    
    .@McDawg on my way to Scotland w/ a Becks!    
    
    
    Running Github like a paywall science journal http://wgrover.com/writing.html#science_for_github    
    
    
    Vowed to not shave until Mendeley 1.0 stable is released. Oh boy.    
    
    
    Current state of Beard 1.0 dev preview  http://yfrog.com/ke4gnavj    
    
    
    +1 RT @David_Dobbs: @IanMulvany c'mon, ian. step up for the company.    
    
    
    How "Open" is PubMed Central really? Answer, not very open at all http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/tools/openftlist/    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just blogged. "Why We Publish" http://www.mendeley.com/blog/academic-life/why-we-publish/    
    
    
    I take it back. Perhaps Europe/UK can't compete with Silicon Valley.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Just checked http://bit.ly/omsYyp seems like the chinese are taking over, or is the NER playing trick on us?    
    
    
    Just blogged (again)! "Why we Publish" http://www.mendeley.com/blog/academic-life/why-we-publish/    
    
    
    FYI - some glitches leading to 404. Hence the repost.    
    
    
    .@researchremix Cites are already biased & used indiscriminately, let's at least bias them with added-value open content    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @researchremix a "biased" citation, in my experience, is 9 times of 10 an specific unnecessary inclusion. OA is a big pool.    
    
    
    @axfelix search weighting is mainly abt full text giving more relevant results than metadata alone. OA issue aside, we'd still do it    
    
    
    So having learned Mendeley it does not work with my new 64 bit laptop. balls    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Hi Jason it is windows 7 specifically around the Word 2010 64 bit plugin. I am a huge fan of Mendeley.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Hi Jason it is windows 7 specifically around the Word 2010 64 bit plugin. I am a huge fan of Mendeley.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Thank you for the reply but I am unable install 32 bit office. Do you have a time frame to working up to 64bit? Thank you    
    
    
    The digital age is the end of the copyright era. Someone just needs to tell the lawyers re: http://nyti.ms/o3YLOu    
    
    
    .@drs1969 True abt indictment being theft, not copyright. That said, OA as @wilbanks cites, wld have avoided this mess.    
    
    
    .@drs1969 My feeling abt copyright in digital age is that it is legally upheld biz model that slows, not advances, research. Reform, yes    
    
    
    .@drs1969 To reform copyright, let new biz models emerge from how the market uses digital objects, rather than proscribe rules beforehand    
    
    
    And to think I had once aspired to become a U.S. astronaut. RIP NASA flight program.    
    
    
    Insanity. Out-of-copyright science articles stuck behind a $19/paper JSTOR paywall. Until now http://bit.ly/ot8DqM    
    
    
    Will the JSTOR/PirateBay news be Academic Publishing's Napster moment? i.e. end of the paywall era in favor of new biz models?    
    
    
    *raises hand. I know! I know!  RT @cpf118: What is Mendeley? http://bit.ly/nMMBQf    
    
    
    Mendeley 1.0 is here! Which means I can now shave Beard 1.0!  http://yfrog.com/h3q30phj    
    
    
    @jendahling Sweet gig you landed! Nuclear physics?! ;)    
    
    
    Mustache 1.0 is now growing RT @IanMulvany: holy shit, @jasonHoyt has shaved, must mean that Mendeley 1.0 is out!    
    
    
    RE@ChemConnector  So creating your citation list via http://bit.ly/pICZqI needs some work!    
    
    
    I have one. RT @rvidal: Tell us about your ideal science app & we’ll get someone to build it. http://www.mendeley.com/blog/developer-resources/tell-us-about-your-ideal-science-app-well-get-someone-to-build-it/ …    
    
    
    @phylogenomics I'm mobile today, but heard you're having issues w docs vanishing. Cld you email me a verbose log file? 'Help>FAQ' 1/2    
    
    
    @phylogenomics may have system-specific issue, so if log doesn't help let's set up a call later Monday w engineer here in London 2/2    
    
    
    I like! RT @PLoS: Tim O'Reilly comments on the PLoS/Mendeley API Binary Battle "[make] science go faster" http://tinyurl.com/TimO-ReillyBinaryBattle …    
    
    
    Science app ideas from the crowd http://bit.ly/nRJ2rW  (join the PLoS/Mendeley API Binary Battle)    
    
    
    @MendeleySupport  I work for http://bit.ly/o6jEWw  and I want to add a button "Export to Mendelay".Do you have a 20x20px  or bigger image?    
    
    
    Hehe, "...dinos lived at least 500yrs ago" New blog via @phylogenomics on num of species article http://bit.ly/oa49AU     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt It's impossible to respect the "Legibility" and "Clearing Space" in an icon 20x20 px. See this example. http://bit.ly/o5hIZ1     
    
    
    What do people think of the feed tab on Spotify? Useful? Interesting? Items relevant to you?    
    
    
    Interesting. "Academic publishers make Murdoch look like a socialist" in the Gaurdian http://bit.ly/om8d58     
    
    
    I had more typos in my last tweet than my entire thesis. :/    
    
    
    Scholarly Kitchen at it again with their BS comebacks. This time against Guardian's Monbiot http://bit.ly/pGJQJf     
    
    
    .@drs1969 Safe to say the writers of both stories have an agenda. I'll leave it at that. No need to comment on blog    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt always nice to start off with a few sweeping personal slights too...    
    
    
    Was Monbiot's blog rhetoric or more? See this analysis on library STM costs http://bit.ly/k4Ljwo  Slides 5-8,12    
    
    
    How old is that in "blog years?" Congrats! RT @PLoS: Happy first birthday to PLoS Blogs - http://bit.ly/PLoSBlogsOneToday …    
    
    
    Amazeballs. Yesterday Mendeley users added half a million articles. Took us five months to get our first 500K. Total now 109M    
    
    
    Rumor is true. Hackday at Mendeley HQ in London on Sun. Speak w/ @mfenner @ianmulvany @jasonhoyt for more info #solo11    
    
    
    API stat. In 2 wks Mendeley will pass 1000 developers using the API launched 14 months ago. #solo11    
    
    
    .@IanMulvany Was the applause that publishers are killing off PDF in favor of HTML5? #solo11    
    
    
    Just open sourced the Twendeley app at the Mendeley/Science Online hackday #solo11 https://github.com/jjhoyt/Twendeley …    
    
    
    .@pixievondust You can try out Twendeley at http://bit.ly/ad5nKQ  or get the source code at https://github.com/jjhoyt/Twendeley …    
    
    
    Second app of the day now on Chrome extension store "Mendeley Context Search" http://bit.ly/nVJz1h  #solohack11    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt any interesting things being worked on?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt it's "only" using the page title? #solohack11    
    
    
    Updated Mendeley Context Chrome extension. Now shows Mendeley readership for PubMed articles  http://yfrog.com/ny8b3p     
    
    
    Cool! @mfenner tackles article-level metrics by extending the open sourced @PLoS API server http://bit.ly/pU3gpw     
    
    
    Off to Whitstable, England for final weekend  holiday outside London before the baby!    
    
    
    That's awesome for newsfeed updates! RT @IanMulvany: unofficial chrome extension for Mendeley is nice: https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/dmjdlnefabajccabhbemdnodgelechkd …    
    
    
    +shagtastic judges panel RT @mendeleyAPI: Just 15 days left to enter the $16K Mendeley PLoS API contest http://bit.ly/e9EiYE     
    
    
    Looks Presidential RT @mendeleyAPI: Liking the blue feel of this third party Mendeley app for Android "Scholarley" http://bit.ly/pxFJFH     
    
    
    Excellent. iPhone crashed, had to do restore, nothing backed up (txts, phone nums, photos) since Nov 2010 apparently.  Boo-yah. Life restart    
    
    
    Huge $$$ prizes RT @mendeleyAPI: Last call to enter the PLoS & Mendeley apps for researchers contest! Blog http://bit.ly/pxhYwl     
    
    
    Any ideas why most academic publishers don't use unique names for downloaded PDFs? e.g. SDarticle.pdf instead of insertDOI.pdf    
    
    
    Reading Scholarly Kitchen is like running into that stodgy old professor in the hall who refuses to accept a new dogma posed in his field    
    
    
    Guide to using Mendeley on Android - blog http://www.mendeley.com/blog/tipstricks/android-on-mendeley-an-app-guide/ …    
    
    
    Groupon seemingly in trouble again with exec depart. & revenue revise. Also, see this prediction from last year http://bit.ly/rb3DMQ     
    
    
    Mayor Boris tells us to report bad roadworks. I like the bad example photo http://bit.ly/p5hwrX     
    
    
    Ha! "How about zero?" Scientist meets publisher to negotiate a paper deal #OA http://youtu.be/GMIY_4t-DR0     
    
    
    Open Access journals to account for 90% of articles by 2020 one analyst estimates http://bit.ly/mPvydD     
    
    
    Entrepreneurs near Seattle! Join Startup weekend EDU edition & pitch/build the next startup Sep 30th http://bit.ly/q2eLxO     
    
    
    Literally no time for twitter, so much going on and so little time to take a look :(    
    
    
    Fab! RT @Droideley: Droideley (#Mendeley #Android client) installed on 1000+ devices! Cool :)    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @mendeley_com Is there a way to get more API calls? Asking for a Binary Battle-Submission that'd like 2 perform 1 Mio requests ;)    
    
    
    In the past 7 yrs Apple stock has grown 5000%. Holy $(#@    
    
    
    Cool for scifi/dystopia/fantasy book fans. Flowchart guide to NPRs top 100 scfi books http://bit.ly/rbQ3ch     
    
    
    Great article on why scientists need to be more vocal in public & publish in open. Ans: Cuz the public is hurting http://bit.ly/p4W2As     
    
    
    Great article on #openscience & public trust - 'Social Media for Scientists Part 1: It’s Our Job' - http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/science-sushi/2011/09/27/social-media-for-scientists-part-1-its-our-job/ … @jasonHoyt @mrgunn    
    
    
    Princeton bans academics from handing over copyright to publishers. Promoting OpenAccess http://bit.ly/pdbhC9  #OA    
    
    
    The Princeton banning of handing over copyright has sent a shiver down my spine & a shock wave across academic publishing.    
    
    
    New group to collect Uni policies on #copyright & #OA for other Unis to model after Princeton precedent http://bit.ly/p7naDh     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt It's not quite new - Harvard, MIT, Duke, Uni of Kansas and others have similar policies - see http://roarmap.eprints.org/     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt banned how? Does Princeton retain?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt ah! I was thinking the Press, not Uni. Thanks for clarifying. Will/does Mendeley auto-tap/link to such repositories?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt a good shiver right?    
    
    
    Willing to pay $5/mo 4 streaming music, but not 4 something that improves your research (career)? #whatsWrongWithWorldToday    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt My career should pay me, not vice versa.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt ... with a highly uncertain dividend. Even stock market trading seems more rewarding. Or gambling.    
    
    
    .@egonwillighagen I was speaking in general terms abt investing in your career. Not abt Mendeley or similar tools cc @dominikb1888    
    
    
    Last day to enter the Mendeley/@PLoS Binary Battle apps contest! Winners announced Nov 30th http://bit.ly/hETJ55     
    
    
    Congrats to @plos on their refreshed website & mission statement! http://www.plos.org/     
    
    
    I think that's a 1st RT @Pewology: Whenever I end up on Mendeley.com, I keep expecting it to be a UNATCO website.    
    
    
    Founded http://Ologeez.org 2006. Last commit end '08. Joined competitor Mendeley 3mo later. Shutting down Ologeez Oct 7 2011    
    
    
    Hello World. No baby as of yet. Amazingly, I will actually tell you when he does arrive. It's not a secret. So, please stop asking. XO!    
    
    
    Apple could have saved $13B in lost market cap today by calling the iPhone 5 instead of 4S. Oops.    
    
    
    @jasonhoyt @mrgunn @enroweb is there a blog post of entries coming? I want to check out the competition! #binarybattle    
    
    
    Attn academics and students! RT @mrgunn: In London? Want to help Mendeley out? Join us for user testing next week: http://bit.ly/r0A3KG     
    
    
    New arrival! My son baby Elliot was born this morning in true Binary Battle style on 11-10-11! http://yfrog.com/o05j8wrj     
    
    
    Baby Elliot's first shot and breath of life  http://yfrog.com/h7ajrsquj     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Baby Elliott Hoyt? As in, yours?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt congratulations, nice DOB!! Hope mother and baby are well. Enjoy! ;)    
    
    
    Yesterday's @NewYorker cartoon "Turns out everyone here is self-published." The future of academic publishing? #OpenAccess Wk    
    
    
    The modern family  http://yfrog.com/h374ymxj     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt is he on Twitter yet? :)    
    
    
    Cool use of the Mendeley & @PLoS APIs in the openSNP project http://opensnp.org/snps/26324#mendeley … #personalGenomics    
    
    
    As a techie, I'm embarrassed to admit this: I just now replaced my iPhone 3G after 2.5 yrs. iPhone 4S baby.    
    
    
    Top 40 Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle . Day One http://bit.ly/rUdgGc     
    
    
    Day 2 of the Top 40 Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle http://bit.ly/s0JYgL     
    
    
    Wow! RT @axfelix: @mendeley_com @plos I'm blown away by results of the binary battle. This is more & better work than has been done in yrs    
    
    
    MT @axfelix: OMG it's a citation visualization that's actually useful for browsing. OMG. I'm going to go make coffee. http://vyzkumap.net/     
    
    
    Day 3 of Top Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-@PLoS Binary Battle is now out! http://bit.ly/tswT7q     
    
    
    Day 4 of Apps to benefit science in the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle. +full-list recap http://bit.ly/vtcZFO     
    
    
    If we can sequence a human genome for $100, why can't we openly publish for $100? http://openrepub.org/  via @OpenRePub    
    
    
    Ausgezeichnet! RT @delaiglesia: New blog post (German): Mendeley/PLoS API Binary Battle http://bit.ly/uPGI3P     
    
    
    The boy weighed in at 10lbs 12oz in his latest checkup. Three pounds in just 4 weeks since he was born! Mama has some good milk    
    
    
    Happy Birthday, Carl Sagan. I'm still inspired.    
    
    
    Siri. Please tweet ... Oh wait. Silly me for thinking an integrated Twitter with iOS 5 would work w/ you. Siri - "STFU, Jason."    
    
    
    Why in the H-E-double hockey sticks am I not at #Berlin9 ? I want to marry you.    
    
    
    #Berlin9 why wld I publish in a journal that didn't have the sense to secure the .com/org domain names b4 announcing itself? eLife?    
    
    
    The top 20 things. Ever. http://bit.ly/3n6rFh     
    
    
    .@PLoS & @Mendeley_com will be announcing the Binary Battle Top 10 apps to impact science in about one hour.    
    
    
    Announcing the Top 10+1 Apps in the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle http://bit.ly/s7uE8k     
    
    
    .@openSNPorg congrats! Great app and concept :)    
    
    
    Also check out the complete Binary Battle rundown w/ judges + the Top 10+1 apps on the dev portal http://bit.ly/twkfLB     
    
    
    Sh%t! Swearing more in life reduces pain tolerance when you stub your toe & shout f%&. Research says http://1.usa.gov/tPPWF6     
    
    
    More amazing apps almost in the Binary Battle Top 10 http://www.qrate.me  http://vocabulari.se  http://moodley.fidesol.org     
    
    
    Congrats to the 50 millionth DOI assignee from CrossRef! Oddly enough, it's a scanned paper from 1985 http://bit.ly/vR6vQl     
    
    
    Public voting now open to decide who should win the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle! http://bit.ly/u1WjHL     
    
    
    Hope they fire that "officer" RT @markasaurus: Everything I thought would never happen in this country http://bit.ly/sJ12gu     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt the shit that's happened here recently makes me want to mail my University of California diploma back to Sacramento    
    
    
    liked:  "(for those of you who missed it) PLoS One is launching a brand new altmetrics collection. Details and CFP..." http://mnd.ly/u39pbP     
    
    
    Heat-map of the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle voting across the world thus far http://yfrog.com/o02qep     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @mendeley_com What are you guys using to create that visualisation? Looks good.    
    
    
    The world needs both the "Microsofts" & "Apples." Tradeoff is backwards compatibility vs. innovation; diff need/diff times    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt when the world is moving from desktop to tablets, businesses to the cloud, don't see where backward compatibility would matter    
    
    
    Fair to say that Dropbox is just a fancy GUI for git repos?    
    
    
    Ironically, story behind pay wall RT @michael_nielsen: Paul Allen on the case for open science: http://on.wsj.com/vFPWx4     
    
    
    45 minutes until we announce the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle Apps for Science winners.  5PM GMT / 9AM PST    
    
    
    #oa openSNP wins PLoS/Mendeley Binary Battle http://bit.ly/vwmCZV  on PLoS BLog, and Mendeley blog http://bit.ly/siSrCj     
    
    
    @helgerausch Congrats for all the test-writing. I'm keeping an eye on the logs and server load right now :D    
    
    
    Devs of @totalimpactdev said of Binary Battle "You've inspired innovation that wasn't otherwise happening" Thx! let's keep inspiring!    
    
    
    Check out the interview with the Binary Battle Apps for Science winner, @openSNPorg http://bit.ly/unhn1w     
    
    
    Help the Mendeley-PLoS Binary Battle winner, @openSNPorg, win a grant to genotype people for free http://bit.ly/trV9gU     
    
    
    ZOMG. I'm babysitting Elliot tonight, by myself. Father/son party!    
    
    
    And spit up all over his outfit within 10 minutes of mama leaving. Party's started!    
    
    
    I want a pair of these. Sergey Brin was 2500 years behind. pic.twitter.com/TR6vnxX2    
    
    
    Happy belated fifth birthday, @PLoSone ! http://bit.ly/rUjqMV  cc @PLoS    
    
    
    Sad news all, I left Mendeley. What a great 3yrs! Good news, started project to disrupt another industry.    
    
    
    Postdoc truck http://upmic.wordpress.com/2012/01/03/postdoc-truck/ …    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt which industry? ;) You did an awesome job at Mendeley, THANKS!    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Good luck! Looking forward to see your future projects! Are you staying in London?    
    
    
    At Somerset House pic.twitter.com/jDG1RLwb    
    
    
    .@subcide Haven't seen Sherlock. Better question though, are his thoughts in anachronistic font?    
    
    
    Elsevier execs spanked  '...whose sole purpose it is to lobby governments into preventing Open Access' http://bjoern.brembs.net/comment-n819.html …    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Curious to hear what's next :-)    
    
    
    w/ RWA & SOPA, Elsevier+paywall publishers are only delaying their inevitable crash. Shareholders will be jumping ship soon    
    
    
    Now that I've left Mendeley I can freely state that AAP+Elsevier are the biggest threats to science existing today    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt Why?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt eh? what? why? Lancet/Cell/Scopus/Research4Life (etc) chopped liver?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt What are you smoking and please can I have some?!    
    
    
    Commercial publishers: make vast profits, buy protective legislation, rinse, repeat. bit.ly/zBJpHK  by @brembs via @Klortho    
    
    
    Good article and written on my 35th b-day! RT @BoraZ: Does the journal really matter anymore?  http://bit.ly/z3DJDx     
    
    
    I always ask myself, "Have I failed enough to succeed yet?" 10 things entrepreneurs [SHOULD] fail at http://tcrn.ch/z9XJhu     
    
    
    praise in triplicate @jasonHoyt ditto @jasonpriem @researchremix thanks for the great work. (I still love the "change the world" photo)    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt happy birthday. :)    
    
    
    .@CameronNeylon Did someone say 'beer?' cc @mfenner @wjjessen    
    
    
    Elsevier+Execs made 14 'donations' to main #RWA Congress backers, Issa & Maloney, in 2011 http://bit.ly/xcsgq9     
    
    
    Time to vote them out. List of US Congress members taking contributions from Elsevier http://bit.ly/xNBZEC     
    
    
    .@subcide Even if the contributions totaled just $1, it still shows legislation can be bought by outsiders.    
    
    
    Great! RT @gfry: @jasonHoyt Jason, have you seen "Open Knowledge Saves Lives. #OpposeHR3699 ! http://bit.ly/wJ6oVF  #RWA    
    
    
    You don't get to destroy science just because it doesn't fit your biz model #RWA    
    
    
    And coding resumes.  return $awesome;    
    
    
    How Microsoft would redesign the BOX of Apple product. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=EUXnJraKM3k …    
    
    
    Do startups need 'Wartime CEOs?' - "Wartime CEO violates protocol in order to win." http://bit.ly/eqMuIl     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt startups in general?  I would say no.    
    
    
    First day on a brand new planet!    
    
    
    @jasonhoyt Hey jasonhoyt, I just mentioned you in my comment on "Tea Party Nation Sells Out to Newt Gingrich Based o....    
    
    
    Annoying @VirginAtlantic "pre-flight courtesy" call is actually a sales call, costing me mobile minutes + time.    
    
    
    Wow. @37signals sounds like they'd be fans of SOPA. Drop the hate of @curebit already. You both look foolish.    
    
    
    Adding some fuel RT @wilbanks: After years of activism, first true body blow to Elsevier comes from passive resistance http://bit.ly/zYS18t     
    
    
    Uk folk hows your lovefilm streaming experience? Seems jerky to me, not buffering, but jerky.    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt cheers for info , whats film selection like on netflix?    
    
    
    @jasonHoyt cheers for info , whats film selection like on netflix?    
    
    
    Ten Things You're Not Allowed to Say at Davos http://blogs.hbr.org/haque/2011/01/ten_things_youre_not_allowed_t.html …    
    
    
    An equity analyst's take on the Elsevier boycott http://t.co/IYiJXzNqvia @stephen_curry cc:  @jasonhoyt    
    
    
    Elsevier is "committed to the broadest possible dissemination of published research." Until it hurts profit$ http://bit.ly/yZvsUl     
    
    
    Out now. I co-authored a chapter on usage metrics in science (avail from MIT Press)  http://yfrog.com/obezlmyj  #mendeley    
    
    
    More double speak from publishers to law makers abt OA as threat to viability of research. This time in UK parliament: http://bit.ly/ACkxej     
    
    
    Speaking today in San Francisco at Molecular Med Tri-Con. I talk data! Yum http://bit.ly/A7aRVL     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @BioMedCentral: 2012 Benjamin Franklin Award Finalists Named http://ow.ly/9kARH  #science #openaccess    
    
    
    Shouldn't have to be Indiana Jones to find a research paper http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/02/google-trained-minds-cant-deal-with-terrible-research-database-ui/253641/ …    
    
    
    I decided to perform a literature search using ONLY Mendeley. Got some awesome results - http://bit.ly/zPeZbd     
    
    
    … but it helps? RT @jasonHoyt: You shouldn't have to be Indiana Jones to find a research paper http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/02/google-trained-minds-cant-deal-with-terrible-research-database-ui/253641/ …    
    
    
    1 of my former PhD thesis advisors just shared a link to his latest genomics paper, which is behind a paywall. I felt like chastising him    
    
    
    And it will *only* cost me $20 to "rent" his paper for the day from Genome Research. Fabulous!    
    
    
    Work/Family balance lesson #32-When present, BE present. Partner gently reminded me this morn while I was working on the laptop, in bed    
    
    
    The always interesting @petermurrayrust & his synopsis on the scholarly pub debate held w Elsevier & others http://bit.ly/AbrVAS     
    
    
    .@invisiblecomma @petermurrayrust you can't copyright a fact, which is why the US takes a friendly legal stance on text mining, UK following    
    
    
    Fail already. SearchMe tried this RT @TheNextWeb: Oolone: A visual search engine designed by a London neuroscientist http://tnw.to/1DWzS     
    
    
    My academic goth friends will like this; Journal of Dracula Studies. For real. http://www.blooferland.com/drc/index.php?title=Journal_of_Dracula_Studies …    
    
    
    Amused that my GMail auto-detects mail from Google corporate as spam.    
    
    
    Great! RT @creativecommons: Announcing the Why Open Education Matters Video Competition! w/prizes up to $25,000: http://bit.ly/wE20uP  #OER    
    
    
    Good market intel RT @wilbanks: Challenges in big data. By some of the shiniest brains in big data. http://bit.ly/xn2D3w ”    
    
    
    congrats on a productive conversation! ;) RT @researchremix: New post: Talking text mining with Elsevier http://wp.me/p4g7f-fU     
    
    
    In the latest OA newsletter, @PeterSuber argues that non-#OA publishers knowingly distort the facts http://bit.ly/yIo0on     
    
    
    The 1953 double helix paper was never peer-reviewed at Nature.  Is there a new pub model in that fact? http://bit.ly/y1vQUn     
    
    
    Important RT @thePeerJ: 12 points to fight the misinformation campaign led by non-OA publishers against #OA & #FRPAA http://bit.ly/xsuKrm     
    
    
    @jasonHoyt @David_Dobbs tried reading note about the 1953 paper you referred to. current pub model did not allow me: pic.twitter.com/9u4rqZp5    
    
    
    Visions of Terminator. This scares me. DARPA has developed the world's fastest robot cheetah: http://glpo.st/zYMMbj     
    
    
    It's concerning when academic publishers claim to advance science, but then oppose bills in congress that wld do such #FRPAA    
    
    
    The American Association of Publishers now promoting xenophobia argues @mbeisen http://bit.ly/Ajz1ev  #FRPAA    
    
    
    