Veient el partit del Barça en un hotel a Manchester, i ... gol the Thiago! aquest nano es impresionant.    
    
    
    what is the best way to follow today's Apple show? #iPhone5    
    
    
    @carmerossell pero on ho veuras/seguiras? compres crispetes i tot?    
    
    
    @carmerossell però si avui no anuncien el iPhone 5 sinó el iPhone 4S! oooohhhhh....    
    
    
    A very say day for innovation lovers. Steve Jobs made me had a lot of fun in my daily work. I hope the company will continue his success.    
    
    
    @martinvars Completely agree with the traditional definition of nationalism. But, in Spain the term nationalism is used in another context.    
    
    
    @martinvars Europe, Asia and Africa...    
    
    
    Interviewing a Danish engineer. Half of the engineers in Barcelona from outside Spain... I believe diversity adds value to any project.    
    
    
    iCloud infrastructure cost $1b !    
    
    
    To Brussels, for the first time if I am not mistaken! (@ Aereoport de Barcelona - El Prat. Porta B28) http://4sq.com/uKClin     
    
    
    I'm at Sa Punta http://4sq.com/v5sLwF     
    
    
    On són els indignats?    
    
    
    I have just posted my talk at IJCAI here: http://marctorrens.net/2011/11/11/speaker-at-ijcai-2011-industry-day/ …    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @cerclefiber m'interessa molt, miraré de venir!    
    
    
    Very interesting video about new technologies and connectivity: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=50MQQ9K_X6Y …    
    
    
    I'm at Strands Barcelona (Marina, 16-18, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/bLscP6    
    
    
    BBC News - Eurozone debt web: Who owes what to whom? http://bbc.in/s8yEx6     
    
    
    I'm at T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN) (Terminal 1 El Prat de Llobregat, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    My little contribution as part of the Scientific Advisory Board to a great project: http://Chicisimo.com ! http://marctorrens.net/2011/11/23/scientific-advisor-for-chicisimo/ …    
    
    
    quin partit... impresionant! i nomes portem 30 minuts! Visca el Barça!    
    
    
    Very interesting video about Steve Jobs starting NeXT: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sOlqqriBvUM …    
    
    
    At TED Barcelona... About to start! pic.twitter.com/OnFh9GSY    
    
    
    M'agrada, com a mínim hi ha sensibilitat. http://internacional.elpais.com/internacional/2011/12/04/actualidad/1323030449_522201.html …    
    
    
    I'm at T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN) (Terminal 1 El Prat de Llobregat, Barcelona) w/ 4 others. http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    Read The Marc Daily ▸ today's top stories are contributed by @xamat  and  @aldamiz ▸ http://paper.li/marctorrens/~list?topic=Technology …    
    
    
    The 20 Best New Startups Of 2011 http://www.businessinsider.com/20-best-startups-technology-inventions-2011-12?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Interesting, about social media: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H61WvxOm1AM …    
    
    
    Introducing the Strands iPhone App, version 3.0! http://bit.ly/bPcwLT    
    
    
    @martinvars This is not a translation but a bad pronunciation. It is like pronouncing Barthelona instead of Barselona as it is in Catalan.    
    
    
    Fantastic, Apple is surpassing Microsoft's value on the stock market: http://nyti.ms/98qu5g    
    
    
    Entrevista a Aragón Radio por el premio Webby a moneyStrands.com: http://bit.ly/cK3xy9 #moneystrands    
    
    
    Flying to Brussels to finish the year in a nice way, let's see how it goes!    
    
    
    http://m.elblogsalmon.com/economia-domestica/cinco-razones-para-no-pagar-el-impuesto-de-los-tontos-comprar-loteria …    
    
    
    @xamat @sandrewge why do u use windows? Go for a serious OS!    
    
    
    The 10 Best TED Talks of 2011 by @jzb http://rww.to/tYYdR9  via @RWW    
    
    
    Strands has been awarded: 2011 RED HERRING GLOBAL TOP 100!  http://www.redherring.com/RHG/2011/top100.html …    
    
    
    I'm taking Human-Computer Interaction online for free at Online Education Stanford University. http://www.hci-class.org/  http://www.hci-class.org/     
    
    
    I am looking for a nice bar in Vienna to watch the FC Barcelona match tomorrow evening. Anyone?    
    
    
    I've just created an infographic of my CV. Check it out! http://bit.ly/vk36Lt?r=torrens … (via @vizualizeme) Original format...    
    
    
    Nice! RT @StrandsRecs: We're excited to close out Q2 with 15 great new retail customers and new plugins: http://bit.ly/coKbOx    
    
    
    EUR/USD < 1.1999    
    
    
    Hello World!    
    
    
    @edusampi Sí, hem mirat diferentes opcions per mantenir el servei pero sense exit. Ens sap molt greu, gracies pel suport i bon entranament!    
    
    
    I am hiring for moneyStrands!
http://tinyurl.com/dgobxt    
    
    
    Any good front-end or back-end engineer interested in being part of a great startup? @Chicisimo http://chicisimo.com/fashion/buscamos-talento/ …    
    
    
    Strands Finance Was Named a Winner of the Red Herring Top 100 - Bloomberg http://www.bloomberg.com/article/2012-01-02/am27Y6LMCS20.html … via @BloombergNow    
    
    
    NY Times: Spain’s Falling Prices Fuel Deflation Fears in Europe http://tinyurl.com/cj3zkl    
    
    
    Barcelona first ‘tap and go’ city in Europe - http://FT.com  - Technology http://on.ft.com/wEh0x8     
    
    
    Machine Learning 4 All! http://wp.me/p234d6-3x  via @bigml    
    
    
    Cap a New York! (@ T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN)) http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    @martinvars yes, it does!    
    
    
    Excellent talk, I highly recommend it, very inspiring! Luis von Ahn: Massive-scale online collaboration #TED http://on.ted.com/ADog     
    
    
    At the Webby cocktail, good atmosphere and awsome place with a 360 degrees view of Manhattan! (@ The Top of The Standard w/ 25 others)    
    
    
    I'm at Uncle Jack's Steakhouse (44 W 56th St, btw 5th & 6th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/5w0x9q    
    
    
    I'm at Apple Store (767 5th Ave, btw 58th & 59th St, New York) w/ 9 others. http://4sq.com/2GAjpC    
    
    
    Heading towards Switzerland, and tomorrow arriving to BCN just in time for the exciting match!    
    
    
    Having good time at the Webby ceremony! Pictures will follow... (@ The Webby Awards w/ 37 others) http://4sq.com/cIMa2H    
    
    
    Best burger in NY? Probably here! (@ Burger Joint at Le Parker Meridien w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/7TaY8F    
    
    
    Heading to London. On Thursday in Switzerland, I think I will enjoy lots of snow...    
    
    
    “@dpapagia: 6 startups to watch in 2012: 2 on education! http://mashable.com/2012/01/08/6-startups-to-watch-in-2012/ …” education and technology will be huge in the following years.    
    
    
    Terminal T2 in BCN airport. Fully underutilized. Pathetic. An example of throwing away public money. pic.twitter.com/vwnaoa0c    
    
    
    I'm at Roka (40 Canada Square, Canary Wharf, btw North & South Colonade, London) http://4sq.com/wmnZDR     
    
    
    Fantastic plane to go from london to Bern... pic.twitter.com/IvuPVzkY    
    
    
    @oscarjulve one of the best Japanese restaurant in Lon. Per flipar!    
    
    
    Flying to London for #finovate. Really looking forward to an exciting conference!    
    
    
    @polnavarro vens a finovate?    
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Black Friar http://instagr.am/p/Gvn2_BOiqk/     
    
    
    Interview about moneyStrands.com and its Webby award (in Spanish): http://bit.ly/c22iqD    
    
    
    Loved The Company Men (via Boxee)  http://b0x.ee/e3R8VM     
    
    
    I'm at Strands Barcelona (Marina, 16-18, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/bLscP6    
    
    
    Tech Start-Ups Take On Banks http://on.wsj.com/z84SfX  via @WSJ    
    
    
    I'm at L'imperial Café (240 rue de rivoli, Paris). http://4sq.com/6D7HYp    
    
    
    Just testing my app.... I have started to save €25,500.00 for Emergency Savings with the Strands Personal Finance saving tool    
    
    
    @carmerossell you cannot even imagine it :-)    
    
    
    Book on Distributed E-Research (I am on the Editorial Board) ;-) http://www.igi-global.com/book/collaborative-distributed-research/58272 …    
    
    
    Nice! Apple's TV Will Be 'The Biggest Thing In Consumer Electronics Since The Smartphone'—Munster http://www.businessinsider.com/apple-tv-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    He apoyado la petición Say to @neeliekroesEU we want a single #opendata license in the #EU #1OdataLicenseEU - http://bit.ly/zU7iKq     
    
    
    TED2012 remixed: It's Time for TED http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDHET3aCI2U&sns=tw … via @youtube    
    
    
    A TV3 haurien d'estudiar més matemàtiques: si l'Espanyol ha guanyat poc estadísticament al Madrid, avui té més possibilitats de guanyar.    
    
    
    Bryan Stevenson: We need to talk about an injustice http://on.ted.com/AUDM  #TED    
    
    
    Cap a Milano!    
    
    
    I'm at Apple Store (Via Rizzoli, 16, Bologna) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/AdVxz0     
    
    
    Nice recommendation, Dario! (@ Il Giardino dei Segreti) http://4sq.com/z0q0nj     
    
    
    I'm at IBM Barcelona (Barcelona, Barcelona) http://4sq.com/yV8Y6Q     
    
    
    Panel on The Brave New Mobile Ecosystem. Now discussing open federated models, interesting! #strandsfinance pic.twitter.com/l5KNyHdX    
    
    
    Who owns the customer in open federated models in the banking industry? The operators, the banks, ...? #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    New generation of customers will use mobile ecosystems in a completely different way. In which way? #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Banks taking care of payments. Operators taking care of technology. Someone should take care of user experience! #strandsfinance #mobyday    
    
    
    David Urbano from La Caixa: moving customers from branches to digital channels. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa gets 1000 innovation ideas from their employees through an internal platform. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa getting innovation sources from external developers organizing open competitions: e.g. FinnApp party. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa mobile 42% of mobile banking share in Spain. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    In La Caixa, mobile banking growing is exponential, web banking growing is linear! #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa mobile technology detects device and just presents different templates based on device constraints. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Price conversion cool native app from La Caixa #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    First bank in the world with contactles ATM. No card is needed just mobile phone. #laCaixa #mobeyday #strandsfinance.    
    
    
    La Caixa opens the first Smart TV banking app for Samsung. #laCaixa #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    It is not about m-payment, payment is the last thing you want in a shopping experience! #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Sean Gilchrist on the Closing keynote: Barclays Pingit - mobile payments come to Britain. #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    mobile payments made easy: you only need to know name and phone number to make the payment for registered users #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Pingit most challenging thing was to come up with a very simple and easy to use solution (user experience). #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Pingit is above Barclay's expectations, after a couple of months in production. #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Next Mobey Forum in Belfast on 23-24 May! #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Gooooooooooollllllll!    
    
    
    Congratulations @bigmlcom , this is awesome! 282 days of hacking in 3 minutes: http://wp.me/p234d6-7I  via    
    
    
    Som-hi Barça!    
    
    
    Roma en estat pur...  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/Jx1KKDuioL/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/Jx1W1RuioO/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/JytNEKuitA/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Place Vendôme http://instagr.am/p/K-NqG1uigs/     
    
    
    Que parisenc q es tot a Paris!  @ Place du Marché Saint-Honoré http://instagr.am/p/K-S8_yOiiY/     
    
    
    Ara toca Louvre! http://instagr.am/p/K-auZBuimG/     
    
    
    I'm taking Human-Computer Interaction - a free @coursera online class. Join me and sign up at  https://www.coursera.org/course/hci     
    
    
    @poll cereal    
    
    
    Es brutal la quantitat de Bentleys i Ferraris que es veuen a Londres, sembla que els regalin, estan sonats!    
    
    
    I just got up to 9,121 in #DoodleJump!!! Beat that!yt.       http://bit.ly/DoodleJump-App  pic.twitter.com/G2F1dZKM    
    
    
    Just completed a 9.04 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1k6fuo  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.49 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1kbfx9  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2012/06/13/business/global/bailout-in-spain-leaves-taxpayers-holding-the-bag.html?_r=3&emc=eta1 …    
    
    
    Just completed a 7.54 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1klxre  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    “@PrimaRiesgoBot: 569  | +2 | 7.13% | 18/06/2012 10:30” uf...    
    
    
    @JaumeBarbera Felicitats pel singu d'avui i els altres. És brutal. Si hi haguéssin més espais com aquest no ens enganyarien tant. Segur.    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.36 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1leuqb  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Kids are sleeping, I had dinner, "Breaking Bad" time!    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @ealmirall quina enveja, ja em podrieu haver convidat!    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.75 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1m1gx6  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    I am flying tonight to Zurich. Any recommendations for a cool bar to watch Italy-Germany?    
    
    
    If you are looking for the best technology team, I am sorry because I already have it and won't let it go!    
    
    
    Good meeting in London, off to Helsinki now!    
    
    
    Off to Berlin    
    
    
    #transavia flight (from AMS to BCN) delayed more than 5 hours, we are arriving at 2AM instead of 9PM, pathetic!    
    
    
    Am I going to land in the new T1 terminal in BCN airport?    
    
    
    @aldamiz donde estas?    
    
    
    @ReviewPro Congratulations!    
    
    
    Moltes felicitats a BMAT, aixo nomes es el principi! RT @bmat We won the XXI National (Spanish) Entrepreneurship Competition today!!!    
    
    
    Better medicine, brought to you by big data http://gigaom.com/cloud/better-medicine-brought-to-you-by-big-data/ …    
    
    
    Breaking Bad season 5!    
    
    
    Marissa Mayer's 9 Principles of Innovation http://lnkd.in/9pA99S     
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/819rx - This is the online chat of Telefonica (imagenio)... how is that possible? not enough revenue to have a good o ...    
    
    
    @xberneda apretant el boto on/off i el buto de davant alhora durant uns segons    
    
    
    Travelling to Trento, Italy, for UMAP 09. Short distance, long trip!    
    
    
    @JaumeBarbera sí, però el rescat ve amb condicions, no és gratuit.    
    
    
    @carmerossell molt Monzonia aixo jeje    
    
    
    Just tried the new Mac OS #MountainLion. It is really great! Many small but very usefull features.    
    
    
    Tweeting directly from the new Safari http://www.apple.com/osx/whats-new/features.html#timemachine …    
    
    
    great update from http://Chicisimo.com ! http://www.europapress.es/portaltic/internet/noticia-chicisimo-pinterest-moda-20120721100011.html …    
    
    
    @LoBonAndorra felicitats per l'uniforme a la cerimonia olimpica... molt be, jaqueteta de xandall, pantalons curts i botes. Com a casa!    
    
    
    At Strands we are looking for talented UI Engineers with Javascript or/and Flash skills. http://lnkd.in/_zc3P2    
    
    
    #umap2009 Industry Panel is finished, and I am relatively happy with it.    
    
    
    About to watch the triathlon in London!    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.19 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1thqmp  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 4.89 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1tnzvm  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    The Catalan Bailout | @XSalaimartin Blog http://salaimartin.com/randomthoughts/item/405-the-catalan-bailout.html …    
    
    
    Strands was issued US Pat 7,797,321, "System for Browsing through a Music Catalog using Correlation Metrics of a Knowl…http://lnkd.in/zk3NBz    
    
    
    Protest Rally in Catalonia Adds a Worry for Spain http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/12/world/europe/12iht-barcelona12.html …    
    
    
    Strands Becoming a Leader in the Personal Finance Management Market  http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20090706005113/en    
    
    
    Recommender Systems has started and people seem to enjoy it! #recsys2010
http://lnkd.in/-5svFb    
    
    
    A Roma! Pizza o pasta? ...    
    
    
    In Moscow, any good value restaurant recommendation? Anything to see apart from the tourist areas?    
    
    
    Despres de dues reunions i unes quantes aventures a Moscou, finalment a l'aeroport cap a Istambul!    
    
    
    Forrester Research publishes a case study about BBVA Tu Cuentas http://bit.ly/tywQe    
    
    
    Going to the IBM Smarter Industries Symposium in Barcelona.    
    
    
    Singapore! Hot and rainy... and jet-laged.    
    
    
    Clarke Quay (Singapore) pic.twitter.com/eYy5WRZB    
    
    
    @gsburguet thanks, conference starting now! All is setup, so ready for execution!    
    
    
    #finovate Tibco Software presenting context-aware recommendations involving merchants in an active way: interesting approach.    
    
    
    @walkingcrowd a veure si ens veiem!    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/3QuK4A10    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/ghCVHG7Q    
    
    
    Let’s Talk Your Data, Not Big Data | Innovation Insights | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/insights/2012/11/lets-talk-your-data-not-big-data/ …    
    
    
    Congratulations Chicisimo! http://thenextweb.com/insider/2012/11/25/chicisimo/?fromcat=all …    
    
    
    You've Got 30,000 Days To Live... Reverse Engineer Your Life To Make Them Count http://techcrunch.com/2012/12/11/sir-ray-avery-nz-makes-you-dangerous/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Cap a Paris!    
    
    
    Cap a Zurich!    
    
    
    Just completed a 8.01 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a2bokmf  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.53 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a2bu75a  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @mgarrigap molt interessant, Marc.  A veure si quedem I m'expliques!    
    
    
    Data for dummies: 6 data-analysis tools anyone can use http://gigaom.com/2013/01/31/data-for-dummies-5-data-analysis-tools-anyone-can-use/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    Credit Agricole launching one of the first financial services appstores based on their APIs #Finovate #api #3scale    
    
    
    Unleash The Brawn Of Big Data With Small Steps - Forbes http://onforb.es/WH7LdD     
    
    
    What is the best mind mapping app for Mac?    
    
    
    @VicGee thnks!    
    
    
    Finovate Europe 2013: Digital Financial Innovation | Forrester Blogs http://blogs.forrester.com/benjamin_ensor/13-02-13-finovate_europe_2013_digital_financial_innovation …    
    
    
    @marcmng anims!    
    
    
    InMaps - I visualized my LinkedIn network http://lnkd.in/bGwvuH    
    
    
    Why We Love Beautiful Things http://nyti.ms/12qqXjs     
    
    
    Luxury Chelsea, it is too much! pic.twitter.com/DxWmIICgzf    
    
    
    Awesome TED talk! Amanda Palmer, "The art of asking": http://youtu.be/xMj_P_6H69g     
    
    
    @flupianez Look at #9: http://www.forbes.com/sites/martinzwilling/2013/03/11/predictive-analytics-is-a-goldmine-for-startups/ …    
    
    
    @pau    
    
    
    Big data: Crunching the numbers | The Economist http://econ.st/JwA9uE     
    
    
    Cloudera ML: New Open Source Libraries and Tools for Data Scientists http://lnkd.in/Mrr5Cv     
    
    
    Want Your Company to Grow? Fire Your Managers! | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130320152447-5799319-want-your-company-to-grow-fire-your-managers …    
    
    
    10 Job Skills Startups Will Kill For http://on.mash.to/Z6gX84  via @mashable    
    
    
    I just purchased Keynotopia prototyping templates. Get yours at http://bit.ly/GetKeynotopia  via @keynotopia    
    
    
    A deep dive into Barcelona’s startup ecosystem, and how it’s much like the Sagrada Família http://tnw.to/h0eOf  via @TNWinsider    
    
    
    Sushi at the Emirates tower in Dubai, not bad for my first night here! pic.twitter.com/5YV4AUWQiH    
    
    
    @marcmng cullons no, sushi ;-)    
    
    
    Views from our last meeting in Abu Dhabi! pic.twitter.com/U2zg0WdC3U    
    
    
    Five Tips to Negotiate Better with Just About Anyone http://lifehacker.com/five-tips-to-negotiate-better-with-just-about-anyone-493106085 …    
    
    
    Just completed a 12.13 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a34hyrq  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Achieved a new personal record with @RunKeeper: Distance... http://bit.ly/11wXSwB  #FitnessAlerts    
    
    
    Just completed a 3.86 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a36lghn  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @30minuts Interessant el tema de privacitat i internet...    
    
    
    Oups... Ja no me'n recordava, un gin tonic a Bern son 20 euros.... Quina passada!    
    
    
    Check out "TNW @ Barcelona - in partnership with Barcelona.IO and Estrella Damm" http://tnwbarcelona-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Computing Now | Artificial Intelligence and Big Data : http://oal.lu/vYCDa     
    
    
    @oscarmarinmiro es una oportunidad de big data! Estos aparatos recogen datos cada hora, etc :-)    
    
    
    Big Data: Does Size Really Matter? | Innovation Insights | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/insights/2013/09/big-data-does-size-really-matter/ …    
    
    
    Nice building, in Paris! pic.twitter.com/MXEOzm7052    
    
    
    http://holykaw.alltop.com/5-habits-of-successful-aspiring-entrepreneurs?tu4=1 …    
    
    
    Startups need clear biz roadmap, executive summary http://www.zdnet.com/startups-need-a-clear-biz-roadmap-executive-summary-7000020683/ …    
    
    
    Que poc m'agrada matinar...    
    
    
    I signed up for Machine Learning on @Coursera! https://www.coursera.org/course/ml  #ml    
    
    
    This is very cool http://www.technologyreview.com/view/522111/how-to-burst-the-filter-bubble-that-protects-us-from-opposing-views/?utm_campaign=socialsync&utm_medium=social-post&utm_source=facebook …    
    
    
    Looking at a news release: http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20090929005421/en    
    
    
    @fxn proveidor?    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/qpHrE BBVA and ING projects both powered by Strands!    
    
    
    Spanish house prices: How low should they go? http://bit.ly/4AArf1    
    
    
    Very interesting TED talk on the bad side of the web personalization. Eli Pariser calls it the "filter bubble". http://on.ted.com/9DDC    
    
    
    Interesting book by Eli Pariser on the "filter bubble" on the web. http://amzn.to/ms3YF7 #in    
    
    
    @greglinden The problem is that the user in not in power of his own personalization. It is all about the lack of control.    
    
    
    Interview at "Cinco Días" about Strands Finance: http://bit.ly/lFnTqv #strands    
    
    
    @marciobarrios Gracias! nos seguiremos viendo, seguro.    
    
    
    Very interesting TED talk by the COO of Facebook about women and leadership. http://bit.ly/hcnwRz    
    
    
    A Strands patent on Music Visualization has been granted! http://www.freepatentsonline.com/7650570.pdf    
    
    
    At Strands we are looking for exceptionally talented engineers. We need very good web  front-end engineers, and java backend engineers.    
    
    
    Cap a Kiev, a veure què tal és...    
    
    
    http://spf.strands.com    
    
    
    I finished the reviews for the book Collaborative E-Research as part of the Editorial Advisory Board! http://bit.ly/iKAruT     
    
    
    Finished all my RecSys paper reviews on time!    
    
    
    Marc Vidal @ First Tuesday BCN. Tuesday, February 2nd: http://www.firsttuesday.es/    
    
    
    Announcement: #Tutorial "Evaluating Recommender Systems" by Guy Shani http://recsys.acm.org/2010/tutorials/ #recsys #barcelona 2010    
    
    
    @ferransoriano #ciut40 Molt bons exemples del "wisdom of crowd" en un sector tradicional i implementat a Spanair.    
    
    
    e-hitchhiking una bona iniciativa per implementar el viatge "fent dit" a través de les xarxes socials. #ciut40    
    
    
    Emprenedoria local @nockin_com #ciut40    
    
    
    #ciut40 recollida2011 un exemple d'iniciativa ciutadana que avança a l'administracio publica    
    
    
    This morning I've chaired the industry track at http://www.umap2011.org/  and one of the speakers was missing... first time I've seen that.    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @puntXpunt Marc, molt bones slides, en serio. S'aprecia molt un estil diferent als tipics bullet points amb text.    
    
    
    Looking for talented engineers: http://www.linkedin.com/jobs?viewJob=&jobId=868659&svfId=445489&trk=    
    
    
    I did my talk at IJCAI (Industry Day), I am reasonably happy, and getting plenty of interesting ideas and new contacts. #ijcai    
    
    
    Trying out the new Mac OS X Lion, it rocks! It is hard to get used to the new scroll bar, but it is now consistent with the iPhone one.    
    
    
    Veient el partit del Barça en un hotel a Manchester, i ... gol the Thiago! aquest nano es impresionant.    
    
    
    what is the best way to follow today's Apple show? #iPhone5    
    
    
    @carmerossell pero on ho veuras/seguiras? compres crispetes i tot?    
    
    
    @carmerossell però si avui no anuncien el iPhone 5 sinó el iPhone 4S! oooohhhhh....    
    
    
    A very say day for innovation lovers. Steve Jobs made me had a lot of fun in my daily work. I hope the company will continue his success.    
    
    
    @martinvars Completely agree with the traditional definition of nationalism. But, in Spain the term nationalism is used in another context.    
    
    
    @martinvars Europe, Asia and Africa...    
    
    
    Interviewing a Danish engineer. Half of the engineers in Barcelona from outside Spain... I believe diversity adds value to any project.    
    
    
    iCloud infrastructure cost $1b !    
    
    
    To Brussels, for the first time if I am not mistaken! (@ Aereoport de Barcelona - El Prat. Porta B28) http://4sq.com/uKClin     
    
    
    I'm at Sa Punta http://4sq.com/v5sLwF     
    
    
    On són els indignats?    
    
    
    I have just posted my talk at IJCAI here: http://marctorrens.net/2011/11/11/speaker-at-ijcai-2011-industry-day/ …    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @cerclefiber m'interessa molt, miraré de venir!    
    
    
    Very interesting video about new technologies and connectivity: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=50MQQ9K_X6Y …    
    
    
    I'm at Strands Barcelona (Marina, 16-18, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/bLscP6    
    
    
    BBC News - Eurozone debt web: Who owes what to whom? http://bbc.in/s8yEx6     
    
    
    I'm at T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN) (Terminal 1 El Prat de Llobregat, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    My little contribution as part of the Scientific Advisory Board to a great project: http://Chicisimo.com ! http://marctorrens.net/2011/11/23/scientific-advisor-for-chicisimo/ …    
    
    
    quin partit... impresionant! i nomes portem 30 minuts! Visca el Barça!    
    
    
    Very interesting video about Steve Jobs starting NeXT: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sOlqqriBvUM …    
    
    
    At TED Barcelona... About to start! pic.twitter.com/OnFh9GSY    
    
    
    M'agrada, com a mínim hi ha sensibilitat. http://internacional.elpais.com/internacional/2011/12/04/actualidad/1323030449_522201.html …    
    
    
    I'm at T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN) (Terminal 1 El Prat de Llobregat, Barcelona) w/ 4 others. http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    Read The Marc Daily ▸ today's top stories are contributed by @xamat  and  @aldamiz ▸ http://paper.li/marctorrens/~list?topic=Technology …    
    
    
    The 20 Best New Startups Of 2011 http://www.businessinsider.com/20-best-startups-technology-inventions-2011-12?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Interesting, about social media: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H61WvxOm1AM …    
    
    
    Introducing the Strands iPhone App, version 3.0! http://bit.ly/bPcwLT    
    
    
    @martinvars This is not a translation but a bad pronunciation. It is like pronouncing Barthelona instead of Barselona as it is in Catalan.    
    
    
    Fantastic, Apple is surpassing Microsoft's value on the stock market: http://nyti.ms/98qu5g    
    
    
    Entrevista a Aragón Radio por el premio Webby a moneyStrands.com: http://bit.ly/cK3xy9 #moneystrands    
    
    
    Flying to Brussels to finish the year in a nice way, let's see how it goes!    
    
    
    http://m.elblogsalmon.com/economia-domestica/cinco-razones-para-no-pagar-el-impuesto-de-los-tontos-comprar-loteria …    
    
    
    @xamat @sandrewge why do u use windows? Go for a serious OS!    
    
    
    The 10 Best TED Talks of 2011 by @jzb http://rww.to/tYYdR9  via @RWW    
    
    
    Strands has been awarded: 2011 RED HERRING GLOBAL TOP 100!  http://www.redherring.com/RHG/2011/top100.html …    
    
    
    I'm taking Human-Computer Interaction online for free at Online Education Stanford University. http://www.hci-class.org/  http://www.hci-class.org/     
    
    
    I am looking for a nice bar in Vienna to watch the FC Barcelona match tomorrow evening. Anyone?    
    
    
    I've just created an infographic of my CV. Check it out! http://bit.ly/vk36Lt?r=torrens … (via @vizualizeme) Original format...    
    
    
    Nice! RT @StrandsRecs: We're excited to close out Q2 with 15 great new retail customers and new plugins: http://bit.ly/coKbOx    
    
    
    EUR/USD < 1.1999    
    
    
    Hello World!    
    
    
    @edusampi Sí, hem mirat diferentes opcions per mantenir el servei pero sense exit. Ens sap molt greu, gracies pel suport i bon entranament!    
    
    
    I am hiring for moneyStrands!
http://tinyurl.com/dgobxt    
    
    
    Any good front-end or back-end engineer interested in being part of a great startup? @Chicisimo http://chicisimo.com/fashion/buscamos-talento/ …    
    
    
    Strands Finance Was Named a Winner of the Red Herring Top 100 - Bloomberg http://www.bloomberg.com/article/2012-01-02/am27Y6LMCS20.html … via @BloombergNow    
    
    
    NY Times: Spain’s Falling Prices Fuel Deflation Fears in Europe http://tinyurl.com/cj3zkl    
    
    
    Barcelona first ‘tap and go’ city in Europe - http://FT.com  - Technology http://on.ft.com/wEh0x8     
    
    
    Machine Learning 4 All! http://wp.me/p234d6-3x  via @bigml    
    
    
    Cap a New York! (@ T1 Aeroport de Barcelona (BCN)) http://4sq.com/aYjljF    
    
    
    @martinvars yes, it does!    
    
    
    Excellent talk, I highly recommend it, very inspiring! Luis von Ahn: Massive-scale online collaboration #TED http://on.ted.com/ADog     
    
    
    At the Webby cocktail, good atmosphere and awsome place with a 360 degrees view of Manhattan! (@ The Top of The Standard w/ 25 others)    
    
    
    I'm at Uncle Jack's Steakhouse (44 W 56th St, btw 5th & 6th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/5w0x9q    
    
    
    I'm at Apple Store (767 5th Ave, btw 58th & 59th St, New York) w/ 9 others. http://4sq.com/2GAjpC    
    
    
    Heading towards Switzerland, and tomorrow arriving to BCN just in time for the exciting match!    
    
    
    Having good time at the Webby ceremony! Pictures will follow... (@ The Webby Awards w/ 37 others) http://4sq.com/cIMa2H    
    
    
    Best burger in NY? Probably here! (@ Burger Joint at Le Parker Meridien w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/7TaY8F    
    
    
    Heading to London. On Thursday in Switzerland, I think I will enjoy lots of snow...    
    
    
    “@dpapagia: 6 startups to watch in 2012: 2 on education! http://mashable.com/2012/01/08/6-startups-to-watch-in-2012/ …” education and technology will be huge in the following years.    
    
    
    Terminal T2 in BCN airport. Fully underutilized. Pathetic. An example of throwing away public money. pic.twitter.com/vwnaoa0c    
    
    
    I'm at Roka (40 Canada Square, Canary Wharf, btw North & South Colonade, London) http://4sq.com/wmnZDR     
    
    
    Fantastic plane to go from london to Bern... pic.twitter.com/IvuPVzkY    
    
    
    @oscarjulve one of the best Japanese restaurant in Lon. Per flipar!    
    
    
    Flying to London for #finovate. Really looking forward to an exciting conference!    
    
    
    @polnavarro vens a finovate?    
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Black Friar http://instagr.am/p/Gvn2_BOiqk/     
    
    
    Interview about moneyStrands.com and its Webby award (in Spanish): http://bit.ly/c22iqD    
    
    
    Loved The Company Men (via Boxee)  http://b0x.ee/e3R8VM     
    
    
    I'm at Strands Barcelona (Marina, 16-18, Barcelona). http://4sq.com/bLscP6    
    
    
    Tech Start-Ups Take On Banks http://on.wsj.com/z84SfX  via @WSJ    
    
    
    I'm at L'imperial Café (240 rue de rivoli, Paris). http://4sq.com/6D7HYp    
    
    
    Just testing my app.... I have started to save €25,500.00 for Emergency Savings with the Strands Personal Finance saving tool    
    
    
    @carmerossell you cannot even imagine it :-)    
    
    
    Book on Distributed E-Research (I am on the Editorial Board) ;-) http://www.igi-global.com/book/collaborative-distributed-research/58272 …    
    
    
    Nice! Apple's TV Will Be 'The Biggest Thing In Consumer Electronics Since The Smartphone'—Munster http://www.businessinsider.com/apple-tv-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    He apoyado la petición Say to @neeliekroesEU we want a single #opendata license in the #EU #1OdataLicenseEU - http://bit.ly/zU7iKq     
    
    
    TED2012 remixed: It's Time for TED http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDHET3aCI2U&sns=tw … via @youtube    
    
    
    A TV3 haurien d'estudiar més matemàtiques: si l'Espanyol ha guanyat poc estadísticament al Madrid, avui té més possibilitats de guanyar.    
    
    
    Bryan Stevenson: We need to talk about an injustice http://on.ted.com/AUDM  #TED    
    
    
    Cap a Milano!    
    
    
    I'm at Apple Store (Via Rizzoli, 16, Bologna) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/AdVxz0     
    
    
    Nice recommendation, Dario! (@ Il Giardino dei Segreti) http://4sq.com/z0q0nj     
    
    
    I'm at IBM Barcelona (Barcelona, Barcelona) http://4sq.com/yV8Y6Q     
    
    
    Panel on The Brave New Mobile Ecosystem. Now discussing open federated models, interesting! #strandsfinance pic.twitter.com/l5KNyHdX    
    
    
    Who owns the customer in open federated models in the banking industry? The operators, the banks, ...? #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    New generation of customers will use mobile ecosystems in a completely different way. In which way? #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Banks taking care of payments. Operators taking care of technology. Someone should take care of user experience! #strandsfinance #mobyday    
    
    
    David Urbano from La Caixa: moving customers from branches to digital channels. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa gets 1000 innovation ideas from their employees through an internal platform. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa getting innovation sources from external developers organizing open competitions: e.g. FinnApp party. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa mobile 42% of mobile banking share in Spain. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    In La Caixa, mobile banking growing is exponential, web banking growing is linear! #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    La Caixa mobile technology detects device and just presents different templates based on device constraints. #mobyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Price conversion cool native app from La Caixa #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    First bank in the world with contactles ATM. No card is needed just mobile phone. #laCaixa #mobeyday #strandsfinance.    
    
    
    La Caixa opens the first Smart TV banking app for Samsung. #laCaixa #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    It is not about m-payment, payment is the last thing you want in a shopping experience! #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Sean Gilchrist on the Closing keynote: Barclays Pingit - mobile payments come to Britain. #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    mobile payments made easy: you only need to know name and phone number to make the payment for registered users #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Pingit most challenging thing was to come up with a very simple and easy to use solution (user experience). #strandsfinance #mobeyday    
    
    
    Pingit is above Barclay's expectations, after a couple of months in production. #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Next Mobey Forum in Belfast on 23-24 May! #mobeyday #strandsfinance    
    
    
    Gooooooooooollllllll!    
    
    
    Congratulations @bigmlcom , this is awesome! 282 days of hacking in 3 minutes: http://wp.me/p234d6-7I  via    
    
    
    Som-hi Barça!    
    
    
    Roma en estat pur...  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/Jx1KKDuioL/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/Jx1W1RuioO/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Fontana di Trevi http://instagr.am/p/JytNEKuitA/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo  @ Place Vendôme http://instagr.am/p/K-NqG1uigs/     
    
    
    Que parisenc q es tot a Paris!  @ Place du Marché Saint-Honoré http://instagr.am/p/K-S8_yOiiY/     
    
    
    Ara toca Louvre! http://instagr.am/p/K-auZBuimG/     
    
    
    I'm taking Human-Computer Interaction - a free @coursera online class. Join me and sign up at  https://www.coursera.org/course/hci     
    
    
    @poll cereal    
    
    
    Es brutal la quantitat de Bentleys i Ferraris que es veuen a Londres, sembla que els regalin, estan sonats!    
    
    
    I just got up to 9,121 in #DoodleJump!!! Beat that!yt.       http://bit.ly/DoodleJump-App  pic.twitter.com/G2F1dZKM    
    
    
    Just completed a 9.04 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1k6fuo  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.49 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1kbfx9  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    http://www.nytimes.com/2012/06/13/business/global/bailout-in-spain-leaves-taxpayers-holding-the-bag.html?_r=3&emc=eta1 …    
    
    
    Just completed a 7.54 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1klxre  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    “@PrimaRiesgoBot: 569  | +2 | 7.13% | 18/06/2012 10:30” uf...    
    
    
    @JaumeBarbera Felicitats pel singu d'avui i els altres. És brutal. Si hi haguéssin més espais com aquest no ens enganyarien tant. Segur.    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.36 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1leuqb  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Kids are sleeping, I had dinner, "Breaking Bad" time!    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @ealmirall quina enveja, ja em podrieu haver convidat!    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.75 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1m1gx6  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    I am flying tonight to Zurich. Any recommendations for a cool bar to watch Italy-Germany?    
    
    
    If you are looking for the best technology team, I am sorry because I already have it and won't let it go!    
    
    
    Good meeting in London, off to Helsinki now!    
    
    
    Off to Berlin    
    
    
    #transavia flight (from AMS to BCN) delayed more than 5 hours, we are arriving at 2AM instead of 9PM, pathetic!    
    
    
    Am I going to land in the new T1 terminal in BCN airport?    
    
    
    @aldamiz donde estas?    
    
    
    @ReviewPro Congratulations!    
    
    
    Moltes felicitats a BMAT, aixo nomes es el principi! RT @bmat We won the XXI National (Spanish) Entrepreneurship Competition today!!!    
    
    
    Better medicine, brought to you by big data http://gigaom.com/cloud/better-medicine-brought-to-you-by-big-data/ …    
    
    
    Breaking Bad season 5!    
    
    
    Marissa Mayer's 9 Principles of Innovation http://lnkd.in/9pA99S     
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/819rx - This is the online chat of Telefonica (imagenio)... how is that possible? not enough revenue to have a good o ...    
    
    
    @xberneda apretant el boto on/off i el buto de davant alhora durant uns segons    
    
    
    Travelling to Trento, Italy, for UMAP 09. Short distance, long trip!    
    
    
    @JaumeBarbera sí, però el rescat ve amb condicions, no és gratuit.    
    
    
    @carmerossell molt Monzonia aixo jeje    
    
    
    Just tried the new Mac OS #MountainLion. It is really great! Many small but very usefull features.    
    
    
    Tweeting directly from the new Safari http://www.apple.com/osx/whats-new/features.html#timemachine …    
    
    
    great update from http://Chicisimo.com ! http://www.europapress.es/portaltic/internet/noticia-chicisimo-pinterest-moda-20120721100011.html …    
    
    
    @LoBonAndorra felicitats per l'uniforme a la cerimonia olimpica... molt be, jaqueteta de xandall, pantalons curts i botes. Com a casa!    
    
    
    At Strands we are looking for talented UI Engineers with Javascript or/and Flash skills. http://lnkd.in/_zc3P2    
    
    
    #umap2009 Industry Panel is finished, and I am relatively happy with it.    
    
    
    About to watch the triathlon in London!    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.19 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1thqmp  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 4.89 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a1tnzvm  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    The Catalan Bailout | @XSalaimartin Blog http://salaimartin.com/randomthoughts/item/405-the-catalan-bailout.html …    
    
    
    Strands was issued US Pat 7,797,321, "System for Browsing through a Music Catalog using Correlation Metrics of a Knowl…http://lnkd.in/zk3NBz    
    
    
    Protest Rally in Catalonia Adds a Worry for Spain http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/12/world/europe/12iht-barcelona12.html …    
    
    
    Strands Becoming a Leader in the Personal Finance Management Market  http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20090706005113/en    
    
    
    Recommender Systems has started and people seem to enjoy it! #recsys2010
http://lnkd.in/-5svFb    
    
    
    A Roma! Pizza o pasta? ...    
    
    
    In Moscow, any good value restaurant recommendation? Anything to see apart from the tourist areas?    
    
    
    Despres de dues reunions i unes quantes aventures a Moscou, finalment a l'aeroport cap a Istambul!    
    
    
    Forrester Research publishes a case study about BBVA Tu Cuentas http://bit.ly/tywQe    
    
    
    Going to the IBM Smarter Industries Symposium in Barcelona.    
    
    
    Singapore! Hot and rainy... and jet-laged.    
    
    
    Clarke Quay (Singapore) pic.twitter.com/eYy5WRZB    
    
    
    @gsburguet thanks, conference starting now! All is setup, so ready for execution!    
    
    
    #finovate Tibco Software presenting context-aware recommendations involving merchants in an active way: interesting approach.    
    
    
    @walkingcrowd a veure si ens veiem!    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/3QuK4A10    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/ghCVHG7Q    
    
    
    Let’s Talk Your Data, Not Big Data | Innovation Insights | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/insights/2012/11/lets-talk-your-data-not-big-data/ …    
    
    
    Congratulations Chicisimo! http://thenextweb.com/insider/2012/11/25/chicisimo/?fromcat=all …    
    
    
    You've Got 30,000 Days To Live... Reverse Engineer Your Life To Make Them Count http://techcrunch.com/2012/12/11/sir-ray-avery-nz-makes-you-dangerous/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Cap a Paris!    
    
    
    Cap a Zurich!    
    
    
    Just completed a 8.01 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a2bokmf  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 6.53 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a2bu75a  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @mgarrigap molt interessant, Marc.  A veure si quedem I m'expliques!    
    
    
    Data for dummies: 6 data-analysis tools anyone can use http://gigaom.com/2013/01/31/data-for-dummies-5-data-analysis-tools-anyone-can-use/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    Credit Agricole launching one of the first financial services appstores based on their APIs #Finovate #api #3scale    
    
    
    Unleash The Brawn Of Big Data With Small Steps - Forbes http://onforb.es/WH7LdD     
    
    
    What is the best mind mapping app for Mac?    
    
    
    @VicGee thnks!    
    
    
    Finovate Europe 2013: Digital Financial Innovation | Forrester Blogs http://blogs.forrester.com/benjamin_ensor/13-02-13-finovate_europe_2013_digital_financial_innovation …    
    
    
    @marcmng anims!    
    
    
    InMaps - I visualized my LinkedIn network http://lnkd.in/bGwvuH    
    
    
    Why We Love Beautiful Things http://nyti.ms/12qqXjs     
    
    
    Luxury Chelsea, it is too much! pic.twitter.com/DxWmIICgzf    
    
    
    Awesome TED talk! Amanda Palmer, "The art of asking": http://youtu.be/xMj_P_6H69g     
    
    
    @flupianez Look at #9: http://www.forbes.com/sites/martinzwilling/2013/03/11/predictive-analytics-is-a-goldmine-for-startups/ …    
    
    
    @pau    
    
    
    Big data: Crunching the numbers | The Economist http://econ.st/JwA9uE     
    
    
    Cloudera ML: New Open Source Libraries and Tools for Data Scientists http://lnkd.in/Mrr5Cv     
    
    
    Want Your Company to Grow? Fire Your Managers! | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130320152447-5799319-want-your-company-to-grow-fire-your-managers …    
    
    
    10 Job Skills Startups Will Kill For http://on.mash.to/Z6gX84  via @mashable    
    
    
    I just purchased Keynotopia prototyping templates. Get yours at http://bit.ly/GetKeynotopia  via @keynotopia    
    
    
    A deep dive into Barcelona’s startup ecosystem, and how it’s much like the Sagrada Família http://tnw.to/h0eOf  via @TNWinsider    
    
    
    Sushi at the Emirates tower in Dubai, not bad for my first night here! pic.twitter.com/5YV4AUWQiH    
    
    
    @marcmng cullons no, sushi ;-)    
    
    
    Views from our last meeting in Abu Dhabi! pic.twitter.com/U2zg0WdC3U    
    
    
    Five Tips to Negotiate Better with Just About Anyone http://lifehacker.com/five-tips-to-negotiate-better-with-just-about-anyone-493106085 …    
    
    
    Just completed a 12.13 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a34hyrq  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Achieved a new personal record with @RunKeeper: Distance... http://bit.ly/11wXSwB  #FitnessAlerts    
    
    
    Just completed a 3.86 km run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a36lghn  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @30minuts Interessant el tema de privacitat i internet...    
    
    
    Oups... Ja no me'n recordava, un gin tonic a Bern son 20 euros.... Quina passada!    
    
    
    Check out "TNW @ Barcelona - in partnership with Barcelona.IO and Estrella Damm" http://tnwbarcelona-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Computing Now | Artificial Intelligence and Big Data : http://oal.lu/vYCDa     
    
    
    @oscarmarinmiro es una oportunidad de big data! Estos aparatos recogen datos cada hora, etc :-)    
    
    
    Big Data: Does Size Really Matter? | Innovation Insights | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/insights/2013/09/big-data-does-size-really-matter/ …    
    
    
    Nice building, in Paris! pic.twitter.com/MXEOzm7052    
    
    
    http://holykaw.alltop.com/5-habits-of-successful-aspiring-entrepreneurs?tu4=1 …    
    
    
    Startups need clear biz roadmap, executive summary http://www.zdnet.com/startups-need-a-clear-biz-roadmap-executive-summary-7000020683/ …    
    
    
    Que poc m'agrada matinar...    
    
    
    I signed up for Machine Learning on @Coursera! https://www.coursera.org/course/ml  #ml    
    
    
    This is very cool http://www.technologyreview.com/view/522111/how-to-burst-the-filter-bubble-that-protects-us-from-opposing-views/?utm_campaign=socialsync&utm_medium=social-post&utm_source=facebook …    
    
    
    Looking at a news release: http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20090929005421/en    
    
    
    @fxn proveidor?    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/qpHrE BBVA and ING projects both powered by Strands!    
    
    
    Spanish house prices: How low should they go? http://bit.ly/4AArf1    
    
    
    Very interesting TED talk on the bad side of the web personalization. Eli Pariser calls it the "filter bubble". http://on.ted.com/9DDC    
    
    
    Interesting book by Eli Pariser on the "filter bubble" on the web. http://amzn.to/ms3YF7 #in    
    
    
    @greglinden The problem is that the user in not in power of his own personalization. It is all about the lack of control.    
    
    
    Interview at "Cinco Días" about Strands Finance: http://bit.ly/lFnTqv #strands    
    
    
    @marciobarrios Gracias! nos seguiremos viendo, seguro.    
    
    
    Very interesting TED talk by the COO of Facebook about women and leadership. http://bit.ly/hcnwRz    
    
    
    A Strands patent on Music Visualization has been granted! http://www.freepatentsonline.com/7650570.pdf    
    
    
    At Strands we are looking for exceptionally talented engineers. We need very good web  front-end engineers, and java backend engineers.    
    
    
    Cap a Kiev, a veure què tal és...    
    
    
    http://spf.strands.com    
    
    
    I finished the reviews for the book Collaborative E-Research as part of the Editorial Advisory Board! http://bit.ly/iKAruT     
    
    
    Finished all my RecSys paper reviews on time!    
    
    
    Marc Vidal @ First Tuesday BCN. Tuesday, February 2nd: http://www.firsttuesday.es/    
    
    
    Announcement: #Tutorial "Evaluating Recommender Systems" by Guy Shani http://recsys.acm.org/2010/tutorials/ #recsys #barcelona 2010    
    
    
    @ferransoriano #ciut40 Molt bons exemples del "wisdom of crowd" en un sector tradicional i implementat a Spanair.    
    
    
    e-hitchhiking una bona iniciativa per implementar el viatge "fent dit" a través de les xarxes socials. #ciut40    
    
    
    Emprenedoria local @nockin_com #ciut40    
    
    
    #ciut40 recollida2011 un exemple d'iniciativa ciutadana que avança a l'administracio publica    
    
    
    This morning I've chaired the industry track at http://www.umap2011.org/  and one of the speakers was missing... first time I've seen that.    
    
    
    @mgarrigap @puntXpunt Marc, molt bones slides, en serio. S'aprecia molt un estil diferent als tipics bullet points amb text.    
    
    
    Looking for talented engineers: http://www.linkedin.com/jobs?viewJob=&jobId=868659&svfId=445489&trk=    
    
    
    I did my talk at IJCAI (Industry Day), I am reasonably happy, and getting plenty of interesting ideas and new contacts. #ijcai    
    
    
    Trying out the new Mac OS X Lion, it rocks! It is hard to get used to the new scroll bar, but it is now consistent with the iPhone one.    
    
    
    