@jmantissa awesome! http://www.jausart.com/     
    
    
    A Nonie and art admin day, + both were actually quite nice after such intense editing all week. Later: Troy and Abed, and lots of 'em.    
    
    
    Troy and Abed in the moooorning! #community    
    
    
    @charlottefrost likes my book (so far at least)    
    
    
    Working on Kickstarter campaign w/ Scott Kildall + US Artists fundraiser w/ Jessica Meuninck-Ganger. Exciting new projects! # yay #art    
    
    
    In next 2 days, I must review grad student apps between various Nonie outings + meetings. Is it me, or did weekends stop existing long ago?    
    
    
    Two incontrovertible things: Anthropogenic Global Warming is Real, and the Wall Street Journal is a Political Rag http://bit.ly/y1jyVI     
    
    
    I'm rendering video. A sketch for some new art. It feels really nice to be working on art. @charlottefrost can keep my book draft for a bit.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost hooray for making stuff! so fun with you on Thurs! PS I told Nicole and she is keen to chat about your project...    
    
    
    Just got back from @creativecap (Creative Capital) info session here in Milwaukee. AMAZING. I <3 Ruby Lerner. We need 20 more just like her.    
    
    
    Not a very good night's sleep. Mind blazing with ideas, anxieties and excitement of varying degrees. Coffee. More coffee.    
    
    
    awake    
    
    
    Productive morning.    
    
    
    This has been a really long day. And I still have several hours of work to go. Good thing I like art/teaching/reading/writing so much.    
    
    
    Democrats: you are using the wrong language! Instead of calling it "The Buffet Rule," call it "Flat Tax for Millionaires and Billionaires."    
    
    
    I FINK U FREEKY, and I like you a lot. Serious. http://bit.ly/AcFwjj     
    
    
    Michael Szpakowski's lovely 'Lawrence Weiner Erasure' - a work of conceptual art http://flic.kr/p/bkhhua     
    
    
    Rachel @maddow is coming to Milwaukee! If only I could afford tickets for me and the Mrs... Meh, I'll still buy the book. RECALL WALKER!!!    
    
    
    Main art, writing books, doing stuff, yeh ...    
    
    
    I heard there was a football game today or something. I was catching up on eps of Community. But hey, Giants are cool - my daughter says so.    
    
    
    Crazy days! Art and writin and teaching and all....    
    
    
    I know Situationist is meant to be capitalized. What about Relational Art / Aesthetics? (Other than when I'm referring to the book.)    
    
    
    "art is always both a limitation and a magnification"    
    
    
    Greg Martens is one of the most amazing artists / students / people I've ever had the pleasure to work with. http://bit.ly/wEE2Os     
    
    
    I am watching Short Circuit with my daughter. Srsly.    
    
    
    @MikeBrenner now all she does is ask for "input! input!"    
    
    
    All meetings and editing a proposal today. After 2 straight hours of answering emails. At least there's coffee.    
    
    
    Getting warmer. Getting warmer!... No, not Milwaukee - that's actually getting colder. I just mean I'm almost done with my book!    
    
    
    Mocking up image layouts and begging for permission to use them from other artists. Yes, I'm an art geek: I am having so much fun! #AcWri    
    
    
    I signed up for a marathon today, in October. I'm up to 3 miles now, only 23 more to add... Yikes!    
    
    
    Awesome awesome awesome news for @nathanielstern and @kildall - so totally exciting. Public info coming soon...    
    
    
    @Brianputz new project...    
    
    
    @artcity Lovely to see you and yes, interesting show re: #newexchanges at @miad_edu ... Also, you should come to the desert with us.    
    
    
    @artcity deal on both counts - will let you know when we can start talking about it publicly.    
    
    
    Just remembered I'm going to LA next week. Can anyone there watch my daughter on Thurs mornin during my CAA panel? Also, wanna hang out? #LA    
    
    
    @nicolegeary sure, we can grab coffee! I'll be meandering between going gaga at other sessions, doing my own + spending time with the fam!    
    
    
    Today: gymnastics, lunch + piano lesson with Nonie, Creative Capital grant proposal, Sense Lab skype + CAA prep. Also, pizza for breakfast.    
    
    
    @FineLineMag gorgeous installation at MIAD, and I'm loving following the new site / blog! Where can I buy all back issues locally in MKE?    
    
    
    @TwoCoats Google+ keeps telling me that people are adding me, and I keep meaning to do something about it...    
    
    
    @artfagcity macklemore. definitely macklemore. i'm especially fond of the bush song.    
    
    
    Secret World of Arrietty - super sweet. Nonie and I really enjoyed it, and then some time in the park.    
    
    
    Hey kid. _Hi daddy._ Let's go to California tomorrow. _Sure._ Cool. #CAA    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity was at the Tar Pits with with my family + @marctasman yesterday, then the New Media Caucus thing. Where were you?    
    
    
    Black Venus panel at #CAA2012 this morning=great! New Media Caucus Pecha Kucha thing on Wed = Awesome. + my panel yesterday of course rocked    
    
    
    @charlottefrost: "ah so modest! ;-)" - well, I didn't actually present on my panel, so I'm speaking of the awesomeness of my colleagues...    
    
    
    @charlottefrost there IS no upstaging your Derridance. Except maybe with your Spinoza Shimmy.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost Lyotard Lindy    
    
    
    @charlottefrost Jamesian Jitterbug and Whitehead Waltz... OK, I'll stop. Do not want to overload @collegeart / #CAA2012 with our fine moves.    
    
    
    LA: ok bye. That was kinda fun. looking forward to looking up all the cool new props I met! #CAA2012 #CAA    
    
    
    This Colbert video on branding is hilarious - but it also made me go out and buy Wheat Thins. http://bit.ly/Ab8Oad  #wheatthins #colbert    
    
    
    @kickstarter or @RocketHub or  @USAforART ? Differences? Insights? Doing 2 media artworks + can't decide b/w them for each one #crowdfunding    
    
    
    Art is great.    
    
    
    The Daily Show's Samantha Bee Demolishes Grover Norquist http://bit.ly/AyxM0R     
    
    
    William Kentridge receives Dan David Award! $1 Million for “scientific, technological and cultural accomplishments” http://huff.to/y685Wy     
    
    
    Sidonie says, "Daddy, you like mommy's dinners a lot. That's why your belly is getting bigger."    
    
    
    Congratulations @juspar !!! Insect Media has won the Anne Friedberg book award. http://bit.ly/z7hjG9     
    
    
    @artcity gives a considerable amount of thought, and time, to grappling with MIAD's recent show. http://bit.ly/A37ZUQ     
    
    
    I wish I knew sooner that you could delete tweets and facebook posts...    
    
    
    The State of the Art is Elsewhere: “Print/Out” at The Museum of Modern Art - great article! http://bit.ly/AqiCKU     
    
    
    So cool! Metropolis II by Chris Burden (the movie) http://youtu.be/llacDdn5yIE  (h/t Kennan Ferguson)    
    
    
    Lytro Light Field Camera - this blows my mind a little bit. http://bit.ly/wNainO     
    
    
    Hey @GeorgeJirasek : I ran into / met some great folks at CAA in LA, from Chicago, and am all fired up to restart upgrade MKE. You in?    
    
    
    dangerous thought... RT @charlottefrost: I keep accidentally direct messaging people, for my next trick I'll public message a private tweet!    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity sorry to miss it, too. tho hanging single volunteer piece this morning was far more work than it should've been.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost totally. also, you should call me poochlet in public more often. it makes me blush, in a good way.  #poochlet    
    
    
    @charlottefrost oh she does look cool, and the drummer is KYOOT! Am prepping for Erin and Brian 2omorrow, so send my best...    
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost Sunday Brunch would be better for me (especially if I can bring Nonie, but even if not)    
    
    
    I <3 The Sense Lab and all my colleagues in it. What a lovely chat today, + looking forward to a catch-up with others next week! #goodpeeps    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity  I have Charlie and the Choco factory tix with nonie at 4. Could do before that with her, if possible?    
    
    
    OMG best afternoon in so long, with Erin Manning and Brian Massumi. I <3 you guys!    
    
    
    25 minutes total on the elliptical and a tread mill are better than no workout at all. ... ... Right?    
    
    
    @charlottefrost is currently speaking at C21, and sounding very smart. And also funny. "Filmism" and zombies are being featured. #themes    
    
    
    Aaaaaaah! Inbox! (still ignoring for a few more days....)    
    
    
    Sure, I'll make great art with you and go to France for it. I mean, if I have to.    
    
    
    @nicolegeary great to meet you in LA! This is a year-ish long project, which'll involve tests in MKE, Montreal and more. Yay art!    
    
    
    Just got a big university grant to finish a suite of interactive installations: equipment, catalog, laptop, assistants + travel $$. Yay.    
    
    
    Up since 4 AM. Meh.    
    
    
    Three big projects added in as many weeks. A little scary, but kinda awesome. Collabs with Scott Kildall + Erin Manning, + a solo suite.    
    
    
    Jon Stewart: Investigative journalism is dead. Live long instigative journalism!    
    
    
    Do tell. RT @charlottefrost: VERY over-excited 'squeeeeeeeeeeeee'-style exclamation at upcoming thingys....    
    
    
    Thing 12 I learned this week: Nonie is allergic to Amoxicillin. Good to know. #strepthroat    
    
    
    hahaha this is what editors are for! RT @charlottefrost: Stern quote: ...in order to practice and experience the birth of Chinese dragons...    
    
    
    @artcity breaks the story! @kildall + @nathanielstern of @wikipediaart are sending tweets into deep space for ISEA2012 http://bit.ly/zMuTYD     
    
    
    @charlottefrost mmmmmm. Sil's.    
    
    
    Planning 2013 Gallery AOP show in South Africa w/ Jessica Meuninck-Ganger. New work from @center21, essay by @rgrusin, workshops at @UJ_FADA    
    
    
    I had a List of things I remembered I had to do when playing with my daughter this morning. But then I forgot them all before I got home.    
    
    
    Furtherfield Gallery's debut show in Finsbury Park makes you question what you put online (From Enfield Independent) http://bit.ly/xurvvg     
    
    
    4 miles this morning in Estabrook park, then an entire day w. Nonie: park, pizza, play at the Marcus, hot cocoa + tag with friends! Lovely.    
    
    
    Gonna be a busy one this week. If you haven't already scheduled something with me, don't bother trying.    
    
    
    hahaha RT @alan_butler: one day, you'll see your name in vinyl    
    
    
    Lasers are cool. Radio, too. And aliens. I like aliens. Also, Twitter. And public art. Let's see if we can combine them all, yeh? At ISEA?    
    
    
    Community is back this week!!! Troy and Abed in the mooooorning! http://bit.ly/9rH8Hp     
    
    
    Working on a few UWM things while waiting for my car maintenance. Guy next to me is snoring really loudly and I hate how annoying I find it!    
    
    
    Anyone know where to buy a super powerful radio transmitter that does 1420 megahertz? For the aliens, you know? #radio #transmission #art    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @robmyers a cave painting, a few meninas, some water lilies, and a urinal walk into a bar (woodcut, I think)...    
    
    
    Hey @artcity ! R U gonna hang out w/ me + @charlottefrost this afternoon after our mad editing session? I can pick you up (or meet U) 4-ish.    
    
    
    Mad editing session with @charlottefrost . All #AcWri up in this hiz-ouse!    
    
    
    @artcity just call. we want you to come.    
    
    
    @CarCareKiosk editing an academic book, that is. wanna help?    
    
    
    Working with grad students is the best part of my job.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost is a good editor. #AcWri #arts #future #book    
    
    
    An American who gets irony! BRILLIANT TED talk on "copyright math" - lies the entertainment industry tells us w numbers http://bit.ly/xoRoA2     
    
    
    @charlottefrost says break apart + disperse parts of Ch. 1. Am thinking some 4 the intro, the next chapter + following, + of course TRASH    
    
    
    brain hurts    
    
    
    I like writing SO much more than editing. Can someone else do the cutting and pasting, and I'll do the transitions? #AcWri    
    
    
    Editing process: cut, move, paste, transition; yes, no, delete, transition; move, cut, transition, YES. Repeat til book is done. #AcWri    
    
    
    Tool At Hand exhibit at Sweetwater rocked http://bit.ly/FPwCV0   - MAM show looks great http://bit.ly/FPZHdo  @joygarnett @GeorgeJirasek    
    
    
    I just can't see the shape of the Intro now that the following chapter has been cut + dispersed. It'll come, but it's hard right now. #AcWri    
    
    
    @artcity how'd the rest of the day go? Looking forward to the finished vids!    
    
    
    Awake most of the night.    
    
    
    in the blog: Help Jessica and me make art! http://nathanielstern.com/blog/2012/03/20/help-jessica-and-me-make-art/ …    
    
    
    Please help Jessica Meuninck-Ganger and me produce our next exhibition in South Africa. Crowd funding with US Artists: http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    Playing with Arduino, shift registers and LEDs before moving to shift registers to control animated audio signals. FUN! (wIth Bryan Cera)    
    
    
    I'm on a plane. No really. + I'm sending messages about sending messages to space. From a plane. http://youtu.be/cngnhXxBiFE  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @artfagcity http://master-list2000.com   is run by A. Bill Miller http://bit.ly/GJLhwL  - great guy. UW-Milwaukee grad, too.    
    
    
    @gridworks1 you're welcome :)    
    
    
    Didn't sleep so well last night. I think a morning run + then a swim in the sea with my brother-in-law will make me feel a bit better. #FL    
    
    
    I'm busy, too, you know. Lots of stuff: family, art, writing, teaching, admin - good things, lots of work. AND I'm not rude to people. #jerk    
    
    
    Editing a book. On a plane. Nonie is watching Enchanted. We're on our way to Chicago to see an old friend, then back to MKE. We need naps.    
    
    
    Twitter spam getting a little out of control these days. Do you think the aliens will like this glimpse into our culture? #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @kildall Kildaaaaaaaaaaall!    
    
    
    @charlottefrost early lunch with @kildall and victoria and me? noon, izumi's?    
    
    
    What else can art look like? What else it can it be?    
    
    
    Indeed RT @rgrusin: What else can it do?  What can it change?  RT @nathanielstern: What else can art look like? What else it can it be?    
    
    
    Also, NEW DOCTOR WHO TRAILER --- WOOOOOOO! http://huff.to/H4snXd  (or should I say inspector spacetime? http://huff.to/HcRVjC  )    
    
    
    @hmm__ @nathanielstern one quote from my upcoming book: "digital is as digital does"    
    
    
    @hmm__ @rgrusin another quote from my upcoming book: "art and philosophy [are] potential practices of one another"    
    
    
    @troyrhoades How might art otherwise?    
    
    
    OK, 2 solid hours to work on this. Closing all browsers, readers, mail clients and decks. Interwebs: you'll have to do without me for a bit.    
    
    
    lalalalalalalala #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @Lediris thanks for the support! more crowdfunding help welcome :) http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    Days like this, where I hear about Pink Slime, make me wish I'd been vegetarian (again) for the last while: http://bit.ly/GZJnIG  #pinkslime    
    
    
    What a terrible evening.    
    
    
    Listening to Tim Lenoir speak at @center21 / UW-Milwaukee, with @charlottefrost @rgrusin and others    
    
    
    Making twitter art w/ @kildall - it's gonna be HUGE. Anybody have a contact there they wanna share? #tweetsinspace #twitter #youlikeus    
    
    
    My brain hurts more than a little bit.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost In my C21 office, and yeh - come by befor eyou head down.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost now i am behind you (back left of the room). Have to sneak out to go get my daughter before the end....    
    
    
    Oh. Ehm. Eff. Gee. (And other acronyms.)    
    
    
    Kaganopup!!!!!    
    
    
    Oh, I <3 you Rachel @maddow + have since Air America started! Sorry to miss U here in MKE - us teachers took pay cuts. http://bit.ly/HmGN4Z     
    
    
    Writing a book while Nonie jumps. No, really; we're at a jumping castle park with WiFi. Adults not allowed to jump :( #wishIwas5    
    
    
    Watching HUGO with my daughter. Beautiful homage to film! Reminds me why I'm an artist - sometimes, it's just magical.    
    
    
    OH YEH! Penultimate draft of my book is off to the editor and it is GOOOOOD! Thanks for all the great suggestions @charlottefrost #AcWri    
    
    
    You really shouldn't invite me to things where I have to keep quiet. Movies, theatre, talks... academic meetings...    
    
    
    @wugmump I miss you. Nonie and I are coming for a week or so in early June. Play date for kids _and_ grown-ups?    
    
    
    @wugmump Yay! I'm buying my tix this week, and we'll make a plan :)    
    
    
    Answering emails, attending meetings, running miles, teaching, AND making art. Your move, TUESDAY. #mwahahaha    
    
    
    Wednesday, you are going DOWN!    
    
    
    Basically, MySpace. RT @karppi: What Facebook Would Have Looked Like in the ’90s. http://bit.ly/HGDANY     
    
    
    @nicolegeary Tag team! As long as Wednesday doesn't partner with Monday, we can take it! Take THAT Wednesday! #beatthedays    
    
    
    Didn't do as well against Wednesday as I hoped, but Thursday, Oh Thursday, I can take YOU. #beatthedays    
    
    
    I like it when good things happen to good people.    
    
    
    I totally pwn Thursday April 5. #beatthedays    
    
    
    Showing interactive installation "stuttering" http://bit.ly/I1qd6B  in Madison next week. Come see if you can! http://on.fb.me/I1q7vX     
    
    
    Still need 70% more funding for my project with Jessica. Please donate! http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    10 K run this morning, about an hour and 15 mins. Not bad for my first real "long run." A bit sore, but manageable. w00t!    
    
    
    @tretheke Teh Treth!!!!    
    
    
    Halfway there, 11 days left, please help fund art! http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    Oh inbox, why must you always be so difficult? Stay DOWN. #beatthedays    
    
    
    Late, but just about on my way to Madison for an exhibition at the Art Lofts gallery at UW. http://bit.ly/IWjZXV     
    
    
    about 9 miles in the rain - mos def my toughest run yet (both distance and weather). wish me luck! http://soc.li/UcvwzpR     
    
    
        
    
    
    @alyxpryn tweet in space?    
    
    
    Two days left, 80% funded, $1000 dollars to go. Please help! http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    All your retweets are belong to us. #retweet    
    
    
    Tonight! Joseph DeLappe talk, "Protest, Memory and Reenactment," FREE at the UWM Artist Lecture Hall! http://bit.ly/Jcg8Ds     
    
    
    The New Aesthetic is less an aesthetic, + more a recognition of bias and trend. A good thing, worth critical analysis, but a bit overblown.    
    
    
    Less than one day left, 92% there! Please make a small tax-deductible donation and get free art! http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    WE'RE SO CLOSE! 9 hours left, $70 to go. Don't you want to send us over? Donate now! http://bit.ly/GCP3Kg     
    
    
    Nice day at Kenilworth Open Studios, Milwaukee    
    
    
    10 mile run - my longest yet! - at an average of 9:59 per mile. W00T!    
    
    
    MT @center21: Weather Patterns: [me], Brian Massumi, Erin Manning et al. project at #c21nonhuman conference: http://tinyurl.com/6wwx3ja     
    
    
    Tweeeeeeets iiiiiiiiin Spaaaaaaaaaaaaace!!!! donate, make it happen, spread the word. with @kildall http://rkthb.co/7291  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @mattkuhlman yeh! was about to email you - please retweet to help raise funds if you don't mind http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    MT @jaynewt: http://bit.ly/I4M7q1  TWEETS IN SPACE FOR F*CKS&KE y'all -- fund this! this must happen! go go! #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Tweets in Space on http://Forbes.com ! Please contribute! http://lnkd.in/hNCJtx     
    
    
    Tweets in Space on http://Forbes.com ! Please help us make this project happen! http://onforb.es/JJDyDh  and donate at http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Leg still pretty sore from 10 mile run last weekend, but gonna try to do this 10K in the rain. Here we go...    
    
    
    10 k race, 51:52 time, avg 8:21 per mile. w00t!!!!    
    
    
    My legs are really sore.    
    
    
    So glad Brian Massumi + Erin Manning are here! Looking forward to arrival of Christoph Brunner, @troyrhoades  + other #c21nonhuman speakers    
    
    
    awake.    
    
    
    Ow my legs really hurt.    
    
    
    Oh. Ehm. Eff. Gee. Send your tweets into space! All you need to do is help raise funds. http://rkthb.co/7291  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @troyrhoades you guys are too too funny. (I'm in)    
    
    
    Remind me again why technology is so great? #installation    
    
    
    1/2 the system working. 42 speakers animating LCD soundsystem 1 at a time as our test. Let's hang + animate some air (w fans)! #c21nonhuman    
    
    
    @rgrusin yeh, but i'm pretty tired - still in Curtin! smooch :)    
    
    
    @caleb_scharf pens a great piece on #TweetsInSpace 4 Scientific American! http://bit.ly/IJQJAc   We still need yr help! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Now on the FRONT PAGE of Scientific American! http://bit.ly/14vewS     
    
    
    @artcity thanks ML. Thanks also for doing such a great job breaking the story!    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/oczjuep  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    PS I think I can add #c21nonhuman to this story... http://bit.ly/JY476E     
    
    
    @alyxpryn still wrapping my head around it. very excited about thinking you, bennett, + massumi's new paper/book together....    
    
    
    From Kenna Verguson: Help, I'm a Rock!  http://youtu.be/Ukbu9dmmzJg  #c21nonhuman    
    
    
    MT @katebolick: In my dream last night Angelina Jolie told me she had all those kids so someday she'll have heaps of artistic collaborators    
    
    
    A few unnecessary (opposite of niceties?), some great art, provocative papers, + good conversation. Overall awesome conference #C21nonhuman    
    
    
    Hey @StephenAtHome - this is up your alley: http://bit.ly/JY476E     
    
    
    @charlottefrost honored to make the list. Thnk U for the great year, great day + all that stuff I just left your place with! Miss U already.    
    
    
    So far, I like South Africa's M&G new web site. MT @ChrisRoper: "So ... we built a new website" - http://bit.ly/Kwicwa  via @mailandguardian    
    
    
    MT #FF MKE artists!  @FineLineMag @aj_avery @Eddie_V_Art @ricstultz @JKaminskiPhoto @KpollyMKE @faythelevine @turnislefthome @alyssadanger    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace hits NY Daily News + gets super Twitterverse! buzz! http://nydn.us/IQxyVq  But we still need yr support: http://bit.ly/I4M7q1     
    
    
    @TweetSmarter #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @AndyBarovick #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @nikkiwoods #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @GeralynK #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @prempiyush #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @manyko2 #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @rocketman528 #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @SeanDonahoe #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @henrikboyander #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @VBalasubramani #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @cleveland129 #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @WendiMooreAgncy #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @DirectorySootle #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @HarlemVoice #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @JustinBiebersTv #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @Kriisiis #tweetsinspace is still fundraising for transmission + would appreciate support. Pls RT http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    MT @juspar: In the midst of #c21nonhuman a good read from @rgrusin on Harman, Massumi, + lots more: http://bit.ly/JN8ajx     
    
    
    @wugmump Scientific American and the New York Daily News. Srsly. Look it up.    
    
    
    @wugmump http://bit.ly/JY476E  and http://nydn.us/IQxyVq  for http://rkthb.co/7291  - pass it on...    
    
    
    IMHO Object Oriented Ontology is not about objects (but abstractions) or ontology (but epistemology). It's structuralism by another name.    
    
    
    Looking for student design ideas. The prize: a team of engineers for yr prototype, and some start-up funds. Pass it on. http://bit.ly/IXJRG4     
    
    
    Hey fellow professors: Best XKCD ever... http://xkcd.com/1052/     
    
    
    RHIZOME MEMBERS: pls vote for new project by me and @kildall! http://bit.ly/JfnND1     
    
    
    I just backed "MK-EaT #2 - Don't take art off the Table!" on kickstarter - you should, too! http://kck.st/Jfsk91     
    
    
    @jjpulizzi look forward to it!    
    
    
    @StephenAtHome 16 days left to send #TweetsinSpace - message Gorlock + others on GJ667Cc! http://rkthb.co/7291  + http://bit.ly/JY476E     
    
    
    There seems to be some confusion between @dskendall and @kildall - the latter is the collaborator with @nathanielstern on #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Tweets in Space makes Time Magazine Web site!!!! http://ti.me/ISVVq6  #tweetsinspace Don't 4get we still need yr help!    
    
    
    @artfagcity then she's not paying attention    
    
    
    @MikeBrenner yes, please (but keep their cool kinetic sculpture collection, right?)    
    
    
    If you're in the UK 2morrow morning or up late + online 2nite, I'll be on BBC Radio News @ 6:50 AM London time, talking about #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @charlottefrost The flagship news show on BBC Radio 4!    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @staceywng Good call! Live listening: http://bbc.in/16Xmsb  + next 7 days http://bbc.in/1WpJqt     
    
    
    @StephenAtHome #tweetsinspace now on Time's website + tomorrow morning on BBC Radio 4 - why are you missing this story? http://ti.me/ISVVq6     
    
    
    On my way to an interview with @charrlls on BBC Radio 4 @bbcr4today - live in less than an hour if you wanna listen! http://bbc.in/KrDx7j     
    
    
    @tomcolls only during performance time - we want a real potency to the real-time conversation!    
    
    
    MT @BBCr4today #TweetsInSpace will be beamed to closest exoplanet that might support life on 21 Sept  http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @_MattShaw ta! could still use support in making it happen! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @MuirBowden @BBCr4today : yes, we'll calculate for GJ667Cc in 22 years' time. WOrking with engineers on everything!    
    
    
    @tomcolls Still finalizing exact time, but September 21 send #tweetsinspace around 2-3AM London time - see http://bit.ly/wIyYKo   for updates    
    
    
    MT @domburch: again on @bcbradio later today (4-6pm London time). Going to have a space theme in honour of #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Listen to me on BBC Radio 4 late last night (early this London Morning) - on the TODAY show! http://bbc.in/JEVsI2  #r4today    
    
    
    @charlottefrost I'm proud of you too. Wanna have lunch together later?    
    
    
    @charlottefrost done and sent back. it's great. I brought lunch, so will come by your office and perhaps we can sit outside? 1-ish?    
    
    
    Totally agree. RT @RocketHub: We try :) RT @astrobokonon: You guys and gals over at @RocketHub are awesome!    
    
    
    Thanks @Jacattell  !  http://bit.ly/wIyYKo  for info, + we're still crowdfunding to make it happen at http://rkthb.co/7291  -help appreciated!    
    
    
    Plastic-Eating Fungi Found in the Amazon May Solve World’s Waste Problem - Amazing! http://on.mash.to/y84R5s     
    
    
    @charrlls Thanks, yeh, was nervous but I think it went well. Nice that folks are listening - glad to do it! /cc @kildall    
    
    
    @StephenAtHome BBC + Daily Mail, now! Gorlock wants you to send #TweetsinSpace via The Report! http://bit.ly/LIvBOD  + http://bit.ly/IQY9aM     
    
    
    @bradleylbar: "journalists’ lack of attention to scholars + union activities lead them to miss many stories" http://bit.ly/Kgczxg     
    
    
    Rest in peace, Fred Stern. You were a good man, and even better family.    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace features on CNET (+ TV), Rockethub, & more! See http://bit.ly/J2oa1P  for deets + pls consider donating: http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    I think I might stop watching TED talks starting today. http://bit.ly/JcYELY     
    
    
    Troy and Abed in the Morning - Nights #sixseasonsandamovie    
    
    
    @twhid awesome!!! Congrats!    
    
    
    Thanks @tjoosten  and @Commun310  !!! #tweetsinspace http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    4 days for Tweets in Space funds. Great press, but way down on fundraising (33%), despite badgering efforts. link = http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Oh. My. God. BEST WHISKEY EVER! http://bit.ly/LCWJlQ     
    
    
    My little girl is six years old today. Can you believe it?    
    
    
    @stephenathome you are nearly back from vacay - time to send #tweetsinspace to Gorlock. Tweeeeets iiiin Spaaaaace! http://bit.ly/JY476E     
    
    
    Rare occurrence: #tweetsinspace crowd-fund extended b/c of imminent press - pls consider donating, not even 1/2 there! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    rainy staycation day catching up on Game of Thrones (both the books and show)    
    
    
    @stephenathome http://tweetsinspace.org/  #gorlock    
    
    
    @artcity love it. will send a mail tomorrow with some thoughts!    
    
    
    I just voted. #recallwalker    
    
    
    9.2 miles with Maurice Dumit, 9:12 pace. Nice one, dude!    
    
    
    @wugmump saturday afternoon play / night sleepover? Just me + Nonie, June 9...    
    
    
    @wugmump could maybe even do AEOLIAN RIDE GOVERNER's ISLAND...?    
    
    
    @artcity @staceywng  interesting. how will our roles coalesce?    
    
    
    MT @staceywng: Well I (can also) plan to just mostly look on from afar, act bossy, and aim the occasional poignant statement at @artcity    
    
    
    Completely overwhelmed by all the birthday wishes. Thank you! What I want: a new governor. Here's hoping my birthday wish comes true!    
    
    
    I suppose I knew this was coming, but was hoping it wouldn't. America / WI: things are going to get way worse. And you voted for it. Sigh.    
    
    
    @wugmump why do you hate me?    
    
    
    Scary yet understandable how many colleagues + teachers have mentioned being back on the job market in the last 12 hours. #wisconsin    
    
    
    i love #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Awesome day with @wugmump + family at Figment, going back to Gov Island again to see Jill LaRocco Buckley-Jones & Jessica Findley today.    
    
    
    Just a li'l 3-miler around some Greenbelt on the Shaolin this morning. Off to gallery hop, perhaps hooking up w Chris Ulivo or Paddy Johnson    
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost #MKEmake ? #outofthepicture ? #artWri ? #VidArt ? #iDunno ...    
    
    
    me, too RT @charlottefrost: @artcity @nathanielstern I like #arthussle & #MKEmake BTW xxx    
    
    
    Great day in NYC! Tom Sachs at Creative Time, Talent at Marianne Boesky, Diane Victor at David Krut, Eyebeam, Foxy, Winkleman, Bitforms.    
    
    
    Daughter, Daddy, Grandma day: hair cuts, father's day gifts, Chuck E Cheese and The Avengers. Plus, lunch.    
    
    
    False advertising: Research is not driven "by small teams of plucky entrepreneurs [but] giant bureaucratic projects." http://bit.ly/K1LWLY     
    
    
    mod: Corporate bureaucrats use the pretext of short-term, bottom-line thinking to squelch anything revolutionary http://bit.ly/K1Nzcl     
    
    
    Rhizome members: Tweets in Space is a finalist for a commission. Please consider ranking us number 1 on the site: http://bit.ly/LJJvTj     
    
    
    I love it when old friends you were in ska-punk bands with in high school turn up, + turn out to be awesome artists. http://bit.ly/OH8gOE     
    
    
    I bet it will, @ChrisButzen #tweetsinspace - also, #ChasingUFOs    
    
    
    funny how in MKE it's a given that you grill with wood, or maybe coal. on staten island, it's impressive. Milwaukee: 1, Shaolin: 0.    
    
    
    Despite the lack of regime change (read: Scott Walker), looking forward to being back in MKE tomorrow. Lighthouse Run on Sat. should be fun!    
    
    
    My car + this Summer are CURSED! After Nicole was rear-ended a few weeks ago, now I bashed a PARKED CAR. I'm so upset w myself right now.    
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost this week: installation 4 Aus, ISEA 13 + CAA 14 proposals, Tweets funding+transmission plan, an etching #arthustle    
    
    
    Drafts for ISEA 2013 + CAA 2014 done, + a sketch 4 my etching. Will take time to complete, but may add review 2 my week's sched. #arthustle    
    
    
    2 draft proposals, press release, twitter ware work + lots of soldering today. #arthustle    
    
    
    Kevin Smith + Jen Schwalback make fun of us on their show "SMorning Show + Tell #4: Rocket Schwience" http://youtu.be/dPecc7QVzU4  #awesome    
    
    
    Tweets in Space partners with National Geographic http://bit.ly/L0yibD     
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost been up since 5 doing admin for Tweets + British bureaucrats at PSi. Sometimes I hate contemporary life. #arthustle    
    
    
    5 days left to reach new $5700 goal + send #tweetsinspace ($2365 to go). Partners include ISEA+NatGeo. Please donate!  http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Dealt w customs 4 Spanish art exhibit, insurance 4 UK art, gonna cross-train + work on a tenure review b4 meeting with A Basting. #arthustle    
    
    
    If every one of my Twitter followers donated just $5, we'd be done. http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Tweeeeeets in Spaaaaaace! Only 4 days left and we need $2251 to reach our new goal - every bit helps!  http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    In print today!  MT @artcity @kildall Love the article about the Tweets in Space Race w/ us + @natgeo #tweetsinspace http://ht.ly/bHWIy     
    
    
    Only 3 days left and about $2K to go! You know you want to help. Go on then. Tweeeeets iiiiiin Spaaaaaaace! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    2day + tomorrow only!  NatGeo licensing will help, but we're still working at a loss. Please consider a small donation! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    I will never work with @flyfrontier (Frontier Airlines) again. Least helpful bunch of prigs in the Universe. Avoid at all costs. #frontier    
    
    
    Nat Geo money came through! 85% there and less than 2 days left. Pls donate to #tweetsinspace ! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Friends: 38 hours and 13% to go for funding Tweets in Space. Please oh please make a weekend donation! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    Final push: 95% funded with 23 hours to go! If you are reading this, pls consider a small donation! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    19 hours and stil at 95% - c'mon Interwebs, don't you wanna space travel? Your patronage is appreciated! Do it, do it! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    15 hours and at 97%!!! Friends, almost there, today's the day, last chance to help out! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    We're funded! Transmission, software + servers covered. 14 hrs left 2 help w equipment, shipping, admin, flights + food http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    @artcity awesome! Mostly finishing up TiS fund stuff, getting ready for Leeds, planning a busy July. Get together when I am back? #arthustle    
    
    
    8 hours left to contribute - we appreciate all your support! http://rkthb.co/7291     
    
    
    in the blog: Call for participation – Sentimental Constructions: an ethico-aesthetics of collaboration http://nathanielstern.com/blog/2012/06/25/call-for-participation-%e2%80%93-sentimental-constructions-an-ethico-aesthetics-of-collaboration/ …    
    
    
    PUBLIC ART CALL FOR PARTICIPATION IN THE UK (Leeds) - THIS WEEK!!! http://bit.ly/MPSl0B     
    
    
    I've landed in Leeds! (well, landed in Manchester and then took a train to Leeds, technically.) Fish + Chips tonight, PSi thereafter.    
    
    
    Totally exhausted in Leeds, but really glad to see some of my fellow Sense Labbers! More to come...    
    
    
    @rgrusin rethinks mediation + breathing with Erin Manning's installation "Stitching Time" at 18th Biennale of Sydney http://bit.ly/MwsoPF     
    
    
    Bad but good, odd + lovely - definitely an interesting morning of public art in Leeds. Pix, vids + stories soon! #sentimentalconstructions    
    
    
    Bill Maher to Mitt Romney: "Let me help you move America forward, into the past." http://bit.ly/KM6jx8     
    
    
    Congrats to grad student Bryan Cera, for a first place in the instructables "Make it Real Challenge" w/ an MA project! http://bit.ly/NxmGxs     
    
    
    Leeds work online http://bit.ly/Nxpw5P  ; interview with OLB live http://bit.ly/NxpD0Z  ; inbox nearly empty; workin on book. #arthustle    
    
    
    News from the Noniesphere! http://nerdtobe.net/2012/07/04/june-2012/ …    
    
    
    4th of July Haiku: To hot to braai, on / fourth of July. I intend / to roast a chicken.    
    
    
    Bill Moyers on the rich getting richer @Upworthy. http://www.upworthy.com/why-america-where-only-the-rich-get-richer-is-not-a-democracy?g=2 …    
    
    
    My interview with Lane Hall of Wisconsin's Overpass Light Brigade @furtherfield http://bit.ly/NxpD0Z     
    
    
    I just backed Expanding Eyebeam's Public Presence in Chelsea on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/KZJf1N     
    
    
    Lovely day mostly spent making art and catching up with Jessica Meuninck-Ganger. And now: BEER!    
    
    
    @ilona_andrews I get it.    
    
    
    I'm late coming to the party - geek cred plummeting! - but OMG @feliciaday is prob one of the coolest people ever. Lots of vids to watch!    
    
    
    Printmaking, writing, drawing, email, proposals, videos, editing, interviews, tenure reviews, electronics, patches, + stuff - #arthustle    
    
    
    in the blog:  Scaling Creative Solutions in Educational Leadership http://nathanielstern.com/blog/2012/07/09/scaling-creative-solutions-in-educational-leadership/ …    
    
    
    Super fun day with my assistants in the studio! #arthustle    
    
    
    "What would happen if you hit a baseball pitched @ 90% speed of light?" Didn't think it possible, but XKCD got COOLER - http://bit.ly/L5Cacf     
    
    
    #arthustle    
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost I intend to keep up the #arthustle craziness thru Aug10. Big plans, then a few days off before UWM contracts start.    
    
    
    "imagine for a moment...what news," or the country for that matter, "might be like if it were more like Sorkin's idea" http://bit.ly/Mntgrn     
    
    
    @artcity totally agree re:monologue. also thought of our conversations in ep 3: "great journalists lost in the noise." wish it were real 2.    
    
    
    Today: drawing for Dynamic Stasis (South Africa show) + Tweets in Space (TiS), audio + animations for TiS, some reading + writing #arthustle    
    
    
    Been spending some time with the work of @leewalton today. Lovely, really smart stuff! http://www.leewalton.com/     
    
    
    I've begun running w/ the Badgerland Striders: 6 miles 2 wks ago, + 2 mile increases every week, steady 10ish minute pace. Today: 10 miles.    
    
    
    Totally daddy geek moment: me and the kid watching Iron Man 2 in the lounge, while firing up the grill on the balcony. Teh Awesome.    
    
    
    Jessica + I are artists in residence on the Gallery AOP site for the next few months, while prepping for our next show. http://bit.ly/Nchp4A     
    
    
    Join me at ISEA2012 for Tweets in Space | Albuquerque, New Mexico! https://www.regonline.com/ISEA2012  #ISEA2012 | Powered by #RegOnline #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Residency blog, email supporters, inbox: done. To do: flatten paper, print plate 1 of woodblock, finish most of Chapter 1 edits. #arthustle    
    
    
    It's 6:30? Crap, I totally overslept....    
    
    
    It's hot. Missed my run today. Kinda tired. Studio is empty. Time for a Chai? Yeh; Chai, then book editing. #arthustle    
    
    
    @charlottefrost Cheers!    
    
    
    Contrary to nobody's belief, writing and editing an academic book is not the easiest thing ever. #arthustle    
    
    
    Best + funniest book review I've read in a long time. Complete w/ animated GIFs! : Katrina Lumsden on 50 Shades of Grey http://bit.ly/KVtXMl     
    
    
    @cynthialawson Thanks 4 link! Synchronicity: your name came up @ meeting yesterday about great people doing interesting community/media art!    
    
    
    The 1:45 Clip That Cuts Through The Bullsh*t About Romney's Time At Bain http://www.moveon.org/share/45374c     
    
    
    More in-process shots for my + Jessica Meuninck-Ganger's upcoming GALLERY AOP show, Dynamic Stasis (January in Joburg)! http://bit.ly/O1lSH4     
    
    
    I don't care if the reviews are mostly bad, and some of the characters often annoy me (I often annoy myself, after all). I love The Newsroom    
    
    
    Cool documentation of my collaborative sound project with a grad student + some friends. http://bit.ly/MOoIMG  Tech help h/t to @coinop29    
    
    
    MT @artcity: Looking forward to #galnite w @nathanielstern. Start in the Third Ward, then to Dean Jensen then to Inova! Where are U headed?    
    
    
    Trip to zoo interrupted by kid's illness. Instead watched 1977 Freaky Friday, Up + new Smurfs, built tents + made shadow puppets. Now: BBQ    
    
    
    Finally got to reading @juspar interview - his thoughts on the academy, time, and new thinking are especially brilliant http://bit.ly/NsmjI9     
    
    
    Off for my 30-ish hour editing retreat: no matter what, my book goes off to my editor/publisher tomorrow at 5 pm. Wish me luck! #arthustle    
    
    
    Just the online/companion chapter to go, then details like TOC + biblio before send-off. That's a pretty good book I just wrote! #arthustle    
    
    
    BOOK = DONE.  w000000000000t! http://implicitbody.net/  #arthustle    
    
    
    PS multiple 0s in w00t means repeating "own." We own own own own OWN (etc) the Other Team. @charlottefrost @artcity    
    
    
    My body knows the book is done, and wants me to sleep. Sore throat and headache. Should not have made plans today. Meh.    
    
    
    Today was meant to be my first 14-miler as part of marathon training, but my knee told me to shove it around 12. Limping + in much pain :(    
    
    
    Join me in helping make it happen for Send Students to Prospectives '12 Festival! on @indiegogo http://igg.me/p/191592?a=982740&i=twtr …    
    
    
    omfg facebook web site is DOWN from my side!!! I think I'm going to OUTSIDE!    
    
    
    Not the morning I was hoping for or expecting. MONDAYS. Meh. Here's hoping the rest of the day is better and more productive. #arthustle    
    
    
    After my knee injury on Saturday, taking one more day off running. Will cross-train. Maybe do pool running or sumtin later. Not giving up!    
    
    
    Trying to imagine Joburg in the snow. Friends: post photos! #johannesburgcalling    
    
    
    MT @charlottefrost: The last paragraphs of @nathanielstern 's forthcoming book I'm editing make me tearful! #spoileralert #embodiedemotion    
    
    
    MT @artcity: Wow @charlottefrost how often does an academic book make one tearful? Leave it to @nathanielstern. Can't wait! #arthustle    
    
    
    Maybe hanging my projector from the air vent wasn't the best idea, but I didn't have any other options, really. And it only moves a _little_    
    
    
    @juspar I like analogous art :)    
    
    
    Michigan Stats Suggest Every $1 Invested in the Arts Yields $51 for Economy, http://bit.ly/RuS4CJ  #arthustle - via @hyperallergic    
    
    
    Lovely day with my daughter and @artcity yesterday: brunch, the zoo, and more!    
    
    
    OK, it's a catch-up day. Gonna do syllabi, lectures, clean studio, update website, back up laptop, install new OS and apps, etc. #arthustle    
    
    
    More than 24 hrs later, we found Jack (our cat) prowling around the front of the house, meowing for help. Dehydrated + shaken, happy 2B home    
    
    
    How can I fall so far behind on "work," when my contract hasn't even started yet? #contemporarylife    
    
    
    just got Nicole a half case of fine wine.... Checkout | Lot18 http://shar.es/7WLTb  via @sharethis    
    
    
        
    
    
    We all jump, and we all die. Hahahaha. http://what-if.xkcd.com/8/     
    
    
    Wasn't looking forward all-day meeting kicking of the school year; but hey, I have great colleagues. Was nice :) #uwm #psoa #art+design    
    
    
    I just had my SECOND bicycle stolen on UWM campus within one month - WITH the lock. I take back what I said about a nice day. GRRRRR!    
    
    
    @artcity Glad you like! No worries. Will email...    
    
    
    My ongoing, virtual artist in residence at Gallery AOP! http://galleryaop.com/view.asp?pg=residence …    
    
    
    Treman Park! Ithaca NY! Hiking, weddings, pretty things! Yay!    
    
    
    Nauseous in Detroit, but pretty sure it's lack of sleep, dehydration and plane / motion sickness rather than anything inherent to the city.    
    
    
    My new bicycle lasted 4 days before it, too, was stolen. That is 3 stolen bikes (with locks!) in less than 3 weeks. #angry    
    
    
    Sad strategy worth embracing: "don't lead with the facts... lead with the values - [to] give facts a fighting chance" http://bit.ly/MBWMsk     
    
    
    Just finished The Newsroom. I want Aaron Sorkin to run a REAL newsroom, please. But hey, at least it's good television. #fourthbranch    
    
    
    friends: please tweet using the #tweetsinspace for the next 10 minutes: we are testing our various wares. Thanks!!!! Tweeting to aliens soon    
    
    
    lalalalalala #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    having a minor timestamp issue. #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    thanks everybody - everything is just about ready for #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    testing the control center #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    almost there #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    oooh, this looks nice #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    oh hi @chrisbutzen - we are on the same web site! #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @ChrisButzen can't test that one double-tweet issue, as I am already logged in ( @kildall ?), but everything else is grand. #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace. weird @ChrisButzen I am trying to say @kildall - kildall - and it said you again... #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    again... may want to look into that. only one mention allowed maybe? #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    dinnertime with "my girls" - lemme know if you need more help later #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    scott @kildall + @nathanielstern will talk #tweetsinspace LIVE on WI Public Radio, 3-4 PM CST today. Call or email in! http://wpr.org/merens     
    
    
    #tweetsinspace did you miss the @kildall + @nathanielstern WPR interview? Check it here: http://bit.ly/12oalP  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace makes @techdirt : "Tweets... In... Space...." http://bit.ly/QESWoc     
    
    
    What is this "Internet" you speak of? #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    I NOW DECLARE #TWEETSINSPACE !!!!!    
    
    
    jessica says, i <3 #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    The world thought it would never happen, but Nicole and I are finally upgrading to Smart Phones next week. #iPhone5    
    
    
    Friday Sept 21, 8:30-9 PM MT, add #tweetsinspace to your tweets + they will beamed towards GJ667Cc: an exoplanet that might support life!    
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/phK2L  send your tweets in space!  Sept 21 8:30 PM Mountain time, beam messages to GJ667Cc #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Marc Garrett interviews @kildall and @nathanielstern on @furtherfield. It's a good read! http://www.furtherfield.org/features/interviews/tweets-space-interview-scott-kildall-and-nathaniel-stern … #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    OMG it's time for bed already! Sooooo tired. Good night New Mexico. Good night world. Good night GJ667Cc. #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @artcity @ktondryk rumor has it that the GJians (pronounced gee-JAY-jee-ans) like beverages. just sayin. #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @ktondryk @artcity while I'm with Kim on the name + vibe of Comet, the view from Blu / Pfister might be calling me. #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Thanks for the tweets, and for being there, @cynthialawson ! Looking forward to catching up tonight, as well as your visit in the Spring.    
    
    
    Fri, Sep 21, 9:30-10PM CST, add #tweetsinspace to send texts to an exoplanet that might support biological life: http://ow.ly/dMWVT     
    
    
    @artcity having a drink with Robert Drummond (finalist for public art in MKE) and we're both gushing over you, in New Mexico.    
    
    
    @darrylhebbes Because.    
    
    
    @caleb_scharf writes about #tweetsinspace in Scientific American (again) today! Pls participate. http://bit.ly/UmIO1Y  #SciAmBlogs    
    
    
    @ChrisButzen @kildall pick you up in 30.    
    
    
    @artcity writes another really smart article on #tweetsinspace - pls participate tonight! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/170676896.html …    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace makes Wired! They cast doubt on our transmission science, but get the art is "an introspective exercise" http://bit.ly/P6j8Wm     
    
    
    Just a little discussion on I @#$%! love science's facebook page… https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=476031569084526&set=a.456449604376056.98921.367116489976035&type=1 …    
    
    
    I have a feeling my life will be pretty different about 5 hours and 44 minutes from now. #tweetsinspace http://tweetaliens.org/tweets/tweets.php …    
    
    
    and now, the Washington Post. #tweetsinspace http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/compost/post/friday-night-twitter-destroys-the-earth/2012/09/21/027a9f90-0434-11e2-8102-ebee9c66e190_blog.html …    
    
    
    my daughter says, "aliens, you're weird" #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace - Everything is a go! We've got the database collecting, live control panel, + real-time animated performance for #ISEA2012    
    
    
    Tweeeeeets iiiiiiiin spaaaaaaaace!!!!! It works, it's alive! #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    How do you love? #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    Wait come back! We're actually really cool!  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @_MoJuju_ great question. Send sunset photos!!  #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    @sethandrewjacob yes. Let's go bowling.    
    
    
    Thanks everyone for an AMAZING #tweetsinspace performance at #ISEA2012 .. Images + transmision updates on our site soon http://tweetsinspace.org     
    
    
    It's always been about us. Also, 10 Pieces of Advice for Artists From Jerry Saltz: http://blogs.artinfo.com/artintheair/2012/09/21/10-pieces-of-advice-for-artists-from-jerry-saltzs-keynote-speech-at-expo-chicago/ … #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    If anyone got decent video of #tweetsinspace at #ISEA2012 last night, + doesn't mind being part of our documentation, pls contact us. Ta!    
    
    
    @WilliamBeutler Thanks, great! @wiredscience seems to get the work is "an introspective exercise," but not their role in it… #tweetsinspace    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace received approximately 1 tweet per second for the duration of our 30 min performance. Prep for transmission begins next week!    
    
    
    New Mexico, I miss you already. #tweetsinspace #ISEA2012    
    
    
    Tweetbot.    
    
    
    Hangin in my studio with Oron Catts. So cool. #bioart    
    
    
    @artcity you're here! come to sushi after?    
    
    
    @artcity yeh, i figured it out a bit later. amazing talk. you should try to make it tomorrow.    
    
    
    I really need a day off. Soon.    
    
    
    At photo sheet with Ilya Avdeev. Too much make up!    
    
    
    Hanging out in studios    
    
    
    #SLSA2012 conference off to great start. Oron Catts blew my mind.    
    
    
    Hanging out with Patrick Lichty. What a great day!    
    
    
    My wife's cool    
    
    
    Do most cats love pistachio nuts, or is it just my weirdos?    
    
    
    Using Siri to retweet while playing tag at the park. I think I love the iPhone five    
    
    
    Almost ready for transmission. #TweetsInSpace    
    
    
    Jessica MG and I just confirmed most of our new South African / Gallery AOP show for the Lynden Gallery in Milwaukee in the new year!    
    
    
    @cynthialawson actually, yeh, it'll be up while you are here!    
    
    
    Not so ready to face the week    
    
    
    I think I can. I think I can!    
    
    
    @alyxpryn yeh, interesting stuff going on - but alone w/ Nonie for weekend + so unable to attend much. I need to hear about OOF: is it real?    
    
    
    With Jessica. Going to get a crate to ship our art to South Africa.    
    
    
    @alyxpryn @the_eco_thought listening now…    
    
    
    @alyxpryn I first want to get to yours :)    
    
    
    @alyxpryn going offline to dsicuss with you - glad to be in touch!    
    
    
    Never make your drive case-sensitive!    
    
    
    Everything takes forever. Seriously.    
    
    
    Having trouble concentrating today. Also, the paint doesn't match    
    
    
    Re-reading Mark BN Hansen's paper on Bill Viola. Really good. #NewMediaArt    
    
    
    Wait, where did my morning go?    
    
    
    Art City - Experts gather to show off their views of art - can wait to see all of this new feature with @artcity !!! http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/arts/experts-gather-to-show-off-their-views-of-art-qt6vn80-171934171.html …    
    
    
    @WilliamBeutler @kildall @cynthialawson @artcity I am now reading every single #tweetsinspace ... + getting really emotional. Quite magical    
    
    
    Gorgeous #interactiveart at the Barbican - h/t Ed Cooper. About movement, sensation + yr relation with the environment. http://www.dezeen.com/2012/10/04/rain-room-by-random-international-at-the-barbican/ …    
    
    
    Yevgenyiya Kaganovich's new show is totally awesome! #ecobagartthings    
    
    
    With @artcity    
    
    
    My work with Jessica, getting ready for shipment to GALLERY AOP in South Africa! http://galleryaop.com/view.asp?ItemID=16&tname=tblComponent4&oname=Artists+in+Residence&pg=front …    
    
    
    Flu shot yesterday. Nausea today. Meh.    
    
    
    At the movies with my girls    
    
    
    Culvers or Kopps?    
    
    
    Me 2- great! MT @juspar: Saw proofs for chapter "The Primacy of Movement: Variation, Intermediality and Biopolitics in Tero Saarinen’s Hunt"    
    
    
    Batteries can be annoying.    
    
    
    Roller coasters are good    
    
    
    _Almost_ caught up after New Mexico + SLSA stuff, leave for Montreal on Monday, 1 wk catch up again, then off to San Fransisco. #artistlife    
    
    
    The Romney strategy explained by The Onion. It's funny cuz it's true.  http://www.theonion.com/articles/romney-proudly-explains-how-hes-turned-campaign-ar,29845/?utm_source=Facebook&utm_medium=SocialMarketing&utm_campaign=standard-post:quote:default …    
    
    
    I couldn't disagree more. #noIwillNotTellYouWhatIamTalkingAbout    
    
    
    Awake and tired. Meh.    
    
    
    Montreal countdown: 4 days. Looking forward to seeing my peeps at the Sense Lab!    
    
    
    super fun UWM art event for new Art+Design undergrads today #artathon    
    
    
    Art is good.    
    
    
    Between piano and dance class: chicken and jazz hands. pic.twitter.com/Jgpuijhd    
    
    
    A detail from the gorgeous Rory Donaldson piece I bought for Nicole's birthday - hanging in our flat. pic.twitter.com/ka2rQeZk    
    
    
    Nonie posed me like Tigress to take our photo. At the animation studio in the Milwaukee Art Museum. pic.twitter.com/DtmlgVVa    
    
    
    Montreal, here I come.    
    
    
    At the airport. Giving written feedback on grad student papers. On my way to work with awesome people. Alright then.    
    
    
    It seems media theorists tend to write good art catalog essays. Or at least this 1 in MKE does. I suppose it's not necessarily all of them.    
    
    
    What an amazing privilege to work with such an astonishingly smart and generous group of people. Thank you, world. Thank you, Sense Lab.    
    
    
    The Sense Lab!!! I heart these folks. pic.twitter.com/BVqHxgY0    
    
    
    I don't want to leave! #senselab #montreal    
    
    
    Education as it should be, and it WORKS. Gov't / admin, pls pay attention! http://bit.ly/PNR0vO  h/t / RT @andrewmurphie and @mazpow    
    
    
    @THE_skrauss ah, ya know?    
    
    
    Halloween + magic! pic.twitter.com/Fvrj9rUK    
    
    
    In line to vote early! Wisconsin Milwaukee    
    
    
    @wugmump you ok, buddy?    
    
    
    @artcity Fabulous cafeteria? I know you were right next to me, but maybe we weren't eating at the same place… :) GREAT to see you!    
    
    
    @artcity next time, I choose the joint. … ... It may be around the corner, and involve Irish Coffee and brats.    
    
    
    Morning has thus far seen: NCIIA proposal, grad student texts, driving the kid to school, infrared light setup, email. It's only 10. Go me!    
    
    
    Tweetpiphany of the day: autotune = cowbell. More autotune! http://www.funnyordie.com/videos/80a71ef8cb/more-cowbell …    
    
    
    Heading to San Francisco for "Determining Domain" exhibition at Intersection for the Arts, opening Nov 7 with Wiki Art! http://theintersection.org/2012/10/determining-domain/ …    
    
    
    Having a few drinks with my good friend @kildall in the mission, SF. Good times.    
    
    
    What Is the Labor of Art Writing? (Part 2) http://hyperallergic.com/59651/what-is-the-labor-of-art-writing-part-2/ … via @hyperallergic @powhida    
    
    
    Nico the tuxedo cat! Soon to be featured in a Tweets in Space video... w @kildall pic.twitter.com/e864QLec    
    
    
    Install at Intersection, SF pic.twitter.com/CuDMf2tb    
    
    
    Mini ITP reunion + 1!!! pic.twitter.com/tOVDnHzV    
    
    
    Super fun discussion about my work at the exploratorium here in San Francisco! Thanks to the attending crowd...    
    
    
    Term 2. We’ve got Tammy Baldwin and Elizabeth Warren in the Senate, Alan Grayson in the House (pun intended). Let’s get some work done!!!    
    
    
    Probably should have checked if SF MoMA was open before heading over. Ah well, I still get to see art at alt venues tonight!    
    
    
    @mmasnick good to see you old friend! You are doing great things. Oh, + if you hit the EFF event, tell them thanks again from @wikipedia_art    
    
    
    Hey @artcity - you are on another exhibition! At Intersection for the Arts. pic.twitter.com/Emw4xIvF    
    
    
    6.42 miles at around a 9:05 pace (10 min first mile, increasing all along), with Maurice Dumit. Then a great brunch with Josie Osborne.    
    
    
    AWESOME. RT @ilona_andrews: Okay, I would so totally watch this.  http://youtu.be/07s-cNFffDM     
    
    
    Totally emo the last few days. Need to chill. Breathe, Nathaniel.    
    
    
    I think I need a "no inbox after 7pm" rule. I can still work if I need to, but no inbox. Thoughts?    
    
    
    Day 1 of “no inbox after 7 PM.”  I must resist! #noinboxpost7    
    
    
    Somehow threw my back out while sleeping.  Now awake and in pain. Ouch.    
    
    
    4 am awakeness. meh.    
    
    
    Intended to do "4 easy miles" with Maurice Dumit (my physio, and friend), wound up being my fastest 10K yet. 6.52 miles, 8:23 pace.    
    
    
    Looking for completely transparent but fibrous paper (or something to draw on). Must be see-through at a distance - on a window. Thoughts?    
    
    
    So, there's this book I wrote. And it comes out next year, probably in April. Pretty cool. http://implicitbody.net     
    
    
    @artcity on it    
    
    
    @myszkalewis silk organza wins!    
    
    
    Things are happening. And while that may seem tautological, that's because it is.    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/kZW87F9l    
    
    
    There's so much. Happy and sad, scared and alive, anxious and gleeful, generous and spiteful, loved and loving. I'm thankful for all of it.    
    
    
    Nothing like the hospital on Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    At Art versus craft, Milwaukee    
    
    
    In response to Facebook I use the Internet more. But mostly Twitter as of late. Just sayin.    
    
    
    I finally got to reading Ruth Leys' critique of affect. It is at best a complete misreading, and at worst (cont) http://tl.gd/k5gb1p     
    
    
    I should have read Non-representational Theory long ago. Thank you, Nigel Thrift.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The planets are aligned! #tweetsinspace are currently being beamed into space!!!!    
    
    
    #asgoesjanesville yeeeeeeeh!!!!    
    
    
    #asgoesjanesville feel like crying. And also punching someone.    
    
    
    #asgoesjanesville Amazing film.    
    
    
    My daughter is reading me a story on the way to school    
    
    
    UWM alum and Milwaukee native Michelle Grabner named one of the curators for the Whitney Biennial!!! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/181440891.html …    
    
    
    You know those days that you should just stay home? You should avoid Internet and email conversations on those days too. #selfadviceneeded    
    
    
    10k. Much slower this time. But it's still 10k.    
    
    
    Just finished the new Dresden book. Holy crow! DID NOT expect THAT! Awesome.    
    
    
    Whiskey and bourbon and burgers with @rgrusin. Life is good.    
    
    
    First ever Pilates class. Gurgle.    
    
    
    Back 2 back intensive meetings since 8AM. All I've ingested - besides university policy + art criticism - is coffee + a cookie. Still going.    
    
    
    Beer makes everything at least a little bit better    
    
    
    Congratulations to the totally awesome work of UWM Design students (and Faculty!) at their show last night on Grand Avenue. Well done!    
    
    
    Not gonna be ready to leave in 2 weeks! & my "work-holiday" is really "work-while-away." Sigh. At least there's art + old friends in Joburg.    
    
    
    So glad not to be in Miami. Really. #artfairs    
    
    
    Ready for bed. I'm going out.    
    
    
    Our GALLERY AOP online residency concludes with a catalog by @rgrusin - Joburg show with Meuninck-Ganger opens 26 Jan! http://galleryaop.com/view.asp?ItemID=17&tname=tblComponent4&oname=Artists%20in%20Residence&pg=front …    
    
    
    Officially a Fulbright grantee: "specialist" program is funding a series of my arts/research workshops @ University of Johannesburg, Jan '13    
    
    
    Sick in bed, skipping whole day - 4 events. But also online, playing with OF interactive art Kinect hacks, new Wordpress site hacks + more.    
    
    
    New site with Jessica is live! New work for South Africa + Milwaukee, older work archived as hi-res images + videos. …http://jessicameuninckganger.nathanielstern.com     
    
    
    Did I mention that my amazing wife landed herself a Humanities Doctoral Fellowship at the University of the Western Cape? Doing @ a distance    
    
    
    I will be in South Africa 1 week from today. Looking forward to seeing old friends and family! (… between workshops + the exhibition...)    
    
    
    Just pre-ordered Erin Manning's new book, which looks amazing! "Always More Than One: Individuation's Dance" http://www.amazon.com/Always-More-Than-One-Individuations/dp/0822353342/ref=sr_1_4?ie=UTF8&qid=1356223766&sr=8-4&keywords=erin+manning …    
    
    
    24 ounces if Xmas!!! pic.twitter.com/mPcP3RoS    
    
    
    Johannesburg, Cape Town: here I come. Looking forward to catching up! You bring the wine, I'll bring some cheer. See you in a bit, then.    
    
    
    Ah, Joburg, I missed ya! So lovely to be among old friends, new friends, outside in Summer. Thank goodness for braais!    
    
    
    Wow, @artcity did not hold back on 2012 in review. It's a must read, the whole thing. http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/185065711.html …    
    
    
    Sadly, most Cape Town galleries are closed while I'm here, but I'll hit a couple. Looking forward to the exhibits in Joburg next week!    
    
    
    Nice interview w/ @kildall and me, organized and edited by Eva Kekou on @4Hum. Good blend of art/theory and fluff! http://4humanities.org/2013/01/interview-with-scott-kildall-and-nathaniel-stern/ …    
    
    
    My daughter is growing up bilingual. Her American side understands sarcasm, and her South African side gets irony.    
    
    
    Playing w/ PHP (new site), C++ (kinect hack), CV (needs update) + Nonie (my kid) in Cape Town. Nice holiday #aGeekyArtsAcademicInSouthAfrica    
    
    
    OK, Joburg. Prepare yourself. We'll be there later today. #exhibition #fulbright #family+friends #yayArt    
    
    
    10K run around Rosebank - Johannesburg, South Africa. #welcomehome    
    
    
    Heading to @UJ_FADA (University of Johannesburg, Faculty of Art, Design + Architecture), to prep for my Fulbright workshops on #artswriting    
    
    
    @artcity is being modest. No doubt she + her peeps played a role in MKE being named one of America's top 12 art cities. http://ht.ly/gBn3o     
    
    
    Sad news, lovely obit. Colin Richards: brilliant thinker + artist, whose influence resonates throughout Southern Africa http://www.timeslive.co.za/sundaytimes/2013/01/06/obituary-colin-richards---fine-artist-and-academic …    
    
    
    My first ever #spin class without @kildall - I pretended he was there, though, to keep me motivated! #johannesburg    
    
    
    Getting invites and catalog ready for show at GALLERY AOP. Looking forward! …http://jessicameuninckganger.nathanielstern.com/dynamic-stasis/  #johannesburg    
    
    
    @artcity pens a beautiful introduction into the intense and interesting work of Tyanna J. Buie #milwaukeeart http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/186421711.html#!page=1&pageSize=10&sort=newestfirst …    
    
    
    Very proud to be on the editorial board of the now-live, peer-reviewed, interdisciplinary theory/practice journal, http://www.moebiusjournal.org     
    
    
    Just finished my first day giving workshops at @UJ_FADA - intense, but I believe very helpful + productive, if response is any indication    
    
    
    Day 2 of my Fulbright workshops at @UJ_FADA - academic writing + publishing, subsidies + trajectories, for artists + designers #needWeekend    
    
    
    A grad student from last semester on Fox. Skrauss does a great job, + they captured his essence pretty well. Congrats! http://fox6now.com/2013/01/17/artist-responsible-for-unique-riverwalk-sculpture-explains-art/ …    
    
    
    Finally, a half-day off! I think I'll go here: http://www.safarinow.com/destinations/roodepoort/naturereserves.aspx …    
    
    
    Show opening this Saturday at 2PM, with talk at 2:30. Hanging today - looking great in the space, catalog also fab!!! http://us1.campaign-archive1.com/?u=f51a68dd625e9d4ae3f40a67a&id=6b602f4372&e=2228d57627 …    
    
    
    Blown away by my visit to #artistproofstudio in Joburg today. Amazing history, amazing work, fantastic community. http://www.artinamericamagazine.com/news-opinion/finer-things/2012-07-01/south-africa-print-studio/ …    
    
    
    Botanical Gardens w/ Jessica Meuninck-Ganger, several art openings (nice one, #Stevenson), drinks + dinner with Gordon Froud + Diane Victor    
    
    
    Very proud of my Student Startup Challenge students, and of the work we've been doing together at @uwm http://youtu.be/2WcdB_OBxrk     
    
    
    Our opening at GALLERY AOP was just lovely... Thank you so much to those who attended, gave feedback, and bought work! #joburgart    
    
    
    Atlanta airport. #HomewardBound    
    
    
    Jetlag. Awake at 3. Maybe I can empty my inbox and try to get some paperwork done?… I'd rather be sleeping, reading, eating....    
    
    
    I believed everyone, but I'm still boggled at how easy the #kinect makes interactive/CV art with #openFrameworks. #updatingEverythingNow #OF    
    
    
    Thinking positive: #jetlag means more time to play with #openFrameworks    
    
    
    Does anyone know when the Mac OSX #openFrameworks will work in 10.8 without 10.6 quicktime dependencies? I tire of rebooting… #OF    
    
    
    @angus_davidson sadly, the 64-bit OF does not work with video and the 10.6 sdk breaks with the most recent versions of Xcode + OSX!    
    
    
    Up at 4:30 AM. Better than 3, like the last few days. And I can prepare my class. But man, it's cold here! #needCoffee    
    
    
    @angus_davidson yeh, worked for Xcode 4.4, not 4.5. And a few other things work very differently, so had to go back + forth. Not worth it!    
    
    
    Did anyone out there get nice video of #tweetsinspace in New Mexico? we're mixing down a new vid, + could really use performance footage!    
    
    
    Pure Nonie. H/T Jim Charles pic.twitter.com/zzOxGvik    
    
    
    @angus_davidson yeh, I got copying the sdk etc working with 4.4, then with the upgrade to 4.5, no more. one more downgrade was the straw...    
    
    
    It's really, really, really cold (and snowy) out there. Did I mention I miss South Africa sometimes? #Milwaukee    
    
    
    Nice day gallery hopping in #MKE w/ @artcity … Highlights were Watts high tea, and Tory Folliard show, Color. Feature: http://toryfolliard.com/artists/derrick-buisch/ …    
    
    
    Photo shoot for @MMagazineMke at @lyndensculpture garden today. Show looking good + I'm looking forward to the "artists to watch" feature!    
    
    
    Feverishly working on new web site; want it up before #CAA. Then, the "real work" of my Jun-Aug exhibition in South Africa! #interactiveart    
    
    
    As a young parent, this may be one of my favorite XKCDs ever. http://xkcd.com/1170/     
    
    
    Very proud to announce my brand new web site! http://nathanielstern.com     
    
    
    Artists + printmakers: Mar 20 - 23, I'll be at SGCI, Peck School of the Arts + MIAD! Learn more / register at Print Mke http://printmke2013.org/registration/     
    
    
    Live install of "surfacing" across a dozen windows, w/ Jessica Meuninck-Ganger @ Lynden Sculpture Garden #distillLife pic.twitter.com/hJJUwReo    
    
    
    Dang! Moving Wordpress sites means redirects are different, of course. Sorry if a few external links didn't work over weekend. All fixed!    
    
    
    New participatory + dynamic #print installation with Jessica Meuninck-Ganger at @lyndensculpture http://nathanielstern.com/artwork/surfacing/ … #distillLife #drawing    
    
    
    On my way to #NYC for #CAA panel on networked + mixed reality art, a talk @ Bloomfield, looking at art, sleep catch-up (fingers crossed)...    
    
    
    Hello Staten Island. … … … OK now what? … I know I used to have fun here sometimes! #CAA #NYC    
    
    
    zombie apocalypse love story. empty theatre. Staten Island on Valentine's Day. #seriouslyLoveThis #shouldBeWorking #warmbodies    
    
    
    I'm on the free+open #CAA2013 panel, "Pieces + Bits," 9:30-12 TODAY, Murray Hills Suite, 2nd floor Hilton. On Internet + Physical hybrid art    
    
    
    Some of the audience at our #caa2013 hybrid / Internet art panel... pic.twitter.com/0cNN2jm8    
    
    
    Projection workshop chat thing at @eyebeamnyc pic.twitter.com/fq12oUo6    
    
    
    @sidbranca you missed a really fantastic panel... great presenters, great dialog. thanks #caa2013 !    
    
    
    Looking forward to panel, "The Work of Art Criticism in the Age of E-zines + Blogging," 2:30 pm, Beekman Parlor #CAA2013 @charlottefrost    
    
    
    @charlottefrost doing the digital (criticism) CAA2013 pic.twitter.com/aYR2z0qi    
    
    
    Shout out to the forthcoming art critic documentary by @artcity - @charlottefrost #CAA2013    
    
    
    I heart Amy and Sean pic.twitter.com/mT9YmcxQ    
    
    
    That was nice. #NYC #CAA2013 #artsfuturebook #implicitart @artcity @charlottefrost    
    
    
    Chelsea highlights: Robin Rhodes @LehmannMaupin, Yevgeniy Fiks @WinklemanNYC, Marina @zurkow @bitforms gallery, chat @DavidKrutNY. #niceday    
    
    
    Back to #milwaukee. Nice few weeks: art, writing, teaching, visiting artists @cynthialawson + several South Africans. Hope not much #admin !    
    
    
    Re-reading #TheStoryteller by #WalterBenjmain for an independent study with one of my grad students. Brilliant + beautiful, as I remember.    
    
    
    @cynthialawson Colombia, Colombia, #Colombia, Colombia. Also, #Milwaukee. See you next week! Art, food, chats, stuff. Looking forward.    
    
    
    I'll be on the 8 o'clock buzz, WORT fm, Monday morning 8:40 CST, talking #tweetsinspace amongst other things.... http://www.wortfm.org/news/shows/8oclock-buzz/ …    
    
    
    Check out my now-archived live radio interview on @WORTnews #tweetsinspace #wikipediaart @kildall http://wortfm.org/interactive-artist-nathaniel-stern-is-on-the-web-and-out-in-space/ …    
    
    
    @cynthialawson is my hero. And here in Milwaukee. Stuck at the gate in snow! #yayArt    
    
    
    In #MKE + love art? Check the @cynthialawson artist talk tonight - free, 7pm, ACL / #Peck #UWM. Slow art, activism, teaching, awesomeness.    
    
    
    Amazing artist talk, discussion, + dinner conversation by/with @cynthialawson last night. Thank you for coming, thanks #Peck for sponsoring.    
    
    
    Fancy pants feature on "5 artists to watch" in M Magazine, #Milwaukee, with yours truly and good company. http://nathanielstern.com/text/2013/m-magazine/ …    
    
    
    I second what @artcity says. http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/194784541.html …    
    
    
    A little #arthistory + a little #artsfuture - just checked myself into a downtown MKE hotel for 24 hours of book proof editing. #comingsoon!    
    
    
    Super cool moment: I walked into my hotel room to find a laid out copy of the @MMagazineMke where I am featured in one of the cover stories.    
    
    
    @furtherfield is totally awesome. They've changed the way I think many times. I just made a donation; so should you. http://www.furtherfield.org/get-involved/donate/donate-now …    
    
    
    Book talk, interactive art, moving images on paper, and more! http://us1.campaign-archive2.com/?u=f51a68dd625e9d4ae3f40a67a&id=3ebda2c90d&e=2228d57627 …    
    
    
    Extremely proud of our @uwmpsoa Art and Design students. What a fantastic exhibition! Congratulations to the 5 of you. #contemporary #art    
    
    
    Who needs power? Community engagement @uwm and #penelopeproject show us what they are made of even without it!!!    
    
    
    Laptop hard drive crash. Again. Screw this, I am upgrading to SSD. Need more time, ah! #wastedDay #wishIwasMakingArt    
    
    
    I hope some of you can come to my interactive art demo + book pre-talk on Thursday, 6PM at @uwmpsoa - INOVA gallery! https://www.facebook.com/events/338591376262308/ …    
    
    
    Richard John Forbes at his artist talk @uwmpsoa @UWM #southafrica pic.twitter.com/V2K1TfRVVU    
    
    
    #SGCI / #printMKE is finally here! So looking forward to hosting friends from @DavidKrut, @DavidKrutNY and Gallery AOP, + seeing great art!    
    
    
    #PrintMKE and #SGCI are a huge triumph. What amazing events, people, art, ideas, techniques… Tremendous job, fantastic makers, all around.    
    
    
    Death Metal Press!!! #SGCI #printMKE pic.twitter.com/WcBMKjZv1f    
    
    
    Planning my #ISEA2013 panel with Andrew Goodman, @andrewmurphie and Lone Bertelsen on interactive art and ethics. Skyping from South Africa!    
    
    
    Normally, not a huge fan of waking at 4AM; but got some awesome Kinect / openFrameworks code going for upcoming show - stoked! #implicitbody    
    
    
    1st ever live meeting/edit in Google Docs, w @charlottefrost. Productive! & v. close to launching our #implicitbody / #interactiveart book!    
    
    
    What lovely conversation with Joe Grennier / @jpg_mke about his MA show this morning. Congratulations, Joe. Now: coffee.    
    
    
    Nothing like sometime out of town to get back to training! http://mmf.cc/14Qmgk1  #run #running    
    
    
    The Museum of Wisconsin Art (MOWA) opens its (new) doors tomorrow! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/201551761.html …    
    
    
    Nice piece on Niki Johnson's larger body of solid work (not just the condom pope) by @artcity - def worth a read! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/202253481.html …    
    
    
    I am now represented by @ToryFolliard gallery in the American Midwest! And I still work with Gallery AOP in South Africa, of course :)    
    
    
    Got a product/app idea but don't know how to start? Submit your plan to http://bit.ly/12MaRS4 . YOU could win $10k to startup! @UWM_SSC #uwm    
    
    
    Downloaded and started reading @patlichty's awesome new book! http://networkcultures.org/wpmu/portal/publication/no-12-variant-analyses-interrogations-of-new-media-art-and-culture-patrick-lichty/ …    
    
    
    The "school for poetic computation" looks pretty rad! http://sfpc.io  @zachlieberman    
    
    
    I'm sorry this happened, Boston. My heart goes out to you. I'm thankful for my life, family and friends.    
    
    
    Yes, I'm really busy, and behind on everything. I think we all are. But today I really had to stop + think about what wonderful live I have.    
    
    
    MT: Yes, I'm really busy & behind on everything. I think we all are. But today I had to stop + think about what a wonderful life I have.    
    
    
    Interactive art: recoded enter, elicit + stuttering w/ Kinect+other cool updates in #openFrameworks; 2/3rds done w/ new piece! #implicitbody    
    
    
    Wait, what? It's Monday again? It's nearly May? Gah! I have to make sure to schedule time to eat in my calendar this week… :)    
    
    
    Sometimes, super cool opportunities come out of nowhere. The trick, I am learning, is making time to navigate them w/ the care they deserve.    
    
    
    Love this new work by Shane Hope!!! http://slog.thestranger.com/slog/archives/2013/04/23/the-batty-nanomolecular-paintings-of-shane-hope?fb_action_ids=10152806713230393&fb_action_types=og.likes … and http://gizmodo.com/5995293/artist-nanofactures-paintings-using-a-3d-printer-and-molecular-modelling-software?fb_action_ids=10152806721285393&fb_action_types=og.likes …
3D prints as yummy organic paintings...    
    
    
    My wife is really cool. I like hanging out with her. I want to do it more. I just told her so. I hope we can arrange something.    
    
    
    Heading to Orono for a couple of days next week, to chat to some folks at University of Maine. Anything I should do/see there or in Bangor?    
    
    
    Planning a two-floor Wits Art Museum exhibition of 7 interactive works with @teganBristow in Johannesburg, June - August 2013! #implicitbody    
    
    
    I ran 4.41 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/17phYi4  #run #running    
    
    
    Spinning bliss at park #2 for the day... pic.twitter.com/L9Yp6UPvcT    
    
    
    @vigvr @ConAnderton thanks for the appreciation, kind words, follow!    
    
    
    This is not the TED talk I imagined I'd give, if I ever gave one. But, collaboration is about new outcomes, right?!!! Catch it May 9 in MKE.    
    
    
    This week is a tough one, with a lot of great projects and opportunities coming to a head. Was that a deadline I just saw fly by? Pretty!    
    
    
    2:30 AM, getting ready for flight to Maine, trying to pretend I'm bright eyed and bushy tailed. I think I can!    
    
    
    The bags under my eyes have bags under them. Hmmmm. That just means I need different lighting, right? Or a bit more base? ...    
    
    
    Beautiful manifesto from my friends ubermorgen. Hat tip to @furtherfield http://www.ubermorgen.com/manifesto/     
    
    
    View from the Villa Terrace Art Museum window. Exhibition is great! #chasingHorizons pic.twitter.com/GZEL9Opq5D    
    
    
    5 minutes into her talk, I've decided I love fellow upgrader @michacardenas … My students loved your workshop + I hope to talk to you later!    
    
    
    Reality deniers? @rgrusin: neon-liberal? RT @dgolumbia: #c21dsd @mckenziewark a totality that needs a different name - not #neoliberal    
    
    
    Catalog essay in penultimate draft? Check. Book + book cover proofed? Check. TED slides ready? Check. Grading? Hey kid, let's go to the Zoo!    
    
    
    OMG this week is nuts. Code, practice talk, grade, meetings, design catalog, GAH! Must find time to eat+sleep. And whiskey. Need whiskey.    
    
    
    Ready for her big piano recital - playing Bob the Builder and Take me out to the Ballgame! pic.twitter.com/tGvvdLRcfP    
    
    
    @wugmump I'll be in South Africa! Wanna join?    
    
    
    Strategic planning meeting at #UWM. Sitting with two of my favorite colleagues, from Engineering + the Research Foundation. Can be fun?...    
    
    
    Ilya + I giving TEDx talk tomorrow: Slow Innovation. 2:30pm CST. Live stream at https://new.livestream.com/tedx/events/2050736 … + more info http://www.tedx-milwaukee.com/nathaniel-stern/ …    
    
    
    Maybe just a little nervous... #tedxmke pic.twitter.com/FNBHmA4X5D    
    
    
    thanks @billmalcolm @vigvr ! Was a great day for MKE and TED and I think. #tedxmke    
    
    
    Today, I code. In between meetings. But still. There's time for it. Yay, art!    
    
    
    "'Imagine the world we'd live in if we spent more time imagining the world we could live in,' said Nathaniel Stern." http://northside.fox6now.com/news/arts-culture/234881-art-picks-steam-tedxharambee#.UZFgS5es5iw.twitter …    
    
    
    What a beautiful day!    
    
    
    Just got me some Summer dosh - an award from the Technology Development Fund at UWM. Thanks UWM Research Foundation!    
    
    
    Anybody in tweetland have experience building marine rated rigs for camera equipment? I wanna scuba with my scanner… http://nathanielstern.com/art/tag/compressionism/ …    
    
    
    You will pay attention to me or else have no sink and bad breath all day. Purr. pic.twitter.com/MSI3e4NWOV    
    
    
    Piano, brunch, park, dance lessons, play date. Maybe the world does revolve around my daughter, and maybe that's not such a bad thing!    
    
    
    Photos of 'Body Language,' a decade+ long interactive art suite, now online. All 4 pieces opening in Joburg, June 12! http://nathanielstern.com/artwork/body-language/ …    
    
    
    I ran 4.41 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/16zNYDb  #run #running    
    
    
    4.41 http://mmf.cc/16zNYDb  Time to start training again. This time, maybe I'll get to a full marathon? (Half last time, barely)    
    
    
    Final debug+settings 4 Body Language interactive art suite, then packing it up 4 Wits Museum in Joburg! #implicitart http://nathanielstern.com/artwork/body-language/ …    
    
    
    That was a fair amount of alcohol. And no small amount of BBQ. Thanks Kennan. Good start to the Summer!    
    
    
    Gonna be a very interesting next couple of months for sure! #implicitbody #etc    
    
    
    I can't believe my amazing daughter is seven years old today! Happy birthday, baby. pic.twitter.com/XVjVxcZgWm    
    
    
    Got a new commission yesterday: drawing+video on 60" LCD with JMG from our ongoing series. Exciting! #implicitbody …http://jessicameuninckganger.nathanielstern.com     
    
    
    Latest version of @slidedeck developer/pro broke about half the youtube videos on my site. Sorry, working on it. Links to youtube still work    
    
    
    I ran 6.90 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/175VcPF  #run #running    
    
    
    Leave for South Africa in 5 days. Not even close to ready. Can't wait!!! #implicitBody #interactiveArt #exhibition #witsArtMuseum #vacation    
    
    
    @SlideDeck got the temp solution you emailed and it's working fine. Thanks for being on top if things!    
    
    
    Release versions of #BodyLanguage done + am packing up for #WAM exhibition. I <3 #openFrameworks !!! #implicitbody http://nathanielstern.com/artwork/body-language/ …    
    
    
    I ran 2.64 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/10AIP9L  #run #running    
    
    
    Beautiful catalog w/ essay by Charlie Gere just back from the printers! Download here: http://nathanielstern.com/text/2013/catalog-body-language/ … #implicitbody #interactiveArt    
    
    
    Today: celebrate 11 years of marriage with Nicole Ridgway. Tomorrow: fly to South Africa to set up some art. Charmed life.    
    
    
    Early birthday presents. Yum. #singleMalt pic.twitter.com/uW2P7mfEwR    
    
    
    I ran 8.24 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/15ouii4  #run #running    
    
    
    Ok, Milwaukee. See you in about a month. Johannesburg, see you very soon!    
    
    
    Good morning Wits! @teganBristow, thanks for the hospitality; nice to see ya. Joburg, we have some catching up to do! #witsArtMuseum    
    
    
    Just stopped by #Maboneng / #ArtsOnMain. My oh my, it's good to be home. Hello Joburg, and hello old friends!    
    
    
    Getting ready for the show in Joburg! #implicitbody http://us1.campaign-archive2.com/?u=f51a68dd625e9d4ae3f40a67a&id=b163e8c076&e=2228d57627 …    
    
    
    Beautiful influx of birthday wishes this morning! I feel cared for. Tonight: dinner with some friends at the Troyeville Hotel, Johannesburg!    
    
    
    Moving into the #WtsArtMuseum today. Lots and lots to do! #implicitbody https://www.facebook.com/events/111945899016232/ …    
    
    
    Wall text for our #implicitbody #interactiveArt show at Wits Art Museum. Opens Wednesday!!! pic.twitter.com/bFZnF8i3pf    
    
    
    TONIGHT! My opening with @teganBristow at the Wits Art Museum. Hope to see some of you there! #implicitbody pic.twitter.com/E5TvcCE6uE    
    
    
    250+ folks @ #witsArtMuseum #interactiveArt opening, including 1 of my fave artists, William Kentridge! #implicitbody pic.twitter.com/m53ynVO87J    
    
    
    @k_treen Marmite, actually - very happy it's so available here in South Africa, as opposed to when I'm state-side. Agreed: great panel!    
    
    
    thnx @SonyaRademeyer - @teganBristow and I are super happy with it! Up for 2 months if in Gauteng. No plans for Cape show… yet. Suggestions?    
    
    
    After S. Africa opening, I Skyped to ISEA for #interactiveArt panel http://www.isea2013.org/events/im-position-a-minor-politics-for-interactive-art-panel/ … + am on group show in NYC http://www.ipcny.org/node/2136     
    
    
    3 days of fiction! Reacquainting myself with two of my fave characters: @ilona_andrews' Kate Daniels, + @RobertJSawyer's Caitlin Decter.    
    
    
    @kjpociask sorry I missed @eyeofestival; am in South Africa at the mo, but I'm sure a chat can be arranged when I'm back in town - holla!    
    
    
    @kjpociask sure thing. back in July...    
    
    
    Nice weekend. I have some pix to upload and thoughts to tweet. I'll get there eventually. But right now: inbox. Gah - help me!!!    
    
    
    Beautiful photos of my and @teganBristow's #witsArtMuseum show in Joburg by Christo Doherty! http://www.flickr.com/photos/christopics/sets/72157634142003313/ … #implicitbody    
    
    
    Father's day with Christo Doherty + his family in Suikerbosrand Nature Reserve, Johannesburg. Lovely hike + picnic! pic.twitter.com/fYeOdP1tNZ    
    
    
    Four more days to apply to the Renew Digital Arts Festival 2013 in Copenhagen! http://re-new.org/cal/call/     
    
    
    Lovely William Kentridge lecture / "drawing lesson" at Wits. Amazing speaker, generous artist & thinker. pic.twitter.com/3nawQgvy4c    
    
    
    Joburg. Troyeville. Prawns. Lovely. pic.twitter.com/b708p2ZNcq    
    
    
    Lovely walkabout w/ @teganBristow at #WitsArtMuseum yesterday. 45 interested folks, great questions, fun interactions. Up for 2 more months!    
    
    
    @teganBristow and I had a blast talking about our work to 45+ interested and playful folks at the #WitsArtMuseum pic.twitter.com/5UMZ8f1Cw1    
    
    
    Last Day in Joburg! Thank you so much to everyone for their hospitality, not to mention great work together. @teganBristow, you especially.    
    
    
    OK, Milwaukee. I'm home. I need a few days to settle + then we'll do some things. And stuff. Don't forget stuff. Like art. And running. Yeh!    
    
    
    @charlottefrost the companion chapter to my forthcoming book has a lot of info on this - including that Ellis and many others...    
    
    
    I ran 4.70 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/124zhA1  #run #running    
    
    
    still pretty jetlagged. meh.    
    
    
    stayed asleep past 5 am today. yes, eat that jet lag!    
    
    
    Nonie dancing at Summerfest. With @artcity pic.twitter.com/v8uIlRDvIO    
    
    
    Grrrrrrrrrrr! Aaaaaargh! Meh! Bleh! And I say again, grrrrrrrrr!    
    
    
    Apologies to folks trying to access my sites. Server issues at @hostgator. I might switch hosts after the fix; this issue has been appalling    
    
    
    Sites finally seem to be running smoothly again. Maybe soon I'll even update with new videos from South Africa / the Wits Art Museum!    
    
    
    Independent study w/ UMaine grad student @BenjaminBurpee. Next up: photos alongside Erin Manning's new book (chaps 1-3) - looking forward!    
    
    
    I ran 6.66 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/12LTfUD  #run #running    
    
    
    I too want to be a tide of shit. #implicitbody http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YzGjO5aHShQ …    
    
    
    Thoughtful discussion b/w @WinklemanNYC + @Powhida. Things I've been thinking about + things I should/will be. http://www.edwardwinkleman.com/2013/07/a-conversation-with-william-powhida-on.html …    
    
    
    Light reading at the beach. Nonie in the background, but occasionally foregrounded, of course... pic.twitter.com/4xWnTW39x9    
    
    
    Oh Milwaukee. Be still my heart. pic.twitter.com/3jJP3s0hb8    
    
    
    Madison's WORT FM had me back to talk about my projects, including those w/ @kildall + @teganBristow. Archived at http://www.wortfm.org/nathaniel-stern-back-for-more/ …    
    
    
    I ran 3.45 mi with @MapMyRun. http://mmf.cc/1deqDFa  #run #running    
    
    
    3.5 mile run that ended with a dear spotting on Lake Drive. Good start to the day! pic.twitter.com/c7hBt7iuJP    
    
    
    The ArtMobile!!! With Jessica Meuninck-Ganger in Milwaukee, WI pic.twitter.com/YrVoWyEcAi    
    
    
    OMFG I love my collaborator and friend Erin Manning!!!! Inspirational and exciting to talk upcoming projects with you today!    
    
    
    I ran 5.06 mi with @mapmyrun. Check out my route in Milwaukee, WI! http://mmf.cc/18S0mit  #run #running    
    
    
    A substantial review of my and @teganBristow's show in the Mail and Guardian this past week! http://nathanielstern.com/text/2013/mail-guardian-3/ …    
    
    
    HD videos of South African show now live! 5 clips: overview w/ voiceover + documentation of each piece (2 mins per). http://nathanielstern.com/artwork/body-language/ …    
    
    
    Bloody Mary. Beer chaser(s). Pizza. Kid playing, me surfing the interwebs. 80 degrees. It actually feels like summer. <3ing Sunday July 14!    
    
    
    My book on interactive art is available for pre-order, ships August 5th! http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1780240090?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=1780240090&linkCode=shr&tag=interartandem-20 … #implicitbody #interactiveart #arthistory    
    
    
    Actually, @center21 and @gylphi: right now my book is _#2_ on Amazon Hot New Releases (Conceptual Art)! http://ow.ly/n3kuI  #implicitbody    
    
    
    More on my interactive art book, now available for pre-order... http://eepurl.com/CmJzX     
    
    
    My li'l rock star w/ Milwaukee / Project Runway star, Miranda Levy. Congratulations to two kick ass zombie killers! pic.twitter.com/2WKJJAhDe6    
    
    
    @mirandalevy was AWESOME last night - on the show + in person. My daughter wants to be u when she grows up. I like the idea #DesignerMiranda    
    
    
    @victorlirio i'm an artist. rules?    
    
    
    My daughter, Nonie, in the paper with her idol: Zombie apocalypse / Project Runway fashion designer, @mirandalevy pic.twitter.com/kY32YWhTsA    
    
    
        
    
    
    @victorlirio ok, we can be friends :)    
    
    
    @victorlirio you are pretty cool yourself (your site)… alright, alright. sometimes rules are good. just not for my friends (or daughter) :)    
    
    
    #arthistory #implicitbody @gylphi @charlottefrost http://amzn.to/18qVbDw  pic.twitter.com/n4adxlwLik    
    
    
    Nonie and I just paid our respects to Cissie Peltz, former cartoonist and 20+ year gallerist. She did great things.    
    
    
    I'm on a boat, yo. (Selfie) pic.twitter.com/hLhnnIo6On    
    
    
    Auto correct says we're having a side of Brussels Proust with dinner tonight.    
    
    
    Nonie on our tennis lessons: I am getting better, but also experiencing different things, and learning to control my disappointment!    
    
    
    3 cool things: 1. Book in press! 2. Price down! 3. "purchased with" Brian Massumi! Feeling good today #implicitbody http://amzn.to/17xLfH4     
    
    
    Moebius wants submissions on the theme “Art in the Age of High Security”. Respond to Hasan Elahi interview at link! http://www.moebiusjournal.org/content/call-submissions …    
    
    
    MT @gylphi: My book is at #1 for Hot New Releases in Arts & Photography Criticism on Amazon! http://fb.me/NLYOQ7o0  #implicitbody    
    
    
    Gonna be a hektik few months (what else is new?). Cuz, y'know, I got some cool sh!t goin down... S'alright. #implicitbody #art #andAllThat    
    
    
        
    
    
    Critical Mass print portfolio site. The works, inspired by Richard Noyce's books, have already shown internationally! http://criticalmass.nathanielstern.com     
    
    
    Hadn't KNOWN that. Congrats: good news for everyone... MT @ChrisRoper: on the appointment of @ChrisRoper + MG future: http://grubstreet.co.za/2013/07/25/chris-roper-as-editor-tells-us-digital-is-everything-to-mail-guardians-future/ …    
    
    
    OK, new project getting started where I'll make event- / performance / installation-ish art w/ Jennifer Johung + Erin Manning in NYC. Win.    
    
    
    @artcity @heidiwitz @RadioMilwaukee @MikeBrenner @staceywng Miss you too. Off to Door County!    
    
    
    Ah, can't wait to see!!! RT @gylphi: Print copies of Interactive Art and Embodiment by @nathanielstern have arrived! pic.twitter.com/3fuoxlCtVJ    
    
    
    Wow! WAM review compares me to Aaron Sorkin, my art to The West Wing! "The politics of meaning + voice" http://www.bdlive.co.za/life/entertainment/2013/08/01/the-politics-of-meaning-and-voice … #implicitbody    
    
    
    14.3 miles, 10:40 pace. Longest run EVER. w00t!    
    
    
    Macbook Air 1.7 GHz i7, 8 GB memory, 512 GB solid state drive. Just transferred my files, + am very satisfied with no longer being "pro".    
    
    
    Book is out!!! 1st Amazon batch shipped yesterday, they get another batch tomorrow + ship some more! #implicitbody http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1780240090/ref=as_li_ss_tl?ie=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=390957&creativeASIN=1780240090&linkCode=as2&tag=interartandem-20 …    
    
    
    $2.5m Monet painting on Amazon. READ THE COMMENTS - hilarious! http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00E1TDKZ8?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393177&creativeASIN=B00E1TDKZ8&linkCode=shr&tag=interartandem-20 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Today: housecleaning, emails, art proposal-writing, movies with the kid, pasta. Maybe some presentation preparation and/or scuba studying.    
    
    
        
    
    
    More great Christo Doherty photos of Meaning Motion at Wits Art Museum. Closes after this weekend! #implicitbody
http://www.flickr.com/photos/christopics/9476920869/ …    
    
    
    Best Skype moment w/ Curt Cloninger: "New York artists truly believe their home is the center of the universe. It's hilariously parochial."    
    
    
    Sundowner booze cruise with the wife and some friends. pic.twitter.com/wRrfJ4YXyb    
    
    
    Off to Montreal to collaborate with some of my favorite people, at The Sense Lab. Hooray! #yayArt    
    
    
    Here's the folks I'm hanging out and working with on my trip to Montreal right now. http://www.montrealgazette.com/life/SenseLab+goes+distance+with+Three+Mile+Meal/8812113/story.html …    
    
    
    @irini_mirena Have you been? I'm sure @teganBristow will host well, but for sure hit up Arts on Main, and do The Troyeville for LM prawns!    
    
    
    #senselab #lackofinfo pic.twitter.com/zzkuQAwGwq    
    
    
    MT: @wugmump: red burns, RIP. i love what she made and will be forever grateful. safe travels.”    
    
    
    Sorry to hear about the amazing Red Burns' passing. She left the world a better place than she found it, changed many lives 4 the better.    
    
    
    @BrennerBrewing will save Milwaukee from itself! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/220809801.html …    
    
    
    More images coming soon. Sense Lab event has been amazing!!!! #senselab #lackofinfo pic.twitter.com/QKKQDgoeS0    
    
    
    such an amazing day! #senselab #3milemeal #lackofinfo EVERYDAY KOSHER: Becoming a Friend of Hutchison http://everydaykosher.blogspot.com/2013/08/becoming-friend-of-hutchison.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Magical week: I feel rejuvenated, challenged, interested, interesting, + loved (+a bit tired, but ready to do it over again). #senselab    
    
    
    First big academic day of the school year, an all day meeting. Wish I could hang out with my colleagues w/o the laundry list, but se la vi!    
    
    
    More on the amazing #RedBurns, who helped me become a better teacher, student, artist… http://mobile.nytimes.com/2013/08/27/nyregion/red-burns-godmother-of-silicon-alley-dies-at-88.html?partner=rss&emc=rss&utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter& … and http://rhizome.org/editorial/2013/aug/26/red-burns-lives-on/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+rhizome-fp+%28Rhizome+%3E+Front+Page%29 …    
    
    
    School's starting+my calendar hates me, but I'm happy. Montreal was amazing, book+art=doing well, wife=lovely, +daughter=super fun. So there    
    
    
    squeezing in an hour of writing time. busy couple of weeks!    
    
    
    Strange + stressful day, that ended with my first ever open water scuba dive, followed by a party with some fantastic folks. #doinItForMyArt    
    
    
    Remember that amazingly relentless good mood I was bragging about? Yesterday+today are pretty close to killing it.    
    
    
    I'm training to SCUBA for a subaqueous art project I'm planning over the next year or so. My ears feel weird. #gonnaBeAwesome #implicitbody    
    
    
    First day of classes. Here we go! #UWM    
    
    
    MKE East Side Library commission finalists proposals: http://www.mpl.org/file/branch_east.htm#rfq … I'm among 5 amazing artists. Tell us what you think! #publicArt    
    
    
    My Creative Writing / Writing for Creation graduate course is gonna be awesome. Thanks to Nicole Ridgway for the syllabus I'm adapting! #uwm    
    
    
    @troyrhoades almost done with the syllabus, will send along soon!    
    
    
    #IthinkIcanIthinkIcanIthinkIcanIthinkIcan    
    
    
    just took my first yoga class in about a decade. with a light fever. tough, but my legs like me better than they did before the class...    
    
    
    1st week of classes (w/ major admin), while finishing a chapter, getting scuba certified, + training for marathon = best time to get sick.    
    
    
    Totally hopping at @lyndensculpture for Inuksuit! @PresentMusic pic.twitter.com/IyQC57uVUt    
    
    
    Beautiful piece on late Red Burns in Wired mag. Amazing woman, + gutsy enough to give me shit @ my own wedding... http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/09/focus-on-people-not-tech-and-other-impt-lessons-for-interaction-design-and-life/ …    
    
    
    @andrewmurphie: re-reading Parables today? #massumi is a good read for sure!    
    
    
    So excited for my graduate workshop today!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I am officially a certified, advanced open water scuba diver!!! #compressionism    
    
    
        
    
    
    Long week.    
    
    
    All book orders filling now! (Wipes sweat from brow.)  #implicitbody http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1780240090?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=1780240090&linkCode=shr&tag=interartandem-20&qid=1379161055&sr=8-1&keywords=nathaniel+stern … via @amazon    
    
    
    I can't seem to get rid of this headachy, drippy, cough thing, and it's making it hard to keep up. Grrrr.    
    
    
    Oy. And meh. 'Meh and Oy," I say!    
    
    
    It may be time to go to the doctor.    
    
    
    Good health care summary; admittedly stuff I know / i've been saying, but better said... @realjohngreen via @Upworthy http://www.upworthy.com/his-first-4-sentences-are-interesting-the-5th-blew-my-mind-and-made-me-a-little-sick-2?g=2 …    
    
    
    Milwaukee gallery says their collector loves our new commission; Johannesburg gallery says concrete+steel installation just about sold. NICE    
    
    
    Great show I'm on in London! #implicitbody #compressionism http://eepurl.com/FzAhb     
    
    
    Just ordered a Raspberry Pi for me+my team, workin on hardware interfaces for underwater performative art scanning. So cool! #compressionism    
    
    
    Nonie caught her dinner!!! pic.twitter.com/9ACrd3OgVX    
    
    
    Sunday morning cookout! pic.twitter.com/EB2cVCZ0xa    
    
    
    Katja Kwastek's new book looks great, should work well in parallel to my own! Just ordered one... http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0262019329?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=0262019329&linkCode=shr&tag=interartandem-20&qid=1379940890&sr=8-1&keywords=aesthetics+of+interaction+in+digital+art … via #implicitbody    
    
    
    Student in my class today: "I love this deep shit."    
    
    
    Just logged 3 more training SCUBA dives for sub-aqueous scanner art project. Research on open source case/system going well! #compressionism    
    
    
    helping out a friend with his new web site today!    
    
    
    Either my Raspberry Pi is a dud, or getting started with downloads + installations is harder than it should be. Hoping it's the former #fail    
    
    
    Was specific Raspberry Pi or the power supply; got new ones + am running in 10 mins, rather than 4 hours wasted. On to the coding! #succeed    
    
    
    Sunrise on a boat in the middle of Lake Michigan. pic.twitter.com/Kr7p6CxMNb    
    
    
    Toronto.    
    
    
    #tweetsinspace reunion! pic.twitter.com/BeSvFPA4CV    
    
    
    Now 10 years old, 4chan is the most important site you never visit http://bit.ly/1aGxO9r  via @dailydot    
    
    
    Bridge to USA. pic.twitter.com/L6XyuRQEXl    
    
    
    Nice to have Oron Catts back at UWM. #nonhuman pic.twitter.com/UdVKFvWp7Z    
    
    
    @MikeBrenner you are kick@ass. Milwaukee and beer are the answer to the government shutdown! http://video.foxnews.com/v/2735677170001     
    
    
    I'd like to start a new Acronym (capital "A"). OMFH. On My F^ck!ng Honor.  OMFH, I only had one cookie! Please commence usage.    
    
    
    OMFH, trickle down DOES NOT WORK    
    
    
    Oh I miss NYC. pic.twitter.com/a4D8YKJaRY    
    
    
    @BradyDale OMG I totally forgot u live here now! Yes, I'm going 2 Transfer tonight, + then a drink with @artfcity after, if u want 2 join.    
    
    
    Transfer Gallery - good stuff! pic.twitter.com/6BucpUmCoo    
    
    
    Fun times at @transfergallery last night, w/ @BradyDale @malcolm__levy @sarahcolebrnett + some cool art. Congratulations to @rollinleonard    
    
    
    It's a soldering open source goodness kind of day. #raspberryPi pic.twitter.com/mI0nrRPWQv    
    
    
    PDF version of my book's companion chapter now available on Turbulence! http://stern.networkedbook.org  Full e-book coming soon @gylphi #implicitbody    
    
    
    Oh! Python uses relative indentation for its groupings! Makes a lot more sense now. I suppose I should have read the manual. #MyWayIsFaster    
    
    
    London exhibition press! #implicitbody "Conceptually, this is genius. Practically speaking, this is genius…" http://www.brixtonblog.com/everything-wants-to-run-at-block-336/16940 …    
    
    
    If in Madison area, I'm about to be interviewed on 88.9 WORT FM by Brian Standing about my new, open source, sub-aqueous imaging system!    
    
    
    MT @ProlefeedStudio: Frankensteined flatbed scanner under the sea! @nathanielstern @WORTnews #monbuzz http://nathanielstern.com/text/2013/wort-fm-3/ … #implicitbody    
    
    
    Did not get much sleep last night. Full day. Advice?    
    
    
    @jasonrwalters see you've been playing with OSX Mavericks and #openFrameworks. OK for older 10.6 SDK projects as well?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Heading out for scientific diver certification, my first boat dive on Lake Michigan. Wish it was warmer! pic.twitter.com/8EcfNmDyeU    
    
    
    Woke up with a bad reaction to my flu shot. #ick #fail    
    
    
    @Block336Gallery thanks for the #FF - doing great stuff over there!    
    
    
    Starting a new collaboration w/ Manning + Johung: wickedly smart + subtly beautiful investigation of ecology. Can't wait to make it happen!    
    
    
    I totally want to buy the house up the street, and we definitely can't afford it. But it tells me something about my feelings re: Milwaukee.    
    
    
    LOL, Ed Norton as Owen Wilson just made my morning! http://dailypicksandflicks.com/2013/10/27/snls-wes-anderson-parody-movie-trailer-the-midnight-coterie-of-sinister-intruders-video/ …    
    
    
    Doctor Who 50th Anniversary. 3D iMax at Mayfair, Wisconsin. Who's with me (and Nicole and Nonie)? http://www.bbcamerica.com/anglophenia/2013/10/doctor-50th-anniversary-special-bbc-america-announces-3d-screening-events/ …    
    
    
    Well, that didn't go as expected. Or hoped for. But when life throws you rotten tomatoes, you should make someone else eat them.    
    
    
    Oh man, this cold and sore throat took a real turn for the worse. Ick, I say. Ick, Ick, Ick.    
    
    
    Two steps forward, two steps back. No, not Paula Abdul, working with technology….    
    
    
    @vegdem start the art lovers young!!!    
    
    
    Planning first NY solo show, in collaboration w/ Erin Manning, curated by Jennifer Johung in Brooklyn. Exciting new direction for all of us!    
    
    
    Going "home" to my alma mater, Cornell U in Ithaca, on 11/14 to talk about my work. Part of the Arts Council Biennial http://cca.cornell.edu/nathanielstern/     
    
    
    Interesting night, chatting to collaborators in neuroscience, media + psych. Idea: artworks that focus attention pic.twitter.com/l5Kuwxe4dl    
    
    
    Texas. Touching down in 7 hours, and counting. ASTR here I come. #implicitbody    
    
    
    Any of my peops at #ASTR2013 in Dallas? What u up to the next few days?    
    
    
    Coffee.    
    
    
    Going to see some art in Dallas now. Yay, art.    
    
    
    Cornell University talk this Thursday. #implicitbody pic.twitter.com/tuAXFHJFgG    
    
    
    It's funny how 6 grad students in the same class can say such different things about the assignments, my teaching, + class goals.    
    
    
    Object Oriented Philosophy: quirky + interesting stories, then harsh + without-a-doubt conclusions that have little to do w/ those stories.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost off the top, no. there's have been a few movements to get women online, some public crits, but not interventions I know of.    
    
    
    Awake    
    
    
    Philly, on route to Ithaca. Wish I got a full night's sleep last night. Soooooo tired!    
    
    
    Hi Ithaca! Hi Collegetown Bagels. Cornell, see you in a bit. Max/MSP+Jitter workshop tonight, artist talk tomorrow, here through the weekend    
    
    
    Two MKE artists on Whitney Biennial, including the awesome Paul Druecke - super smart + nice guy. Thrilled for them! http://www.jsonline.com/blogs/entertainment/232049971.html …    
    
    
    Lovely visit to Cornell - thanks to all my friends + hosts, + to those who came to my talk + workshop, etc. Ithaca was great! #implicitbody    
    
    
        
    
    
    Panel I'm on in about an hour.  http://toryfolliard.com/news/coexist-panel-discussion-miad-november-21-2014/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Playing with vacuum forming art at Discovery World! pic.twitter.com/dpVSsSOGxw    
    
    
    A mostly lazy day, playing board games with the kid, cleaning up, editing my artist statement a bit, listening to an audio book. Needed!    
    
    
    That is a lot of snow.    
    
    
    Waiting for Dr Who to start! pic.twitter.com/KbH1I0yrjZ    
    
    
    Two Milwaukee greats: Mary-Louise Schumacher @artcity and Nicolas Lampert. https://soundcloud.com/mary-louise-schumacher/art-city-radio-nicolas-lampert …    
    
    
    Early Black Friday deals on Amazon. Just got me a hard drive and a tablet. http://www.amazon.com/b/ref=as_acph_cc_bfdw_1124_1130?_encoding=UTF8&camp=1789&creative=9325&linkCode=ur2&node=384082011&tag=interartandem-20 …    
    
    
    All aboard the rational idea train! (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/this-future-map-of-the-united-states-is-way-cooler-than-any-current-map-of-the-u?g=2 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kimbal long time no see! just got in touch with Jen, too. yr doing great things, as always; thrilled to see it all.    
    
    
    @kimbal nah, was just thinking of u 2 & wanted 2b in touch. Wish I had when in Snowmass a few years back! Hope we do c u again soon!    
    
    
    It's weird, but I really like my Windows 8 tablet. I may use it more than just for scanning underwater art. #compressionism #implicitart    
    
    
    Anybody ever tried to install #Vuescan on #RaspberryPi? Not that happy with #SANE results, gonna try tomorrow… #compressionism #implicitbody    
    
    
    The Art+Technology studio MFA at the University of Wisconsin - Milwaukee is now accepting applications! http://nathanielstern.com/art-and-technology-mfa-at-the-university-of-wisconsin-milwaukee/ … #implicitbody    
    
    
    Packed house for Nicolas Lampert's book launch! A People's Art History of the US. At Boswell Books, Milwaukee pic.twitter.com/by3xOpyO8p    
    
    
    I rarely think of my career lately. I think about what I can do, better: as artist, writer, teacher, parent... It's nice to be a grown up.    
    
    
    @furtherfield: 17 years bridging arts, technology, + social change, and actively challenging neoliberalism http://www.furtherfield.org/features/articles/furtherfield-and-contemporary-art-culture-where-we-are-now …    
    
    
    The world is a darker place without you, Madiba. But a better place because of you. #nelsonmandela    
    
    
        
    
    
    @emiliusvgs Thanks for your interest in my book! I don't know the date, but a kindle version is expected v. soon from @gylphi #implicitbody    
    
    
    That went well.    
    
    
    Portfolio review today and next Wednesday. Let's see what the newest crop is made of!    
    
    
    Up to 3 trips to South Africa in 2014, all art and research related, w/ a bit of fun on the side. (And prawns of course. From Mozambique.)    
    
    
    Woke up from a dream where 7 disparate ideas formed the start of an exciting book. Guess what I'm doing on sabbatical (Sp 15)! #implicitbody    
    
    
    Tickets to FL and Montreal booked. Still waiting on South African flight. Gonna be a crazy January!    
    
    
    SPOILER: In Frozen, a young woman saves herself + her sister through an act of (familial) true love that requires no prince. Bravo Disney!    
    
    
    no more computer today. and trying not to touch phone's email or apps either. just reading and meetings. let's see if I can manage.    
    
    
    FYI, 2 half days are not enough to read, much less read + grade, a dissertation. Good to know. Guess what might be coming on vacation w/ me!    
    
    
    Just a few more (massive) things to deal with, then off to hang out with my sister Samantha and her family next week!    
    
    
    peeve of the day: subconscious=popular culture term regarding perception + focus. unconscious=pyschoanalytic term about our minds + thought.    
    
    
    Building some more tables for the studio. pic.twitter.com/o124D9wsxy    
    
    
    TEDx talk! The energy in the room is not justified by the video + poor sound quality, but I'm glad to see it online. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uqOVWNmMRIk …    
    
    
    No I'm not. Yes you are. No I'm not. Yes you are, infinity. #conversationsWithChildren    
    
    
    Coming down with something. Probably caught from my niece and nephew. Merry holidays!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thorough and thoughtful Milwaukee (and surrounds) arts year in review, http://www.jsonline.com/entertainment/arts/30-americans-among-best-2013-art-shows-in-milwaukee-b99141717z1-237343001.html … from @artcity    
    
    
    Nonie (my daughter) says I am "awkweird". Teh Awesome.    
    
    
    Daddy, I'm cold.
You are wet and therefore cold; if you get dry, you will not be cold.
That's wautological.
OMG I love you.    
    
    
    The problems with TED. I agree with all of this…. We need to talk about TED | Benjamin Bratton http://gu.com/p/3yfvc/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Happy New Year, everyone. May we all have the strength to give one another a little more.    
    
    
    Heading to Epcot to scuba w/ some sharks - overpreparing for my marine scanner art, or just crazy? You decide. #compressionism #implicitbody    
    
    
    @jmantissa awesome! http://www.jausart.com/     
    
    
    A Nonie and art admin day, + both were actually quite nice after such intense editing all week. Later: Troy and Abed, and lots of 'em.    
    
    
    Troy and Abed in the moooorning! #community    
    
    
    @charlottefrost likes my book (so far at least)    
    
    
    Working on Kickstarter campaign w/ Scott Kildall + US Artists fundraiser w/ Jessica Meuninck-Ganger. Exciting new projects! # yay #art    
    
    
    In next 2 days, I must review grad student apps between various Nonie outings + meetings. Is it me, or did weekends stop existing long ago?    
    
    
    Two incontrovertible things: Anthropogenic Global Warming is Real, and the Wall Street Journal is a Political Rag http://bit.ly/y1jyVI     
    
    
    I'm rendering video. A sketch for some new art. It feels really nice to be working on art. @charlottefrost can keep my book draft for a bit.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost hooray for making stuff! so fun with you on Thurs! PS I told Nicole and she is keen to chat about your project...    
    
    
    Just got back from @creativecap (Creative Capital) info session here in Milwaukee. AMAZING. I <3 Ruby Lerner. We need 20 more just like her.    
    
    
    Not a very good night's sleep. Mind blazing with ideas, anxieties and excitement of varying degrees. Coffee. More coffee.    
    
    
    awake    
    
    
    Productive morning.    
    
    
    This has been a really long day. And I still have several hours of work to go. Good thing I like art/teaching/reading/writing so much.    
    
    
    Democrats: you are using the wrong language! Instead of calling it "The Buffet Rule," call it "Flat Tax for Millionaires and Billionaires."    
    
    
    I FINK U FREEKY, and I like you a lot. Serious. http://bit.ly/AcFwjj     
    
    
    Michael Szpakowski's lovely 'Lawrence Weiner Erasure' - a work of conceptual art http://flic.kr/p/bkhhua     
    
    
    Rachel @maddow is coming to Milwaukee! If only I could afford tickets for me and the Mrs... Meh, I'll still buy the book. RECALL WALKER!!!    
    
    
    Main art, writing books, doing stuff, yeh ...    
    
    
    I heard there was a football game today or something. I was catching up on eps of Community. But hey, Giants are cool - my daughter says so.    
    
    
    Crazy days! Art and writin and teaching and all....    
    
    
    I know Situationist is meant to be capitalized. What about Relational Art / Aesthetics? (Other than when I'm referring to the book.)    
    
    
    "art is always both a limitation and a magnification"    
    
    
    Greg Martens is one of the most amazing artists / students / people I've ever had the pleasure to work with. http://bit.ly/wEE2Os     
    
    
    I am watching Short Circuit with my daughter. Srsly.    
    
    
    @MikeBrenner now all she does is ask for "input! input!"    
    
    
    All meetings and editing a proposal today. After 2 straight hours of answering emails. At least there's coffee.    
    
    
    Getting warmer. Getting warmer!... No, not Milwaukee - that's actually getting colder. I just mean I'm almost done with my book!    
    
    
    Mocking up image layouts and begging for permission to use them from other artists. Yes, I'm an art geek: I am having so much fun! #AcWri    
    
    
    I signed up for a marathon today, in October. I'm up to 3 miles now, only 23 more to add... Yikes!    
    
    
    Awesome awesome awesome news for @nathanielstern and @kildall - so totally exciting. Public info coming soon...    
    
    
    @Brianputz new project...    
    
    
    @artcity Lovely to see you and yes, interesting show re: #newexchanges at @miad_edu ... Also, you should come to the desert with us.    
    
    
    @artcity deal on both counts - will let you know when we can start talking about it publicly.    
    
    
    Just remembered I'm going to LA next week. Can anyone there watch my daughter on Thurs mornin during my CAA panel? Also, wanna hang out? #LA    
    
    
    @nicolegeary sure, we can grab coffee! I'll be meandering between going gaga at other sessions, doing my own + spending time with the fam!    
    
    
    Today: gymnastics, lunch + piano lesson with Nonie, Creative Capital grant proposal, Sense Lab skype + CAA prep. Also, pizza for breakfast.    
    
    
    @FineLineMag gorgeous installation at MIAD, and I'm loving following the new site / blog! Where can I buy all back issues locally in MKE?    
    
    
    @TwoCoats Google+ keeps telling me that people are adding me, and I keep meaning to do something about it...    
    
    
    @artfagcity macklemore. definitely macklemore. i'm especially fond of the bush song.    
    
    
    Secret World of Arrietty - super sweet. Nonie and I really enjoyed it, and then some time in the park.    
    
    
    Hey kid. _Hi daddy._ Let's go to California tomorrow. _Sure._ Cool. #CAA    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity was at the Tar Pits with with my family + @marctasman yesterday, then the New Media Caucus thing. Where were you?    
    
    
    Black Venus panel at #CAA2012 this morning=great! New Media Caucus Pecha Kucha thing on Wed = Awesome. + my panel yesterday of course rocked    
    
    
    @charlottefrost: "ah so modest! ;-)" - well, I didn't actually present on my panel, so I'm speaking of the awesomeness of my colleagues...    
    
    
    @charlottefrost there IS no upstaging your Derridance. Except maybe with your Spinoza Shimmy.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost Lyotard Lindy    
    
    
    @charlottefrost Jamesian Jitterbug and Whitehead Waltz... OK, I'll stop. Do not want to overload @collegeart / #CAA2012 with our fine moves.    
    
    
    LA: ok bye. That was kinda fun. looking forward to looking up all the cool new props I met! #CAA2012 #CAA    
    
    
    This Colbert video on branding is hilarious - but it also made me go out and buy Wheat Thins. http://bit.ly/Ab8Oad  #wheatthins #colbert    
    
    
    @kickstarter or @RocketHub or  @USAforART ? Differences? Insights? Doing 2 media artworks + can't decide b/w them for each one #crowdfunding    
    
    
    Art is great.    
    
    
    The Daily Show's Samantha Bee Demolishes Grover Norquist http://bit.ly/AyxM0R     
    
    
    William Kentridge receives Dan David Award! $1 Million for “scientific, technological and cultural accomplishments” http://huff.to/y685Wy     
    
    
    Sidonie says, "Daddy, you like mommy's dinners a lot. That's why your belly is getting bigger."    
    
    
    Congratulations @juspar !!! Insect Media has won the Anne Friedberg book award. http://bit.ly/z7hjG9     
    
    
    @artcity gives a considerable amount of thought, and time, to grappling with MIAD's recent show. http://bit.ly/A37ZUQ     
    
    
    I wish I knew sooner that you could delete tweets and facebook posts...    
    
    
    The State of the Art is Elsewhere: “Print/Out” at The Museum of Modern Art - great article! http://bit.ly/AqiCKU     
    
    
    So cool! Metropolis II by Chris Burden (the movie) http://youtu.be/llacDdn5yIE  (h/t Kennan Ferguson)    
    
    
    Lytro Light Field Camera - this blows my mind a little bit. http://bit.ly/wNainO     
    
    
    Hey @GeorgeJirasek : I ran into / met some great folks at CAA in LA, from Chicago, and am all fired up to restart upgrade MKE. You in?    
    
    
    dangerous thought... RT @charlottefrost: I keep accidentally direct messaging people, for my next trick I'll public message a private tweet!    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity sorry to miss it, too. tho hanging single volunteer piece this morning was far more work than it should've been.    
    
    
    @charlottefrost totally. also, you should call me poochlet in public more often. it makes me blush, in a good way.  #poochlet    
    
    
    @charlottefrost oh she does look cool, and the drummer is KYOOT! Am prepping for Erin and Brian 2omorrow, so send my best...    
    
    
    @artcity @charlottefrost Sunday Brunch would be better for me (especially if I can bring Nonie, but even if not)    
    
    
    I <3 The Sense Lab and all my colleagues in it. What a lovely chat today, + looking forward to a catch-up with others next week! #goodpeeps    
    
    
    @charlottefrost @artcity  I have Charlie and the Choco factory tix with nonie at 4. Could do before that with her, if possible?    
    
    
    