You (YOU!) Can Take Stanford's 'Intro to AI' Course Next Quarter, For Free - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/pMgs4S    
    
    
    IBM, NCSA abandon petascale supercomputer project http://bit.ly/o993ZQ    
    
    
    Kudso Thai RT @@thait: Lightbox is currently one of the top photo apps in the Android Market! http://lightbox.com/qT5KJho    
    
    
    13-Year-Old Makes A Solar Breakthrough With Fibonacci Sequence : TreeHugger http://flpbd.it/E0jD     
    
    
    The 25 Most Influential Business Management Books - TIME http://ti.me/oFBLqu     
    
    
    Are you, or do you know, a great front-end developer? join Cloudera
http://jobvite.com/m?3ERp8fwM  #job    
    
    
    Good Read: Why Amazon Can't Make A Kindle In the USA - Forbes http://onforb.es/n5ClH5     
    
    
    Congrats to @hackingdata for being picked by MIT @TechReview as one of 35 innovators under age of 35: http://bit.ly/mWlA1M     
    
    
    Funny video with random folks answering the question "What is Hadoop?" http://vimeo.com/27928858     
    
    
    This is a genius combo, watch if you are a fan of Mario or Portal or both: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WtcGiZelPfk …    
    
    
    Intelligence Solutions for Government from @Carahsoft: @Cloudera - The Fastest Way to Apache Hadoop http://bit.ly/ocbbQu     
    
    
    Image: Detective @Monk_USA would struggle a lot if he visited Cloudera's men restroom in San Francisco http://flic.kr/p/aiJhAb     
    
    
    Video: A funny/creative HadoopSong by Jake Leichtling: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FyJuMnvMQFY …    
    
    
    Funny: Chatbot Tries to Talk to Itself, Things Get Weird - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/rpCPGG     
    
    
    WrxbxtdwEwywteteczhhdggnhgcddfd.ttgjjngjedqqeewwwee    
    
    
    @aliimam no, that is Arabic. Jk, it is a pocket tweet :)    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Software Quality Engineer at Cloudera - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/7hqh4g     
    
    
    I second that -> RT @KatieS: #Yahoo was the first job I ever loved and am rooting for it to succeed. Suggestion: hire @robsolomon1 as CEO.    
    
    
        
    
    
    You might want to pre-order this book: HBase: The Definitive Guide by @larsgeorge http://www.amazon.com/dp/1449396100/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_aMPBob0EJ4YKT … via @amazon    
    
    
    Video from inside a car when the Japan Earth Quake/Tsunami hit, the power/energy is simply amazing. 津波日本 http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IQqmp9OOE1E …    
    
    
    @EriniDoss glad u liked it.    
    
    
    Job opportunity: Senior UI Engineer at Cloudera - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/EYvfxU     
    
    
    Hire For The Ability To Get Shit Done http://bit.ly/oCgCnx     
    
    
    Architects Using Robots to Build Beautiful Structures (from @IEEESpectrum) http://bit.ly/qfa0N3     
    
    
    Come see my talk today at #strataconf: How Hadoop is Revolutionizing Business Intelligence and Advanced Data Analytics http://strataconf.com/stratany2011/public/schedule/detail/21750 …    
    
    
    Scary Impressive Shit -> Scientists Reconstruct Brains' Visions Into Digital Video http://gizmo.do/onUQ0F     
    
    
    "Failing means getting blocked on an intended course, backing out, and restarting. Losing means persisting in your failing ways, refusing to    
    
    
    change your current course, and instead putting significant effort into justifying the course." Geoffery Moore http://bit.ly/obJnw9     
    
    
    Hadoop + A Few Million Monkeys Randomly Recreate Shakespeare (by @jessetanderson) http://bit.ly/nL0BnR     
    
    
    The @Accel_Partners Global CEO summit yesterday was a blast, kudos on a very well executed entertaining/educational event.    
    
    
    Very proud of our recently announced partnerships with @RevolutionR (http://bit.ly/oRFwdY ) and @Pervasive (http://bit.ly/qgYZ3G )    
    
    
    Nooooo! RT @paloaltoweekly: #Obama: We as country, as parents, need to up our game, get kids to put away video games,    
    
    
    yes, use Cloudera instead :) -> RT @DEVOPS_BORAT First step in design your own distributed system: Don't.    
    
    
    Slides for preso I gave at #strataconf last week: How Apache Hadoop is Revolutionizing BI and Data Analytics http://slidesha.re/pD8sOF     
    
    
    Great blog post by my co-founder and CEO (@mikeolson) on Apache #Hadoop and "The Community Effect" http://bit.ly/nIcks6  (we in it together)    
    
    
    Impressive video of the AlphaDog robot, the control system in this thing is mind boggling: http://bit.ly/qVXz4y  more at http://bit.ly/qrXbnU     
    
    
    New open-source contribution from @cloudera by @josh_wills - Crunch: easy, efficient MapReduce pipelines in Java http://bit.ly/qRei3Z     
    
    
    Very happy to see the announcement today between @Cloudera and @Microstrategy (one of the best BI companies out there) http://bit.ly/oI7dc9     
    
    
    On Balancing Short-Term with Long-Term: It's Time To Say A Big 'Thank You' To Amazon http://read.bi/vdRh1D     
    
    
    Terminator is coming closer - Stunning Video of PETMAN Humanoid Robot From Boston Dynamics - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/u05eYj     
    
    
    HadoopWorld is sold out --> http://www.hadoopworld.com/  (see you all in NYC next week)    
    
    
    Congrats to @hackingdata & @dpatil for being mated by @timoreilly as one of World's 7 Most Powerful Data Scientists http://onforb.es/sU77k8     
    
    
    @drluckyspin thanks Todd, looking forward to catching up at #hw2011    
    
    
    @josephby thanks Joseph and @rich_wong    
    
    
    Charles looking sharp at Hadoop World #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aCYpLT     
    
    
    Photo: @mikeolson during main keynote at Hadoop World #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aD3BW1     
    
    
    Photo: @elicollins singing on the Hadoop World stage :) #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aD3KhL     
    
    
    Photo: Ping Li (@ping_accel) looking smart at Hadoop World #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aD1eEZ     
    
    
    Photo: Doug Cutting (@cutting) rocks the Hadoop World stage (note original Hadoop in lower left) #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aDduYB     
    
    
    Photo: Doug Cutting (@cutting) rocks Hadoop World stage (note original Hadoop in lower left) #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aDdwyk     
    
    
    Photo: Aaron Myers (@atm) looking professorial at Hadoop World talk on HDFS HA #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aDehFR     
    
    
    Come attend my talk today on how #Hadoop is revolutionizing Business Intelligence & Data Analytics at Hadoop World (1pm in NY West) #hw2011    
    
    
    Photo: Todd Lipcon (@tlipcon) shows off his beard and stellar Hadoop performance gains at Hadoop World #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aDigty     
    
    
    Watch @drewtweat from Cloudera on Cisco's website (wait for 3rd graphic): http://bit.ly/s9X9be "    
    
    
    Photo: James Markarian (@InformaticaCorp CTO) gave a stellar keynote at Hadoop World, excellent preso, kudos http://flic.kr/p/aDqb73  #hw2011    
    
    
    Link to download all presos from Hadoop World 2011 http://www.slideshare.net/cloudera  #hw2011 (@om, thx for pointing out bad link)    
    
    
    So cute :) => RT @cutting: http://yfrog.com/h88f5yepj  Hadoop World comes home    
    
    
    And an even better link to download the #Hadoop World 2011 presos is http://bit.ly/sSysvw  #HW2011    
    
    
    Photo: Not to be outdone by @cutting boys, Sarah wears the Hadoop World tattoo on her cheek :) #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/aEHYJQ     
    
    
    Full list of video interviews by @wikibon and @siliconangle at Hadoop World 2011 (find me in 2 of them) http://bit.ly/rAMsgY  #hw2011 #hadoop    
    
    
    The Geometry of Startup Valuations http://bit.ly/tRTac8     
    
    
    Today @4:15pm I'm giving a #Hadoop introductory talk at Stanford's EE380 Comp Systems Colloquium http://bit.ly/uhVFFa  (also streamed live)    
    
    
        
    
    
    InfoWorld's top 10 emerging enterprise technologies: Apache #Hadoop is number 4 http://bit.ly/usdTOF     
    
    
    Video of talk I gave at Stanford's EE380 introducing Apache #Hadoop http://bit.ly/thtPRM  also the slides are at: http://slidesha.re/soo34E     
    
    
    "In Search of Hadoop" interesting graphs from @linkedin on where #Hadoop people are http://bit.ly/sllt0L  (via @MichaelRappa)    
    
    
    Today we released Cloudera Manager 3.7, I am super proud of this release, get it at http://bit.ly/rzMsmK  & see video: http://tcrn.ch/tdtBkC     
    
    
    Who's Behind This Chainsaw-Wielding Killer Robot? -  http://bit.ly/rqCQMI  (via @IEEESpectrum)    
    
    
    Hilarious (and sad) -> Late Night: Jon Stewart on 'All-American Muslim' controversy - http://latimes.com  http://lat.ms/rUAm9F     
    
    
    Video of brutality in #Egypt, female protester stripped and beaten in public (so what do they do behind closed doors!) http://bit.ly/sRsWqf     
    
    
    Good one->RT @martenmickos: If you have integrity, nothing else matters. If you don't have integrity, nothing else matters. - Alan K Simpson    
    
    
    Great writeup by @mitsuhiko on First Person Shooters, network lag compensation, and "How a Shooter Shoots" http://bit.ly/tMZpMj     
    
    
    Nice Slideshow by IEEE: From Pong to PlayStation 3 http://bit.ly/ugZNlx     
    
    
    @thait you're very brave Thai, are you the only tourists there?    
    
    
    #merrychristmas to all my christian friends    
    
    
    @thait I wish you guys a wonderful time in Egypt, make sure to see the Citadel and go south to Luxor/Aswan for Karnak and Abu Simbel temples    
    
    
    Great photos by @thait who is vacationing in #egypt right now http://lightbox.com/postcard/SbCFdKXSU6OOpAlOi-2DLw … (Thai is my cofounder from my first startup)    
    
    
    Video: I am totally getting this: CnC Generals 2 using the @Battlefield 3 #Frostbite graphics engine http://bit.ly/v603Nm  @officialcnc    
    
    
    In case you missed the news, Cloudera/Oracle are partners now -> "Oracle fills another gap in its Big Data offering" http://bit.ly/xxCLcK     
    
    
    Thanks @Michael_Saylor (@MicroStrategy CEO) for inviting partners to dinner on his yacht (the Harle) at #mstrworld http://flic.kr/p/bibno2     
    
    
    Daughters racing at office. http://flic.kr/p/92SW4x    
    
    
    Our newest Marketing video for Cloudera -> Profit From All Your Data: http://bit.ly/wag0Kz     
    
    
    @DarylPietro you can see that boxes diagram in slide 16 of this preso: http://www.cloudera.com/resource/hadoop-world-2011-presentation-slides-how-hadoop-revolutionized-business-intelligence-and-advanced-data-analytics …    
    
    
    @techmilind thx milind, I should have indeed mentioned the monster :)    
    
    
    @merv thanks merv, you know how these things go :)    
    
    
    Impressive -> Self-guided bullet could hit laser-marked targets from a mile away http://bit.ly/yLd5cS     
    
    
    @imranm thanks Imran.    
    
    
    @ulaar thanks Vishy, will do.    
    
    
    @dpatil thanks DJ, nothing compared to the Gen Flux thing on Fast Company, I am but a humble student of yours :)    
    
    
    @Coachonthego thanks Jerry, we miss you.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats to @Linkedin's CEO @jeffweiner for winning CEO of the year by @TechCrunch's 2011 #Crunchies, also for the @SAI SV100 -well deserved    
    
    
    Awesome/Hilarious writeup from @baconmeteor on "Why Arabic is Terrific" http://bit.ly/AqwbJc  (via @mikeolson via @emckean )    
    
    
    We released CDH4beta1 today http://bit.ly/Al6TPg  includes: High Availability for NN, both MR & MR2, plus a  ton of perf/scale improvements.    
    
    
    Nice twist on Newtonian physics :) "An Object in Love will remain in Love *Forever*" see others at http://bit.ly/zT75iq  (via @tlipcon)    
    
    
    @merv great meeting you today Merv, thanks for all the tweets too :)    
    
    
    @lintool my guess-> Elephants can go long distances carrying a lot (throughput), Horses can go short distances really fast (latency)    
    
    
    [INFOGRAPHIC] Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn And The Hierarchy Of Needs http://bit.ly/y2HT0V     
    
    
    Insightful post by @moatazr : 5 Key Components of a Successful Interest Graph http://on.mash.to/xDfTJ2     
    
    
    Today's Dilbert is ingenious, it is about the Higgs Boson, aka the "The God Particle" http://bit.ly/wzOyOa     
    
    
    Super psyched that @alsaldich joined us as VP Marketing. He helped turn @RiverBed into the juggernaut it is, he'll do wonders at @Cloudera    
    
    
    Listen to @henryr's charming British accent while demoing the Log/Event Mgmt & Alerting features of @Cloudera Manager http://bit.ly/ys29eM     
    
    
    "U must have a belief that there is something u can do that nobody else can & if u do it the world will be a better place" by @martenmickos    
    
    
    Photo: Not to be outdone by @cutting clan, Sarah wears the Hadoop World tattoo on her cheek :) #hw2011 http://flic.kr/p/bk1qRm     
    
    
    Diagnosoft is raising round B for their point-of-care Clinical Analytics system. Noble mission & great product/team http://bit.ly/ydixhV     
    
    
    @evilops Thanks ptr, please don't hesitate to let me know if you find any security gaps in their website :) http://www.offerna.com     
    
    
    @evilops afaik GroupOn doesn't have any presence in Egypt, so don't think competitor, think future acquisition target :)    
    
    
    I am talking at the Gov Big Data Forum 2012 in Wash DC tomorrow at 11:30am http://bit.ly/xdgjFr  I expect @bobgourley to heckle me :)    
    
    
    @om you need to make the hash tag for upcoming structure more visible on the main site at http://bit.ly/xDrGCD  I couldn't find. What is it?    
    
    
    I and 700+ people will be at @GigaOm Structure:Data 2012 in NYC on 3/21 & 22, highly recommend u also attend http://bit.ly/zArePa  #dataconf    
    
    
    Catch my @cloudera talks today at Univ of East London Royal Docks Business School, then tomorrow at #DigitalLon conf http://bit.ly/yS4TzT     
    
    
    If you like my talks then click this link and up vote my BI talk proposal for Hadoop Summit: http://bit.ly/xGplZc  (do it now, takes 1 sec)    
    
    
    Nice interactive viz from NYTimes: The Geography of Government Benefits http://nyti.ms/yqtzaR     
    
    
    One of my favorite quotes: "What are you waiting for? You're faster than this. Don't think you are, know you are." Morpheus, The Matrix 1999    
    
    
    I just backed FLIPCASE, @ahwong's ingenious creation, a collapsible glasses case, I recommend u back it too: http://kck.st/AA9OdZ     
    
    
    @ahwong np, thx to u for such a smart/practical design.    
    
    
    I will be at @GigaOm's Structure:Data conference Wed/Thu of this week, catch me there http://bit.ly/xDrGCD  #dataconf @dataconf    
    
    
    @luigicampos thanks, very soon.    
    
    
    Come Work Here -> Cloudera Named One of the Bay Area's Best Places to Work http://bit.ly/GWlUeS     
    
    
    Congrats, about time :) -> RT @MikeCafarella
After many years, WebTables makes it onto the Web: http://www.google.com/fusiontables/search?corpus=web&hl=en&q=us+presidents …    
    
    
    The deadline to submit a talk to Strata/Hadoop World is in 10-days (Apr 23rd), so go do it now: http://oreil.ly/IG3G1O  #strataconf #hw2012    
    
    
    Congrats to @martenmickos & @richwolski at @eucalyptuscloud for $30 Million Series C http://bit.ly/HIdVAv  keep it up, only gets harder :)    
    
    
    Congrats to all my friends at @Splunk for hitting the $3B mark right off the gate, kudos: http://yhoo.it/HWHstJ     
    
    
    Very sad for Barcelona :( well done @RealMadrid    
    
    
    "It is wise to direct your anger towards problems - not people; to focus your energies on answers - not excuses" William Arthur Ward.    
    
    
    Read the abstract -> "If money doesn't make you happy, then you probably aren't spending it right" http://bit.ly/IxhUCt  (via @chadcc)    
    
    
    “Wise men speak because they have something to say; Fools because they have to say something.” Plato. #quote    
    
    
    Just came back from a great dinner cooked by @frankartale at his place, now this is a full service VC :) pic.twitter.com/E56S8DJT    
    
    
    "The mediocre teacher tells. The good teacher explains. The superior teacher demonstrates. The great teacher inspires." William Arthur Ward    
    
    
    Just finished Uncharted on the PS Vita, extremely clever use of motion control, touch screen, camera http://bit.ly/JGQb2m  @PSVitaNews    
    
    
    Totally Agree -> Dustin Moskovitz (dmoskov) says Y Combinator’s “No Idea” round is bad for Silicon Valley http://bit.ly/KK1RhQ     
    
    
    Very proud of our engineering team, at same time that they finishing CDH4 we release update 4 for CDH3 on schedule http://bit.ly/JclEsK  #do    
    
    
    I am talking 9AM PT tomorrow (Tue 5/15) @Infaworld about How #Hadoop Compliments Existing BI Systems! http://bit.ly/J5RFlL  #IW2012    
    
    
    Video showing control of robotic arm using brain signals (BrainGate) http://bit.ly/JVOVXm     
    
    
    This is pretty slick, from MIT, Video Magnification of Frequency and Color (see hand pulse & baby breath at end): http://youtu.be/ONZcjs1Pjmk     
    
    
    Nice Story: “The richness is in me, in my heart and in my head, not in my pockets," said Filipaj http://on.msnbc.com/KLIJEo     
    
    
    Video: Amazing real-time illumination/reflection demo for Unreal Engine 4 (a rendering engine used in many games): http://youtu.be/MOvfn1p92_8     
    
    
    Lina (my 15 yr old) while I was filling a web reg form "oh dad, you have to scroll down to pick your year of birth, you're so old" :)    
    
    
    @PatrickMoorhead thanks :)    
    
    
    Kmpiupiipyoukyouyuu    
    
    
    @jdcryans ??    
    
    
    @jdcryans @nattybnatkins @tensigma that was Amr's pocket actually :)    
    
    
    @jdcryans @nattybnatkins @tensigma btw, Egypt's x-president is currently in an unobservable state between life and death, so Amr's Cat is ok    
    
    
    Stop calling it the "God Particle!" http://bit.ly/MUWxvN     
    
    
    Video clip of @hackingdata talking about Facebook and data on NBC Nightly News: http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/3032619/#40879371    
    
    
    Yahoo Homepage Before and After Marrisa Mayer :) » Amr Awadallah Blog http://bit.ly/NQUgTi     
    
    
    Meet the Flickr/SlideShare of Data Visualizations -> http://bit.ly/MEeLkP     
    
    
    @henryr you really need to resurrect your blog :)    
    
    
    Fresh off the presses, learn how to configure #hadoop security/kerberos in CDH: http://bit.ly/gqOT71    
    
    
    This just happened: HP partners with Cloudera, they'll resell our software now, very cool. http://bit.ly/NLMVUy     
    
    
    After a long hot day of fasting, that first sip of water at sun set tastes like heaven, let's preserve this precious resource #ramadan    
    
    
    I love to follow folks who tweet little, but when they do tweet they spew gems.    
    
    
    Learn about column statistics in Apache Hive http://www.cloudera.com/blog/2012/08/column-statistics-in-hive …    
    
    
    Photo: Enjoyed a special King's College tour with @henryr on a sunny Cambridge day, beautiful campus. pic.twitter.com/0L1ckG3Q    
    
    
    @ash_patel but then she (palin) equates burning the Quran to building the ground0 mosque.    
    
    
    Watched "The Raid: Redemption" last weekend, awesome movie, highly recommend it if you into fighting/action movies: http://imdb.to/p9ff68     
    
    
    @mikeolson Thanks Mike, it has been a long month :)    
    
    
    Short high level animation explaining what Cloudera & Hadoop can do for you: http://vimeo.com/cloudera/get-started-with-hadoop-using-cloudera-enterprise …    
    
    
    @esammer lol :)    
    
    
    (via Dilbert) Yes, Big Data is an aphrodisiac, come work for @Cloudera :) http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2012-09-05/ …    
    
    
    One Word: Reach    
    
    
    Data Is Useless Without the Skills to Analyze It - Jeanne Harris - Harvard Business Review http://bit.ly/UUMryk     
    
    
    indeed :) by Cloudera's @henryr -> RT @steveyentweets: best plain english paxos overview: http://the-paper-trail.org/blog/?p=173    
    
    
    Photo: Very well done #cosplay for BioShock from DragonCon 2012  http://flpbd.it/rMDrc     
    
    
    Love it when Hadoop & Gaming intersect: http://bit.ly/OzhR8H     
    
    
    I just liked "Work at Cloudera" on Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/49279772     
    
    
    very upset that this video was pulled by @espn http://es.pn/ckMQ91, my son really wanted to see it.    
    
    
    seriously, I need @flipboard for windows, pretty plz.    
    
    
    Very happy that Alejandro @tucu00 started w/ Cloudera engineering team this week, he helped create the Oozie project http://bit.ly/96dDwb    
    
    
    The decoy hologram in #HaloReach adds a very clever dynamic to gameplay, also skull hunter is a rather innovative game type    
    
    
    @fzk would be happy too, email me to discuss    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/XoMN-zg7r3M?a  A Toy Train in Space    
    
    
    @parand I don't work out :)    
    
    
    @otrajman that was an excellent dilbert.    
    
    
    Very sad that @gremblor decided to leave Cloudera to start his own company, it was a fun two years Aaron, good luck dude.    
    
    
    The Cloudera catered lunch today tasted delicious but is proving to be gas inducing.    
    
    
    @jpatanooga the next gen twitter/facebook is called @flipboard, have your dad give it a try if he got an ipad    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/F7pYHN9iC9I?a  Amazing mind reader reveals his 'gift'    
    
    
    20 days left till Hadoop World, only a few spots left, register NOW before the doors close ($295) http://bit.ly/91G6B0 #hadoop #hw2010    
    
    
    I just hit 1000 followers on twitter, @ladygaga better watch out ;)    
    
    
    @nealrichter yep, elephant meat, that is the only animal big enough to cover me :) btw, that was disgusting, people can't find food to eat    
    
    
    @sampullara @eckartwalther lol, you know I get an sms message everytime you guys do that :)    
    
    
    @anutron plz don't install minecraft, that said, what is the link to get it? :)    
    
    
    Cloudera partnerships team (aka Ed) is on fire so far we announced Vertica, Netezza, Greenplum, Quest/Oracle, Teradata, http://bit.ly/aSX85m    
    
    
    @squarecog lol, indeed, there is also rumors that Teradata might become HP :) not clear who will pickup Vertica though.    
    
    
    @targyros congrats for the funding #asterdata    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/XNBP18nrRdw?a  The iPhone 5 (Parody) Ad: A Taller Change    
    
    
    CDH4.1 Now Released! http://www.cloudera.com/blog/2012/10/cdh4-1-now-released …    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/b1cz8IasV4w?a  The Popinator    
    
    
    @tlipcon yep,  unfortunately    
    
    
    For #BigData recommendations for government sector, read BigData Commission report @Cloudera co-created w/ @TechAmerica http://bit.ly/PVMXu7     
    
    
    Thx Ollie for tour at @skyboximaging office today, super cool stuff. See photo for their original show-n-tell satellite pic.twitter.com/Uqa0eoNf    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/yWLClUwAHGc?a  SimCity | Gameplay Strategy Video #1    
    
    
    #Looper. Movie. Good. Very Good. See It.    
    
    
    Neat -> Toyota Robotic Arm for Disabled Humans. http://bit.ly/QRBT30     
    
    
    @puppetmasterd I love @flipboard, but I hate it too, its addicting, and wastes almost an hour of time everyday.    
    
    
    @dmenninger congrats on your new role at @ventanaresearch, interesting move :)    
    
    
    @khanacademy congrats for $2m award from Google's 10^100, keep up the good/noble work.    
    
    
    @dmenninger yep see you at Hadoop World #hw2010    
    
    
    . @scott_dietzen @PureStorage congrats for the @WSJ Tech Innovation award,  we'll deserved - jealous :)    
    
    
    Photo: @scott_dietzen, CEO of  @PureStorage, owns the stage at GigaOm #structureeurope 2012 pic.twitter.com/vE2V47RG    
    
    
    Photo: @scott_dietzen, CEO of  @PureStorage, owns the stage at GigaOm #structureeurope 2012 pic.twitter.com/pjLgm7ay    
    
    
    Photo: @martenmickos, CEO @eucalyptuscloud, onstage w/ @om at GigaOm #structureeurope 2012. pic.twitter.com/WhlCVusV    
    
    
    Photo: @nik on stage with @derrickharris at #structureeurope talking about Dark Social (hidden social interactions) pic.twitter.com/HxRpX855    
    
    
    I hate it when auto pilot takes over while I am driving, made a completely wrong turn from where I need to be.    
    
    
    I love it when other companies contact our engineers trying to hire/steal them then we turn that around as a lead for our sales team :)    
    
    
    thritto RT @phunt: ditto: RT @owen_omalley: Going to Bay Area Hadoop User Group tonight. http://bit.ly/cQAJxH    
    
    
    @esammer keep emailing dude, ignore that jefe, work *is* life/fun, that is my mantra too.    
    
    
    @esammer and btw, that *is* what your jefe also does :)    
    
    
    @techmilind you'll certainly get my gratitude, and karma too :)    
    
    
    Photo: @mikeolson announces Cloudera Impala (low latency SQL for Hadoop) at #strataconf #hw2012 #biggerquestions pic.twitter.com/tIWz6zMo    
    
    
    I don't care how good the product is, and even if it is free, I'll never use box.noise    
    
    
    @boia01 it is on right path for educating enterprises about problems hadoop can solve, which is the goal (as opposed to research)    
    
    
    My name is Amr, and I am *not* a terrorist. Seriously, watch "My Name Is Khan", a beautiful movie about tolerance http://imdb.to/9l1382    
    
    
    To manage hyper-growth, get your launch trajectory right | LinkedIn http://lnkd.in/wEAqrB     
    
    
    Highly recommend this post by @NetworkString from @DataSift, great writeup on how to configure networking for Hadoop http://bit.ly/VYT72N     
    
    
    Read about our Bread Maker: http://bit.ly/VZdhtj     
    
    
    Photo: @cloudera's new branding, structured (left) comes together with unstructured (right) to complete your thinking. pic.twitter.com/7jNdWZQ5    
    
    
    Want to learn how to use Impala for interactive SQL on Hadoop? Free training here: http://bit.ly/ScNveI     
    
    
    I just liked "how to make perfect pour-over coffee and time your french press steeping with r" on Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/43305640     
    
    
    Cloudera and HP – Working Together for a Bigger, Better Data World | SiliconANGLE http://bit.ly/ScVrN0     
    
    
    OH: with @Cloudera Impala you now can have your cake (Batch SQL w/Hive) and eat it too (Low Latency SQL w/Impala) http://tiny.cloudera.com/ipsaz     
    
    
    Congrats get him on HDFS again :) @squarecog Awesome crop of new hires this week. Hadoop PMC member Raghu Angadi joining the Analytics team!    
    
    
    Do you have a website that you hate and want to shoot down? If so then this bookmarklet is for you: http://erkie.github.com/ (via @tlipcon)    
    
    
    A vendor-independent comparison of NoSQL databases: Cassandra, HBase, MongoDB, Riak http://bit.ly/Wh9BU8     
    
    
    @gridgain search    
    
    
    This is a wicked good 3D sound demo, close your eyes and listen with a headphone on: http://bit.ly/bcJLDG (via @rayanandi)    
    
    
    Very excited to be giving the opening keynote at Cloudera World Tokyo in 15mins, more than 600 folks registered #cwt2012    
    
    
    @showyou yes, Impala on HBase is good for interactive OLAP. Connect with our team for upgrading from CDH3 to CDH4.    
    
    
    Photo: Give Away to attendees at Cloudera World Tokyo to celebrate new logo and Impala launch #cwt2012 pic.twitter.com/01YOPZFO    
    
    
    Wow, this shadow checker board optical illusion is ridiculous, I can't trust my eyes any more: http://bit.ly/bl6doB (via @gerster)    
    
    
    Photo: Clouderans busy at work in Cloudera Japan office @clouderajp pic.twitter.com/byxXd1wd    
    
    
    Qliktech integrates with Cloudera: http://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/qliktech-integrates-cloudera-impala-deliver-130000414.html …    
    
    
    Love note from 6 year old (Sarah) left on a whiteboard at work http://flic.kr/p/9b35Bp    
    
    
    @kevinweil that was certainly an unfortunate oversight, we love Pig, please use the blank white tags to make a Pig badge    
    
    
    What is that coming out of your Pocket? #hw2010 @cutting http://flic.kr/p/8Jttxp    
    
    
    The Cloudera Distribution for Hadoop, including Pig :) #hw2010 http://flic.kr/p/8JvUFV    
    
    
    Ed Albanese (our head of business development), is live on siliconangle.tv talking about our partnership strategy #hw2010    
    
    
    Thanks for all the happy birthday wishes. Yes, I am 40 years old today :)    
    
    
    Toshiba Unveils Robot for Disaster Response - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/WWRgLw     
    
    
    This just happened: Cloudera raises $65M in Round E, bringing total raised to $140M http://dthin.gs/THTeNi     
    
    
    Good one -> "Some Recruiter I Used To Know" : http://youtu.be/Ba6Igu1MvE0  via @youtube    
    
    
    Photo: Thanks Larry, you too :-) pic.twitter.com/8GZlayHv    
    
    
    Free software and discounted training for Academia from Cloudera: http://bit.ly/12wmAjX     
    
    
    Congrats to the @firebase crew for launching the security API - long over due :), more details here: http://bit.ly/U0RxHJ     
    
    
    To Jeff Smisek, CEO of @United_Airlines, do right by your customers, send a new plane for the 200+ people you got trapped for 24 hrs in YYT    
    
    
    @ibrastix sure    
    
    
    @Neo_4583 thx, good excuse :)    
    
    
    @Robert_Justice lol :)    
    
    
    I am on a panel at #qcon SF next week, here is a promo code for $100 off AWAD100 http://qconsf.com/sf2010/conference    
    
    
    Cloudera raises a "hefty" round of funding, this should be the last one: http://bit.ly/cMhhZ4    
    
    
    Cloudera plans to double in size by hiring another 50 employees after raising a $25 million funding round: http://bit.ly/bQPWm4 #hadoop    
    
    
    Data Science SciFi: Watch Fringe S3E3 (The Plateau), excellent example of data science gone a bit too far :) http://youtu.be/KXYVhfBJXOw     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Hadoop Pumpkin: by Jon Zuanich http://flic.kr/p/8PHnqJ    
    
    
    Congrats to @puppetlabs & @puppetmasterd ->
VMware invests $30 million in Puppet Labs: http://bit.ly/10qqh7S  #puppetize    
    
    
    I voted today for the first time ... ever, feels good (I became US Citizen last year, never voted in Egypt)    
    
    
    I am giving a talk today 2:15pm on Impala, Hadoop, and EDW optimization at at #mstrworld, come with tough questions (Room: Mouton 2)    
    
    
    @fffabulous thx for intro and congrats. @PimV nice to e-meet you.    
    
    
    Photo: Excellent Machine Learning Dilbert today, very well done. pic.twitter.com/oAIjwbQl    
    
    
    10min video of yours truly oozing advice to budding middle-eastern entrepreneuers at @techwadiorg 2013 VC Forum: http://bit.ly/11Eambt     
    
    
    Photo: Larry Ellisons' golf ranch in Palm Springs (for an Oracle Big Data customer workshop): http://realestate.aol.com/blog/2011/02/11/larry-ellison-buys-rancho-mirage-estate-at-discount … pic.twitter.com/KTqfDo0A    
    
    
    Meet one of our super star support engineers @kate_ting : http://blog.cloudera.com/blog/2013/02/meet-the-engineer-kathleen-ting/ …    
    
    
    congrats to @firebase team http://techcrunch.com/2013/02/13/firebase-public-beta/ …    
    
    
    Data trumps bullshit (Tesla vs NY Times):  http://bit.ly/12NNC4H  Kudos to @elonmusk, very ballsy :) just like a proud parent would be.    
    
    
    Congrats @mikeolson for being one of 11 trail blazing people changing biz as picked by @fortunemagazine http://money.cnn.com/gallery/news/companies/2013/02/07/trailblazers.fortune/8.html …    
    
    
    I am giving a talk about #Hadoop, @Cloudera, and #BI tomorrow (1/27) 9:30am at #mstrworld (Latour 1), come with tough questions.    
    
    
    Get your plumbing straight: these fundamental #Hadoop usage patterns are the wax-on wax-off of #datascience http://blog.cloudera.com/blog/2013/02/big-datas-new-use-cases-transformation-active-archive-and-exploration …    
    
    
    Congrats -> Bank Systems and Technology Names NGDATA one of “7 Big Data Players to Watch” http://bit.ly/ZbPlyC     
    
    
    Excited -> @YourStorydotin & @Accel to host @Cloudera CTO and co-founder, Amr @Awadallah on 14th March in #Bangalore http://ow.ly/ibT44     
    
    
    Blog post: What does a CTO do? http://bit.ly/W6apZP     
    
    
    @bunsen I fixed the comments issue, try again now, thx for letting me know.    
    
    
    Join @Cloudera and @QlikView next Tue at 9am to learn about harnessing the power of big data http://go.qlikview.com/GLBL_2013_H1_Big_Data_Live_Web_PRG_Tch1_LP.html?sourceID1=QV_EV_Site&ga-link=promo …    
    
    
    Wed morning PT -> When Hadoop, when data warehouse? #gigaom webinar with @paulmiller @ImAmyO @richardwinter #bigdata http://ow.ly/iHh6P     
    
    
    I am in Bangalore (first time), meet me tomorrow at the Big Data event by @Accel partners India and @YourStorydotin http://bit.ly/WGOXgF     
    
    
    Very excited about this -> @Talend Big Data Certified on CDH4  http://bit.ly/YZchk4     
    
    
    Congrats @cwensel and @Concurrent team for $4M in new funding (and new CEO) http://gigaom.com/2013/03/20/concurrent-gets-4m-for-higher-level-hadoop/ …    
    
    
    @msevillatweets thank you, it was a great chat, you totally get it :)    
    
    
    Read about Cloudera ML Data Science tools http://blog.cloudera.com/blog/2013/03/cloudera_ml_data_science_tools/ …    
    
    
    Mr. Mubarak this is about you, not the gov under you, plz resign. @BarackObama it is hypocritical you still support that dictator #Egypt    
    
    
    You can watch my talk about "Hadoop for BI" from the Gartner BI summit here: http://bit.ly/Xs3ayg     
    
    
    @brfayek I was there last Dec, I usually visit once every two years.    
    
    
    Gratz to @DrBassemYoussef  for Time 100 Most Influential People, and Jon Stewart rocks by saying Bassem is his hero http://ti.me/11mQ9Sn     
    
    
    .@cloudera is 3rd organic search result for hadoop on Google, right after the Apache and Wikipedia entries http://bit.ly/17M2i9I  #hard2beat    
    
    
    Cloudera Opens EMEA HQ In East London’s Tech City http://tcrn.ch/ZJdjSV     
    
    
    Cloudera Teams With Leading Universities to Bridge the Big Data Talent Gap: http://on.wsj.com/ZFpzXs     
    
    
    I hate companies that start talking/selling products that don't exist yet, not even a working prototype. At @cloudera we do first then talk.    
    
    
    I am speaking at @BrownUniversity "Putting Big Data to Work" symposium tomorrow morning http://bit.ly/15MTX6k     
    
    
    Independent Research Firm (@gigaom) Forecasts SQL-on-Hadoop Market Disruption From Category Leader Cloudera http://mwne.ws/15MYeGZ     
    
    
        
    
    
    Very excited about our closer partnership with SAS: Cloudera Announces Strategic Alliance With SAS http://mwne.ws/17tHa7e     
    
    
    Cloudera revs up Impala SQL for Hadoop • The Register http://bit.ly/15amOCu     
    
    
    .@kennethn thanks, mom/dad are ok. It is sad but glorious at same time. Never imagined I'll see the day #Egypt-ians stand up against tyranny    
    
    
    Deadline for Strata + Hadoop World 2013 proposals coming up quick, submit before 5/16 http://oreil.ly/Zt41dT     
    
    
    Watch @MikeOlson and Doug @Cutting talk about #hadoop & #bigdata on CNBC's Squawk Box (aired yesterday) http://bit.ly/1368LdN     
    
    
    Heart breaking interview by @AJEnglish w/ @monasosh from Liberation Square http://bit.ly/gT3txV also see http://bit.ly/fpm9XV #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    Cloudera Announces Cloudera Developer Kit, Enabling Developers to Build Hadoop Apps Faster http://mwne.ws/YIcUFh     
    
    
    Splunk and Cloudera Ink Strategic Alliance to Bring Together Big Data Expertise | Business Wire http://bit.ly/YId5k3     
    
    
    Learn how your college/university can fill the Hadoop talent gap. Cloudera Academic Partnership webinar Thurs 5/16 http://ow.ly/l1pwt     
    
    
    HBaseCon 2013 is filling up quick, register now before it is too late: http://hbasecon.com/schedule  #hbase #hadoop @cloudera    
    
    
    Early signs for start of big data VC bubble collapse, I predict more is coming -> Drawn to Scale is closing down — http://bit.ly/YPgTxy     
    
    
    Register for this Webinar if you are curious how @MicroStrategy works with @Cloudera Impala http://bit.ly/12sTEbP     
    
    
    Cloudera and VMware Work Together to Accelerate Enterprise Use of Hadoop in Virtual and Cloud Environments http://mwne.ws/189nB6Q     
    
    
    New chant in Egypt: Condoleezza, Condoleezza, please give Mubarak a Visa [to leave Egypt that is] #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    The Real Reason Hadoop Is Such A Big Deal In Big Data – ReadWrite http://bit.ly/10HWj3J     
    
    
    Demo: MicroStrategy on Hadoop using Cloudera Impala http://vimeo.com/66925437  @microstrategy #hadoop #clouderaimpala    
    
    
    Minnah wants Mubarak out too :) [Mini Rally at Stanford Campus] http://flic.kr/p/9fYbzZ    
    
    
    Live video for the the Cloudera Forum about to start, new product announcements, you can watch it here http://bit.ly/11C9v5u  #nostatusquo    
    
    
    Free eLearning course for the newly launched Cloudera Search http://bit.ly/1b6W7vQ     
    
    
    It’s Time: Cloudera Takes Aim at the Legacy Data Management Solutions Market http://j.mp/12rVXkN  #NoStatusQuo #Hadoop    
    
    
    I will be giving a keynote today after James Markarian at @InformaticaCorp World, streamed live at http://bit.ly/1b6YMWg  #IW2013    
    
    
    Video for my keynote from @InformaticaCorp World 2013: http://youtu.be/KhiJ4eBC-bQ  #IW2013    
    
    
    @BarackObama: Mubarak Out *Now*, and stop financial aid to tyrants #egypt #jan25 (please RT)    
    
    
    HBaseCon 2013 rockked, read more about it here http://bit.ly/19B1qHr  #HBaseCon    
    
    
    .@Cloudera is proud to be in the Top 10 #BigData Startups for @CIOonline. Vote for your favorites here: http://bit.ly/15XUTSG  via @JWVance    
    
    
    Super psyched that Tom Reilly http://linkd.in/18WQ5lN  joined @Cloudera as CEO, more psyched @mikeolson is now Chairman http://bit.ly/18WPQak     
    
    
    Congrats to entire @Firebase team for closing their round A http://bit.ly/17sAEkN     
    
    
    Video: Checkout demo of the slick Hue App for @Cloudera Search http://buff.ly/1c5nSFy  @gethue    
    
    
    Kudos -> "@greenbacker: Just passed the Cloudera Certified Developer for Apache Hadoop exam on my first try #CCDH @BericoTech"    
    
    
    Honored to be on this list, especially that @ping_accel & @aneelb on it: 50 Most Powerful in Enterprise Tech http://bit.ly/12bBH3X  #kissup    
    
    
    @zedlewski lol :)    
    
    
    Cloudera Wins 2013 American Technology Award from TechAmerica Foundation http://buff.ly/11X6JZ5     
    
    
    "open-source community now regularly writes better software than billions of dollars in government money can buy," http://buff.ly/11X7sJH     
    
    
    Cloudera releases new high-speed connector for Teradata systems http://buff.ly/12pugWV     
    
    
    Watch interview w/ @Cloudera's VP of Products (Charles @Zedlewski) at #HadoopSummit http://buff.ly/1cvE1EF  (I recommend you follow him too)    
    
    
    Prepare for change! This is not your father’s database industry — Tech News and Analysis http://buff.ly/1cvWSPL     
    
    
    Go #Egypt, stay free, 1000 Congrats. ألف مبروك    
    
    
    Cloudera expands into Nashua office - http://NashuaTelegraph.com  http://bit.ly/11AhDKI     
    
    
    Cloudera leads European Hadoop market http://buff.ly/12ncVys     
    
    
    Help Egypt eliminate the Wall of Fear: http://bit.ly/hZEL6w or on Facebook http://on.fb.me/erGboh #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    DARPA-funded project uses social media to predict suicide by soldiers: http://buff.ly/15gIDf3     
    
    
    Myrrix Joins Cloudera to Bring "Big Learning" to Hadoop http://buff.ly/13ky1NI     
    
    
    Cloudera Unveils New Data Impact Awards Program to Honor Innovative Applications of Apache Hadoop http://buff.ly/15PMaDt     
    
    
    Breaking News: Cloudera Impala is Fast. Really Fast. http://buff.ly/12ToUPO     
    
    
    Mubarak is a true dictator, deaf, blind, delusional, in total denial, *believes* Egypt is his and Egyptians are his slaves #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    Video demo for @MicroStrategy running interactive reporting on Hadoop via @Cloudera Impala http://buff.ly/15Smm9R     
    
    
    Infographic: Cloudera leads Top 10 #InDemand Tech Startups Among Bay Area Engineers in 2013 (via @linkedin) http://buff.ly/132YDP9     
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: Motorola Mobility’s Award-Winning Unified Data Repository |  http://buff.ly/166dxXT     
    
    
    48 Hot Tech Companies To Build A Career (yep, arachleff picks @cloudera too, thx) http://buff.ly/18BtefH     
    
    
    Cloudera Takes Hadoop Security to the Next Level With Sentry: Fine-Grained Authorization for Impala and Apache Hive http://bit.ly/13EpFRo     
    
    
    48 Hot Tech Companies To Build A Career (yep, @arachleff picks @cloudera too, thx) http://buff.ly/18BtefH     
    
    
    Forbes: These 10 Tech Startups Attract Insane Interest On @LinkedIn http://buff.ly/1dYIqk9     
    
    
    Video demo: @Zoomdata running on a 4 Billion record/day dataset with @Cloudera Impala on the back-end http://buff.ly/169VNgA     
    
    
    Egyptians, I am so proud today, u showed the Pharoah that he is here 2 work for us. To future president, do ur job or u're out #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    @finkd Zuck plz meet w/ Wael :) In this CNN interview @ghonim thanks Facebook for sparking the Egypt revolution http://bit.ly/hEo9Bo #jan25    
    
    
    .@ClouderaU Data Science Challenge:Classification, Clustering, and Collaborative Filtering http://buff.ly/16ZaaCu     
    
    
    Announcing Parquet 1.0: Columnar Storage for Hadoop http://buff.ly/16Zvtny     
    
    
    Cloudera's @MikeOlson: Hadoop vs. Closed Source Is Not a Fair Fight  http://buff.ly/172Gg0p     
    
    
    Celebrating birthday of Egypt's freedom with other Egyptians in Memorial Park, Cupertino, CA http://flic.kr/p/9hFEZH    
    
    
    Photo: @Cloudera new headquarters, this is our 5th location over last 5 years, hopefully it will hold us for a while http://buff.ly/19hvhGf     
    
    
    NetworkWorld named their top 15 most powerful Big Data companies and @Cloudera makes the cut as a newcomer http://buff.ly/14456dZ     
    
    
    Q&A: Crossing the mainframe-to-big-data chasm - Computer Business Review http://buff.ly/13Tci0r  @syncsort @cloudera    
    
    
    What Customers are Saying about Cloudera @Search http://buff.ly/1btgPrZ     
    
    
    Excellent @hbase response from @LHofhansl @saintstack @akpurtell -> Taking the Bait: http://buff.ly/14Mr0ZA     
    
    
    Congrats to @Firebase team for going GA today http://bit.ly/128R7Gu  (nice to see CBS, Atlassian, and Yahoo as customers).    
    
    
    Wanna learn Data Science but can't decide what to wear to class? You can now take @cloudera online training (in bed) http://buff.ly/13oVShI     
    
    
    Use discount code Admin_10 to save 10% on enrollment in Cloudera-delivered Administrator classes (excludes partners) http://ow.ly/nXHRU     
    
    
    Excellent post by Colin McCabe on how improved short-circuit reads bring better performance & security to Hadoop http://buff.ly/14vKr2X     
    
    
    Video from @WSJ: The Elephant Threat to Big Tech (includes a brief Hadoop genesis and speculation on @Cloudera IPO) http://buff.ly/14vRZ5z     
    
    
    One of my most favorite use cases for @Cloudera and Hadoop, not to mention that @SkyBoxImaging guys are very cool :) http://buff.ly/16qXwgS     
    
    
    Nice video by Catherine Ray about her @Cloudera internship this summer: http://buff.ly/16kjH58  (more on her channel: http://buff.ly/16kjHlm )    
    
    
    Video: Slick illustration by @jessetanderson for #MapReduce parallelism using a deck of cards http://buff.ly/1dxNmir  #hadoop    
    
    
    Which to pick? #XboxOne or @Playstation #PS4? I have both the Xbox 360 and PS3, so only plan to get one of the new consoles.    
    
    
    @ToddQuest mostly FPS games, so Battlefield 4, CoD Ghosts, etc. I do like the @Naughty_Dog games, but also like #Halo franchise.    
    
    
    @jessetanderson agreed on the RRoD fiasco (that is fixed though).    
    
    
    Nice visualization (by @kovasboguta) of Twitter influencers associated with Egypt's Jan 25 revolution http://bit.ly/gmRu70  #egypt #jan25    
    
    
    @aliimam yeah, but @Bungie's new game (#Destiny) will be available for both. Also @Naughty_Dog games (Uncharted, Last of Us) are only for PS    
    
    
    The upcoming CDH5 beta will be based on the Hadoop 2 GA release: http://buff.ly/12Iyzgm     
    
    
    @kevinverse didn't decide yet, but leaning more towards PS4.    
    
    
    Saying #bigdata and security/privacy don't mix, is like saying guns and safety don't mix. It isn't the technology, it is how you abuse it.    
    
    
    Molecular basis for jet lag found http://buff.ly/14KDT4h     
    
    
    Great CBS @60Minutes interview with @Google's Wael @Ghonim on how/why the #Egypt revolution succeeded http://bit.ly/fyEAdC #jan25    
    
    
    Video featuring @cutting and @hackingdata "Unaccept the Status Quo | Expect More of Your Data" http://buff.ly/14Wv6MK  @cloudera    
    
    
    New date for origin of ancient Egypt  http://buff.ly/19gMeMI     
    
    
    Kudos to @loggly on a great Gen2 launch, 100s of new customer signups, and $10M in new funding http://buff.ly/19iVRup  http://tcrn.ch/15DQP7L     
    
    
    @ImAmyO Amy, very psyched that you started, I look forward to seeing you at @cloudera Sessions: http://bit.ly/15DTs9z     
    
    
    Super psyched that @Cloudera Search is now GA and ready for production workloads, learn more and grab it here http://buff.ly/17I7Al8     
    
    
    So sad, dude decapitated his own head while flying a remote control helicopter http://gawker.com/remote-control-helicopter-partially-decapitates-teen-in-1259586314 …    
    
    
    Just wow: using the AIDS virus to create "serial killer" cells that destroy cells infected with Leukemia/Cancer http://buff.ly/1adx1gz     
    
    
    Bruce Schneier: NSA surveillance: how to stay secure http://buff.ly/1adEhsS     
    
    
    @stewhir @lintool thanks for correction, english is my second language :)    
    
    
    Bossie Awards 2013: @Cloudera Impala selected as one of best open source big data tools - InfoWorld http://buff.ly/14gao9S     
    
    
    Are you a big data innovator? if so apply for the Strata #HadoopWorld Startup Showcase http://buff.ly/17Ihep8  #hadoopworld    
    
    
    @owen_omalley thanks owen, agree with your observation, vaporware shouldn't win a prize like this, I hear it is very imminent though.    
    
    
    Improving the Big Data Toolkit: Excellent job by @merv educating the @nytimes on what Hadoop 2.0 will bring http://buff.ly/1eqpqQf     
    
    
    @MoSarwat thanks :)    
    
    
    Gratz to @linabakalina (my daughter), her photo submission was an editor pick by @nytimesphoto http://buff.ly/18f3Yt8  #apple #palyhigh    
    
    
    Very cool: An Incredibly Detailed Size Comparison Chart of Science Fiction Spaceships http://buff.ly/16APk1B     
    
    
    @BassamSalem thanks :)    
    
    
    @BigDataSpeaker thx    
    
    
    @mhausenblas thx, bio looks correct to me    
    
    
    @mhausenblas I c, will let them know, thx for catching    
    
    
    Photo: Lina Awadallah (@linabakalina) in @VerdeMagazine (the Paly High school magazine) #palyhigh pic.twitter.com/B0g2CgLyAn    
    
    
    Tune in on Oct 16th to hear @PaulSonderegger interview me and George Lumpkin on how #Hadoop and #DataWarehouse are better together:    
    
    
    @Linus_Nova you can register for the event at: http://bit.ly/1e7Ry7Y     
    
    
    Take a peek at the platform we use internally to scalably support all of our customers http://buff.ly/1ctIIDr     
    
    
    .@Cloudera now has free lunch everyday for employees, we are also opening an SF office very soon, come work here: http://bit.ly/ansYAw    
    
    
    Photo w/ @mtarpenning cofounder of @teslamotors, he gave excellent preso at VPE/CTO Community of Practice event today pic.twitter.com/g3nxXPbA1K    
    
    
    @steve_mock @MetricInsights I am looking forward to it too.    
    
    
    @steve_mock steve, didn't see this till now, glad I did bump into you at the show case. Good stuff.    
    
    
    @steve_mock congrats.    
    
    
    @ABridgwater lol, you're welcome.    
    
    
    @philshem sure, glad you found it useful.    
    
    
    Free @OReillyMedia eBook: Cloudera Impala http://buff.ly/16Q17sD     
    
    
    @hkanji thx "on track" is the operative keyword here :)    
    
    
    Excellent and funny critique: "@mikeolson: I bet @MapR wishes there was no @alanctgardner. http://agardner.me/post/1383099874352 …"    
    
    
    Welcome @Savvis, @SoftLayer, @tsystemscom & @Verizon to the Cloudera Connect: Cloud partner program! http://j.mp/1f7gKfp     
    
    
    IDC Report: @Cloudera Leading Hadoop Distro Choices  http://buff.ly/1axDl5u  via @datanami    
    
    
    Photo: @Cloudera World Tokyo 2013 about to start, 1000+ people at the event! Getting ready for keynote. pic.twitter.com/NP7klKebwv    
    
    
    Free @Udacity online course for Hadoop and MapReduce by @Cloudera's talented VP of Training @sarahsproehnle http://buff.ly/IhudWi     
    
    
    From @Cloudera devel blog: How-to: Use the HBase Thrift Interface, Part 2: Inserting/Getting Rows: http://buff.ly/1gLPYdl     
    
    
    Video: Hear Tom Reilly (@Cloudera's CEO) explain what an Enterprise Data Hub is capable of http://buff.ly/1gLR6NZ  (via @AllAnalytics)    
    
    
    Sun Dogs in Minneapolis (Ice crystals at -8F lead to this effect at sun rise) #sundogs #sunrise http://instagram.com/p/hpSKA2inJr/     
    
    
    @MoSarwat I was, back in Bay area now.    
    
    
    @davorincapan thx :)    
    
    
    Full room at cloudera sessions in Munich, @RyanSGoldman up on stage. @ The Charles http://instagram.com/p/hvLLLuCnGi/     
    
    
    Pic: This would have been an awesome view if there was no fog :) (#London) http://instagram.com/p/hx3968CnJ8/     
    
    
    Very proud to have @SkyboxImaging as a customer, watch the amazing pictures from SkySat-1, unbelievably vivid colors http://buff.ly/19hWRS6     
    
    
    @mathewbutler customer meetings.    
    
    
    Thanks @crnawards for picking @Cloudera 5 as one of The 10 Coolest Big Data Products Of 2013 http://buff.ly/J7jD4E     
    
    
    Don't you just hate when you close your main @googlechrome window before a secondary window then lose all the open tabs from main session :(    
    
    
    Impala: Another Google Inspired Platform Enters The Mainstream Data World | TechCrunch http://buff.ly/18vE8E3     
    
    
    How-to: Do Statistical Analysis with Impala and R: http://buff.ly/IRceGU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Australians open-minded about Big Data: Cloudera  http://buff.ly/18U6uTm     
    
    
    Cloudera Goes Cloud With Amazon - InformationWeek  http://buff.ly/18VMmQK     
    
    
    Youtube video playlist for a number of @Cloudera customers talking about their use cases http://buff.ly/1cocAQy     
    
    
    Photo: on camel by the pyramids in Egypt http://instagram.com/p/iYixCHCnL0/     
    
    
    @awadallah you're more than welcome ya Basha :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    "The value of a person isn't what they achieved but what they aspire to achieve" Khalil Gibran @ Taboula http://instagram.com/p/ihTeahinBL/     
    
    
    Photo: I am told Obama visited this Mosque when he came to Egypt few years back. @ Masjed Sultan Hassan http://instagram.com/p/ik-8qICnFg/     
    
    
    The Citadel in profile. @ The Saladin Citadel of Cairo | قلعة صلاح الدين http://instagram.com/p/ilDbJKinJL/     
    
    
    King Farouk's resting place @ Masjed Al-Rifai http://instagram.com/p/ilDbs7CnJM/     
    
    
    Alhakem Mosque: This place used to be packed with tourists, now it is just my family inside. Sad. @… http://instagram.com/p/ilVFZSinGn/     
    
    
    This restaurant in #Cairo has an amazing view and food is delicious, highly recommend @ Citadel View… http://instagram.com/p/ilgQJJCnBD/     
    
    
        
    
    
    The beautiful #Nile hours before midnight 2013 from 24th floor of Sofitel hotel. #Cairo @ Sofitel… http://instagram.com/p/imO8zSCnDc/     
    
    
    @msevillatweets Thx, to you too    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo of @SofitelCairoEG hotel from yacht cruise in Nile with #Cairo Tower in background left. @… http://instagram.com/p/ioN0v4CnP4/     
    
    
    Photo: #Cairo Tower behind Nile @ Cairo Tower | برج القاهرة http://instagram.com/p/ioPbv4inBq/     
    
    
    Highly recommend the #Nile yacht ride from this place and food from Happy Dolphin right beside. #cairo… http://instagram.com/p/ioc6U5inFl/     
    
    
    Photo of old AUC library, w/ Ahmed El Alfi (@aoalfi) touring #GrEEK campus in downtown #Cairo. @ AUC… http://instagram.com/p/isy-5kCnB3/     
    
    
        
    
    
    w/ Ahmed El Alfi (@aoalfi) touring the new #GrEEK campus in downtown #Cairo. @ AUC Greek Campus http://instagram.com/p/iszyKCinCW/     
    
    
    The blue room in #AUC #GrEEK campus @ AUC Greek Campus http://instagram.com/p/is0aS3inC3/     
    
    
    Beautiful courtyard of old American University of #Cairo #AUC #GrEEK campus w/Ahmed El Alfi (@aoalfi)… http://instagram.com/p/is1BX7inDT/     
    
    
    #TahrirSquare locked down by APCs before Friday prayer. #cairo @ Tahrir Square | ميدان التحرير http://instagram.com/p/is5voainGa/     
    
    
    Crowded Khan El Khalili after Friday prayer #cairo @ Khan El Khalili (Al Hussein) http://instagram.com/p/itD3z-CnNB/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Image: Funny Hadoop Chinese Fortune Cookies at Cloudera today :) http://flic.kr/p/9pqpqU    
    
    
    Video on Hadoop MapReduce at @om #bigdataconf w/ @garyorenstein, me, @bwerther, @drluckyspin, @10gen CEO, Mike Hoskins http://bit.ly/eCHLvm    
    
    
    Congrats @Cloudera for winning 2010 Wikibon CTO Award for Best Infrastructure Technology Innovation: http://bit.ly/g2x7Mk    
    
    
    In a display of exquisite etiquette @Cloudera' Founder/CEO announced that they “will be more careful in the future” http://bit.ly/fIycV7    
    
    
    @techmilind mike is one of the founders.    
    
    
    @techmilind Mike was there at the founding of @Cloudera, he gave the pitch to Accel Partners and helped secure the domain name.    
    
    
    Congrats to all my #India friends for the cricket world championship. #wc2011    
    
    
    Kudos to @gremblor & co for releasing FlumeBase: SQL-based real-time streaming data analysis on top of Flume http://bit.ly/gvHAfm    
    
    
    @viveklak sorry, just go to opencompute.org    
    
    
    Congrats to @Accel_Partners' Andrew Braccia @agbraccia for selection as one of Elite 8 to watch in VC (by Forbes) http://bit.ly/h1xerb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Super happy that Kirk Dunn joined @Cloudera as Chief Operating Office, just in time to hit gas pedals into overdrive http://mwne.ws/hRxRFs    
    
    
    This is a big deal --> RT @mikeolson: today we released the GA version of our Apache Hadoop-based stack, CDH3: http://bit.ly/gaJwhq    
    
    
    I am talking about Hadoop present & future RT @DoDIISWW: Time running out, dont forget to register!  http://www.ncsi.com/dodiis11/index.html    
    
    
    Nice interview on @CNBC w/ Ping Li (@ping_accel) http://bit.ly/gZ3b05 (Ping, thanks for the Cloudera mention :) )    
    
    
    The Deal Is On: Groupon Gets a Great Deal for Its Data using Cloudera's Distribution for Apache Hadoop http://mwne.ws/fa2Ihy    
    
    
    Cloudera picked as one of "Hottest" Silicon Valley Companies by @Lead411 http://bit.ly/hKm0RK (our neighbor @BoxDotNet was also picked)    
    
    
    (Thx Steve and Chad) Youtube founders acquire Delicious from Yahoo! http://ycorpblog.com/2011/04/27/youtube-acquire-delicious/    
    
    
    Congratz to @cwsteinbach for being added to the Apache Hive Project Management Committee, well deserved http://bit.ly/j3oj04    
    
    
    At DoDIIS? then come attend my break out talk tomorrow (Mon) at 15:45 to hear about future of the Hadoop stack http://bit.ly/iNNouW #DWW11    
    
    
    The Irony: @BarackObama's number of tweets was 1337 just after tweeting he'll address nation re/ Bin Laden death http://bit.ly/iVoTjx    
    
    
    @bobgourley thanks for the nice note, I am the one who was honored to have you in the audience :) #DWW11    
    
    
        
    
    
    Cloudera gets @tiesv award as one of top 50 most Enterprising Technology Startups for 2011 in Software/Cloud Computing http://bit.ly/mdBQNV    
    
    
    Cloudera debuts on list of open source firms to watch in '11 (via @zdnet) - http://zd.net/kAjtpg    
    
    
    Is There A Peak Age for Entrepreneurship? http://tcrn.ch/jWGV0f    
    
    
    American Airlines (#AA20) from SFO->JFK lands early in DEN due to secondary generator failure, now we wait 5 hours for new flight :(    
    
    
    We are honored to be hosting the @TDWI SV chapter @Cloudera today, especially that @RalphKimball is the speaker http://bit.ly/kE5fEX #tdwisv    
    
    
    This is especially true for @Cloudera :) --> 5 Reasons to Join a Startup After Graduating http://bit.ly/lP7OZS    
    
    
    RSA finally comes clean: SecurID is compromised http://bit.ly/kPj5S8    
    
    
    Thx Todd, chicken is on me :) -> RT @tlipcon: *crosses fingers, slaughters a chicken, and drinks espresso* HADOOP-7106 here we go    
    
    
    A little bit of recruiting http://bit.ly/lwwMF3    
    
    
    Obama: 'We don't have enough engineers' - Computerworld http://bit.ly/lHIII4    
    
    
    U.S. Senator Calls Robot Projects Wasteful. Robots Call Senator Wasteful - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/ixqOAw    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Business Agility" is one of the key themes at GigaOm Structure 2011, I heard that phrase 37 times since day started #structureconf    
    
    
    Nice writeup by @zettaforce on @radar: Get started with Hadoop: From evaluation to your first production cluster - http://oreil.ly/mSIiwB    
    
    
    Microsoft Releases Kinect SDK, Roboticists Cackle With Glee - http://bit.ly/kFJG40    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    IBM develops 'instantaneous' memory, 100x faster than flash -- Engadget http://engt.co/kWuQh9    
    
    
    Watch @mikeolson talking about the @Cloudera Enterprise 3.5 management suite & SCM Express (fast/easy Hadoop installer) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hR1uMZh7p4Q&feature=share …    
    
    
    You're welcome :) RT @davidgreco: Cloudera's SCM Express is simply amazing, finally a simple way for setting an hadoop cluster! Good job    
    
    
    Impressive: Turn Call of Duty into a New Star Wars: Battlefront Game http://bit.ly/rmrDIe    
    
    
    So many memories from the first one, PlanetSide2 is revealed http://bit.ly/pdGNCN    
    
    
    Can you reproduce YouTube on Oracle's Exadata? http://zd.net/qHcCA6    
    
    
    Watch video of Cloudera SCM Express in action, get a full Hadoop *cluster* up and running in mere minutes: http://bit.ly/n5WEKW    
    
    
    Controlling a Quadrotor Using Kinect http://bit.ly/oEX53G    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hear hear RT @acmurthy: Looking forward to getting hadoop 0.23 out, lots of goodies already with promise of more down the pipe!    
    
    
    Stellar photo of father and son from first STS shuttle launch compared to last one 30 years later http://bit.ly/q29MYe    
    
    
    Go Todd go :) RT @tlipcon: random read microbenchmark: Hadoop 0.20.x: 72k/sec. Hadoop 0.23: 120k/sec. w/ HDFS-2080: 130k/sec. more coming.    
    
    
    This Friday (July 22nd) is *last* day to submit a talk for Hadoop World 2011 so stop procrastinating and go do it now http://bit.ly/oPBo7F    
    
    
    @sampullara I love Big Bang Theory, I know people like those characters, and their comics/gaming jokes are spot on.    
    
    
    Very cool -> Monroe or Einstein: Check If You Need Glasses at Your Computer http://lifehac.kr/oW0sMt    
    
    
    Big Science: The 10 Most Ambitious Experiments in the Universe Today | Popular Science http://bit.ly/qHZjWq (via @atm)    
    
    
    Hilarious -> Freaky Robot Mouth Learns to Sing - IEEE Spectrum http://bit.ly/n46bcw    
    
    
    Sarah Awadallah (7 year old) helping recruit for Cloudera :) http://flic.kr/p/a7zFFr    
    
    
    Nice indeed RT @jeric14: lots of release votes on Apache #Hadoop this week: Pig 0.9, hadoop0.20.204, hcatalog 0.2.  Nice to see the progress    
    
    
    Medal of Honor Cat http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PXRX47L_3yE&feature=share …    
    
    
    A robot that flies like a bird (from TED) totally worth watching http://on.ted.com/9XIZ    
    
    
    