@ChuckWendig I have both read and not read your tweet.  This space for rent.    
    
    
    Do we believe that secret predictive election models are real, or just lucky?    
    
    
    @mattcutts holding out for postgress.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield http://election.princeton.edu/methods/  has Matlab code and some degree of process documentation.    
    
    
    @gilgul like the bumper sticker says, שומר מרחק.  Stay safe.    
    
    
    @gilgul Hebrew iPhone autocorrect apparently not up to my poor Hebrew.    
    
    
    @abdur @bcherry but there is a real concern that eventually they will be that 80s hair band you don't quite remember the name of.    
    
    
    Threads-in-bubbles on the Gaza war are depressingly similar to threads-in-bubbles on the election. Two utter parallel universes.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield unsure why its ok to shoot missiles as long as no one gets hurt. #wtf    
    
    
    That might've been the first DARPA kickoff with lolcats, but I'm not sure.    
    
    
    @elunca still waiting for renormalization of Klout scores by Klout_score(horse_ebooks).  ;-)    
    
    
    @kansandhaus the road to Java is indeed paved with good intentions. So, if you design a programming language, you should avoid having those.    
    
    
    @msbernst have you tried following @cmunell?    
    
    
    Positive customer experience at Radio Shack. The end may be nigh.    
    
    
    iPhone 5 was too spooky thin. Otterbox is the cure.    
    
    
    Hey @UseClear, feat req: I want to copy a block of text (an email with the grocery list) and autosplit it into list items when pasting.    
    
    
    @zephoria that doesn't sound good.    
    
    
    @haroldfeld it's the flip side of its ok to shoot rockets at people if they're not very accurate.    
    
    
    Hamas pro tip: agree to cease fire, but don't actually cease. http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-4310174,00.html …    
    
    
    @haroldfeld, xkcd is calling for you... http://bit.ly/UOsw1Z     
    
    
    @UseClear that just rocks. Thx!    
    
    
    DayOne keeps losing entries. Not good for a journal app.    
    
    
    I last did C++ in the prior millenium. What's the best starting point to get back up to speed?    
    
    
    Lots of folks using classifiers as black boxes. Folks, there are snapping turtles in those boxes. #ymmv    
    
    
    @junklight and start from...? I have a much thumbed but very dusty 2nd ed Stroustrup, and that's all.    
    
    
    @orr971 unsure why I should be optimistic about remote backups when the app loses data on local storage.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase @arjenpdevries what about collection bias?    
    
    
    They need a Pulitzer for p0wning so they can give it to the Onion.    
    
    
    @hyheng still investigating, unfortunately.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase You can tell me or Ellen or Lori about broken input.gz links on the TREC website, and we'll fix them.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase What do you think about systems that line up horizontally? vertically? Gets to sensitivity of the method.    
    
    
    @msbernst and you can amortize the hosting cost over lots of papers.    
    
    
    Martha's First Law of Power Laws: Everything is linear, when graphed log-log with a fat magic marker.    
    
    
    @DelFest when will the lineup be announced?    
    
    
    Very nice meeting of the DC area IR Experts (DIRE) today. Thanks @BenCarterette and Hagit Shatkay and Dawn Lawrie!    
    
    
    @etzioni @greglinden I think we can do it if we all give 110%.    
    
    
    @hyheng Give it a try now, it should be working!    
    
    
    @dtunkelang nice quickie on evaluation, but actually doesn't help the reader understand relevance...    
    
    
    @delsweil @dtunkelang and on the flip side, the simplifications and tradeoffs made to make it measurable.    
    
    
    Practical machine learning tricks from the KDD 2011 best industry paper http://prsm.tc/DmCOdp  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @ej I see many of the usual suspects. Hope you're having fun!    
    
    
    @jussikarlgren @dtunkelang unsure how to implement that for a researcher outside a large-scale search company.    
    
    
    @delsweil @RichardDawkins is disappoint.    
    
    
    ....l..íí    
    
    
    @iadh if only we had some technology that could learn your preferences from examples.    
    
    
    @iadh the hardest part is actually the interface for tracking msgs and managing misclassifications.    
    
    
    @mattcutts yeah, aren't eigenvectors just the sh:t. I was so happy the day Google invented them.    
    
    
    ....l.ííí    
    
    
    @yvolkovich who needs FB? :)    
    
    
    It's probably preliminary to say this before I even write much code in it, but Pythonista is a reason to own an iPad all on its own.    
    
    
    @metzlerd do computational advertising faculty need to bring in their own funding, and can they do it however they might like to?    
    
    
    ...líííí    
    
    
    Free tip for email spammers: spam in languages I don't speak is not entertaining, is easily classed as spam, and the conversion rate stinks.    
    
    
    @cshirky every media outlet (well, papers, tv, radio, and the like) fits that description.    
    
    
    @atpassos_ml when you can snatch the decision boundary from my hand, it will be time for you to leave.    
    
    
    ...ílíííí    
    
    
    @danbri VLC2, a research coll from CSIRO, is from '97: http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.61.7206&rep=rep1&type=pdf …    
    
    
    Home, sick. Reduced to reading @haroldfeld's voluminous tweets on #WCIT.    
    
    
    @bederson how about Emacs key bindings?    
    
    
    @johnbreslin @chrisdiehl and we have @lintool working on the next level of scale.    
    
    
    $perl = 25. Thanks, Larry.    
    
    
    @abdur yeah, but Higgs Boson?    
    
    
    @iadh the tricky part is building your own LHC. Multi-kajillion dollar science is hard to replicate.    
    
    
    @hmason alias mroe    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sign up to come participate in TREC 2013: http://trec.nist.gov/pubs/call2013.html …    
    
    
    Looks like a quiet week here next week, finally!  Anyone want to write a SIGIR paper?    
    
    
    @mdreid We say, "In theory, theory and practice are the same, but in practice, they're different."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl what, like Clear Channel?  That's why radio died.    
    
    
    @mdreid I know the quote, but heck if I can pronounce that name.    
    
    
    Hey @useclear, what happened to the shake gesture to paste a bunch of things as a list?!? #killerfeatureiskilled    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl eagerly awaiting Tarantino's new Al-Qudsploitation genre flick.    
    
    
    Got invited to a Dagstuhl seminar. Any experiences out there?    
    
    
    @ted_dunning mind if I ask how quantifiable "amazing" is? What sort of task does this approach work well for?    
    
    
    @hmason @ted_dunning we've found simple logistic regression works well for spam detection in email and web pages.    
    
    
    Turns out the new Tarantino movie isn't at all about Python web frameworks.    
    
    
    @ted_dunning Cool. Cite? Define "interesting"?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries are you shilling for the organizers?    
    
    
    @otisg Is that good? Was thinking of diving into 4.0 as a major rewrite opportunity for our system. Best to wait?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries @peter_r_bailey @tetsuyasakai Good grief it sounds like we can just hold it on Twitter.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas @arjenpdevries @peter_r_bailey @tetsuyasakai @CharlotteHase looks like they invited all the usual suspects.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte my law of unsupported claims: pls show the data.    
    
    
    Wow. http://www.gatestoneinstitute.org/3517/redacted-iraqi-jews … via @haroldfeld    
    
    
    @bkeegan @msbernst can I play it back using a camera phone, if the resolution is high enough?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I pinged Nicola on that question... lots of evaluation topics on that program.    
    
    
    Current playlist: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/How_the_West_Was_Won_(Led_Zeppelin_album) …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai an intro to IR evaluation; history, methods, tricks, pitfalls. I'll need P+R but otherwise, metrics are yours. ;-)    
    
    
    Teaching someone the wonders of 'find | cat | tr | sort | uniq | wc' as NLP Pipeline 1.0.  #iloveunix    
    
    
    Sing it, @BloombergView. MT U.S. Internet Users Pay More for Slower Service http://bloom.bg/UbB9UM  (via @EdwardTufte)    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I'll listen.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai does not après ski usually involve alcohol?    
    
    
    @MarthaBunton @lljohnston Today's WaPo article doesn't make the researcher access we've been talking about sound like it'll happen. Sad.    
    
    
    @msbernst all the easy scans and non-typos are done. It's hit the global minimum.    
    
    
    @hmason I'm pretty disappointed with that article. If I'd known it was just to complain at Twitter, I'd not have agreed to be interviewed.    
    
    
    @djoerd actually, I don't think Twitter's a bad guy at all. Unhappy? They should give you your money back.    
    
    
    Strongly considering posting my actual interview responses as comments to this. http://www.buzzfeed.com/nostrich/how-twitter-gets-in-the-way-of-research …    
    
    
    @JamesMcMinn go for it. Feel free to email me if you want advice on this.    
    
    
    @nostrich Thinking this morning more about how to comment in a way that starts the discussion you want -- how to get data, what kinds.    
    
    
    I thought Katherine Heigl would be perfect for defense chief...    
    
    
    My call is very important to you, but apparently not important enough to up-staff the call center.    
    
    
    A nice summary of Python frameworks for Hadoop, from Cloudera: http://bit.ly/UYGmSK     
    
    
    @bradfordcross still waiting for my Java-powered garbage compactor.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl lots of good papers at SIGIR on this over the past few years.    
    
    
    @mdreid "When I was your age, the phones were so old they couldn't make calls, just take pictures."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl anecdote is a poor substitute for experiment.    
    
    
    Very nice looking tool, haven't tried it yet but I might. http://mcb.berkeley.edu/labs/zusman/dave/svg2key/ …    
    
    
    Any folks at #nistcloud this week who want to talk web, social media, text and video data for research, come find me. We have a booth.    
    
    
    @mrflip when are you turning up at NIST this week?    
    
    
    Making evil plans for TREC KBA.    
    
    
    I wish it were possible to actually find information on FB.    
    
    
    Let me put it another way. FB's current search is so useless, their announcement fills me with joy. It would be hard to not improve things.    
    
    
    @breyten my friends pass along links and stories all the time which are impossible to recover two weeks later. Re-finding in FB is big.    
    
    
    Vint Cerf speaking this morning at NIST #nistcloud    
    
    
    Cerf compares cloud interoperability to the days of DECNET and SNA. Imagine when we have the equivalent of TCP/IP among clouds.    
    
    
    Cerf: MOOCs invert the classroom. watch the lecture on your own, come to class to solve problems. Powerful idea.    
    
    
    @fjsteele doesn't work so hot for running joint computation across the walls.    
    
    
    I think the NRA is saying they want armed federal agents at every school. Unsure the 2nd amendment will help an insurrection at that point.    
    
    
    Data-driven dating. I think I'm in love. http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887323374504578217973101313736.html …    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon I'm over it.  I was only in love with her model.    
    
    
    URL is http://www.iaa-archives.org.il/ . MT @Arquivistica Israel Antiquities digitalizes archives http://bit.ly/10BxmZ8  cc @lljohnston    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @Arquivistica @lljohnston Also worst search interface ever.  Perhaps it dates from the Mandate era.    
    
    
    @hmason also pls @horse_ebookbookgoose, taking snippets from reviews.    
    
    
    http://blog.archive.org/2013/01/20/bulk-downloading-aaron-swartz-and-terms-of-service/ … by @brewster_kahle    
    
    
    Bought a book on google play. Clicked 'download PDF'. Got an ACSM file pointing to a document. #wtf how do I get the PDF I paid for?    
    
    
    Also Google Play just stinks as a book reader for PDF, both in Chrome and in their app.    
    
    
    So cannot decide if this ebook drm shit is Googles fault, adobes fault, or Morgan Claypool's fault.    
    
    
    Bought a book. Can't read it. The new illiteracy. #drm    
    
    
    Ok, now my question is, how do I download and then remove the DRM from a book which I have bought, given its ACSM key file?    
    
    
    Soln: 1) use Adobe DigEd to get the encrypted PDF. 2) pip install pycrypto. 3) two scripts from http://thescienceofdestruction.wordpress.com/2011/08/10/downloading-and-decrypting-adobe-adept-drm-protected-ebooks-on-linux/ …. Gaaah, done.    
    
    
    Unsure where to report general suckage with Google Books. That was way too much hacking needed for fair use.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai hang in there, I see clear skies in your future.    
    
    
    Google writeup on multi-armed bandits. http://analytics.blogspot.com/2013/01/multi-armed-bandit-experiments.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=linkedin …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl I think there's an NLP-completeness proof that any such program is equivalent to dissociated-text.    
    
    
    Spent the day hacking, or, "Why Ian Can't Program". #embarrasing    
    
    
    If we got rid of all the crappy travel websites there would be a lot more room on the net for cat videos. Just sayin'    
    
    
    Wondering about the effects of inhaling airborne pulverized road salt.    
    
    
    @bemikelive I was going to write "On the use of the word 'on' to lead SIGIR paper titles."    
    
    
    Need a Mail.app extension that sees the word "attached" in an outgoing email, without an attachment, and confirms the send. #gmailmylifepls    
    
    
    @lljohnston Nope, @VeryGrumpyCat would never say "sorry".    
    
    
    I was feeling left out because I never knew Aaron Swartz. But, hey, I did know David LaMacchia. http://swartz-review.mit.edu/question/what-questions-should-mit-be-asking-stage-aaron-swartz-review/response/what-if-anything-did …    
    
    
    I mean, we were in like first grade, but he was my first geek buddy. Getting his big brother off the Apple ][+ was impossible.    
    
    
    Just btw, David and Brian had an Apple, and went to MIT. I had a Timex Sinclair 1000, and went to UMBC. There you go.    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr you rock. Pinging Mark to see if he has that old code.    
    
    
    @stewhir Outlook is so not the solution.  Outlook is the precipitate.    
    
    
    @kegill somewhat better coverage at http://www.latimes.com/news/world/worldnow/la-fg-israeli-health-authorities-issue-guidelines-on-controversial-birthcontrol-shots-20130128,0,7037665.story …    
    
    
    Putting the finishing touches on a TREC adhoc evaluation demo with Lucene 4.1, for my PROMISE class. Stay tuned for github link.    
    
    
    A demo on Cranfield-style IR evaluation, using Lucene and TREC data: https://github.com/isoboroff/trec-demo …. Goes with a class I'll be giving next week.    
    
    
    @lintool a much nicer demo of a much richer system, I should put a link to it.    
    
    
    @gsingers let me know if this is useful or not: https://github.com/isoboroff/trec-demo …    
    
    
    @gilgul @PhilipMeyer4 s/computational/all/    
    
    
    Aiiigh my feed, it's full of pr0n #sexi2013 #academicsgonewild    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai sorry we didn't get more time to hang out. Safe trip home!    
    
    
    Awesome talks today from @elunca and Peter Mika.  These week-long schools are better for the teachers than the students.    
    
    
    Finishing up a wonderful week of teaching, talking, learning, and a little skiing in Bressanone. Thx to PROMISE and to all who attended.    
    
    
    Article from @cshirky on MOOCs and the current sea change coming at universities. 
http://lnkd.in/8SnqEs     
    
    
    @sinanaral Funny, I can't find the job announcement on LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Acclimatizing to the US after spending the week in Italy. Coffee from DD done, next stop NIST cafeteria. #coffee #fail    
    
    
    @jaykreps I would so live for the puzzler.    
    
    
    Clueweb12 is in the house. As long as I don't open the box it can't consume all my time...    
    
    
    #icwsm2013 is up over 500 abstract submissions. Thanks, friends!    
    
    
    @milesosborne should open tonight.    
    
    
    @haroldfeld in fact without the human genome there would be no jobs at all.  Unless it would be like the Matrix.    
    
    
    Adding 'pun quality' field to #icwsm2013 review form.    
    
    
    @lintool you are truly on a roll. Congrats.    
    
    
    TREC 2013 microblog collection is at 75M tweets and counting.    
    
    
    TREC 2013 datasets are coming in the door.  The new ClueWeb collection (for use in the web, sessions, and context tracks) has arrived on my…    
    
    
    @milesosborne it's at the limit of downloadable, with a flock of ec2 instances. We are trying a new model this year, eval as a svc.    
    
    
    Spent some time this week playing with http://sharelatex.com .  It's a nice idea, but the editor itself is useless for actual writing.    
    
    
    SIGIR tutorial proposal submitted.    
    
    
    #icwsm2013 has a serious embarrassment of riches problem this year. We were not ready to grow this fast!    
    
    
    @sharelatex I'm used to writing LaTeX in Emacs. Kind of a shock to have an editor without even find/replace. Where to begin?    
    
    
    @sharelatex you might never be as powerful as Emacs, but you could strive  to be as documented.    
    
    
    The TREC 2013 welcome message has gone out, officially beginning the TREC season. To participate, pls sign up at http://trec.nist.gov/     
    
    
    Anyone out there used http://textrazor.com  for more than just playing yet? Interested in experiences with large volumes of messy text.    
    
    
    rpy2 is amazing. I predict I will get just as frustrated with it as I do with native R. #perfecttranslationofuserexperience    
    
    
    Aiming for inbox O(log n)    
    
    
    Hey @wetatvfm, someone came to our door tonight soliciting donations. For real?    
    
    
    @dpatil I've seen folks pull rabbits out of hats too. It's more than data, and its more than "something out of it."    
    
    
    @tjake In my locale, "defenestrate" is to remove WIndows, either by reinstalling with Linux or replacing them with Macs.    
    
    
    Anyone Jewish heading for @DelFest? Thinking about camping for shabbos.    
    
    
    @carlyeks @tjake Don't blame the hardware for software problems.    
    
    
    I'm _still_ disappointed that http://drive.google.com/  doesn't take me to a self-driving car webcam. #iwaspromisedselfdrivingcarsdammit    
    
    
    @lljohnston @agrotke and a pony.    
    
    
    @hmason at job?    
    
    
    @xamat at least, keeping read status on the client and hiding them behind many cliches or taps!    
    
    
    @kansandhaus If New York is the center of the universe, International New York is ... bigger?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai some of those I am reviewing have not been withdrawn quickly enough...    
    
    
    Looking for an array-based suffix tree impl in Java.    
    
    
    Or, are literal RE string searches (REs without operators) faster than String.indexOf()? After how many searches?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff one answer:  https://sites.google.com/site/yuta256/sais …    
    
    
    i can haz good paper to review?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries uh dude that was almost a year ago.    
    
    
    When USAToday leads a story with "Turns out there's a cool use for trigonometry" I just want to punch someone. http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/02/26/meteor-russia-apollo-space/1948673/ …    
    
    
    The USA Today is like those jocks I went to high school with.    
    
    
    If you're sitting in your car reading your tablet over 4G about tracking meteors using webcams, and your only reaction is "MATH COOL DUH" ..    
    
    
    </tweetrant>    
    
    
    May have to resort to actually writing my own data structures. Most Java folks seem to have forgotten how. I know I'm rusty.    
    
    
    I have a CentOS 5 box which keeps changing /dev/null to a regular file. Anyone seen this and know the culprit?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff seems to be caused by using the mysql cmd as root...    
    
    
    @seamless says, "We didn't find any matches for the keyword 'kosher', [how about these non-kosher restaurants?]" Oh, well.    
    
    
    @djoerd it's definitely mysql(1), gonna strace that sucker.    
    
    
    So pleased that 'shit*says' works as a people query on Twitter. Good job @ruslansv et al.    
    
    
    @djoerd that bug thread is a riot.    
    
    
    Sometimes you just have to lock the door and hack for an hour to make the rest of the day approachable.    
    
    
    Done reviewing for SIGIR. My stack was decidedly below the expected value of the historical acceptance rate. Ah well.    
    
    
    @LeonDerczynski maybe. I've spent lots of time thinking about what the community reqs are to make a PVLDB happen, in the ctxt of SIGIR...    
    
    
    Looking for the tumblr or reddit captioning pictures of Dennis Rodman and Kim Jong-Eun.    
    
    
    The four C's of telecommuting: coffee, cats, couch, and code.    
    
    
    Reading lit on wrapper induction and trying to map it to current ML software packages. I so need to go back to school.    
    
    
    @JeffD classics from the 90s & early 00s. I don't have a hard extraction problem, just looking for the right learning model 4 pat selection    
    
    
    @nealrichter we have a twitter crawler for sharing tweets by reference. Trying to get it to write itself from the gardenhose feed.    
    
    
    I have a new business plan to enable very expensive, convenient access to bad coffee.    
    
    
    @peter_r_bailey except on twitter. where it's ok. to write in sentence fragments. and all lower case an stuff.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte corollary to the standard rule that bureaucracy is monotonically nondecreasing.    
    
    
    Coming up for air after spending the day training TREC KBA assessors.    
    
    
    Impressed by Woosh (https://pypi.python.org/pypi/Whoosh ). Way too heavy for what I need right now, but a most impressive API.    
    
    
    Snowquester has devolved into a slush fund exercise.    
    
    
    @leifos yes, also lacks an in-memory index. I needed something small and quick and easy, Woosh had one.    
    
    
    Makes me want to write something  MT “@textons: LaTeX document style files in­spired @EdwardTufte http://www.ctan.org/tex-archive/macros/latex/contrib/tufte-latex …”    
    
    
    Every time a web application supports Emacs keybindings in text boxes, an angel gets its wings.    
    
    
    @nancybaym If its the P-Funk Mothership my resume is in your email.    
    
    
    @kegill but if they hasn't given that money to pre-K etc, no one would have been able to go.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas @jteevan leaps-tall-buildings-in-a-single-bound?    
    
    
    @mounialalmas I shall endorse you for kicking ass.    
    
    
    @jteevan for putting 36 hours into every day.    
    
    
    EasyChair has crossed all wires. I'd like to think we #icwsm broke it but we're just not that big.    
    
    
    @kegill Fed funding of education goes beyond loans and grants to college students... from Dept of Ed to NSF, NIH, and DARPA.    
    
    
    @abdur @lintool @gilad it turns out that @SottedReviewer has you all beat to the punch.    
    
    
    Damn meetings, all the good Pope jokes have already been told.    
    
    
    Google docs needs git blame.  That is all.    
    
    
    @hmason unhappy    
    
    
    When I pulled up Google Reader, a dialog informed me that it's shutting down 7/1.  Only button to press said "Ok".  It wasn't.    
    
    
    XLS-complete: (adj) when the data comes in Excel format, but Excel is useless for analyzing it, and it's too big to port. See EasyChair.    
    
    
    Cool tweets from #NSFTask. Also nice to see Slideshare previews in-line.    
    
    
    Note to reviewers: "Nominate for best paper" != "Was this the best paper among the crap we made you read?"    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG part of the XLSC class is that the XLS spreadsheet is to honking huge to load in any other spreadsheet program.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase I prefer to try and identify the one paper everyone at the conference should really hear.    
    
    
    @lintool you sir are a MacBook Pro.    
    
    
    @sottedreviewer is not funny if you're the PC chair.  Just sayin.    
    
    
    Srsly, @icwsm is not fooling. Monday for real.    
    
    
    "It has been said that EasyChair is the worst conference platform except all the others that have been tried." - Sir Winston Churchill    
    
    
    @anildash maybe Apple's telling you that you need to get out of the city a bit.    
    
    
    The Maccabeats do Les Mis for Passover: http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?v=qmthKpnTHYQ&desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DqmthKpnTHYQ …    
    
    
    Neil Fraser on CS education in Vietnam: http://neil.fraser.name/news/2013/03/16/ … (via @yana) Observations on what they learn and helping CS in dev.countries    
    
    
    Apparently, always leaving off promised attachments from emails is *not* called Attachment Disorder.    
    
    
    @ggref actually not yet, see tweets from @carlzimmer    
    
    
    In honor of news about cable bundling agreements, listening to UHF by Weird Al    
    
    
    @nancybaym you didn't reply, "the princess is in another castle"?!    
    
    
    The SIGMOD blog wishes for more realistic 'big data' datasets... Data like TREC.    
    
    
    Thanks Mounia for not forgetting the link like I did. http://lnkd.in/e9Px7Q     
    
    
    @EdwardTufte pretty, but I'm unsure what data you're visualizing. What questions should I ask of that viz?    
    
    
    World's longest traceroute: I don't always block ICMP, but when I do, I like to leave you hanging.    
    
    
    Hey @stringdusters, beginning mando player here. Got sheet music or other tips for Golden Ticket? One of my all time faves.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield you can never play too many musical instruments, unless you're trying to do it all at once.    
    
    
    @leifos user thinks, "aha, I found a relevant document, maybe I can get out of the fMRI machine now."    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald congrats!    
    
    
    @ccb @hmason watch that usage agreement!    
    
    
    Hello world, back online after Passover.    
    
    
    @mdreid Dunno about math, but all of science rests on the Central Limit Theorem ;-)    
    
    
    @josh_wills fer pete's sake, my cat is a better software engineer than any statistician.    
    
    
    @jteevan Just to make it a proper meme... http://qkme.me/3tpsdm     
    
    
    @jteevan if only we could turn this into a paper.  Hmm... #sigir2014    
    
    
    @djoerd @tetsuyasakai @mounialalmas @arjenpdevries Osu!    
    
    
    Well, shoot, there goes this weekend. http://www.flickr.com/photos/kenfagerdotcom/6496851849/in/pool-41224503@N00/ …    
    
    
    @tjake You should try it in parallel next time if you want that breakage to really scale.    
    
    
    @xamat my faves start the same way but just straight out ask for leads.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @xamat yeah, sad but that great tip on a gig in Nigeria just didn't come together for me.    
    
    
    Have very nearly raised the cluster from the dead. About to commence serious ClueWeb and Tweets2013 crunching.    
    
    
    service hadoop-lead-guitar strat    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog program chairs gotta chair.    
    
    
    @John4man I hope not. When I'm not at work it's important to me to be not working.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte The moral of that article is really the cornerstone of science: if you think you know what's going on, think again.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas did you include information on student travel grants?  If not I will email you details.    
    
    
    Heard via Facebook that @eugeneAgichtein is ok. Slowly getting notifications from other #boston friends.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl another take: tracking emerging events is hard even for lots of expert humans working in parallel. Cc DARPA et al pls.    
    
    
    Kudos to @lintool for 'hosting' the TREC microblog hackfest this morning.    
    
    
    My Jawbone Icon survived a trip through the laundry.  Didn't see that capability in any of the reviews...    
    
    
    @kansandhaus not if you use a framework that bangs your head against a brick wall for you.    
    
    
    Sometimes after hours of telecons, spreadsheets, & mtgs, I gotta head for the machine room with a screwdriver and reclaim some humanity.    
    
    
    My tutorial on building IR test collections has been accepted for #SIGIR2013! Looking forward to it.    
    
    
    I'll be giving a full-day tutorial on building IR test collections at SIGIR 2013 in Dublin. The course is especially targeted towards grad …    
    
    
    Hey @tlipcon, I think i'm seeing HADOOP-8568 trying to spin up HBase under CDH4.2. Can u help me? cc @cloudera    
    
    
    @kestelyn @tlipcon @cloudera Will do, thanks!    
    
    
    @kestelyn I didn't pay for anything, so I didn't expect more than a mailing list (or a DM from @tlipcon ;-). Thx!    
    
    
    @kansandhaus @smyles You should look to the experience of the shogun in Edo-period Japan: very agile, good for eliminating project waste.    
    
    
    @delsweil @CharlotteHase Then we'll see ye in Dublin.    
    
    
    @kansandhaus clan    
    
    
    @kansandhaus finally all those back issues of Lone Wolf and Cub are paying off.    
    
    
    @agrotke If by "Silver Spring" you mean the downtown area (inside the beltway), drop me a DM when you get settled!    
    
    
    Got my tix for @DelFest, really looking forward to that!    
    
    
    @gilad that's so 00s. I dig the Eastern European translation mills pimping for pagerank. No, do not want Slavic trans of my site, thxbye.    
    
    
    Today's project: ClueWeb12 + Hadoop + Solr. I don't work weekends but my cluster does.    
    
    
    Pushing ClueWeb12 into Solr at about 1000 pages/min... any tips on making it faster? (1/2)    
    
    
    I'm running 6 shard servers and 22 Hadoop mappers feeding the shards using SolrCloud, commit'ing when the mapper completes.    
    
    
    Correction, that should read 1000-1200 pages/second.    
    
    
    @codeslack The first part is easy, b/c in Lucene 4, IndexWriters are append-only, so you can write indexes into HDFS.    
    
    
    @djoerd how's the interactive query latency?    
    
    
    Omg my timeline, it's full of #chi2013    
    
    
    Solr tip: to speed up indexing through a CloudSolrServer, multithread your document extraction and server.add() call.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield I tried to read your tweet, buJava: Out of heap space.    
    
    
    This is why you should follow @lintool, and read (almost) everything he writes: map-reduce and monoids – http://arxiv.org/abs/1304.7544     
    
    
    @djoerd That's throughput, not latency. I read the docs online and the API is for batch experiments, but I need interactive search.    
    
    
    @djoerd yeah, query latencies of more than a second make for very crabby TREC assessors.    
    
    
    @djoerd They explore the collection during topic development, both to invent them and to verify that test topics are appropriate.    
    
    
    @gsingers wish I were there. Scaling to 1B is tricky enough.    
    
    
    Does anyone know how to catch Hadoop tasks that fail due to heap full, and not mark them "fails", but just output their split and move on?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff state if the art solution is to just break into smaller jobs. I thought that was what map reduce was for.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I mean, it's big data. I don't actually care about any particular small part if it.    
    
    
    @agrotke I'll check my old floppies.    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon My version: if you're the smartest person in the room, you're in the wrong room.    
    
    
    Hey @twitter, thanks for storing DM read flags on the client, so I can re-read my mail on all my machines.    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon home or work? Level of support? Budget?    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon 10-15TB of commodity hard drives is half your budget. Many good cheapie boxes in that range tho.    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon no, the storage I've bought is a step or two up from where you are looking. Sry!    
    
    
    Contrary to the SIGIR 2013 program just posted, I will not be giving a tutorial about Matt Crane (U Otago), but rather on test collections.    
    
    
    In search of a cunning plan to get to SPIRE 2013 in Jerusalem.    
    
    
    After N years in gov't, bureaucracy _still_ makes me say "dafuq?!" every time I run into it.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai Maybe I was unclear, I'm happy to also give a tutorial about Matt, especially if Andrew Trotman helps out.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @jteevan They say, 'the unexamined life is not worth living.'  You'd have to ask him, I guess ;-)    
    
    
    SolrCloud cluster maxing out at 150M docs. I love deadlines.    
    
    
    My hadoop cluster is taunting me.    
    
    
    @otisg regarding walking directories to find cores: can i stitch together independent cores built w/ same schema into a single SolrCloud?    
    
    
    Pro Solr tip of the day: when your indexer chokes around 200M docs, make sure u didn't leave a shard in your home dir over NFS. #iamanidiot    
    
    
    @diakoff depends on what you mean by 'performance'. Also what you mean by XML.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wake me when we have printable medicine.    
    
    
    @hmason sometimes after you've been trapped in NetHack for just too long, the only rational response is :q!    
    
    
    @bde Normalize all klout scores by klout_score(horse_ebooks)    
    
    
    Know that when you ask @gsingers a good question, you get a good answer: http://searchhub.org/2013/05/09/update-accessing-words-around-a-positional-match-in-lucene-4/ …    
    
    
    If that Google Glass thing takes off, I'm betting on an Apple monocle called 'iPatch'.    
    
    
    @Caterina at least they're relevant. I've never had LI make a relevant job recommendation for me.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie the geo mean is equal to the arithmetic mean of the log of the values. It's a data cleaning method, essentially.    
    
    
    Some days I miss that good old "Segmentation fault, core dumped."    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG lol, no, Java NPEs without stack traces.    
    
    
    @carlzimmer I hope you mean "facial"!    
    
    
    @carlzimmer I should click through your links more often. I thought my old office had patented fecal transplants via management chain.    
    
    
    "Kindly bare with ACM and Sheridan as the new Open Access procedures are all implemented and the kinks worked out." #tooopenaccess    
    
    
    It used to be that installing Windows was something that happened to other people.    
    
    
    The internet wins again: digitized lessons from Jethro Burns (d.1989). http://www.robcoleman.com/jethro/index.html …    
    
    
    @mattcutts very cool. Would love to hear about your metrics. Might there be a chance of a labeled spam URL dataset?    
    
    
    @mattcutts there are old collections from the AIRweb conferences. it'd be neat to e.g. label a subset of ClueWeb12 or OpenCrawl.    
    
    
    @bradfordcross setting up the order on http://Bricklink.com  right now!    
    
    
    @mattcutts We are working on a web spam project. Can you DM me an email address so I can ask a couple deeper questions? #Thx*10^6    
    
    
    Reading about pump.io.    
    
    
    That feeling when you have a song in your head, but iTunes doesn't have the album.    
    
    
    @eytanadar I am inspired to make one that says, "Abort, retry, ignore?"    
    
    
    @PatParslow no after hearing The Safety Dance in a gas station, I really need to listen to all of Pop Goes The World.    
    
    
    @PatParslow forgot to add #firstworldproblems I guess.    
    
    
    @bradfordcross +1    
    
    
    When they take Reader down I'm just going to use the version in the Google Cache.    
    
    
    @haroldfeld headline: "Autocrat overthrown by cats in tubes."    
    
    
    Bulk-loaded HBase right up to the fall-over point.  Wow, not graceful.    
    
    
    HBase tip: 'disable'ing a table makes it inaccessible, but all your regions are still there. You can swap tables in and out.    
    
    
    @jteevan omg you are Alex Doonesbury!    
    
    
    Bootstrappin like a boss    
    
    
    @ezraklein Kinda wish they'd included an "Is this news?" question. Because it's olds.    
    
    
    I wonder why Feds traveling on official passports aren't automatically in TSA Pre. #wtf    
    
    
    @elad1 And for that we have the House Gov't Oversight committee.    
    
    
    @ezraklein They should pull in the government oversight committee.  They were all over that squirting fish thing.    
    
    
    Too much NSA news for you? Here is a video of a cockatiel whistling the theme from My Neighbor Totoro. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=O7D-1RG-VRk# …!    
    
    
    Strongly recommend folks skip the future "OS X Wizards" release. #Apple #cantwin    
    
    
    @lljohnston Actually using massive tape archives is not a new problem... apparently no one wants to solve it!    
    
    
    I can't decide if I want a new Mac Pro because I want to fit my G4 Cube innards inside, or if I want a Mac Pro inside my G4 Cube housing.    
    
    
    WaPo nails it (http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/dana-milbank-edward-snowdens-nsa-leaks-are-the-backlash-of-too-much-secrecy/2013/06/10/eddb4462-d215-11e2-a73e-826d299ff459_story.html?hpid=z2 …) and the nation yawns (http://www.people-press.org/2013/06/10/majority-views-nsa-phone-tracking-as-acceptable-anti-terror-tactic/ …)    
    
    
    @msbernst Am going to use that to start a conf, Justin Zobel's program to write random papers, and that other thing to do random talks.    
    
    
    @bederson no, actually, the under-the-hood OS updates to improve battery life are the lead feature.    
    
    
    @hmason kind of. Feel free to email me with questions.    
    
    
    @bederson definitely a top feature list for the rest of us.    
    
    
    Draw random lines from huge files: https://gist.github.com/isoboroff/5775326 …    
    
    
    @gsingers just wait for that first core dump.    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge @gsingers yeah but I don't need the stack trace on those.    
    
    
    http://analytics.twitter.com  timeline activity is just too fun.  Way to go guys.    
    
    
    Heading to NTCIR in Tokyo.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @arjenpdevries David Carmel, fusing results from multiple queries.    
    
    
    Omg between @haroldfeld and @ezraklein my feed is full of wonk this morning. C'mon geeks bail me out!    
    
    
    @abdur  btw was going to visit Hombu dojo so I could tweet you from there but was afraid for personal safety.    
    
    
    @abdur nevertheless tweeting on the mat probably not ok.    
    
    
    Alon Halevy's worldwide coffee recommendations. http://www.macchiatone.com/alon-s-favorite-cafes …    
    
    
    Boston is the place to be in 2013 for social media conferences, with http://icwsm.org  in July and http://cosn.acm.org  in the fall.    
    
    
    Jean Tague shout out! #ntcir10    
    
    
    Having trouble focusing on track overviews after @claclarke filled my brain with time-biased gain. #ntcir10    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai @claclarke @IR_oldie @fdiaz_msr aaayii! We ended up in palaceside, tomorrow we shall make bigger plans.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie thx this is a great compact resource. I wish I'd written it.    
    
    
    Trying to understand CRF, structured perceptron, structured SVM, and good old HMM. Feels like I'm at a costume party.    
    
    
    Granted I'm an idiot about machine learning, in that the papers make no sense to me unless I implement it.    
    
    
    Pythonista (Python for iOS) + GitHub gists = awesome.
 http://ipad.appstorm.net/how-to/utilities/pythonista-101-the-scripting-community/ …    
    
    
    Got stomped by @IR_oldie at darts.    
    
    
    @flaviomartins write to Ellen Voorhees, trec at nist dot gov.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai 0CLICK.    
    
    
    #ntcir10 is winding down. About to give a quick tour of TREC and TAC.    
    
    
    @wewebber nicely written. Or, as we tell the students, don't train on the test set.    
    
    
    @kegill there's salary and fully-loaded FTE cost. Isn't it the same at university?    
    
    
    @kegill article on how a contractor is more expensive than the president. It's miscounting lots of things.    
    
    
    Since no one keeps track of who answered their surveys, I've decided not to answer surveys so that I don't have to keep track it.    
    
    
    Federal employee viewpoint survey, I'm looking at you, and not with my happy face.    
    
    
    @kegill there're overheads, then there's over-your-heads.    
    
    
    @iadh That can't be Glasgow, too much sunshine. I'm sure you're keeping the room dark so no one freaks out. ;-)    
    
    
    @shaunconnolly @acmurthy now all you need is a Big Honking USB Hub.    
    
    
    Don't push my stack, bro!    
    
    
    From my anti-social-media spouse. pic.twitter.com/sd2ALG73JR    
    
    
    @delsweil I tried Google Translate and it was no help.    
    
    
    @adruin what paper is that from? Interested in how search ability and effectiveness are measured...    
    
    
    Trackpad died, out of batteries, reduced to using an old Mighty Mouse with a bum scroll ball. #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    @OrenTsur What's the plan?    
    
    
    @OrenTsur uh, this dissertation you turned in. DId I lose context by switching languages?    
    
    
    @OrenTsur very good for you!    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai oh you thought you could get away, didn't you?    
    
    
    @haroldfeld wow, did someone in News World remember that the real story is NSA, and not Snowden?    
    
    
    @IR_oldie perhaps after waiting seven months for reviews, the author got fed up?    
    
    
    A library is conducive to work because it smells like books.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie tighten the timeline on all sides. "If we do not receive your revisions in two weeks we will assume the submission is withdrawn."    
    
    
    @anildash I wonder what is planned for all that data. Will it be available back to users?    
    
    
    @pomeranian99 @tjake "Dad, can I have X?" "No." "Mom, can I have X?" ...    
    
    
    Statistics jokes via Nathan Yau http://bit.ly/17HNrjt     
    
    
    @anildash I would pay good money to see George Lucas get some funk on.    
    
    
    @tlipcon is there a more technical site for CDH Search? Would like to read dirty details before 'yum install'ing and playing.    
    
    
    @tlipcon never mind, found it: http://www.cloudera.com/content/support/en/documentation/cloudera-search/cloudera-search-documentation-v1-latest.html …    
    
    
    @etzioni @mounialalmas waiting for the paper that mixes two models and degrades performance.    
    
    
    Looking forward to #ICWSM next week!
http://lnkd.in/3BT73U     
    
    
    @SalhaAlzahrani probably, but not currently scheduled. Materials will be on the web.    
    
    
    @WittedNote @mounialalmas I would have just said "wrong"...    
    
    
    Once again Flight Tracker Pro demonstrates its worth. JetBlue not winning at communication today.    
    
    
    Getting ready for #icwsm. Wonder who is here this year?    
    
    
    Best espresso close to Kresge Auditorium? #icwsm #caffeine    
    
    
    This auditorium has a pipe organ. #icwsm #thingspcchairsshouldreallybetoldaheadoftime    
    
    
    Shouldn't we actually measure the lack of robustness?  Otherwise we are injecting ourselves into the data again.  #icwsm    
    
    
    Attn @hmason ur missing a meme talk #icwsm    
    
    
    Nice point by first speaker about explainability of fit as opposed to goodness. #icwsm    
    
    
    I wonder about cascades that are more conversational, or about sharing a piece of information. #icwsm    
    
    
    The two cascades presented represent a shared experience but one that didn't matter to any depth>1 participants of the cascade.    
    
    
    Does your conference have its own cookies?  Didn't think so. #icwsm pic.twitter.com/CLG1qqoZaL    
    
    
    @arnabdotorg no, just sign this consent form please.    
    
    
    Are people good at estimating audience size?  Maybe people that don't self-censor are poor estimators. #icwsm    
    
    
    View from the #icwsm reception at the Media Lab pic.twitter.com/mv6DRJx5fT    
    
    
    @arnicas !! Did not at all mean to imply the forum was not useful. Wondering how users collect actual info if that's what they want.    
    
    
    @matthewhurst yeah where r u man, even your future employees are here. It's getting hard to keep making your excuses :-)    
    
    
    Yes, I am somewhat disappointed no one put anything on top of the MIT dome while we were here. #icwsm    
    
    
    BTW, need to reshare my all-time favorite tumblr, http://obamaischeckingyouremail.tumblr.com/  #icwsm    
    
    
    @natpoor BYO...    
    
    
    @milesosborne social spaces where the primary task is curation and gatekeeping are different in interesting ways. #icwsm    
    
    
    @milesosborne Note for example that Facebook fundamentally cannot be used for curation.    
    
    
    As someone who works specifically with older users I've been looking forward to this talk #icwsm    
    
    
    Really liked the friendship paradox talk, but wish for a stronger definition of information and interestingness. #icwsm    
    
    
    Not all tweets are equally informative or interesting. #icwsm    
    
    
    @natpoor not a podium, a lectern.  A podium would solve this problem.    
    
    
    @jvitak @alicetiara the first time you see it, it's nifty. By the third slide, it's not nifty anymore.  By the third talk, dramamine.    
    
    
    @lintool Paper about friendship paradox might have interesting implications for the effectiveness of lazyweb search.    
    
    
    @yvolkovich that was interesting but not informative.    
    
    
    @nicole_ellison's method slides: doin it rite. #icwsm    
    
    
    I would love to see comparisons to requests in different media. #icwsm cc @jvitak    
    
    
    Because you can't find it from the AAAI front page: the papers at the current #icwsm conference: http://www.aaai.org/ocs/index.php/ICWSM/ICWSM13/schedConf/presentations …    
    
    
    #icwsm dataset-request is very popular this week!  Please remember it is answered by a real person who may not reply right away.    
    
    
    @milesosborne #icwsm should be possible, stackoverflow makes dumps available.    
    
    
    @johndburger @milesosborne http://cheezburger.com/3061746176     
    
    
    #icwsm didn't xkcd show nicely how information overload is a constant for any stream size?    
    
    
    @nhodas http://xkcd.com/1227/  #icwsm    
    
    
    @KristinaLerman @nhodas "Everyone talks about the weather, but no one does anything about it."-Twain    
    
    
    Dynamics of novel hashtag adoption #icwsm cc @abdur    
    
    
    Yes in fact this is work-related. pic.twitter.com/c024RlBniV    
    
    
    If folks haven't settled on a watering hole yet, some of us are heading to Meadhall, feel free to join us #icwsm    
    
    
    Looks like I'm free in Boston on Thursday. Anyone want to meet up?    
    
    
    In the spirit of full disclosure, I saw @natpoor drinking a flavored coffee from Dunkin Donuts. #icwsm #calumny    
    
    
    @natpoor not that there's anything wrong with that.    
    
    
    Current status: http://imgflip.com/i/2cu9m     
    
    
    @jvitak there are two kinds of people in the world: people who think there are two kinds of people, and people who don't. #icwsm    
    
    
    #icwsm tightrope metaphor much more friendly than memes using stills from A Clockwork Orange.    
    
    
    This app looks like a lot of fun to play with.  http://www.textal.org/     
    
    
    @bkeegan @grammarnerd @syardi @smunson there's no git-blame, but http://thomas.loc.gov  is your friend.    
    
    
    #icwsm some people say more in two minutes than others say in twenty.    
    
    
    @smunson "At http://smunson.com , the tightrope balances you." :-)    
    
    
    Does someone have a "Grumpy Richard Dawkins" meme? #icwsm    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff pic.twitter.com/SsRT9wYKYs    
    
    
    Awesome viz talk by @wattenberg and @viegasf closing up #icwsm    
    
    
    @anildash s'ok, we all did.    
    
    
    @ncilla @arjenpdevries see, we're mad at the NSA because they're not paying.    
    
    
    Compiling references for my SIGIR tutorial.  I love Zotero, so far... we'll see about sharing and collaboration features.    
    
    
    @smeh Yeah a little wary of the Mendeley-Elsevier connection.  Probably I shouldn't worry, but I do.    
    
    
    @mendeley_com I have no illusions regarding the market value of my data. Elsevier is just not my favorite company.    
    
    
    I take back what I said about Textal. It might be fun to play with if it actually worked. #fail    
    
    
    Post from Yahoo! on how our understanding of search has really just started. No, the problem is not solved. 

http://lnkd.in/vz3Zfh     
    
    
    Bibliography for my SIGIR tutorial on building test collections: http://isoboroff.github.io/Test-Colls-Tutorial/biblio.html … Comments and additions appreciated!    
    
    
    @mounialalmas I did say suggestions appreciated. Want papers on how to build and whether it worked.    
    
    
    @elunca yes, all the materials will be online.    
    
    
    @richardm_ thanks for the leads!    
    
    
    @martinpotthast thanks!    
    
    
    Nice talk by James Sensenbrenner on the differences between relevant and responsive items, and who determines what. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=AHJX-Hhd_4w …    
    
    
    @ezraklein AND YOUR SOUL!!!    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai jiujitsu injury.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas This is exactly the kind of thing I wanted! IOU the beverage of your choice.    
    
    
    @martinpotthast Thanks for the leads from PAN, but the details on TC construction and validation in those papers is too small for me.    
    
    
    Version 2.0 of my SIGIR tutorial bibliography: https://isoboroff.github.io/Test-Colls-Tutorial/biblio.html …. Again, additions and corrections appreciated!    
    
    
    @tjake especially if it's self-training.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai that's just what a spam account would say cc @Horse_ebooks    
    
    
    @mark_riedl @eugeneAgichtein @Dan_Rowinski tell me when Postgres goes open beta.    
    
    
    World: watch out using Apple's cloud iWork beta, it has many bugs.    
    
    
    Apple: please let me report bugs, otherwise it's not a beta, it's a poor release plan.    
    
    
    beware TexLive updates arriving while trying to write a paper    
    
    
    Classic IR publications at http://sigir.org : http://www.sigir.org/museum/allcontents.html …    
    
    
    Includes gems by KSJ, van Rijsbergen, Salton, Keen, and more.    
    
    
    Correction for Tom Lehrer: if people can't communicate, they should switch mobile providers.    
    
    
    Toying with the idea of posting draft slides for my #sigir2013 tutorial on building test collections...    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG hmmm Slideshare plugin not working...    
    
    
    @matthewstoller @haroldfeld if Summers tweets his junk we are all doomed.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG they are really still lacking a lot of polishing.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG So I'm really saying "I'm not happy with these slides yet, maybe I should show them to everyone." I am an internet victim.    
    
    
    @mdreid Gerry Salton, a student of Aiken, was one of the founders of the CS department at Cornell in 1965.    
    
    
    My Macbook Air does indeed have a fan; to turn it on, use MS Lync.    
    
    
    @jteevan clean t-shirt?    
    
    
    @jteevan @elad1 I don't need to be banging my head on doorways any more than I already do!    
    
    
    @gilad added skill: adding skills    
    
    
    @SIGIR2013 @dtunkelang @techmatchmaker Next step: cafepress rush order.    
    
    
    Slides for my #sigir2013 tutorial on building test collections: https://isoboroff.github.io/Test-Colls-Tutorial/Tutorial-slides/ …    
    
    
    @guidozuc stay tuned, I hope to issue updates.    
    
    
    @jteevan won't be fancy, alas, the tux was at the cleaners.    
    
    
    @zephoria congratulations, welcome to the funnest journey yet.    
    
    
    @sigirf If you requested kosher food, you might not know that we do have it and it is yummy. Ask at banquet.    
    
    
    Best coffee near TCD, up Dawson St. @sigirf pic.twitter.com/joGjkGQrCs    
    
    
    @sigirf why is a magnifying glass the icon for search? Think about it.    
    
    
    @jteevan @sigirf another hint that tabs of ranked lists are not a very good organizational tool.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @sigirf next time you try to find a needle in a haystack, try doing it with either of those and let me know if that works.    
    
    
    Pro tip: itertools.permutations() for recovering a forgotten pass code sequence. You can try one per hour and not lose your place.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase lots of other alphabets and syllabaries are available. I propose katakana should be next.    
    
    
    NDCG@1: nothing to normalize, accumulate, or discount. Discuss amongst yourselves. cc @sigirf    
    
    
    So nice to run into @ggref this morning. #sigir2013    
    
    
    #SIGIR in Chile: pic.twitter.com/GvB6fIEvhC    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai @CharlotteHase I am so doomed.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase and for the next year.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase ACM is trying various ideas on opening access. Some SIGs (incl SIGIR) are piloting different options. (1/2)    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase (2/2) SIGIR's decision was to allow free access to all SIGIR conference papers for a year following the conference.    
    
    
    A nice short writeup on SIGIR 2013 from Dan Tunkelang: http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130805134105-50510-search-what-s-cooking-in-the-lab … Don't miss the tweets (his and others) at #sigir2013    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald is the spec for that API online, or do I need to be in their program to see it?    
    
    
    Of all the folks who might've bought out WaPo, I can imagine far far worse for the future of journalism.    
    
    
    Just want to say I've had a Post delivered to my doorstep for over 15 years, even without Prime.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald thx. that's helpful for me. Thinking about making APIs for TREC collections.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG don't despair... for every #Delta, there exists an epsilon.    
    
    
    @bkeegan haven't been following hubbub, but tweets can be deleted, accounts can be deleted, and tweets can be made private. Byebye link.    
    
    
    Twitter design flaw: the average limerick appears to be 160-180 characters long.    
    
    
    @bkeegan I can get books and journals from multiple places, but tweets only from Twitter.    
    
    
    @gilad link to Hebrew limerick archive pls    
    
    
    @gilad so true to form, yet so ... tame!    
    
    
    Sorry, just tuned in. Apparently Elon Musk just had a crappy trip between LA and SF?    
    
    
    @mounialalmas he's not the messiah, he's a very naughty boy!    
    
    
    Dear WaPo: thanks for making your content harder to get for a paying subscriber. pw;dr    
    
    
    So sad to learn that @HCIR_GeneG passed away. I never would have guessed seeing him in Dublin would be my last chance to learn from him.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl according to @jerepick sudden diagnosis of leukemia, then a stroke.    
    
    
    Still reeling from the news about @HCIR_GeneG    
    
    
    @srenals have you read it? SIGIR made the right decision.    
    
    
    @milesosborne it doesn't have 6k citations due to the quality if the research, but bc of the impact of Google.    
    
    
    @milesosborne if u implement the paper on real data you also see that PR is a very small part of good ranking.    
    
    
    @milesosborne at the time of its publication, any paper has zero citations. Publishing them after they're already highly cited is tricky.    
    
    
    @ML_Hipster deep learning ones do.    
    
    
    Anyone know how hard it would be to give Solr an actual real JSON parser?    
    
    
    @alambert I have a pile of JSON data. Here, Solr, ingest it all, don't make me write code, and don't barf on subobjects etc.    
    
    
    @alambert e.g. flatten structures automatically and sensibly, all with dynamic fields.  Oh also no barfing.    
    
    
    Dear Apache Project: I am intrigued by your website and would like to read your actual documentation. When you have some. kthxbye.    
    
    
    (Today, I'm looking at you, Giraph, but really it could be anyone except httpd.)    
    
    
    @alambert So do you have actual documentation for your product, or just webinars? I'm going to shove two billion web pages into it,  (1/2)    
    
    
    @alambert (2/2) and your very sparse website doesn't really lead me in the right direction.    
    
    
    Beware world, cranky @ian_soboroff is on the prowl for documentation, and when he doesn't get it, he can be damn snarky.    
    
    
    @alambert Yeah, read that file in the tarball. I'm a little past the hello-world stage of search. Is there real docu anywhere?    
    
    
    @alambert I mean, for a shiny wrapper around Solr, it would be nice to know how to use the shiny.    
    
    
    @alambert was unhappy trying to keep a large solr install from falling over under a large batch index job. Guess I can go RTSL.    
    
    
    @alambert Pretty much every search problem I have starts with "index these hundreds of millions of things". How? Pls not curl.    
    
    
    @alambert btw sorry to rant at you, I know you're trying to be helpful.    
    
    
    @alambert my favorite lg is the one that scales and has documentation ;-) Will try porting my Solr Hadoop bulk loader to elastic.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase now I know who to ask about it. Look what happened to the last guy.    
    
    
    @m_guerini @milesosborne  I propose a new journal, "J. Crazy Shit", that only publishes papers that raise more questions than they answer.    
    
    
    @milesosborne @m_guerini it's like that conference, !SIGIR, that only accepts papers on IR that are not possible to evaluate.    
    
    
    "Just google it, baby." - Bootsy Collins    
    
    
    I'm demoing Twitter for NIST assessors.    
    
    
    RIP Marian McPartland... few know how to appreciate music as you did.    
    
    
    That feeling when you're at a talk you went to, just b/c whatever, and you realize that was the most important thing you did all day.    
    
    
    Thinking it's time for a new dance music genre of, by, and for sysadmins: yp-funk.    
    
    
    I can't believe I'm asking this, here goes. Who is making the best desktop Windows PCs these days?    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon what brings you to town?    
    
    
    @belafleckbanjo @IntlBluegrass That looks incredible... any chance it'll be recorded?    
    
    
    I don't wanna boss, I just wanna bang on the code all day...    
    
    
    #GooglePoetics for my day. pic.twitter.com/2mwcN5za83    
    
    
    Interesting article about copyright and fair use, in the context of King's 'Dream' speech: http://wapo.st/17kHZP5  via @washingtonpost    
    
    
    @kegill sad not to see an adventurous if sad Beatles cover.    
    
    
    @kohlschuetter coolest part is: that is a RPi running Unix emulating an original Mac.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl @akshayjava Are you using it for clean sites or messy ones?    
    
    
    LDAP: as complicated as possible, but not complicateder.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl I thought deep learning was a NN with a hidden layer. Deep SCM is what, a kernel?    
    
    
    @mikiobraun @ChrisDiehl me,  I'm waiting for the inevitable Inception references. Oh wait I'm late to the party again. #godeeper #backprop    
    
    
    @mikiobraun @ChrisDiehl how in the heck do you converge a hyperplane that way? Assumes hiddens are IID but they're surely not by design?    
    
    
    @agrotke better than amusing spending on the usual.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Confirmed. That's not right. I'll follow up on that, thanks for the report.    
    
    
    Thirty years between my Apple //e and my iPhone, and there remains one common interface tech between them: the audio port.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai thumbs up!    
    
    
    @mounialalmas but the location is oh so exclusive!    
    
    
    Bluetooth: a wireless discharging technology.    
    
    
    So sry old school website. Too wide; didn't read.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang How good is good enough?    
    
    
    @BoredElonMusk when you get some time, I could really use an all-electric minivan.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl Time Machine is your bff    
    
    
    @dtunkelang no, I meant what are their numbers? "Good" POS tagging is not interesting technically.    
    
    
    @hmason all I get is "RTFM".  Huh?    
    
    
    @hmason could be worse, could be texinfo    
    
    
    iOS 7 broke Find My Friends. Hm.    
    
    
    iOS 7 notification center is even more useless than before. Pro tip: I don't care what today's weather was.    
    
    
    They call it "forecasting" for a reason.    
    
    
    Also, telling me I have appointments but not what they are is not helpful. Tap through to calendar? Nope.    
    
    
    Perhaps Jony Ive doesn't do meetings.    
    
    
    Sorry I'm missing #dsa13 this year, but thanks to tweets from @lljohnston I get to read the good stuff.    
    
    
    Account got hacked. Apologies if you got really random dm's from me.    
    
    
    Wash the windows. #thingstododuringtheshutdown    
    
    
    Brush the cat #thingstododuringtheshutdown    
    
    
    It's a train they call the City of NIST, I'll've sent 500 emails when the day is done.    
    
    
    @sam_bush tie b/w Junior Heywood, Diamond Joe, and Hot Tamales. #robertjohnson_ftw    
    
    
    @lintool depends on how enterprisy your nas is...    
    
    
    A federal shutdown affects the city of DC, too.  http://m.washingtonpost.com/local/dc-politics/dc-officials-ponder-whether-to-defy-federal-shutdown-and-keep-city-government-open/2013/09/24/9e743060-24cb-11e3-ad0d-b7c8d2a594b9_story.html …    
    
    
    @mounialalmas @elunca comes from not strongly defining a task.    
    
    
    iOS 7 Calendar, how do I loathe thee?  Let me count the ways...    
    
    
    @agrotke @postlocal After the election, politicians are sworn in.  Thereafter, they are only sworn at.    
    
    
    Free tip for LinkedIn's news recommender team: if it was yesterday's news, it's not actually news anymore.    
    
    
    @agrotke lol... even if the #shutdown occurs, we must report to perform an orderly shutdown. (I've never shut down an orderly before!)    
    
    
    Thx for the jokes, Twitter. It helps, but I still have to go in this morning to shut everything down.    
    
    
    iOS 7 fail #543: can't edit playlists on the phone. #wtf    
    
    
    @iadh I hope not, but it's not in my hands.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I take this back.  You can, but the interface got obscured. iOS 7 and I are just not getting along.    
    
    
    I wonder if I can write a SIGIR paper while we're shut down. Affiliation: none.    
    
    
    Another iOS 7 casualty: my Otterbox case. Too many controls right at the edge of the screen. Replacement suggestions?    
    
    
    Lisp: functional programming. JavaScript: dysfunctional programming.    
    
    
    Recruiter bait: try to hire me before the shutdown ends.    
    
    
    @matthewhurst would prefer to commute or be remote, but am open to the right offer.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @matthewhurst lol    
    
    
    @mblondel_ml I recommend reading the coverage in the Washington Post. @ezraklein has been tweeting very good links.    
    
    
    Lots of cool tweets from #ictir2013 have to spend some furlough time reading    
    
    
    This week was for doing performance reviews. Just sayin. #shutdown    
    
    
    @BoredElonMusk sounds like a fitbit app.    
    
    
    Anyone know a good mycologist? pic.twitter.com/I5URADvaYZ    
    
    
    Evite has nothing for a furlough party. #wtf    
    
    
    @mrflip dear Jony, you haven't done your job, sry. #ios7    
    
    
    @MMiiina you are not the mycologist I'm looking for :-)    
    
    
    A légpárnás hajóm tele angolnával.    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog an important phrase to know in any language. Now, I have no idea how to -pronounce- it...    
    
    
    @MMiiina better for you than these shrooms, mos def    
    
    
    @ayman @cmdrtaco is now an NSF PM? I should give him a call, my karma is still excellent.    
    
    
    My feed is full of #hcir2013. Even if I'd planned to go, the #shutdown would have put a stop to that. Sigh.    
    
    
    The #hcir2013 tributes to John Reidl and Gene Golovchinsky are very touching. Such a sad year.    
    
    
    Dear iPhone, it's not at all clear how to connect [app name] to iTunes, even if i wanted to. Did anyone test this OS before releasing it?!    
    
    
    @gilad @OrenTsur I thought the quote from תהלים was especially poignant.    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog you mean it git even more annoying than it was in 4.1?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @krisztianbalog I always check with @gsingers and @otisg before upgrading Lucene.    
    
    
    @kermmartian no, maybe from CMU?    
    
    
    Yet another iOS 7 bug: it ignores timezones in mail .ics attachments. And because it's someone else's mtg, you can't correct it.    
    
    
    @tlipcon when we needed build systems for our build systems, we should have thrown in the towel then and there.    
    
    
    @ezraklein it's not amazing. This Congress is totally OK with failure.    
    
    
    @ezraklein or, Crisis in Infinite Committees.    
    
    
    @elunca if Monday is your prior you are doomed.    
    
    
    Hey search engines, let me save the first page of results with a shortened link, please.    
    
    
    @objkshn @ezraklein can u imagine a political process where success or failure were defined by the common good achieved?    
    
    
    Workday 8 of the #shutdown. Started making up my own forms to fill out.    
    
    
    It's a shame more folks don't think of the defense and IC appropriations as entitlement programs out of control.    
    
    
    At UMBC to hang out at the Mid-Atlantic Student Colloquium on Speech, Language, and Learning. Definitely not working.    
    
    
    @xamat oh dear    
    
    
    It is truly said that idle hands are the devil's tools.    
    
    
    @JustinBasilico @xamat @LinasTw I hope it learns BM25-F, that would be properly meta.    
    
    
    I always liked American Scientist better than Scientific American.    
    
    
    Everyone thinks we'll get our back pay. Actually, the bill passed by the House (and not yet by the Senate) gives agencies discretion. (1/2)    
    
    
    (2/2) So if your agency was going to have to furlough to get through the 2014 sequester, guess what, you just did it. cc @ezraklein    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @jkonstan @leifos @alansaid What's the recommender user task that is represented by recall?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang that's high precision in the residual, which is different.    
    
    
    Unsure if John Boehner is inscrutable or just has no scrutes.    
    
    
    @gilad but can I get it next day with Prime?    
    
    
    @msbernst I'm thinking of becoming a data spiritual leader.    
    
    
    Channeling Marie DesJardins in the time management sense.  Or trying to, at least.  Inbox O(1).    
    
    
    Oh, and you'll all be happy to know I'm back at work at NIST, meaning an end to political tweets from me.    
    
    
    @knowtheory Always hoped @scifri would do more actual experiments on the air. Nice to know it's happening!    
    
    
    @ezraklein Also, big IT is really hard to do right. And if you have to do it like the gov't has to do it, it's nearly impossible.    
    
    
    @ezraklein Think of http://healthcare.gov  as the FBI's unified casefile system, but for HHS.  Then you say, well, duh.    
    
    
    2nd-to-last farmers market at NIST for the year. We lost three weeks to the shutdown, now I can eat better again.    
    
    
    I wonder if my SGI IRIS graphics head would work with the new Macbooks. #thereAreNoNewProductNames    
    
    
    ECIR 2014 is the same week as Passover. Sigh.    
    
    
    UMich, a kickass place to be, is looking for IR faculty: https://www.si.umich.edu/aboutsi/open-faculty-positions …    
    
    
    Has anyone else using iOS 7 found that they can't turn off Find My IPhone?    
    
    
    Looking for a migration guide for moving from CDH4 to HortonWorks.    
    
    
    @anildash actually thought about this one for a while. Realized my productivity hack is to drop off my kids at school.    
    
    
    I was really hoping for OS X "Grumpy Cat"    
    
    
    Business idea: contract deidentification of medical records. Free service to support open research on records. Need a funder.    
    
    
    I have an idea for a business, and need some management help and a funder.  If you like the idea and know someone, pass it along.

The core…    
    
    
    Got a linkedin recruiter ping from CGI Federal. Umm, no thanks?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang I hope she did it well. Schools are asking kids to code during the interview these days.    
    
    
    Numbers 3.0 dropped *autocompletion*? Apple is truly having a #wtf month.    
    
    
    A Debian bug report I filed TEN YEARS AGO is still unfixed. I want a cookie. https://bugs.launchpad.net/ubuntu/+source/gnome-system-tools/+bug/14392 …    
    
    
    @elunca disagree.    
    
    
    @gingdottwit @dagstuhl Curious how Norbert feels about average temperatures.    
    
    
    "The installation is not as well-documented but therefore the configuration files are much simpler."    
    
    
    @elunca probably because when we want to talk to people about IR evaluation, all those people are at SIGIR.    
    
    
    Tried to install a Ruby on Rails app. #neveragain    
    
    
    May I please timetravel to the day that Python actually replaces R (and not with something uglier, ohai rpy2)    
    
    
    It's Oct 30, the grocery store has Christmas trees out and tulips for sale. Truly there is no time like the present.    
    
    
    @lljohnston on the Storage for Preservation meeting at LOC in Sep.  http://blogs.loc.gov/digitalpreservation/2013/10/planning-for-preservation-storage/ …    
    
    
    They call it "Word", but I don't think they had the words in mind that I say when I have to use it.    
    
    
    Wish I was at #cikm2013.  I will be next year... I'd better be, I'm the IR co-chair!    
    
    
    > library(all_the_libraries) 
Error in library(all_the_libraries) :
  there is no package called ‘all_the_libraries’ #mylifeinR    
    
    
    @djoerd reminds me of getting spam with JS exploits. Didn't work so well in Emacs Gnus. And, funny, no one ever tried an elisp virus.    
    
    
    @et I'm being compelled to make bar charts. Do you have a support group I could join?    
    
    
    @ET Whups you're not the ET person I was looking for (@EdwardTufte), sorry for the confusion!    
    
    
    @lintool Hey, never let it be said that journalists are afraid to talk to technical people and then write about what they think they heard.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte I'm being compelled to make bar charts. Do you have a support group I could join?    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte if it escalates to pie charts I'm calling the UN.    
    
    
    Yes, on Mac OS you can drag from Mail to Reminders, and from Reminders to Calendar.    
    
    
    Some days you're the stakeholder, some days you're the vampire.    
    
    
    Inbox asymptotically approaching zero.  And will never quite make it.    
    
    
    Hey WaPo, buy out @xkcd. You'd score a statistical graphics wizard AND fixed your moribund comix pages AT THE SAME TIME.    
    
    
    @abdur wow    
    
    
    @jonathankoren (get-off 'my-lawn)    
    
    
    @josh_wills @dtunkelang my cat is better at software engineering than any likely sample of statisticians.    
    
    
    @porkmail email me at NIST.    
    
    
    A tangible way of restoring order to a govt that had become, in Cox’s words, “emotionally constipated.” http://m.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/lincoln-memorial-lawn-mowing-hero-chris-cox-gets-a-chainsaw-for-his-shutdown-efforts/2013/11/13/8630e180-4c97-11e3-9890-a1e0997fb0c0_story.html …    
    
    
    Apple maps you have failed me for the last time    
    
    
    @gilad well, Arlington, but yeah.    
    
    
    Bug report/feature req: often I need my computer to Shut Up, but the only menu item I have close to that is Shut Down.    
    
    
    Since the decision in the Authors Guild case, I'm going thru my books finding the copyright blocks that say 'no IR systems' and giggling.    
    
    
    -bash: wtf: command not found    
    
    
    @informor @dtunkelang Also, last I checked, @horse_ebooks had a klout score of 75 or something, so you also have to renormalize.    
    
    
    No, you can not have your own build tool.    
    
    
    Sorry, I can't use your new programming language unless it comes with it's own inscrutable build system.    
    
    
    #TREC2013 kicking off this morning.    
    
    
    Calibri's ligatures make me wince.  That is all.    
    
    
    Machine learning folks have 300 different words for 'hack'.    
    
    
    @tadejtadej aka "REEEEally stochastic"    
    
    
    @elunca summary: it's time for a best-practices document and tests-of-goodness for qrels.    
    
    
    TREC 2013 winding up... next week, I go into SIGIR mode.  #w00t    
    
    
    For TREC 2014, there will be a new Clinical Decision Support track: given a case history, return PubMed docs for diag, tests, trtmt    
    
    
    Inspired by my autocorrect, a new software engineering metric: FLOCs, f--ing lines of code.    
    
    
    Goodbye, Arik Einstein... :-(    
    
    
    Wikipedia says, "The bands Parliament and Funkadelic cannot be easily separated."  Ain't that the truth.    
    
    
    @bradplumer @ezraklein I don't think that's what "one click" is supposed to mean.    
    
    
    Deep learning, by Jack Handy.    
    
    
    Lots of nice looking paper titles at #ecir2014 ... sorry I won't be able to be there...    
    
    
    @IR_oldie don't forget vituperative.    
    
    
    @elunca the track overview. See http://trec.nist.gov/proceedings/proceedings.html … and cite the one from the right year.    
    
    
    Best Chanukah present ever. pic.twitter.com/dsaU0IDPVe    
    
    
    No, I am not interested in attending your webinar.    
    
    
    Probabilistic Programming in Quantitative Finance http://prsm.tc/U1QF7d  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Via @nglance: http://kingjamesprogramming.tumblr.com/  you will laugh your parens off.    
    
    
    @anildash @elipariser @Upworthy some nice ideas, many not new. The critical problem is how to measure whether it works or not.    
    
    
    @WSDM2014 @fdiaz_msr when does the program go up?    
    
    
    Upgraded to 10.9.1 from 10.8, immediately found two really bad bugs. Automounts broken and Thunderbolt eth0 after waking from sleep. #wtf    
    
    
    @abdur @tylr seems legit    
    
    
    Large CSV files in Emacs: M-x org-mode, M-x mark-whole-buffer, M-x org-table-create-or-convert-from-region, and get a monospace font.    
    
    
    @hadleywickham Will there ever be a useful doc page for "layer"?? (http://docs.ggplot2.org/current/layer.html …) Pretty please?    
    
    
    Fact is, without StackOverflow, R is nearly unusable.    
    
    
    Where do the StackOverflow folks go when StackOverflow is down?    
    
    
    Am I the only person who thinks of gold lamé whenever I say "LibreOffice"?    
    
    
    @hadleywickham it's just there's no way to discover what's in those ellipses, short of reading the code. Maybe ggwhatspossible(fn_name)?    
    
    
    TREC 2014 call for participation: http://trec.nist.gov/pubs/call2014.html …    
    
    
    It's not BeautifulSoup for Java, but it comes pretty damn close: Jsoup http://jsoup.org/     
    
    
    I have a reborn Tweets2011 crawler looking for brave testers: https://github.com/isoboroff/twitter-corpus-tools/tree/html-scraper …    
    
    
    In OS X Mavericks, NFS options in automounter maps aren't recognized. Soln: put them in autofs.conf. #bug    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai +1. If those ugrads get real interested in IR eval we have good student visit programs.    
    
    
    Stiglitz's op-ed is concerned with financial (or fiduciary) trust, but I read the entire thing with the Snowden revelations in mind. (1/2)    
    
    
    (2/2) what will be the damage to the internet?  Does the simplistic notion of "route around damage" make even less sense than it did before?    
    
    
    @hmason I approve of k-means here... anything to do with scotch should be done slowly.    
    
    
    @bkeegan hey we can't all be Rick Astley.    
    
    
    @ChuckWendig I have both read and not read your tweet.  This space for rent.    
    
    
    Do we believe that secret predictive election models are real, or just lucky?    
    
    
    @mattcutts holding out for postgress.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield http://election.princeton.edu/methods/  has Matlab code and some degree of process documentation.    
    
    
    @gilgul like the bumper sticker says, שומר מרחק.  Stay safe.    
    
    
    @gilgul Hebrew iPhone autocorrect apparently not up to my poor Hebrew.    
    
    
    @abdur @bcherry but there is a real concern that eventually they will be that 80s hair band you don't quite remember the name of.    
    
    
    Threads-in-bubbles on the Gaza war are depressingly similar to threads-in-bubbles on the election. Two utter parallel universes.    
    
    
    @jcmayfield unsure why its ok to shoot missiles as long as no one gets hurt. #wtf    
    
    
    That might've been the first DARPA kickoff with lolcats, but I'm not sure.    
    
    
    @elunca still waiting for renormalization of Klout scores by Klout_score(horse_ebooks).  ;-)    
    
    
    @kansandhaus the road to Java is indeed paved with good intentions. So, if you design a programming language, you should avoid having those.    
    
    
    @msbernst have you tried following @cmunell?    
    
    
    Positive customer experience at Radio Shack. The end may be nigh.    
    
    
    iPhone 5 was too spooky thin. Otterbox is the cure.    
    
    
    Hey @UseClear, feat req: I want to copy a block of text (an email with the grocery list) and autosplit it into list items when pasting.    
    
    
    @zephoria that doesn't sound good.    
    
    
    @haroldfeld it's the flip side of its ok to shoot rockets at people if they're not very accurate.    
    
    
    Hamas pro tip: agree to cease fire, but don't actually cease. http://www.ynetnews.com/articles/0,7340,L-4310174,00.html …    
    
    
    @haroldfeld, xkcd is calling for you... http://bit.ly/UOsw1Z     
    
    
    @UseClear that just rocks. Thx!    
    
    
    DayOne keeps losing entries. Not good for a journal app.    
    
    
    I last did C++ in the prior millenium. What's the best starting point to get back up to speed?    
    
    
    Lots of folks using classifiers as black boxes. Folks, there are snapping turtles in those boxes. #ymmv    
    
    
    @junklight and start from...? I have a much thumbed but very dusty 2nd ed Stroustrup, and that's all.    
    
    
    @orr971 unsure why I should be optimistic about remote backups when the app loses data on local storage.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase @arjenpdevries what about collection bias?    
    
    
    They need a Pulitzer for p0wning so they can give it to the Onion.    
    
    
    @hyheng still investigating, unfortunately.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase You can tell me or Ellen or Lori about broken input.gz links on the TREC website, and we'll fix them.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase What do you think about systems that line up horizontally? vertically? Gets to sensitivity of the method.    
    
    
    @msbernst and you can amortize the hosting cost over lots of papers.    
    
    
    Martha's First Law of Power Laws: Everything is linear, when graphed log-log with a fat magic marker.    
    
    
    @DelFest when will the lineup be announced?    
    
    
    Very nice meeting of the DC area IR Experts (DIRE) today. Thanks @BenCarterette and Hagit Shatkay and Dawn Lawrie!    
    
    
    @etzioni @greglinden I think we can do it if we all give 110%.    
    
    
    @hyheng Give it a try now, it should be working!    
    
    
    @dtunkelang nice quickie on evaluation, but actually doesn't help the reader understand relevance...    
    
    
    @delsweil @dtunkelang and on the flip side, the simplifications and tradeoffs made to make it measurable.    
    
    
    Practical machine learning tricks from the KDD 2011 best industry paper http://prsm.tc/DmCOdp  via @prismatic    
    
    
    @ej I see many of the usual suspects. Hope you're having fun!    
    
    
    @jussikarlgren @dtunkelang unsure how to implement that for a researcher outside a large-scale search company.    
    
    
    @delsweil @RichardDawkins is disappoint.    
    
    
    ....l..íí    
    
    
    @iadh if only we had some technology that could learn your preferences from examples.    
    
    
    @iadh the hardest part is actually the interface for tracking msgs and managing misclassifications.    
    
    
    @mattcutts yeah, aren't eigenvectors just the sh:t. I was so happy the day Google invented them.    
    
    
    ....l.ííí    
    
    
    @yvolkovich who needs FB? :)    
    
    
    It's probably preliminary to say this before I even write much code in it, but Pythonista is a reason to own an iPad all on its own.    
    
    
    @metzlerd do computational advertising faculty need to bring in their own funding, and can they do it however they might like to?    
    
    
    ...líííí    
    
    
    Free tip for email spammers: spam in languages I don't speak is not entertaining, is easily classed as spam, and the conversion rate stinks.    
    
    
    @cshirky every media outlet (well, papers, tv, radio, and the like) fits that description.    
    
    
    @atpassos_ml when you can snatch the decision boundary from my hand, it will be time for you to leave.    
    
    
    ...ílíííí    
    
    
    @danbri VLC2, a research coll from CSIRO, is from '97: http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.61.7206&rep=rep1&type=pdf …    
    
    
    Home, sick. Reduced to reading @haroldfeld's voluminous tweets on #WCIT.    
    
    
    @bederson how about Emacs key bindings?    
    
    
    @johnbreslin @chrisdiehl and we have @lintool working on the next level of scale.    
    
    
    $perl = 25. Thanks, Larry.    
    
    
    @abdur yeah, but Higgs Boson?    
    
    
    @iadh the tricky part is building your own LHC. Multi-kajillion dollar science is hard to replicate.    
    
    
    @hmason alias mroe    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sign up to come participate in TREC 2013: http://trec.nist.gov/pubs/call2013.html …    
    
    
    Looks like a quiet week here next week, finally!  Anyone want to write a SIGIR paper?    
    
    
    @mdreid We say, "In theory, theory and practice are the same, but in practice, they're different."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl what, like Clear Channel?  That's why radio died.    
    
    
    @mdreid I know the quote, but heck if I can pronounce that name.    
    
    
    Hey @useclear, what happened to the shake gesture to paste a bunch of things as a list?!? #killerfeatureiskilled    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl eagerly awaiting Tarantino's new Al-Qudsploitation genre flick.    
    
    
    Got invited to a Dagstuhl seminar. Any experiences out there?    
    
    
    @ted_dunning mind if I ask how quantifiable "amazing" is? What sort of task does this approach work well for?    
    
    
    @hmason @ted_dunning we've found simple logistic regression works well for spam detection in email and web pages.    
    
    
    Turns out the new Tarantino movie isn't at all about Python web frameworks.    
    
    
    @ted_dunning Cool. Cite? Define "interesting"?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries are you shilling for the organizers?    
    
    
    @otisg Is that good? Was thinking of diving into 4.0 as a major rewrite opportunity for our system. Best to wait?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries @peter_r_bailey @tetsuyasakai Good grief it sounds like we can just hold it on Twitter.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas @arjenpdevries @peter_r_bailey @tetsuyasakai @CharlotteHase looks like they invited all the usual suspects.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte my law of unsupported claims: pls show the data.    
    
    
    Wow. http://www.gatestoneinstitute.org/3517/redacted-iraqi-jews … via @haroldfeld    
    
    
    @bkeegan @msbernst can I play it back using a camera phone, if the resolution is high enough?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I pinged Nicola on that question... lots of evaluation topics on that program.    
    
    
    Current playlist: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/How_the_West_Was_Won_(Led_Zeppelin_album) …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai an intro to IR evaluation; history, methods, tricks, pitfalls. I'll need P+R but otherwise, metrics are yours. ;-)    
    
    
    Teaching someone the wonders of 'find | cat | tr | sort | uniq | wc' as NLP Pipeline 1.0.  #iloveunix    
    
    
    Sing it, @BloombergView. MT U.S. Internet Users Pay More for Slower Service http://bloom.bg/UbB9UM  (via @EdwardTufte)    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I'll listen.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai does not après ski usually involve alcohol?    
    
    
    @MarthaBunton @lljohnston Today's WaPo article doesn't make the researcher access we've been talking about sound like it'll happen. Sad.    
    
    
    @msbernst all the easy scans and non-typos are done. It's hit the global minimum.    
    
    
    @hmason I'm pretty disappointed with that article. If I'd known it was just to complain at Twitter, I'd not have agreed to be interviewed.    
    
    
    @djoerd actually, I don't think Twitter's a bad guy at all. Unhappy? They should give you your money back.    
    
    
    Strongly considering posting my actual interview responses as comments to this. http://www.buzzfeed.com/nostrich/how-twitter-gets-in-the-way-of-research …    
    
    
    @JamesMcMinn go for it. Feel free to email me if you want advice on this.    
    
    
    @nostrich Thinking this morning more about how to comment in a way that starts the discussion you want -- how to get data, what kinds.    
    
    
    I thought Katherine Heigl would be perfect for defense chief...    
    
    
    My call is very important to you, but apparently not important enough to up-staff the call center.    
    
    
    A nice summary of Python frameworks for Hadoop, from Cloudera: http://bit.ly/UYGmSK     
    
    
    @bradfordcross still waiting for my Java-powered garbage compactor.    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl lots of good papers at SIGIR on this over the past few years.    
    
    
    @mdreid "When I was your age, the phones were so old they couldn't make calls, just take pictures."    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl anecdote is a poor substitute for experiment.    
    
    
    Very nice looking tool, haven't tried it yet but I might. http://mcb.berkeley.edu/labs/zusman/dave/svg2key/ …    
    
    
    Any folks at #nistcloud this week who want to talk web, social media, text and video data for research, come find me. We have a booth.    
    
    
    @mrflip when are you turning up at NIST this week?    
    
    
    Making evil plans for TREC KBA.    
    
    
    I wish it were possible to actually find information on FB.    
    
    
    Let me put it another way. FB's current search is so useless, their announcement fills me with joy. It would be hard to not improve things.    
    
    
    @breyten my friends pass along links and stories all the time which are impossible to recover two weeks later. Re-finding in FB is big.    
    
    
    Vint Cerf speaking this morning at NIST #nistcloud    
    
    
    Cerf compares cloud interoperability to the days of DECNET and SNA. Imagine when we have the equivalent of TCP/IP among clouds.    
    
    
    Cerf: MOOCs invert the classroom. watch the lecture on your own, come to class to solve problems. Powerful idea.    
    
    
    @fjsteele doesn't work so hot for running joint computation across the walls.    
    
    
    I think the NRA is saying they want armed federal agents at every school. Unsure the 2nd amendment will help an insurrection at that point.    
    
    
    Data-driven dating. I think I'm in love. http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887323374504578217973101313736.html …    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon I'm over it.  I was only in love with her model.    
    
    
    URL is http://www.iaa-archives.org.il/ . MT @Arquivistica Israel Antiquities digitalizes archives http://bit.ly/10BxmZ8  cc @lljohnston    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @Arquivistica @lljohnston Also worst search interface ever.  Perhaps it dates from the Mandate era.    
    
    
    @hmason also pls @horse_ebookbookgoose, taking snippets from reviews.    
    
    
    http://blog.archive.org/2013/01/20/bulk-downloading-aaron-swartz-and-terms-of-service/ … by @brewster_kahle    
    
    
    Bought a book on google play. Clicked 'download PDF'. Got an ACSM file pointing to a document. #wtf how do I get the PDF I paid for?    
    
    
    Also Google Play just stinks as a book reader for PDF, both in Chrome and in their app.    
    
    
    So cannot decide if this ebook drm shit is Googles fault, adobes fault, or Morgan Claypool's fault.    
    
    
    Bought a book. Can't read it. The new illiteracy. #drm    
    
    
    Ok, now my question is, how do I download and then remove the DRM from a book which I have bought, given its ACSM key file?    
    
    
    Soln: 1) use Adobe DigEd to get the encrypted PDF. 2) pip install pycrypto. 3) two scripts from http://thescienceofdestruction.wordpress.com/2011/08/10/downloading-and-decrypting-adobe-adept-drm-protected-ebooks-on-linux/ …. Gaaah, done.    
    
    
    Unsure where to report general suckage with Google Books. That was way too much hacking needed for fair use.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai hang in there, I see clear skies in your future.    
    
    
    Google writeup on multi-armed bandits. http://analytics.blogspot.com/2013/01/multi-armed-bandit-experiments.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=linkedin …    
    
    
    @ChrisDiehl I think there's an NLP-completeness proof that any such program is equivalent to dissociated-text.    
    
    
    Spent the day hacking, or, "Why Ian Can't Program". #embarrasing    
    
    
    If we got rid of all the crappy travel websites there would be a lot more room on the net for cat videos. Just sayin'    
    
    
    Wondering about the effects of inhaling airborne pulverized road salt.    
    
    
    @bemikelive I was going to write "On the use of the word 'on' to lead SIGIR paper titles."    
    
    
    Need a Mail.app extension that sees the word "attached" in an outgoing email, without an attachment, and confirms the send. #gmailmylifepls    
    
    
    @lljohnston Nope, @VeryGrumpyCat would never say "sorry".    
    
    
    I was feeling left out because I never knew Aaron Swartz. But, hey, I did know David LaMacchia. http://swartz-review.mit.edu/question/what-questions-should-mit-be-asking-stage-aaron-swartz-review/response/what-if-anything-did …    
    
    
    I mean, we were in like first grade, but he was my first geek buddy. Getting his big brother off the Apple ][+ was impossible.    
    
    
    Just btw, David and Brian had an Apple, and went to MIT. I had a Timex Sinclair 1000, and went to UMBC. There you go.    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr you rock. Pinging Mark to see if he has that old code.    
    
    
    @stewhir Outlook is so not the solution.  Outlook is the precipitate.    
    
    
    @kegill somewhat better coverage at http://www.latimes.com/news/world/worldnow/la-fg-israeli-health-authorities-issue-guidelines-on-controversial-birthcontrol-shots-20130128,0,7037665.story …    
    
    
    Putting the finishing touches on a TREC adhoc evaluation demo with Lucene 4.1, for my PROMISE class. Stay tuned for github link.    
    
    
    A demo on Cranfield-style IR evaluation, using Lucene and TREC data: https://github.com/isoboroff/trec-demo …. Goes with a class I'll be giving next week.    
    
    
    @lintool a much nicer demo of a much richer system, I should put a link to it.    
    
    
    @gsingers let me know if this is useful or not: https://github.com/isoboroff/trec-demo …    
    
    
    @gilgul @PhilipMeyer4 s/computational/all/    
    
    
    Aiiigh my feed, it's full of pr0n #sexi2013 #academicsgonewild    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai sorry we didn't get more time to hang out. Safe trip home!    
    
    
    Awesome talks today from @elunca and Peter Mika.  These week-long schools are better for the teachers than the students.    
    
    
    Finishing up a wonderful week of teaching, talking, learning, and a little skiing in Bressanone. Thx to PROMISE and to all who attended.    
    
    
    Article from @cshirky on MOOCs and the current sea change coming at universities. 
http://lnkd.in/8SnqEs     
    
    
    @sinanaral Funny, I can't find the job announcement on LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Acclimatizing to the US after spending the week in Italy. Coffee from DD done, next stop NIST cafeteria. #coffee #fail    
    
    
    @jaykreps I would so live for the puzzler.    
    
    
    Clueweb12 is in the house. As long as I don't open the box it can't consume all my time...    
    
    
    #icwsm2013 is up over 500 abstract submissions. Thanks, friends!    
    
    
    @milesosborne should open tonight.    
    
    
    @haroldfeld in fact without the human genome there would be no jobs at all.  Unless it would be like the Matrix.    
    
    
    Adding 'pun quality' field to #icwsm2013 review form.    
    
    
    @lintool you are truly on a roll. Congrats.    
    
    
    TREC 2013 microblog collection is at 75M tweets and counting.    
    
    
    TREC 2013 datasets are coming in the door.  The new ClueWeb collection (for use in the web, sessions, and context tracks) has arrived on my…    
    
    
    @milesosborne it's at the limit of downloadable, with a flock of ec2 instances. We are trying a new model this year, eval as a svc.    
    
    
    Spent some time this week playing with http://sharelatex.com .  It's a nice idea, but the editor itself is useless for actual writing.    
    
    
    SIGIR tutorial proposal submitted.    
    
    
    #icwsm2013 has a serious embarrassment of riches problem this year. We were not ready to grow this fast!    
    
    
    @sharelatex I'm used to writing LaTeX in Emacs. Kind of a shock to have an editor without even find/replace. Where to begin?    
    
    
    @sharelatex you might never be as powerful as Emacs, but you could strive  to be as documented.    
    
    
    The TREC 2013 welcome message has gone out, officially beginning the TREC season. To participate, pls sign up at http://trec.nist.gov/     
    
    
    Anyone out there used http://textrazor.com  for more than just playing yet? Interested in experiences with large volumes of messy text.    
    
    
    rpy2 is amazing. I predict I will get just as frustrated with it as I do with native R. #perfecttranslationofuserexperience    
    
    
    Aiming for inbox O(log n)    
    
    
    Hey @wetatvfm, someone came to our door tonight soliciting donations. For real?    
    
    
    @dpatil I've seen folks pull rabbits out of hats too. It's more than data, and its more than "something out of it."    
    
    
    @tjake In my locale, "defenestrate" is to remove WIndows, either by reinstalling with Linux or replacing them with Macs.    
    
    
    Anyone Jewish heading for @DelFest? Thinking about camping for shabbos.    
    
    
    @carlyeks @tjake Don't blame the hardware for software problems.    
    
    
    I'm _still_ disappointed that http://drive.google.com/  doesn't take me to a self-driving car webcam. #iwaspromisedselfdrivingcarsdammit    
    
    
    @lljohnston @agrotke and a pony.    
    
    
    @hmason at job?    
    
    
    @xamat at least, keeping read status on the client and hiding them behind many cliches or taps!    
    
    
    @kansandhaus If New York is the center of the universe, International New York is ... bigger?    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai some of those I am reviewing have not been withdrawn quickly enough...    
    
    
    Looking for an array-based suffix tree impl in Java.    
    
    
    Or, are literal RE string searches (REs without operators) faster than String.indexOf()? After how many searches?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff one answer:  https://sites.google.com/site/yuta256/sais …    
    
    
    i can haz good paper to review?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries uh dude that was almost a year ago.    
    
    
    When USAToday leads a story with "Turns out there's a cool use for trigonometry" I just want to punch someone. http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2013/02/26/meteor-russia-apollo-space/1948673/ …    
    
    
    The USA Today is like those jocks I went to high school with.    
    
    
    If you're sitting in your car reading your tablet over 4G about tracking meteors using webcams, and your only reaction is "MATH COOL DUH" ..    
    
    
    </tweetrant>    
    
    
    May have to resort to actually writing my own data structures. Most Java folks seem to have forgotten how. I know I'm rusty.    
    
    
    I have a CentOS 5 box which keeps changing /dev/null to a regular file. Anyone seen this and know the culprit?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff seems to be caused by using the mysql cmd as root...    
    
    
    @seamless says, "We didn't find any matches for the keyword 'kosher', [how about these non-kosher restaurants?]" Oh, well.    
    
    
    @djoerd it's definitely mysql(1), gonna strace that sucker.    
    
    
    So pleased that 'shit*says' works as a people query on Twitter. Good job @ruslansv et al.    
    
    
    @djoerd that bug thread is a riot.    
    
    
    Sometimes you just have to lock the door and hack for an hour to make the rest of the day approachable.    
    
    
    Done reviewing for SIGIR. My stack was decidedly below the expected value of the historical acceptance rate. Ah well.    
    
    
    @LeonDerczynski maybe. I've spent lots of time thinking about what the community reqs are to make a PVLDB happen, in the ctxt of SIGIR...    
    
    
    Looking for the tumblr or reddit captioning pictures of Dennis Rodman and Kim Jong-Eun.    
    
    
    The four C's of telecommuting: coffee, cats, couch, and code.    
    
    
    Reading lit on wrapper induction and trying to map it to current ML software packages. I so need to go back to school.    
    
    
    @JeffD classics from the 90s & early 00s. I don't have a hard extraction problem, just looking for the right learning model 4 pat selection    
    
    
    @nealrichter we have a twitter crawler for sharing tweets by reference. Trying to get it to write itself from the gardenhose feed.    
    
    
    I have a new business plan to enable very expensive, convenient access to bad coffee.    
    
    
    @peter_r_bailey except on twitter. where it's ok. to write in sentence fragments. and all lower case an stuff.    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte corollary to the standard rule that bureaucracy is monotonically nondecreasing.    
    
    
    Coming up for air after spending the day training TREC KBA assessors.    
    
    
    Impressed by Woosh (https://pypi.python.org/pypi/Whoosh ). Way too heavy for what I need right now, but a most impressive API.    
    
    
    Snowquester has devolved into a slush fund exercise.    
    
    
    @leifos yes, also lacks an in-memory index. I needed something small and quick and easy, Woosh had one.    
    
    
    Makes me want to write something  MT “@textons: LaTeX document style files in­spired @EdwardTufte http://www.ctan.org/tex-archive/macros/latex/contrib/tufte-latex …”    
    
    
    Every time a web application supports Emacs keybindings in text boxes, an angel gets its wings.    
    
    
    @nancybaym If its the P-Funk Mothership my resume is in your email.    
    
    
    @kegill but if they hasn't given that money to pre-K etc, no one would have been able to go.    
    
    
    @mounialalmas @jteevan leaps-tall-buildings-in-a-single-bound?    
    
    
    @mounialalmas I shall endorse you for kicking ass.    
    
    
    @jteevan for putting 36 hours into every day.    
    
    
    EasyChair has crossed all wires. I'd like to think we #icwsm broke it but we're just not that big.    
    
    
    @kegill Fed funding of education goes beyond loans and grants to college students... from Dept of Ed to NSF, NIH, and DARPA.    
    
    
    @abdur @lintool @gilad it turns out that @SottedReviewer has you all beat to the punch.    
    
    
    Damn meetings, all the good Pope jokes have already been told.    
    
    
    Google docs needs git blame.  That is all.    
    
    
    @hmason unhappy    
    
    
    When I pulled up Google Reader, a dialog informed me that it's shutting down 7/1.  Only button to press said "Ok".  It wasn't.    
    
    
    XLS-complete: (adj) when the data comes in Excel format, but Excel is useless for analyzing it, and it's too big to port. See EasyChair.    
    
    
    Cool tweets from #NSFTask. Also nice to see Slideshare previews in-line.    
    
    
    Note to reviewers: "Nominate for best paper" != "Was this the best paper among the crap we made you read?"    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG part of the XLSC class is that the XLS spreadsheet is to honking huge to load in any other spreadsheet program.    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase I prefer to try and identify the one paper everyone at the conference should really hear.    
    
    
    @lintool you sir are a MacBook Pro.    
    
    
    @sottedreviewer is not funny if you're the PC chair.  Just sayin.    
    
    
    Srsly, @icwsm is not fooling. Monday for real.    
    
    
    "It has been said that EasyChair is the worst conference platform except all the others that have been tried." - Sir Winston Churchill    
    
    
    @anildash maybe Apple's telling you that you need to get out of the city a bit.    
    
    
    