In Search Of: Google Plus Federation | eWEEK Labs http://bit.ly/nPSkpJ     
    
    
    #SteveJobs: My only thought is that I really hope he can get well and stay well. #brightspark    
    
    
    My interview about the new @CIOInsight top IT vendor ratings survey results: the winners and the not-winners. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BZ_pCDibhqQ …    
    
    
    My #ITtrends radio interview yesterday with Butler On Business (26-megabyte non-streaming MP3, sorry): http://www.cyberears.com/cybrss/13659.mp3 …    
    
    
    Last week’s http://thepulsenetwork.com/technology/cio-insight/08-24-11-2011-vendor-value-study/ … and this week’s http://thepulsenetwork.com/technology/cio-insight/08-31-11-guy-currier-of-cio-insight/ … interviews on #vendor #ratings. #ITvendors    
    
    
    @Mashape: This is a big deal. More freedom in the application market means more business #versatility, capabilities. http://soc.li/yzFxeRZ     
    
    
    Sun! I see sun! In New York.    
    
    
    Last week’s Butler On Business radio interview on #virtualization (19-megabyte non-streaming MP3, sorry): http://www.cyberears.com/cybrss/13719.mp3 …    
    
    
    #Netflix share and business woes show #cloudfluidity and the affect of lower market friction on #cloud vendors.    
    
    
    A hands-on look at #Windows8 on a tablet, from @darrylktaft: http://soc.li/cCeVypB  #mobility    
    
    
    My segment Wednesday on the Role of the #CMO and being a business leader in a more techie world @thepulsenetwork http://bit.ly/pu7iFO     
    
    
    R.I.P. Steve, and God bless.    
    
    
    Gene Hall, Gartner CEO: The sheer number of disruptive technologies “creating business uncertainty.” @gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner’s research SVP Peter Sondergaard: “Cloud should [now] be your first approach to computing.” @gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner’s research SVP Peter Sondergaard: 60% of IT organizations will have app stores by 2014. @gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner SVP Sondergaard: “By 2017, the CMO may have a bigger technology budget than the CIO.” @ESLundquist @Gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Chief Gartner fellow Daryl Plummer: “Post-modern businesses invest in customer loyalty to the customer.” @Gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner Research VP Hung LeHong: In the future, IT executives will hire “directors of user experience.” @Gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner VP & Distinguished Analyst Tina Nunno: Today IT leaders must be capable of “creative destruction.” @Gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    Gartner’s Nunno: Being capable of “creative destruction” means being “innovative, dynamic, and amazing.” @Gartner_inc #Symposium keynote    
    
    
    IT growth to remain flat in 2012. Gartner fellow Ken McGee: “If IT spending were a stock, you would not have held.” @Gartner_inc #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner’s Research VP David J. Cappuccio: Virtualization is not a project, but a process. @Gartner_inc #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    The excellent strategy framework provided yesterday by @Gartner_inc at #GartnerSYM, and my mild criticism: http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/it_strategies/gartners_transformation_of_it_strategy.html …    
    
    
    More thoughts from #GartnerSYM: The #Cloud Remains Unclear to Us http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/cloud_computing/the_cloud_remains_unclear_to_us.html … @Gartner_inc    
    
    
    @Gartner_inc says maybe CIOs should give CMOs the technology budget, but manage. Like HR “gives” the salary budget. @ESLundquist    
    
    
    My take on the Internet of Everything from @Gartner_inc http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/mobility/gartners_internet_of_everything.html … #M2M #mobility #wireless #WWAN #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Cool! Qualcomm Presents Its Snapdragon Mobile Platform and the Bug Circus Generator http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CPwDkVnF-YQ&feature=share … #mobility    
    
    
    @VelocityWong The spam web site. I am getting tons of these spam robo-comments. Though dentists probably do make more than we do.    
    
    
    Let me amend: #Stevejobs, you made a few deeply unhappy. And a billion others happier. His “abrasive style”: http://reut.rs/nDE4qK  @reuters    
    
    
    HP’s PC Decision May Not End [Channel] Turmoil http://channelnomics.com/2011/10/24/hp%e2%80%99s-pc-decision-turmoil/ … Me: I thought #HP’s outstanding channel programs would insulate it.    
    
    
    About Our Next Cloud-Computing Research http://bit.ly/n44HI7  #cloud    
    
    
    @csturdevant Living in the Bay Area keeps you mindful of your disaster preparedness, huh? http://labs.eweek.com/archives/nothing-like-a-temblor … #DR    
    
    
    Starting development on our next #cloud computing study. http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/     
    
    
    @srwellman Seeing as the apps for the other two rather stink, I’m not surprised. Wait for Google+, though?    
    
    
    @srwellman (a) Being HTML5 won’t make the coding job better on its own, and (b) we also could use a standard mobile API….    
    
    
    @nkolakowski I do not understand. This is one of my favorite drinks.    
    
    
    Is hardware spending helping delay business hiring? http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/hardware_infrastructure/okay_the_hardware_infrastructure.html … #desktops #notebooks #servers    
    
    
    #HP holds on to #PC business: http://mobile.eweek.com/c/a/Desktops-and-Notebooks/HPs-PC-Division-No-Longer-LatchKey-Kid-839064/?kc=rss … Me: Thanks for playing.    
    
    
    #Windows7 to be the predominant PC #OS by the end of the year: http://soc.li/MSK6sfT  @Gartner_inc @nkolakowski @eWEEKNews    
    
    
    @nkolakowski @petedehn @Gartner_inc @eWEEKNews Use-case segments are the key. Windows 7 probably dominates on PC types you care most about.    
    
    
    I understand the cynics who say #cloud computing is nothing new, and it IS a technology. http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/cloud_computing/commenter_andy_replied_to_my.html …    
    
    
    #Cloud computing, circa 1911: http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/cloud_computing/cloud_computing_in_1911.html …    
    
    
    Transparency joins trust as differentiator in a #cloud era.@Google opens up on its tracking: http://soc.li/IW7O8iR  @ClintBoulton @eWEEKNews    
    
    
    Boomi just one example of the soon-to-boom #cloud developer market. http://bit.ly/sPqD1m  @eWEEKNews @Boomi    
    
    
    Exclusive: 2012’s four fastest-growing IT investment areas: http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/trends/the_four_fastest-growing_technology_areas.html … #tablets #mobility #virtualization #ITtrends    
    
    
    Hadn't thought much about #virtualization of the back channel. @nextio Could be critical....    
    
    
    More new questions at @CloudExpo. Will #singlefabric settle or fuel the networking bandwidth arms race? @bigswitchnews    
    
    
    Could data collection mechanisms do some work locally to reduce the size while increasing the quality of the data stream? #BI #mobility    
    
    
    #Virtualization doesn’t make our exclusive research-based list of the top #ITtrends of 2012 @baseline_mag http://www.baselinemag.com/c/a/Innovation/Top-10-Business-Trends-for-2012-149938/ … Why not?    
    
    
    Don’t ever call winners among #Android, #iOS, etc. http://betweenthelines.baselinemag.com/content/mobility/mobile_platforms_dont_call_any_winners.html … #mobility @jlouderb @baseline_mag @nkolakowski @jasonbrooks    
    
    
    @nkolakowski @jlouderb @baseline_mag @jasonbrooks But /success/ rates of technologies are /often/ predicted on long timelines.    
    
    
    @jasonbrooks @nkolakowski For now, guys. For now. #webOS is nowhere now, but has a real chance at resurrection.    
    
    
    @jasonbrooks @nkolakowski So you agree with me! You’re telling me there’s a chance! YEAH!    
    
    
    @jasonbrooks @nkolakowski Well gents, now Reisinger has weighed in, making your position definitive. http://www.channelinsider.com/c/a/Hewlett-Packard/10-Reasons-HPs-WebOS-Strategy-Wont-Work-480238/?kc=CITCIEMNL12212011STR1 …    
    
    
    Glasses-free #3D on a Mobile 720p Screen, Cool: http://labs.eweek.com/archives/glasses-free-3d-on-a-mobile-720p-screen-cool … And why the enterprise should care. #mobility @eweeklabs @csturdevant    
    
    
    P.J. Connolly’s 2012 Appleverse wish list: http://labs.eweek.com/archives/things-id-like-to-see-from-the-appleverse-in-2012 … @eweeklabs    
    
    
    Mobile Media Spending To Hit $55B In 2012 http://www.mediapost.com/publications/article/166623/mobile-media-spending-to-hit-55b-in-2012.html … @mediapost    
    
    
    Nokia posts over $1B loss just in 4Q11 http://www.telecoms.com/39012/nokia-posts-e954m-loss-in-q4/ … Me: How’s that partnership looking, #Microsoft? #mobility @nkolakowski    
    
    
    BTW, #Motorola posted a puny loss in 4Q12 http://www.reuters.com/article/2012/01/26/us-motorolamobility-idUSTRE80P23W20120126 …. Not a blow for Google, nope. #mobility #eggsinonebasket @nkolakowski    
    
    
    @nkolakowski @lawinski It’s fine for eating so long as you share.    
    
    
    For the next three months everyone, if I write “4Q12” I mean “4Q11,” and feel free to laugh at me.    
    
    
    @nkolakowski I’m bullish on Windows Phone as you know, Nick—just not on the amazingness of the Nokia partnership. #eggsinonebasket #mobility    
    
    
    @nkolakowski @lawinski You are so pessimistic. If it doesn’t kill you, it makes you stronger.    
    
    
    Opportunities from #healthcare using #social media: http://soc.li/Klor6UU  @alisoncdiana I’m speaking in March at http://healthitinsight.com/     
    
    
    Billion-dollar quarterly loss, anyone? More bad news for the #Euroconomy: #Nokia layoffs. http://huff.to/xQnTnJ  @nkolakowski #mobility    
    
    
        
    
    
    Been thinking about cookie-free user recognition for years. http://www.adtruth.com/why.html  @Ad_Truth #privacy    
    
    
    There's a child at my daughter's school named Hiree. 3 years old. Is that about the #economy?    
    
    
    I said 3 y. ago in internal memo ZDE should go to this model. Not sure I still agree; have learned a lot. http://lnkd.in/Bq8xje     
    
    
    Windows 8 on ARM Could Challenge Apple iPad 3 http://soc.li/qpofp8L  Me: W8 is Microsoft’s secret IT weapon. @eWEEKnews @nkolakowski    
    
    
    Tech Unlike: Hey Browser! Don’t Assume One Day Is Typical http://techunlike.blogspot.com/2012/02/hey-browser-dont-assume-one-day-is.html?spref=tw … @Samsung #tablets #mobility #productivity    
    
    
    @pcalento Enjoy! Wish I was going myself.    
    
    
    @GordonPlutsky Happy to see all the glum faces up there about the Super Bowl, are you?    
    
    
    BlackBerry PlayBook 2.0 review: http://tabtimes.com/review/ittech-os-blackberry/2012/02/21/blackberry-playbook-20-review-email-and-calendar … Don’t count anyone out in #mobility; RIM still has enterprise advantages. @nkolakowski    
    
    
    #SxSW infographic http://bit.ly/y5mt6M  U.S. fans look like a better #DRM bet than European.    
    
    
    @Evernote needs to get its #cloud infrastructure straight. It keeps reverting notes to old, superceded versions.    
    
    
    Living in NYC means running, running, running. Right? And today it means running, running, running in the rain.    
    
    
    Microsoft releases Windows 8 Consumer Preview | @TabTimes http://tabtimes.com/feature/ittech-os-windows/2012/02/29/microsoft-releases-windows-8-consumer-preview-and-it-much … Me: I continue to be bullish on the importance of Windows 8.    
    
    
    But to me, a rising business specialty, not a new paradigm. IBM’s Bhambri on #bigdata marketing: http://rww.to/wh6QyQ  @RWW @SMFulton3    
    
    
    Super-cool imagined integration of nature and habitation: 2012 Skyscraper Design Competition http://media.talkingpointsmemo.com/slideshow/skyscraper-competition/1-258658 … @TPM @eVoloMagazine    
    
    
    @Gartner_inc: “Personal Cloud” to Replace PC by 2014 http://www.wired.com/cloudline/2012/03/personal-cloud-2014/ … Nonsense. Should say #cloud will _augment_ PC use. @wired    
    
    
    Yes! Media is home of all market research innovation and growth today. Google gets into MR: http://bit.ly/HmOIKM  @ResearchShare    
    
    
    @ResearchShare Murphy is right that Google’s move into market research is good for MR. http://www.greenbookblog.org/2012/03/30/google-makes-their-market-research-play-now-what/ … This is a retail MR play, folks.    
    
    
    HP’s split personality http://shar.es/rf2pU  @Elliotmark1    
    
    
    @nkolakowski Nice work! http://slashdot.org/topic/bi/  Need to check out SlashCloud, too.    
    
    
    Nice summary of the #cloud reassessment moment we’re in @lmwalsh2112 http://channelnomics.com/2012/06/08/delivering-solutions-peak-cloud/ …    
    
    
    #Cloud risk in a nutshell. Users must be able to use #LinkedIn, but then your org’s public image is in LinkedIn’s hands. #cloudfail    
    
    
    It’s fine to have 1,000 points of #opensource #cloud. Integration will always be critical anyway. @InformationWeek http://twb.io/KRlsmF     
    
    
    @Gartner_inc: #SDN a critical 2013 trend & may move value from NW devices to a central controller. Me: Implies commoditization. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner: #Hybrid #cloud critical in 2013 & not about tech; complexity up but cost down. Me: Does simplify, for users and admins. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Device and OS freedom at hand due to #cloud? Gartner says client & #server architectures will change. Think image not machine. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner’s Cappuccio says IT tasked with all three of agility, service levels, good economics & they don’t always overlap. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner: By 2014 30% of orgs using #SaaS for IT ops tools will switch to on-premise because of poor service levels. #cloud #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    (I work @DellEnterprise.) Nice analogy for today’s #infrastructure from Dell’s Andy Rhodes: A car with parts from many makers. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    (I work @DellEnterprise.) Dell’s Rhodes expands #convergence definition to three layers: hardware, mgmt, packaging. #DoMoreIT #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    (I work @DellEnterprise.) Dell’s Rhodes: With #converged, experts can add high value, not instance VMs or add blades. #DoMoreIT #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    (I work @DellEnterprise.) #Dell’s Active System #converged customer @iland reduced #infrastructure deployment time 5x. #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner defining sol’n architecture as union of info, tech, and biz viewpoints. Me: But user viewpoint big driver. #iwork4dell #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner’s Cearley: #Cloud is not about savings. Me: Hallelujah! Cearley: It’s about agility. Me: It’s about focus. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Nice perspective from Gartner’s Cearley: The security environment is _different_ with #cloud, not worse (or better). #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Nice #cloud strategic model from Gartner uses application benefit, challenge levels to determine platform, approach. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    I know I’ve said for years that agility is the key #cloud benefit. But now I think “focus” is a better way to express this. #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Gartner: To adopt #cloud, IT must rethink how org’ed and governed. Me: It will actually happen the other way round. #iwork4dell #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner: IT should act as (sole) #cloud provider _and_ broker, meaning #hybrid IT with goal to “protect and serve.” #iwork4dell #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    Gartner “#hybrid IT” concept, IT as #cloud provider + broker, complicates things. How to integrate new IT silos? #iwork4dell #GartnerSYM    
    
    
    @GordonPlutsky “Unique.”    
    
    
    @michael_keen Follow-up questions in the session are highlighting this. 3+ new IT groups, reporting up to where and how working together?    
    
    
    @michael_keen An attendee just said, “We’re losing the thread of enterprise arch.” (Answer was, “It becomes a multi-sourcing arch., t/b/d.”)    
    
    
    @michael_keen Agree. Didn't see a prescription in the session on how, though. New org elements were added instead. #iwork4dell    
    
    
    At Gartner’s “fabric-based” (converged) session, few fans of vertical application-based stacks in the audience. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Gartner: Resource pool managers are the key differentiators for #converged models, and foundation for #cloud mgmt. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Gartner: Need #cloud strategy to have #converged strategy. >Strong endorsement of converged as a key cloud approach! #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    @michael_keen I think I overstated it. From its clients, Gartner is seeing strong cloud onramp via “fabric” solutions.    
    
    
    Gartner’s David Mitchell Smith reminds his audience: #cloud disrupts as much for vendors as for IT. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Gartner’s Smith reveals they created #BPaaS category to sensibly encompass Google. >Now I get it! Web sites. Good! #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    @rglauser @Gartner_inc Completely agree but also this is more we’ll have to define for #cloud. #cloudconfusion #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Cloud vendor approaches by their history. HW, SW, SP, but also open source & “personal cloud.” >Useful. #GartnerSYM #iwork4dell    
    
    
    @mobilearchitect I think that’s backwards. #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Dell has shipped 1M webscale servers in five years to arm the cloud http://gigaom.com/cloud/dell-has-sold-1m-webscale-servers-in-five-years/ … >Congrats @DellDCS! #iwork4dell    
    
    
    #ARMprocessors seem to be getting everywhere. What’s their advantage over #intel? @PCWorld: http://www.pcworld.com/article/2013429/dell-testing-64bit-arm-server-with-chip-from-appliedmicro.html … @pcworld #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Again, what exactly is the #ARMprocessors advantage over #Intel? Apple might use for their desktops. @BW: http://buswk.co/SQ6JI3  #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Looking for insights from @LaunchClinic on effective and pragmatic storytelling for an IT vendor. #iwork4dell    
    
    
    @Dell customers share insights and advice about accelerating the adoption of #cloud - via @NnamdiatDell | http://del.ly/6017pmmT     
    
    
    With Cloud, Everything Old Is New Again http://techpageone.com/technology/with-cloud-everything-old-is-new-again/ … #iwork4dell    
    
    
    I am just going to call it “#cloud” from now on. No “the.” http://techpageone.com/technology/what-we-talk-about-when-we-talk-about-cloud/ …    
    
    
    Nice summary of the challenges of taking desktop #db applications to #cloud. @FJO_Writes_Tech http://del.ly/6014pLKe  #appdev #cloudification    
    
    
    GigaOM’s week in #cloud : #Amazon gets mobile, #HP reopens old wound; #Dell delays. @gigabarb http://del.ly/6011pLtH  #OpenStack #iwork4dell    
    
    
    I’ve started following a remarkable colleague’s impressive #art hobby. She sez: Use More Paint! @teresadeonis http://del.ly/6016pLtM     
    
    
    Your #cloud #virtualdesktop on a stick: http://del.ly/6014VWQa  #iwork4dell    
    
    
    In What Realm Does Cloud Really Operate? Clearing up cloud claims to solve everything. http://del.ly/6015VoEJ  #IaaS #SaaS #iwork4dell    
    
    
    Dell survey cited, #smallbiz 69% prefer #cloud apps to off-the-shelf. @USATODAY http://del.ly/6017VoAS  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Smallbiz 69% prefer #cloud apps @USATODAY http://del.ly/6014VUzp  > Fast and efficient. But if you grow, beware of lock-in. #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Hybrid #Cloud: The Best of Both Worlds | Tech Page One @ZDB2B http://del.ly/6016VUNE  > Public vs. private is a false choice. #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Dell PowerEdge C6220 #cloud #server wins an @infoworld Technology of the Year award: “great flexibility” http://del.ly/6015VUAH  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    It’s Called “#Cloud” Because It Used to Mean Something Different | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6012VqHq  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    We called it “#cloud” because that described how it looked. But that’s not what it means any more. http://del.ly/6016Vqgu  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Dell PowerEdge #server Fresh Air technology for operations at higher temperatures and #greenIT savings http://del.ly/6014Vqmn  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Apple cuts iPhone parts orders @WSG http://del.ly/6010VsyC  > Always know, _every_ #brand / #businessmodel has vulnerabilities. #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Cloud growing up? “Pre-adolescent stage.” > It’s Looking Like the Year of #Cloud #Security @MikellAtDell http://del.ly/6016VsPn  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Another speed play for #cloud. > Cloud #appdev saves developers 1 hr. of every 8 @evansdatacorp @pjkrill http://del.ly/6018VswM  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Let’s Consider Some Names for #Cloud | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6012VsUw  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Cloud used for growth, Dell example > Hitting The Reset Button In Federal IT @kjones150 http://del.ly/6015VtBt  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    What It’s Like To Ride SpaceX’s Grasshopper Reusable #Rocket (VIDEO) @TPM http://del.ly/6017VteJ  #spaceflight    
    
    
    Cloud-Based Development ≠ Development of #Cloud | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6017VQhS  #appdev #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Channel essential to big #ITtrends like #cloud. > Dell Engineers Club launched - The Times of India http://del.ly/6019VvhL  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Good debate-starter. > Java vs. C#: Which Performs Better in the 'Real World'? @WriteWithJeff @srwellman http://del.ly/6018VaEC  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    I keep plugging away at this > A Practical Definition of #Cloud | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6014VaFy  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    First and sixth pretty iffy but a really good watch list > #Cloud trends in 2013 | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6013VIjd  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AAdkB3  #OpenFlow has a good future because there are big IT vendors (like my employer, Dell) seeking to disrupt. But it’s...    
    
    
    Get #ITservicelevels into the conversation … now | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6017VIox  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Cloud isn’t about service or deployment models > Cloud-Supporting vs. ‘Actually’ Cloud | Tech Page One http://del.ly/6014VFJ4  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    #Cloud “has already won” (bonus: The Who) > Enterprise Technology @ascohen http://del.ly/6016VFiA  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    @stephenodonnell Hello there. I look forward to following your remarks, and to sharing conversations about this crazy world of #IT.    
    
    
    @DellintheClouds helps customers spin up #privatecloud through @Rackspace program http://del.ly/6014V7Zo  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Myths of Weight Loss Are Plentiful, Researcher Says http://nyti.ms/WRAMk4     
    
    
    On big game day, @Dell has its own take on #workplaybalance http://del.ly/6012n61w  #domore #iwork4dell    
    
    
    On big game day, @Dell has its own take on #workplaybalance http://del.ly/6016n6Kp  #domore #iwork4dell    
    
    
    On big game day, @Dell has its own take on #workplaybalance http://del.ly/6012n6Kw  #domore #iwork4dell    
    
    
    On big game day, @Dell has its own take on #workplaybalance http://del.ly/6013n6Kb  #domore #iwork4dell    
    
    
    New #converged solution for SAP #HANA announced at @Dell Technology Camp Europe @InformationWeek http://del.ly/6010n6Tu  #CI #Iwork4Dell    
    
    
    Baobabs under #stars a stunning shot (10th photo) > 2013 Sony World Photography Awards @TPM http://del.ly/6014n8Yy     
    
    
    Maybe this is why so many artists are misfits? > Letting go of certainties to fuel #creativity @teresadeonis http://del.ly/6017nDRt     
    
    
    Mobile and #cloud computing spur tripling of micro server shipments in 2013, says IHS @DIGITIMES http://del.ly/6016nD54  #iwork4dell    
    
    
    @DellNetworking Makes #SDN Push With New Switch, #OpenFlow Support @eWEEKNews http://del.ly/6012nEsM  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Entrepreneur Ed Bussey at @encountry Forum, how Michael @Dell inspired him @KellyDolanUK @edwardbussey http://del.ly/6012n3FA  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    This concept can be stretched further > @SpectorAtDell on: What is an #Infrastructure #Cloud? http://del.ly/6013nOXZ  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Uh-oh. For a while at one time, my name meant “d-bag” … supposedly. http://qr.ae/TRApf     
    
    
    Creativity as competitive advantage - Part 1 (using agencies) @teresadeonis http://del.ly/6016nPXE  > Me: You will still get the credit, too    
    
    
    1st rule for #social tech: “Don’t be creepy” > When Do You Take Off Your #GoogleGlasses? | LinkedIn http://del.ly/6014nujy     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/krxr94  More like "necessary alternative to #BYOD " >    
    
    
    @Dell teams with @VMware on pre-configured #virtual desktop pool @ZDNet http://del.ly/6018nw1y  #VDI #Iwork4Dell    
    
    
    Great #jazzbass groove for the day, from Esperanza Spalding @youtube http://youtu.be/Nppb01xhfe0     
    
    
    #MDM enables a single version of truth. @Boomi delivers MDM’s next generation quickly and effectively: http://del.ly/6017n70L  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Dell @Boomi AtomSphere named a top 10 #cloud tool by @CIO_Australia http://del.ly/6018X8mp  @DellintheClouds #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Check those bridge heights, truck and camper drivers! via @TPM http://www.prochan.com/view?p=da1_1351183858 …    
    
    
    @Dell Launches Dell Create, Media and Entertainment Consultancy @StreamingMedia @TDreier http://del.ly/6013XGEb  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    @DellNetworking launches Active Fabric solutions featuring #SDN > Keeping things open. @eWEEKNews http://del.ly/6011XKFz  #cloud #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Hello, Guy Currier here, longtime #BI, #IT, and #cloud market researcher now @Dell Boomi. First time participating here. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @SoftwareHollis National debt is a great #bigdata analogy! #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner I thought of #Hypecycle too but think #bigdata is way to the left right now. Baby stage. #Iwork4dell #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Small steps today toward full #bigdata should yield big rewards. #Iwork4dell #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Good #bigdata start. RT @howarddresner: Org. I know doing cool things operationally. PhDs. Analysis in RDBMS, #BI #Iwork4dell #BIWisdom    
    
    
    RT Right! @RevenueMaven: diff is name & content RT @tech_colorado: Most companies have been doing big data for years. … #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner @RevenueMaven Most won’t know how to manage their online persona. #newclasdivide #Iwork4dell #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Thanks @howarddressner for hosting. See you again soon. #Iwork4dell #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @SoftwareHollis Good to meet you, too.    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog Thanks for the warm welcome.    
    
    
    @mikejulietbravo Those two hail from a cultural soup region but their family considers themselves Chechen.    
    
    
    We'll be talking #enterpriseIT #SW, services Wednesday in SF – join us virtually. http://del.ly/6010Xu2k  #DoMore #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    1 hr. from now re: #convergence and #cloud: @BernardGolden, @cote, a provider, and a user http://del.ly/6012XViY  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Swainson, @JoanneMorreti, Kendra: @DellSoftware eases modern #IT challenges, to help it #DoMore http://del.ly/6018XnUE     
    
    
    Dell’s @cote: Let #cloud make the capabilities "chaos" blossom, later pull it all in. 18:00 mark: http://del.ly/6010XnF8  #DoMore    
    
    
    TIP: When you’re in a bathroom stall, turn off the Keyboard Clicks on your iPhone. #kindacreepy    
    
    
    Good recap of yesterday’s @DellSoftware announcements @rachelking http://del.ly/6017XXNV  #BYOD #BI #cloud #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    @samcharrington Agree. The #cloud model creates market fluidity and kills market friction.    
    
    
    Hello again, Guy Currier here, I’ve been a #BI, #IT, and #cloud market researcher and now am @Dell Boomi. Second time here. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner Thanks for the warm welcome. I agree with @ManBagBlog that it’s reporting that has shown leaps. #thatsallthough #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner Agree but if you think about tablet-based reporting, big demand generator from the executive level. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @GenesisSAP @EvansBI This generational familiarity will increase demand and give support to solve #BI implementation problems #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI @howarddresner Very good point! #IT is overstressed and sees the structural issues but not many answers yet. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI @howarddresner #IT has real business concerns, but risk-oriented and technical. It is learning to be faster right now. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI @ManBagBlog @howarddresner Of course #cloud will help all round but is not a #magicpill #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog Oh, organizations and subsequently #IT are attacking everything at once! #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Thanks for another great discussion @howarddresner and everyone. See you again soon #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Fastest check-in and security ever thanks to Sunday morning and the new @Delta line at @AUStinAirport    
    
    
    Off for a week of #dataarchitecture #datagovernance #integration learning. And I thought I was only a coding geek (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Listening to @DataTodd Sicard of BCBS of Minnesota explain how to create a #dataarchitecture that will actually get done #EDW13    
    
    
    BCBS of MN 19s Sicard: When theory meets reality, #realityalwayswins. So the architect must anticipate reality @DataTodd (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Neat idea from BCBS of MN's Sicard: "Scope+1." What's just outside of scope and must be clear will NOT be done @DataTodd (#EDW13)    
    
    
    #EDW13 attendees seem to be going wild for #Hadoop #BigData. Why? Because it's wicked tech? (#EDW13)    
    
    
    BCBS of MN's Sicard sez if data behavior at nasty/crazy level (e.g. SOA), testing an added problem of its own @DataTodd (#EDW13...    
    
    
    Might be more boozing outside the orientation session than listening inside #letloose (#EDW13)    
    
    
    @cote In-N-Out comes to Round Rock first, right?    
    
    
    These Facebook Home ads are #kindacreepy    
    
    
    Outstanding pick-up @HaifeiLi > RT @infoworld McAfee spots Adobe Reader PDF-tracking flaw http://shar.es/lbRPm  #informationsecurity    
    
    
    Should be a nice San Diego morning once the fog burns off. (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Just sat down for hardcore #dataintegration learning session from April Reeve of EMC @datagrrl (#EDW13)    
    
    
    EMC's Reeve: the business side of #dataintegration is too often ignored (#EDW13)    
    
    
    EMC's Reeve: "Not enough is being done to manage the full lifecycle of data" @datagrrl (#EDW13)    
    
    
    EMC's Reeve sez the adv. of batch processing is speed (quick per transaction), esp. w/ compliance needs @datagrrl (#EDW13)    
    
    
    EMC's Reeve sez real-time #integration shifts focus to process modeling. Me: this suits biz alignment @datagrrl (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Really great point from EMC's Reeve. Data warehouse was invented to give speed, but #cloud means very varied latency @datagrrl ...    
    
    
    Sounds like lots of great concepts in #datagovernance tutorial, e.g. everyone governs, scope is what differs @rseiner (#EDW13)    
    
    
    @Datagrrl Thank you for schooling us on #dataintegration needs opportunities strategies    
    
    
    Mike Ferguson of Intelligent Business Strategies on MDM: for biz mgmt buy-in describe impact of NOT managing the data @mikeferguson1 #EDW13    
    
    
    @mikeferguson1 sez mass participation in #datagovernance breeds mass adoption. Me: and mass consent (#EDW13)    
    
    
    In @mikeferguson1's tutorial he tells us what MDM is really for. It's to remove strands in your #spaghettiarchitecture (#EDW13)    
    
    
    @mikeferguson1: Elements of #masterdata single view are global IDs, master single biz view, and knowledge of ALL mappings (#EDW...    
    
    
    Remaining users are more dedicated > Facebook lost 6MM U.S. visitors last month, 4% http://del.ly/6018Xd4u  #bettermedia    
    
    
    @mikeferguson1 Is #MDM an enabler of #singlescreen (in general)? (#EDW13)    
    
    
    "Seen Offc Space, where the character complains abt having 8 bosses? Well, I have 54." @Dell BYOD solns http://del.ly/6014XetI  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    Our customer's presentation on decentralized resource interoperation (#EDW13)    
    
    
    When the need to hyper-scale dictates #cloud, how to maintain and manage data? The LinkedIn example #Iwork4dell (#EDW13)    
    
    
    LinkedIn's Alex Lai: predictive analytics #dataintegration "turned salespeople from beat cops into Batman" #Iwork4dell (#EDW13)    
    
    
    In 2005 @boomi "bet the company" on cloud - learn what that means for #middleware and #MDM (#EDW13)    
    
    
    #Governance critical to #SOA success, says Harvard Pilgrim's Biderman. Few in room have it (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Harvard Pilgrim's Biderman: #SOA #governance is about the plumbing, not what's in the pipes (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Nice plug by Biderman for your new book @Datagrrl (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Maneesh Joshi @SnapLogic: Stack becoming commoditized. Me: moves value toward biz functionality (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Finally the clouds burning off in San Diego - but not the #cloud (#EDW13)    
    
    
    Address biz needs for social #datagovernance; personal needs are 2nd step, sez http://Data.com 's Orun @DataMinstrel (#EDW13)    
    
    
    http://Data.com 's Orun: Social #datagovernance scales very well when driven by biz value @DataMinstrel (#EDW13)    
    
    
    More #datagovernance coolness from Dan Meers. Data is inherently inert; it's people and process you're actually managing (#EDW1...    
    
    
    Right back atcha RT @Datagrrl: Fun tweeps at #EDW13 w @DataMinstrel #FF #data    
    
    
    The real reason why @Dell wants to go private: To fondle big Boomis http://del.ly/6012XWon  > @boomi Summer '13 release    
    
    
    #Integration of "on-prem and #cloud apps w/o totally disrupting existing envirs" @boomi @ChrisMcNabb1 http://del.ly/6011XqwH  #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    @DellintheClouds 'refining' OpenStack public #cloud plans - Network World http://m.networkworld.com/news/2013/051513-dell-openstack-cloud-269778.html … #Iwork4dell    
    
    
    @mphnyc People listen to vendors saying tech answers problems all on its own. They forget about process, training, briefings #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @GenesisSAP @mphnyc Incorporating #BI into the business as a process more important than deploying the tech #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @BillyBobBrigmon Might agree with you about #BI success metric but then the finger-pointing only starts #BIWisdom    
    
    
    So they are saying “Mission Accomplished?” RT @howarddresner: From our latest #BI Study, 40% say completely successful w/ BI #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Hello, Guy Currier back again, longtime #BI, #IT, and #cloud market researcher now marketing @Dell @Boomi #applicationintegration #BIWisdom    
    
    
    #BI interest is not down, people just starting to realize they don’t know what it means #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner #BI sentiment measured how, with what base sizes? #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner @chuck_hooper Definitely the beginning of more value. #InfiniteMarketing #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog That is why I asked about sample size :-) #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @howarddresner @RevenueMaven I think data professionals mean “unstructured” by #BigData but everyone else, “explosion of data” #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @huck5 @howarddresner Hard to imagine there will never be training or change in biz or IT mindset for #BigData #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @huck5 Yes, I am talking about #BigData market not individual journeys which will be problematic to say the least #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @huck5 Sounds like it has #InfiniteMarketing potential #infinitelypervasivelargedata #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Thanks, everyone! Interesting check-in on the state of #BigData, and we coined two new terms for it. #InfiniteMarketing #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Hello, first-timer Guy Currier here, longtime #cloud, #IT, and #BI market researcher now marketing @Dell @Boomi #cloudviews    
    
    
    A1 @dstrom The goals are all that matter. Set #cloud goals early, whatever they are. That is the tough part #cloudviews    
    
    
    @kdemacop Those of us who’ve been hyping #cloud for all these years knew its success would be bigger than expected #cloudviews    
    
    
    A1. Even if toughest part for #cloud is setting goals, 2nd-toughest is finding ALL the metrics that that measure its success #cloudviews    
    
    
    A2. Lack of adoption (siloing, limited capability), time to value >3 months, launch cost higher than planned = #cloudfailure #cloudviews    
    
    
    A2. Misalignment to goals is actual #cloudfailure, but siloing, lengthy deployment, cost drive _perceived_ cloud failure #cloudviews    
    
    
    A3. #Backup, #replication, #integration the three keys to #cloud success and avoiding vendor lock-in #cloudviews    
    
    
    Very good point! > RT @maishsk @AndiMann Part of a service can use cloud, trick is dissect into layers & move suitable ones #cloudviews    
    
    
        
    
    
    A5. Helps if we all still take the long view about #cloud adoption #cloudviews    
    
    
    Agree > RT @NerdBlurt: @GuyCresearchIT @maishsk @tcrawford #cloud until ppl are educated and adopt the new they prefer old way #cloudviews    
    
    
    @grifmon Value of #privatecloud is in maintaining #IT control while improving service and experience for end-users #cloudviews    
    
    
    A6. #cloudconfusion is the new normal, if you ask me #cloudviews    
    
    
    For _every_ org at this point > RT @bmkatz: A6. for open-minded mature orgs cloud is a defacto tool in tool belt #cloudviews    
    
    
    @bmkatz Agree, but reality already smacking them in face even if they tell themselves it’s only a light breeze #cloudviews    
    
    
    Great chat everyone, thanks @CloudCommons for hosting! @cmneedles @CA_cloud #cloudviews    
    
    
        
    
    
    @bmkatz You’re not cynical enough about #techadoption or #IT. I guess you were never a reseller #cloudviews    
    
    
    Focus #appdev tightly on your IP > Google Making It Easier to Build #Mobile Apps @TechManTalking http://del.ly/6011kg2D     
    
    
    @ChrisMcNabb1 at #CloudSlam: “In #healthcare #cloud offers a new #TCO model, that’s the real value”    
    
    
    @tsbarton at #CloudSlam: Novartis needed to meet current #middleware needs, but new platforms too e.g. #mobility, #cloud    
    
    
    @tsbarton at #CloudSlam: #middleware licensing cost is not the big bang of saving money or time or of innovating > it’s ops    
    
    
    @shannonatdell And thank you Ms. Shannon. Yes, I am thrilled!    
    
    
    High demand indicator > @MeriTalk: #Cloud could save $11B for #healthIT @HITNewsTweet @GovHITeditor http://del.ly/6016khdM     
    
    
    Thanks @lewandog for hosting today’s #BIWisdom tweet chat. Dashboards get users excited, which drives more use (two Qs with one A!)    
    
    
    Good point! Dashboards can over-control reporting > RT @lewandog: @chuck_hooper #BIWisdom So...information suppression is also a factor?    
    
    
    #informationoverload A: We say we are delivering information, but the art of #BI is actually in what not to show. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    #informationoverload A: If the #BI UX is transparent, that builds trust and answers problem, for better insights. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @lewandog Agree but my point is that it should be clear that the #BI system is being selective by design. #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog I’d be surprised if as many as 1 in 20 #BI UXes or dashboards are transparent. I think more like 1% #BIWisdom    
    
    
        
    
    
    My new post on the quintessential tasks for fully adopting #cloud: http://del.ly/6012ZOKu  @TechPageOne    
    
    
    The coming appification and LOBification of IT > What #futureIT dep’t will look like @TechPageOne http://del.ly/6012ZOfg     
    
    
    @mphnyc Try Twubs.    
    
    
    Thanks @huck5! Guy Currier here again. #BI, #BigData, #IT, #cloud watcher for years. Now at @Dell @Boomi (#integration cloud / #iPaaS).    
    
    
    This is about delivery channel, not application. #Cloud delivery impacts #BI at the dashboard level @ManBagBlog @jenstirrup #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog Give partners more control of what they see via #cloud and they will bring their agendas into your #BI #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @jenstirrup I meant that the UX is the point of impact and the #cloud affect on #BI works backwards from there #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @MarkBradbourne @ManBagBlog Point of #cloud is give some control to user, at UI. That power shift affects control of your #BI #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @MarkBradbourne Yes. But other point of #cloud is to allow you to draw that line, so you only gain better biz relationships #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI #IThealth is going to the #cloud. Cloud SPs are bending over backwards to show security, compliance #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @MarkBradbourne Nice one! #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @jenstirrup @EvansBI @huck5 @ManBagBlog Def. of “leaving Portugal” must be precise. Acct-holders can get acct info anywhere, no? #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @nancykoppdw That’s for sure—the perennial #ITsecurity problem #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @nancykoppdw Depends on the specific name. Amazon yes, because they are good. But it only takes one #cloud fool #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI But #cloud scales for multiple users unlike on-premises, bringing large-scale–level #ITcompliance to SMBs too #BIWisdom    
    
    
    True that! > RT @nancykoppdw: #cloud will allow us to spend resources on innovation as opposed to operations, that's something #biwisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog I think lack of understanding of pretty much everything about #cloud is barrier, not just risk levels #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI IT will want #privatecloud before public. Users won’t care and will just get public #cloud on their own #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @EvansBI Hah! This is why I got into the #integration business #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog Uneasiness from loss of control is a big #BI barrier, from both #cloud delivery and #explosivedatagrowth #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @ManBagBlog @nancykoppdw Me too, data pipeline challenges is a terrific #BI topic #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @nancykoppdw There are many #cloud delivery vendors now—look up application modernization #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @nancykoppdw I shouldn’t answer because my employer (Dell) offers it ;-). Thanks for a great discussion, everyone #BIWisdom    
    
    
    @jenstirrup @EvansBI @huck5 @ManBagBlog #Cloud can deliver in-country #data stores. #Latency would be an issue, tho #BIWisdom    
    
    
    Tech and the triathlete > Neat @Dell and @Intel promotional video recently tweeted again by @khwilliamson http://del.ly/6017ZTIh     
    
    
    On the movement of #enterpriseapps to #cloud @miklernout @EntApps2Day    
    
    
    Infographic: Turning Internal Experts into #Social Influencers from the super-sharp @AmyTennison http://del.ly/6017Zkch  #SocBiz    
    
    
    @SwampyTheGator I Tri-Ducked "Meet Swampy" #wheresmywater pic.twitter.com/wEBIHlYtOX    
    
    
    @mariaburpee Ha ha, now we all want to know what ELSE you've been called.    
    
    
    Sometimes you need to @Happify (with the science of happiness) @becketmorgan @TechPageOne http://del.ly/6012ZWa6     
    
    
    @mariaburpee Nice! I met Mother Teresa. She pinched my cheek (I was 28).    
    
    
    5 Elements Your #Cloud Infrastructure Needs to Enable #Application Agility @bernardgolden @CIOonline http://del.ly/6018ZQtO     
    
    
    New U.S. Dept. of HHS study: provider #data exchange up 41% ’08–’12 h/t @health_care_IT http://del.ly/6017Zv7B  #healthIT #HIE    
    
    
    Nice one @AmyTennison! > Social Business Lessons @TechPageOne http://del.ly/6019ZxcS  #socialmedia #socialmarketing    
    
    
    @JoanneMoretti @DellSoftware on Dell’s emergence in IT software and services @DBJDanielle @DallasBizNews http://del.ly/6018ZLps     
    
    
    @JoAnneMoretti @JoannMoretti Yes it was! Thanks, Jo Anne. LOL I will take better care next time.    
    
    
    Please join the #BIWisdom tweet chat today at 1 PM / 10 AM hosted by @ManBagBlog #BI #businessintelligence #BigData #analytics    
    
    
    Yes, at this point #cloud _improves_ #informationsecurity > Cloud and #healthIT @DrAndyLitt @DellHealth http://del.ly/6018ZNoy     
    
    
    Take that @awscloud > @IBMcloud $1B #Cloud Deal w/ Interior Dept. @ElenaBigApple @InformationWeek http://del.ly/6017ZCAh  #CloudFirst    
    
    
    @editingwhiz A little surprised I wasn’t following you already. Check my bio, I am now at @Dell @boomi    
    
    
    Yes! I’ve said for years that top reason is “losing control”  > Why enterprises are frightened of #cloud http://del.ly/6011wFnH     
    
    
    Nice clear discussion of #DevOps from @barton808 @Dell http://del.ly/6016bEBn  @chrissyfarr @VentureBeat    
    
    
    @ktburnside Are you at #SMaC2013 in person? Come find me! (I just want to embarrass you on the big board)    
    
    
    @lizbbullock Great to see you at the @Dell #SMaC2013 UnConference. Looking forward to hearing about your latest successes    
    
    
    Infographic: @Netskope tracks #cloud app usage http://del.ly/6014bmEa     
    
    
    Happy Internet Day, everyone. 44 years ago today, the Internet was turned on    
    
    
    3/21 focus group. Hardcore IT folks, but they preferred business messaging to tech messaging.    
    
    
    The MPAA was created to rate movies. The CTIA? Not so much. http://unhub.com/Nbxt #ctia #ctiaw11 #apps #mediapost    
    
    
    You have an enterprise log-in for your PC. But not for your company-provided smartphone. Problem, no? #mobility    
    
    
    RIM calls it a day and it’s the #OSwars all over again. This time Apple vs. Google instead of vs. Microsoft. #Android #iOS #BlackBerry    
    
    
    AT&T to sell phone with 3-D screen. Means: Even better app interfaces coming! http://bit.ly/gsXuvG    
    
    
    @nkolakowski Nick, what you’re gently not saying is, tablet market only a year old; too early to care about “winners.” http://bit.ly/gsXuvG    
    
    
    This reads like a Sheridan play. I mean really: Mayor Dinwiddie? Really? http://bit.ly/fsjYCy #nytimes    
    
    
    Two nerd-jocks show how computers can sense emotion. http://bit.ly/hUMhRB #nytimes #parallelism    
    
    
    @nkolakowski And in the end, tablets and smartphones will be like PCs, 10% Apple and 90% The Big Brand.    
    
    
    Different kinds of applications come with different security risks. Do these differences change when mobile? #mobility    
    
    
    Crazy mad skills! Indi Cowie performs her trick freestyle moves. http://unhub.com/S-y7 #soccer #nytimes    
    
    
    My editorial director ready to kill me. Once again, last-minute inspiration for event slides. This one on #CloudComputing, big surprise.    
    
    
    LOL Will SC send back all Federal funds that keep the lights on, too? http://bit.ly/geI47N #green #newsrepublic #ap    
    
    
    Marginal burden of a new mobile platform the same no matter how many actual devices you adopt. And new platforms are inevitable. #mobility    
    
    
    Nearly half a BILLION smartphones to sell in 2011, says IDC. http://bit.ly/hb9O1b #mobility #idc #newsrepublic #afp    
    
    
    @nkolakowski Did that Windows Phone 7 IDC report come with an uncertainty warning? ;-) #mobility #idc #eweek    
    
    
    I’m video interviewed about The Great Mobility Battle for the Soul of the Enterprise. http://unhub.com/c72g #mobility #cio #CIOInsight    
    
    
    @nkolakowski Apple’s brand equity trumps Zune’s any day. But on the other hand, people are starting to detest Apple.    
    
    
    Google’s new +1 and Salesforce’s Radian6 acquisition: growing social data flood for businesses. #BI #socialresearch    
    
    
    You and your users’ PCs arrive hobbled out of the box. http://unhub.com/UEnG #PC #Windows    
    
    
    Cool new commercial jets on the horizon. http://bit.ly/fUsb90 #airplanes #travel    
    
    
    When the office pool wins the lottery, the company's screwed, because they all quit.    
    
    
    My webinar yesterday on cloud computing and security. http://unhub.com/RD69 (Just click “LAUNCH.”) #cloud    
    
    
    3-y.-old: “We can use Simon language, Papa.” Me: “What's that?” 3yo: “That's where you use Simons instead of your mouth.”    
    
    
        
    
    
    My interview from 3/2 on secure, compliant #socialnetworking. http://unhub.com/BEXk #security #compliance    
    
    
    The birds are chirping in the trees, and what they're saying is, “It's freaking cold AGAIN.”    
    
    
    PayPal founder to build world's biggest rocket. http://bit.ly/gE9NAu #rocketry #ap #newsrepublic    
    
    
    Being interviewed today on CIO Insight’s weekly show: Hidden Security Spending. http://unhub.com/jA1F #security #CIOInsight    
    
    
    Biggest surprise in my upcoming #Cloud Computing report: 58% using private clouds have no dedicated budget for them. #CIOInsight    
    
    
    It appears that New York City is putting up brand-new physical newsstands in the city. Um, why? #print #media    
    
    
    Novell Launches Mono for Android. http://bit.ly/etwxrP Me: Evolving development platform good for the mobile-cloud era. #appdev #mobile    
    
    
    Register for my webinar on #VDI in higher education next Tuesday: http://unhub.com/guy1 #education    
    
    
    New, expensive approach to manage global carbon levels: http://bit.ly/g8r3Ga    
    
    
    Another IT analyst taken in by flashy vendor. Gartner: Android to trail iPad for years http://techradar.com/942147 #ipad #android #mobility    
    
    
    The first thing for #RIM is to see that it isn't really their fault. http://bit.ly/fAJate #mobility    
    
    
    Critical step in dev of #VDI -- RT @eWEEKNews NxTop Makes Virtual Desktops Mobile http://bit.ly/eVCUcO  #virtualization    
    
    
    #Cloud developers, get to know your hardware again. Now, appliances. http://www.idevnews.com/stories/4619/IMPACT-2011-IBM-Expands-Cloud-WebSphere-Offerings-for-Business-Agility … #appdev #WebSphere    
    
    
    @nkolakowski Talk to @ESLundquist about your Flip—they’re dinosaurs at this point. #mobility    
    
    
    I finally know what #cloud computing is. Or what it isn't: it isn't technology. #CIOInsight    
    
    
    Ha ha, dinosaur watch! Flip portable camera killed. http://bit.ly/dTeDXR #mobility    
    
    
    Now I have a webinar on #VDI in #healthcare, Friday 4/15. Register at http://unhub.com/4QFr    
    
    
        
    
    
    #Hybrid #cloud computing is a non-variant of a non-technology.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Don't believe in deficit spending to boost the #economy? Take a look at the U.K. now, a year into #austerity. #deficit    
    
    
    Just played with a #PlayBook. You can’t play much. Doesn’t look like you’ll be able to work, either. #mobility #RIM #BlackBerry    
    
    
    See my 4/12 webinar on #VDI in #healthcare: http://unhub.com/lvSN (just click LAUNCH)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @srwellman I read this! The situation speaks a little more to the scientist than the science … but I wish more scientists were like him.    
    
    
    Beautiful weather at the moment.    
    
    
    See my 4/12 webinar on #VDI in #legal: http://unhub.com/CUya (just click LAUNCH)    
    
    
    I usually think #Apple sues too much. But given the #Myhrvold strategy, maybe they're right. http://bit.ly/fwJP1s #patents    
    
    
    Upcoming #CIOInsight #cloud computing story preview: Median cloud budgets 15% higher in 2011 compared to 2010.    
    
    
    #Intel earnings up on business demand for PCs. #Windows7 refresh cycle not getting enough credit. http://bit.ly/gDK6Sh    
    
    
    @donreisinger What you’re really saying is that there is such a thing as too much! #Apple, slow down. http://unhub.com/mnNr #iPhone    
    
    
    @carichard For RBI, is that retail-style online services for marketers, or marketing services for those doing their marketing online?    
    
    
        
    
    
    #Amazon #AWS keeps the #cloud availability fear live in the hearts of cloud adopters. http://unhub.com/3PaQ    
    
    
    Happy Easter to those celebrating!    
    
    
    In my #BI eSeminar next week, will talk about business intelligence going mass, and the new BI trade-offs. http://unhub.com/4f4q    
    
    
    Mobile #barcode scanning is promising in the near term because location-based services much more complex to get right. #LBS #mobility    
    
    
    @zdFYRashid @lawinski Come to the back, we’re all still working.    
    
    
    All right, the #BronxZoo #Easter egg hunt only lasted about 30 seconds. Rugby for three-year-olds.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @xpangler Todd, this was originally Sturgeon’s rule (Theodore Sturgeon, sci-fi writer). I didn't know Roddenberry stole that, too.    
    
    
    @xpangler The Internet makes everything better. It’s 99.9% crap.    
    
    
    See my interview from Wednesday on hidden #cloud spending, and the 11% median growth in cloud #ITbudgets this year: http://unhub.com/UEnG    
    
    
    (Link corrected!) My interview from Wednesday on hidden #cloud spending and 11% growth in cloud #ITbudgets: http://unhub.com/xEeK    
    
    
    The #1 problem we never have time to fix: Obsolete/Incomplete Prospects Data Widespread http://www.idevnews.com/stories/4641/Research-Finds-Obsolete-or-Dirty-Data-is-Widespread … #databases #marketing    
    
    
    @jhazard Quite the opposite, I think. Nice article. They will be managing something different.    
    
    
    My Biz Advisor interview on @MerchantCircle recent data on use of #socialnetworking by small businesses: http://unhub.com/s53i    
    
    
    Seagate creates 1-TB hard-drive platter, 3-TB hard drive. http://bit.ly/iDMf9N #storage    
    
    
    @carichard Love it. Are we tweesearchers, then?    
    
    
    It's the beginning of the end for Rotten Tomatoes. What's Wikipedia going to do?    
    
    
    #Opensource is a key component to #BA and #BI. In the end, these will “go mass” to unlock business value. http://www.idevnews.com/stories/4649/Gartner-BI-Summit-2011-Mobile-Open-Source-Keener-Insights-are-Keys …    
    
    
    My story on the Hidden Truth about #Cloud Spending: http://unhub.com/pXTE #ITbudgets    
    
    
        
    
    
    Register for my 5/11 webinar on #cloudcomputing 101: http://unhub.com/2nSO #cloud    
    
    
    SAP takes itself mobile with a high-profile #Amazon #cloud partnership. http://bit.ly/k0rgEW #mobility    
    
    
    Is #network stress today no longer just about #bandwidth? Is it about #integration, too?    
    
    
    China slaps export quota on #rareearth alloys http://bit.ly/lBFeUr Me: on top of Japan problems, this is a way big deal.    
    
    
    Is #Cisco going to sell #Linksys and #WebEx? http://bit.ly/je0Ews Me: WebEx yes, but don't sell Linksys.    
    
    
    I think AMI is missing the point: http://www.idevnews.com/stories/4667/Study-SMBs-Tend-to-Purchase-Clouds-in-Bundles … #Cloudcomputing is mix and match. Everyone can “auto-bundle.”    
    
    
        
    
    
    Separating #privatecloud services from “in house” is engaging in old-fashioned hardware-centric thinking. http://unhub.com/8BsT #cloud    
    
    
    Big #cloud story publishing in Baseline soon. Main point: #SLA and #integration issues need critical focus.    
    
    
    Presenting on #cloud basics at noon Eastern today: #security implications. http://www.eseminarslive.com/c/a/Cloud-Computing/IBM052511/    
    
    
    One of the nicest home-page animations I’ve seen: low-key and worth waiting for the finish. http://unhub.com/r2B- #Flash    
    
    
    @elliotmark1 You are really dredging the bottom of the news barrel, but I like it.    
    
    
    Hm, I just realized that the world ended a month ago.    
    
    
    At #GordonBiersch in Palo Alto with Lundquist they gave me paper survey. HUGE rating grid p. 2. Too much; putting all “average.” #surveyfail    
    
    
    #Citrix after Simon: Will it make a difference for #VWware? http://labs.eweek.com/archives/citrix-after-simon …    
    
    
    @VaTenor Thanks for the FF    
    
    
    @Workday Thanks for the FF    
    
    
    @mhweier Thanks for the FF    
    
    
    @TwistyRoadsCrvr Thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @Virtela Thanks for the tweet    
    
    
        
    
    
    Up next: Angelina Jolie takes a stake in an international spy organization.    
    
    
    After a week-end 50% longer, it's 100% harder to get up for work.    
    
    
    #ITspending returns to the roots, #ITinfrastructure: especially in the #midmarket. Our original research http://unhub.com/g2ax  @CIOInsight    
    
    
    @steve_sutton But this time, ________ really *is* different! (Fill in blank as wished.)    
    
    
    @lawinski Shoot, and I was going to ask if she had a heart of gold.    
    
    
    @huffingtonpost @DailyPygmy Facebook to Launch Facebook Competitor: http://huff.to/pq2Dwk  Me: the Internet leads to “natural monopolies.”    
    
    
    @carichard Traditional publishers have poorer ad products and no natural monopoly. Plus they're content-carriers unlike Google.    
    
    
    #Highavailability #mobility systems tomorrow at Motorola Solutions in Schaumburg, IL. #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    Motorola Solutions CEO Greg Brown speaking at #MSIExecSummit: Not all government spending is equal. Mission-critical prioritized.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Motorola Solutions definition of mission-critical: “moments that matter.” Me: good guide-post for defining yours. #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns CEO Brown: “We absolutely can continue to grow this business.” (Despite market and government conditions.) #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Moto Sol’s CEO Brown: Retail, enterprise business have grown stronger than we thought they would. Me: Consumer-driven trend. #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    Motorola Solutions CEO Greg Brown, July 13th, 2011. #MSIExecSummit http://twitpic.com/5pjjz1     
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns: a customer saw +700% productivity from inventory and pricing optimization (advanced data capture). #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns Product Chief Delaney: For #mobility we offer CIO needs (ruggedness, security) equally with what user wants (UX). #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns Product Chief Delaney: Ongoing comm. with customers has profound effect on profitability (#retail, transport.). #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns Product Chief Delaney: The core of any public safety comm. system is and always will be voice. #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    #Newscorp demonstrating the third rail in #media: Further victimization of victims.    
    
    
    Moto Sol’ns Services Chief Bruce Brda: “#Managedservices the best opportunity we have.” #MSIExecSummit #mobility    
    
    
    Moto Solutions’ hosted, managed public safety “core”: A cloud service for private #LTE. #missioncritical #mobility #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
    Motorola MC17 handheld scanner used by shoppers as they pick items, connecting them with the merchant. #MSIExecSummit #mobility #retail    
    
    
        
    
    
    Moto Sol'ns: 2010s were mobile computg era, 2011s will be “contextual” computg era. Me: I'd say #cloud computg era. #MSIExecSummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    More Delta Airlines #surveyfail. Survey instruction: “The questions below are specific to your flight of December 31, 1969.”    
    
    
    @GordonPlutsky Spitzer works in my wife’s building. Dude is making money, is what he’s doing.    
    
    
    @VelocityWong Meant to say to you yesterday, we got the ride after all, didn’t we?    
    
    
    Don’t scale factual questions. “I chew gum regularly” is either true or false, not some shade of agree or disagree. #surveybasics    
    
    
    Presenting in 20 minutes! on #security, #compliance implications of #cloud computing in #govtech. http://unhub.com/UgAI     
    
    
    