For the last two weeks in November, all NBA games will be played with a partially-thawed turkey.    
    
    
    Turns out that getting the first listing in the yellow pages hasn't helped Adidas much.    
    
    
    Do they drink New Amsterdam vodka in Constantinople?    
    
    
    Resting up for Caturday. http://instagram.com/p/gw6vA4rma-/     
    
    
    Where Children Sleep http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2011/08/08/where-children-sleep-james-mollison/ …    
    
    
    Sometimes humans get it right. Everything You Need To Know About Batkid http://www.buzzfeed.com/ryanhatesthis/everything-you-need-to-know-about-the-make-a-wish-foundation …    
    
    
    My plants have a drinking problem.    
    
    
    Dagummit, Miley! Stop sneaking into my house at night and licking all my silverware!    
    
    
    Even though I turned out to be a defective model, I'm glad my parents never tried to return me.    
    
    
    I swear I thought the cookie was a carrot, officer!    
    
    
    "Avicii" is Swedish for "I'm itchy."    
    
    
    #whatcompels #somepeople #todothis #allthetime #stopit    
    
    
    Who else thought it was Downtown Abbey?    
    
    
    It's never too early to procrastinate.    
    
    
    Spank those patties, Giada!    
    
    
    The most perplexing thing about high-traffic areas is how the hell they got the cars into my living room.    
    
    
    Wild, man. 2013 National Wildlife Photo Contest Winners - National Wildlife Federation http://www.nwf.org/News-and-Magazines/National-Wildlife/PhotoZone/Archives/2013/2013-NW-Photo-Contest-Winners.aspx … via @NWF    
    
    
    Also, now. pic.twitter.com/W5ozLUssRp    
    
    
    First boxelder bug sighting of the season and I have to find it walking across my foot. 

Also, first boxelder bug killing.    
    
    
    If people like Todd drive Scions, I don't want a Scion.    
    
    
    Settle down, cookies. pic.twitter.com/MaECj1s6i0    
    
    
    Sunlight detected. pic.twitter.com/OmemSQvXfp    
    
    
    According to the commercial I just saw, if you LOL, ROTFL or ROTFLMAO, you need to be put on their prescription drug.    
    
    
    Don't you hate is when you fall out of synch with the Earth's rotation & next thing you know you're dog-paddling in the middle of the ocean?    
    
    
    I have yet to shit bricks when I see it.    
    
    
    Why doesn't Weezer just buy a new inhaler?    
    
    
    There's a new translation of the Bible called "The Voice", and Adam Levine is confused as Hell.    
    
    
    KFC now has a $10 Weekend Bucket on Saturdays and Sundays. 

Chicken extra.    
    
    
    Tagging is graffiti with #s.    
    
    
    In other news, Michele Bachmann is leaving her husband for Rob Ford.    
    
    
    0:48 until full charge pic.twitter.com/0DVvVg0wcq    
    
    
    Devil's Cut on the rock pic.twitter.com/WDxYx4Aprz    
    
    
    The quality of a wine is inversely proportional to the amount of TV commercials you see for it.    
    
    
    Serious Cat would know what to do.    
    
    
    These Grape-Nuts are divine! I must have your recipe!    
    
    
    The snowboard was originally called a snurfer. 

Garganel unavailable for comment.    
    
    
    Cocooning a cat in a towel before trying to give her a pill has its own set of challenges.    
    
    
    Digital dashboard displays are a great way to make your car look dated after about, oh, let's say six months or so.    
    
    
    I tried dating Rosetta Stone, but all she does is talk talk talk.    
    
    
    Playtime with Ozzy the Weasel.: http://youtu.be/hy6oaDzy0-Q  via @youtube    
    
    
    The game of Tail Tag begins anew. https://vine.co/v/htDXjmwmFYF     
    
    
    The Daily Show with Jon Stewart — New York pizza vs. Chicago pizza. The magic begins around three minutes in. http://on.cc.com/173ZeXe     
    
    
    I knew it! Breaking Bad Season 5 - Alternate Ending: http://youtu.be/9kZivVxB3vU  via @youtube    
    
    
    I forgot to Caress before I dress.    
    
    
    I'm open! I'm open! pic.twitter.com/UqzeIuXAoN    
    
    
    The ducks all quack and beatniks snap. There's a Cricket on my lap! pic.twitter.com/InuAOPLOLe    
    
    
    On this day in 1847, it was November 17.    
    
    
    Have some knowledge: Eigengrau is the color people see in a completely dark room.    
    
    
    Ring it on. pic.twitter.com/ZMcYBVefpc    
    
    
    The pizza delivery is rather late this time.    
    
    
    I've been looking for The One, but might have to settle for Someone.    
    
    
    A cat just fell off the edge of the media cabinet. 

I guess they have Mondays too.    
    
    
    Second day pill for the cat; I think she's on to me.    
    
    
    @ABurgerADay Nope. That one's in all-caps.    
    
    
    When your facial hair successfully consumes a piece of granola, perhaps it's time to shave.    
    
    
    @Shih_Wei @VisitWilliston @halthomas And then it asked for more.    
    
    
    Sticky rice was invented by someone who refused to admit that they messed up the rice.    
    
    
    Never has a day so blatantly demanded a beer.    
    
    
    Idealuted: An idea that is watered down to the point where you can no longer tell what the idea was    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC But first, make these changes...    
    
    
    Remind me again why I pay $85 a month for the privilege of toting around something that can interrupt me day or night?    
    
    
    Be ye ready? https://vine.co/v/ht3Z5aIALXA     
    
    
    I knew the network took some creative liberties with Sleepy Hollow, but "Lickabod Crane"!?    
    
    
    I thought about smoking a turkey, but which end do you light?    
    
    
    Limoncello cha cha cha. pic.twitter.com/rsunkATWe0    
    
    
    Wait... A council can strip a villain of his or her powers? Why doesn't this happen in comic books?    
    
    
    Cognitive Dissonance: See FOX News.    
    
    
    Committee was once spelled "comity" until a comity went to work on it.    
    
    
    Every spice and every herb has magical curative and strengthening powers, but don't go nuts; just don't eat bland foods.    
    
    
    "I'd love her ass mint! Rahr! Ha ha!" 

— some executive doing badly during his sexual harassment counseling    
    
    
    Day three of trying to give a cat a pill; those who say cats only have a one-minute memory are full of shit.    
    
    
    Axe Body Wash — False hope in a bottle!™    
    
    
    Wa-ha-ha-hooey! http://gizmodo.com/the-world-s-tallest-waterslide-better-end-in-the-world-1467340805 …    
    
    
    @RobHoAdvertisin Then I'll eat it.    
    
    
    I will kneel before no man, 
because that would be disgusting.    
    
    
    Not many people know this, but the "K" in "Special K" is silent.    
    
    
    Holy crap! RealPlayer still exists!    
    
    
    I kinda wanna hear Shrek and Donkey sing Wrecking Ball.    
    
    
    Turn signals are what separate us from the assholes.    
    
    
    You just try being grumpy after watching this. Otters at Chester zoo http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sFqeWTfVi3I …    
    
    
    Heartwarming Reunion: Illinois Tornado Survivor Finds His Missing Dog Buried Alive Under Rubble  http://www.weather.com/news/man-finds-missing-dog-illinois-tornado-rubble-20131118?hootPostID=501ab34399bea71d47874490db91c627 … via @weatherchannel    
    
    
    The only difference I can tell between Spotify's Indie & Alternative radio stations is that Indie plays more Florence + The Machine.    
    
    
    Oh Whatchamacallit, I'm so glad they haven't gotten around to rebranding you like they did with the $100,000 Bar. pic.twitter.com/ZoNTavYJ1R    
    
    
    Walleye & Shrimp Rolls — walleye, shrimp, cucumber salsa & dill served in beer buns. pic.twitter.com/VF8afZWONF    
    
    
    The Avengers trailer: Derp edition: http://youtu.be/-OvMEKqQeFw  via @youtube    
    
    
    Just realized I say things like "goodness gracious" while talking to my cats. 

Also, I talk to my cats.    
    
    
    Before they became "chocolate diamonds", they were known as "shit diamonds".    
    
    
    I was once on a medication that forbade me from eating grapefruit. 

Never in my life had I craved grapefruit until then.    
    
    
    Those two infamous Boy Scout leaders were last seen in Redwood National Park, trying to chop down the trees before they fell on people.    
    
    
    Kitchen Product Porn! Gadgets and Gear That'll Make Your Kitchen Lust-Worthy | Wired Design | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/design/2013/11/designlife-gifts-for-dining-kitchen/ …    
    
    
    How Rock & Roll Legends Would Look If They Were Still Alive Today http://laughingsquid.com/how-rock-roll-legends-would-look-if-they-were-still-alive-today/ … via @LaughingSquid    
    
    
    Jenko's Epic Split — Channing Tatum channels JCVD. : http://youtu.be/EMlpiey20b8  via @youtube    
    
    
    Bismarck Parking Enforcement — They'll make you park.™ pic.twitter.com/nHKfD95AZJ    
    
    
    Houston, we have an accurate depiction. pic.twitter.com/o2mhTl6gs2    
    
    
    @adtothebone (replying to myself) If any of you know the source of this comic, please share! I wanna see more by this person. Thanks.    
    
    
    @MeggyVC Did you see the way the artist depicted our facial hair!? Disgraceful!    
    
    
    @MeggyVC The male astronaut on Apollo is freaking out and the female NASA employee in Houston appears non-harpy-like.    
    
    
    @MeggyVC Ah, but we're both assuming the stubborn astronaut is female. It could be a Zoolander-era Owen Wilson!    
    
    
    @MeggyVC Owen Wilson would've gotten a double post!    
    
    
    @MeggyVC In my world, stubborn, passive-aggressive types are well represented by people in both classically-defined genders.    
    
    
    @MeggyVC Now if we brought nonbinary identities into the conversation...    
    
    
    Cottage cheese and apple slices are good together, BUT THEY'RE NOT PIZZA!    
    
    
    Knuckles on unbent fingers look like they're rather concerned about something.    
    
    
    People on Survivor dress just like the people in Revolution, only the Revolution people's clothes don't have "Revolution" written all over.    
    
    
    Do not click this link unless you've already seen Gravity! Short About the Stranger Sandra Bullock Called From Space http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/11/gravity-short-film-aningaaq/ …    
    
    
    Jarlsberg pic.twitter.com/e37mRsHaPv    
    
    
    @Katone_Curl "Jarlsberg!"    
    
    
    Some people have a monkey on their back. I have a Cricket. pic.twitter.com/bVFGE9nFHQ    
    
    
    @RobHoAdvertisin Yikes!    
    
    
    If you repeat a lie often enough, it becomes FOX News.    
    
    
    As hard as it is to imagine, it's almost as if my cat doesn't want to take her pill.    
    
    
    Insightful. Sad Cat Diary: http://youtu.be/PKffm2uI4dk  via @youtube    
    
    
    Also insightful. Sad Dog Diary: http://youtu.be/Xw1C5T-fH2Y  via @youtube    
    
    
    With a name like Taco John's, it must be authentic!    
    
    
    Hipsters Posing For Video When They Think They Are Posing for Photos - EDM Culture http://www.magneticmag.com/2013/11/hipsters-actually-posing-for-video-when-they-think-they-are-posing-for-photo-edm-culture/ … via @ZippyBippy    
    
    
    Ow! My back! #throwbackthursday    
    
    
    Axl Rose's three most frequently used singing voices were named Wilford, Bumble and Veronica.    
    
    
    Other Famous People With Owen Wilson's Nose  http://www.mandatory.com/2013/11/21/other-famous-people-with-owen-wilsons-nose/ …    
    
    
    PEZ candies aren't very good. 

(reloads PEZ dispenser)    
    
    
    No Irish coffee is complete without a squeeze or two of a fresh leprechaun. pic.twitter.com/uwWqKd5WiU    
    
    
    The Spicy Sicilian, a little bit better than the Bland Barcelonan. pic.twitter.com/2bexhermmr    
    
    
    The full name for Sheamus Fries is Sheamus Didn't Have Enough Ingredients To Make Poutine Fries. pic.twitter.com/1NC6d6fKeK    
    
    
    They're so fluffy! http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy-3_OSx     
    
    
    78%! A WKRP Thanksgiving Quiz | Online Quiz | Mental Floss http://mentalfloss.com/node/14069/take     
    
    
    ♫ It's my Crick in a box! pic.twitter.com/N01kplngDF    
    
    
    A Tea Party edition of the Bible would be missing the Jesus sections.    
    
    
    @NotMattBellamy They make flatware and stuff.    
    
    
    Has any breakfast cereal besides Special K tried to convince us to eat it for nonbreakfasty meals?    
    
    
    ♬ I come from the land of the ice and snow, where the... wait. I'm still here. Dammit.    
    
    
    Breakfast cereal with freeze-dried fruit in it, because fresh fruit is too complicated.    
    
    
    A martial arts guy with a sliver.    
    
    
    @ahtitan I suppose the Chex / Chex Mix thing is in the snack realm as well, eh?    
    
    
    Just when you thought you finally got the Raisin Nut Bran song out of your head after 20 years... http://youtu.be/g7_HrJm8qiM  via @youtube    
    
    
    Run away! This Painting Of The Danish Royal Family Will Steal Your Soul By @drcrypt http://www.fastcodesign.com/3022006/design-crime/this-painting-of-the-danish-royal-family-will-steal-your-soul … via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    @ReenieWeenie Fetch the holy water!    
    
    
    @andylassner There is a syrup available...    
    
    
    A little mermaid named Ariel is kind of like having a zebra named Spot.    
    
    
    "An' now for vun of my favorite pagan tunes. An' a vun an' a two..." 

— Florence Welk    
    
    
    What's wrong with just eating Chinese takeout straight out of the box? 

This turn-it-into-a-plate-OMG thing... meh.    
    
    
    Follow these damned fine people. http://favstar.fm/users/adtothebone/given_to … #FF    
    
    
    Must read: The Guitarist's story. http://adtothebone.tumblr.com/post/67766884649/must-read-the-guitarists-story …    
    
    
    Shouldn't McDonald's new Dollar Menu and More include the rest of the menu too?    
    
    
    Burger King's BBQ Rib Sandwich. McDonald's McRib is no longer worried. pic.twitter.com/L1aZiPE7TS    
    
    
    Ron Burgundy Comes Clean On His Dodge Durango Ads: (Conan) http://youtu.be/MSqF4GG3JTU  via @youtube    
    
    
    Be just like Katniss and kill people from other districts... at Subway!    
    
    
    Human beings are physiologically unable to pronounce "Açaí". 

Seriously. Don't even try.    
    
    
    Spray margarine seems like a great idea. 

That is, until it's about half empty and you have to spray it horizontally.    
    
    
    This was the lousiest Black Friday I can remember.    
    
    
    @GrumpusNation "Raven", you mean.    
    
    
    @AaronLMGoodwin Hey hey hey now!    
    
    
    I thought Bellator would have more tutus.    
    
    
    I compete in Mixed Graphic Arts.    
    
    
    Tostitos Cantina Chips must make people really, really dumb.    
    
    
    Sweet dreams! Absurd Creature of the Week: This Parasite Eats a Fish's Tongue — And Takes Its Place - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/11/absurd-creature-of-the-week-the-parasite-that-eats-and-replaces-a-fishs-tongue/ …    
    
    
    Nicely done, Ellen crew. Mad Men Without Smoking: http://youtu.be/VXKnDwbuQWo  via @youtube    
    
    
    Yamazaki Haiku. 

Got a deal on this single setting. The other 3-7 will have to wait awhile. pic.twitter.com/tU6yLALfce    
    
    
    Cricket Hove — I guess this means she's family, eh? pic.twitter.com/ojTkRqdKp5    
    
    
    Poor Peeta. The Onion Reviews 'The Hunger Games: Catching Fire': http://youtu.be/kyx1U9QjWVQ  via @youtube    
    
    
    Workin' on a fresh batch of hairballs. pic.twitter.com/1f0dTvYWc1    
    
    
    How long does it take to sous-vide a 13-pound turkey? #thanksgivinglive    
    
    
    What's your favorite gravy-based cocktail? #thanksgivinglive    
    
    
    Foiling the bird — shiny or dull side out? #thanksgivinglive    
    
    
    Waiting for Anthony Bourdain to crash the live show. #thanksgivinglive    
    
    
    Dramatic Cricket pic.twitter.com/0dnn1l8xvR    
    
    
    This trail mix doesn't dissolve in water very well.    
    
    
    Vikings were into body maraudification.    
    
    
    Good advice, more or less. pic.twitter.com/YO9uVb4TGz    
    
    
    Naps are very important. #caturday pic.twitter.com/ao510JJdow    
    
    
    Trying to find the funny bone on these elbow macaroni.    
    
    
    @_SetTheHook_ @SharonVonGinger And insulin.    
    
    
    Everybody can bullshit, but not everybody can refrain from bullshit.    
    
    
    You'd think nomorerack-dot-com would be a plastic surgeon specializing in breast reductions.    
    
    
    Thank you for letting me know your commercial used real people; I was under the assumption they were fancy robots.    
    
    
    Sigh. It's been forever since the last time Erin Esurance gave me a booty call.    
    
    
    You know your song's on the way out when it's still in the VH1 Top 20 Countdown but they only play 15 seconds of it.    
    
    
    Merica is Murica with a GED.    
    
    
    When folding t-shirts, the "t" stands for "tedious".    
    
    
    @chadschomber Ermahgerd!    
    
    
    Many people have crabs, but the really nasty ones have lobsters.    
    
    
    Sure are a lot of old guys wearing yellow-framed glasses these days.

Code for being into lemon parties?    
    
    
    In advertising, Michael Bolton is this year's Kenny G. 

Congratulations?    
    
    
    Mehpic — (adjective) Not epic. 

See also: Shmepic.    
    
    
    After seeing Josh Hutcherson with a mullet on Saturday Night Live, they totally have to cast him in the MacGruber sequel.    
    
    
    No matter how interested my cats seem when I do the laundry, they refuse to learn how to do it for me.    
    
    
    Dear MTV/Ridiculousness: Thanks for showing us all those badly-compressed web videos on your hi-def cable channel!    
    
    
    uSell doesn't want to make an offer on my carphone.    
    
    
    This Esquire Network looks an awful lot like G4.    
    
    
    If you laugh or cry out loud, you have a terrible brain disease. Apparently.    
    
    
    I pretty sure that God prefers it when you pray for nice things to happen to others.    
    
    
    Bedhead is still not the new tousled.    
    
    
    I once ran a half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half half marathon.    
    
    
    The weirdest thing about Temper-Pedic mattresses is you have to get angry to get comfortable.    
    
    
    The majestic poo fountain of Golden Corral. https://vine.co/v/hUqmn1rallL     
    
    
    Josh Hutcherson - Josie Sketch (Your Love - Outfield) - SNL 11-23-13 by @idolxfactor1 - http://www.dailymotion.com/video/x17k6wr_josh-hutcherson-josie-sketch-your-love-outfield-snl-11-23-13_people … via @DailymotionUSA    
    
    
    My one week of college acting class finally paid off; to the cops, I was just a tree with an iPhone. pic.twitter.com/HjecZYcUQJ    
    
    
    Grey Goose is when a creepy old man pinches your ass.    
    
    
    Well... It was healthy until I located the runny cheez dispenser. pic.twitter.com/bWnC815Its    
    
    
    Annalee figurines creep me the hell out. pic.twitter.com/XEqg6s26xO    
    
    
    Replacement sink sprayer head from Lowe's works with all hoses MY ASS! 

Wire snap rings are also quite sucky.    
    
    
    @GrumpusNation You have! Also, cactus humpers.    
    
    
    Unique sounds are made by a sniffly-nosed kitty grooming herself. https://vine.co/v/hUMe3UmKVqM     
    
    
    Cloth drawstring onion and garlic keepers. Less light, mo' betta! pic.twitter.com/Q04HeODMOX    
    
    
    Frigidaire 6-month refrigerator water/ice filters cost $30! 

Good thing I got the last one to last three and a half years.    
    
    
    Well, this wrecked me. Beautiful but heart-breaking pictures of terminally ill pets http://dailym.ai/1deUMK3  via @DailyMailUS    
    
    
    Sleepurrs. https://vine.co/v/hUOiw2HBKMl     
    
    
    "Until one has loved an animal, a part of one's soul remains unawakened." 

— Anatole France    
    
    
    The moment when you realize the model/actress your teenage self loooooooved is now a granny.    
    
    
    The final dream I have before waking up on Monday morning is usually of bagpipes playing "Amazing Grace".    
    
    
    .@inthefade I bet it was Durkee, as a way to unload all their French-fried onions.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I thought Doctor Who was an owl.    
    
    
    The Best Buy employees in the major appliances department must be awesome breakdancers.    
    
    
    The Beastie Boys Did Not Sue GoldieBlox http://badassdigest.com/2013/11/25/the-beastie-boys-did-not-sue-goldieblox/ … via @GregoryNg    
    
    
    Beastie Boys open letter to Goldieblox: YOU sued US (Why?) | adland.tv http://po.st/XApHyt  via @adland    
    
    
    Has PEZ made a PEZ dispenser that screams when you snap its head back yet?    
    
    
    Likely outcomes of owning a real lightsaber. http://slowrobot.com/i/5940     
    
    
    After running from a horde of armored flamingos wielding Velveeta bricks, perhaps it's time for the doctor to try a new prescription on me.    
    
    
    Yo no hablo japonés.    
    
    
    Kitty antlers or kitty trapper hats? pic.twitter.com/0mdr0Y7oLS    
    
    
    @buscarla Nein.    
    
    
    How many people do you estimate will die at various Walmarts on Black Friday?    
    
    
    Cricket conducts her dream symphony. pic.twitter.com/3eRO9bbyp6    
    
    
    Epicuro Primitivo vendemmia 2010 — This is way tastier than it should be for the price. Thanks, Trader Joe's! pic.twitter.com/siQB1O0csG    
    
    
    Monday nights are for trading the day's whines for wine.    
    
    
    Hank Hill on Christian Rock. http://youtu.be/8TsL0DO-c1E  via @youtube    
    
    
    World's heaviest turkey: 86 pounds http://www.examiner.com/article/world-s-heaviest-turkey-86-pounds … via @examinercom    
    
    
    Nobody knows how to say "Smaug".    
    
    
    ♬ I came in like a wrecking baaaaall! pic.twitter.com/92JnsocQTv    
    
    
    @ryanholota Epicreepy.    
    
    
    Not too sure about these Kellogg's Frosted Pork Rinds.    
    
    
    Continuity is boring.    
    
    
    If it was never in style, it can never go out of style.    
    
    
    Damn. 8 Foods You've Been Eating All Wrong http://shar.es/DoxFK  (mental floss)    
    
    
    whoops. happy thanksgiving http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy-W0hnn     
    
    
    Burg & Curd pic.twitter.com/3wH0f8imKW    
    
    
    Thanksgiving as a kid vs Thanksgiving as an adult http://theoatmeal.com/comics/thanksgiving …    
    
    
    50 States of LEGO: North Dakota http://www.jeff-friesen.com/Legostates34.html …    
    
    
    Why you should never look behind your TV set. http://www.nhm.ac.uk/about-us/news/2005/august/news_6293.html …    
    
    
    Tiny Animals On Fingers http://www.flickr.com/photos/specklet/sets/72157594204828139/with/212039021/ …    
    
    
    New Wave artists aging gracefully.  An 80's world gone by... http://wp.me/p1q6wQ-W9     
    
    
    Ocean Spray, because Bog Spray probably wouldn't sell very well.    
    
    
    @FavstarOfTheDay @Funny2 Thanks!    
    
    
    I shall call you Icarus, for you grew too close to the sun. pic.twitter.com/pc53q8DAp1    
    
    
    Vacuum cleaners... Not a fan. pic.twitter.com/lTJbj6odoI    
    
    
    America's Super Zips http://www.washingtonpost.com/sf/local/2013/11/09/washington-a-world-apart/ …    
    
    
    It's hard waking up to the smell of cold cereal.    
    
    
    Don't forget to leave out grubs and grains for Turkey Claus tonight!    
    
    
    If we had to clean ourselves like cats do, chiropractors would be the wealthiest people on the planet.    
    
    
    Shit! All this time I've been taking theta-carotene    
    
    
    Somebody just emailed me The Password Management Solution I’ve Been Waiting For! 

Crack open the champagne and alert the dancing girls!    
    
    
    GoldieBlox learns a lesson in engineering bad PR | adland.tv http://po.st/iFsYDk  via @adland    
    
    
    North Dakotans know what this is. pic.twitter.com/e4BPAQc6kx    
    
    
    The Club House sammich at Little Cottage Café. pic.twitter.com/bgK2enxpVd    
    
    
    Last night, NBC ran a 2-hour Saturday Night Live Thanksgiving special and didn't show the Tonto, Tarzan and Frankenstein classic. What the!?    
    
    
    Starting Thanksgiving morning off with a big ol' bowl of Kellogg's Frosted Giblets.    
    
    
    Really wish NBC had aired SNL's best Thanksgiving clip during last night's 2-hour SNL Thanksgiving special. pic.twitter.com/PJcbM9Hk2f    
    
    
    I am thankful for coffee. 

#happythanksgiving    
    
    
    This is the last time I try to make turkey in the straw.    
    
    
    Never hide the engagement ring in her plate of Thanksgiving food.    
    
    
    STUPID TURKEY WON'T FIT IN THE TOASTER OVEN    
    
    
    An item in my Amazon shopping basket has changed its price 3,416 times in the last 48 hours. 

Retail roulette?    
    
    
    Huh. You'd think they would've retired the Sex and the City balloons by now. 

#macysparade    
    
    
    The poor Trojan Man balloon is having trouble remaining fully aroused.

#macysparade    
    
    
    The Hindenburg reenactment was a bad idea. 

#macysparade    
    
    
    That damned Katniss keeps shooting down the balloons. 

#macysparade    
    
    
    Cats recognise their owners' voices but never evolved to care, says study http://www.independent.co.uk/news/science/cats-recognise-their-owners-voices-but-never-evolved-to-care-says-study-8966580.html …    
    
    
    If you didn't put it in the bird, it's unstuffing.    
    
    
    Still no Deathmobile. 

#macysparade    
    
    
    Pre-post-Thanksgiving-dinner-nap nap. http://instagram.com/p/hRBNH-Lmc7/     
    
    
    What peeling potatoes looks like in Nikeville. http://instagram.com/p/hRKzFZrmfq/     
    
    
    To make strange, new tech less intimidating, Mom put a doily on her flat screen. http://instagram.com/p/hRL00HrmRr/     
    
    
    Here come the meat sweats!    
    
    
    Ain't nuthin' wrong with old school. Thanks, Ma. http://instagram.com/p/hRneX4rmQz/     
    
    
    "You'll poke an eye out!" 

My tater tool. http://instagram.com/p/hRuWQmrmfm/     
    
    
    I'm at Grand Theatres for The Hunger Games: Catching Fire (Bismarck, ND) http://4sq.com/1aaB0b4     
    
    
    There's something weird about going to see Hunger Games on Thanksgiving.    
    
    
    I'm so doomed. http://instagram.com/p/hSPEOFLmb2/     
    
    
    Shop 'til you drop... and are trampled by a bunch of people. (mental floss) A Brief History of Black Friday http://shar.es/DuVM8     
    
    
    "Do not fire into the crowd." OSHA's Black Friday Crowd Management Safety Guidelines for Retailers https://www.osha.gov/OshDoc/data_General_Facts/Crowd_Control.html …    
    
    
    Finally got that Cabbage Patch Doll! (New Yorker) Everything You Know About Black Friday Is Wrong http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/currency/2013/11/everything-you-know-about-black-friday-is-wrong.html?utm_source=www&utm_medium=tw&utm_campaign=20131128 … via @NewYorker    
    
    
    @JustJordie I won somehow!    
    
    
    @GrumpusNation Nice to know.    
    
    
    @NotMattBellamy I learned a new word!    
    
    
    How to Spatchcock a Turkey | Serious Eats : Recipes: http://www.seriouseats.com/recipes/2009/11/how-to-spatchcock-a-turkey-thanksgiving-butterflying-roasting-recipe.html#.Upir7KllMH8.twitter … This sounds horrifying but I might have to try it next year.    
    
    
    Topping the Billboard Canadian Hot 100 for the 29th week in a row is Avril Lavigne's "Poutine on the Ritz".    
    
    
    Today is Garbage Truck Thanksgiving. https://vine.co/v/hPO7g12wEe7     
    
    
    I'm pretty sure many people get married so they don't have to do all the chores.    
    
    
    It's a shame that Garmen still hasn't named one of their devices "Electra".    
    
    
    Cat hair is pretty much the only thing holding my old laptop together.    
    
    
    Well, if they didn't want me bringing one of these, they shouldn't call it Black Friday. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Baton_(law_enforcement)#Blackjack …    
    
    
    My nephew can't wait for the 3rd Hunger Games movie. 

I told him he could read the books. 

He doesn't want to ruin the movie.    
    
    
    My house sure looked cleaner without all this dang sunlight coming in.    
    
    
    Cyber Monday... Black Friday... Grey Thursday... 

Up next, Whatever Wednesday.    
    
    
    I saved over $3,400 this Black Friday by staying home and not shopping.    
    
    
    Why does the Big Ten Conference logo spell out "B16"? http://www.bigten.org/     
    
    
    Sleeping Booty: What happens when you sit too long.    
    
    
    How Cats Blog : diesel sweeties http://www.dieselsweeties.com/archive/3446#.UpleEK3P3hk.twitter …    
    
    
    I still don't know what the hell happened to me in high school.    
    
    
    I think that Cougarlife commercial just gave me herpes.    
    
    
    Next time you shop for a mattress, don't forget to ask for its Fart Rating. 

If it's less than 65, keep looking.    
    
    
    Can I buy a Honda without the Bolton feature?    
    
    
    Perhaps. ♫ You May Be Right – Billy Joel http://spoti.fi/L7p6Xw  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    .@apierno ♬ When a man loves a latte... ♬    
    
    
    Not quite sure how I feel about Tyler Perry turning all the Ernest movies into Madea movies.    
    
    
    @apierno There are original Bolton songs!?    
    
    
    Saturday spins. ♫ Cults – Cults http://spoti.fi/JsXTzN  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    ♫ Just call me Vixen of the morning... pic.twitter.com/o18kbIAyHG    
    
    
    GROVER NO! pic.twitter.com/6Y21HttCEA    
    
    
    Cats have eyes from another world. pic.twitter.com/fWJPPcCOb8    
    
    
    "If you commit suicide after taking this medication, tell your doctor."    
    
    
    Look at These Amazing Old Pics of the Macy's Thanksgiving Parade | Wired Design | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/design/2013/11/the-macys-thanksgiving-parade-was-way-cooler-in-black-and-white/ …    
    
    
    Never hate somebody until they've earned it.    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure that Richard Branson is a fictional character, like the Mandarin in Iron Man 3.    
    
    
    Just as you're about to have your best game ever, you'll receive a text.    
    
    
    Riiiiicolaaaaa! pic.twitter.com/KXmcSOG1P3    
    
    
    Getting ready to celebrate Caturday with another nap. pic.twitter.com/rcrnF5035J    
    
    
    Unwrapped's Marc Summers... has a vocal... delivery that... gives Shatner... a run for his... money!    
    
    
    "Goddamn Michael Bolton." 

— Kenny G    
    
    
    @Shih_Wei Rahr-pffft even.    
    
    
    So this is happening in Bismarck right now... #anchorman #RonBurgundy pic.twitter.com/EBrmk7ECXx    
    
    
    @Ibatvmc I... approve!    
    
    
    The sonic boom you just heard was from a shard of hazelnut shell that flew across the room and imbedded itself into the wall.    
    
    
    If you have "Nissan" in the title of your TV show, you can't really claim "limited commercial interruption".    
    
    
    If your life's story can be told by a bracelet, you need to live some more.    
    
    
    Last night while snacking on pickled garlic and Gedney Baby Zingers, I wondered why I was still single. pic.twitter.com/LQeuvBPqfv    
    
    
    I'm at @TJMaxx (Bismarck, ND) http://4sq.com/1eEfj7G     
    
    
    They call it extra virgin olive oil because it's ugly and has a bad personality.    
    
    
    Nice parking, petrol patriot. pic.twitter.com/reWkj7grOb    
    
    
    A new study has determined that 103.6% of social media statistics are fabricated.    
    
    
    @adland Yep.    
    
    
    @adland I wonder what out-of-the-way communities we beat out?    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure a vanderpump is the thing ketchup comes out of at McDonald's.    
    
    
    @adland By comparison, those are major markets!    
    
    
    That Starkist and 9Lives are the same company makes me wonder if they ever confused things with each other.    
    
    
    Guac this way. pic.twitter.com/y3zzmCT6vX    
    
    
    Tastes like chicken. pic.twitter.com/NYZ7IHSJM9    
    
    
    Now you too can smell like Kenny Loggins. pic.twitter.com/WTbQP8M8br    
    
    
    "Weepy rashes" is code for "oozing pus". pic.twitter.com/szOYZ45xXm    
    
    
    Pairs nicely. pic.twitter.com/1iKBPUIdBM    
    
    
    Then why did the doctor call this an analgesic!?    
    
    
    "Don't you know the Dewey Decimal System?" Shhh! Take a peek at the world's most exquisite libraries http://www.cnn.com/2013/11/27/world/gallery/most-beautiful-libraries-in-the-world/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Visit the wild kingdom of scumbag animals. http://scumbaganimals.com/     
    
    
    If you compromise yourself too many times, it becomes your specialty.    
    
    
    Monday morning. The old rat race. 
A kitty sneezes in your face.    
    
    
    A reason is something you decide on before doing.

An excuse is something you decide on after doing.    
    
    
    After the freezing rain and sloped driveway into the sloped cul-de-sac, I’m ready to join the Jamaican bobsled team.    
    
    
    For some inexplicable reason, I can only grow facial hair from the left to the right. pic.twitter.com/1bFRN8eL1J    
    
    
    They close in ten minutes. Eek! http://instagram.com/p/hb6nw6rmdi/     
    
    
    I was #647 and it was one minute before the DOT closed. 

NOT STRESSFUL AT ALL. http://instagram.com/p/hcAckDrmWb/     
    
    
    @BismarckMotorCo I did see several Kenny G CR-Vs in your lot this weekend.    
    
    
    This should be good for a nice buzz. pic.twitter.com/JUSE3RFWs1    
    
    
    Monty Python, The Fish Slapping Dance: http://youtu.be/IhJQp-q1Y1s  Ahh, memories.    
    
    
    Nobody finishes a webinar without feeling a bit ashamed that they're the type of person that finishes a webinar.    
    
    
    Think inside the box — This Soundproof Cardboard Shed Lets You Scream in Peace |  http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2013/12/japanese-cardboard-shed/ …    
    
    
    Watch out! She's got a folder! — Feminism According To Stock Photography http://nymag.com/thecut/2013/11/feminism-according-to-stock-photography/slideshow/2013/11/22/feminism_accordingtostockphotography/boxing-1/ …    
    
    
    Tried the Bacon Cheddar McChicken: bacon+chicken = good! Still long for the original-size McChi... #DollarMenu #Klout http://klout.com/brand/mcdonalds/mcdonalds-dollar-menu?n=tw&v=perks_feedback_submit&i=266264 …    
    
    
    Spies Like Us - The G-Force Training: http://youtu.be/0dlG5B6eQHg  Every cul-de-sac should have a human centrifuge.    
    
    
    Real training in a human centrifuge. Whee! http://youtu.be/Sbxguzogm1Q  via @youtube    
    
    
    Learned two new terms today... A-LOC = Almost Loss Of Consciousness / G-LOC = Gravity-induced Loss Of Consciousness 

The more you know.    
    
    
    Up for auction! Harrison Ford "Han Solo" DL-44 Blaster from Star W - by Profiles in History http://www.invaluable.com/auction-lot/harrison-ford-han-solo-dl-44-blaster-from-star-379-c-44e307f3bc#.Up50bxqMG0s.twitter …    
    
    
    The other cat's toy is always more fun.    
    
    
    Sleepytime for Vixen the Limbless Cat pic.twitter.com/TnuNp9zYsq    
    
    
    Kiwa native Andean potato chips pic.twitter.com/ErRkRYR3IO    
    
    
    Foo flashback! Foo Fighters - Big Me: http://youtu.be/pLdJQFTnZfA  via @youtube    
    
    
    "Please enter your card's expiry date."

— a good sign the bill payment service isn't located in the United States    
    
    
    Speak softly and carry a big snow shovel.    
    
    
    "Look! An eagle!" Eagle steals camera near crocodile meat trap http://www.abc.net.au/news/2013-12-02/eagle-steals-camera-near-crocodile-trap/5129114 … @abcnews    
    
    
    It's hard to type "nincompoop" without smiling.    
    
    
    @GuyKawasaki So precious.    
    
    
    "Guns?" 

— some North Dakotan calling in to local morning radio show to answer "4th most common thing kept in a glove compartment"    
    
    
    Overachiever. pic.twitter.com/YQsZ6S4jbe    
    
    
    Trying to figure out why I once thought that shelf-stable, microwaveable spinach 'n' potatoes would be a tasty purchase.    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC Drunky Clay would avoid this stuff like the plague.    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC You may be onto something.    
    
    
    @markalves Things can happen between the beginning and end of a chase.    
    
    
    While I was eating some Korma rice, Culture Club started playing on Spotify.    
    
    
    Snake Island — Guaranteed to not be a tourist trap. http://www.atlasobscura.com/places/snake-island-ilha-de-queimada-grande … via @texturl    
    
    
    Captain Picard sings "Let it Snow!": http://youtu.be/oiSn2JuDQSc  via @youtube (NOTE: Skip the back half.)    
    
    
    Old Finnish People With Things On Their Heads http://www.laravisual.com/old-finnish-people-with-things-on-their-heads/ …    
    
    
    Archery in Film - The Definitive Supercut : http://youtu.be/J1kVgCkBYts  via @youtube    
    
    
    Synchronized Slackers pic.twitter.com/t9SawRx3TW    
    
    
    Sometimes life makes about as much sense as a perfume commercial.    
    
    
    If you thought I could resist buying something called Pickled Pattypan Squash, then you don't know me very well. pic.twitter.com/EMN7ijAq55    
    
    
    I wonder if Clint and his chair still talk.    
    
    
    These UK cookbooks make me think I'd rather like Leon restaurants. pic.twitter.com/wNnrIsWDML    
    
    
    Smaug is a portmanteau of smoke and faug.    
    
    
    An Obituary for the Letter E | Underwire | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/12/obituary-letter-e/ …    
    
    
    Bugs and Spiders Disguised as Poop, Leaves, and Each Other http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/insect-and-spider-mimicry/?viewall=true …    
    
    
    Never be in a restroom the same time as a performance pooper. 

Or after.    
    
    
    If, while shoveling snow, you imagine yourself stoking the fire of a steam locomotive, it doesn't help at all.    
    
    
    As if Elf on a Shelf wasn't disconcerting enough, now you can bring Christmas into your bathroom with Gnome on the Throne!    
    
    
    L7 was the official rock band of the American Chiropractic Association.    
    
    
    I'm a Foo Lover, not a Foo Fighter, baby.    
    
    
    A megaphone is a bullhorn with a truth setting.    
    
    
    What did the North Dakotan say when she dropped her scrubby-sponge?

Loofah uff da. 

This is why there aren't many North Dakotan comedians.    
    
    
    Artificial grape flavor is derived from artificial grape vines.    
    
    
    "Cats, man. Huh." 

— some guy lugging two big tubs of Tidy Cat as he walked by me in PetSmart    
    
    
    Wiped out while carrying a just-purchased 40-pound bag of ice melt to my car. 

Ladies.    
    
    
    Lost in Translation pic.twitter.com/KD9rCSFgmI    
    
    
    Turkey & Spinach Dip Burger pic.twitter.com/AVgOuIrxt4    
    
    
    Fire Cider made with Fireball Whiskey pic.twitter.com/49XF3oiVJR    
    
    
    Your Friday morning wake-up cover song. Stairway to Heaven - The Rock Lobsters: http://youtu.be/YAqwPcGuSpk  via @youtube    
    
    
    Arrogance rarely has the intelligence or skills to justify itself.    
    
    
    The QWERTY keyboard layout was designed specifically to maximize the possibility of funny typos.    
    
    
    I'm not quite sure how to "mill about". 

Like a miller moth bonking around on a light bulb?    
    
    
    Camera fun! NASA Engineers Built an Insanely Complex Bullet-Time Rig For Fun http://gizmodo.com/nasa-engineers-built-an-insanely-complex-bullet-time-ri-1476979464 …    
    
    
    Harry & David peppermint bark nom nom nom. pic.twitter.com/qE5Ygsp0ye    
    
    
    WHY DO I ALWAYS PICK A COCONUT ONE!?    
    
    
    So how many brands have tried to trend-hop on Nelson Mandela's death so far?    
    
    
    There Are 5 Types of Boredom (mental floss) http://shar.es/DQ3yx  Strangely, the list is missing "shmoredom".    
    
    
    Checked in at @quiznos and saved two bucks off a large spicy sausage. Suck it, Foursquare haters. #sublife    
    
    
    Pretty ruff. 100 Years of Breed "Improvement" http://wp.me/p1VSYl-eg     
    
    
    Forte /for tay/ v. Forte /fort/ 
http://www.dailywritingtips.com/forte-or-forte-cache-or-cachet/ … 
The more you know.    
    
    
    Chestnuts in North Dakota —Woot! pic.twitter.com/hurnQwJYDW    
    
    
    Strange how Santa manages to be in car commercials for so many different brands and nobody thinks it's a conflict of interest.    
    
    
    The biggest problem I have with Hunger Games is everybody has really stupid first names.    
    
    
    Disappointed to find out that Passenger (Michael David Rosenberg) wasn't a wee little gnome.    
    
    
    I tried to warn him. http://scranton.craigslist.org/jwl/4210925687.html …    
    
    
    I love that Laika still does things old school. The Boxtrolls | Official Teaser Trailer #2 [HD]: http://youtu.be/1y8E7xJ6MXU  via @youtube    
    
    
    Preflight inspection. pic.twitter.com/RTI9qFNlRW    
    
    
    "... and in the morning, I'm making waffles!" pic.twitter.com/9gzrqCrfZn    
    
    
    Never miss an opportunity to design something cooler than it has to be. (Hungry Jack syrup cap) pic.twitter.com/6CwCeFMzHC    
    
    
    Never buy a product that attempts to compare itself to an Apple product.    
    
    
    Tired from all the napping. pic.twitter.com/wJpbcsWaiH    
    
    
    Looks like Disney got its magic back! Disney's Frozen "Let It Go" Sequence Performed by Idina Menzel: http://youtu.be/moSFlvxnbgk  via @youtube    
    
    
    Cricket waits for you to start running. pic.twitter.com/na5ztWlfQU    
    
    
    Dammit. Just remembered I'm the housekeeper.    
    
    
    Dammit, England! Can't we agree on anything!? pic.twitter.com/UZe88X0VxY    
    
    
    I just removed a T.J. Maxx price sticker in one piece and without leaving any residue. 

Ladies.    
    
    
    Tonight's libation: La Granja 360 Tempranillo / Garnacha 2011 pic.twitter.com/S8UWz49knL    
    
    
    "I cook with wine. Sometimes I even add it to the food." 

— W.C. Fields    
    
    
    "Show your school pride!" can be translated as "Buy this expensive shirt!"    
    
    
    Geico commercials never show the floor of Baxter's car because it's covered in pig shit.    
    
    
    Being a cynic allows you to be pleasantly surprised from time to time.    
    
    
    It's sad that Power Rangers are now neither mighty nor morphin'.    
    
    
    In the late 1800s, they were known as Mighty Morphine Power Rangers.    
    
    
    On December 7th, 1986, Paul Masson sold some wine before its time.    
    
    
    I thought graphic sex involved markers and pens.    
    
    
    Pussycats in plaid. pic.twitter.com/68x97BgTTF    
    
    
    Living in a cul-de-sac, you'd think a helicopter would land here every once in a while.    
    
    
    That dang Suze Orman keeps breaking into my garage and stealing the loose change in my car.    
    
    
    If they made a Jurassic Park Christmas Special, we'd sure as hell watch it.    
    
    
    Sweet dreams! Experience: I discovered a new species up my nose  http://gu.com/p/3khkn/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Covering a surface area of 27,857 square feet, the windows will delight shoppers while enraging window washers.  http://www.wired.com/design/2013/12/emporia-mall/ …    
    
    
    Mmmm... Carpenter coffee. http://www.psfk.com/2013/12/wooden-block-coffee-machine.html#.UqR5IJBwj04.twitter … via @psfk    
    
    
    Rediscovering Palladia.    
    
    
    What The Average American Consumer Will Spend This Christmas http://onion.com/1jcaLJ6  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Bring some LeekSpin into your life. http://www.leekspin.com/     
    
    
    US parachutes 2,000 dead mice into Guam http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/sideshow/operation--mouse-drop-163310851.html?soc_src=mediacontentstory …    
    
    
    "What's 'chi-pottel'?" 

— some shopper    
    
    
    From Italy, the United Pets Crick Crock, designed by Stefano Giovannoni and approved by Vixen. pic.twitter.com/NStPPLQSaH    
    
    
    Not to be confused with the chia penis, which also exists. pic.twitter.com/JtPQMX1XUx    
    
    
    Shoveltastic! Scenes From the History of Snow Removal http://shar.es/DPC0I  via @sharethis    
    
    
    I prefer Spotify over Pandora because so far there aren't any ugly Spotify bracelets being sold in jewelry stores.    
    
    
    Michelle Kwan is generally credited with inventing Kwanzaa.    
    
    
    [goes into bathroom and examines bottle of Paul Shmitchell shampoo]

Dammit!    
    
    
    The forgotten Spice Girl, kicked out just before the first record was completed. pic.twitter.com/ejf6Mx6cyo    
    
    
    Nabisco is now testing Wil Wheaton Wheat Things in select markets.    
    
    
    5 mind-bending facts about dreams http://www.mnn.com/health/fitness-well-being/stories/5-mind-bending-facts-about-dreams …    
    
    
    "Put the 'Ow!' in 'Lowe's'" never really caught on as a slogan.    
    
    
    No big words. pic.twitter.com/aiEItcpbTi    
    
    
    Thank you, The Simpsons, for Dick Fiddler.    
    
    
    String Theory https://vine.co/v/hQJ90xlHhI9     
    
    
    @BrandOneCulture @mPortray Yes.    
    
    
    Never eat rotini when your life is spiraling out of control.    
    
    
    @BrandOneCulture @mPortray Actually, Bismarck is more of a bub than a hub, and definitely not a hubbub.    
    
    
    Inconsiderate Woman On Bus Eating Live Tuna http://onion.com/1963mr3  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Vixen activates her Level 12 Please-Don't-Move Eyes. pic.twitter.com/yaYs7ATHl8    
    
    
    Bad service on your #iphone? Try this 1200 year old phone @NMAI http://www.smithsonianmag.com/ideas-innovations/Theres-a-1200-year-old-Phone-in-the-Smithsonian-Collections-231152081.html#.UqVFkLINjcU.twitter … via @SmithsonianMag    
    
    
    Tried using The Force to clear the driveway. 

Now using The Shovel.    
    
    
    Way More Than You Ever Wanted to Know About Eggnog http://shar.es/DN2vB     
    
    
    Your Monday morning critter vid: You Shall Not Pass, Dog: http://youtu.be/S7znI_Kpzbs  via @youtube    
    
    
    Until my Twitter account is verified, how can I know if I'm real?    
    
    
    When dentists die, they meet St. Peter at the Pearly Whites.    
    
    
    Microwave oatmeal isn't a very strong motivator to start the day.    
    
    
    Jordan almonds. 

Somebody must've already eaten all the Jonathan, Joey, Donnie and Danny almonds. pic.twitter.com/QIbDfQ91MI    
    
    
    Behold, the Infectious Disease Stress Ball: Bubonic Plague https://vine.co/v/hQXAF1JJiWM     
    
    
    Darwin the Ikea monkey "learning to be a monkey again" http://www.thestar.com/news/gta/2013/12/04/darwin_the_ikea_monkey_learning_to_be_a_monkey_again.html … via @torontostar    
    
    
    This beauty was on the first random page I opened up to in my new Dictionary of American Regional English vol. V. pic.twitter.com/MeO06S5asO    
    
    
    "Waiter! There's a hare in my Hennessy."    
    
    
    I live a life of danger — North Dakota shopping mall Chinese buffet sushi pic.twitter.com/oPsJO4IFqn    
    
    
    Tonight's entrée: Brats stewed in sauerkraut. pic.twitter.com/bUHtceaOdt    
    
    
    Purring with purpose, Cricket is serious about quality lap time. pic.twitter.com/NEgcc5KISh    
    
    
    .@WeihenstephanUS What's the difference between Weihenstephan and the Weihenstephaner I'm drinking right now? Curious.    
    
    
    Tonight on Food Network's Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives, Guy Fieri attempts a Triple Lindy.    
    
    
    Terrifying Man Selling Dead Trees Out Of Middle School Parking Lot http://onion.com/IBzrgn  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Facebook May Implement A 'Sympathize' Button http://www.psfk.com/2013/12/facebook-sympathize-button.html#.UqcPni-3tlo.twitter … via @psfk    
    
    
    Deer flees from vengeful flying squirrel |  http://metro.co.uk/2013/11/17/this-picture-of-a-deer-running-away-from-a-flying-squirrel-will-make-your-day-4190341/ … via @MetroUK    
    
    
    Each time I press my belly button, I fall asleep for nine minutes.    
    
    
    Opening a jar of whoopass just isn't the same.    
    
    
    I live for the faux pas, faux pas, faux pas 
I live for the faux pas-pas 
Live for the faux pas-pas    
    
    
    Sometimes I wish I lived in a country where its people type laughter as Jajajajajajaja!    
    
    
    93% of cable & pizza guys express disappointment in how the gals who "want to work something out" look nothing like the gals in the videos.    
    
    
    If I designed silverware, I'd name my company Tine After Tine.    
    
    
    @hubbit Hubbit, you're my favorite Oompa Loompa.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @proscriptus So close.    
    
    
    @proscriptus Now you're just toying with me.    
    
    
    @proscriptus I was looking for Voices Perry, but your alternatives were inspired.    
    
    
    @BrandOneCulture @mPortray And my fart references are down by 12% compared to this time last year.    
    
    
    @darewords Now I need to save up some wampum for volume VI!    
    
    
    Goats v. Avalanche — Pretty amazing. http://youtu.be/8bS4fOHzN1U  via @youtube    
    
    
    Next time you order pizza by the slice, make sure you get the pizza that's in between the slices.    
    
    
    There are only two true pizzas: the marinara and the margherita. 

Pizza Hut tried unsuccessfully to get the P'Zone recognized as the third.    
    
    
    Many Scandinavian surnames didn't have double consonants until after Scrabble became popular.    
    
    
    Removing the exclamation point from "Yay!" drastically changes its meaning.    
    
    
    @rejecter I know.    
    
    
    ♪ This little light of mine, I'm gonna let it... Dammit, Satan!    
    
    
    North Dakota grandmas know that for every two unexpected guests, just throw another can of peas into the casserole.    
    
    
    @bsailer ...then the tater tots got all soggy from the soup...    
    
    
    @WeihenstephanUS Thanks for replyin'. And brewin'.    
    
    
    ♬ Up from the depths... Godzilla - Official Teaser Trailer [HD]: http://youtu.be/QjKO10hKtYw  via @youtube    
    
    
    “Patience is the art of concealing your impatience.”  

— Guy Kawasaki    
    
    
    The best thing about micromanagers is they eventually have massive heart attacks.    
    
    
    Men's Wearhouse is starting to regret replacing George Zimmer with George Zimmerman.    
    
    
    A nightcap for your nightcap from Maker's Mark. http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1053     
    
    
    It's time to play America's favorite game... Mary Kay or Pepto-Bismol? pic.twitter.com/lNRBE7n0Qi    
    
    
    Mmmmmmm... Beefy toddlers. pic.twitter.com/gakye5lRFD    
    
    
    Twenty-firth. pic.twitter.com/ca4SKx3b8W    
    
    
    @Mistressnancy Alas, that was from an NBC report on country education rankings.    
    
    
    @Mistressnancy Indeed.    
    
    
    @TheWordsmith Total.    
    
    
    Your Essential Tips for Safe Winter Driving | Autopia | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/autopia/2013/12/wired-guide-winter-driving/ …    
    
    
    Here Be Dragons - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/the-secret-underwater-world-of-dragons/ …    
    
    
    NYC Taxi Drivers 2014 Beefcake Calendar http://www.nyctaxicalendar.com/     
    
    
    What has your whisky sent you lately?  http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1053     
    
    
    I'm a bit concerned that the upcoming Disney Star Wars movie stars a character named Jedi Clampett.    
    
    
    Do plumbers clog dance?    
    
    
    You bleached your what!?    
    
    
    All my tweets are made in China.    
    
    
    Sometimes it's hard to be a rōnin.    
    
    
    Subway introduces the fat-free SubZero! 

Just hand them five bucks and they'll give you an empty bag.    
    
    
    Protein bars are one of the lead causes of depression.    
    
    
    @RobHoAdvertisin They can if they want to.    
    
    
    Tried the pickled pattypan squash last night. Not bad, but there's something almost alien about them. pic.twitter.com/2CNFjSnmdt    
    
    
    Apple-smoked Gruyere cheese pic.twitter.com/NmjAR95HTD    
    
    
    Does Dr. Oz know that he has endorsed every single diet scheme advertised on radio?    
    
    
    @snyggstyle Mathilda May will protect me.    
    
    
    15 Delightful Cat Breeds’ Origins http://shar.es/OHz4P  Or you could adopt an awesome shelter kitty.    
    
    
    Mystery cheesecake just arrived for me. pic.twitter.com/uObU984593    
    
    
    Meet the robot telemarketer who denies she's a robot: http://ti.me/18keqT0  via @timenewsfeed (shudder)    
    
    
    Arctic Chill in LA (Jimmy Kimmel) : http://youtu.be/7HDhmQuSLRg  via @youtube    
    
    
    Testing the waters. pic.twitter.com/FEr5t8GTFN    
    
    
    The most disturbing thing about NBC's The Sing-Off is that they managed to find ten a cappella groups.    
    
    
    I might've been a much more successful rapper if I hadn't named myself White Fudge.    
    
    
    God, I hope they're paying Jewel and Ben Folds well.    
    
    
    I wonder if the band Hinder knew that their name is also a slang term for buttocks in certain parts of America?    
    
    
    A perfect example of delicious alliteration would be beer brats.    
    
    
    Somewhere there has to be a poet who calls herself Assonancy.    
    
    
    Sometimes you just gotta say "that" instead of "who".    
    
    
    @r00p I think that sprained something.    
    
    
    There's more to the world than Walmart.    
    
    
    I had a work dream last night. Do I put it down on today's or yesterday's timesheet?    
    
    
    20 Real Hilarious and Clever Notes From Children - zdouf! http://www.zdouf.com/3413/20-real-hilarious-and-clever-notes-from-children/ …    
    
    
    "You sit on a throne of lies!" ELF - 8 Bit Cinema: http://youtu.be/msK_YWowQ1U  via @youtube    
    
    
    Dear elves: 

Those hats you wear really don't make you look any taller.    
    
    
    You'd think Santa would've switched to a magical flying Arctic Cat by now.    
    
    
    I'm proud to be part of the generation that first learned about dysentery from a video game.    
    
    
    Sniff. Must have a dog hair in my eye or something. — Shelter Freedom Ride Pics That Will Melt Your Heart http://thebarkpost.com/shelter-freedom-ride-pics-that-will-melt-your-heart/ …    
    
    
    Does trying to catch the dropped mouthwash cap that's ricocheting around in the sink count as cardio?    
    
    
    Horsey in the Womb, Day 85 http://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/The-Serene-Beauty-of-Horses-in-the-Womb-232417291.html?c=y&page=4#.UqnfWoymO-8.twitter … via @SmithsonianMag    
    
    
    "You wanna sammich?" — RSA Shorts - The Power of Empathy: http://youtu.be/1Evwgu369Jw  via @youtube    
    
    
    The Onion Reviews 'The Hobbit: The Desolation Of Smaug': http://youtu.be/ZIy_uLF6xI8  via @youtube    
    
    
    The 2013 Hater's Guide To The Williams-Sonoma Catalog http://deadspin.com/the-2013-haters-guide-to-the-williams-sonoma-catalog-1481230580 …    
    
    
    Benedict Cumberbatch is a young Bill Nye the Science Guy.    
    
    
    iRobot needs to develop a specialized Roomba that pursues and kills spiders.    
    
    
    CBS's Two and a Half Men has changed its name to Two and a Half Seasons Too Long.    
    
    
    Are you a certified asshole? Find out with this quiz! http://electricpulp.com/guykawasaki/arse/ …    
    
    
    @TheWordsmith I'd have less of a problem with them if they respected my personal zone.    
    
    
    Is it wrong that I noticed the typo before the spider? pic.twitter.com/aHblpt28aD    
    
    
    Why cats scratch things. http://www.animalbehavior.org/ABSAppliedBehavior/article-applied-behavior/why-cats-scratch-things …    
    
    
    @jmitchem Eddie would take care of the spiders.    
    
    
    ...and a nice Chianti. pic.twitter.com/vMQQ6eJRkU    
    
    
    They should make Capri Moon.    
    
    
        
    
    
    "For the last time, my middle name isn't Jolly!" 

— Holly Hunter at some Christmas party    
    
    
    Friday sure took its damn sweet time arriving this week.    
    
    
    I'm relatively certain that Michael Richards would say yes to UHF 2.    
    
    
    I bet most unicorns end up cross-eyed.    
    
    
    I used to be paranoid about being paranoid. 

Now I'm paranoid about being paranoid about being paranoid.    
    
    
    Are there young fogies?    
    
    
    The best time to call me is while I'm driving and my phone is in the front pocket of my jeans. 

Apparently.    
    
    
    Because if they called it "eventually oatmeal", not as many people would buy it.    
    
    
    Another nice thing about oatmeal is you can use the leftovers to fill in driveway cracks.    
    
    
    Mel Blanc's marvelous tombstone. pic.twitter.com/jCVmlyl16n    
    
    
    Buffalo wings are fine and all, but I prefer buffalo breasts.    
    
    
    @terrybain Especially when they do that buffalo stance.    
    
    
    I'm not saying that cup of coffee was acidic, but my teeth just dissolved.    
    
    
    Hero pig rescues baby goat: http://youtu.be/g7WjrvG1GMk  via @youtube    
    
    
    @samuelpalin I'm with ya.    
    
    
    Smart and lazy parents just tell their kids that the Elf on a Shelf is quadriplegic.    
    
    
    Today in stock photography: Woman with Cheetah Enjoying Wine http://www.corbisimages.com/stock-photo/rights-managed/42-16828432/woman-with-cheetah-enjoying-wine#.UqtpYFs7N1U.twitter … It was nice of them to give the cheetah its own glass.    
    
    
    Nice view. (credits unknown) pic.twitter.com/6Be0xtj4F2    
    
    
    Double-decker pussycats. pic.twitter.com/DYI8SosYZQ    
    
    
    Toasty. pic.twitter.com/015unv7MgS    
    
    
    Restaurants that water down the ranch dressing, thinking people who like ranch dressing won't notice the difference.    
    
    
    The Onion's Tips For Decorating A Christmas Tree http://onion.com/JivOML  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Amazon customers review UFO detector - and it's hilarious http://www.examiner.com/article/amazon-customers-review-ufo-detector-and-it-s-hilarious … via @examinercom    
    
    
    The complimentary soup served with bread at this Italian restaurant was awful. pic.twitter.com/GURvqffsLr    
    
    
    The chicken risotto seemed rather runny. I later found out it was soup. pic.twitter.com/WGv7jfWvcu    
    
    
    Would you like a burger with your pepperoni? pic.twitter.com/2SL6gC5WAq    
    
    
    When I press the Minute Plus button on my microwave, it gives me 1:00. 

I feel cheated.    
    
    
    Impressive that some cities have districts just for meatpacking.    
    
    
    Pray for me. (@ Walmart Supercenter - @walmarthub) http://4sq.com/193q4lO     
    
    
    If you have a FireHole, seek medical attention immediately. pic.twitter.com/kdJuj5UeLm    
    
    
    Truck Nuts of Walmart pic.twitter.com/lJdFfl75Bj    
    
    
    Vixen forgot to wake up for her nap again. pic.twitter.com/z2ejK5uCcw    
    
    
    Kitty piddies. pic.twitter.com/0bPG5Sr8yi    
    
    
    Pre-Christmas Ham Experiment #1 has begun: pressure + cider + rosemary pic.twitter.com/iyoUVR04ZC    
    
    
    As long as the pressure thingy stays between the first and second line, it shouldn't explo... Aiiiiiiiiiieeeee! pic.twitter.com/f4C9GynFPO    
    
    
    Ham's done! https://vine.co/v/h2FOIXAjDTb     
    
    
    Perched Pussycat pic.twitter.com/LMfEhCWIDe    
    
    
    Cricket can't believe that Caturday is almost over already. pic.twitter.com/zVm2SBrgXo    
    
    
    You know you have a genuine Swedish pancake turner when it says "Bork!" after each flip. pic.twitter.com/rhwdEEAxT7    
    
    
    They Might Be Giants covering Chumbawamba's Tubthumping made me very happy.: http://youtu.be/JAAbuGX-qEY  via @youtube    
    
    
    The best part of walkin' up is havin' somethin' better than Folgers in your cup. pic.twitter.com/llSruyCCdK    
    
    
    On this day in 2003, we finally stopped Hammer time.    
    
    
    Has any dude ever used the bonus body wash & aftershave that come in cologne gift packs or are they just thrown in a drawer to collect dust?    
    
    
    I bet Moses found it easy to clear his driveway after a snow.    
    
    
    It's nice running into someone you know at Big Lots and neither one of you tries to hide.    
    
    
    Jambalaya Pasta pic.twitter.com/DaLTX73M9Z    
    
    
    "Deluxe" and "chunk" aren't really two words that belong together. pic.twitter.com/fXnq9p06Oh    
    
    
    I thought Supercross was a contest to see who could get the angriest.    
    
    
    If you buy these two products at the same time, the checkout gal is going to make certain assumptions about you. pic.twitter.com/p8cTDifWzx    
    
    
    External hard drives make excellent butt warmers. Apparently. pic.twitter.com/mLFuXwVt6p    
    
    
    @Akselev Don't wanna know.    
    
    
    You'd think Amy Adams' nose would have a Twitter account by now.    
    
    
    Combining Shop and Sex Ed proved troublesome for the cash-strapped middle school. pic.twitter.com/6Ha6EuzD3k    
    
    
    "Why didn't anybody tell us?" 

— some FOX News reporter after looking up "journalism" on Wikipedia for the first time    
    
    
    It's hard not to feel let down by current Dairy Queen commercials after the previous campaign did stuff like this... http://vimeo.com/47137326     
    
    
    Kitty whiskers are weird and wonderful things. pic.twitter.com/LzyafCpH0k    
    
    
    Breaking News: 

Using the latest in microchip and GPS technologies, Paula Cole has successfully tracked her first cowboy.    
    
    
    Yuki The Shiba Says Hello: http://youtu.be/lL5qfWrmiSo  via @youtube    
    
    
    You ever get the feeling you were a waitress in a cocktail bar?    
    
    
    From the early days of MTV: Joe Jackson - Steppin' Out: http://youtu.be/dopneKcyNXU  via @youtube    
    
    
    I'm holding out for Google Contact Lens.    
    
    
    From the spoonful of sugar to the magic bag to the ability to fly, all the evidence was there that Mary Poppins was a drug fiend.    
    
    
    The worst part about Friday the 13th is eventually there's Monday the 16th.    
    
    
    I really hope I didn't just quote Garfield.    
    
    
    Dang. Forgot to buy a fresh spool of line for my nose hair trimmer.    
    
    
    Where in the world is Clayton Santiago? http://instagram.com/p/h_MlLmrmS8/     
    
    
    Story of my life. http://instagram.com/p/h_rlN9rmar/     
    
    
    ♫ Icy road, take me home, to the place I belooooooong!    
    
    
    For those of you who experienced the joys of 80s video arcades, it's the Sinistar soundboard! http://www.soundboard.com/sb/JokeDeity     
    
    
    I trimmed my nose hair for this!?    
    
    
    Today my family said goodbye to our huge and fluffy country cat, Fluffy. He was 16. (more(… http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy11R7rCZ     
    
    
    To a cat, mixed nuts are a festive toy bonanza. https://vine.co/v/h0AJX6vLhnV     
    
    
    So many emotionally-exhausting dreams last night, but I didn't want them to stop.    
    
    
    And... the little drummer boy just woke up a very fussy baby Jesus.    
    
    
    If I don't sleep with my contacts in, my dreams are blurry.    
    
    
    A Fluffy Farewell http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1057     
    
    
    @JonNelsonJDN Darn feelings.    
    
    
    I'd like to thank the Academy but I can't remember why.    
    
    
    http://wordsmith.org 's word of the day...

Hebetate: (verb) To make dull or obtuse. 

Example: The executive really hebetated our ideas.    
    
    
    Pimento loaf, the fruitcake of meat. pic.twitter.com/fUuI4UTVtc    
    
    
    A mother cat teaching her kitten how to drink water. Squee, I say. Squee.  http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy11UZSce     
    
    
    .@adland @aronsolomon Perhaps you can settle for a nice pair of olive loafers?    
    
    
    "Spin tire for tumbling pigs." https://vine.co/v/h0JQiLjFWMl     
    
    
    Dairy companies have never had much luck selling their salty and bitter creams.    
    
    
    Is that Celine Dion or Sarah Jessica Parker? #TheVoice    
    
    
    Woman Learns Invaluable Lesson About Not Picking Fights with Stray Cats http://gawker.com/woman-learns-invaluable-lesson-about-not-picking-fights-1484881340 … via @debihope    
    
    
    Purdy song. ♫ Things I Never Needed – Grace Potter & The Nocturnals http://spoti.fi/JxpfyP  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Top Scientific Discoveries of 2013 - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/top-scientific-discoveries-2013/ …    
    
    
    Ach du lieber! Fun with German. http://youtu.be/gG62zay3kck  via @youtube    
    
    
    0.034% — Amount of things that went viral that were designed to go viral.    
    
    
    A guy from New Jersey was just caught trying to sell F-bombs to Al-Qaeda.    
    
    
    I hate it when that happens. http://youtu.be/9WoM2bHfr48  
(Ignore the science and enjoy.)    
    
    
    Don't you hate it when the pastry chef forgets to shave the almonds and you get their little pubic hairs stuck in your teeth?    
    
    
    Turnips for Deer would be the best band name of all time. pic.twitter.com/kLaO8k7G3X    
    
    
    Sweet dreams from Santa! pic.twitter.com/OcQFGwD0Eb    
    
    
    Photo: That was close. http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy11a6lpc     
    
    
    Terrible real estate agent photographs http://terriblerealestateagentphotos.com     
    
    
    Impressively, all these parts belong to the same cat. pic.twitter.com/a0MNfi47FD    
    
    
    Sadisfries.    
    
    
    The "go to jail" card from BibleOpoly. pic.twitter.com/deurQAQy7x    
    
    
    Poor Don Glover.  http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy11afcOG     
    
    
    A spur of the moment purchase. pic.twitter.com/wWKEal7G7a    
    
    
    ♫ In the still of the night I hear the wolf howl, honey, sniffing around your door... pic.twitter.com/8JagvAdMkL    
    
    
    The only 2013 holiday gift guide you need. http://oobject.com/home/flag/oobject-2013-gift-guide/80346/ …    
    
    
    In the long version of the Bose noise-cancelling headphones commercial, the dude gets hit by a bus.    
    
    
    Because Febreze is sooooo last millennium. http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1059     
    
    
    The mighty hunter waits in her camo blind for just the right moment. https://vine.co/v/h0pleKWtvMj     
    
    
    The mighty hunter, part 2. https://vine.co/v/h0DuPYvAE2q     
    
    
    57% of The Sing-off's viewers tuned in to take a gander at Jewel's cleavage.    
    
    
    You may have riches, looks, luck and success, but I have FROG jam! 

Ahhh, crud. pic.twitter.com/5wLtrGZBC9    
    
    
    How a Working-Class Couple Amassed a Priceless Art Collection http://shar.es/OlsO1  An incredible couple and incredible story!    
    
    
    Just realized that today's my divorciversary! Hooray!    
    
    
    It's a shame that couples don't pose for divorce photos.    
    
    
    My improvised divorciversary drink: Cask & Cream & Devil's Cut with a splash of Kahlua. I call it the Bitch Begone. pic.twitter.com/nOWXOH79hQ    
    
    
    I have yet to learn how to do the worm without crushing my balls.    
    
    
    I don't believe in angry sex because it's one step away from stabby-shooty sex.    
    
    
    It's nice having a forced air furnace but it bothers me how we've taken away the air's freedom.    
    
    
    Yes, Cricket. Santa knows you've been a good kitty. pic.twitter.com/gPPMdUdN2H    
    
    
    Obnoxious Friend Won't Stop Attaining Major Life Milestones http://onion.com/WsQWVM  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    When did "villain" become "antihero"?    
    
    
    Just saw a rogue groomsman wandering around downtown with a hairbrush.    
    
    
    Hero Rats — Pretty awesome. http://tmblr.co/Zsj6Yy11gPdBN     
    
    
    The easiest way to stop zombies is by throwing cauliflower at them.    
    
    
    Cricket chides me for having to go to work this morning. pic.twitter.com/6fM76T0D3W    
    
    
    For the winter months, the band Chevelle changes its name to Shovelle.    
    
    
    Every NFL Team Should Have Its Logo Redone Like This | Wired Design | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/design/2013/12/nfl-logos-cleverly-re-imagined-as-european-soccer-crests/ …    
    
    
    The Straight Dope: How come portraits on coins are in profile while those on bills are full face?: http://www.straightdope.com/columns/read/1068/how-come-portraits-on-coins-are-in-profile-while-those-on-bills-are-full-face#.UrQ-a2wM-Xs.twitter …    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure I don't want to know the grooming practices of early humans.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Some Pinterest people's personal potpourris of pursuits perplex me. pic.twitter.com/KYynFpPtfe    
    
    
    @AdLawGuy Way.    
    
    
    I think the Sunkist orange I ate earlier contained all the seeds taken from the Clementines.    
    
    
    Nerdtastic. An Engineer's Guide to Cats 2.0 - The Sequel: http://youtu.be/zsl_auoGuy4  via @youtube    
    
    
    McDonald's in France has a sandwich called Le Double Shiny Bacon.  http://www.mcdonalds.fr/produits/sandwichs/le-double-shiny-bacon …  That is all.    
    
    
    I wonder how much web fluid the Internet goes through in a day.    
    
    
    The new Yahoo! Mail thinks my name is Trevor. I don’t feel like a Trevor. Trevor? pic.twitter.com/dj5vqiMuqr    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC Nooooooooooo!    
    
    
    We Went to the Amazon to Find Out What Makes These Weird Web-Tower Things - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/web-tower-mystery-solved/ … Solved! ...sorta.    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC Nooooooooooooo!    
    
    
    This week I received cabbage rolls and deer sausage from friends. Hooray for friends!    
    
    
    I'm starting to wonder if somebody assassinated the Red Stripe ambassador.    
    
    
    The really jerky assassins are called assassassins.    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure that kid is stoned. pic.twitter.com/V76AHoV8V1    
    
    
    This Christmas, give them a stocking stuffer they'll never forget. pic.twitter.com/n1LVX1K9UH    
    
    
    Gilda would approve. http://videolog.tv/456266  pic.twitter.com/rpLao9NdbP    
    
    
    The Marvel Universe Is Way Better When Ghost Rider Is a Hamster http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/12/marvel-universe-superhero-animals/ …    
    
    
    Warning: Ineffective against clock thieves. pic.twitter.com/JVBtKAbwB4    
    
    
    ZZ Top was surprised to find that CD sales at Walmart jumped 3,000% this week.    
    
    
    If you want a cart at Target, you're SOL. pic.twitter.com/iantqgBEkc    
    
    
    Fried oysters. pic.twitter.com/2GmUZP7Gvf    
    
    
    Frog legs. And butts. pic.twitter.com/6mLDBeyPMX    
    
    
    They really don't want me to clean their favorite pillow. pic.twitter.com/B0lpzbhHzU    
    
    
    And now I know what happens when you try to wash sheer window panels.    
    
    
    ♬ You're shovelin'
 That's your price for white
 All this snow is mighty bright
 You'll be shovelin' more tonight    
    
    
    They call them tree skirts because your cats will skirt around on them.    
    
    
    Lil Bub's Magical Yule Log Video: http://youtu.be/ZuHZSbPJhaY  via @youtube    
    
    
    What do NFL fans at the game do during commercial breaks? 

Needlepoint, mostly.    
    
    
    Gerber life insurance commercials confuse me; do you get money if the kid dies or does the kid get money if you die?    
    
    
    Chevy's Santa wins.    
    
    
    Has anybody told the Tea Party what teabagging means yet?    
    
    
    Helping me not get the chores done. pic.twitter.com/KYC2YX16fj    
    
    
    It's beginning to look a lot like Cricket. pic.twitter.com/EXF4grwl8O    
    
    
    The conveniences of a pre-lit tree disappear when a string in the middle stops working.    
    
    
    That bird is not very respectful of Baby Jesus. pic.twitter.com/7tz8pbR7P9    
    
    
    @proscriptus A fine name.    
    
    
    This is either Applebee's Marsala mushroom sirloin or the scene of a horrific traffic accident. pic.twitter.com/dajT4f60hx    
    
    
    Gin gone wrong. pic.twitter.com/KgUtxmki2L    
    
    
    Orange Push-up: Disaronno, Svedka Clementine, orange juice and cream pic.twitter.com/EH79uNYh2H    
    
    
    "Hey Ya!" — OutKast 
"Ho Hey" — The Lumineers 
"Ho Ho Ho" — Santa Claus 
"Ya?" — My Ex    
    
    
    This cheese is embarrassed. pic.twitter.com/7CJXr82ogg    
    
    
    Not sure why the National Weather Service bothers issuing wind chill advisories; wind chill don't listen to nobody!    
    
    
    I want to work on a perfume/cologne commercial, because the only rule appears to be that it can't make any sense.    
    
    
    Run away! Bugs That Live Under Your Skin and Other Creepy Discoveries This Year - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/this-year-in-creepy-science/ …    
    
    
    Of Squirrels and Men: How We Moved Squirrels Into Our Cities http://po.st/ROxkCb  via @popsci Squirrel!    
    
    
    I wonder what punctuation mark would best end this sentence    
    
    
    That's brisk, baby! pic.twitter.com/J1r99gQhI9    
    
    
    Yes, Virginia, there is an escape clause.    
    
    
    This would be an excellent time for Phil Robertson to come out of the closet.    
    
    
    With some of that nautical lingo, sailors must giggle a lot.    
    
    
    "It's Christmas Eve, not Christmas Steve!" 

— some confused homophobe    
    
    
    Memories. "(Do It On My) Twin Bed - Saturday Night Live:  http://www.nbc.com/saturday-night-live/video/do-it-on-my-twin-bed/n44605/#.UrhQeH01r3U.twitter …    
    
    
    What should I first try on the critters tonight: kitty antlers, kitty santa hats or kitty earflap red plaid hunter caps?    
    
    
    I bet Suzanne Somers' friends and family get tired of receiving unsold Thighmasters for Christmas every year.    
    
    
    Nice how some Christmas cards are now more expensive than some gift budgets.    
    
    
    @Shih_Wei @MikeTalonNYC Edible Christmas cards... I think you're on to something here!    
    
    
    @MikeTalonNYC @Shih_Wei ♬ The Camptown ladies sign this card, doodads, doodads...    
    
    
    Chinese five spice spare ribs with Hoisin bbq sauce. I think the five spices were anise, anise, anise, anise & anise. pic.twitter.com/QQYRnDrwg9    
    
    
    The Menards Guy is the most medicated spokesman in America. pic.twitter.com/cSAKgPIBL1    
    
    
    CHRISTMAS PICKLE ACTIVATED pic.twitter.com/Zje8nD50O5    
    
    
    Cricket Holiday Hat Trial 1: Failure pic.twitter.com/9hoYN4eFa1    
    
    
    Vixen Holiday Hat Trial 1: Failure pic.twitter.com/fMBKeTYlzP    
    
    
    I'm beginning to suspect that cats don't like wearing hats.    
    
    
    Sigh. No visit from Proactive Santa.    
    
    
    There's a special hell for Xmas ornament designers that position the eye & loop so the ornament turns sideways when you put in on the tree.    
    
    
    Even with the addition of festive holiday garland, this statue is still so very, very wrong. pic.twitter.com/nVgIOUWYnR    
    
    
    SNOWBOT ACTIVATED https://vine.co/v/hEEudmXFiHZ     
    
    
    Don't clean until Christmas Eve... GREAT PLAN, CLAY!    
    
    
    Glitter. Glitter everywhere. So much glitter. Glitter.    
    
    
    Note to self: Never give a gift in a hexagon box again. pic.twitter.com/3JsvUypEKV    
    
    
    The girls took down their first reindeer today. I'm so proud! pic.twitter.com/vHzU693bLB    
    
    
    You do your Christmas village your way, I do my Christmas village my way. https://vine.co/v/hEVYZngT6XD     
    
    
    Current status. http://instagram.com/p/iU1QxLLmQZ/     
    
    
    Not sure how the wise men could see the star with all this snow.    
    
    
    It's beginning to look a lot like bedtime. pic.twitter.com/dYKooiRDnv    
    
    
    That'll teach me to dream of a white Christmas. 

[grabs shovel]    
    
    
    Make sure all Christmas presents are properly incubated. pic.twitter.com/Vf3Gwlcfcl    
    
    
    This Christmas, focus on what matters. pic.twitter.com/d8shYttLMi    
    
    
    Hershey's Kisses peanut butter cookies are a good part of this incomplete breakfast.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Santa forgot to give me telekinetic powers. Again.    
    
    
    Do angels remove their halos when they get a haircut?    
    
    
    The secret to a successful relationship is good harking skills.    
    
    
    Hove Christmas Tree 2K13 by day pic.twitter.com/t6yz4W0NOB    
    
    
    Pretentious Holiday Stroll home fragrance by Ralph Lauren. I'm not sure what Santa is doing. pic.twitter.com/1rEnjGSHqI    
    
    
    When the big potato you just peeled slips and falls down the garbage disposal hole.    
    
    
    Attached garages in North Dakota make perfect emergency Christmas dinner leftover refrigeration units.    
    
    
    Spuds sprung. pic.twitter.com/RvFq4Xcbtk    
    
    
    The earlier experiments paid off. Christmas rosemary cider pressure cooker ham was exceptional. pic.twitter.com/2DUfkV8CT1    
    
    
    We included fresh greens and cream with Christmas dinner because that's the way it's always been done. pic.twitter.com/bDlTOWucO8    
    
    
    Vixen decided to take advantage of my nephew during his Christmas food coma. pic.twitter.com/2d7B7ktPfV    
    
    
    An evil game. pic.twitter.com/nuV6gn07lU    
    
    
    Cricket tries making a Bronx cheer. pic.twitter.com/EYl6gwmEZ5    
    
    
    One year ago today, I took two lovely ladies home with me (They're sisters even!) and I've had no regrets. pic.twitter.com/DJP9ralD6x    
    
    
    All right, which one of you tweeted me the flu?    
    
    
    Who Framed Roger Rabbit: The Inside Story http://www.neatorama.com/2013/12/26/Who-Framed-Roger-Rabbit-The-Inside-Story/ …    
    
    
    Absurd Creature of the Week: 'Pufferfish on Steroids' Gets as Big as a Truck - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/absurd-creature-of-the-week-3/ …    
    
    
    Purdy. Back to the Future - Alan Silvestri - On Acoustic Guitar - Alvarez Guitars: http://youtu.be/zQj6LxJTEQY  via @youtube    
    
    
    Today's goal: Solid food.    
    
    
    "Ask not what your country can do for you, hmm?" 

— Yoda F. Kennedy    
    
    
    Nature - Winners Gallery - National Geographic Photo Contest 2013 - National Geographic http://on.natgeo.com/1ce7nw0   via @NatGeo    
    
    
    Letting your accounting department make marketing decisions is like giving ice cream to the lactose intolerant.    
    
    
    "Copay" is code for "Your insurance sucks."    
    
    
    A day off from work and I'm at the doc. Thug life. http://instagram.com/p/ib-S6QLmYM/     
    
    
    Twitter just hasn't been the same since they removed the poke feature.    
    
    
    Been coming here for years but didn't notice the error until today. pic.twitter.com/z85UXz7Bnv    
    
    
    Z-Pak, steroids and codeine, oh my! pic.twitter.com/PNFA4IScT5    
    
    
    Vixen takes board games very seriously. pic.twitter.com/aVE77CENLY    
    
    
    The Waltons are for people who found Little House on the Prairie too exciting.    
    
    
    Ow! My Balls! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_8yGGtVKrD8 …    
    
    
    So if I switch to T-Mobile, a company with 45 million customers and annual revenues of $21 billion, I'll be a rebel?    
    
    
    Not for those with abandonment issues. http://distractify.com/culture/arts/the-most-spectacular-abandoned-places-in-the-world/ … via @Distractify    
    
    
    @CaffeineAndHate @GrumpusNation This explains the horse.    
    
    
    Geronimo! The Straight Dope: Why don’t commercial jets have parachutes?: http://www.straightdope.com/columns/read/3141/why-don-t-commercial-jets-have-parachutes#.Ur5JJ-fk-8A.twitter …    
    
    
    @apierno It's Rhodamine Red, you bastard!    
    
    
    @apierno Mutinous Magenta?    
    
    
    Know-it-alls never do.    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Tibbles the Merciless" — 10 of History's Most Power-Hungry Cats http://shar.es/9nhQs     
    
    
    McSweeney’s Internet Tendency: List: Flora and Their Corresponding Holiday Ritual Call to Action if Encountered.: http://www.mcsweeneys.net/articles/flora-and-their-corresponding-holiday-ritual-call-to-action-if-encountered#.Ur7NLmYh8zY.twitter …    
    
    
    Don't know what you got 'til it's gonged.    
    
    
    Turns out the Infiniti that Santa got me for Christmas was stolen.    
    
    
    Bobby Flay is doing a show with a Vermont theme. This explains the Canadian bacon.    
    
    
    Why aren't all channels available in HD by now?    
    
    
    The Pioneer Woman's recipe for Rocky Mountain Oysters: 

1) Remove from boy cow. 
2) Boil for 90 hours. 
3) Top with ranch dressing.    
    
    
    Alt. rock out of Nashville. ♫ Battle Scars & Broken Hearts – Darling Parade http://spoti.fi/10MkvPi  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    The wild squatters of an abandoned cottage in Finland. Photographs by Kai Fagerström.

http://www.kafa.fi/pages/the-house-in-the-woods.php …    
    
    
    MTV Hits just played a Justin Bieber song. Why was there a duck singing backup vocals?    
    
    
    Vixen booty. pic.twitter.com/IUgSVcKCSf    
    
    
    Body optional. pic.twitter.com/4gDvxiYVL2    
    
    
    When you have no reason to leave the house, which makes you want to leave the house even more.    
    
    
    Let's roast chestnuts! Step 1: Cut through the shells so they don't explode. pic.twitter.com/4QzJTlEE08    
    
    
    Let's roast chestnuts! Step 2: Simmer in salty water for a quick bit. pic.twitter.com/1jak3juEfE    
    
    
    Let's roast chestnuts! Step 3: Drain, plop in pan and put in 425° preheated oven for 15 minutes. pic.twitter.com/yaSLSnW0Pp    
    
    
    Let's roast chestnuts! Step 4: Remove from oven, put in plate and cover with towel for 10+ minutes. pic.twitter.com/SXyTRyuz3O    
    
    
    Let's roast chestnuts! Step 5: Uncover, peel and eat! Yum! pic.twitter.com/LoaNZETDX5    
    
    
    @damana Hah! Yup, unless you have one hell of a lab.    
    
    
    @deeped Tuneeght ve-a're-a gueeng tu ruest chestnoots! Bork Bork Bork!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Gremlins 2 is on The Hub. Life is good.    
    
    
    @deeped Strange. I've restricted the tin foil to my underwear.    
    
    
    C-A... T-U-R... D-A-Y... Night! pic.twitter.com/AgRXBa6J6L    
    
    
    Shouldn't "Saturday night" be "Saturnight"?    
    
    
    @texturl Exactly.    
    
    
    I'm guessing that the Sparkle Fairy is single.    
    
    
    ♫ Nog, nog, noggin' on heaven's door... #kefir pic.twitter.com/9FQdjBym0I    
    
    
    @elizabite not too shabby.    
    
    
        
    
    
    That moment when you go over your account and realize how much you spent for Christmas.    
    
    
    My most intense relationships have always been the doomed ones.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Better Off Dead - The Q-Tip scene.: http://youtu.be/Hic4RKe0sp0  via @youtube    
    
    
    Rumor has it that Ann Coulter has his pubic hair shaved in the shape of a swastika.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Have the people making Sears commercials ever been to an actual Sears?    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure blue tortilla chips are made out of denim.    
    
    
    Toby Keith has a no-guns policy at his new Virginia restaurant, forcing Virginians to learn how to use silverware instead.    
    
    
    Back in my day, Charmin didn't make us have to choose between soft and strong.    
    
    
    Never work for a company that stocks its employee restrooms with 1-ply toilet paper.    
    
    
    Shouldn't miniature golf balls be smaller?    
    
    
    Cats have some wicked pro wrestling moves.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Working on a blog post. 

Which do you like better? 

Teeny-weeny or teensy-weensy?    
    
    
    Or to make it more interesting, trying sharing it with a stranger. pic.twitter.com/228v9advkr    
    
    
    The cracker with commercials that were so annoyingly awful, I still refuse to buy them, even at Big Lots prices. pic.twitter.com/oKP2E8TZNP    
    
    
    @JonNelsonJDN Thanks. I think there's a regional preference for each one, but I'm not sure what those regions are!    
    
    
    Question: How long do you leave your Christmas tree up? pic.twitter.com/hRugRE8zmR    
    
    
    @inthefade Wednesday, February 26.    
    
    
    Branding Nabisco a Little Bit Better (an adtothebone blog column thingy) http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1062     
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN With God all things are possible.    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Or cats.    
    
    
    @adland Very definitive.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Santa, me and Nurse Becky from a Christmas of yore. pic.twitter.com/n7XzNo5p3i    
    
    
    @GrumpusNation Under Nurse Becky's hat.    
    
    
    @Skittered_ I blame the apron.    
    
    
    @Skittered_ Hey! Those were my pants!    
    
    
    @Skittered_ One of these days I'll tell you where dip comes from.    
    
    
    This Wasp-Eating Falcon Laughs at Your Puny Stings - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/this-wasp-eating-falcon-laughs-at-your-puny-sting/ …    
    
    
    Oof. Scientists tell us their favourite jokes: 'An electron and a positron walked into a bar…' http://gu.com/p/3ycxy/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Mondagony.    
    
    
    Share this if you agree that telling people to share things if they agree comes off as a little bit desperate.    
    
    
    Monday! Monday! Monday! Monday! 
MONDAY! MONDAY! MONDAY! MONDAY!

— me trying to trick myself into being pumped up for Monday    
    
    
    Since I take probiotics, I won't be able to compete in the Olympics. Sorry, fans!    
    
    
    Branding Nabisco a Little Bit Better — unasked-for advice from adtothebone http://www.adtothebone.com/?p=1062     
    
    
    Today I stood up to Monday, went nose to nose, looked at it straight in the eyes and found out that it has shit-withering bad breath.    
    
    
    @bsailer darn efficient of you.    
    
    
    When you push a button on the JCPenney display, he swears at you. pic.twitter.com/A0xPr99T0g    
    
    
    The awesome story of Winston Churchill's portait by Yousef Karsh  http://wp.me/pvhXv-rL  via @aalholmes    
    
    
    Elijah Wood and Macaulay Culkin pic.twitter.com/0zwUio7Wu0    
    
    
    @adland Cassleton is about 170 miles to the east, much closer to Fargo. Scary stuff!    
    
    
    You are what you eat. pic.twitter.com/wz4J4O1qKi    
    
    
    Still on antibiotics so I can't drink. Plan B. pic.twitter.com/OEmrcQOVQA    
    
    
    "Nothing to see here. Move along." 

— some North Dakota oil industry rep    
    
    
    In other news, @Skittered_ made a video out of one of my tweets…  http://youtu.be/s7Pe-wzFMww     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Skittered_ I presumed sharing was my part of the Skittered business plan, so I just had to oblige. Happy new year!    
    
    
    Life is too short for processed cheese.    
    
    
        
    
    
    You don't hear much about unsightly toenail fungus these days.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I want it shaken AND stirred.    
    
    
    How now kowtow?    
    
    
    And that's what happens when Spider-Man tries to applaud.    
    
    
    Spider-Man, no! Machete-wielding Spider-Man robs convenience store. http://www.clickorlando.com/news/man-wearing-spiderman-mask-robs-central-florida-store/-/1637132/23668222/-/yqceth/-/index.html?hpt=ju_bn4 … HT @RobHoAdvertisin    
    
    
    I'm convinced that restroom motion-detecting paper towel dispensers have a fuck-you setting.    
    
    
    Happy Hogmanay!    
    
    
    World's Third Oldest Bible Displayed at Smithsonian, with extra Jesus words! http://on.natgeo.com/K9IxBU   via @NatGeo    
    
    
    Come to think of it, there really aren't all that many songs about rainbows.    
    
    
    Got a fresh loaf of 12-grain bread, a tub of 1% fat cottage cheese and I'm ready to not party!    
    
    
    My cats are having a hell of a time trying to learn the lyrics to "Auld Lang Syne".    
    
    
    The Grepolis MMORPG TV commercial does a great job of letting us know how lame it is.    
    
    
    Not quite sure why they make prescription drugs with side effects worse than the conditions they treat.    
    
    
    Rumors abound of an eHarmony/Ashley Madison merger.    
    
    
    Nobody's ever been able to pay attention to an entire Macy's commercial.    
    
    
    Watch out for white males dancing tonight. pic.twitter.com/iJou2jZzLg    
    
    
    According to the TV commercial, "Humira adalimumab" is pronounced "hue-mare-ah ad-a-lim-um-am-ma-muh-ma-muh-ma-muh-mob".    
    
    
    Fire Burger Deluxe with jalapeño bacon, pepper jack, fried jalapeños, chipotle mayo, hot sauce and more. pic.twitter.com/NO3nzv7mVn    
    
    
    Because LiqueurPie sounded much too naughty. pic.twitter.com/gw7GP8MAdP    
    
    
    And the end-of-year Ryan Seacrest Nivea commercial has begun.    
    
    
    The "H" is silent. pic.twitter.com/2lHXyBRyvI    
    
    
    Pitbull's starting to look more like Mini-Me every time I see him.    
    
    
    New Year's Eve with Jim Gaffigan and Conan O'Brien shooting lasers out from their nipples. pic.twitter.com/KNrbLUHH7N    
    
    
    HAPPY NEW YEAR! pic.twitter.com/hUBnhEKe87    
    
    
    If it's a Personal Identification Number, shouldn't there be more than 10,000 of them?    
    
    
    Remember when we used to write the wrong year on our checks, back when we used to write checks?    
    
    
    Oh, like you've never eaten toast over your kitchen sink before.    
    
    
    Post-Christmas clearance sale find: Metal star pic.twitter.com/bDp7YDw3XN    
    
    
    Sometimes you just have to go out and shovel snow while it's still snowing.    
    
    
    Post-Christmas clearance sale find: Metal snowflake... I think. pic.twitter.com/XoYEImbAcK    
    
    
    Grain scoops make the best snow shovels. 

And impromptu snow sleds.    
    
    
    Post-Christmas clearance sale find: A stocking for the cats. pic.twitter.com/43cWXkJTIC    
    
    
    May 2014 kick ass, but without kicking our asses.    
    
    
    @LeneBruun Tough call!    
    
    
    @garrett_moon "What's a year?"    
    
    
    @aethelwolfe Sword then.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    You people and your Gregorian calendar.    
    
    
    A business without people is a building.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    North Dakota winter grilling has several hurdles to overcome. pic.twitter.com/fHJ8whfZjJ    
    
    
    Still washing Christmas dishes.    
    
    
    wut pic.twitter.com/xLhMCDwA3O    
    
    
    If YOU'RE dating SOMEONE who posts AFFIRMATIONS and PLEDGES typed like THIS, break UP with them NOW!    
    
    
    Sheesh. Show up just 24 hours late for a party and they look at you like you're an idiot.    
    
    
    It's supposed to drop down to -22°F tonight so I'm eating a big bowl of smashed black beans and habanero Rotel.    
    
    
    You'd think codeine would come in pomegranate flavor by now.    
    
    
    Some Thursday morning creative inspiration. Photographers Create the Tiniest of Dramas on Your Dinner http://www.wired.com/rawfile/2014/01/tiny-scenes-playing-out-on-your-favorite-foods/ …    
    
    
    The Onion’s Tips For Hosting A New Year’s Eve Party http://onion.com/1fWVE3h  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    This is not my jam.    
    
    
    They keep saying that engagement is the secret to social media success but all these rings are getting damned expensive.    
    
    
    Here I am at my first rap battle. 
My brain is blank except for prattle. 
Random swear word! Fuckin' ayyy! 
I'm a honkey born this way.    
    
    
    Shame that Macy's hasn't yet licensed this song for its promotions. ♫ Sail – AWOLNATION http://spoti.fi/IlTmMN  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    These burger-flavored Carnation Instant Lunches are awful.    
    
    
    I once tried to swing on a star but it vaporized me.    
    
    
        
    
    
    It's 2014 and my bank still doesn't have a hizzle mortgage officer.    
    
    
    Imagining Nike ballet slippers.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Random quasi-inspirational quote that doesn't really say anything.    
    
    
    I'd retweet more if I was rewarded with a nice snack.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Creature Feature: 10 Fun Facts About the Rock Hyrax (Or, Are You Ready to Rock Hyrax?) - Wired Science http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2014/01/the-creature-feature-10-fun-facts-about-the-rock-hyrax-or-are-you-ready-to-rock-hyrax/ …    
    
    
    Random Festive Cat Toy pic.twitter.com/2FrRTHbixH    
    
    
    Mediterranean spinach salad with beer bun pic.twitter.com/u2bltXpyyc    
    
    
    North Dakota sunset 01-02-1014 pic.twitter.com/1TgokS85hC    
    
    
    Post-Christmas clearance sale find: Distressed metal star pic.twitter.com/r1veLGgjtZ    
    
    
    A Few Facts You Might Not Know About the TV Series Batman http://www.neatorama.com/2014/01/02/A-Few-facts-You-Might-Not-Know-About-the-TV-Series-Batman/ …    
    
    
    Post-Christmas clearance sale find: Distressed metal and mirror thingamabob pic.twitter.com/ESSJIq7Qr9    
    
    
    @VisitWilliston All the gas flaring is your area's version of the midnight sun, eh?    
    
    
    Owl Picture -- Bird Photo -- National Geographic Photo of the Day http://on.natgeo.com/1fpyItm   via @NatGeo    
    
    
    "Durr." A Vibrating Watch That Messes With Your Perception of Time | Wired Design | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/design/2014/01/a-vibrating-watch-that-messes-with-your-perception-of-time/ …    
    
    
    In America, doing crunches in the morning means a bag of Doritos.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The codpiece is cold this morning.    
    
    
    We're all people of Walmart, but many of us have found ways of overcoming this disability.    
    
    
    I'm pretty sure that Mitt Romney had a treehouse with an oval office built by now.    
    
    
    