S/O to @WakaFlockabsm leader in the music industry! He is in the Billion Club!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio waddup    
    
    
    Working on get @kingkrucial @ATOworldwide who are my Boss's get a video production with @souljaboy and @WakaFlockabsm    
    
    
    My favorite group is come from @Misfit_Go and that's @souljaboy is watching now! And @WakaFlockabsm have to check those niggas are huge    
    
    
    Turn up @WakaFlockabsm is time to touch things and turn it in gold! From the streets the real empire!    
    
    
    From the streets no one stop @WakaFlockabsm now in the empire he is making gold anything he touch! @atmybest197 and I love your work    
    
    
    In 2014 the festival of #HipHop in #Finland will be crazy half of those who do #music and are from #NewYork will be there @EShowsTV deals    
    
    
    No mater what keep in eyes on the route is the only way to walk till the end!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio get at me bro gm    
    
    
    “@WakaFlockabsm: Time 2 kill the stage” killing stages from the first day!    
    
    
    #Ready4Reform is time to make the correct change! A change what will make our migration system more strong and push our economy to grow!    
    
    
    Immigrants started 28% of all new U.S. businesses in 2011 - http://slidesha.re/1akJgLf  #Ready4Reform    
    
    
    @RepJerryNadler I'm #Ready4Reform that strengthens our economy! Please act now on #immigration reform. @FWD_us #CIR    
    
    
    "@BBBimmigration: Breaking: @SpeakerBoehner say's he's still #Ready4Reform and trying to "get this thing done" http://www.politico.com/story/2013/11/john-boehner-immigration-99797.html …"    
    
    
    Say you're #Ready4Reform. Add your name today: http://OFA.BO/g86Jfa  #immigration    
    
    
    @Astro_Ron some one from other planet follow me! Thanks for that follow back    
    
    
    This is about money and is the only thing what you have to care about! The rest is just a he with no winners    
    
    
    @Astro_Ron some one from other planet follow me! Thanks for that follow back    
    
    
    NYC come SEE ME! 

11/25 

https://www.facebook.com/events/475522015900593/ …
RSVP?    
    
    
    NYC come SEE ME! 

11/25 

https://www.facebook.com/events/475522015900593/ …
RSVP?    
    
    
    S/O to the family @atmybest197 @EShowsTV @souljaboy @M2thakSODMG @KingKrucial @IamBCoolin @LilDope @moeager @OfficialKushGod @SAVAGEhaRD    
    
    
    S/o to my homie @AlexD_SODMG    
    
    
    Early mornin turnup! S/o @SouljaBoy @Fabrizio #SODMG    
    
    
    S/O to the family @Misfit_Go @OfficialDubP @ATOworldwide @DJAAANYC @sodmg    
    
    
    Loyalty over everything but if you don't respect my royalties then don't expect from me any loyalty    
    
    
    S/O to the family @TAZDMT    
    
    
    @souljaboy my family @EShowsTV @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG has everything in place 4u and the tour. What's good ?    
    
    
    I need to ask @souljaboy I am a #SODMG let's read his tweet hope the answer is a yes!    
    
    
    I met Ahmed and I dedicated the first Flashes of Thoughts Braille copy to him pic.twitter.com/egsdOA4TwY    
    
    
    I met Ahmed and I dedicated the first Flashes of Thoughts Braille copy to him pic.twitter.com/egsdOA4TwY    
    
    
    For real is not from God have to make line and wait!    
    
    
    @WellsFargo hey guys hit my dm!    
    
    
    @WellsFargo hey guys hit my dm!    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up money don't stop! Let make #HipHop    
    
    
    WOW. Identity thief tried charging $1000's to my credit card in India but @WellsFargo caught it just in time. Thanks for looking out, y'all!    
    
    
    Video: Soulja Boy - Turnin Up http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh5poSYOmHB94AB3o2 … #WSHH via @worldstar    
    
    
    booking info: @sodmg    
    
    
    To much BS when you handle small artist! I can't believe talking on my fucking back that why I keep it real only with my Fam    
    
    
    Turn up http://www.sodmgstore.com     
    
    
    FF @lemurwrangler @calestous @tmsruge @Astro_Nicole @astro_aggie @adllewellyn @GlobalVzla @OneYoungWorld @grameencl @FragileOasis    
    
    
    FF @lemurwrangler @calestous @tmsruge @Astro_Nicole @astro_aggie @adllewellyn @GlobalVzla @OneYoungWorld @grameencl @FragileOasis    
    
    
    S/O @WakaFlockabsm @Fabrizio @EShowsTV . Much love 2 all of ya    
    
    
    @Fabrizio turn up    
    
    
    Salute to my manager @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @YStijd turn up    
    
    
    "@souljaboy: go follow @sodmg and i will follow you back"
Holla @atmybest197 and @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @souljaboy check dm and iMessage    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello NY is infested of rats! Loyalty instead of freedom, loyalty before and after royalty #CodeOfKings    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello what's good my homie?  We all need to get up with my team @Fabrizio @EShowsTV asap    
    
    
    @HOFABANG the next deal is with our big boss @M2thakSODMG    
    
    
    Suck a RICH nigga DICK    
    
    
    Suck a RICH nigga DICK    
    
    
    Power and Money make Mobs quiet but Luxury things make mobster reals bosses!    
    
    
    S/O to @AniqZafar lets repet our favorite phrase "vamos a ver...." Salute My friend hope everything is good over there    
    
    
    S/O to @AniqZafar lets repet our favorite phrase "vamos a ver...." Salute My friend hope everything is good over there    
    
    
    Crank that!    
    
    
    pray that @Sodmg becomes the number 1 label and group in music    
    
    
    God bless    
    
    
    S/O to @souljaboy for allow us to work with the King of hip hop    
    
    
    @Qmachette your stuff is dope I hear you on your personal page! And till your put your people on the right I am with you 100% if u allow me    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Let's Talk Biz    
    
    
    Turn up @souljaboy you are making the difference and our partners love it    
    
    
    When @SouljaBoy talk About business be dont play! He Will kill this game on December 17! So be ready    
    
    
    Turn up time    
    
    
    I need clear this stuff before january! love hard work but this is for professionals lol    
    
    
    “@souljaboy: http://old.hulkshare.com/s26mb1m0r08w 😎” Turn Up! is time to get some money!    
    
    
    Turn up or get out from my route cuz I am walking to success! Troubles only make me more stronger! #Fam    
    
    
    S/O to @WarithNiallah    
    
    
    Turn up! Time to build the empire @souljaboy let's get the new album to the top ten @atmybest197 wake up    
    
    
    Working with large clients! my brother @atmybest197 and @EshowsTV are or priority! But now we are supporting @Souljaboy and the @SODMG Fam    
    
    
    Drooling> Life-size replica of Mercedes supercar in @Sony #GT6 shown at the @LAAutoShow http://cnnmon.ie/17VnM7l  pic.twitter.com/fxkTv3Wvpv    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG    
    
    
    http://www.amazon.com/Jab-Right-Hook-Story-Social/dp/006227306X/ …
#rightHook
#enoughsaid    
    
    
    http://Facebook.com/dabeezy1     
    
    
    find a good reason to hit my DM do it, if not then don't waste your time! If you don't have a clear goal then I can't make anything about    
    
    
    Go follow @REAL_SODMG is time for the family is time for Hip Hop @SODMG #SOD #MoneyGang    
    
    
    This family have only boss's @Souljaboy @atmybest197 @M2thakSODMG and those name have is fire on they music    
    
    
    @ImYoungChizz sup boss    
    
    
    Wake is time to work!    
    
    
    Today is UnFollow day so cleaning my TL don't get offended if you go out but I only Fuck with loyal niggas the rest go to the trash    
    
    
    Fabrizio!!! Talk to me!! What's good #SODMG RT @Real_SODMG: “@Fabrizio: @ImYoungChizz sup boss” turn up boss    
    
    
    @Interscope turn up we have things I will like to discuss    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    The music industry is not easy! Is not sweet is hard as hell so let's have a real talk and get ready to get the money    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    My boy @DJAAANYC will be busy this weekend at @stage48nyc    
    
    
    Ppl is about the BS between one artist instead to be about the own shit and get fire music! Keep eyes in your shit not about others shit    
    
    
    @deejaynogood turn up    
    
    
    Ppl is about the BS between one artist instead to be about the own shit and get fire music! Keep eyes in your shit not about others shit    
    
    
    @CEOFlameGotti have his mouthful of true    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello turn up big boss    
    
    
    @Jowynalex I don't hate to!    
    
    
    Got you @souljaboy    
    
    
    Don't get upset cuz i don't reply quickly but i have severals things to do related to Money we are making till you are looking how to get it    
    
    
    Is funny when a no one ask me "you know who I am?" And I say no I don't know!    
    
    
    Nobody likes a RAT LoL pic.twitter.com/GFTPX3oaE1    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    Where is every one?    
    
    
    @KingKrucial go Follow @richnice2    
    
    
    Turn up this is to take over    
    
    
    This business is for those who are ready to take success from the back or from any other place they can!    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving  to every one in the USA! S/O to the family @SouljaBoy @AtMyBest197 @Real_SODMG @AlexD_SODMG @HT @DJAAANYC @kingkrucial    
    
    
    salute and happy thanksgiving @OfficialDubP @ATOworldwide @GGMSTL @moeager @DonaldLawrence    
    
    
    Happy ThanksGiving @WakaFlockabsm    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to the bitch @NaquanReese my respect to the next idol    
    
    
    Salute to @LilDope @Jack_Moore7 @OfficialKushGod @flostorm @YoungKeiko happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    @IamRonnyLehmann turn up big boss    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to my brothers @HypeSir and @Standish913    
    
    
    Happy holidays @TheRealKingOpm hope we can see you soon    
    
    
    Turn up @Sodmg let's get the world down till our feet @souljaboy    
    
    
    Turn up @IamBCoolin happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy Turkey Day @SODMG @souljaboy @Fabrizio ♻️    
    
    
    @PvTruest @SODMG @souljaboy dope dope    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion sup    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion happy thanksgiving Preston thanks for the #FollowBack much respect    
    
    
    Much respect to @WarithNiallah happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving @HOFABANG @THEPIFFMAN    
    
    
    Money make sense but power make things easy! Happy Thanksgiving @ILLUMINATIAM    
    
    
    Fuck double F! I got in shot with that Escobar email came on big boss don't play like that    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to the bitch @NaquanReese my respect to the next idol    
    
    
    @cib110 info@fabrizzio.it    
    
    
    Got notice #BitCoins cost now is 1133 $$$$ holly shit a few months ago cost just 150 how many do you have?    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    Is time to come and make deals are you ready for?    
    
    
    I am not looking for more artist, I am already working with #Kings S/O to those who are in our #Family roster    
    
    
    I am loyal to those who stand up with me when everything looks bad, and I respect those who are there to do business when things looks good    
    
    
    @ImYoungChizz turn up man! Is time to make things happen    
    
    
    Turn up @KingKrucial and congratulations for the deal with @VEVO now is time to make 1M of sales on @iTunes    
    
    
    Viva Las Mexico pic.twitter.com/b53m47DMNT    
    
    
    Bitch I am not here to waste my time if you don't have time for wait till I end real deals then go and fuck yourself    
    
    
    @Lloydbanks turn up! How was the show in #Dubai?    
    
    
    @WakaFlockabsm fuck that Waka app is fucking any other penny artist app!    
    
    
    Download now!!!!! http://get.wakaville.com  RT pic.twitter.com/BMIUOtEPn4    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    Turn up @DJMany @IAmShawtyboy is time to make #VIPRecords    
    
    
    Our label is called VIP Music Records are you ready?    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    I done ran up the moneyyy    
    
    
    @BIDJuventud email me gary at Vaynermedia com    
    
    
    This week we will start closing deals and officially signing artist to VIP Music Records    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion thanks for the favorite! We decide to move and put the label out so turn up let's discuss    
    
    
    time to work we will made a tour with @DailyLoud including @af_rome @whokr and @kingkrucial hope @WakaFlockabsm allow us to go up with him    
    
    
    You do music? Yes, but your last hit was when I was 21    
    
    
    Thanks for the media support @WarithNiallah    
    
    
    No, no! is not I am not in is you are out! So don't expect this game be the same after we make this move    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    So Sleepy.    
    
    
    Wake up @kingkrucial    
    
    
    You ever see numbers like this? pic.twitter.com/K03WNk54I8    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    @Qmachette s/o he stand up when the bitches run away    
    
    
    Our label will invest do be ready! But don't need you begging at me! I need you making money cuz is what matter for me    
    
    
    @GageDC this is my Brother and is part of my family so fuck this who don't hola at Gage    
    
    
    Our label will invest do be ready! But don't need you begging at me! I need you making money cuz is what matter for me    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    HTF if you don't have money as me, will you ever teach me how to make more money? I only fuck with my family and you hear who they are    
    
    
    @PvTruest I am a #VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    I swear if you don't follow @GageDC & @antkingsmith there's NO real $hxt on your TL. Lol    
    
    
    whats good @stachemedia #REDSony    
    
    
    Our roster will be cut in up to 75% Sorry guys But not money means not part of the DON Family    
    
    
    NEW VIDEO: @Eminem #RAPGOD http://intersco.pe/Il1QqB     
    
    
    I am not #Rich I am just a crazy entrepreneur who make money building his own dreams    
    
    
    11:11 - Make A Wish.... #LovingLife    
    
    
    Those who are looking for a pay check from our label need to understand our pay days are after you show us real numbers    
    
    
    No today!    
    
    
    Check our next week my G on @MTV and @VH1 S/O to @KingKrucial    
    
    
    No I am not part of any other Family than my own empire family so #TurnUp    
    
    
    I know you are fake when your best answer is an excuse    
    
    
    @richnice2 turn up    
    
    
    Turn @THEPIFFMAN    
    
    
    Just landed in Mexico turn up at the show tonight    
    
    
    #1017 #MentionMe    
    
    
    #1017 #MentionMe    
    
    
    @gucci1017 follow back is time to take overseas back    
    
    
    http://www.datpiff.com/Soulja-Boy-The-King-mixtape.555926.html …    
    
    
    My account have only six 0 afters positive numbers what about yours?    
    
    
    My account have only six 0 afters positive numbers what about yours?    
    
    
    watching college football more often after that half i just seen, never watched college football before until today lol    
    
    
    watching college football more often after that half i just seen, never watched college football before until today lol    
    
    
    Go follow our best DJ @DJAAANYC    
    
    
    @BrooklynNets holly shit you still not following me back what you wait for?    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/jfChK1keaR    
    
    
    Turn up @badboyrecords @anthonysabadboy    
    
    
    Wake body @yungyungpallo    
    
    
    @HipHopTXL Turn up    
    
    
    I hear you @yungyungpallo i think we should talk    
    
    
    Money make noise    
    
    
    @Real_SODMG what it do #TurnUp    
    
    
    R.I.P @RealPaulWalker    
    
    
    Why Do People Feel Guilty When You Mention Anything.    
    
    
    Again our label is called VIP Music Records and our live TV platform is @EShowsTV    
    
    
    Why Do People Feel Guilty When You Mention Anything.    
    
    
    if I offer you a deal will you take it?    
    
    
    #NP Swagga On A Million - Young Chizz #SundayAfternoonShow with @WaleOzolua    
    
    
    Money matters, numbers matters so if you are no making numbers with your music don't expect a deal from a label    
    
    
    Labels don't eat words like "I am the next idol" or "I have the next hit" they believe in "I am selling xxxxxx on @itunes" #GetYourDeal    
    
    
    Take me 5 years make 1 million, and I am not proud of it because others make it in a month! So I keep working    
    
    
    People who focus on the "label deal" are complete wrong! They have to focus on the "fans deal" what will make the label dream real    
    
    
    Loyalty make royalties! Is not in any other way    
    
    
    Talking with @Facebook about a large Campaign for the Label, honestly the network of Facebook is more complicate to handle    
    
    
    I really love my Picture with @Iron_Man pic.twitter.com/8kPWtpTdLo    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/kf3kH042G7    
    
    
    Love my Cowboy hat pic.twitter.com/S3SMzyJOW9    
    
    
    Just finished a long day or interviews & photo shoots. Now time for another meeting then sound check at @CavalliClubDxb. #Dubai    
    
    
    I am not like any of those who have only money on they head because I have the money in my packages and the business in my head    
    
    
    S/o to @VVIPTV go check they webpage    
    
    
    #Dubai    
    
    
    Wake up #America turn up #UK S/O #Dubai    
    
    
    @Fabrizio  congrats on your success wit ur new label situation.. Meet y'all at the top!! RNS    
    
    
    Wake up #America turn up #UK S/O #Dubai    
    
    
    December 5    
    
    
    @souljaboy @HookStarz @Tyga @Fabrizio  I think its time for another track... #ballaholiks101 WE GET IT IN..@TRAPAHOLICS PROJECT MEDUSA 1831    
    
    
    Go Follow @_itsXING    
    
    
    Before sending me an e-mail or a #Twitter DM ask yourself what's the to contact me or how can I help so we don't waste time    
    
    
    Dope article. Send this to New Line cinema so they can give us the money we need to do LAST FRIDAY. http://globalgrind.com/2013/11/29/life-lessons-you-can-learn-from-the-movie-friday-list-gif/?utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    @macklemore only have 20 dollars on my package don't apply to my life but is one of my favorite songs    
    
    
    if you share a video be sure 10k or more ppl view it! Because your music can be good but no one care about it! Ppl care about $$(Numbers)$$    
    
    
    The only people we who I work are on my webpage and then my partner! So don't tie me to the past cu I live in the future    
    
    
    @DJAAANYC @QUINTINOO salute family    
    
    
    Live on @WKRBradio 90.3FM get it now on http://Soundcloud.com/djaaa  pic.twitter.com/i7MZ36XzyS    
    
    
    Dirty true is you are not playing at all #NewYork is my town!    
    
    
    S/o The Homie @Fabrizio #Salute #GGM #SODMG    
    
    
    Dope article. Send this to New Line cinema so they can give us the money we need to do LAST FRIDAY. http://globalgrind.com/2013/11/29/life-lessons-you-can-learn-from-the-movie-friday-list-gif/?utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    If you lose my respect then you lose everything!    
    
    
    #MMG MUSIC: @TheRealTracyT ft @MeekMill "16" http://bit.ly/TracyTMeek16     
    
    
    My team own things what are yours? May in your dreams :)    
    
    
    S/O to @PrestonMillion tour in motion! And hands ready to work    
    
    
    I am part of the #MDT Million Dollar Team we don't join Money Team! Because everyone have money but just a couple have millions    
    
    
    December 5    
    
    
    "@Fabrizio: December 5" MY BIRTHDAY. #PRAY2GOTTI    
    
    
    don't ask me to hit you up, because my fists are pure gold and can break jaws #MDT (Million Dollar Team)    
    
    
    Turn up @Tmobile Making deals    
    
    
    Salute to @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    December 5….    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    @richnice2 go follow @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    @TuneCore hit my DM have some questions    
    
    
    Go check my G @jalanbravo https://soundcloud.com/bravomuzikgroup/for-the-moment-j-bravo-ft/s-iwpB3 …    
    
    
    El sábado estabamos en el semáforo con fabri y tres chicas como 49 veces miraron ehhh para mi que le miraron a @fabrizio    
    
    
    Go check is http://www.sodmggang.com  is #CyberMonday @SouljaBoy have special discounts out there    
    
    
    following everyone back today that rt this and need a follow that didnt get one yet. retweet this    
    
    
    Ready or not December 5 is the #Day    
    
    
    I don't need nothing else but I love to have always more than I actually have    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG is time to make a show with @Tyga not kiding    
    
    
    Hold on @Drake you need to hit me back so we can get @KingKrucial in    
    
    
    @souljaboy the big boss @HOFABANG will hit you again to make another collaboration at this time with @Tyga for the Medusa project    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG is time to make a show with @Tyga not kiding    
    
    
    S/O to @SouljaBOy and his label #SODMG was a Take over on Mexico    
    
    
    You made it...    
    
    
    @Souljaboy Made it!    
    
    
    @souljaboy Waddup nigga 💯    
    
    
    Turn up    
    
    
    S/O to @EmersonWindy    
    
    
    “@souljaboy: Turn up” we are up    
    
    
    I was bed ridden yesterday, had the highest fever in history RT @VIPMusicRecords: @ImYoungChizz wake up boss    
    
    
    Our label have Rep. In Canada, USA, Europe and Latin American! And we are looking for indie artists    
    
    
    @Jayecane I hate ppl who try to compare me    
    
    
    Say no more! pic.twitter.com/gIw4gF5ZMs    
    
    
    @CEOMiamiMike appreciate the info, @AtMybest197 my partner will love to discuss about meeting with our parents in Dubai    
    
    
    Things what you should know about @CEOMiamiMike http://www.myfoxmemphis.com/video?autoStart=true&topVideoCatNo=default&clipId=9564211 … #Support #NGO @Bidjuventud    
    
    
    December 5 is the day    
    
    
    Habemus new phone @SamsungMobile Galaxy Note 3 hit my DM so I can have your phone! Thanks @TMobileHelp    
    
    
    New phone @SamsungMobile Galaxy Note 3 is for auto defense (means huge) but if you wanna be in my contact list DM your number and name    
    
    
    @HOFABANG @laflamethrower1 i AM Also near to get in talk with @EmersonWindy    
    
    
    Waste of time… they don't active it yet    
    
    
    Whats up @Souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    Get he best Distribution Package working with @SouljaBoy and @Real_Sodmg    
    
    
    Let's keep the game clear! And you know what I mean!    
    
    
    SMH… quiet on home waiting on some money get move and get calls with threats is the most funny shit    
    
    
    From this moment we are not in good standing with any of you… and you know who i refer to…. so keep your ass far from me    
    
    
    From this moment we are not in good standing with any of you… and you know who i refer to…. so keep your ass far from me    
    
    
    @DJAAANYC whATS GOOD    
    
    
    Turn up #Dubai @HOFABANG Next video is on the land of the #kings    
    
    
    ethic is something what make the difference between a Good business and a wrong business….    
    
    
    Check Out @maravimusic & @LALovetheboss  - Stuntin Hard http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XXn3EI5xTzw … #RT #BreakoutArtist    
    
    
    Hope after all of this go and come everything work like is suppose...    
    
    
    Much love to everyone    
    
    
    @atmybest197 today!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio where are u at ? People keep hollering at me 4u. Get at me asap    
    
    
    Got the Dm Boss @WakaFlockabsm will setup a call conference this week with the point person (Brick) and my partner @atmybest197    
    
    
    S/o to our family member @TheRealKingOpm    
    
    
    Ministers discussed plenty of ideas on increasing teacher competence, upgrading teaching methods, &enhancing student stkills #uaebrainstorm    
    
    
    “@JohnBoy: Call Soulja Boy 716-249-9040” that's not his phone number    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    @JohnBoy ahhhh    
    
    
    Turn up #VIPGang #MDT (Million Dollar Team)    
    
    
    Turn up @atmybest197    
    
    
    @RealDJTripleA THEY ARE GOOD @TDBank_US    
    
    
    From now rare will buy a @hp they @HPSupport is a mess! I will prefer to keep a #Mac    
    
    
    @Fabrizio wats ur email?    
    
    
    OMW! Long day    
    
    
    My respect to @MichelleObama a woman with character!    
    
    
    @BarackObama show to the world, what a real man have to do! He respect @MichelleObama decisions! where captain directs, no sailor directs    
    
    
    Success never come alone or without hard work! I you are looking success be ready to walk in the hard way    
    
    
    #Music    
    
    
    S/O to @DonaldLawrence for all the inspirational material he always post! #KeepItReal and from the soul    
    
    
    A leader find solutions a loser the problems! Focus in what success means    
    
    
    Dreams are only dreams till the moment you put your hands to build things!    
    
    
    The same way a success man use can to achieve his goals can make other person fall in mistakes    
    
    
    Love what you do to build what you want!    
    
    
    Big S/O to @YoungKeiko keep the work hard! No one can stop you in your goals! #HipHop with soul    
    
    
    Coming some #Selfmade @GGMSTL pic.twitter.com/BRFfhq84GC    
    
    
    God bless ur steps, and help u to achieve ur goals! But don't forget to be thankful for anything he give or take from u because he knows    
    
    
    The streets ain't for everybody... that's why they made sidewalks.... Use them #bighomieFlock    
    
    
    The streets ain't for everybody... that's why they made sidewalks.... Use them #bighomieFlock    
    
    
    Don't tell me you have the key to make money if you can't make money yourself!    
    
    
    Turn up @gucci1017 to much tweets that music need a good place to be performed! Get a my family!    
    
    
    World Premiere: @Gucci1017 Ft. @MigosATL - Jackie Chan [Prod. By @ZaytovenBeatz] S/O @djplugg http://trapsntrunks.com/2013/12/11/gucci-mane-ft-migos-jackie-chan-prod-zaytoven/#.UqkcebReqdc.twitter …    
    
    
    Check out @therealtracyt @fattrel showing love to some fans in DC. Blessed them with MMG Priorities… http://instagram.com/p/hzf16UMky9/     
    
    
    This is What happen when @KingKrucial walk outside or go to any public space pic.twitter.com/yKhN3V3FYS S/O to the King    
    
    
    @LiveNation is The Nation of the Music tours!    
    
    
    @Jayecane Is like when you go to the bathroom and says fuck no paper toiled you don't wanna hear apologizes only see the paper toiled    
    
    
    Most of the ppl wanna get something in exchange of nothing! This is a business no budget no services!    
    
    
    Respect over any Royalty!    
    
    
    http://www.instagram.com/souljaboy     
    
    
    Next on the line    
    
    
    @IamBCoolin turn up! birthday boss! Wish you a happy birthday you should jump in a flight to LA and turn the party on    
    
    
    Turn up Family @atmybest197    
    
    
    turn up boss @lilbthebasedgod check your dm    
    
    
    you better don't perform in any venue in NY cuz the police can catch you for hold Business property.    
    
    
    @SouljaKidSodmg turn up    
    
    
    Have a little surprise coming for you all in a bit…any guesses as to what it is?! #BritneySurprise    
    
    
    They told me I couldn't. So that's why I did. 💯    
    
    
    Our filial @MetroMusicDe will cover @Tiesto events at #Venezuela congratulations to @ErnestoGraterol for the Achievement! @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    I am really curious to know what's @britneyspears #BritneySurprise let see    
    
    
    @HIDEFINITE_ no hostile boss! I respect you! But I don't like to be tie to issues what are not on my hands!    
    
    
    @HIDEFINITE_ if our company offer u something then our company delivery if the client delivery the payment! Other business I can't says any    
    
    
    I much rather do business  with  1 person and make a killing then 2 work with a bunch and it's all a waste of time. I'm very selective    
    
    
    How Business work: a Buyer pay for something then the Seller delivery something! Any other way is waste of time! So get your ass out of here    
    
    
    Well reporting tweets! Sorry for the tweet but I hate liers and scam! And ppl who don't say the true! Is the worst    
    
    
    Well reporting tweets! Sorry for the tweet but I hate liers and scam! And ppl who don't say the true! Is the worst    
    
    
    @djaaanyc @Fabrizio need them beats    
    
    
    The worst thing happen when you dont think!    
    
    
    Any action always have a repercussion! Take the wrong way for sure will bring you to the wrong place!    
    
    
    Help? Help no one! Because when you help ppl you have high possibilities of get issues for something you was suppose to never do!    
    
    
    Mistakes are made by anyone, but correct mistakes is something only real and success people make!    
    
    
    Why do something wrong when you can do it right.    
    
    
    I was involve in politics, but I never see so many issues like in the music industry pic.twitter.com/rHYnP6Gmed    
    
    
    yall hoes worried about ig direct u need to worry about a job to get direct deposit ya bish    
    
    
    I have to says one thing in this business I made Good enemies but I also do good friends and I really respect Both! But support only the 2nd    
    
    
    Think smart so you no act stupid, BUT look stupid so you don't give no one any advantage    
    
    
    Some Artist does mess up their career. When they choose to roll with bad mind.. Now dey money stop coming. They want to call promoter back.    
    
    
    lol lol...gwan from here!!!!!    
    
    
    Some Artist does mess up their career. When they choose to roll with bad mind.. Now dey money stop coming. They want to call promoter back.    
    
    
    If you will made laundry be sure don't mix the white clothes with the color clothes! #justsaying    
    
    
    Some Artist does mess up their career. When they choose to roll with bad mind.. Now dey money stop coming. They want to call promoter back.    
    
    
    What?! I can't believe we just got invited to go on tour wit 2 chainz!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Waz Hatnin Man, I'm One Of @KingKrucial Artist. Just wanna Let You know, You Got A Good Dedicated Artist Behind You. He 1000%    
    
    
    I don't agree calling it Drama but is several ppl called it like that then is drama lol    
    
    
    Issue solved, drama ended! The one who do the mistake recognize the mistake and the one who got the drama (me) will stop the drama (1/2)    
    
    
    Watch out for all the fakes that say they can get you on LMT and or increase score or whatever.  It's all lies!!! Hit me if U have ?'s #LMT    
    
    
    So after a go and forward with @djaaanyc he explain to me there was a misunderstanding and I agree everyone can make mistakes! So we r fine    
    
    
    So after a go and forward with @djaaanyc he explain to me there was a misunderstanding and I agree everyone can make mistakes! So we r fine    
    
    
    So after a go and forward with @djaaanyc he explain to me there was a misunderstanding and I agree everyone can make mistakes! So we r fine    
    
    
    I just posted a #keek! http://www.keek.com/!QQl6dab     
    
    
    Turn up Big boss @IamBCoolin the family member! You should hit @KingKrucial    
    
    
    @souljaboy @JackieChain74 @Real_SODMG @Fabrizio @HOFABANG CHEERIOS COMING SOON !!!!!!! #BALLAHOLIKS101    
    
    
    Working with @WTFTheRealJoJo this should be epic! Turn up hope my advise help you a little    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    Fuck bs I speak real shit! If you don't do anything don't expect shit!    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    Business are made with MONEY and to get money you should do something @GageDC that's all those who complaint have made nothing    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    @Fabrizio he goin off on twitter ! Lmao, come deal wit a real artist 💯💯💯💯    
    
    
    Hey guys I am not charity if that's make you mad then I can't do anything! But if you can spend money and I can then we can make a deal    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    S/o the fakest! @Fabrizio he wants loyalty but has to give none! Don't get spoon fed BS like me & @DJAAANYC did! #SnakesInTheGrass    
    
    
    "@GageDC: @OfficialKushGod @KingKrucial @Fabrizio wowzers lmao" Lol... Yall Foolin. But Regardless I Wish everyone A Gucci Livin.    
    
    
    No your money, no your company and the one who made fault is the owner of the money cuz never "feed" you? Came on go grow :)    
    
    
    Fuck the BS but seriously can some one tell me how the fuck comes I have to put my money in someone hangs just because he want?    
    
    
    "@GageDC: @OfficialKushGod @KingKrucial @Fabrizio wowzers lmao" Lol... Yall Foolin. But Regardless I Wish everyone A Gucci Livin.    
    
    
    "@GageDC: @OfficialKushGod @KingKrucial @Fabrizio wowzers lmao" Lol... Yall Foolin. But Regardless I Wish everyone A Gucci Livin.    
    
    
    "@GageDC: @OfficialKushGod @KingKrucial @Fabrizio wowzers lmao" Lol... Yall Foolin. But Regardless I Wish everyone A Gucci Livin.    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Don't hate me to be how I am, hate yourself to don't do what you should do to be better than me! Cuz I don't care as far as I can "eat"    
    
    
    Don't hate me to be how I am, hate yourself to don't do what you should do to be better than me! Cuz I don't care as far as I can "eat"    
    
    
    How are u your Honorable Prince @Turki  i hope that we can talk about @Fabrizio proposal soon    
    
    
    In the real life no one care how biggest is your twitter account because what in real life count is how biggest is your bank account    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    I'm just Honest fuck yall    
    
    
    I'm just Honest fuck yall    
    
    
    Sorry but when I wake up I don't bake, same before sleep! I never bake because I prefer to count money than bake it!    
    
    
    GOT DAMNIT WESTERN UNION AND FUCKING PAYPAL...THE SOURCE OF MANY OF MY HEADACHES!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    GOT DAMNIT WESTERN UNION AND FUCKING PAYPAL...THE SOURCE OF MANY OF MY HEADACHES!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    That's my Boy @LilDope @KingKrucial @atmybest197 @AlexD_SODMG @VIPMusicRecords you need to come to the state but like yesterday    
    
    
    Brought* not bring "@Fabrizio: @OfficialKushGod @GageDC have you bring a penny to the table? What you bring to us? Let me know pls!"    
    
    
    Im confused you juss call me an asshole? "@Fabrizio: @Me by the way my name Fabrizio my friends call me Fabio! And my enemies asshole! :)"    
    
    
    I was boutta say whatd i do ? Lol "@Fabrizio: @TheRealJonnDoe no lol I says "my friends call me Fabio and my enemies call me asshole""    
    
    
    I was boutta say whatd i do ? Lol "@Fabrizio: @TheRealJonnDoe no lol I says "my friends call me Fabio and my enemies call me asshole""    
    
    
    @TheRealIceTre is hacked by @theswaggmantv @Support should check it    
    
    
    Hey guys @safety this account @TheRealIceTre GOT Hack pls take care of it!    
    
    
    @djaaanyc appreciate it boss man!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Sir can you please check your DM,need your help,will really appreciate.    
    
    
    @Fabrizio everything straight?    
    
    
    @Fabrizio everything straight?    
    
    
    @Fabrizio everything straight?    
    
    
    Y'all should bring this #Video to the top http://youtu.be/YfGSCIzRbnM  the #MoneyGang CEO @SouljaBoy need to see all your support    
    
    
    Turn up @EmersonWindy and @Lloydbanks is time to make it!    
    
    
    Less taxes, Less Government! More Freedom    
    
    
    Turning back to what I know what to do politic advise!    
    
    
    2014 Will be the year opening Fabrizio (trademark registered) Politic Advise! Getting a lobby lawyer will drive me crazy again    
    
    
    @Real_SODMG #BALLAHOLIK..SWAG STUPID..THATS JUST WHAT IM USED TO..MY MONEY OH SO LONG..GOT DAMN I BALL SO HARD... MAN I WAS BORN FOR THIS!!!    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you wanna scare those niggas out there boss    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you wanna scare those niggas out there boss    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you wanna scare those niggas out there boss    
    
    
    @djaaanyc next time!! will be back end of january!    
    
    
    What will all of us have for your bday @ATOworldwide    
    
    
    Don't talk better show with actions!    
    
    
    "@Fabrizio: What will all of us have for your bday @ATOworldwide" im pretty sure yall got me a bust down rolex    
    
    
    I don't care where you work McDonalds Pizza Hut Whataburger anywhere you work is cool. Making money while your in school is cool    
    
    
    Once again this music industry is full of Drama!    
    
    
    You know you have no respect when the Boss say Christmas Music on your show.. Shut up you bumm... Am the boss lol    
    
    
    @WhoKR flight here flight there is time to make music here and there and land in the stage any time the public want    
    
    
    @Sa_Guwap @Buck_LGR some ppl don't understand about Loyalty you give they everything and they give you 0 loyalty!    
    
    
    You can talk wherever you want about @souljaboy but fuck y'all because I will keep support his label and his music! Turn up #King Soulja    
    
    
    You can talk wherever you want about @souljaboy but fuck y'all because I will keep support his label and his music! Turn up #King Soulja    
    
    
    Like this tribute to @NelsonMandela http://youtu.be/8TY1jKuKbKM     
    
    
    Dreams come easy, just sleep and you will see it! Success come hard so stand up and put your hands to work    
    
    
    If we follow you RETWEET #GGM    
    
    
    Money is not an issue till the gov put his hand on it    
    
    
    lmfao godbless 🙏& shes in ap honors @ashxrai😂pic.twitter.com/8aBDfuFt8W    
    
    
    U know a person don't have shit when that person start trying to sale you his dreams! Normally who have a good idea sale projects not dreams    
    
    
    RT @MarussiaSpb: It will be forever today! @tiesto pic.twitter.com/0RDsv5PMG5    
    
    
    @DonaldLawrence Jesus    
    
    
    Let see how is go @Google @twitter @pheed @keek @Facebook @Pinterest Done where else should I need to get #Verified    
    
    
    Let see how is go @Google @twitter @pheed @keek @Facebook @Pinterest Done where else should I need to get #Verified    
    
    
    Let see how is go @Google @twitter @pheed @keek @Facebook @Pinterest Done where else should I need to get #Verified    
    
    
    @Fabrizio yo    
    
    
    Sorry ppl was having my mentions filter so can't see some of you guys! Now is solve    
    
    
    Turn up @vine go follow me over there    
    
    
    @Fabrizio yo    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up ?    
    
    
    I am always concern why every one ask me "what's up" in Spanish that's means "Que pasa" and only is ask when something happen lol    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up ?    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up ?    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up ?    
    
    
    @DanielGoddard whats Good Daniel    
    
    
    Salute me when you see me! my boy @kingKrucial on @VEVO the rest is just a talk http://www.vevo.com/artist/king-krucial …    
    
    
    @KingKrucial on @VEVO http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2xCNAUQYkH8 … growing one day at the time    
    
    
    mothefukas have me crazy with the deal when they was more close than me with they @souljaboy & @THEPIFFMAN lol pic.twitter.com/lGGF0uIuwH    
    
    
    @THEPIFFMAN that's not funny shit! But good you are with the king! Hahahahah You should told me that!    
    
    
    777    
    
    
    @GGMSTL fuck wit yall music #LETSWORK    
    
    
    Ppl is drama for this and for that! Stop the BS go make music and don't worry who use any name! Unless you have a #TradeMark    
    
    
    @SODMG Lets Meet Sinxe you klaimin you didnt hear about us You From Brooklyn I Am Too Whats Poppin Fuxk this twitter Shxt wassup    
    
    
    @GGMSTL fuck wit yall music #LETSWORK    
    
    
    @Fabrizio @RealLokitoBizz  y'all chill n let's get this money!! @RealLokitoBizz we fam and @Fabrizio we cool so it's all good!!! RT    
    
    
    @Fabrizio @RealLokitoBizz  y'all chill n let's get this money!! @RealLokitoBizz we fam and @Fabrizio we cool so it's all good!!! RT    
    
    
    Who is in my #Squad?    
    
    
    Who is in my #Squad?    
    
    
    Who is in my #Squad?    
    
    
    Who is in my #Squad?    
    
    
    The #VIPSquad get on our squad tomorrow and till next week Verses and Feat from @KingKrucial (inquires about videos are welcome to)    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up homie    
    
    
    @Fabrizio What's up homie    
    
    
    Follow the Team @SouljaBoy @M2thakSODMG @Fabrizio @Atmybest197 @AlexD_Sodmg    
    
    
    Turnt up with the CEO @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Follow My Lil Homie @MouseMyers    
    
    
    Yo @souljaboy i am an early bird to sleep and an early bird to wake up! Turn up    
    
    
        
    
    
    S/o to the CEO @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @TheRealMestizo turn up    
    
    
    @JASONLYRIC what's up! Turn up    
    
    
    @Fabrizio turn up family    
    
    
    Will hit any one from the #VIPSquad who RT or use our hashtag    
    
    
    Happy birthday to @ATOworldwide and @djwats01    
    
    
    No one on our team need your money! But there is rules to join and you need to understand make money cost money! so Turn Up    
    
    
    @JASONLYRIC what's up! Turn up    
    
    
    Nobody gives a fuck fabrizio    
    
    
    #Squad    
    
    
    @Fabrizio can you #submit music to you guys?    
    
    
    Nice to meet you @Incwell and my pleasure to have you on board @TheRealMestizo    
    
    
    Turn up @VIPMusicRecords @fabrizio 2014 we gonna take over    
    
    
    Turn up #VIPSquad    
    
    
    The one who tweet the name of my callertune will get a S/O mention the artist and the song    
    
    
    @Fabrizio come to DC and get some lasagna next time bruh! Peace 🙏    
    
    
    Turn up king @souljaboy    
    
    
    Turn up #VIPSquad and @SODMG family Loyal to my team loyal to the business!    
    
    
    I'm not a delivery guy! So stop sending DMs asking me to send music here and there! I will not push shit what is not part of our company!    
    
    
    overseas tour with the King of the rap! So far talking about #Canada - #UK - #Dubai and closing on #USA 2014 the Return and is not superman    
    
    
    I don't work with upcoming artist believing they will made it! I work with artist who already made it! Working in present not in future    
    
    
    Success don't come because of someone else actions! Success come because your actions! So stop the Bs and put your hands to work    
    
    
    U will make it! when you understand what cares is the money and the fans base the rest? Fuck the rest! Because fans and money is what matter    
    
    
    S/O to @theyoungdread we got big things coming    
    
    
    @LiveMixtapes turn up    
    
    
    Should no be a problem as far as u tell me the true but if I pay u for something u say u will do and u don't do it! Then u have an issue    
    
    
    People always saying I'm fake @Real_SODMG I'm not flexin @atmybest197 @Fabrizio @souljaboy rock with us pic.twitter.com/04hTqWdWLN    
    
    
    Planing with @richnice2 a complete tour for #canada #caribe let us put you on the route! Invest to success @VIPMusicRecords @SODMG    
    
    
    @champagnegang4l you should be more smart! Moves like the one you do today don't bring you no where! #Salute    
    
    
    For how long can u keep lying? U better fix the issue because if I have pay u and u don't delivery then we have an issue! #FabrizioQuote    
    
    
    @Fabrizio my Lil brother @StylezNY produces and has tracks for sale. Get at him with work    
    
    
    @champagnegang4l you should be more smart! Moves like the one you do today don't bring you no where! #Salute    
    
    
    @Fabrizio my Lil brother @StylezNY produces and has tracks for sale. Get at him with work    
    
    
    @champagnegang4l you should be more smart! Moves like the one you do today don't bring you no where! #Salute    
    
    
    @StylezNY did u hit @Fabrizio?    
    
    
    We @ 1,000 Views JUG - Nintendo Ark Unsigned  http://youtu.be/qyBnLSklG6w     
    
    
    @OfficialKushGod @IAmAceCasino @SouljaBoy @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @Fabrizio sir can you please check your DM,need to talk business.    
    
    
    Turn up @souljaboy    
    
    
    Is our turn of tour! Wake family @EshowsTv @VIPMusicRecords and @atmybest197    
    
    
    Turn up @KingKrucial this is not about how many this about goals achieve! @Vevo tour    
    
    
    Go check @KingKrucial @vevo Channel!    
    
    
    Turn up Family @KingKrucial @TheRealKingOpm @YoungKeiko @OfficialDubP and @OfficialKushGod | @atmybest197 @EShowsTV    
    
    
    @GGMSTL turn up the best group    
    
    
    Wake up family! Holidays are not just to enjoy are to work hard    
    
    
    @TheRealKingOpm turn up Strollin rich!    
    
    
    Tweet #StrollinRich hash tag and mention @TheRealKingOpm I will be sure @SODMG check you DMs!    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas @atmybest197 @souljaboy @KingKrucial @GGMSTL @TheRealKingOpm @OfficialDubP @richnice2    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas @OfficialKushGod @LilDope @DJMany @djaaanyc @moeager @Jayecane @DonaldLawrence @GageDC    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas @HOFABANG @TcLuchini @LarryMossBurg    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas  @Jack_Moore7 @flostorm @YoungKeiko    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas @IamBCoolin @IamRonnyLehmann @Standish913 @Astro_Ron    
    
    
    I wanna wish to every one of you a Merry Chritsmas @BIDJuventud @PartnersAmerica    
    
    
    Fuck yourself if you have a question about me! Ask me no one else! And don't claim you work with me unless you have a contract with me!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio - HAPPY HOLIDAYS FAMO!
2014 LETS GET IT HEAVY!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Small money bring more issues than huge money but both can bring issues!    
    
    
    A few days before 2013 end, so don't wait till the 2014 arrive, put your hands to work and get all the success you can    
    
    
    @Fabrizio call me    
    
    
    I think we will have an issue! Don't ask why because I already ask so many times and don't get a straight answer! Better say NO!    
    
    
    #phamily hope all of you enjoy the new year! Much love #pheeders @pheed http://pheed.com/p/43646321     
    
    
    Drake ft. Soulja Boy - We Made It: http://youtu.be/RmBB_3sFNkQ  via @youtube    
    
    
    We are ending the 2013 working on a Hip Hop tour and also a Rock tour #canada and #Caribbean    
    
    
    @DjKingAssassin turn up!    
    
    
    Go follow @indie500records today    
    
    
    @mosseri sup boss! Turn up I have a short question if you have a time hit back this New Yorker!    
    
    
    @adamconner yo! How come endorsements are not endorsements ? Salute    
    
    
    @jordan_harp salute Jordan have a couple of questions!    
    
    
    Just woke up to the bad news... my condolences and prays go out to @WakaFlockabsm family! R.I.P Kayo Redd    
    
    
    @IglooMediaBase what's good? Thanks for the follow    
    
    
    Quality Over Quantity    
    
    
    The beginning of the end @justinbieber documental make only 1,25 M in the first week!    
    
    
    We go to Canada on 2014 with @SODMG Major Artist and 4 of the best @VIPMusicRecords Artist! Turn Up #VIPGang 12 dates confirmed    
    
    
    We made it on 2013 while you try and wish to made it on 2014! Our year is today no tomorrow! #WeMadeIT and keep making it!    
    
    
    @souljaboy you made it every day! Keep doin it because is giving results #SODMG    
    
    
    Turn up @GGMSTL @KingKrucial @YoungKeiko @OfficialDubP @TheRealKingOpm @OfficialKushGod @IamBCoolin @LilDope @TheRealMestizo @Incwell    
    
    
    At #TheCompound with @deejaynogood @tonynuggs @DSchaeferNJ Tryna hit a buzzer beater! @MIHNJ @ReefieRiffe where you at?    
    
    
    listen to this 🔥🔥🔥
http://hnhh.co/mfzty  via @HotNewHipHop pic.twitter.com/bWQ6hRHWrh    
    
    
    At #TheCompound with @deejaynogood @tonynuggs @DSchaeferNJ Tryna hit a buzzer beater! @MIHNJ @ReefieRiffe where you at?    
    
    
    listen to this 🔥🔥🔥
http://hnhh.co/mfzty  via @HotNewHipHop pic.twitter.com/bWQ6hRHWrh    
    
    
    Go check my boss new hit https://soundcloud.com/octobersveryown/drake-we-made-it-freestyle/s-ASvqW … @souljaboy & @drake we made it    
    
    
    @Fabrizio what's up    
    
    
    @Fabrizio how's things going    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ThatChrisGore sup Chris    
    
    
    Now @Fabrizio dont want to respond to me??? Smh    
    
    
    Wish all the success possible before the 2013 end also wish to all Loyal Members of @Sodmg from @Souljaboy n @VIPMusicRecords a Success 2014    
    
    
    @OfficialDubP @KingKrucial @YoungKeiko @GGMSTL @LilDope @TheRealKingOpm @flostorm 2014 is no yet here but we Made it! Thanks to @Souljaboy    
    
    
    Special thanks to @Atmybest197 the members of @EshowsTV the @Real_SODMG team @M2thakSODMG @CEOMiamiMike and again @Souljaboy 2014 success    
    
    
    Salute to @FGottiAgnello #PrayToGotti because #NewYork still remember All the success #Respect    
    
    
    Special message to @djaaanyc and @OfficialKushGod the team! Happy end of 2013    
    
    
    New achievements and all the success to @DjKingAssassin #Turn up #VIPGang    
    
    
    Happy New Year @HANET_SA I don't forget about you! We have things to do! And I am ready to make it happen    
    
    
    Honorable Prince @Turki this 2014 is the year what we should use to make things move more faster than in the past!    
    
    
    Brother this 2014 is your year @HOFABANG and here you have not just a "worker" you have a friend who will help you in anything you need    
    
    
    Welcome 2014!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Happy New Year man! The best is yet to come!!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio happy new year bruh!!! See u on top is the new slang we say for 2014!!!salute!!!    
    
    
    BIG 2014 FOR YOU @Fabrizio    
    
    
    Wake up ppl! is a New Year and is time to start working, I will be Back on January 6! So be ready huge things are coming    
    
    
    Something I lean from 2013 is those who wanna grow and get success don't wanna give anything away! BUT those who have success invest more    
    
    
    Success is something you should build with hard work and investing! Success don't come just with wishes!    
    
    
    You can wish a Ferrari and be at the stages with @Eminem but if you don't invest in yourself then don't expect shit!    
    
    
    S/O to @indie500records    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/LHY5rgB46r    
    
    
    With talent artist engage fans but with branding artist improve they profit    
    
    
    @WORLDSTAR turn up    
    
    
    Yes is me @bradmantv I am removing the community manager on that account    
    
    
    Hit my DM @atmybest197    
    
    
    @EShowsTV why did you delete all of our DMs?  I am going to unfollow you and @Fabrizio until you guys figure stuff out and text professional    
    
    
    Get headache the first day of the year is not from God definitely    
    
    
    @EShowsTV why did you delete all of our DMs?  I am going to unfollow you and @Fabrizio until you guys figure stuff out and text professional    
    
    
    Fuck with me http://instagram.com/p/ioz3rAt9Ab/     
    
    
    Don't believe it unless you see it!  http://pheed.com/p/44083195     
    
    
    Go follow @SodmgRecords & @SODMG    
    
    
    Turn up @DjKingAssassin    
    
    
    Is time to make huge moves @HRyda    
    
    
    Is time to make huge moves @HRyda    
    
    
    2014 arrive with #Caribe tour and #Canada Tour #HipHop partnership to bring @SODMG and @VIPMusicRecords Artist overseas    
    
    
    15 Billionaires Who Were Once Dirt Poor http://www.businessinsider.com/billionaires-who-came-from-nothing-2013-12 …    
    
    
    @Metallica in the center of the world (Quito, Ecuador) http://www.metallica.com/tour/mar-18-2014-quito.asp …    
    
    
    Quito, #Ecuador Love for the #Rock pic.twitter.com/3lg9BeiEWB    
    
    
    Success is what everyone is looking for, but hard work is what everyone have lose!    
    
    
    Question: How an artist can grow up without money? Answer: working hard to get money    
    
    
    A success person look for the right place to invest, the loser type (who believe can be lucky) look 4 a place where can get something 4 FREE    
    
    
    Just woke up in Vegas about to turn my swag up the music is ready #2014 #WeMadeIt😎    
    
    
    @WakaFlockabsm CEO OF BRICK SQUAD MONOPOLY    
    
    
    Turn up #VIPGang this is @VIPMusicRecords team and @SODMG family    
    
    
    @BrandonKing4787 @Erik_Kynard everyone knows one! And #twitter have a lot of they :)    
    
    
    @DJRansomDollars the kid @djaaanyc tried playing my partner @Fabrizio as well. Lil nigga talking about the bread he got lol putting claims    
    
    
    @DJRansomDollars the kid @djaaanyc tried playing my partner @Fabrizio as well. Lil nigga talking about the bread he got lol putting claims    
    
    
    Street talking if I was on his skin I will not go out from home Street ppl talk different language take care of business in different way    
    
    
    I make same mistakes when I was a "kid" and cost me a lot of "pain" learn    
    
    
    Why ppl should start 2014 in the wrong way?    
    
    
    Get your Music Videos at @bet @MTV @VH1 @mtvjams @RevoltTV @mtvU @Much Vibe! Get a budget and hit us!    
    
    
    good morning. I'm on the road, #WorldTour14 has begun. pic.twitter.com/o4nUPNn9Cn    
    
    
    Get your Music Videos at @bet @MTV @VH1 @mtvjams @RevoltTV @mtvU @Much Vibe! Get a budget and hit us!    
    
    
    good morning. I'm on the road, #WorldTour14 has begun. pic.twitter.com/o4nUPNn9Cn    
    
    
    How different things are when you fight with some one who dominate the language!    
    
    
    @djaaanyc my nigga u starving!! Want me to post a screen shot of u begging me for $50 dollars 5hrs ago? @Fabrizio u see this phony shit?    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    Serious business don't speak to much, they ways work to much    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    What's up fam @THEPIFFMAN how that song is doing    
    
    
    Don't hate me to be how I am, be better than me or walk on the same way I am then claim wherever you want    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    @djaaanyc since when we have to pay gas to get on a bus? @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG @JohnBoy @OfficialKushGod @DJRansomDollars he a funny kid    
    
    
    @TrophyBoi_ARK sup fam    
    
    
    @TrophyBoi_ARK sup fam    
    
    
    Happy birthday #MichaelSchumacher forza campeon @InsideFerrari    
    
    
    It's an honor to have two Indy rock legends recording at The Pop Machine 
#Jon E. Gee #Mike Petrow.    
    
    
    I Just Landed In…! Jay Z Brings Out Rick Ross During “Magna Carta” Tour Stop (VIDEO) http://globalgrind.com/2014/01/03/jay-z-brings-out-rick-ross-miami-magna-carta-tour-video/ …    
    
    
    Let's work    
    
    
    Let's work    
    
    
    Let's work    
    
    
    @deBlasioNYC @BilldeBlasio I know the love is mutual (we don't like each other) but don't u think is time for 311 respond complaints quickly    
    
    
    Are you ready? #HipHop to take over    
    
    
    @Go hear @LilTunezS5MG new song http://youtu.be/82MCYngsSwE  big boss @djwats01 @OfficialKushGod @TheRealMestizo @DJRansomDollars @DjMixMasterG    
    
    
    Saddened by the news of Mazaradi's tragic passing my thoughts and prayers go out to his family and friends #smsaudio    
    
    
    @WORLDSTAR turn up    
    
    
    S/O to @WakaFlockabsm leader in the music industry! He is in the Billion Club!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio waddup    
    
    
    Working on get @kingkrucial @ATOworldwide who are my Boss's get a video production with @souljaboy and @WakaFlockabsm    
    
    
    My favorite group is come from @Misfit_Go and that's @souljaboy is watching now! And @WakaFlockabsm have to check those niggas are huge    
    
    
    Turn up @WakaFlockabsm is time to touch things and turn it in gold! From the streets the real empire!    
    
    
    From the streets no one stop @WakaFlockabsm now in the empire he is making gold anything he touch! @atmybest197 and I love your work    
    
    
    In 2014 the festival of #HipHop in #Finland will be crazy half of those who do #music and are from #NewYork will be there @EShowsTV deals    
    
    
    No mater what keep in eyes on the route is the only way to walk till the end!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio get at me bro gm    
    
    
    “@WakaFlockabsm: Time 2 kill the stage” killing stages from the first day!    
    
    
    #Ready4Reform is time to make the correct change! A change what will make our migration system more strong and push our economy to grow!    
    
    
    Immigrants started 28% of all new U.S. businesses in 2011 - http://slidesha.re/1akJgLf  #Ready4Reform    
    
    
    @RepJerryNadler I'm #Ready4Reform that strengthens our economy! Please act now on #immigration reform. @FWD_us #CIR    
    
    
    "@BBBimmigration: Breaking: @SpeakerBoehner say's he's still #Ready4Reform and trying to "get this thing done" http://www.politico.com/story/2013/11/john-boehner-immigration-99797.html …"    
    
    
    Say you're #Ready4Reform. Add your name today: http://OFA.BO/g86Jfa  #immigration    
    
    
    @Astro_Ron some one from other planet follow me! Thanks for that follow back    
    
    
    This is about money and is the only thing what you have to care about! The rest is just a he with no winners    
    
    
    @Astro_Ron some one from other planet follow me! Thanks for that follow back    
    
    
    NYC come SEE ME! 

11/25 

https://www.facebook.com/events/475522015900593/ …
RSVP?    
    
    
    NYC come SEE ME! 

11/25 

https://www.facebook.com/events/475522015900593/ …
RSVP?    
    
    
    S/O to the family @atmybest197 @EShowsTV @souljaboy @M2thakSODMG @KingKrucial @IamBCoolin @LilDope @moeager @OfficialKushGod @SAVAGEhaRD    
    
    
    S/o to my homie @AlexD_SODMG    
    
    
    Early mornin turnup! S/o @SouljaBoy @Fabrizio #SODMG    
    
    
    S/O to the family @Misfit_Go @OfficialDubP @ATOworldwide @DJAAANYC @sodmg    
    
    
    Loyalty over everything but if you don't respect my royalties then don't expect from me any loyalty    
    
    
    S/O to the family @TAZDMT    
    
    
    @souljaboy my family @EShowsTV @Fabrizio @AlexD_SODMG has everything in place 4u and the tour. What's good ?    
    
    
    I need to ask @souljaboy I am a #SODMG let's read his tweet hope the answer is a yes!    
    
    
    I met Ahmed and I dedicated the first Flashes of Thoughts Braille copy to him pic.twitter.com/egsdOA4TwY    
    
    
    I met Ahmed and I dedicated the first Flashes of Thoughts Braille copy to him pic.twitter.com/egsdOA4TwY    
    
    
    For real is not from God have to make line and wait!    
    
    
    @WellsFargo hey guys hit my dm!    
    
    
    @WellsFargo hey guys hit my dm!    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up money don't stop! Let make #HipHop    
    
    
    WOW. Identity thief tried charging $1000's to my credit card in India but @WellsFargo caught it just in time. Thanks for looking out, y'all!    
    
    
    Video: Soulja Boy - Turnin Up http://www.worldstarhiphop.com/videos/video.php?v=wshh5poSYOmHB94AB3o2 … #WSHH via @worldstar    
    
    
    booking info: @sodmg    
    
    
    To much BS when you handle small artist! I can't believe talking on my fucking back that why I keep it real only with my Fam    
    
    
    Turn up http://www.sodmgstore.com     
    
    
    FF @lemurwrangler @calestous @tmsruge @Astro_Nicole @astro_aggie @adllewellyn @GlobalVzla @OneYoungWorld @grameencl @FragileOasis    
    
    
    FF @lemurwrangler @calestous @tmsruge @Astro_Nicole @astro_aggie @adllewellyn @GlobalVzla @OneYoungWorld @grameencl @FragileOasis    
    
    
    S/O @WakaFlockabsm @Fabrizio @EShowsTV . Much love 2 all of ya    
    
    
    @Fabrizio turn up    
    
    
    Salute to my manager @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @YStijd turn up    
    
    
    "@souljaboy: go follow @sodmg and i will follow you back"
Holla @atmybest197 and @Fabrizio    
    
    
    @souljaboy check dm and iMessage    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello NY is infested of rats! Loyalty instead of freedom, loyalty before and after royalty #CodeOfKings    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello what's good my homie?  We all need to get up with my team @Fabrizio @EShowsTV asap    
    
    
    @HOFABANG the next deal is with our big boss @M2thakSODMG    
    
    
    Suck a RICH nigga DICK    
    
    
    Suck a RICH nigga DICK    
    
    
    Power and Money make Mobs quiet but Luxury things make mobster reals bosses!    
    
    
    S/O to @AniqZafar lets repet our favorite phrase "vamos a ver...." Salute My friend hope everything is good over there    
    
    
    S/O to @AniqZafar lets repet our favorite phrase "vamos a ver...." Salute My friend hope everything is good over there    
    
    
    Crank that!    
    
    
    pray that @Sodmg becomes the number 1 label and group in music    
    
    
    God bless    
    
    
    S/O to @souljaboy for allow us to work with the King of hip hop    
    
    
    @Qmachette your stuff is dope I hear you on your personal page! And till your put your people on the right I am with you 100% if u allow me    
    
    
    @Fabrizio Let's Talk Biz    
    
    
    Turn up @souljaboy you are making the difference and our partners love it    
    
    
    When @SouljaBoy talk About business be dont play! He Will kill this game on December 17! So be ready    
    
    
    Turn up time    
    
    
    I need clear this stuff before january! love hard work but this is for professionals lol    
    
    
    “@souljaboy: http://old.hulkshare.com/s26mb1m0r08w 😎” Turn Up! is time to get some money!    
    
    
    Turn up or get out from my route cuz I am walking to success! Troubles only make me more stronger! #Fam    
    
    
    S/O to @WarithNiallah    
    
    
    Turn up! Time to build the empire @souljaboy let's get the new album to the top ten @atmybest197 wake up    
    
    
    Working with large clients! my brother @atmybest197 and @EshowsTV are or priority! But now we are supporting @Souljaboy and the @SODMG Fam    
    
    
    Drooling> Life-size replica of Mercedes supercar in @Sony #GT6 shown at the @LAAutoShow http://cnnmon.ie/17VnM7l  pic.twitter.com/fxkTv3Wvpv    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG    
    
    
    http://www.amazon.com/Jab-Right-Hook-Story-Social/dp/006227306X/ …
#rightHook
#enoughsaid    
    
    
    http://Facebook.com/dabeezy1     
    
    
    find a good reason to hit my DM do it, if not then don't waste your time! If you don't have a clear goal then I can't make anything about    
    
    
    Go follow @REAL_SODMG is time for the family is time for Hip Hop @SODMG #SOD #MoneyGang    
    
    
    This family have only boss's @Souljaboy @atmybest197 @M2thakSODMG and those name have is fire on they music    
    
    
    @ImYoungChizz sup boss    
    
    
    Wake is time to work!    
    
    
    Today is UnFollow day so cleaning my TL don't get offended if you go out but I only Fuck with loyal niggas the rest go to the trash    
    
    
    Fabrizio!!! Talk to me!! What's good #SODMG RT @Real_SODMG: “@Fabrizio: @ImYoungChizz sup boss” turn up boss    
    
    
    @Interscope turn up we have things I will like to discuss    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    The music industry is not easy! Is not sweet is hard as hell so let's have a real talk and get ready to get the money    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    Stop the Bs if my tweets are to offensive for you if because you love the lies from other people! I am here to tell you the fucking true    
    
    
    My boy @DJAAANYC will be busy this weekend at @stage48nyc    
    
    
    Ppl is about the BS between one artist instead to be about the own shit and get fire music! Keep eyes in your shit not about others shit    
    
    
    @deejaynogood turn up    
    
    
    Ppl is about the BS between one artist instead to be about the own shit and get fire music! Keep eyes in your shit not about others shit    
    
    
    @CEOFlameGotti have his mouthful of true    
    
    
    @FGottiAgnello turn up big boss    
    
    
    @Jowynalex I don't hate to!    
    
    
    Got you @souljaboy    
    
    
    Don't get upset cuz i don't reply quickly but i have severals things to do related to Money we are making till you are looking how to get it    
    
    
    Is funny when a no one ask me "you know who I am?" And I say no I don't know!    
    
    
    Nobody likes a RAT LoL pic.twitter.com/GFTPX3oaE1    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    Where is every one?    
    
    
    @KingKrucial go Follow @richnice2    
    
    
    Turn up this is to take over    
    
    
    This business is for those who are ready to take success from the back or from any other place they can!    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving  to every one in the USA! S/O to the family @SouljaBoy @AtMyBest197 @Real_SODMG @AlexD_SODMG @HT @DJAAANYC @kingkrucial    
    
    
    salute and happy thanksgiving @OfficialDubP @ATOworldwide @GGMSTL @moeager @DonaldLawrence    
    
    
    Happy ThanksGiving @WakaFlockabsm    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to the bitch @NaquanReese my respect to the next idol    
    
    
    Salute to @LilDope @Jack_Moore7 @OfficialKushGod @flostorm @YoungKeiko happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    @IamRonnyLehmann turn up big boss    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to my brothers @HypeSir and @Standish913    
    
    
    Happy holidays @TheRealKingOpm hope we can see you soon    
    
    
    Turn up @Sodmg let's get the world down till our feet @souljaboy    
    
    
    Turn up @IamBCoolin happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy Turkey Day @SODMG @souljaboy @Fabrizio ♻️    
    
    
    @PvTruest @SODMG @souljaboy dope dope    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion sup    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion happy thanksgiving Preston thanks for the #FollowBack much respect    
    
    
    Much respect to @WarithNiallah happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving @HOFABANG @THEPIFFMAN    
    
    
    Money make sense but power make things easy! Happy Thanksgiving @ILLUMINATIAM    
    
    
    Fuck double F! I got in shot with that Escobar email came on big boss don't play like that    
    
    
    Happy thanksgiving to the bitch @NaquanReese my respect to the next idol    
    
    
    @cib110 info@fabrizzio.it    
    
    
    Got notice #BitCoins cost now is 1133 $$$$ holly shit a few months ago cost just 150 how many do you have?    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    Is time to come and make deals are you ready for?    
    
    
    I am not looking for more artist, I am already working with #Kings S/O to those who are in our #Family roster    
    
    
    I am loyal to those who stand up with me when everything looks bad, and I respect those who are there to do business when things looks good    
    
    
    @ImYoungChizz turn up man! Is time to make things happen    
    
    
    Turn up @KingKrucial and congratulations for the deal with @VEVO now is time to make 1M of sales on @iTunes    
    
    
    Viva Las Mexico pic.twitter.com/b53m47DMNT    
    
    
    Bitch I am not here to waste my time if you don't have time for wait till I end real deals then go and fuck yourself    
    
    
    @Lloydbanks turn up! How was the show in #Dubai?    
    
    
    @WakaFlockabsm fuck that Waka app is fucking any other penny artist app!    
    
    
    Download now!!!!! http://get.wakaville.com  RT pic.twitter.com/BMIUOtEPn4    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    Turn up @DJMany @IAmShawtyboy is time to make #VIPRecords    
    
    
    Our label is called VIP Music Records are you ready?    
    
    
    After crazy days! The people return to the normal activity    
    
    
    I done ran up the moneyyy    
    
    
    @BIDJuventud email me gary at Vaynermedia com    
    
    
    This week we will start closing deals and officially signing artist to VIP Music Records    
    
    
    @PrestonMillion thanks for the favorite! We decide to move and put the label out so turn up let's discuss    
    
    
    time to work we will made a tour with @DailyLoud including @af_rome @whokr and @kingkrucial hope @WakaFlockabsm allow us to go up with him    
    
    
    You do music? Yes, but your last hit was when I was 21    
    
    
    Thanks for the media support @WarithNiallah    
    
    
    No, no! is not I am not in is you are out! So don't expect this game be the same after we make this move    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    So Sleepy.    
    
    
    Wake up @kingkrucial    
    
    
    You ever see numbers like this? pic.twitter.com/K03WNk54I8    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    @Qmachette s/o he stand up when the bitches run away    
    
    
    Our label will invest do be ready! But don't need you begging at me! I need you making money cuz is what matter for me    
    
    
    @GageDC this is my Brother and is part of my family so fuck this who don't hola at Gage    
    
    
    Our label will invest do be ready! But don't need you begging at me! I need you making money cuz is what matter for me    
    
    
    @HOFABANG you are my target! shit you need to be under our Label!    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    HTF if you don't have money as me, will you ever teach me how to make more money? I only fuck with my family and you hear who they are    
    
    
    @PvTruest I am a #VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    Count your penny's cuz I will see which is the weight of the suitcase where I put a few bills    
    
    
    I swear if you don't follow @GageDC & @antkingsmith there's NO real $hxt on your TL. Lol    
    
    
    whats good @stachemedia #REDSony    
    
    
    Our roster will be cut in up to 75% Sorry guys But not money means not part of the DON Family    
    
    
    NEW VIDEO: @Eminem #RAPGOD http://intersco.pe/Il1QqB     
    
    
    I am not #Rich I am just a crazy entrepreneur who make money building his own dreams    
    
    
    11:11 - Make A Wish.... #LovingLife    
    
    
    Those who are looking for a pay check from our label need to understand our pay days are after you show us real numbers    
    
    
    No today!    
    
    
    Check our next week my G on @MTV and @VH1 S/O to @KingKrucial    
    
    
    No I am not part of any other Family than my own empire family so #TurnUp    
    
    
    I know you are fake when your best answer is an excuse    
    
    
    @richnice2 turn up    
    
    
    Turn @THEPIFFMAN    
    
    
    Just landed in Mexico turn up at the show tonight    
    
    
    #1017 #MentionMe    
    
    
    #1017 #MentionMe    
    
    
    @gucci1017 follow back is time to take overseas back    
    
    
    http://www.datpiff.com/Soulja-Boy-The-King-mixtape.555926.html …    
    
    
    My account have only six 0 afters positive numbers what about yours?    
    
    
    My account have only six 0 afters positive numbers what about yours?    
    
    
    watching college football more often after that half i just seen, never watched college football before until today lol    
    
    
    watching college football more often after that half i just seen, never watched college football before until today lol    
    
    
    Go follow our best DJ @DJAAANYC    
    
    
    @BrooklynNets holly shit you still not following me back what you wait for?    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/jfChK1keaR    
    
    
    Turn up @badboyrecords @anthonysabadboy    
    
    
    Wake body @yungyungpallo    
    
    
    @HipHopTXL Turn up    
    
    
    I hear you @yungyungpallo i think we should talk    
    
    
    Money make noise    
    
    
    @Real_SODMG what it do #TurnUp    
    
    
    R.I.P @RealPaulWalker    
    
    
    Why Do People Feel Guilty When You Mention Anything.    
    
    
    Again our label is called VIP Music Records and our live TV platform is @EShowsTV    
    
    
    Why Do People Feel Guilty When You Mention Anything.    
    
    
    if I offer you a deal will you take it?    
    
    
    #NP Swagga On A Million - Young Chizz #SundayAfternoonShow with @WaleOzolua    
    
    
    Money matters, numbers matters so if you are no making numbers with your music don't expect a deal from a label    
    
    
    Labels don't eat words like "I am the next idol" or "I have the next hit" they believe in "I am selling xxxxxx on @itunes" #GetYourDeal    
    
    
    Take me 5 years make 1 million, and I am not proud of it because others make it in a month! So I keep working    
    
    
    People who focus on the "label deal" are complete wrong! They have to focus on the "fans deal" what will make the label dream real    
    
    
    Loyalty make royalties! Is not in any other way    
    
    
    Talking with @Facebook about a large Campaign for the Label, honestly the network of Facebook is more complicate to handle    
    
    
    I really love my Picture with @Iron_Man pic.twitter.com/8kPWtpTdLo    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/kf3kH042G7    
    
    
    Love my Cowboy hat pic.twitter.com/S3SMzyJOW9    
    
    
    Just finished a long day or interviews & photo shoots. Now time for another meeting then sound check at @CavalliClubDxb. #Dubai    
    
    
    I am not like any of those who have only money on they head because I have the money in my packages and the business in my head    
    
    
    S/o to @VVIPTV go check they webpage    
    
    
    #Dubai    
    
    
    Wake up #America turn up #UK S/O #Dubai    
    
    
    @Fabrizio  congrats on your success wit ur new label situation.. Meet y'all at the top!! RNS    
    
    
    Wake up #America turn up #UK S/O #Dubai    
    
    
    December 5    
    
    
    @souljaboy @HookStarz @Tyga @Fabrizio  I think its time for another track... #ballaholiks101 WE GET IT IN..@TRAPAHOLICS PROJECT MEDUSA 1831    
    
    
    Go Follow @_itsXING    
    
    
    Before sending me an e-mail or a #Twitter DM ask yourself what's the to contact me or how can I help so we don't waste time    
    
    
    Dope article. Send this to New Line cinema so they can give us the money we need to do LAST FRIDAY. http://globalgrind.com/2013/11/29/life-lessons-you-can-learn-from-the-movie-friday-list-gif/?utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    @macklemore only have 20 dollars on my package don't apply to my life but is one of my favorite songs    
    
    
    if you share a video be sure 10k or more ppl view it! Because your music can be good but no one care about it! Ppl care about $$(Numbers)$$    
    
    
    The only people we who I work are on my webpage and then my partner! So don't tie me to the past cu I live in the future    
    
    
    @DJAAANYC @QUINTINOO salute family    
    
    
    Live on @WKRBradio 90.3FM get it now on http://Soundcloud.com/djaaa  pic.twitter.com/i7MZ36XzyS    
    
    
    Dirty true is you are not playing at all #NewYork is my town!    
    
    
    S/o The Homie @Fabrizio #Salute #GGM #SODMG    
    
    
    Dope article. Send this to New Line cinema so they can give us the money we need to do LAST FRIDAY. http://globalgrind.com/2013/11/29/life-lessons-you-can-learn-from-the-movie-friday-list-gif/?utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    If you lose my respect then you lose everything!    
    
    
    #MMG MUSIC: @TheRealTracyT ft @MeekMill "16" http://bit.ly/TracyTMeek16     
    
    
    My team own things what are yours? May in your dreams :)    
    
    
    S/O to @PrestonMillion tour in motion! And hands ready to work    
    
    
    I am part of the #MDT Million Dollar Team we don't join Money Team! Because everyone have money but just a couple have millions    
    
    
    December 5    
    
    
    "@Fabrizio: December 5" MY BIRTHDAY. #PRAY2GOTTI    
    
    
    don't ask me to hit you up, because my fists are pure gold and can break jaws #MDT (Million Dollar Team)    
    
    
    Turn up @Tmobile Making deals    
    
    
    Salute to @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    December 5….    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    @richnice2 go follow @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    Don't wake my twitter account up unless you're cutting me a check $$$$ @VIPMusicRecords do you see this shit @DJSONYT @ATOworldwide lmao    
    
    
    @TuneCore hit my DM have some questions    
    
    
    Go check my G @jalanbravo https://soundcloud.com/bravomuzikgroup/for-the-moment-j-bravo-ft/s-iwpB3 …    
    
    
    El sábado estabamos en el semáforo con fabri y tres chicas como 49 veces miraron ehhh para mi que le miraron a @fabrizio    
    
    
    Go check is http://www.sodmggang.com  is #CyberMonday @SouljaBoy have special discounts out there    
    
    
    following everyone back today that rt this and need a follow that didnt get one yet. retweet this    
    
    
    Ready or not December 5 is the #Day    
    
    
    I don't need nothing else but I love to have always more than I actually have    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG is time to make a show with @Tyga not kiding    
    
    
    Hold on @Drake you need to hit me back so we can get @KingKrucial in    
    
    
    @souljaboy the big boss @HOFABANG will hit you again to make another collaboration at this time with @Tyga for the Medusa project    
    
    
    Turn up @HOFABANG is time to make a show with @Tyga not kiding    
    
    
    S/O to @SouljaBOy and his label #SODMG was a Take over on Mexico    
    
    
    You made it...    
    
    
    @Souljaboy Made it!    
    
    
    @souljaboy Waddup nigga 💯    
    
    
    Turn up    
    
    
    S/O to @EmersonWindy    
    
    
    “@souljaboy: Turn up” we are up    
    
    
    I was bed ridden yesterday, had the highest fever in history RT @VIPMusicRecords: @ImYoungChizz wake up boss    
    
    
    Our label have Rep. In Canada, USA, Europe and Latin American! And we are looking for indie artists    
    
    
    @Jayecane I hate ppl who try to compare me    
    
    
    Say no more! pic.twitter.com/gIw4gF5ZMs    
    
    
    @CEOMiamiMike appreciate the info, @AtMybest197 my partner will love to discuss about meeting with our parents in Dubai    
    
    
    Things what you should know about @CEOMiamiMike http://www.myfoxmemphis.com/video?autoStart=true&topVideoCatNo=default&clipId=9564211 … #Support #NGO @Bidjuventud    
    
    
    December 5 is the day    
    
    
    Habemus new phone @SamsungMobile Galaxy Note 3 hit my DM so I can have your phone! Thanks @TMobileHelp    
    
    
    New phone @SamsungMobile Galaxy Note 3 is for auto defense (means huge) but if you wanna be in my contact list DM your number and name    
    
    
    @HOFABANG @laflamethrower1 i AM Also near to get in talk with @EmersonWindy    
    
    
    Waste of time… they don't active it yet    
    
    
    Whats up @Souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    Get he best Distribution Package working with @SouljaBoy and @Real_Sodmg    
    
    
    Let's keep the game clear! And you know what I mean!    
    
    
    SMH… quiet on home waiting on some money get move and get calls with threats is the most funny shit    
    
    
    From this moment we are not in good standing with any of you… and you know who i refer to…. so keep your ass far from me    
    
    
    From this moment we are not in good standing with any of you… and you know who i refer to…. so keep your ass far from me    
    
    
    @DJAAANYC whATS GOOD    
    
    
    Turn up #Dubai @HOFABANG Next video is on the land of the #kings    
    
    
    ethic is something what make the difference between a Good business and a wrong business….    
    
    
    Check Out @maravimusic & @LALovetheboss  - Stuntin Hard http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XXn3EI5xTzw … #RT #BreakoutArtist    
    
    
    Hope after all of this go and come everything work like is suppose...    
    
    
    Much love to everyone    
    
    
    @atmybest197 today!    
    
    
    @Fabrizio where are u at ? People keep hollering at me 4u. Get at me asap    
    
    
    Got the Dm Boss @WakaFlockabsm will setup a call conference this week with the point person (Brick) and my partner @atmybest197    
    
    
    S/o to our family member @TheRealKingOpm    
    
    
    Ministers discussed plenty of ideas on increasing teacher competence, upgrading teaching methods, &enhancing student stkills #uaebrainstorm    
    
    
    “@JohnBoy: Call Soulja Boy 716-249-9040” that's not his phone number    
    
    
    @souljaboy turn up    
    
    
    @JohnBoy ahhhh    
    
    
    Turn up #VIPGang #MDT (Million Dollar Team)    
    
    
    Turn up @atmybest197    
    
    
    @RealDJTripleA THEY ARE GOOD @TDBank_US    
    
    
    From now rare will buy a @hp they @HPSupport is a mess! I will prefer to keep a #Mac    
    
    
    @Fabrizio wats ur email?    
    
    
    OMW! Long day    
    
    
    My respect to @MichelleObama a woman with character!    
    
    
    @BarackObama show to the world, what a real man have to do! He respect @MichelleObama decisions! where captain directs, no sailor directs    
    
    
    Success never come alone or without hard work! I you are looking success be ready to walk in the hard way    
    
    
    #Music    
    
    
    S/O to @DonaldLawrence for all the inspirational material he always post! #KeepItReal and from the soul    
    
    
    A leader find solutions a loser the problems! Focus in what success means    
    
    
    Dreams are only dreams till the moment you put your hands to build things!    
    
    
    The same way a success man use can to achieve his goals can make other person fall in mistakes    
    
    
    Love what you do to build what you want!    
    
    
    Big S/O to @YoungKeiko keep the work hard! No one can stop you in your goals! #HipHop with soul    
    
    
    Coming some #Selfmade @GGMSTL pic.twitter.com/BRFfhq84GC    
    
    
    God bless ur steps, and help u to achieve ur goals! But don't forget to be thankful for anything he give or take from u because he knows    
    
    
    The streets ain't for everybody... that's why they made sidewalks.... Use them #bighomieFlock    
    
    
    The streets ain't for everybody... that's why they made sidewalks.... Use them #bighomieFlock    
    
    
    Don't tell me you have the key to make money if you can't make money yourself!    
    
    
    Turn up @gucci1017 to much tweets that music need a good place to be performed! Get a my family!    
    
    
    World Premiere: @Gucci1017 Ft. @MigosATL - Jackie Chan [Prod. By @ZaytovenBeatz] S/O @djplugg http://trapsntrunks.com/2013/12/11/gucci-mane-ft-migos-jackie-chan-prod-zaytoven/#.UqkcebReqdc.twitter …    
    
    
    Check out @therealtracyt @fattrel showing love to some fans in DC. Blessed them with MMG Priorities… http://instagram.com/p/hzf16UMky9/     
    
    
    This is What happen when @KingKrucial walk outside or go to any public space pic.twitter.com/yKhN3V3FYS S/O to the King    
    
    
    @LiveNation is The Nation of the Music tours!    
    
    
    @Jayecane Is like when you go to the bathroom and says fuck no paper toiled you don't wanna hear apologizes only see the paper toiled    
    
    
    Most of the ppl wanna get something in exchange of nothing! This is a business no budget no services!    
    
    
    Respect over any Royalty!    
    
    
    http://www.instagram.com/souljaboy     
    
    
    Next on the line    
    
    
    @IamBCoolin turn up! birthday boss! Wish you a happy birthday you should jump in a flight to LA and turn the party on    
    
    
    Turn up Family @atmybest197    
    
    
    turn up boss @lilbthebasedgod check your dm    
    
    
    you better don't perform in any venue in NY cuz the police can catch you for hold Business property.    
    
    
    @SouljaKidSodmg turn up    
    
    
    Have a little surprise coming for you all in a bit…any guesses as to what it is?! #BritneySurprise    
    
    
    They told me I couldn't. So that's why I did. 💯    
    
    
    Our filial @MetroMusicDe will cover @Tiesto events at #Venezuela congratulations to @ErnestoGraterol for the Achievement! @VIPMusicRecords    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    What's popping @Fabrizio @VIPMusicRecords with the drama?    
    
    
    