$$: Information Arbitrage - Sound thinking for unsound times http://ow.ly/5Zggq    
    
    
    meet the guy @cdixon @asenkut @infoarbitrage @firstround @AOLVentures backed: Ari Jacoby, @solvemediainc @venturestudio http://bit.ly/pSr5G0    
    
    
    ff# @jessicalawrence @randygiusto @UNYstartups @solvemedia @arijacoby @tzmartin @jen_mcfadden @vivenkat @jalak @tweet_massimo @trikro    
    
    
    Meet the guy @cdixon @asenkut @infoarbitrage @firstround & @AOLVentures all backed! @AriJacoby @SolveMedia http://bit.ly/pSr5G0 on...    
    
    
    From Friday: Entrepreneur Survival Guide: Some Motivation, Courtesy of Uncle Nikolai:  http://ow.ly/63pSJ #25thHour #survive    
    
    
    ff# @lsanza @vikvenkat @jdorkin @ngavronsky @cliffpavlovic @kunalchaudhari @amandahesser @john_frankel @stefan_ne @shanereiser @adamostrow    
    
    
    Chegg Chugging Along: Unleashes Digital Textbook Rentals, Aims To Be 'LinkedIn For College Students' http://ow.ly/681GK    
    
    
    Bubble-heads- have a read :)  Marc Andreessen on Why Software Is Eating the World - WSJ.com http://ow.ly/68gHK    
    
    
    this guy & Andreessen should hang-out, similar world view: Irving Kahn 105-Year-Old Banker: Economic Downturn Just a Blip http://ow.ly/68hBw    
    
    
    Kabooommmm: Skype acquires GroupMe http://ow.ly/68RTN    
    
    
    Invest in People - #GroupMe http://ow.ly/68WkM by @davetisch    
    
    
    Must read! RT @davidcohen: New on my blog: "The Mentor Manifesto" http://www.davidgcohen.com/2011/08/28/the-mentor-manifesto/ …    
    
    
    Michael Arrington launching venture fund - The Term Sheet: Fortune's deals blog Term Sheet http://ow.ly/6jdS4    
    
    
    What do you need? | The Monster In Your Head http://ow.ly/6lWHD    
    
    
    BOOM.... General Assembly Gets Funding From Yuri Milner and Jeff Bezos | Betabeat — News, gossip and intel from Silicon Alley 2.0....    
    
    
    $$$ must read for entrepreneurs RT @marksbirch: The Trouble with Non-Investor Investors | Strong Opinions @marksbirch http://bch.me/nVMCP8     
    
    
    Question: does anyone know how solid the .ly domains are given all the turmoil in Libya? I heard they are actually Libya's "country code"    
    
    
    good one from @wadhwa What Spain could learn from a former colony - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/6xML3 #Espana    
    
    
    check out my buddy @porlando 's course on startups @skillshare Startups Unplugged -- Structure for your Startup  http://ow.ly/6DTb0    
    
    
    Neil Capel, CEO of @Sailthru on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/oVvwIv  @neilcapel to fledgling entrepreneurs: you need to "go full force"    
    
    
    "You need to go full force" says @NeilCapel CEO of @sailthru to entrepreneurs on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/oVvwIv     
    
    
    ff# @to2 @fabricegrinda @mashinsky @vivsharma @unystartups @jrizk33 @venturestudio @startupgenome @warbyparker @stephenfleming @frankjpinto    
    
    
    ff# @amitklein @shanesnow @shanereiser @joefernandez @ceonyc @zsims @zamland @paigecraig    
    
    
    ff# @mevans1 @therunthrough @learnvest @NeilCapel @bradsvrluga @stacyspikes @adamostrow @davetisch @echo_nyc @ffventure @bhargreaves    
    
    
    Great piece guys! RT @nickseguin: it takes a village to raise a #startup - piece by @mmcedward, @MarcNager and I http://huff.to/qwh2WS     
    
    
    Well said  RT @bsiscovick RT @vacanti If starting a co, email monthly updates to big list of friends/mentors w recent progress, help needed    
    
    
    "share your ideas" RT @davidblerner @venturestudio : Ari Rabban, CEO of http://Phone.com  http://bit.ly/oZA7Db     
    
    
    ff# @echo_nyc @annaivey @svenningsen @vcdeallawyer @to2 @ganeumann @nickseguin @startuppro @bfeld @markloranger @bfeld @stephenfleming    
    
    
    Andreessen Horowitz Joining in Y Combinator Start Fund - Kara Swisher - News - AllThingsD http://ow.ly/6YijD     
    
    
    Has anyone seen the documentary "Something Ventured" yet? #startups #entrepreneurship    
    
    
    the next profession to be displaced: publishers: Amazon Rewrites the Rules of Book Publishing - http://NYTimes.com  http://ow.ly/6Z3X7     
    
    
    AmEx as VC!? Leads $12 Million Round In Clickable, Which Wants To “Become The AdWords Of Social” | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/70h8L     
    
    
    13 Startups Facebook Acqui-Hired For Millions Of Dollars http://ow.ly/70kzc     
    
    
    TechStars’ second New York class shines in their debut — Tech News and Analysis http://ow.ly/71zdY     
    
    
    wow: RT @marksbirch: Talking to the Homeless & the Theatre of Everyday Life by @ScottBrit http://bch.me/q2S3Qs  - Scott is good people    
    
    
    POST: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know to Succeed (3) Know Something! http://bit.ly/pvCbOE  @startupamerica    
    
    
    @scottbrit agree!    
    
    
    @pkedrosky i remember when Nicklaus last won the Masters and everyone bought that oversized putter!    
    
    
    IronMike getting into tech! RT @miketyson: Sat w/ @dickc & @john today. These guys are a part of building future & I want to be part of it.    
    
    
    Interview: @venturestudio w/ @john_frankel founding partner of @ffventure on working w/great entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/tvj4Dd     
    
    
    agree RT @joefernandez: This is amazing - The Measured Life: What's Your Klout Score? http://on.wsj.com/rtoomq     
    
    
    Startup Lessons from David Cohen and the TechStars | Blog | Daily Dose | http://Entrepreneur.com  http://ow.ly/79Bei     
    
    
    soon kicking off evening convo w/ @infoarbitrage cc: @jrizk333 @columbiavc @dwhittemore who's joining? @iaventures + CVC= $$    
    
    
    @infoarbitrage is dropping knowledge $$ RT @teddotcom: Great CVC talk tonight with @davidblerner and @infoarbitrage. Hats off to @jrizk333    
    
    
    good read! RT @sarahprevette: What I learned from raising venture capital http://awe.sm/5Y0RD     
    
    
    want to learn about product mgmt? my good pal @dwhittemore teaching Product Management for Startups on Skillshare:  http://ow.ly/7bjia     
    
    
    Kaboom: Codecademy Raises $2.5 Million To Teach You How To Code | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7bs3z     
    
    
    congrats guys RT @zsims: Ryan and I are thrilled to announce the next steps for @Codecademy - http://blog.codecademy.com/codecademyaddi …    
    
    
    Fortune Finance just picked up my piece on: Are super-angels extinct? http://bit.ly/gla8Jd    
    
    
    powerful stuff: A Sister’s Eulogy for Steve Jobs - http://NYTimes.com  http://ow.ly/7dw51     
    
    
    congrats to STELLAService team: Raising $5 Million to Keep You In the Know: STELLAService blog http://ow.ly/7n3Ng     
    
    
    kaboom: "Calling Bullshit On The Series A Crunch" | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7oDfF     
    
    
    Fascinating approach! RT @TheNickFrost: 1% Of Nothing Launches To Get Startups Donating Equity http://sul.st/rZmZfD     
    
    
    Must Read: The Real Cost of Patent Trolls http://ow.ly/7tTbF  courtesy @bfeld    
    
    
    The Rise Of The Health Startup? A Peek At The 13 Companies In Rock Health’s Inaugural Batch | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7tTEL     
    
    
    On getting product-market fit: My talk w/ @sachinkamdar CEO of @parsely on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/t4f0az  cc: @montalenti    
    
    
    @iaventures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJiz cc @infoarbitrage @bsiscovick who's next?    
    
    
    Ohio-based @NCTVentures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJtI congrats! who's next?    
    
    
    5am ventures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJx5 who is next? cc @shanesnow @shanereiser    
    
    
    next time you think you're real busy, read this: Jack Dorsey's Twitter & Square Work Schedule - http://ow.ly/7zmi7     
    
    
    good piece on how: Accelerators Groom Technology Ventures for Success | PBS NewsHour | Nov. 22, 2011 | PBS http://ow.ly/7DiKn     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!!    
    
    
    here comes 3D printing: The printed world | The Economist http://ow.ly/7Gkrq     
    
    
    congrats @warbyparker team: Go West, Young Men: style file: daily fashion, party, and model news http://ow.ly/7Gz9f     
    
    
    Leonsis, Case found $450 million fund to aid Washington area start-up firms - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/7Lgi1     
    
    
    big news! Spotify Launches New App Platform, Announces Move to NY - http://NYConvergence.com  http://ow.ly/7LEUh     
    
    
    big news RT @mashable: Facebook to Open New York Engineering Office - http://on.mash.to/tX3EMe     
    
    
    Startup Incubator WeWork Labs Gets A New 75,000 Square Foot Office In NYC http://ow.ly/7MSIS     
    
    
    Who is right? Interesting discussion: The case for old entrepreneurs - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/7MSQs     
    
    
    Wow! Bullseye! RT @abarrera Beware of those who say they help entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/dGpKXs <-- Ready, steady, FLAME!!    
    
    
    @brian_sirkia agree!    
    
    
    ff# @mterrim @justbobbibrown @toryburch  incredible and inspiring event for the foundation- congrats- what a great mission!    
    
    
    @toryburch @justbobbibrown @KendraBracken @aliwing @AlicesTeaCup @JCrew_Insider it was a blast, thanks!    
    
    
    good post from @bikenyc (Stuart Ellman): Do Not Cut Off Your Colleagues - RRE Ventures http://ow.ly/7VoFY     
    
    
    My TedX talk: "Why Wait 'Til You Graduate?" http://lnkd.in/wSychU     
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/7tDD8f     
    
    
    great for NYC... would love to learn REAL story tho! Silicon Island: What Cornell’s NYC Tech Campus Will Look Like http://ow.ly/8cEXV     
    
    
    Boom.... M.I.T. Game-Changer: Free Online Education For All - Forbes http://ow.ly/8ePxA     
    
    
    incredible post from one of my favorite people, @shanesnow "Screw expectations" ─ revolutions.is http://ow.ly/8f4Pr     
    
    
    Prediction: 2012 is the year of Brooklyn in tech cc: @armbrusting @brooklyn_vc #lovemyhometown    
    
    
    Despite Attacks, Klout Is Poised To Boost Its Influence | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/8fQKs     
    
    
    well said by @ronconway RT @vcdeallawyer: Business: Where angels will tread | The Economist http://econ.st/vvafzq     
    
    
    fascinating stuff guys RT @numberfire: The Basketball NERD rankings are updated: Who is too high/low? http://ow.ly/8jPwi     
    
    
    good one here: RT @contently: Hey Everyone! Tell Us - Do You Have A Blogging Calendar? http://bit.ly/uY8zSd     
    
    
    good nuanced post on Stealth Mode: Elad Blog: Is Stealth Mode Stupid? http://ow.ly/8l9jz  thoughts?    
    
    
    if u were wondering what al this talk about hacking education is, see this: My Teacher Is an App - http://WSJ.com  http://ow.ly/8lvDG     
    
    
    congrats to the guys at @contently Raise $2 Million to Play Matchmaker for Journalists and Brands |  Advertising Age http://ow.ly/8lGOs     
    
    
    congrats! RT @columbiaentprog: Jeremy Miller '10 http://FSAStore.com  featured on Fox Biz news http://ow.ly/8opFT  cc: @fsa_store    
    
    
    Mike "Consiglieri" Duda @mikeduda appears @venturestudio next week. shoot me questions you have for him re: tech, 2012, branding, anything    
    
    
    good event: NYVC: Speaker Series with Nikhil from SoftBank Capital - Eventbrite http://ow.ly/8sY0Z     
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/U_YsKC     
    
    
    Jeff Clavier @jeff builds a bigger seed fund - The Term Sheet: Fortune's deals blog Term Sheet http://ow.ly/8Ix9q     
    
    
    it's safe to say that this gentleman means business: Dwolla – Entering a growth stage with new partners -  http://ow.ly/8WEjH     
    
    
    best post of day so far: Five Myths About Venture Capital: http://ow.ly/8WUzm  nice one @vcbrazil    
    
    
    Great post: RT @mccannatron:  The difference between entrepreneurs and everyone else http://ow.ly/1Ga4es     
    
    
    With New $27 Million Fund, ff Venture Capital Is On A Roll (Interview) | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/97zE9  congrats cc: @armbrusting    
    
    
    Reid Hoffman's 10 Rules for Entrepreneurial Success | http://Entrepreneur.com  http://ow.ly/981K6     
    
    
    interesting on many levels: The DIY 'Maker Movement' Meets the VCs http://ow.ly/99oaA  ie. @bfeld sounded smart, others- not so much :)    
    
    
    this may land heavier than a Klitschko body-punch for some, but it's true RT @sheynkman: Ungerminated: Trouble w/ Seeds http://bit.ly/xMj2kW     
    
    
    a candid view: "NYC is becoming a big Tech Town as well as everything else it already is" Martin Varsavsky | English http://ow.ly/9a0mT     
    
    
    gutting it out... RT @amolsarva: 11 years to 1mm http://post.ly/5X9o8     
    
    
    Yes! RT @VikVenkat: RT @mubeenamalik: Congratulations to @clotheshorse http://ow.ly/9ft2J  @VikVenkat @dwhittemore @willcharczuk    
    
    
    In 2011 I'll be listening to people with domain expertise and not to the so-called "news" of the day.    
    
    
    Cool story RT @newsycombinator: How I got a job from a Hacker News post http://j.mp/zkb1FH     
    
    
    Check it out: RT @sree: Speaking at 10a ET digital media @BRITEconf w/ @mattquint @toastmax @magnify @w3edge * follow at #briteconf    
    
    
    .@amirshake can we interview you tomorrow for @venturestudio on mashable?    
    
    
    @nciia who from nciia is @ SXSW?    
    
    
    @ashoka who from ashoka is coming to SXSW?    
    
    
    @ramyadeeb ramy, inviting you to come on our show which airs on Mashable.. we can shoot tomorrow (friday).. let us know.. we r at SXSW    
    
    
    @drewhouston drew- can u do an interview w/us tomorrow? will be on mashable.. we are at SXSW    
    
    
    @amirshake @KristinaWeise can one of your execs come to driskill hotel tomorrow, friday, we are filming here..    
    
    
    @seventhgen heard you guys are @ SXSW... can you come on our show? it airs 2x a wek on mashable... u guys are doing great things    
    
    
    @AshokaU who from AshokaU is @ SXSW? we'd love to have u on mashable/ @venturestudio    
    
    
    @KristinaWeise just did    
    
    
    @stevecase are you avail for an interview? goes up on mashable    
    
    
    amazing hosts, superb guests @ great location.. thank you! @joedcoleman @jehangirirani @contently @shanesnow @ericaswallow @benparr @tarekp    
    
    
    @lenberg what time is @soundcloud event starting? cc: @jehangirirani    
    
    
    looking worldwide for folks who want to be entrepreneurship curators for their home-towns:   http://ow.ly/9FgNr  ping: @startupgenome    
    
    
    New Blog Post:  @davidblerner: Getting from Zero to One (5): It's All About the People http://bit.ly/hViLXX    
    
    
    Deep: RT @shanereiser: "I Changed My Job Title and Won’t Go Back" http://khrt.co/FO4KC7  by @joshviney    
    
    
    Congrats to @JoeFernandez - The Young Influentials: 20 Under 40 Who Are Wicked Smart and Rebooting Your World http://shar.es/pvOzu     
    
    
    @getwakefield is awesome: RT @brycelongton: RT @GetWakefield: Startup City Report: Waterloo, Ontario http://ow.ly/9Pdep     
    
    
    interested in #entrepreneurship? follow @getwakefield today's email: Startup Dorms & Gates’ Fave Canadian Fishing Hole http://bit.ly/GNZ7xl     
    
    
    New Blog Post on Building Your Startup Team: Getting from Zero to One Series: "It's All About the People" http://bit.ly/hViLXX    
    
    
    New Blog Post: Mapping Out Your Startup Some More: http://ow.ly/3uaas   (part of Getting From Zero to One Series) http://ow.ly/3uaat    
    
    
    EDU going to get uprooted big time: ie. The Stanford Education Experiment Could Change Higher Learning Forever http://ow.ly/9RnUm     
    
    
    this guy's the real McKoy: James Cameron Now at Ocean's Deepest Point http://ow.ly/9RVhr     
    
    
    congrats! RT @kmin: LOVING the blazers @QuincyApparel just launched today! @alexnels, @cmwalla & team http://www.quincyapparel.com  #quincylaunch    
    
    
    cool! RT @kauffmanfdn: Infographic: 68 Startup Weekends At-a-Glance: the 54-hour event where people come t... http://kff.mn/HgC3vI     
    
    
    remarkable RT @collabfund: Half all U.S. households contain at least one Apple product: http://bit.ly/H1zGNm  (via @ttunguz)    
    
    
    Quincy Apparel Launch Party is awesome!!  http://ow.ly/1Jrtwv   cc: @QuincyApparel    
    
    
    please RT: looking for awesome curators in following cities/states for @startupgenome : LA, Boulder, Vancouver, Austin, Miami, Tokyo, Moscow    
    
    
    congrats to @QuincyApparel on a tremendous launch party yesterday... fantastic group... cc: @dbdsocial @rbvprenice @robcromer @cmwalla    
    
    
    BluePrint Health DemoDay: entrepreneurs are just crushing it!! #Bphealth12 @bphealth great job guys!    
    
    
    #ff @benjimarkoff @cmwalla @ADCADE @robcromer @rbvprentice @dbdsocial @1CharlesH @to2 @crashdev @stefan_ne @updater @diegosaezgil @tarekp    
    
    
    FF# @ColumbiaVC @needlvrm @bphealth @rashaunps @myaidin @icouchme @meddikapp @goprocured @symcatdotcom @inquisithealth @5oclockrecords    
    
    
    @brian_sirkia @bopeabody bo knows smart... Great book, agree    
    
    
    cool post: Old School Venture Capital http://ow.ly/a4yPH  how things are in Brazil right now...    
    
    
    Fascinating RT @redroverhq:Minerva Project scores $25 million in seed money to build a new elite university online http://bit.ly/HL3Cj9     
    
    
    I'll be moderating @DecodedFashion on April 30, @LincolnCenter. It's about connecting Fashion & the best Tech Startups http://bit.ly/yfcYlp     
    
    
    Just releasing my Series on University Entrepreneurship here for those interested in the subject: http://ow.ly/3un4M    
    
    
    Get A Drink And A Job At NYC Uncubed, The New Silicon Alley Talent Fair | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/acTKL     
    
    
    @perrychen perry- we'd love to have u on show- DM us if u can with email addy    
    
    
    @hackforchange would love to have you on the show... Follow us and let's DM    
    
    
    @Recyclebank @greenrank appreciate it!    
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/B_pUhb     
    
    
    brutally frank advice! RT @bill_gross: My answer on Quora to: How do you split your time between two projects? http://b.qr.ae/gmTqw8    
    
    
    Txs hoss! RT @to2: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know to Succeed (5) Finding a Mentor http://bit.ly/K0djVL     
    
    
    Txs! RT @NYUEntrepreneur: Spot on! RT @davidblerner:What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know (5) Finding a Mentor http://ow.ly/1L4gxn     
    
    
    Cool panel @decodedfashion w/ @amycole @rebeccaminkoff @saks @heyitsnoah @catecorcoran #decodedfashion commerce & content    
    
    
    @techballers @space530 great meeting you guys!    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @lererventures: Food52 wins James Beard Award f/Publication of Year! @food52 @amandahesser @merrillstubbs http://bit.ly/ISEkdA     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @comiXology: ComiXology Announces 65M Downloads, Inks Multi-year Deal To Distribute Marvel Digital Comics http://ow.ly/1LS2J7     
    
    
    Agree! RT @mikearsenault: Startup folks should subscribe to @Wakefield Awesome content/daily stories, startup culture http://ow.ly/1MoEKL     
    
    
    My talk on @venturestudio with RT @martyodlin CEO Bamboo Bike Studio: an anti-consumerist visionary http://bit.ly/LaOWpA  #visionary    
    
    
    Amen! RT @sree: Tip for @LinkedIn bios: Don't call yourself a "digital media visionary" or "thought leader" * Those are labels others give u    
    
    
    My talk with the company changing the game in book publishing RT @pubslush: AMAZE PRESS! thanks @venturestudio http://on.mash.to/L6kl12     
    
    
    #FF @jkagan @publush @bphealth @pilarmari @anavictoriaga @Sati_fied @_bchen @joelmontgomery @chartbeat @Wakefield @bradsvrluga @garyvee    
    
    
    #FF @fabricegrinda @amitklein @nancylublin @dosomething @fabref @rameshharidas @armbrusting @wadhwa @jehangirirani @catone @benjimarkoff    
    
    
    @Pilarmari @startupgenome txs!    
    
    
    .@alexavontobel with you!    
    
    
    Prediction: @msuster out of practice, will get carried-out :) I'm in the UK!! See this image for what my life was like http://instagr.am/p/MB28anJUzu/     
    
    
    @msuster "i didnt let the side down!" he says from the pub floor :)    
    
    
    Incredibly eloquent and deep must read post for anyone in startup world RT @ganeumann: Great Riches and Low Theft. RW: http://bit.ly/M2xGIe     
    
    
    "Build a canvas and they will fill it" says @kurnit at #VFC yesterday.    
    
    
    New Post: The Founder's Eye http://bit.ly/MLSW1s  #picasso #founder    
    
    
    @JeffFajans awesome. Stay in touch!    
    
    
    New Post: RT @davidblerner: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know (7) Grants &amp; Competitions http://bit.ly/MxGSnD  cc: @to2    
    
    
    New Post: TRUST  http://bit.ly/NWNo4L  #Entrepreneurship    
    
    
    It's on! RT @updater: NYC startup interns: 45 minutes left to RSVP for the Intern Army chat with Dave Lerner. Details: http://www.intern-army.com .    
    
    
    From @edyson : "The job of an angel is not to pick winners, but to pick potential winners and help them become winners." #angelinvesting    
    
    
    If u r moving, must read! RT @updater: Ten Commandments of Change of Address, brought to you by @Updater http://ow.ly/d00A1  #moving #USPS    
    
    
    Translation: we got shamed by tech community & flipped: Amended Decision on @Uber in Massachusetts http://ow.ly/d01tw   cc: @ScottKirsner    
    
    
    Psyched!! RT @shanereiser: Announcing my side project: @StartupGenome - What is it and how we got started: http://bit.ly/PpzPf9     
    
    
    He did a great job! RT @BenjLerer: yay for @davetisch http://blog.davidtisch.com/post/29638236867/newadventures … excited/frightened for what he tackles next    
    
    
    Yes @shanereiser : @startupgenome project getting nice coverage! http://www.siliconprairienews.com/2012/08/startup-genome-takes-local-approach-categorizing-visualizing-ecosystems …    
    
    
    Common misconception: @sgblank doesn't believe in planning. No- just don't develop operating/business/execution plan b4 product/market fit    
    
    
    Half-life of a VP of Sales in a startup about 14 months- @sgblank    
    
    
    Org charts and titles are toxic to startups early on: @sgblank    
    
    
    "Somehow people seem to spend $1 more than the venture money they raise"  @sgblank    
    
    
    Who is using the business model canvas?    
    
    
    "technology is nice but it's not the business folks" @sgblank    
    
    
    "Until about 1995 we only had one real channel... It was physical... then Netscape went public..." @sgblank    
    
    
    "don't confuse the price of your product with your actual revenue model" make sure u have one: @sgblank @bobdorf @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    ok, so it's getting to that time: almost ready for people to.... "get out of the building!!" @sgblank @bobdorf @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Q: "what does testing the problem mean" A: don't pitch 'Em on your product right away, do they *have* a problem? If so what is it? @sgblank    
    
    
    deep: "what if we could solve your problem like this?" @sgblank @bobdorf    
    
    
    "founders- you actually have to start with an opinion..." just be ready to test it and for it to change.. @sgblank @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    "market researchers are great at predicting the past" entrepreneurs are trying to change the future @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    "Listen for the outlier data, not to survey monkey data.. E'ship is an art, not an accounting exercise" Learn how to *really* listen    
    
    
    "a problem with every category of your business model is not a pivot, it's a restart!" :) @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Love this: RT @robgo: New post: Captivating Investors with Secrets - And Some Other Fundraising Tips http://robgo.org/2012/08/29/captivating-investors-with-secrets-and-other-fundraising-tips/ …    
    
    
    "best time to consider taking corporate VC is Series B or later" @sgblank #leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Caution RT @infoarbitrage: Multinationals Stake Claim in VC http://nyti.ms/OTFSKb  At growth stage there can be real value-add, but be careful    
    
    
    +1 RT @BestVendor: Check out our new lists feature and write your own. There's a reward involved... :) http://bit.ly/Pxj0P8     
    
    
    Holy #^*! @schlaf just killed-it in front of my class @ Columbia B School. elucidated NYC's startup ecosystem like I've never seen #unreal    
    
    
    +1 Chess Concepts Peter Thiel Used To Become A Billionaire | http://Inc.com  http://ow.ly/dFS1i     
    
    
    Read-it and RT - Amazing Guide to NYC Tech courtesy of the great @schlaf http://ow.ly/dMlzE   huge effort!! cc: @startupgenome    
    
    
    Must read post by the terrific @bobdorf RT @Xconomy: Why Too Many Startups Suck - http://bit.ly/Sc5Yut     
    
    
    This is a big deal- please RT @startupgenome: Embed Startup Genome maps - anywhere | The Startup Genome Blog http://bit.ly/PjFR1h     
    
    
    Wow, @medikly just crushed it at @bphealth demo day #bphdd12    
    
    
    Boom: @symbiosishealth just crushed everything at demo day, wow... @bphealth    
    
    
    NEW POST: Lessons from a Young Master http://bit.ly/RtmnqR  #teaching #learning    
    
    
    NEWER POST: Lessons from Sandy http://bit.ly/YpI1Bg  #sandy #nurses    
    
    
    NEW POST: Death of a Mentor: Reflections http://bit.ly/UoibgC  (this was a tough one) #mentorship    
    
    
    New Post: RT Measuring Founder Strength http://bit.ly/SLb4hL  kudos to @saarsaar    
    
    
    updated infographic of angel investor landscape: http://ow.ly/3Gso9    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @jehangirirani: For all you entrepreneurial data hounds... it doesn't get better than this! http://ow.ly/gfgzC  @startupgenome    
    
    
    Was I punked on my own show by @john_frankel or not? :)  happy holidays to all cc: @ffvc @armbrusting http://ow.ly/gohZe  :) cc:...    
    
    
    Boom: just shipped: RT @startupgenome: New blog post: You can now merge cities or create completely custom Regions - http://bit.ly/UV3wMB     
    
    
    the 10 types of hair on early-stage deals http://ow.ly/3IK7A    
    
    
    post: Sometimes Nothin' Can be a Real Cool Hand http://ow.ly/3IKID    
    
    
    the "X" factor in business... it's there or it ain't.... http://ow.ly/3IKOY  #go jets    
    
    
    new post: RT @davidblerner: I Am Incubator http://bit.ly/gILn9F    
    
    
    New Post: So, What's a "Pain Point in the Market"?  http://ow.ly/hxTC3  cc: @updater @joevc @bsiscovick    
    
    
    What a day: my students @donnerchait of @travefy & @dbaird13 of blocpower making news: http://ow.ly/i9ELY  and http://ow.ly/i9ELZ     
    
    
    .@Bradharrison1 @allenmorgan RT @Wakefield: Ur next trip to airport doesn't have 2 b miserable. Check: @GateGuru http://bit.ly/WakeGate     
    
    
    Gulp... Can't wait for this series by @ganeumann : Reaction Wheel: Why I'm Not an Angel http://ow.ly/jingz     
    
    
    going to this: RT @rodkurtz: Entrepreneurs ask me, "How can I get media coverage?" Next week, I'll show you how. http://bit.ly/Xu04bb     
    
    
    NEW POST:  Why Do So Many Partnerships End in Disaster http://bit.ly/186l7Uw  @OPENForum    
    
    
    NEW POST: @davelerner: The Supremacy of Warm Introductions http://bit.ly/ZmYpVC  #startups @OPENForum    
    
    
    BOOM: Dance all night: @Jukely tells you which concerts to see and which friends to see them with | VentureBeat http://ow.ly/qBwNj     
    
    
    My Conversation with entrepreneur/journalist Shane Snow of Contently.com http://bit.ly/eEgkPG  discuss b-model in depth, team, silicon alley    
    
    
    @msuster weighs in on debate: What’s The Real Deal With AngelList? http://ow.ly/444YI    
    
    
    must read: @msuster weighs in on debate: What’s The Real Deal With AngelList? http://ow.ly/4455K    
    
    
    My Conversation on Venture Studio w/ Shane Snow of www.contently.com http://ow.ly/4458O @shanesnow (entrepreneur, journo, designer, writer)    
    
    
    cool product! Foundry Group Puts $500,000 Into Attachments.me http://ow.ly/46Oia congrats @bfeld    
    
    
    RT The latest news and analysis from China's perspective, read Edward Nigro is @TheChinaInsider http://thechinainsider.com/blog/    
    
    
    Primate Makes Daring Escape From Cage, Becomes Entrepreneur: Society Uneasy, Mainstream Press Obscures His True Origins http://bit.ly/fXlZOl    
    
    
    good clear-eyed insights here: The ridiculous Vivek Wadhwa furore and the new Boston Tea Party - Fred Destin http://ow.ly/476Hz    
    
    
    R u in a partnership?: "We value trust, respect, and consensus. We never vote. We don't exercise vetos. We don't yell."  http://ow.ly/47Rp7    
    
    
    terrific opportunity w/great folks: RT @bsiscovick: RT @infoarbitrage: Please check out / RT @iaventures Summer internship bit.ly/fKjKFJ $    
    
    
    New Post: Primate Makes Daring Escape From Cage, Becomes Entrepreneur: Society Uneasy, Press Obscures His True Origins http://ow.ly/48xvg    
    
    
    My conversation on Venture Studio w/ Mark Loranger of Square 1 Bank http://bit.ly/g18r1O ie. for entrepreneurs: what is a venture bank? etc    
    
    
    Skype Founder To Students: Don’t Follow The Obvious Path - Venture Capital Dispatch - WSJ http://ow.ly/4d6lW    
    
    
    agree with @zamland: Jim Plush's Blog - This may be the best resume I have ever seen http://awe.sm/5GlAl  wow... $$    
    
    
    Vinny Vacanti, CEO of Yipit on the odyssey of a first-time entrepreneur & learning to code http://bit.ly/hDhvEH @vacanti @jdmoran    
    
    
    ff# @vacanti @robgo @drewconway @makdchou @amandahesser @to2 @chartio @armbrusting @jehangirirani @markloranger @stellajordy @joshrweinstein    
    
    
    congrats @benjlerer "Thrillist Melds Editorial Content and Commerce" - NYTimes.com http://ow.ly/4iBc6    
    
    
    Part II of conversation w/ @vacanti CEO of Yipit: "Traction is King", learning to code, and more http://ow.ly/4jtEv cc @jdmoran @hackernews    
    
    
    cool post from @cdixon  MIT is a national treasure - cdixon's posterous http://ow.ly/4kE6z    
    
    
    A must read: New Rules for the New Internet Bubble « Steve Blank http://ow.ly/4kG8v    
    
    
    FF# @nikoliaA @to2 @arorasaurabh @vacanti @jacobbrody @jjbesnainou @dwhittemore @stellajordy @joshrweinstein @robgo @amandahesser    
    
    
    great piece: Is There a New Technology Bubble? Ben Horowitz Doesn't Think So. | Ben Horowitz | Voices | AllThingsD http://ow.ly/4n4Ua    
    
    
    Conversation with @to2 Trevor Owens: Entrepreneur, Super-Connector, Community Organizer http://bit.ly/gKFO27 @venturestudio @samantha_smith    
    
    
    My convo w/ @STELLAjordy CEO re: STELLAService, biz model & Steve Nash/Consiglieri's investment @MikeDuda @SteveNash http://ow.ly/4tseP    
    
    
    My convo w/ @joshrweinstein CEO YouAre.TV http://bit.ly/hw6aNU we talk chess, startups & his wild entrepreneurial journey @peterthiel    
    
    
    great day today chatting with @davetisch @bhargreaves and @nickseguin cc: @venturestudio    
    
    
    convo w/ @davetisch about the epic @techstars NYC DemoDay & behind the scenes stuff cc: @fakedavetisch @bfeld @davidcohen http://ow.ly/4DkcB    
    
    
    for left coast: @davetisch talks about epic @techstars NYC DemoDay & behind scenes stuff cc: @bfeld @davidcohen http://ow.ly/4DLOn    
    
    
    @fakedavetisch ok. Standby    
    
    
    Thrillist CEO @benjlerer tells story of @thrillist on @VentureStudio + acquiring @jackthreads & talks @lererventures http://ow.ly/4H6WR    
    
    
    smart, practical & in that sense, a "cutting-edge" move by a university.... Joichi Ito Named Head of M.I.T. Media Lab  http://ow.ly/4I407    
    
    
    Y Combinator Success Leads To Copycats, Incubator Raiders - Venture Capital Dispatch - WSJ http://ow.ly/4I4Ev    
    
    
    My convo on @venturestudio w/ the terrific @jonathanglick CEO of @sulia http://ow.ly/4LYdV    
    
    
    .@reecepacheco @jehangirirani  yes reece u were on the @davetisch interview: http://ow.ly/4NsQC come on the show in person next time    
    
    
    @fakedavetisch ok. Sent the interview questions over just now!    
    
    
    bravo to this guy for writing a much needed piece on this!: The Next 10 Years Will Be Great For Both Founders And VCs http://ow.ly/4PNZD    
    
    
    some of VC @mattcharris thoughts re: @BankSimple, @OnDeckCapital & fintech as told to me on @venturestudio http://ow.ly/4SCyi    
    
    
    well said: "You’re not entitled to anything. Hustle for everything you’re worth"  The Startup Foundry http://ow.ly/4TM31    
    
    
    Watching live feed of Social Media Weekend http://bit.ly/socmediaweekend, track chatter at #smwknd or http://bit.ly/smwkndhash yes! @sree    
    
    
    @2carvin speaking w/ @sree now....  Watching live feed of Social Media Weekend http://bit.ly/socmediaweekend #smwknd    
    
    
    .@acarvin says "never forget there is no longer any such thing as an audience" @sree @emilybell @NYT_jenpreston    
    
    
    .@NYT_JenPreston where do we find andy's curated twitter lists? #smwknd can someone post?    
    
    
    blog post: 5 qualities of great entrepreneurs: http://ow.ly/4UZBp    
    
    
    VID: So what's the Kauffman FDN @KauffmanFDN all about? My convo w/ @nickseguin Mgr Entrepreneurship @venturestudio    
    
    
    Mashable Video Interview: Inside Tips from Entrepreneurs and Investors http://bit.ly/e20DFB    
    
    
    So, You Think You Have to Deal With A**holes? Think Again http://ow.ly/5Jyzk    
    
    
    cool new fashion startup- great founders: Point, Click, Shoot — a New Site by Editors for Editors - Media News - WWD.com http://ow.ly/5OAiH    
    
    
    @MikeBrownJr @nickgiglia @reecepacheco @softtechvc @stacyspikes @vacanti @zamland @Arrington @bhargreaves @dwhittemore @ffventure @kprentiss    
    
    
    the terrific @therunthrough team covered on Mashable: Private Site Connects Fashion Designers & Editors for Shoots http://ow.ly/5R72z    
    
    
    POST: An Entrepreneur's Commandment: Do What Thou Lovest -  http://ow.ly/5Rghs (was reminded of this today)    
    
    
    solid read from @sheynkman When do VCs make mistakes? - Passionate Intensity http://ow.ly/5UB8O    
    
    
    ff# @kloutperks @john_frankel @vikvenkat @dwhittemore @cliffpavlovic @sheynkman @madamian @echo_nyc @leemhoffman @jfernandez @ebellity    
    
    
    ff# @amandahesser @jehangirirani @schlaf @bpmilne @shanesnow @kevinbluer @coderkid    
    
    
    $$: Information Arbitrage - Sound thinking for unsound times http://ow.ly/5Zggq    
    
    
    meet the guy @cdixon @asenkut @infoarbitrage @firstround @AOLVentures backed: Ari Jacoby, @solvemediainc @venturestudio http://bit.ly/pSr5G0    
    
    
    ff# @jessicalawrence @randygiusto @UNYstartups @solvemedia @arijacoby @tzmartin @jen_mcfadden @vivenkat @jalak @tweet_massimo @trikro    
    
    
    Meet the guy @cdixon @asenkut @infoarbitrage @firstround & @AOLVentures all backed! @AriJacoby @SolveMedia http://bit.ly/pSr5G0 on...    
    
    
    From Friday: Entrepreneur Survival Guide: Some Motivation, Courtesy of Uncle Nikolai:  http://ow.ly/63pSJ #25thHour #survive    
    
    
    ff# @lsanza @vikvenkat @jdorkin @ngavronsky @cliffpavlovic @kunalchaudhari @amandahesser @john_frankel @stefan_ne @shanereiser @adamostrow    
    
    
    Chegg Chugging Along: Unleashes Digital Textbook Rentals, Aims To Be 'LinkedIn For College Students' http://ow.ly/681GK    
    
    
    Bubble-heads- have a read :)  Marc Andreessen on Why Software Is Eating the World - WSJ.com http://ow.ly/68gHK    
    
    
    this guy & Andreessen should hang-out, similar world view: Irving Kahn 105-Year-Old Banker: Economic Downturn Just a Blip http://ow.ly/68hBw    
    
    
    Kabooommmm: Skype acquires GroupMe http://ow.ly/68RTN    
    
    
    Invest in People - #GroupMe http://ow.ly/68WkM by @davetisch    
    
    
    Must read! RT @davidcohen: New on my blog: "The Mentor Manifesto" http://www.davidgcohen.com/2011/08/28/the-mentor-manifesto/ …    
    
    
    Michael Arrington launching venture fund - The Term Sheet: Fortune's deals blog Term Sheet http://ow.ly/6jdS4    
    
    
    What do you need? | The Monster In Your Head http://ow.ly/6lWHD    
    
    
    BOOM.... General Assembly Gets Funding From Yuri Milner and Jeff Bezos | Betabeat — News, gossip and intel from Silicon Alley 2.0....    
    
    
    $$$ must read for entrepreneurs RT @marksbirch: The Trouble with Non-Investor Investors | Strong Opinions @marksbirch http://bch.me/nVMCP8     
    
    
    Question: does anyone know how solid the .ly domains are given all the turmoil in Libya? I heard they are actually Libya's "country code"    
    
    
    good one from @wadhwa What Spain could learn from a former colony - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/6xML3 #Espana    
    
    
    check out my buddy @porlando 's course on startups @skillshare Startups Unplugged -- Structure for your Startup  http://ow.ly/6DTb0    
    
    
    Neil Capel, CEO of @Sailthru on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/oVvwIv  @neilcapel to fledgling entrepreneurs: you need to "go full force"    
    
    
    "You need to go full force" says @NeilCapel CEO of @sailthru to entrepreneurs on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/oVvwIv     
    
    
    ff# @to2 @fabricegrinda @mashinsky @vivsharma @unystartups @jrizk33 @venturestudio @startupgenome @warbyparker @stephenfleming @frankjpinto    
    
    
    ff# @amitklein @shanesnow @shanereiser @joefernandez @ceonyc @zsims @zamland @paigecraig    
    
    
    ff# @mevans1 @therunthrough @learnvest @NeilCapel @bradsvrluga @stacyspikes @adamostrow @davetisch @echo_nyc @ffventure @bhargreaves    
    
    
    Great piece guys! RT @nickseguin: it takes a village to raise a #startup - piece by @mmcedward, @MarcNager and I http://huff.to/qwh2WS     
    
    
    Well said  RT @bsiscovick RT @vacanti If starting a co, email monthly updates to big list of friends/mentors w recent progress, help needed    
    
    
    "share your ideas" RT @davidblerner @venturestudio : Ari Rabban, CEO of http://Phone.com  http://bit.ly/oZA7Db     
    
    
    ff# @echo_nyc @annaivey @svenningsen @vcdeallawyer @to2 @ganeumann @nickseguin @startuppro @bfeld @markloranger @bfeld @stephenfleming    
    
    
    Andreessen Horowitz Joining in Y Combinator Start Fund - Kara Swisher - News - AllThingsD http://ow.ly/6YijD     
    
    
    Has anyone seen the documentary "Something Ventured" yet? #startups #entrepreneurship    
    
    
    the next profession to be displaced: publishers: Amazon Rewrites the Rules of Book Publishing - http://NYTimes.com  http://ow.ly/6Z3X7     
    
    
    AmEx as VC!? Leads $12 Million Round In Clickable, Which Wants To “Become The AdWords Of Social” | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/70h8L     
    
    
    13 Startups Facebook Acqui-Hired For Millions Of Dollars http://ow.ly/70kzc     
    
    
    TechStars’ second New York class shines in their debut — Tech News and Analysis http://ow.ly/71zdY     
    
    
    wow: RT @marksbirch: Talking to the Homeless & the Theatre of Everyday Life by @ScottBrit http://bch.me/q2S3Qs  - Scott is good people    
    
    
    POST: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know to Succeed (3) Know Something! http://bit.ly/pvCbOE  @startupamerica    
    
    
    @scottbrit agree!    
    
    
    @pkedrosky i remember when Nicklaus last won the Masters and everyone bought that oversized putter!    
    
    
    IronMike getting into tech! RT @miketyson: Sat w/ @dickc & @john today. These guys are a part of building future & I want to be part of it.    
    
    
    Interview: @venturestudio w/ @john_frankel founding partner of @ffventure on working w/great entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/tvj4Dd     
    
    
    agree RT @joefernandez: This is amazing - The Measured Life: What's Your Klout Score? http://on.wsj.com/rtoomq     
    
    
    Startup Lessons from David Cohen and the TechStars | Blog | Daily Dose | http://Entrepreneur.com  http://ow.ly/79Bei     
    
    
    soon kicking off evening convo w/ @infoarbitrage cc: @jrizk333 @columbiavc @dwhittemore who's joining? @iaventures + CVC= $$    
    
    
    @infoarbitrage is dropping knowledge $$ RT @teddotcom: Great CVC talk tonight with @davidblerner and @infoarbitrage. Hats off to @jrizk333    
    
    
    good read! RT @sarahprevette: What I learned from raising venture capital http://awe.sm/5Y0RD     
    
    
    want to learn about product mgmt? my good pal @dwhittemore teaching Product Management for Startups on Skillshare:  http://ow.ly/7bjia     
    
    
    Kaboom: Codecademy Raises $2.5 Million To Teach You How To Code | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7bs3z     
    
    
    congrats guys RT @zsims: Ryan and I are thrilled to announce the next steps for @Codecademy - http://blog.codecademy.com/codecademyaddi …    
    
    
    Fortune Finance just picked up my piece on: Are super-angels extinct? http://bit.ly/gla8Jd    
    
    
    powerful stuff: A Sister’s Eulogy for Steve Jobs - http://NYTimes.com  http://ow.ly/7dw51     
    
    
    congrats to STELLAService team: Raising $5 Million to Keep You In the Know: STELLAService blog http://ow.ly/7n3Ng     
    
    
    kaboom: "Calling Bullshit On The Series A Crunch" | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7oDfF     
    
    
    Fascinating approach! RT @TheNickFrost: 1% Of Nothing Launches To Get Startups Donating Equity http://sul.st/rZmZfD     
    
    
    Must Read: The Real Cost of Patent Trolls http://ow.ly/7tTbF  courtesy @bfeld    
    
    
    The Rise Of The Health Startup? A Peek At The 13 Companies In Rock Health’s Inaugural Batch | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/7tTEL     
    
    
    On getting product-market fit: My talk w/ @sachinkamdar CEO of @parsely on @venturestudio http://bit.ly/t4f0az  cc: @montalenti    
    
    
    @iaventures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJiz cc @infoarbitrage @bsiscovick who's next?    
    
    
    Ohio-based @NCTVentures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJtI congrats! who's next?    
    
    
    5am ventures updates profile on our crowdsourced map of world venture community http://ow.ly/3nJx5 who is next? cc @shanesnow @shanereiser    
    
    
    next time you think you're real busy, read this: Jack Dorsey's Twitter & Square Work Schedule - http://ow.ly/7zmi7     
    
    
    good piece on how: Accelerators Groom Technology Ventures for Success | PBS NewsHour | Nov. 22, 2011 | PBS http://ow.ly/7DiKn     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!!    
    
    
    here comes 3D printing: The printed world | The Economist http://ow.ly/7Gkrq     
    
    
    congrats @warbyparker team: Go West, Young Men: style file: daily fashion, party, and model news http://ow.ly/7Gz9f     
    
    
    Leonsis, Case found $450 million fund to aid Washington area start-up firms - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/7Lgi1     
    
    
    big news! Spotify Launches New App Platform, Announces Move to NY - http://NYConvergence.com  http://ow.ly/7LEUh     
    
    
    big news RT @mashable: Facebook to Open New York Engineering Office - http://on.mash.to/tX3EMe     
    
    
    Startup Incubator WeWork Labs Gets A New 75,000 Square Foot Office In NYC http://ow.ly/7MSIS     
    
    
    Who is right? Interesting discussion: The case for old entrepreneurs - The Washington Post http://ow.ly/7MSQs     
    
    
    Wow! Bullseye! RT @abarrera Beware of those who say they help entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/dGpKXs <-- Ready, steady, FLAME!!    
    
    
    @brian_sirkia agree!    
    
    
    ff# @mterrim @justbobbibrown @toryburch  incredible and inspiring event for the foundation- congrats- what a great mission!    
    
    
    @toryburch @justbobbibrown @KendraBracken @aliwing @AlicesTeaCup @JCrew_Insider it was a blast, thanks!    
    
    
    good post from @bikenyc (Stuart Ellman): Do Not Cut Off Your Colleagues - RRE Ventures http://ow.ly/7VoFY     
    
    
    My TedX talk: "Why Wait 'Til You Graduate?" http://lnkd.in/wSychU     
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/7tDD8f     
    
    
    great for NYC... would love to learn REAL story tho! Silicon Island: What Cornell’s NYC Tech Campus Will Look Like http://ow.ly/8cEXV     
    
    
    Boom.... M.I.T. Game-Changer: Free Online Education For All - Forbes http://ow.ly/8ePxA     
    
    
    incredible post from one of my favorite people, @shanesnow "Screw expectations" ─ revolutions.is http://ow.ly/8f4Pr     
    
    
    Prediction: 2012 is the year of Brooklyn in tech cc: @armbrusting @brooklyn_vc #lovemyhometown    
    
    
    Despite Attacks, Klout Is Poised To Boost Its Influence | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/8fQKs     
    
    
    well said by @ronconway RT @vcdeallawyer: Business: Where angels will tread | The Economist http://econ.st/vvafzq     
    
    
    fascinating stuff guys RT @numberfire: The Basketball NERD rankings are updated: Who is too high/low? http://ow.ly/8jPwi     
    
    
    good one here: RT @contently: Hey Everyone! Tell Us - Do You Have A Blogging Calendar? http://bit.ly/uY8zSd     
    
    
    good nuanced post on Stealth Mode: Elad Blog: Is Stealth Mode Stupid? http://ow.ly/8l9jz  thoughts?    
    
    
    if u were wondering what al this talk about hacking education is, see this: My Teacher Is an App - http://WSJ.com  http://ow.ly/8lvDG     
    
    
    congrats to the guys at @contently Raise $2 Million to Play Matchmaker for Journalists and Brands |  Advertising Age http://ow.ly/8lGOs     
    
    
    congrats! RT @columbiaentprog: Jeremy Miller '10 http://FSAStore.com  featured on Fox Biz news http://ow.ly/8opFT  cc: @fsa_store    
    
    
    Mike "Consiglieri" Duda @mikeduda appears @venturestudio next week. shoot me questions you have for him re: tech, 2012, branding, anything    
    
    
    good event: NYVC: Speaker Series with Nikhil from SoftBank Capital - Eventbrite http://ow.ly/8sY0Z     
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/U_YsKC     
    
    
    Jeff Clavier @jeff builds a bigger seed fund - The Term Sheet: Fortune's deals blog Term Sheet http://ow.ly/8Ix9q     
    
    
    it's safe to say that this gentleman means business: Dwolla – Entering a growth stage with new partners -  http://ow.ly/8WEjH     
    
    
    best post of day so far: Five Myths About Venture Capital: http://ow.ly/8WUzm  nice one @vcbrazil    
    
    
    Great post: RT @mccannatron:  The difference between entrepreneurs and everyone else http://ow.ly/1Ga4es     
    
    
    With New $27 Million Fund, ff Venture Capital Is On A Roll (Interview) | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/97zE9  congrats cc: @armbrusting    
    
    
    Reid Hoffman's 10 Rules for Entrepreneurial Success | http://Entrepreneur.com  http://ow.ly/981K6     
    
    
    interesting on many levels: The DIY 'Maker Movement' Meets the VCs http://ow.ly/99oaA  ie. @bfeld sounded smart, others- not so much :)    
    
    
    this may land heavier than a Klitschko body-punch for some, but it's true RT @sheynkman: Ungerminated: Trouble w/ Seeds http://bit.ly/xMj2kW     
    
    
    a candid view: "NYC is becoming a big Tech Town as well as everything else it already is" Martin Varsavsky | English http://ow.ly/9a0mT     
    
    
    gutting it out... RT @amolsarva: 11 years to 1mm http://post.ly/5X9o8     
    
    
    Yes! RT @VikVenkat: RT @mubeenamalik: Congratulations to @clotheshorse http://ow.ly/9ft2J  @VikVenkat @dwhittemore @willcharczuk    
    
    
    In 2011 I'll be listening to people with domain expertise and not to the so-called "news" of the day.    
    
    
    Cool story RT @newsycombinator: How I got a job from a Hacker News post http://j.mp/zkb1FH     
    
    
    Check it out: RT @sree: Speaking at 10a ET digital media @BRITEconf w/ @mattquint @toastmax @magnify @w3edge * follow at #briteconf    
    
    
    .@amirshake can we interview you tomorrow for @venturestudio on mashable?    
    
    
    @nciia who from nciia is @ SXSW?    
    
    
    @ashoka who from ashoka is coming to SXSW?    
    
    
    @ramyadeeb ramy, inviting you to come on our show which airs on Mashable.. we can shoot tomorrow (friday).. let us know.. we r at SXSW    
    
    
    @drewhouston drew- can u do an interview w/us tomorrow? will be on mashable.. we are at SXSW    
    
    
    @amirshake @KristinaWeise can one of your execs come to driskill hotel tomorrow, friday, we are filming here..    
    
    
    @seventhgen heard you guys are @ SXSW... can you come on our show? it airs 2x a wek on mashable... u guys are doing great things    
    
    
    @AshokaU who from AshokaU is @ SXSW? we'd love to have u on mashable/ @venturestudio    
    
    
    @KristinaWeise just did    
    
    
    @stevecase are you avail for an interview? goes up on mashable    
    
    
    amazing hosts, superb guests @ great location.. thank you! @joedcoleman @jehangirirani @contently @shanesnow @ericaswallow @benparr @tarekp    
    
    
    @lenberg what time is @soundcloud event starting? cc: @jehangirirani    
    
    
    looking worldwide for folks who want to be entrepreneurship curators for their home-towns:   http://ow.ly/9FgNr  ping: @startupgenome    
    
    
    New Blog Post:  @davidblerner: Getting from Zero to One (5): It's All About the People http://bit.ly/hViLXX    
    
    
    Deep: RT @shanereiser: "I Changed My Job Title and Won’t Go Back" http://khrt.co/FO4KC7  by @joshviney    
    
    
    Congrats to @JoeFernandez - The Young Influentials: 20 Under 40 Who Are Wicked Smart and Rebooting Your World http://shar.es/pvOzu     
    
    
    @getwakefield is awesome: RT @brycelongton: RT @GetWakefield: Startup City Report: Waterloo, Ontario http://ow.ly/9Pdep     
    
    
    interested in #entrepreneurship? follow @getwakefield today's email: Startup Dorms & Gates’ Fave Canadian Fishing Hole http://bit.ly/GNZ7xl     
    
    
    New Blog Post on Building Your Startup Team: Getting from Zero to One Series: "It's All About the People" http://bit.ly/hViLXX    
    
    
    New Blog Post: Mapping Out Your Startup Some More: http://ow.ly/3uaas   (part of Getting From Zero to One Series) http://ow.ly/3uaat    
    
    
    EDU going to get uprooted big time: ie. The Stanford Education Experiment Could Change Higher Learning Forever http://ow.ly/9RnUm     
    
    
    this guy's the real McKoy: James Cameron Now at Ocean's Deepest Point http://ow.ly/9RVhr     
    
    
    congrats! RT @kmin: LOVING the blazers @QuincyApparel just launched today! @alexnels, @cmwalla & team http://www.quincyapparel.com  #quincylaunch    
    
    
    cool! RT @kauffmanfdn: Infographic: 68 Startup Weekends At-a-Glance: the 54-hour event where people come t... http://kff.mn/HgC3vI     
    
    
    remarkable RT @collabfund: Half all U.S. households contain at least one Apple product: http://bit.ly/H1zGNm  (via @ttunguz)    
    
    
    Quincy Apparel Launch Party is awesome!!  http://ow.ly/1Jrtwv   cc: @QuincyApparel    
    
    
    please RT: looking for awesome curators in following cities/states for @startupgenome : LA, Boulder, Vancouver, Austin, Miami, Tokyo, Moscow    
    
    
    congrats to @QuincyApparel on a tremendous launch party yesterday... fantastic group... cc: @dbdsocial @rbvprenice @robcromer @cmwalla    
    
    
    BluePrint Health DemoDay: entrepreneurs are just crushing it!! #Bphealth12 @bphealth great job guys!    
    
    
    #ff @benjimarkoff @cmwalla @ADCADE @robcromer @rbvprentice @dbdsocial @1CharlesH @to2 @crashdev @stefan_ne @updater @diegosaezgil @tarekp    
    
    
    FF# @ColumbiaVC @needlvrm @bphealth @rashaunps @myaidin @icouchme @meddikapp @goprocured @symcatdotcom @inquisithealth @5oclockrecords    
    
    
    @brian_sirkia @bopeabody bo knows smart... Great book, agree    
    
    
    cool post: Old School Venture Capital http://ow.ly/a4yPH  how things are in Brazil right now...    
    
    
    Fascinating RT @redroverhq:Minerva Project scores $25 million in seed money to build a new elite university online http://bit.ly/HL3Cj9     
    
    
    I'll be moderating @DecodedFashion on April 30, @LincolnCenter. It's about connecting Fashion & the best Tech Startups http://bit.ly/yfcYlp     
    
    
    Just releasing my Series on University Entrepreneurship here for those interested in the subject: http://ow.ly/3un4M    
    
    
    Get A Drink And A Job At NYC Uncubed, The New Silicon Alley Talent Fair | TechCrunch http://ow.ly/acTKL     
    
    
    @perrychen perry- we'd love to have u on show- DM us if u can with email addy    
    
    
    @hackforchange would love to have you on the show... Follow us and let's DM    
    
    
    @Recyclebank @greenrank appreciate it!    
    
    
    David B. Lerner http://lnkd.in/B_pUhb     
    
    
    brutally frank advice! RT @bill_gross: My answer on Quora to: How do you split your time between two projects? http://b.qr.ae/gmTqw8    
    
    
    Txs hoss! RT @to2: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know to Succeed (5) Finding a Mentor http://bit.ly/K0djVL     
    
    
    Txs! RT @NYUEntrepreneur: Spot on! RT @davidblerner:What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know (5) Finding a Mentor http://ow.ly/1L4gxn     
    
    
    Cool panel @decodedfashion w/ @amycole @rebeccaminkoff @saks @heyitsnoah @catecorcoran #decodedfashion commerce & content    
    
    
    @techballers @space530 great meeting you guys!    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @lererventures: Food52 wins James Beard Award f/Publication of Year! @food52 @amandahesser @merrillstubbs http://bit.ly/ISEkdA     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @comiXology: ComiXology Announces 65M Downloads, Inks Multi-year Deal To Distribute Marvel Digital Comics http://ow.ly/1LS2J7     
    
    
    Agree! RT @mikearsenault: Startup folks should subscribe to @Wakefield Awesome content/daily stories, startup culture http://ow.ly/1MoEKL     
    
    
    My talk on @venturestudio with RT @martyodlin CEO Bamboo Bike Studio: an anti-consumerist visionary http://bit.ly/LaOWpA  #visionary    
    
    
    Amen! RT @sree: Tip for @LinkedIn bios: Don't call yourself a "digital media visionary" or "thought leader" * Those are labels others give u    
    
    
    My talk with the company changing the game in book publishing RT @pubslush: AMAZE PRESS! thanks @venturestudio http://on.mash.to/L6kl12     
    
    
    #FF @jkagan @publush @bphealth @pilarmari @anavictoriaga @Sati_fied @_bchen @joelmontgomery @chartbeat @Wakefield @bradsvrluga @garyvee    
    
    
    #FF @fabricegrinda @amitklein @nancylublin @dosomething @fabref @rameshharidas @armbrusting @wadhwa @jehangirirani @catone @benjimarkoff    
    
    
    @Pilarmari @startupgenome txs!    
    
    
    .@alexavontobel with you!    
    
    
    Prediction: @msuster out of practice, will get carried-out :) I'm in the UK!! See this image for what my life was like http://instagr.am/p/MB28anJUzu/     
    
    
    @msuster "i didnt let the side down!" he says from the pub floor :)    
    
    
    Incredibly eloquent and deep must read post for anyone in startup world RT @ganeumann: Great Riches and Low Theft. RW: http://bit.ly/M2xGIe     
    
    
    "Build a canvas and they will fill it" says @kurnit at #VFC yesterday.    
    
    
    New Post: The Founder's Eye http://bit.ly/MLSW1s  #picasso #founder    
    
    
    @JeffFajans awesome. Stay in touch!    
    
    
    New Post: RT @davidblerner: What Every Student Entrepreneur Needs to Know (7) Grants &amp; Competitions http://bit.ly/MxGSnD  cc: @to2    
    
    
    New Post: TRUST  http://bit.ly/NWNo4L  #Entrepreneurship    
    
    
    It's on! RT @updater: NYC startup interns: 45 minutes left to RSVP for the Intern Army chat with Dave Lerner. Details: http://www.intern-army.com .    
    
    
    From @edyson : "The job of an angel is not to pick winners, but to pick potential winners and help them become winners." #angelinvesting    
    
    
    If u r moving, must read! RT @updater: Ten Commandments of Change of Address, brought to you by @Updater http://ow.ly/d00A1  #moving #USPS    
    
    
    Translation: we got shamed by tech community & flipped: Amended Decision on @Uber in Massachusetts http://ow.ly/d01tw   cc: @ScottKirsner    
    
    
    Psyched!! RT @shanereiser: Announcing my side project: @StartupGenome - What is it and how we got started: http://bit.ly/PpzPf9     
    
    
    He did a great job! RT @BenjLerer: yay for @davetisch http://blog.davidtisch.com/post/29638236867/newadventures … excited/frightened for what he tackles next    
    
    
    Yes @shanereiser : @startupgenome project getting nice coverage! http://www.siliconprairienews.com/2012/08/startup-genome-takes-local-approach-categorizing-visualizing-ecosystems …    
    
    
    Common misconception: @sgblank doesn't believe in planning. No- just don't develop operating/business/execution plan b4 product/market fit    
    
    
    Half-life of a VP of Sales in a startup about 14 months- @sgblank    
    
    
    Org charts and titles are toxic to startups early on: @sgblank    
    
    
    "Somehow people seem to spend $1 more than the venture money they raise"  @sgblank    
    
    
    Who is using the business model canvas?    
    
    
    "technology is nice but it's not the business folks" @sgblank    
    
    
    "Until about 1995 we only had one real channel... It was physical... then Netscape went public..." @sgblank    
    
    
    "don't confuse the price of your product with your actual revenue model" make sure u have one: @sgblank @bobdorf @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    ok, so it's getting to that time: almost ready for people to.... "get out of the building!!" @sgblank @bobdorf @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Q: "what does testing the problem mean" A: don't pitch 'Em on your product right away, do they *have* a problem? If so what is it? @sgblank    
    
    
    deep: "what if we could solve your problem like this?" @sgblank @bobdorf    
    
    
    "founders- you actually have to start with an opinion..." just be ready to test it and for it to change.. @sgblank @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    "market researchers are great at predicting the past" entrepreneurs are trying to change the future @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    "Listen for the outlier data, not to survey monkey data.. E'ship is an art, not an accounting exercise" Learn how to *really* listen    
    
    
    "a problem with every category of your business model is not a pivot, it's a restart!" :) @leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Love this: RT @robgo: New post: Captivating Investors with Secrets - And Some Other Fundraising Tips http://robgo.org/2012/08/29/captivating-investors-with-secrets-and-other-fundraising-tips/ …    
    
    
    "best time to consider taking corporate VC is Series B or later" @sgblank #leanlaunchpad    
    
    
    Caution RT @infoarbitrage: Multinationals Stake Claim in VC http://nyti.ms/OTFSKb  At growth stage there can be real value-add, but be careful    
    
    
    +1 RT @BestVendor: Check out our new lists feature and write your own. There's a reward involved... :) http://bit.ly/Pxj0P8     
    
    
    Holy #^*! @schlaf just killed-it in front of my class @ Columbia B School. elucidated NYC's startup ecosystem like I've never seen #unreal    
    
    
    +1 Chess Concepts Peter Thiel Used To Become A Billionaire | http://Inc.com  http://ow.ly/dFS1i     
    
    
    Read-it and RT - Amazing Guide to NYC Tech courtesy of the great @schlaf http://ow.ly/dMlzE   huge effort!! cc: @startupgenome    
    
    
    Must read post by the terrific @bobdorf RT @Xconomy: Why Too Many Startups Suck - http://bit.ly/Sc5Yut     
    
    
    This is a big deal- please RT @startupgenome: Embed Startup Genome maps - anywhere | The Startup Genome Blog http://bit.ly/PjFR1h     
    
    
    Wow, @medikly just crushed it at @bphealth demo day #bphdd12    
    
    
    Boom: @symbiosishealth just crushed everything at demo day, wow... @bphealth    
    
    
    NEW POST: Lessons from a Young Master http://bit.ly/RtmnqR  #teaching #learning    
    
    
    NEWER POST: Lessons from Sandy http://bit.ly/YpI1Bg  #sandy #nurses    
    
    
    NEW POST: Death of a Mentor: Reflections http://bit.ly/UoibgC  (this was a tough one) #mentorship    
    
    
    New Post: RT Measuring Founder Strength http://bit.ly/SLb4hL  kudos to @saarsaar    
    
    
    updated infographic of angel investor landscape: http://ow.ly/3Gso9    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @jehangirirani: For all you entrepreneurial data hounds... it doesn't get better than this! http://ow.ly/gfgzC  @startupgenome    
    
    
    Was I punked on my own show by @john_frankel or not? :)  happy holidays to all cc: @ffvc @armbrusting http://ow.ly/gohZe  :) cc:...    
    
    
    Boom: just shipped: RT @startupgenome: New blog post: You can now merge cities or create completely custom Regions - http://bit.ly/UV3wMB     
    
    
    the 10 types of hair on early-stage deals http://ow.ly/3IK7A    
    
    
    post: Sometimes Nothin' Can be a Real Cool Hand http://ow.ly/3IKID    
    
    
    the "X" factor in business... it's there or it ain't.... http://ow.ly/3IKOY  #go jets    
    
    
    new post: RT @davidblerner: I Am Incubator http://bit.ly/gILn9F    
    
    
    New Post: So, What's a "Pain Point in the Market"?  http://ow.ly/hxTC3  cc: @updater @joevc @bsiscovick    
    
    
    What a day: my students @donnerchait of @travefy & @dbaird13 of blocpower making news: http://ow.ly/i9ELY  and http://ow.ly/i9ELZ     
    
    
    .@Bradharrison1 @allenmorgan RT @Wakefield: Ur next trip to airport doesn't have 2 b miserable. Check: @GateGuru http://bit.ly/WakeGate     
    
    
    Gulp... Can't wait for this series by @ganeumann : Reaction Wheel: Why I'm Not an Angel http://ow.ly/jingz     
    
    
    going to this: RT @rodkurtz: Entrepreneurs ask me, "How can I get media coverage?" Next week, I'll show you how. http://bit.ly/Xu04bb     
    
    
    NEW POST:  Why Do So Many Partnerships End in Disaster http://bit.ly/186l7Uw  @OPENForum    
    
    
    NEW POST: @davelerner: The Supremacy of Warm Introductions http://bit.ly/ZmYpVC  #startups @OPENForum    
    
    
    BOOM: Dance all night: @Jukely tells you which concerts to see and which friends to see them with | VentureBeat http://ow.ly/qBwNj     
    
    
    My Conversation with entrepreneur/journalist Shane Snow of Contently.com http://bit.ly/eEgkPG  discuss b-model in depth, team, silicon alley    
    
    
    @msuster weighs in on debate: What’s The Real Deal With AngelList? http://ow.ly/444YI    
    
    
    must read: @msuster weighs in on debate: What’s The Real Deal With AngelList? http://ow.ly/4455K    
    
    
    My Conversation on Venture Studio w/ Shane Snow of www.contently.com http://ow.ly/4458O @shanesnow (entrepreneur, journo, designer, writer)    
    
    
    cool product! Foundry Group Puts $500,000 Into Attachments.me http://ow.ly/46Oia congrats @bfeld    
    
    
    RT The latest news and analysis from China's perspective, read Edward Nigro is @TheChinaInsider http://thechinainsider.com/blog/    
    
    
    Primate Makes Daring Escape From Cage, Becomes Entrepreneur: Society Uneasy, Mainstream Press Obscures His True Origins http://bit.ly/fXlZOl    
    
    
    good clear-eyed insights here: The ridiculous Vivek Wadhwa furore and the new Boston Tea Party - Fred Destin http://ow.ly/476Hz    
    
    
    R u in a partnership?: "We value trust, respect, and consensus. We never vote. We don't exercise vetos. We don't yell."  http://ow.ly/47Rp7    
    
    
    terrific opportunity w/great folks: RT @bsiscovick: RT @infoarbitrage: Please check out / RT @iaventures Summer internship bit.ly/fKjKFJ $    
    
    
    New Post: Primate Makes Daring Escape From Cage, Becomes Entrepreneur: Society Uneasy, Press Obscures His True Origins http://ow.ly/48xvg    
    
    
    My conversation on Venture Studio w/ Mark Loranger of Square 1 Bank http://bit.ly/g18r1O ie. for entrepreneurs: what is a venture bank? etc    
    
    
    Skype Founder To Students: Don’t Follow The Obvious Path - Venture Capital Dispatch - WSJ http://ow.ly/4d6lW    
    
    
    agree with @zamland: Jim Plush's Blog - This may be the best resume I have ever seen http://awe.sm/5GlAl  wow... $$    
    
    
    Vinny Vacanti, CEO of Yipit on the odyssey of a first-time entrepreneur & learning to code http://bit.ly/hDhvEH @vacanti @jdmoran    
    
    
    ff# @vacanti @robgo @drewconway @makdchou @amandahesser @to2 @chartio @armbrusting @jehangirirani @markloranger @stellajordy @joshrweinstein    
    
    
    congrats @benjlerer "Thrillist Melds Editorial Content and Commerce" - NYTimes.com http://ow.ly/4iBc6    
    
    
    Part II of conversation w/ @vacanti CEO of Yipit: "Traction is King", learning to code, and more http://ow.ly/4jtEv cc @jdmoran @hackernews    
    
    
    cool post from @cdixon  MIT is a national treasure - cdixon's posterous http://ow.ly/4kE6z    
    
    
    A must read: New Rules for the New Internet Bubble « Steve Blank http://ow.ly/4kG8v    
    
    
    FF# @nikoliaA @to2 @arorasaurabh @vacanti @jacobbrody @jjbesnainou @dwhittemore @stellajordy @joshrweinstein @robgo @amandahesser    
    
    
    great piece: Is There a New Technology Bubble? Ben Horowitz Doesn't Think So. | Ben Horowitz | Voices | AllThingsD http://ow.ly/4n4Ua    
    
    
    Conversation with @to2 Trevor Owens: Entrepreneur, Super-Connector, Community Organizer http://bit.ly/gKFO27 @venturestudio @samantha_smith    
    
    
    My convo w/ @STELLAjordy CEO re: STELLAService, biz model & Steve Nash/Consiglieri's investment @MikeDuda @SteveNash http://ow.ly/4tseP    
    
    
    My convo w/ @joshrweinstein CEO YouAre.TV http://bit.ly/hw6aNU we talk chess, startups & his wild entrepreneurial journey @peterthiel    
    
    
    great day today chatting with @davetisch @bhargreaves and @nickseguin cc: @venturestudio    
    
    
    convo w/ @davetisch about the epic @techstars NYC DemoDay & behind the scenes stuff cc: @fakedavetisch @bfeld @davidcohen http://ow.ly/4DkcB    
    
    
    for left coast: @davetisch talks about epic @techstars NYC DemoDay & behind scenes stuff cc: @bfeld @davidcohen http://ow.ly/4DLOn    
    
    
    @fakedavetisch ok. Standby    
    
    
    Thrillist CEO @benjlerer tells story of @thrillist on @VentureStudio + acquiring @jackthreads & talks @lererventures http://ow.ly/4H6WR    
    
    
    smart, practical & in that sense, a "cutting-edge" move by a university.... Joichi Ito Named Head of M.I.T. Media Lab  http://ow.ly/4I407    
    
    
    Y Combinator Success Leads To Copycats, Incubator Raiders - Venture Capital Dispatch - WSJ http://ow.ly/4I4Ev    
    
    
    My convo on @venturestudio w/ the terrific @jonathanglick CEO of @sulia http://ow.ly/4LYdV    
    
    
    .@reecepacheco @jehangirirani  yes reece u were on the @davetisch interview: http://ow.ly/4NsQC come on the show in person next time    
    
    
    @fakedavetisch ok. Sent the interview questions over just now!    
    
    
    bravo to this guy for writing a much needed piece on this!: The Next 10 Years Will Be Great For Both Founders And VCs http://ow.ly/4PNZD    
    
    
    some of VC @mattcharris thoughts re: @BankSimple, @OnDeckCapital & fintech as told to me on @venturestudio http://ow.ly/4SCyi    
    
    
    well said: "You’re not entitled to anything. Hustle for everything you’re worth"  The Startup Foundry http://ow.ly/4TM31    
    
    
    Watching live feed of Social Media Weekend http://bit.ly/socmediaweekend, track chatter at #smwknd or http://bit.ly/smwkndhash yes! @sree    
    
    
    @2carvin speaking w/ @sree now....  Watching live feed of Social Media Weekend http://bit.ly/socmediaweekend #smwknd    
    
    
    .@acarvin says "never forget there is no longer any such thing as an audience" @sree @emilybell @NYT_jenpreston    
    
    
    .@NYT_JenPreston where do we find andy's curated twitter lists? #smwknd can someone post?    
    
    
    blog post: 5 qualities of great entrepreneurs: http://ow.ly/4UZBp    
    
    
    VID: So what's the Kauffman FDN @KauffmanFDN all about? My convo w/ @nickseguin Mgr Entrepreneurship @venturestudio    
    
    
    Mashable Video Interview: Inside Tips from Entrepreneurs and Investors http://bit.ly/e20DFB    
    
    
    So, You Think You Have to Deal With A**holes? Think Again http://ow.ly/5Jyzk    
    
    
    cool new fashion startup- great founders: Point, Click, Shoot — a New Site by Editors for Editors - Media News - WWD.com http://ow.ly/5OAiH    
    
    
    @MikeBrownJr @nickgiglia @reecepacheco @softtechvc @stacyspikes @vacanti @zamland @Arrington @bhargreaves @dwhittemore @ffventure @kprentiss    
    
    
    the terrific @therunthrough team covered on Mashable: Private Site Connects Fashion Designers & Editors for Shoots http://ow.ly/5R72z    
    
    
    POST: An Entrepreneur's Commandment: Do What Thou Lovest -  http://ow.ly/5Rghs (was reminded of this today)    
    
    
    solid read from @sheynkman When do VCs make mistakes? - Passionate Intensity http://ow.ly/5UB8O    
    
    
    ff# @kloutperks @john_frankel @vikvenkat @dwhittemore @cliffpavlovic @sheynkman @madamian @echo_nyc @leemhoffman @jfernandez @ebellity    
    
    
    ff# @amandahesser @jehangirirani @schlaf @bpmilne @shanesnow @kevinbluer @coderkid    
    
    
    