Amazon Local deals service now developing mobile app for iOS/Android/web http://goo.gl/8D8CO  arch built w/ AWS, RubyOnRails, SOA....    
    
    
    .@PayPal and .@Amazon poised to scoop up the #NFC payments market http://goo.gl/0V33M  will they succeed before the others catch up?    
    
    
    The next wave of cellphone location-based services http://goo.gl/916xo  location-based playlists and phone settings, and more....    
    
    
    Amazon Local deals service now developing mobile app for iOS/Android/web http://goo.gl/8D8CO   .@groupon look out! .@Amazon is coming....    
    
    
    @RotaryJerusalem can you post a map link (msg me to ask how) to kalaniot or other nice sites near Beit Shemesh and Emek HaEla? #beitshemesh    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Do you see the FB Messenger app? Android market on my new S2 on Orange doesn't seem to have it.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Definitely awesome, still in the stage of playing and figuring out what's useful.    
    
    
    @orange_israel @orangeil Why can't I see the new Facebook Messenger app in Android market?    
    
    
    @rabbisedley Curious about the caffeine pill you mentioned taking before Tisha B'Av was it time-release? how didn't it effect you at night?    
    
    
    Great article on recent Jewish charity organizations - http://qurl.com/9mwd1 #fb    
    
    
    I know this happens in San Francisco but here too? RT @triskerrebbe: Big wedding tonight in bet shemesh reb motta frank with rav cheshin    
    
    
    @noahroth If someone's going to label chometz KFP on Passover, why not label it that way all year round?    
    
    
    Nokia researchers publish book on NanoTechnology for Future Mobile Devices - looks very cool...  http://qurl.com/w4gvg  #fb    
    
    
    Nokia researchers publish book on NanoTechnology for Future Mobile Devices - looks very cool... http://qurl.com/vy1zb #Nokia #nanotech    
    
    
    BLOG reply to .@cultofmac claim that Apple's done inventing new devices: Why he's wrong & inventions in the pipeline http://goo.gl/IXzLf     
    
    
    @triskerrebbe "big time" chassidic marriages between two men?    
    
    
    BLOG .@cultofmac claims that #Apple is done inventing new devices: Why he's wrong & inventions in the pipeline http://goo.gl/IXzLf     
    
    
    @triskerrebbe chas veshalom i was surprised you posted a chasana of Motta Frank and Rav Cheshin. Did you mean their children?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld have you seen http://goo.gl/nn9d9     
    
    
    @HilzFuld works for me - goo.gl/nn9d9    
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber @mikeage:Mishpacha article this week or last week's?  I don't see it.    
    
    
    Anyone in #Israel had #GPS not work near the Kineret? Tues my phone GPS worked til Beit Shan but not on the Kineret .@waze .@waze_il    
    
    
    @sashashabb Saw your msg re GPS not working in Israel, was it near the Kineret?    
    
    
    @sashashabb Sorry, can't help you, I just had mine work everywhere but near the Kineret.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Interesting, I actually used to do DB dataset queries for analysis, but the Netherlands would be a big move....    
    
    
    BLOG: .@google buying .@motorola - the 3 C's of convergence, competition & core business http://goo.gl/nPDJo     
    
    
    BLOG .@cultofmac claims #Apple is done inventing new devices: Why he's wrong & some innovations in the pipeline http://goo.gl/kOA67     
    
    
    #Apple's focus on content consumption devices, and why they're not done innovating & reinventing them http://goo.gl/kOA67     
    
    
    @triskerrebbe I suggest that you have kavod choson ve'kalah to say whose wedding it is not it's the wedding of this father and that father    
    
    
    Anyone in #beitshemesh know what happened in #rbsb tonight?  #betshemesh    
    
    
    @RotaryJerusalem Can you reply with the name in Hebrew? can't find it on maps. To tweet a map find on Google maps and click "link"    
    
    
    @RotaryJerusalem May have found it - here's a link - http://qurl.com/v6rd1 Is that an area you'd recommend?    
    
    
    @noahroth maybe the reduction in emergency kugels is the reason for lots of earthquakes lately?    
    
    
    Passover shopping meets the Dubai assassination videos - http://qurl.com/y9rqf - great!  #fb    
    
    
    Passover shopping meets the Dubai assassination videos - http://qurl.com/y9rqf - great!  #israel #passover #pesach #jewish #dubai    
    
    
    Tech for media consumption: How Bill Gates was right but wrong and #Apple was right and right http://goo.gl/7q4is  #microsoft    
    
    
    BLOG: Why we should've predicted Steve Jobs retirement, and why we should expect more #Apple innovations soon: http://goo.gl/0NfsX     
    
    
    Where's the world's outrage? More rockets shot from settlement-free #Gaza http://qurl.com/ys3s2 worker killed http://qurl.com/g94gb #fb    
    
    
    BLOG Why we should've predicted Steve Jobs retirement, and why we should expect more #Apple innovations soon: http://goo.gl/0NfsX  #fb    
    
    
    BLOG Why we should've predicted Steve Jobs retirement, and why we should expect more #Apple innovations soon: http://goo.gl/0NfsX     
    
    
    Fascinating new movement to "reboot" by disconnecting for the Jewish Sabbath http://qurl.com/h315w #fb    
    
    
    Fascinating new movement to "reboot" by disconnecting for the Jewish Sabbath http://qurl.com/h315w #jewish #sabbath #reboot #shabbat    
    
    
    .@TheRealSpaf @ShlomoArgamon prefer Encyclopedia Britanica or cave drawings? RT future designed by Apple&Microsoft http://bit.ly/pPWvSq     
    
    
    2.5 yr old argues for seeing Bob the Builder on computer b4 her bath saying "I need computer now, I need to work" @noahroth    
    
    
    A few weeks with my#GalaxySII makes me even more convinced Samsung has no worries from Goog/Moto http://goo.gl/C0zo2  great phone!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Maybe people have nothing to say....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Ah, many people don't have instant notification, I never used to until I started using Twitter more after founding Grizzly    
    
    
    Interesting http://twitpic.com/6dxxmg  @HilzFuld @patphelan EMAIL incl all POP&IMAP not just Exchange, maybe some Yahoo/Hotmail too, right?    
    
    
    Yo Beit Shemesh folks where can I buy diskonkeys cheap? @HilzFuld @noahroth please fwd to whoever might know thanks!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld thx    
    
    
    @noahroth the way kids go through diskonkeys maybe i should look into wholesale....  thanks!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Doesn't always last me all day, but that may be when I'm using heavy data services etc    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I think fine, certainly no problem I've noticed, but I haven't looked. I'll let you next time it sits idle.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld But I'm also experimenting with some data-heavy apps eg that poll GPS every little while, so may not be representative    
    
    
    @HilzFuld "average" days I'm fine, down to 10-15% when I go to bed. Non-average I use a car-charger etc    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Sorry, that wasn't clear. Days w/ low use I'm down to 10-15% by nighttime, no charger during day. Heavier use days I use charger.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Ya, very happy. Orange. Considered Milestone for the keyboard but opted for 2.3 and gyro and ghz etc    
    
    
    @HilzFuld np    
    
    
    Great article by Charles Krauthammer http://qurl.com/mzhch    - #israel #palestinians #obama #peace #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld zero violence is easy when the nationwide protests really have very little to protest about    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @MitchSchneider priced too low-add pix 2gether & price 10x for the really desperate RT gonna be a billionaire http://bit.ly/pVky7S     
    
    
    @SamsungMobile Does the S Pen work on a Galaxy S II? Can they be bought seperately?    
    
    
    .@SamsungMobile Does the S Pen work on a Galaxy S II? Can they be bought seperately?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld In their promotions they refer to it as the S Pen.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld http://goo.gl/3OB7C     
    
    
    Q for @facebook on #Android on own wall I click camera and am asked photo or video, group wall no video option. Why? #facebook #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth extra-strong, not indestructable. They're both Motorola and through Orange, QWERTY is Milestone2 tough I think is Defy    
    
    
    .@SamsungMobile Can S-Pen be used w/ Galaxy S II ? Is the pen & apps to be standard new feature? I hope so! http://goo.gl/XfdTl     
    
    
    Amazon and PayPal are going to scoop up the NFC mobile payments biz http://goo.gl/aagCC  #amazon @amazon @paypal    
    
    
    .@IncMagazine @Zagat What's the "huh" re Google/Zagat? If u want a good restaurant, would u use plain @Google, Facebook or Google+Zagat?    
    
    
    @noahroth @HilzFuld Noah that's the rumor from http://goo.gl/TEBoL  et al but not believed that seriously    
    
    
    Re the burkas @HilzFuld @noahroth Once saw one w/o eye holes walking up steps, would've been funny if it wasn't so horribly sad    
    
    
    @noahroth Like the phrase anticrastinating, and me too.  Proof that any word can be verbed.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld saw them, that's what I was commenting on!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I know it's really freaky. (My comment was about the steps part) Are the really machmer ones made of wool?    
    
    
    See how #Apple will use logs of iPhone user locations to improve local search: http://goo.gl/QslES  HINT: It's based on #PlaceBase    
    
    
    See what #Apple Placebase team is working on: improving local search by analyzing iPhone location logs http://goo.gl/QslES     
    
    
    See how #Apple will use logs of iPhone user locations to improve local search: http://goo.gl/QslES  HINT: It's based on #PlaceBase    
    
    
    Looking for a #mehadrin #pesach #restaurant in tel aviv anyone know about Prime Grill or any others? #telaviv #passover    
    
    
    Letter to the Editor #17 in the New York Times http://goo.gl/pxub3  #Israel    
    
    
    Whoh! Austrian gov't official tells it like it is about the Turks....  http://qurl.com/4w4hl ...  commentary on Muslim extremists #fb    
    
    
    Palestinians make clear Israel's Gaza war succeeded in reducing rockets against civilians: http://qurl.com/5rfmq #fb    
    
    
    Palestinians make clear Israel's Gaza war succeeded in reducing rockets against civilians: http://qurl.com/5rfmq #israel #terrorism    
    
    
    A new reason for Jews to stop smoking:  http://qurl.com/2nv41 #fb    
    
    
    Palestinian supposedly shot by Israel not dead after all http://qurl.com/dwcmr #fb    
    
    
    Palestinian supposedly shot by Israel not dead after all http://qurl.com/dwcmr #israel #palestinian #hoax    
    
    
    @weissthinking Some speculate that Anthony Goldstein is meant to be a Jewish student at Hogwarts http://qurl.com/n2h9q    
    
    
    @Patheos @thdpr @gleamchaser My book Harry Potter &Torah is http://qurl.com/5l7vl also see http://qurl.com/mmdwp http://qurl.com/4l1fy    
    
    
    @thdpr glad to hear you like the book! Happy to hear any comments...    
    
    
    Very interesting article about issues in the religious world http://qurl.com/ls8rl by the author of http://qurl.com/sp4ny    
    
    
    Nice article http://qurl.com/hrm2l titled Yom HaShoah, Harry Potter, and Reality TV #holocaust #israel #harrypotter    
    
    
    RIP Steve Jobs, the man who transformed every generation's technology from geeky to user-friendly. http://goo.gl/uzZqY     
    
    
    @Mivasair @BoycottAhava do you even TRY for truth? 15 seconds in Google shows Beit Shemesh WAY within green line http://goo.gl/X9J5h     
    
    
    @BoycottAhava @Mivasair OK great, I saw your tweet thru search & didn't see the thread. Isn't Ahava at Dead Sea also in pre-67 Israel?    
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber Found Igeres HaRamban: http://qurl.com/m74gp (doc) & http://qurl.com/ghrjb & http://qurl.com/qyslq (web) note caveat learner    
    
    
    @noahroth FYI http://www.jerusalemkoshernews.com/2010/04/alert-concerning-%E2%80%98the-israel-whiskey-society%E2%80%99/    
    
    
    @zeevsavion Interested in talking have client who might want to talk. Please send contact info or e-mail krulwich@grizzlyanalytics.com    
    
    
    Intel acquiring gesture recognition hardware start-up InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp  big trend in chip-maker acquisitions    
    
    
    Intel acquires gesture recognition start-up, following on LBS start-up few weeks ago http://goo.gl/LwVNp  same trend as Qualcomm    
    
    
    Intel following QualComm acquiring gesture recognition hardware start-up InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp     
    
    
    Intel acquiring second Israeli start-up in one month http://goo.gl/LwVNp     
    
    
    Second big Israeli success in gesture recognition InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp     
    
    
    Intel acquiring gesture recognition hardware start-up InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp  as QualComm did in July    
    
    
    Nokia shows flexible phone http://goo.gl/NenIR  Grizzly Analytics already analyzed the underlying nanotechnology http://goo.gl/nvE5b     
    
    
    Nokia's Kinect "bendy phone" prototype shows nanotechnology getting closer http://goo.gl/nvE5b  could Nokia be back to innovation?    
    
    
    Nokia returning to true market-leading innovation? http://goo.gl/nvE5b  Windows phones may be grerat, but "bendy" may be game-changing    
    
    
    @noahroth learn to like vodka, straight from the freezer. good with herring on a cracker, even better w/ pickles    
    
    
    @noahroth I didn't mention acquired taste, I mentioned good taste.    
    
    
    @noahroth great line, why don't you use it a few more times?    
    
    
    @noahroth I've learned to be amused by you....    
    
    
    Nokia back to market-leading innovation? http://goo.gl/nvE5b  Windows phones may be great but "bendy" nanotech may be game-changing    
    
    
    Intel follows QualComm, acquires gesture recognition hardware start-up InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp     
    
    
    Intel follows QualComm, acquires gesture recognition hardware start-up InVision BioMetrics http://goo.gl/LwVNp     
    
    
    Nokia back to market-leading innovation? http://goo.gl/nvE5b  "Bendy" nanotech will be game-changing more than great Windows phones    
    
    
    @noahroth re Halperin try Zenni Optical - save a fortune compared w/ Israeli places http://goo.gl/cAXYa     
    
    
    Intel opens research in computational intelligence & sensor interpretation http://goo.gl/Yghfp  follows recent gesture recognition buy    
    
    
    Intel new research in computational intelligence & sensor interpretation http://goo.gl/Yghfp  follows recent gesture recognition acquisition    
    
    
    Intel more R&D in Israel: new research in computational intelligence & sensor interpretation http://goo.gl/Yghfp  after several acquisitions    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Doesn't make sense. Didn't happen to my recent blog post on G+. Does it happen for other blogs or just appboy?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Did you set your blog to support FB open graph protocol? Curious if it happens if that's off. (will explain reasoning l8er)    
    
    
    Intel new R&D in computational intelligence & sensor interpretation http://goo.gl/Yghfp  soon after gesture recognition acquisition    
    
    
    @noahroth Try redoing your will....    
    
    
    @noahroth Yep these things just bring out the rosy side of life!    
    
    
    @mikeeisenberg @Integr8ideas there's also a need for experience to succeed. Successful startups almost always have experience in founders    
    
    
    @thdpr Saw yr Tweet re Harry Potter and the Torah - glad you think its fascinating. What other book did you mean was similar?    
    
    
    @KosherCamera what makes your camera kosher?    
    
    
    Articles on Shavuot relating to Harry Potter themes http://qurl.com/gndg6 #fb    
    
    
    Articles on Shavuot relating to Harry Potter themes http://qurl.com/gndg6    #judaism #shavuos #shavuot #jewish #torah    
    
    
    Why pico-projectors & eyeglass displays are coming soon, and why they'll continue the trend Apple started. http://goo.gl/a9k3x     
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber OK I emailed you the Igeres HaKodesh text from a disk collection that someone I know has. Hope it helps!    
    
    
    Nokia differentiates itself with Bluetooth-based indoor positioning, but Google has a patent in that http://goo.gl/wZuGu     
    
    
    .@Nokia thought indoor location by Bluetooth was different from Google indoor maps but #Google has a patent in it... http://goo.gl/wZuGu     
    
    
    I just voted for Waze as "Most Useful Mobile App" #MashableAwards http://on.mash.to/pbWZnh     
    
    
    Nokia uses Bluetooth for indoor GPS. But guess who owns a patent in this? Google! http://goo.gl/wZuGu  @Nokia @google #motorola    
    
    
    Nokia counters Google by using bluetooth for indoor GPS. But guess who owns a patent in this? Google! http://goo.gl/wZuGu     
    
    
    @HilzFuld re FB/path nah FB won't buy for users, and afaik path has no unique tech, can be done in FB by new privacy settings & UI    
    
    
    @HilzFuld still    
    
    
    Indoor Location Technology: 104 page report details R&D at major companies & start-ups http://goo.gl/KhOFP     
    
    
    Qualcomm has strong research in indoor location technology! Soon to be in their chips? http://goo.gl/KhOFP  #qualcomm @qualcomm    
    
    
    Google released indoor maps first, but Microsoft & Nokia have stronger research in the pipeline http://goo.gl/KhOFP     
    
    
    Who would guess BMW has such sophisticated R&D in mobile indoor location? http://goo.gl/KhOFP  One of the co's to use phone sensors    
    
    
    Interesting look at newspaper photography by my cousin the NY Times photographer http://qurl.com/5r7hf #fb    
    
    
    Qualcomm and CSR are both working on hardware support for indoor location on smartphones! http://goo.gl/KhOFP     
    
    
    @HilzFuld sorry I use a FB app daily, and love Android's "share via" integration in pix etc    
    
    
    @HilzFuld ah then I definitely agree about apps on fb (except games, which I can't stand but which lots play)    
    
    
    Samsung, Microsoft, Google, RIM, Qualcomm & CSR all working on indoor location for cellphones! http://goo.gl/aUqQ3  See research details    
    
    
    @menduck @HilzFuld re indoor location & privacy some methods are fully client-side like GPS not necessarily invasive http://goo.gl/aUqQ3     
    
    
    Report on Indoor Location Positioning Technology now at all major report resellers http://goo.gl/3Ncva  Grizzly Analytics    
    
    
    Indoor Location report 104 pages detailing research by @SamsungMobile @Microsoft @Blackberry @Nokia #Apple & others http://goo.gl/aUqQ3     
    
    
    @HilzFuld what do you mean keep them alive? remember whatever you do for your truly important posts :-) others will do for theirs :-(    
    
    
    @HilzFuld That goes back to what I said - should every blog message be retweeted forever? Besides your charm what makes your posts live?    
    
    
    @hoogsteder @HilzFuld Happy to discuss anytime - recent Indoor Location report or anything else http://grizzlyanalytics.blogspot.com     
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber did you get the e-mail I sent with the Igeres HaKodesh text in DOC form?  Hope it helps....    
    
    
    Forbes article looks at what's coming soon in Indoor Location on mobile http://goo.gl/jkT8L  Discusses Google Microsoft Nokia RIM & more    
    
    
    Forbes blog quotes my analysis of Indoor Location tech by Google Microsoft Nokia RIM Samsung Qualcomm & more http://goo.gl/jkT8L     
    
    
    @gldmeier @yetevlev 2 b precise the kanoyim in rbs are breakaways from eida, even the eida has had pashkevilim against them    
    
    
    @gldmeier @yetevlev They're all Jews too, and all Orthodox Jews, and all white shirt wearers.  Being precise matters esp when blaming.    
    
    
    @noahroth I always push my wife to shop in stores that have "husband couches." Add coffee and I'd surrender my credit card....    
    
    
    @gldmeier @yetevlev From a few years ago when a round of violence in RBS-B was starting: http://twitpic.com/1shaju  #beitshemesh #rbs    
    
    
    Video of so-called "peace activists" attacking Israeli soldiers http://qurl.com/q7vwm clearly the goal wasn't to get supplies to Gaza #fb    
    
    
    I think it's my letter 15 in the NY Times http://qurl.com/cf21s amazing how basic facts haven't been in the US press #nytimes #israel    
    
    
    Head of Eida Chareidit blasts writers of pashkevilim (signs on the wall) http://qurl.com/fyszd incredible! #eida #israel #fb    
    
    
    Another Google acquisition: Invite Media http://qurl.com/h85ym #google #invite #media #acquisition    
    
    
    Fascinating set of predictions made in 1931 about life in 2011 http://qurl.com/855m3 what would you predict for life in 2091?  #fb    
    
    
    Fascinating set of predictions made in 1931 about life in 2011 http://qurl.com/855m3 what would you predict for life in 2091? #FB    
    
    
    Mobile Indoor Location: 104 pages of R&D details of Apple, Microsoft, Google, Samsung, RIM & more http://goo.gl/3X3ct     
    
    
    Indoor location: Very few start-ups working on next-generation sensor-based approaches. http://goo.gl/3X3ct   See this 104-page report    
    
    
    Indoor Location R&D by @SamsungMobile @Microsoft @Blackberry @Nokia #Apple @qualcomm & more - http://goo.gl/3X3ct  - GPS coming indoors!    
    
    
    Excellent article on the flotilla saga in Israel - http://qurl.com/yp54f   -  -  #israel #fb #flotilla #gaza    
    
    
    Another great article on the Gaza saga http://qurl.com/h3yq7 -   #fb    
    
    
    Another great article on the Gaza saga http://qurl.com/h3yq7 -   #israel #gaza #hamas #flotilla    
    
    
    Flotilla people supported 9/11 attack against US and Nazis against Jews - http://qurl.com/66cs5 - #fb #flotilla #israel #gaza    
    
    
    @Hoosen_Essack @IsraelMFA @krulwich @r7y6 @jackgunkone @Amgadmuh Intl law says blockade runners can be boarded. Youre on side of terrorists    
    
    
    @r7y6 Israel tried when it withdrew from Gaza & planned future withdrawals, but the Palestinians chose to shoot rockets at Israeli towns    
    
    
    @Hoosen_Essack @IsraelMFA I'm on side that withdrew from Gaza and tried peace, but the Palestinians chose rockets at Israeli civilians    
    
    
    @Hoosen_Essack @r7y6 Only after enduring thousands of rockets at civilians. would anyone else wait that long before self-defense?    
    
    
    Reuters cropped activist weapons out of Flotilla photos http://qurl.com/6ymcz Like they edited Lebanon war photos #israel #flotilla #fb    
    
    
    @IsraelMFA Israel's blockade is fully legal http://qurl.com/2mnqq and Palestinians can stop it by stopping rockets at Israeli civilians    
    
    
    @Hoosen_Essack @r7y6 Easy 4 u 2 say it wasn't self defense you didn't live thru 1000s of missiles shot at Sderot & other towns b4 the war    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Curious whether you've seen feature breakdown of multi-touch: zoom, twist, pinch, etc, and who has what (eg not all MT is equal)    
    
    
    @HilzFuld anyone have list of MT features (eg pinch twist etc) and which phones have which? Q is whetherPalm & Android have same MT as Apple    
    
    
    @HilzFuld re Galaxy S wait in line... :-) it's supposed to be nice, I've seen it but haven't used it yet either    
    
    
    Google Maps added Indoor Location, but Microsoft, Samsung, RIM, Qualcomm and more are reserching doing it better! http://goo.gl/VdCew     
    
    
    Anyone catch whether the front-facing camera will have APIs for 3rd party apps? #iphone4 #wwdc    
    
    
    I would LOVE to have effective cellphone reminders based on my location. Is 2012 the year they take off? http://goo.gl/Qrfk9     
    
    
    Cellphone maps indoors - soon it won't just be Google! http://goo.gl/tttFn   - See who else is taking location based services indoors    
    
    
    Letter published in the Washington Post http://qurl.com/4hmcq re Helen Thomas's hateful comments on Israel and Palestinians    #fb    
    
    
    First cameraphones imitated cameras, then improved on them. Here comes the real transformation! http://goo.gl/2zrgx   GroupShot    
    
    
    Definitely the clearest statement on Middle East I've seen http://qurl.com/r82m5 (parody, but on the mark)  #fb    
    
    
    Definitely the clearest statement on Middle East I've seen http://qurl.com/r82m5 (parody, but on the mark)  #israel #gaza #hamas    
    
    
    Australian newspaper quotes Palestinian Autonomy and Egypt both wanting Gaza blockade NOT to stop http://qurl.com/qkbp6 #israel #gaza    
    
    
    Just saw this great article by Dennis Prager http://qurl.com/2nbc5 an interesting read on a lot of levels....       #fb    
    
    
    Just saw this great article by Dennis Prager http://qurl.com/2nbc5 an interesting read on a lot of levels....       #israel #jewish    
    
    
    @Templesmith Not sure how Harry Potter and Owls fit the Jewish holocaust, but you might enjoy http://qurl.com/3k2s2 excerpt from my book    
    
    
    @KatePlusRainbow cute line re Harry Potter turbans when writing Harry Potter&Torah http://qurl.com/yr9j6 didn't think about head coverings    
    
    
    Rav Steinman says that chareidi school selectivity is "geiva geiva geiva" http://qurl.com/361zt    
    
    
    A different angle on the Emanuel school dispute: chareidim turning dati leumi? http://qurl.com/gfntb    
    
    
    @noahroth which link broken?  both I posted work for me.    
    
    
    @noahroth www.cross-currents.com/archives/2010/06/20/declaration-of-the-american-moetzes-regarding-emmanuel/comment-page-1/#comment-384813    
    
    
    @noahroth np curious what u think re my comment    
    
    
    @noahroth doesn't really change the point    
    
    
    Who remembers Windows 1.0?  I was at Microsoft then, the game was how many clocks could run before slowing down http://qurl.com/gtqzs #fb    
    
    
    NEW REPORT: Indoor Location Services: must-read for retail and other site managers http://goo.gl/xZ2ol  what u need to know & do NOW    
    
    
    New report on Indoor Location Services sold in Korea by LandH http://goo.gl/WRniv  must-read for store and site managers    
    
    
    @noahroth @YUTorah re Harry Potter and Torah I'll listen later but imitation is the highest form of flattery http://goo.gl/QqmSb     
    
    
    New report tells owners of stores, chains, malls, airports, casinos, exhibition centers, conference centers, and other…http://lnkd.in/h4mYfZ     
    
    
    Folks liked our report on indoor location tech http://goo.gl/Cc2t1  so much that we wrote one for business people http://goo.gl/xZ2ol     
    
    
    Blog article on latest news in indoor location positioning from Google and ByteLight http://goo.gl/ZoVrP  Lots of other related R&D!    
    
    
    Indoor Location technology you can use at your store or other location! Over 20 companies profiled http://goo.gl/xZ2ol     
    
    
    BLOG: Predicting the WOW at #MWC 2012 - http://goo.gl/B652a  - besides lots of slightly better phones, what will WOW us?    
    
    
    Indoor cellphone location apps will come soon to Target Walmart Sears Cosco ToysRUs malls - see how here: http://goo.gl/xZ2ol     
    
    
    What will WOW you at #MWC 2012? http://goo.gl/B652a  Things more innovative than slightly better phones! @gsma #mwc12    
    
    
    Hot from #MWC - cellphone projectors! http://goo.gl/0cmfk  Not just for business use anymore! See 3 products & a component....    
    
    
    Hot at #MWC cellphone projectors! http://goo.gl/0cmfk  What would u do with 1? Details of #Samsung Beam, Aiptek for iPhone, ST prototype    
    
    
    @noahroth I'm in Barcelona at MWC best to email til end of week. Or talk after 10pm.    
    
    
    Cute ad about the history of tablets http://goo.gl/p47zu #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth Next you'll be a fan of social events with mechitzas? You think this story could never happen in MO circles?    
    
    
    Projector phones at MWC- love em! http://goo.gl/Hbl5h  Not just for biz, for movies games & media @samsungmobile @ST_World @BTendo    
    
    
    @noahroth Yes I got it but haven't gotten through the backlog yet... tomorrow OK?    
    
    
    my book http://qurl.com/yr9j6 explains: Harry Potter trailer Jewish mystical themes http://qurl.com/2tlfj @faithfulnews @kabbalah_hive    
    
    
    Indoor Location Services: What retail industry managers need to know to prepare for this new technology before your...: http://lnkd.in/jZ4PtF     
    
    
    All the new indoor location technologies being researched, and all the new companies bringing indoor location to...: http://lnkd.in/ZDSzFF     
    
    
    See @nokia indoor location technology at MWC http://goo.gl/dfroO  very good but relies on BLE & beacons - Grizzly Analytics gives details    
    
    
    See @nokia indoor location tech at MWC http://goo.gl/dfroO  Grizzly Analytics gives all the details @nokconv @nokiaresearch @navteq    
    
    
    See most accurate indoor location positioning & read tech details that make it hard 2 bring 2 mass market http://goo.gl/dfroO     
    
    
    @HilzFuld @Nokia Nah once you're going Nokia/WP7 you should go for the 808 PureView. At MWC it made my Galaxy S2 camera pale....    
    
    
    @noahroth agree re homeless hotspots. articles called it degrading but I don't see it and seems that neither did they....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @galbrill which model is that? do you like it?    
    
    
    .@crunchdot Nokia haptic patent u tweeted just latest of long nanotech research incl skin based input & display http://goo.gl/KOI3l     
    
    
    .@ubergizmo Nokia haptic patent u tweeted just latest of long nanotech research incl skin based input & display http://goo.gl/KOI3l     
    
    
    .@UKMobileReview Nokia haptic patent u tweeted just latest of long nanotech research incl skin based input & display http://goo.gl/KOI3l     
    
    
    .@nokia__news Nokia haptic patent u tweeted just latest of long nanotech research incl skin based input & display http://goo.gl/KOI3l     
    
    
    @yishaym @FindBigMail Why is findbigmail different than sorting by size descending?    
    
    
    1.5 million apps does not make Twitter a strong ecosystem http://goo.gl/JQUEW  but read why it's still strong & where its likely to go    
    
    
    1.5 million @twitterapi apps doesn't make a strong ecosystem but a strong platform has a strong future http://goo.gl/JQUEW     
    
    
    Blog post http://goo.gl/JQUEW  Why 1.5 million @twitterapi apps doesn't make an ecosystem, and what this means for @twitter 's future    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld @Tim_Stevens except Apple's usually good at surprising us when we think we won't be surprised.... I bet more to come    
    
    
    @noahroth @shiraabel the quiet part is hard to believe....    
    
    
    Research report on indoor location positioning technology also available at Amazon http://goo.gl/X2WVR     
    
    
    1.5 million @twitterapi apps doesn't make @twitter a strong ecosystem but see predictions for strong future anyway http://goo.gl/JQUEW     
    
    
    See @nokia indoor location demo at MWC http://goo.gl/dfroO  great accuracy but needs Bluetooth 4 Low Energy @nokconv @nokiaresearch @navteq    
    
    
    @noahroth baloney, inhell is not having any contracts..... #countyourblessings    
    
    
    Think #apple should acquire @twitter ? Here's why not and what they'll acquire instead http://goo.gl/CIO1n  @applenws    
    
    
    Who #Apple should buy instead of @Twitter http://goo.gl/CIO1n  @ST_World @glopostech @p2ilabs @hzoinside @omekinteractive @softkinetic    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld Nokia patent u tweeted is latest of nanotech @nokiaresearch incl skin based display & touch & speakers http://goo.gl/KOI3l     
    
    
    Think #apple should acquire @twitter ? Here's why not and what they'll acquire instead http://goo.gl/CIO1n     
    
    
    GPS coming indoors to your store mall museum or hospital http://goo.gl/RKHMR  learn more before your competition    
    
    
    @noahroth re phishing emails no more than usual, which is still painful...    
    
    
    GPS coming indoors to your store mall museum or hospital http://goo.gl/RKHMR  learn more before your competition    
    
    
    Who #Apple should buy instead of @Twitter http://goo.gl/CIO1n  @ST_World @glopostech @p2ilabs @hzoinside @omekinteractive @softkinetic    
    
    
    See @nokia indoor location demo at MWC http://goo.gl/dfroO  great accuracy but needs Bluetooth 4 Low Energy @nokconv    
    
    
    See my video of Nokia's indoor location demo at MWC http://goo.gl/HQ677  See the links in the notes for more on indoor location    
    
    
    See my video of @Nokia indoor location demo at MWC http://goo.gl/HQ677  See links in notes on YouTube for more on indoor location    
    
    
    Daven urgently for Netanel Yosef ben Simcha Sima   #betshemesh #beitshemesh #israel    
    
    
    @EdgeOfNite yes they were, 2 daughters killed and one son in critical care burn unit. I still can't fathom the instant tragedy.    
    
    
    Innovative indoor location positioning based on motion sensing http://goo.gl/xGzHY  by Senion Lab demoed at MWC 2012    
    
    
    .@Nokia Also indoor http://goo.gl/jPOlg  Location based services are a key differentiator for us: http://nokia.ly/HNH4ND  #whereconf    
    
    
    Another MWC indoor location demo, this 1 based on motion sensor tech by Senion Lab http://goo.gl/xGzHY     
    
    
    Innovative indoor location positioning based on motion sensing http://goo.gl/xGzHY  by Senion Lab demoed at MWC 2012 #gps    
    
    
    Indoor GPS at MWC: Contrast @Nokia research http://goo.gl/jPOlg  with start-up Senion Lab http://goo.gl/xGzHY  both cool!#indoor #lbs    
    
    
    Interesting article responding to the NY Times editorial on Google a few days ago http://qurl.com/t5rff           #google #nytimes #fb    
    
    
    @BelzNies where exactly is the new Belz shul? is there a tisch leil Shabbos?    
    
    
    Israeli hospital treats Palestinian child w/ cancer, child's father kills Israelis http://qurl.com/y819g     #israel #fb    
    
    
    Discuss "Point Inside helps retailers push deals on aisle 3" with me on: http://gigaom.com/2012/04/10/point-inside-helps-retailers-push-deals-on-aisle-3/#comment-832586 … via @GigaOM    
    
    
    Lots of motion sensing at #ThinkNext12 umoove pointgrab & lots of kinect advances    
    
    
    New Microsoft mobile scripting language ON(x) is a real game-changer http://goo.gl/QkDyz  #ThinkNext2012 @MicrosoftRnDiL    
    
    
    New @Microsoft mobile scripting platform includes geofencing & motion analysis http://goo.gl/QkDyz  and it runs on #Android not just WP    
    
    
    New @Microsoft mobile scripting platform has geofencing & motion analysis http://goo.gl/QkDyz  runs on #Android @MicrosoftRnDiL    
    
    
    Anyone know where the ceremony Zochrim VeSharim at Binyanei Ha'uma is streaming?    
    
    
    @gillyarcht @taltalk Harry Potter certainly a source of Jewish lessons http://qurl.com/yr9j6    
    
    
    Nice indoor location article @jlendino Besides CSR many chip&mobile&startup cos http://goo.gl/xGzHY  http://goo.gl/jPOlg  @HilzFuld    
    
    
    @harrypotterpuot Happy you review Harry Potter & Torah http://qurl.com/yr9j6 but is it right to steal someone else's review from Amazon?    
    
    
    @noahroth Waze menus are confusing. No way to just enter address. But the traffic data and nav is great. I rec preloading maps in wifi.    
    
    
    Rumor #Apple to buy wireless/multimedia chips for #iPad from Israeli #DSPG - orig http://qurl.com/2k9zb Trans http://qurl.com/d1ldq #fb    
    
    
    @hyacinthblue there was 1 hogwarts student w/ name "Goldstein." And note no crosses just trees. You might like http://goo.gl/7DLSI    
    
    
    @noahroth  and that defense helped with @mrsroth ???    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Sorry the folks who gave you the galaxy would be a better address....    
    
    
    Excellent article from an A.I. prof (and father of murdered Jewish journalist) - discomfort from Israel criticism http://qurl.com/qd1c8  #fb    
    
    
    @krulwich testing something    
    
    
    Indoor location based on inertial motion sensing - in action! http://goo.gl/ot79k     
    
    
    @elizabethh_b re yr camper q if harry potter is Jewish: actor is Jewish and lots of Jewish lessons related http://qurl.com/zj4bd    
    
    
    Unfortunately a must-watch for people in Beit Shemesh http://goo.gl/beny5 illegal workers sneaking in for construction jobs here #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld In case you didn't see http://qurl.com/1b4l4 - almost 1st phone w/ features that others haven't had first    
    
    
    @Muqata News is saying 5 injured...    
    
    
    @HilzFuld if I could get one I'd be using it myself.... :-)    
    
    
    Israeli soldiers attacked by gunfire and mortars near Lebanon border, on the Israel side. Attack was by Lebanese Forces not Hezbola. #fb    
    
    
    Newly updated report on indoor location tech: now 156 pages of corp research & over 30 start-ups http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  lots of predictions    
    
    
    Over 30 start-ups with predicted acquisitions, all in indoor location tech http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  and active research at major mobile co's    
    
    
    What indoor location startups will be bought by Google Apple GroupOn Amazon EBay Facebook etc? Predictions here: http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    BLOG: Indoor location is growing and gaining speed! http://goo.gl/AlrFp  over 30 startups, R&D by major mobile & chip co's, and lots more    
    
    
    .@jonkingsbury Might be interested http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  Lots more than 5 working on indoor location!    
    
    
    .@AppleLevy #CSR included in 163-page new report on indoor location http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    @corbinball re indoor location you might be interested in http://goo.gl/AlrFp     
    
    
    @FWebConsulting re your tweet on indoor location you might be interested in http://goo.gl/AlrFp     
    
    
    .@gpsbusinessnews you might be interested in my new report http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  163 pages on indoor positioning tech    
    
    
    @andreSferraz @ubee_in you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  indoor location positioning report    
    
    
    @tourismcafe @zite you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  updated report on indoor location    
    
    
    @JonnyLeahan @gizmag re indoor GPS you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  163-page updated report on research & start-ups    
    
    
    @euroinnov_philg re indoor gps you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  covers Fraunhofer and over 50 others    
    
    
    @TheMapAddict #geolocation re indoor location you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  163 pages w/ all the approaches & companies    
    
    
    @GPS_For_Cars #GPS #InstantFollowBack you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7  re indoor GPS    
    
    
    @MobileLocation re indoor location you might be interested in http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    Interviewed in GPS BITES about new developments in indoor location http://goo.gl/uRcsy     
    
    
    Interviewed in GPS BITES on the subject of indoor location http://goo.gl/zm5pm     
    
    
    Very nice interview by @hilzfuld of Angry Birds creator - nice perspective on mobile OS platforms etc http://goo.gl/KA1G6    
    
    
    @HilzFuld my pleasure cool interview. interesting that by complementing ios he had the least to say of substance about them ("they lead")    
    
    
    Indoor location is growing and gaining speed! http://goo.gl/l4lnr  Read about growth in this new area...    
    
    
    Over 30 indoor location start-ups, up from less than 1/2 that 6 months ago http://goo.gl/l4lnr  M&A predictions http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    Indoor location growing! http://goo.gl/l4lnr  predicted startup acquisitions by @google #facebook @microsoft &more http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    @ashwinram Interesting Q re net neut is why they keep mentioning Android. Maybe issue is Android phones connecting to back-end servers?    
    
    
    re indoor positioning @gary_hayden there are lots of approaches being researched http://goo.gl/l4lnr  the area is taking off!    
    
    
    @selvan_tengy re indoor positioning there are lots of approaches being researched http://goo.gl/l4lnr  the indoor gps area is taking off!    
    
    
    @andreSferraz @ubee_in re indoor positioning there are lots of approaches being researched http://goo.gl/l4lnr  the area is taking off!    
    
    
    @rosho_tt re indoor positioning there are lots of approaches being researched http://goo.gl/l4lnr  the area is taking off!    
    
    
    @Aqeel_Qureshi lots of R&D about indoor location http://goo.gl/l4lnr  medical apps are a great use! #blind #axs #a11y #GPS #accessibility    
    
    
    Not just long term, steady opening means market values #Facebook roughly same as IPO did @mikeeisenberg (even if propped up a bit)    
    
    
    #NFC #shmeNFC read why I think @PayPal & @amazon will scoop up in-store payments http://goo.gl/tzhmq  Paypal showed this at #MWC    
    
    
    Google Trends http://goo.gl/dOAvD  confirms skyrocketing interest in indoor location. See all the R&D here http://goo.gl/Dz0C7     
    
    
    #Excel question: I have fields that contain links copied from a web page table. anyone know how a #formula can extract the link loc? #fb    
    
    
    SeekingAlpha: Facebook Investors: Stop Whining And Be Patient For Profit http://goo.gl/yRV9b  #facebook @facebook @seekingalpha    
    
    
    @noahroth @neyne @MarkKorman @gldmeier Clalit's centers in Sheinfeld & RBS-A & Big are all great. I'm thinking of switching to them.    
    
    
    Article on @seekingalpha: Facebook Investors: Stop Whining & Be Patient For Profit http://goo.gl/yRV9b  #facebook @facebook #FBipo #ipo    
    
    
    Thanks @mikeeisenberg for advice a year ago to check our @seekingalpha great platform to publish on http://goo.gl/yRV9b  #FBipo    
    
    
    Commented on: Facebook Investors: Stop Whining And Be Patient For Profit http://seekingalpha.com/a/d9ld     
    
    
    @noahroth let me know first, I'll catch you postal on video, could always use some entertainment #selflesscaringfriend    
    
    
    Nice NYT article I hadn't seen it @jmp_nyc but I had a better title http://goo.gl/yRV9b     
    
    
    Anyone know of New York kosher take-out meals that are 100% peanut-free?  #fb    
    
    
    Anyone know of New York kosher take-out meals that are 100% peanut-free? #newyork #kosher #peanut    
    
    
    Start-up M&A predictions: @GloposTech by @Google or @Microsoft, @Combain by @Facebook @4sq or @GroupOn. Learn why: http://goo.gl/uzwpZ     
    
    
    .@google Latitude now works indoors http://goo.gl/liK5u  indoor location is spreading! http://goo.gl/uzwpZ     
    
    
    @yechia heard from @HilzFuld I should talk to you about a US 3G SIM for an Israeli phone. TIA!    
    
    
    @YeChia I heard from Hillel Fuld you can suggest cellular data connectivity solution for visitor to the States.....    
    
    
    @yechia sorry for prev tweets, mistaken identity    
    
    
    @yechiya heard from @HilzFuld u can advise on 3g sim for vacation use in USA in Israeli Orange Galaxy s2    
    
    
    @Yechiya End of july for 2.5 weeks, want to look into options now, not to arrange in a hurry    
    
    
    @Yechiya Can't DM you if you're not following me. Happy to hear prices anytime. But first maybe description of what you offer?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld U used SIM card from Yechiya? I also want to be able to use Waze etc straight from airport. Good connectivity experience?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld 2G or 3G speed? Doesn't matter for most things I guess, but still want to plan accordingly.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld thanks have a gr8 flight back!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I can't DM you back if you're not following me! Anyway I read most Twitter via RSS, so I'm a reader even if I unfollow :-)    
    
    
    See @facebook 's next new directions in mobile http://goo.gl/0Mg3W  #facebook #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld welcome back!    
    
    
    .@Facebook Plan to Monetize Mobile thru Media http://goo.gl/9Ea6g  new article at @seekingalpha #facebook    
    
    
    Read @facebook 's plan to get into the music & video biz http://goo.gl/9Ea6g  based on report #facebook mobile plans http://goo.gl/RdntZ     
    
    
    Finally on Amazon: Rabbi David of Beit Shemesh write this book on Torah from Rav Soloveitchik http://goo.gl/aosZ2 #yutorah @yutorah    
    
    
    re FB @HilzFuld @noahroth go to your profile & click on EDIT for contact info then fix 2nd dropdown next to each addr. how's my profile?    
    
    
    @noahroth @HilzFuld maybe. or maybe some other goal. Not unlike Google's changing non-GMAIL Google accounts 2 years ago.    
    
    
    Rumors of @RIM splitting in 2 - here's why I predicted this in May 2011 and why it's a good idea http://goo.gl/nwuGG  #RIM    
    
    
    Must-see video especially for American progressives: Why are you protesting against Israel? http://goo.gl/mTmp4 #fb    
    
    
    Google may be the first big player to bring maps indoors, but there are dozens of... http://soc.li/KlwAKuB     
    
    
    Google first indoor maps in UK @google but the race doesn't always go to the swift, many others working on it http://goo.gl/s61YA  #indoor    
    
    
    inaccurate @TechNews_Tweets Google FIRST with indoor blue dot, not following Bing. Lots of others working on it http://goo.gl/s61YA     
    
    
    inaccurate @googlegurus Google not rivaling Bing, Google first with blue dot indoors. But others are coming fast! http://goo.gl/s61YA     
    
    
    @noahroth this is when you start learning that your 2y/o isn't in Kansas anymore....    
    
    
    @noahroth For me it was when my kids starting asking me "Abba can you give to me the book" ...    
    
    
    #GoogleVoice rings in #GMAIL but not in GTalk App or Nimbuzz or Fring.  In GMAIL can't answer w/o dialing "1" Any Google Voice advice?    
    
    
    @jonmedved Mazal tov! May they be zoche legadlo leTorah leChupa ulemaasim tovim, and may you enjoy spoiling him and giving him back!    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @YaelBeeri I'm an R&D guy turned mobile tech analyst & strategist for past 5 yr, in Samsung & private. Happy to talk if relevent!    
    
    
    Trying Google Voice in GMAIL talk chat - receiving calls I hear "press 1 to accept" and can't press 1.  Any advice?  #googlevoice #fb    
    
    
    Lots of action in indoor location these days - reports give you all the details: http://goo.gl/8gGIc     
    
    
    @freeincest lots of action in indoor location, it'll definitely be big by 2013 http://goo.gl/8gGIc     
    
    
    Lots of indoor location action! http://goo.gl/8gGIc  Research by all major co's and over 30 start-ups @lbssig @Qualcomm    
    
    
    Lots of companies working on indoor location tech for emergency responders http://goo.gl/8gGIc  @Police_Canada @Citig_Canada    
    
    
    IPod Touch asymptotically approaching iPhone http://qurl.com/gv4h8 maybe with Google Voice? http://qurl.com/dzql9   #fb    
    
    
    IPod Touch asymptotically approaching iPhone http://qurl.com/gv4h8 maybe with Google Voice? http://qurl.com/dzql9 #ipodtouch #googlevoice    
    
    
    Researchers show that numbers of connections is not the key to influence in a social network http://qurl.com/r6dkd #fb #socialnetworking    
    
    
    Offlining movement pushing to disconnect devices on Yom Kippur http://qurl.com/1by7c #fb    
    
    
    New articles on indoor location technology http://goo.gl/G7UrG  interest in the area is certainly growing! #indoorlbs #indoornav    
    
    
    @anupchowdhury lots of indoor technology R&D and start-ups http://goo.gl/8gGIc     
    
    
    Want to understand indoor LBS? See Nokia's http://goo.gl/jPOlg  & a startup's http://goo.gl/xGzHY  we explain it all http://goo.gl/9pPsm     
    
    
    Dual-screen #Samsung Galaxy Reader? http://goo.gl/ylorN  @SamsungMobile #ebook    
    
    
    Comparing @waze & @GoogleMobile Maps http://goo.gl/e74JC  #GoogleMaps turn-by-turn better but #Waze traffic analysis rocks! @waze_il    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Updated when I was in the USA with an American SIM. Haven't tried it here since returning - hope to soon.    
    
    
    Blog comparing @waze & @Google Maps http://goo.gl/e74JC  #Google turn-by-turn better but #Waze traffic data wins! @googlemobile @waze_il    
    
    
    @noahroth re fb comments for a while I've had some comments visible on mobile but not on-line. is that what you mean?    
    
    
    @noahroth blame the ipo price, everyone else is    
    
    
    Why did STMicroelectronics choose now to acquire @BTendo http://goo.gl/AYsfn  more projector phones soon? #iPhone5 with projector?    
    
    
    anyone else have problems now with @godaddy email hosting and support tickets?    
    
    
    @ashwinram @Waze Ashwin I've been a fan of Waze for years http://goo.gl/e74JC  glad to hear it's taking off in the States!    
    
    
    Will #iPhone5 have a projector? Blog article http://goo.gl/AYsfn  looking at STMicroelectronics acquisition of @BTendo    
    
    
    Must be cool tech: @kolyisrael Arab media reporting an Israeli drone killed a terrorist on a motorcycle in Sinai    
    
    
    @GoDaddy seems fixed now. No incident num since your support site didn't respond. Same w/ email & my hosted site. But all OK now.    
    
    
    Will #iPhone5 have a projector? Blog article http://goo.gl/AYsfn  speculates about STMicroelectronics acquisition of @BTendo    
    
    
    Will #iPhone5 have a projector? Blog article http://goo.gl/AYsfn  speculates about STMicroelectronics acquisition of @BTendo @ST_World    
    
    
    @BelzNies Where on DoverSholom is the Rebbe's house? How long after tzais is Tish? Biggest Q: is it le'mayseh friendly for non-chassidim?    
    
    
    @Yechiya SIM on trip was great, gave me straight-from-the-plan access I wanted. Thanks! But TMobile not great choice in the places I was    
    
    
    @Yechiya Definitely good to be back :-) In NYC coverage was gr8 I just spent lots of time in a very remote vacation house, gr8 except klita    
    
    
    @Yechiya Just curious is the follow-me to a US number available as a seperate service or just packaged w/ the cell rentals?    
    
    
    re FB @HilzFuld Now it's called "unsubscribe" it pops up as soon as you like or comment    
    
    
    @HilzFuld see the change I circled from an item of yours as I see it before and after I comment http://twitpic.com/aoa413     
    
    
    @HilzFuld see the change I circled from an item of yours as I see it before and after I comment  http://twitpic.com/aoa4zl     
    
    
    @HilzFuld dunno I did that capture right now    
    
    
    @HilzFuld current working theory: unfollowing works for posts (aka links or status updates) but not for pictures    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I submitted a FB bug report let's see if I hear anything    
    
    
    Facebook and Waze rumored in deal or acquisition talks http://goo.gl/SrtgB  @waze @waze_il @facebook    
    
    
    UPDATED Facebook and Waze rumored in deal or acquisition talks http://goo.gl/SrtgB  added details of synergy - @waze @waze_il @facebook    
    
    
    iPhone5 what will Apple shock us with this time? http://goo.gl/KAknX   Here are a few predictions.    
    
    
    Looking for 2-month jobs for an 18-year old, in Israel, prior to his enlistment. Any possibilities would be appreciated!  #fb    
    
    
    Looking for 2-month jobs for an 18-year old, in Israel, prior to his enlistment. Any possibilities would be appreciated! #israel #job #jobs    
    
    
    A must-watch interview on Arabic TV, for anyone who can read Hebrew subtitles.....  http://goo.gl/eeKyj #fb    
    
    
    Another vid of Prof Kedar this time English http://goo.gl/QipDm note from prev vid he's not against Palestinian state in west bank #fb    
    
    
    What will the #Apple #iphone5 "wow" be this time? Here are 5 predictions. http://goo.gl/Dh351  #waterproof #stylus #NFC #projector    
    
    
    How will #Apple shock us with the #iphone5 ? Here are 5 predictions. http://goo.gl/Dh351  #waterproof #stylus #NFC #projector    
    
    
    Has a day gone by without news about #indoor location technology? http://goo.gl/nAR0l  Learn the details here http://goo.gl/zcZ3Z     
    
    
    Massive violence in Libya not reported in media, disturbing pix: http://goo.gl/Z2sIs  http://goo.gl/o3ueg  #arabspring    
    
    
    .@nytjim Why isn't NYT including disturbing pictures that are already out? http://goo.gl/Z2sIs  http://goo.gl/o3ueg  not just smoke!    
    
    
    @noahroth @mrsroth highly recommend Keyara http://qurl.com/5mqpq but if u can afford it I should b in ur biz, we used a gift for app&desert    
    
    
    The biggest crime of all http://qurl.com/7rvww (hat tip 1A7B) #fb    
    
    
    Facebook down w/ DNS failure makes no sense - hacked? overloaded? DNS failure wouldn't be maintanance.....    
    
    
    Facebook DNS failure note to geeks: server is up at http://qurl.com/291gh but login needs names not IP addrs. note domain name cons.    
    
    
    Soon your smartphone will be waterproof... http://goo.gl/vI52L  @p2ilabs @hzoinside @SamsungMobile @toshiba    
    
    
    Re waterproof phones @UberFacts might be interested http://goo.gl/vI52L     
    
    
    Re waterproof phones @itsMalloy @JessicaClaricex @_Sunuva @BloombergTV @BettyInTheLoop @RWW  they're coming soon - see http://goo.gl/vI52L     
    
    
    Haven't used Waze? See my comparison w/ Google Maps nav http://goo.gl/7Lj9I  @waze @GoogleMobile @googlemaps @waze_il #waze #gps    
    
    
    Cisco starts what I think will be an avalanche of M&A of indoor location start-ups http://goo.gl/EocDK     
    
    
    Is there anyone who DOESN'T want their smartphone waterproof? http://goo.gl/vI52L  @p2ilabs @hzoinside @SamsungMobile @toshiba    
    
    
    Cisco starts the avalanche of M&A of indoor location start-ups http://goo.gl/EocDK  @cisco_mobility @ciscosystems    
    
    
    @HilzFuld http://dilbert.com/strips/comic/1992-06-03/ …    
    
    
    actually @HilzFuld re NFC this is the one I was looking for http://dilbert.com/strips/comic/1992-06-01/ …    
    
    
    Cisco starts the expected avalanche of indoor location M&A - http://goo.gl/EocDK  @cisco_mobility @ciscosystems    
    
    
    Classic Sukkot song updated to modern days.....  http://qurl.com/mj3mf   #sukkot #sukkos #peace #Israel    
    
    
    New indoor location app in Singapore uses innovative sensor-fusion technology to track phones as they move http://goo.gl/eutAq     
    
    
    New indoor location app uses innovative sensor-fusion technology to track phones as they move http://goo.gl/eutAq  @senionlab @singtel    
    
    
    Is there anyone who DOESN'T want their smartphone waterproof? http://goo.gl/vI52L  @p2ilabs @hzoinside    
    
    
    How Amazon & PayPal will win at mobile payments http://goo.gl/u059Z  even more true since #iPhone5 skipped #NFC @amazon @paypal    
    
    
    New indoor location system works also on iPhone! http://goo.gl/hmWsJ  read why this is hard and how they did it. @PoleStar_    
    
    
    Indoor GPS navigation in France http://goo.gl/hmWsJ  and Singapore http://goo.gl/eutAq  - and the M&A is starting http://goo.gl/80Om5     
    
    
    @HilzFuld Every Android fan I know (myself included) knows that iOS's UI is bottom line more usable....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Note I said UI usability. I'm an android fan and think the power and google integration and apps are worth the geekier UI.    
    
    
    Next hurricane will your smartphone be waterproof? http://goo.gl/vI52L  - @p2ilabs @hzoinside #GrizzlyAnalytics    
    
    
    Amazing image & video processing at #TN12 - Magisto Cortica Flayvr Pixtr & more    
    
    
    @quitemindy @fictionnreality You might like my book Harry Potter and Torah http://goo.gl/CF0Yy Jewish discussions of themes from HP    
    
    
    @dance_tenlooks3 @melissaanelli @andrewslack I wrote Harry Potter and Torah http://goo.gl/CF0Yy Jewish discussions of themes from HP    
    
    
    Indoor location moves into the network http://goo.gl/RB4sE  Macy's Miami Childrens Hospital and more    
    
    
    New @Microsoft location-based app discovery approach http://goo.gl/O9B1I  #windowsphone #appdiscovery #lbs    
    
    
    New @Microsoft location-based app discovery research http://goo.gl/O9B1I  #windowsphone #lbs #wp8    
    
    
    When you go to a new place would you want your phone to suggest apps for the new place? http://goo.gl/O9B1I  @windowsphone    
    
    
    Get new mobile apps as you enter new places http://goo.gl/O9B1I  #lbs @microsoft    
    
    
    GeoFencing: New report has 137 pages of R&D details http://goo.gl/mDVG0  @Microsoft @SamsungMobile @AppleTweets @GoogleMobile @EBay    
    
    
    New report on #GeoFencing details over a hundred tech research projects in action http://goo.gl/mDVG0  #lbs #location    
    
    
    The #GeoFencing revolution in mobile apps & services is coming soon http://goo.gl/uFUjN  not just ads and reminders    
    
    
    @noahroth which watch did you get? for exercise or for more than that?    
    
    
    @noahroth Nice I've seen research like that but haven't seen the product. Songs by location or by terrain? Cool if it works.    
    
    
    @noahroth It's being researched by Apple, Samsung, Sony Ericsson & others. I've been curious when it would get to market. Let me know...    
    
    
    GeoFencing is huge. Here's why http://goo.gl/uFUjN  - being researched by @GoogleMobile @Microsoft @AppleTweets @qualcomm @ebay    
    
    
    @heremaps anything to say about indoor positioning? how will you let me see myself moving around an indoor venue map?    
    
    
    @jmp_nyc Hi cuz is it called getting off Facebook if all of a sudden you're much more on Twitter? :-) (Hope all's good there)    
    
    
    @jmp_nyc agree that's why I'm on it but not FB during the workday    
    
    
    Video on the negotiations for the return of Gilad Shalit the Israeli soldier kidnapped by Palestinians http://qurl.com/ht7py #fb    
    
    
    Video on the negotiations for the return of Gilad Shalit the Israeli soldier kidnapped by Palestinians http://qurl.com/ht7py   #israel    
    
    
    Video on the negotiations for the return of #Gilad #Shalit the #Israeli soldier kidnapped by #Hamas http://qurl.com/ht7py    
    
    
    GeoFencing being researched by @GoogleMobile @Microsoft @AppleTweets @qualcomm @ebay and others http://goo.gl/mDVG0  #revolution    
    
    
    Haven't heard of GeoFencing? It's been researched by @GoogleMobile @Microsoft @AppleTweets @qualcomm @ebay & others - http://goo.gl/mDVG0     
    
    
    @noahroth Depends on the altitude of the rocket....    
    
    
    Bus explosion reported in Tel Aviv, no news yet and not yet on major sites. #israel #hamas #terrorism #telaivv    
    
    
    @noahroth I'm thinking it's time we flatten apartment buildings in Gaza. If there's a price to paid in innocent people, why is it ours?    
    
    
    @fundraisinisfun @noahroth You can agree or disagree with a land invasion, but it's not hasty, it's been on hold for almost a week now....    
    
    
    @LiorShemesh I thought about that during the intifada when I was living in Jerusalem. Good idea.    
    
    
    @jmp_nyc yep it started just after i tweeted that    
    
    
    @AntDeRosa are you truly as off as you're being quoted? Israel is targeting people who are attacking us. It's not numbers it's anti-terror    
    
    
    @KolYisrael where was the missile near Beit Shemesh? Lots of confusion here, no siren sounded in Beit Shemesh.    
    
    
    Gesture recognition deals by Samsung & NEC http://goo.gl/rY7jp  but microgestures are coming soon to mobile    
    
    
    @AntDeRosa @NewsOfMideast Hamas hasn't stopped rockets. What makes you think Israel's actions to now are sufficient to stop terror?    
    
    
    GeoFencing - coming soon to apps near you http://goo.gl/uFUjN  #wp8 #android #iOS    
    
    
    Can't wait for #GeoFencing to make apps work automatically and intelligently http://goo.gl/uFUjN     
    
    
    @skjask rickety    
    
    
    @HilzFuld You're already using the Note 2, right? That split-screen multi-tasking looked amazing.....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld How much do you have running? I get less than a day on my Galaxy S2, but that's with Skype and other things running all the time    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Do you run any always-on apps eg Skype? GPS? Use camera? Google+ other sync? I'm curious if u get 2 days because of device or load    
    
    
    @HilzFuld wow that's double the mAh straight away. Nice!    
    
    
    GeoFencing http://goo.gl/XNfic  - coming to mobile OSs now & to apps soon! @GoogleMobile @Microsoft @AppleTweets @qualcomm @ebay    
    
    
    When will #androidapps or #iosapps or #wp8apps use #GeoFencing to run automatically? http://goo.gl/uFUjN     
    
    
    @matt_dillingham glad you enjoyed my GeoFencing blog article. Loads of GeoFencing R&D detailed here http://goo.gl/XNfic     
    
    
    New article on GeoFencing on @SeekingAlpha http://goo.gl/9cgKb  - focus on #apple #ebay @ebay @AppleTweets #GeoFencing    
    
    
    GeoFencing article on @SeekingAlpha http://goo.gl/9cgKb  details research by Apple on efficient #geofencing @AppleTweets #iOS #lbs    
    
    
    Why #Apple will beat #Android to efficient GeoFencing http://goo.gl/9cgKb  - and why @EBay will profit from it - #lbs    
    
    
    @noahroth @Yechiya FYI some Stoli sold in Israel is fake synthetic stuff - if price is too good, or has chug chasam sofer, check it more    
    
    
    @noahroth Philistine @Yechiya    
    
    
    Details of #Apple R&D on GeoFencing http://goo.gl/9cgKb   - and why @EBay will profit from it - #lbs    
    
    
    GeoFencing article on @SeekingAlpha http://goo.gl/9cgKb  - details #Apple research and EBay M&A on #geofencing - #iOS #lbs    
    
    
    @mashable GeoFencing is next big thing in mobile apps http://goo.gl/C74ou  http://goo.gl/9cgKb  http://goo.gl/XNfic     
    
    
    실내 위치 서비스 - 주요 모바일 기업 연구 - http://goo.gl/ef4e8  - http://goo.gl/p1mWu     
    
    
    GeoFencing meets Indoor Location Positioning http://goo.gl/cFJmS  @SenseWhere #lbs    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Law of unintended consequences. But think like a techie - what should happen if you set public tweets but block someone?    
    
    
    GeoFencing - the next #lbs battlefield http://goo.gl/XNfic  this article explains why http://goo.gl/9cgKb  #GeoFencing    
    
    
    Noones secretive like #Apple but here is their GeoFencing R&D http://goo.gl/9cgKb  part of http://goo.gl/XNfic  @AppleTweets #lbs #ios    
    
    
    Have remaining intelligence budget? 163 page report on indoor location technology R&D http://goo.gl/p1mWu  #lbs #gps #indoor #ci    
    
    
    Excellent article in the Boston Globe about Israel...   http://qurl.com/4b52y    #israel #palestinian #peace #jewish    
    
    
    2 weeks to finish your budget? Buy knowledge you'll need next year: indoor location http://goo.gl/p1mWu  or GeoFencing http://goo.gl/XNfic     
    
    
    Quuppa - amazing indoor location positioning! http://goo.gl/tURyD     
    
    
    Amazing video of #indoor #lbs tracking basketball game in action http://goo.gl/tURyD     
    
    
    Sensor fusion goes solo for location tracking http://goo.gl/iR8lZ  @WiFiSLAM #indoor #lbs    
    
    
    @levshapiro re russian adoption that makes US less per capita, right?    
    
    
    @hschein wow - that @HilzFuld would tweet, that's obvious. but your hashtag makes me blush    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @hschein cup of coffee before 5:19    
    
    
    Predicted this in 2011 http://goo.gl/Frndy  RT @PayPal predicts demise for NFC http://goo.gl/cINWj  @nfc_hub @davidmarcus @WatchAdam    
    
    
    @noahroth thank G-d that this time you didn't use instagram....    
    
    
    @noahroth My understanding is accelerometer along with optional foot pad sensor of some kind. has GPS but uses motion sensing in tunnels etc    
    
    
    @noahroth accelerometer et al    
    
    
    GeoFencing the next big area in location technologies http://goo.gl/Dpdxo  see R&D by @appletweets @SamsungMobile @microsoft @GoogleMobile    
    
    
    New book by Rav Avishai David just hit the shelves http://qurl.com/2g7my Discourses of Rav Solovetchik on the parsha #yutorah    
    
    
    New book by Rav Avishai David just hit the shelves http://qurl.com/2g7my Discourses of Rav Solovetchik on the parsha #yutorah @yutorah    
    
    
    Why would a flashlight cellphone app  (maxflash by maxcom) need permissions for my location and network access? #android #security    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I wanted it to turn on the camera flash like my Omnia does, it just whites the LCD. So it's both useless and maybe malicious    
    
    
    @acoomans OK I'll bite why is morph really mising the point? Too late to save them, I'd understand, but why missing the point?    
    
    
    WiFiSLAM answered my questions about how their sensor fusion location tracking works so well standalone http://goo.gl/SkAbX  @WiFiSLAM    
    
    
    Indoor location technology transforming the retail industry http://goo.gl/Ti9PJ  #GPS @meridianapps    
    
    
    Great article by sis-in-law: My Incredibly Ordinary Life: Mom w/ Cerebral Palsy Discusses Parenting w/ Disability http://qurl.com/h5nqv #fb    
    
    
    Indoor location positioning and GeoFencing come together for the retail industry. http://goo.gl/20ZWC     
    
    
    Did u know most indoor location tech doesn't work on iOS? Read about indoor location for retail incl iOS w/ GeoFencing http://goo.gl/20ZWC     
    
    
    @AndriaCheng nice article on indoor location. I'm an analyst in the area http://goo.gl/20ZWC  http://goo.gl/AaSql  happy to talk    
    
    
    @mieky @penberg Switching from NFC to other protocols is a Nokia patent http://qurl.com/1jl9g but did Nokia do phone<->PC by NFC?    
    
    
    Interest in indoor location technologies is growing beyond belief! List the top ten mobile companies, and half of them…http://lnkd.in/_ruEcy     
    
    
    @noahroth wouldn't he learn a lot more by having to finish the day in muddy clothes?    
    
    
    @Yechiya any lead on a SIM (or cellphone) for Spain (Barcelona) ?    
    
    
    Broadcom stakes their claim in chip support for GeoFencing, both outdoor and indoor. http://goo.gl/MJdbY  @broadcom #geofencing #lbs    
    
    
    Indoor location technology enables NFC-like payments without NFC!  http://goo.gl/68SuX     
    
    
    Indoor location technology enables NFC-like payments without NFC!  http://goo.gl/68SuX  @wisesec #lbs    
    
    
    Indoor location tech enables NFC-like payments without NFC!  http://goo.gl/68SuX  #lbs    
    
    
    SK Telecom's indoor location positioning solution in action at MWC 2013 http://goo.gl/8JFc4  @sktelecom #indoor #lbs    
    
    
    Indoor location positioning based on Bluetooth #BLE SK Telecom at MWC http://goo.gl/8JFc4  @sktelecom #indoor #lbs #mwc #mwc2013    
    
    
    Indoor location tech from Korea: @sktelecom demo at MWC 2013. http://goo.gl/8JFc4   Bluetooth beacons, map positioning & GeoFencing    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @niron saw LG Optimus G Pro at MWC: app multitasking in windows, not split screen, great screen. Want one.    
    
    
    @davekellett re comic strip documentary, did you.mean to tweet me or a relative of mine?    
    
    
    Updated 260-page report on indoor location technology http://goo.gl/LhQhl  Major mobile & chip co's & over 50 start-ups #lbs #indoor    
    
    
    Did you know that there are over 50 start-ups in indoor location? Plus lots more major companies researching it http://goo.gl/LhQhl     
    
    
    .@HilzFuld @SebastienPage Apple deal was likely b/c they've been denying wifi data to app dev'ers. @wifislam unique map scanning tech    
    
    
    #Apple acquires @wifislam indoor location start-up http://goo.gl/CzI7t  here are the details of why    
    
    
    @Jessicalessin Re Apple/WiFiSLAM see http://goo.gl/CzI7t  would be happy to give perspective    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @SebastienPage http://goo.gl/CzI7t     
    
    
    Apple acquires @wifislam indoor location start-up http://goo.gl/CzI7t  now indoor will work on #iOS - read how WiFiSLAM is unique    
    
    
    Indoor location R&D by over 90 companies! http://goo.gl/LhQhl     
    
    
    @rosstsimon Anthony Goldstein in Ravenclaw sounds Jewish by name but nothing definite. You might like my book http://goo.gl/CF0Yy    
    
    
    My comment on "Pole Star Unveils Indoor Location Cloud For iPhone, Android (video)" @Forbes: http://onforb.es/YGPXQc     
    
    
    How many indoor location start-ups can you name? We've analyzed over 50!  http://goo.gl/LhQhl   Apple's acquired 1, what will be next?    
    
    
    My latest on @SeekingAlpha explains Apple's acquisition of WiFiSLAM and whats next in indoor location... http://seekingalpha.com/article/1320101-understanding-apple-buying-wifislam-and-what-s-next …    
    
    
    Article on #Apple's buying @wifislam & what's next in indoor location http://goo.gl/1f77r  @Microsoft @Android @SamsungMobile @Qualcomm    
    
    
    First day with a 30 second commute. No traffic. But no Espresso machine (yet)! http://goo.gl/pSC1t   #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Click the link "use google.com in English" at the bottom of google.co.il then don't erase cookies, that works for me    
    
    
    Recent articles quoting Grizzly Analytics on indoor location http://goo.gl/ObECv  #indoorlbs #lbs #indoor    
    
    
    Article on Indoor location: #Apple acquiring @wifislam its about apps not maps http://goo.gl/wJGcH  @SeekingAlpha #lbs #indoorlbs    
    
    
    Article on Indoor location: #Apple acquiring @wifislam its about apps not maps http://goo.gl/wJGcH     
    
    
    For less-techie decision-makers: learn details about indoor location services you can deploy in your site http://goo.gl/lYVJk     
    
    
    @LivenightNacht are u particularly interested in indoor location, or tweet a lot of seekingalpha articles?    
    
    
    @Aislinn_Mahon @localsocial agreed about indoor loc's future. you work in the area? I wrote http://goo.gl/wJGcH  http://goo.gl/LhQhl     
    
    
    Nice article on Nordic indoor location co's: Location location ... location?! part two http://wp.me/p3nGpI-38  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    Are other Netvision users having trouble accessing some sites? Twitter and CNN work, Yahoo and GMAIL don't. Is it me or others too?    
    
    
    OK, works now....    
    
    
    Two articles on Apple & indoor location: What they're doing http://goo.gl/wJGcH  & where industry is going http://goo.gl/1f77r     
    
    
    GPS 실내 : 기술 R & D 및 솔루션의 세부 사항 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    室内GPS技术研发和解决方案的详情 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPSを屋内：技術のR＆Dおよびソリューションの詳細 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Intérieur GPS: Détails de la technologie R & D et solutions http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Dentro de GPS: Detalhes de Tecnologia R & D e soluções http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Indoor location technology: All the tech details and all the solutions on the market http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS al chiuso: Details of Technology R & S e le soluzioni http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS inomhus: Uppgifter om tekniska FoU och lösningar http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS в помещении: Детали технологии R & D и решения http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Indoor location technology: Details of over 50 startups and lots of R&D http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Indoor location - Details of over 50 startups & lots of R&D http://goo.gl/i2IG2  Dozens of co's in over ten countries have bought!    
    
    
    Name 10 major mobile co's, at least 6 have bought this report on indoor location startups & R&D http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    @yakovhorowitz any chance we can convince you to move to Eretz Yisrael? We need you here!    
    
    
    GPS в помещении: Детали технологии R & D и решения http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS inomhus: Uppgifter om tekniska FoU och lösningar http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS al chiuso: Details of Technology R & S e le soluzioni http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Dentro de GPS: Detalhes de Tecnologia R & D e soluções http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Intérieur GPS: Détails de la technologie R & D et solutions http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPSを屋内：技術のR＆Dおよびソリューションの詳細 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    室内GPS技术研发和解决方案的详情 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPS 실내 : 기술 R & D 및 솔루션의 세부 사항 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Espresso meets peepee in the Internet of Things http://goo.gl/QBclp  #IOT @Qualcomm @Huggies @cubesensors    
    
    
    Espresso meets peepee in the Internet of Things http://goo.gl/QBclp  #IOT #internetofthings    
    
    
    My comment on "Are NFC payments dead?" @Forbes: http://onforb.es/11uHtA5     
    
    
    New service helps integrate indoor location tech into your products or business http://goo.gl/Nq3ZY  #lbs    
    
    
    To follow Grizzly Analytics updates articles reports & services, follow @GrizzlyAnalytic or LIKE http://goo.gl/6ANnR     
    
    
    Article on @facebook rumored plans to acquire @waze http://goo.gl/GttdX  @SeekingAlpha @waze_il    
    
    
    Another indoor location acquisition @ArubaNetworks acquires @meridianapps http://goo.gl/wGRde  @GrizzlyAnalytics    
    
    
    Indoor location is hot! @ArubaNetworks buys @meridianapps & #Apple buys @wifislam what's next? Learn more here http://goo.gl/OWByk     
    
    
    GeoFencing: Enabling Location-Based Reminders, Ads, Promotions, Proactive Apps, Security & More http://goo.gl/8gM0J  @GrizzlyAnalytics    
    
    
    More @waze acquisition rumors: @googlemaps @GoogleMobile joins the fray http://goo.gl/wG6ua  or will @facebook win? @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Name 10 major mobile co's, at least 7 bought my report on indoor location tech & startups http://goo.gl/i2IG2  - @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    @shaironen interested in discussing Navin when you have a few minutes - can we schedule a call?    
    
    
    Report explains indoor location to nontechies http://goo.gl/eixjT  how it works, what it can do for you, solutions @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    @HilzFuld projector for movie sharing among teens and young adults. accurate indoor location positioning anywhere.    
    
    
    Rumors say @facebook @waze acquisition talks fell thru - but I'm not convinced http://goo.gl/v2X3U  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Name 10 major mobile co's at least 7 bought this report on indoor location tech & startups http://goo.gl/i2IG2   - @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    GPS 실내 : 기술 R & D 및 솔루션의 세부 사항 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    室内GPS技术研发和解决方案的详情 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    GPSを屋内：技術のR＆Dおよびソリューションの詳細 http://goo.gl/i2IG2     
    
    
    Congrats to @bobr and everyone else at Answers.com on their acquisiton! http://goo.gl/ZgzFw    
    
    
    @noahroth even better is when you try to grab it on its way down and burn your hand on bubbling soup    
    
    
    Latest rumor is @GoogleMobile buying @waze but is it for @googlemaps or for @Android http://goo.gl/lGTCC  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Latest rumor is @GoogleMobile buying @waze but is it for @googlemaps or for @Android ?? http://goo.gl/lGTCC  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    My comment on "Google To Spite Facebook: Buy Waze For $1.3 Billion" @Forbes: http://onforb.es/19VxgNR     
    
    
    Latest rumor is @GoogleMobile buying @waze but is it read? is it for @googlemaps or for @Android ?? http://goo.gl/lGTCC  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Confirmed @Google buying @Waze http://goo.gl/p0G7N  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    What @waze might mean for @google http://goo.gl/BVyf6  - @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Confirmed @Google acquiring @Waze - in a picture pic.twitter.com/LDIPhWmpV4    
    
    
    What Waze might mean for Google http://goo.gl/BVyf6   - @GrizzlyAnalytic @googlemaps @GoogleMobile @waze @waze_il    
    
    
    주요 모바일 기업의 대부분은 실내 위치 기술이 보고서를 구입 http://goo.gl/tfJZ2  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld @Inneractive common denominator: problem looking for solution not technology looking for problem to solve    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld you're misunderstanding. I didn't say unique tech, that's Waze not the others. (continued next tweet)    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld (continued) all were things that folks were already doing a lot of and want to do better. none started w/ tech and looked for use    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld except Waze had tech no one else had done yet w/ movement analysis for traffic reporting. in service of a real need    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Re #Nokia #Microsoft MSFT hiring worldwide lead for MS/Nokia alliance incl MSoffice on Symbian http://goo.gl/sqJcH posted Jan26    
    
    
    Understand the start-up scene from which Waze grew...  http://goo.gl/Cv2XY     
    
    
    Want indoor location tech for your site or app? http://goo.gl/6k43B  - Explanation and details of solutions on the market    
    
    
    Indoor location is worked on by #Google #Apple #Microsoft #Qualcomm & more. Learn details here http://goo.gl/H65WA  @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    GeoFencing lets your phone work for you automatically http://goo.gl/UtSxm  learn about R&D by Google Apple etc http://goo.gl/blqb0     
    
    
    Indoor location: More than 50 start-ups. More than 40 major co's. Can you afford to only know about some of them? http://goo.gl/2G6lY     
    
    
    Indoor navigation: Can you afford not to know about over 50 start-ups and R&D by over 40 major co's? http://goo.gl/2G6lY     
    
    
    268 pages of indoor location positioning R&D details http://goo.gl/2G6lY  Google Microsoft Samsung PoleStar PointInside Apple WiFiSLAM etc    
    
    
    Name 10 top mobile/tech co's at least 7 have bought this report on indoor location tech http://goo.gl/2G6lY  - 268 pages of R&D details    
    
    
    @HilzFuld FB merges messaging with chat, right? maybe they thought of themselves as sending you a message? #unifiedmessagingfail    
    
    
    Indoor location report all the major companies are buying - R&D by major mobile/tech co's and over 50 start-ups - http://goo.gl/6Extk     
    
    
    Indoor location report all the major companies are buying - R&D by major mobile/tech co's and over 50 start-ups - http://goo.gl/6Extk     
    
    
    @A_Ankit Glad you LIKEd my LinkedIn update re indoor location technology report. Happy to offer you a $100 discount http://goo.gl/IFFon     
    
    
    @Percivall Glad you LIKEd my LinkedIn update re indoor location technology report. Happy to offer you a $100 discount http://goo.gl/IFFon     
    
    
    Ruckus Wireless acquired YFind - read about what it means for the network industry http://goo.gl/P5KkJW  - @ruckuswireless @YFindTech    
    
    
    Learn why @ruckuswireless bought @YFindTech - http://goo.gl/jVDpVy  - implications for @NETGEAR @Linksys @USRoboticsCo @Dlink @Edimax    
    
    
    Internet of Things R&D details not in the media http://goo.gl/dlvv0  - #IoT #IoE R&D by @google @Microsoft @Qualcomm @intel @ZTE @Cisco    
    
    
    Internet of Things R&D by @Google @Microsoft @Qualcomm @intel @ZTE @Cisco &more- learn all the details http://goo.gl/dlvv0  - #IoT #IoE    
    
    
    @mordyk Sorry 4 delay in replying. Carrier/network/beacon indoor tech less relevant to Apple acq. I do cover them in http://goo.gl/IFFon     
    
    
    @mordyk Probably true. Is Navanu working in this area?    
    
    
    Internet of Things: Learn technical R&D behind the hype http://goo.gl/DTYpPo  - research by major co's and dev by >25 start-ups #IoT #IoE    
    
    
    Indoor location http://goo.gl/vZCmq8  Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke  GeoFencing http://goo.gl/mzcMRk  Bought by R&D worldwide    
    
    
    Indoor location http://goo.gl/vZCmq8  Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke  GeoFencing http://goo.gl/mzcMRk  Corp R&D centers buy 'em    
    
    
    Internet of Things: Growing battlefield between network mobile & chip co's http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  @SeekingAlpha #IoT #IoE    
    
    
    Internet of Things: Growing battlefield between network mobile & chip co's http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  @Qualcomm @Cisco @intel @GoogleMobile    
    
    
    @HilzFuld I have some accounts push and some not. depends on the interesting/garbage ratio and how business-critical.    
    
    
    Internet of Things #IoT #IoE Article http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  & report w/ R&D details http://goo.gl/K0cVCt  @Qualcomm @intel @GoogleMobile    
    
    
    Internet of Things #IoT #IoE Article http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  & report w/ R&D details http://goo.gl/K0cVCt  @Microsoft @IBM #Apple    
    
    
    Internet of Things #IoT #IoE Article http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  & report w/ R&D details http://goo.gl/K0cVCt  @ZTEPress @ZTE_USA @Cisco    
    
    
    Internet of Things #IoT #IoE Article http://goo.gl/OAPRAq  & report w R&D details http://goo.gl/K0cVCt  @generalelectric @BoschAppliances    
    
    
    진행중인 모바일 기술 연구 : 사물 간 인터넷 http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke  실내 위치 http://goo.gl/vZCmq8  지오 펜싱 http://goo.gl/mzcMRk  @SamsungMobile @SKtelecom    
    
    
    진행중인 모바일 기술 연구 : 사물 간 인터넷 http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke  실내 위치 http://goo.gl/vZCmq8  지오 펜싱 http://goo.gl/mzcMRk  @LGmobileMWC @KoreaTelecom    
    
    
        
    
    
    Indoor location http://goo.gl/vZCmq8   Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke   GeoFencing http://goo.gl/mzcMRk  R&D centers buy 'em    
    
    
    Indoor location R&D by over 40 R&D centers & over 50 startups http://goo.gl/PFN95E  #indoor #location #lbs    
    
    
    Under the Internet of Things hype is a lot of serious R&D & start-ups http://goo.gl/K0cVCt  - #IoT #IoE #InternetofThings    
    
    
    Indoor location http://goo.gl/vZCmq8    Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Ds0Xke    GeoFencing http://goo.gl/mzcMRk   R&D centers buy 'em    
    
    
    Under the Internet of Things hype is a lot of serious R&D & start-ups http://goo.gl/K0cVCt   - #IoT #IoE #InternetofThings    
    
    
    Indoor location R&D by over 40 R&D centers & over 50 startups http://goo.gl/PFN95E  #indoor #location #lbs    
    
    
    Samsung Galaxy Gear smart watch reported confirmed with Sep delivery http://goo.gl/4k7CHt  #Samsung @SamsungMobile    
    
    
    ARM acquisition races Qualcomm & Intel to the next 50 Billion Devices http://goo.gl/Dpzicf  - #IoT #IoE @ARMHoldings @Qualcomm @intel    
    
    
    ARM acquisition races Qualcomm & Intel to the next 50 Billion Devices http://goo.gl/Dpzicf   - #IoT #IoE @SeekingAlpha @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    ARM acquired an Internet of Things company, in a race with Qualcomm and Intel.... http://lnkd.in/VyASxG     
    
    
        
    
    
    Is @nokia working on #nanotechnology phones for 2016? http://goo.gl/XuhCCx     
    
    
    Is @Microsoft moving #WindowsPhone onto feature phones? http://goo.gl/XuhCCx  @MSRNDIL    
    
    
    Gesture recognition: Today's M&A and tomorrow's mobile applications: http://goo.gl/jP0gEY  @intel @Qualcomm @UmooveMe @PointGrab    
    
    
    Chip companies in a race to the Internet of Things.... http://goo.gl/Dpzicf  @ARMMobile @Qualcomm @intel    
    
    
    Indoor location start-ups now out of stealth mode in #Israel ....  http://goo.gl/7Epg3u  @GeniusMatcher @geektimecom #indoor #gps    
    
    
    Mobile tech trend reports by monthly subscription. DM to receive January report free on NFC non-payment uses &more http://goo.gl/K6dxn    
    
    
    Is @nokia working on #nanotechnology phones for 2016? http://goo.gl/XuhCCx     
    
    
    Is @Microsoft moving #WindowsPhone onto feature phones? http://goo.gl/XuhCCx     
    
    
    Gesture recognition: Today's M&A and tomorrow's mobile applications: http://goo.gl/jP0gEY  @intel @Qualcomm @UmooveMe @PointGrab    
    
    
    Chip companies in a race to the Internet of Things.... http://goo.gl/Dpzicf  @ARMMobile @Qualcomm @intel    
    
    
    Indoor location R&D by over 40 R&D centers & over 50 startups http://goo.gl/PFN95E  #indoor #location #lbs    
    
    
    Indoor location start-ups now out of stealth mode in #Israel - http://goo.gl/7Epg3u  @GeniusMatcher @geektimecom @Indoorgo @wisesec    
    
    
        
    
    
    @UmooveMe happy to talk anytime - I'm likely working on more articles and reports that relate to you....    
    
    
    Latest: @WhatsApp 's Quiet Move Into Social Networking & Why @facebook Should Worry - http://goo.gl/8fVwBT  - @SeekingAlpha @GooglePlus    
    
    
    그룹 메시징 소셜 네트워킹에 혼합 - http://goo.gl/e2Audu  - @WhatsApp @facebook @GooglePlus    
    
    
    @jmp_nyc thanks interesting    
    
    
    BLOG: @Broadcom licenses metro indoor location positioning tech from NextNav - http://goo.gl/ZQaIz9  - @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Coming soon in mobile: Indoor location http://goo.gl/xBJQJd  GeoFencing http://goo.gl/vhCeWW  Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Khm9te     
    
    
    Wireless technology designed to support accurate indoor location http://goo.gl/KlTYNS  @DecaWave @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Wireless tech designed for distance ranging and location positioning http://goo.gl/KlTYNS  #Indoor #lbs    
    
    
    Wireless tech designed for distance ranging and location positioning http://goo.gl/KlTYNS  #Indoor #lbs    
    
    
    Apple iBeacons Poised To Legitimize Hardware-Based Indoor Location http://goo.gl/211NQA  - #indoor #lbs #iOS #Apple    
    
    
    New wireless chip from Decawave gives centimeter-precise indoor location http://goo.gl/KlTYNS  - @DecaWave #indoor #lbs    
    
    
    @noahroth @HilzFuld @MarkKorman N see my comment on H's G+ thread https://plus.google.com/+HillelFuld/posts/5QfngWjnwdL … I think it's part of what you're trying to say    
    
    
    @noahroth but I don't agree re valuation. Its always relative, to current market, to future investors, etc. Its never objective value. Ever    
    
    
    @noahroth I usually agree but maybe component-feature software M&A is today's form of licensing... like selling chips to device makers...    
    
    
    @noahroth anyway overall I agree with your point. Easier to make on G+ with more than 140 characters....    
    
    
    What will #Apple do with the @GoPrimeSense gesture recognition technology they just acquired?  http://goo.gl/oh8vUK     
    
    
    Video of indoor location positioning from @DecaWave http://goo.gl/17y87A  - #indoorlocation #lbs    
    
    
    Video of indoor location positioning from @DecaWave http://goo.gl/17y87A   - #indoorlocation #lbs    
    
    
    Coming soon in mobile: Indoor location http://goo.gl/xBJQJd  GeoFencing http://goo.gl/vhCeWW  Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Khm9te     
    
    
    Coming soon in mobile: Indoor location http://goo.gl/xBJQJd   GeoFencing http://goo.gl/vhCeWW   Internet of Things http://goo.gl/Khm9te     
    
    
    New wireless chip from Decawave gives centimeter-precise indoor location http://goo.gl/KlTYNS   - @DecaWave #indoor #lbs    
    
    
    Apple iBeacons Poised To Legitimize Hardware-Based Indoor Location http://goo.gl/211NQA   - #indoor #lbs - also @Qualcomm beacons now    
    
    
    This article on indoor location for retail was written almost a year ago. Will 2014 be the year? http://goo.gl/J3oORu     
    
    
    @Picopros I've certainly thought so http://goo.gl/OApDcE   - http://goo.gl/ZaFxCP  - http://goo.gl/Vl0Guo  - but still waiting!    
    
    
    Bosch Internet of Things subsidiary builds on years of research http://goo.gl/jXXMR1  @BoschGlobal @GrizzlyAnalytic    
    
    
    Bosch IoT subsidiary builds on years of research http://goo.gl/jXXMR1  @BoschGlobal @BoschHomeUK @BoschAppliances @BoschSecurity    
    
    
    @gblander1 Glad u like my IoT post. Would be happy to hear about what SegTerra is up to - krulwich@grizzlyanalytics.com    
    
    
    Bosch IoT subsidiary builds on years of research http://goo.gl/jXXMR1  @BoschGlobal @BoschHomeUK @BoschAppliances @BoschSecurity    
    
    
    @AmosPosner OK, there's just GOT to be a story behind this one....    
    
    
    Quuppa - unique and precise indoor location tech - most read blog article of 2013 - http://goo.gl/i80G5k  - @quuppacom #indoor #lbs    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon re war for control of internet: the free market has taken us this far, it'll take us where we need to go....    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics monday update: Mobile security M&A, BBM on iPhone&Android, Motorola gaming, China Unicom Linux phone.... DM me 4 more....    
    
    
    Anyone know what's with the air raid siren in Beit Shemesh?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @noahroth Hillel, it was a planned siren test?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld thanks    
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber This gets "oldie but goodie" status from when you were in Buffalo, 1 of the 1st of your vortlach I ever said at a Shabbos meal    
    
    
    Nokia's NanoTechnology research for mobile devices: Grizzly Analytics published 83-page report http://goo.gl/RTu1m  #nokia #nanotech #nano    
    
    
    Who bought a company similar to Snaptu that Facebook bought? What power gen is Apple working on? Grizzly customers know! http://goo.gl/Op1fB    
    
    
    @georgeeblancoo Harry Potter and the Holocaust: Intense yes, but not so subtle: Arians and purebloods. But noone discusses this....    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics report on Nokia NanoTechnology Research now for sale through ResearchAndMarkets http://goo.gl/foJUw #nokia #nano #nanotech    
    
    
    Check out Google delivering info over IM - will SMS be next? they already have SMS network for calendar. http://goo.gl/j1Vyr    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics report on Nokia's research in NanoTechnology for Mobile now for sale on ReportLinker http://goo.gl/gcu6X #nokia #nanotech    
    
    
    NanoTechnology Now: Press release on Grizzly Analytics report on Nokia's research on NanoTech for Mobile http://goo.gl/mLXBd @nokia #nokia    
    
    
    @gldmeier Not sure about meeting, but I'm in Beit Shemesh    
    
    
    @noahroth @gldmeier Noah's amusing himself with chumras, he knows the Beit Shemesh eruv is one of the few that's lechatchila min hagemorah.    
    
    
    Difference between a Jewish terrorist and an Arab terrorist http://qurl.com/ggkrp #israel #arab #terrorist #terror #jewish    
    
    
    What feature-phone app co's are M&A targets? What are open issues for location-based alerts? Grizzly subscribers know! http://goo.gl/ZGplN    
    
    
    @samantha_oj6r98 Why the same Hi Tweeters! msg re Nokia Friend View as @RachelgC5Rr4 @hot_vixen3 @octoberswirls @celeste_2qn - work 2gether?    
    
    
    @gldmeier Beit Shemesh eruv has omed meruba al haparutz and no street shaar le'shaar also no intercity road or market road running thru    
    
    
    @gldmeier And FYI, you missed the inside joke, I accuse @noahroth of chumras when I know his methodology is kofer the halachic process    
    
    
    What feature phone app co's are M&A targets? What are open issues for location based alerts? Grizzly subscribers know! http://goo.gl/ZGplN    
    
    
    Press release for Grizzly Analytics report on Nokia research in NanoTechnology for Mobile http://goo.gl/990E4 #nokia #nanotech    
    
    
    @noahroth @gldmeier Ashkenazi and Sefardi = Talmud Bavli and Yerushalmi, duh.  You believe in Talmud, right?    
    
    
    @noahroth then my work here is done....    
    
    
    Who's adding "lanes" to phone GPS? Passive info delivery on phone screensavers? Search by SMS? Grizzly subscribers know! http://goo.gl/15nQI    
    
    
    @bethalltimelow 1 Harry Potter classmate Anthony Goldstein sounds Jewish. Also c book Harry Potter & Judaism http://qurl.com/sq1g3    
    
    
    @noahroth Which Pinati? At the gas station on 38? How was it?    
    
    
    @Noahide Where exactly are the Hanot ruins?  Are they an organized site for people to visit, or just there to be found and seen?    
    
    
    This is an absolute must-read on problems and challenges facing the Jewish world - all parts of it - http://qurl.com/3wk8h #fb    
    
    
    Are @aubrey_w6426e @samantha_oj6r98 @RachelgC5Rr4 @hot_vixen3 @octoberswirls @celeste_2qn real people? Posted same Hi Tweeters msg re #Nokia    
    
    
        
    
    
    Anyone know if Otzar Beit Din wine bought AFTER zman biyur (like now) needs 2 b mafkired? Source please not just opinion #shmita #kashrut    
    
    
    Brilliant http://qurl.com/jggqm read to the end...  #chareidi #pashkevil #fb    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @noahroth @shiraabel @asoldiersmother Noah baloney the demonstrators are 1-2% of Hareidi society.  1-2% of a lot is a lot.    
    
    
    @noahroth Ah, OK, 80% might be close in that case, but I still think lower, many work at teaching or adminstering even if off the books    
    
    
    @noahroth I've been told the best is to buy a pre-paid T-Mobile usim, but I've never done it. To divert voice calls you need to do it here.    
    
    
    @noahroth What? Don't you tweet via SMS? Much faster on most phones. And cheaper when roaming.    
    
    
    @noahroth hope you have/had a safe flight...    
    
    
    New Nokia patent on NanoTech touchscreens http://goo.gl/zZaLO see whole picture Grizzly Analytics report http://goo.gl/f9Qit #nokia #nano    
    
    
    Interesting article on #chareidi demographics and #secular #israeli perception: http://qurl.com/b2w8h    
    
    
    Shavua tov!  Looking for a ride from Beit Shemesh to Jerusalem for a young couple.  #Beit #Shemesh #rbs #jerusalem #ride    
    
    
    @noahroth re Haba Lihogecha Kam Lehorgo Yaakov ran b4 any attack my Q is why fear no gzar din on him OR malach hamavet ma li hacha...    
    
    
    @noahroth (continued) have to say that Esav had bechira to kill him and he was chayav to worry (see Or HaChayim on Yosef in the pit)    
    
    
    Google feature phone service http://goo.gl/ARXe6 Grizzly Analytics customers read implications 4 Google acquisitions http://goo.gl/ekLUJ    
    
    
    #Google feature phone svc http://goo.gl/ARXe6 Grizzly Analytics customers read what this means for Google acquisitions http://goo.gl/ekLUJ    
    
    
    Google feature phone svc http://goo.gl/ARXe6 Grizzly Analytics customers read what this means for Google acquisitions http://goo.gl/ekLUJ    
    
    
    Google feature-phone svc http://goo.gl/ARXe6 Grizzly Analytics customers read what this means for Google acquisitions http://goo.gl/ekLUJ    
    
    
    @noahroth I'm also having weird things happen w/ Wave on Firefox.  Are you using wave for anything interesting, or playing around?    
    
    
    @noahroth I tend to leave hardware to others. Why what's the prob?    
    
    
    Dilbert on Twitter http://qurl.com/dvrzz #dilbert #twitter #fb    
    
    
    Study: Western aliya has added NIS 800m to economy http://qurl.com/s9p4q #aliya #fb    
    
    
    I agree w @noahroth recommendation of Pinati - good food nice place decent prices and a gas station out the window http://qurl.com/94dyh    
    
    
    Nokia N900 price even lower just $499 http://qurl.com/bm2rb reviews are good although I like my Android phone #nokia #n900 #linux    
    
    
    Interesting article given the debate about brain death diagnosis...  http://qurl.com/ndqww #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth @HilzFuld Noah how was the Egged museum? Had fun at Latrun climbing on tanks - good 4 lil kids. KLP icecream at tzomet nachshon.    
    
    
    Reported recall of some Coke in Israel http://qurl.com/2n7n2 only if expiration March 18,19,22 #coke #israel pass it on...    
    
    
    Nokia NanoTech mixes graphene&plasmonic nanostructures 4 photonics & optoelectronics http://goo.gl/vnsBb Grizzly report http://goo.gl/aUyMP    
    
    
    REALLY enjoying Android on my new Samsung Galaxy http://qurl.com/67shq more computery than phone-y but great access to a lot of systems    
    
    
    Nokia indoor positioning http://goo.gl/Jlp42 RF tech for Time/Direction of Arrival. Grizzly Analytics has the details http://goo.gl/ezeu0    
    
    
    Interesting Haaretz article on Chareidim entering the workplace http://qurl.com/9mpnm #fb    
    
    
    Who's using Google Wave? Let me know and send me your e-mail address, it'll only be useful with enough others using it....  #wave #fb    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics subscribers got reports analyzing Nokia & Motorola research in wearable devices. Subscribe now! http://goo.gl/ezeu0    
    
    
    Nokia N97 Mini finally available $579 from Nokia $479 at Amazon http://qurl.com/yd2cs strong location-based social networking #nokia #n97    
    
    
    @noahroth Let me guess, kavod rabbonim isn't found in shas or rishonim?    
    
    
    Disturbing: Rav Elyashiv manipulated by question asker w/ agenda http://qurl.com/4lm5m very lacking in kavod #fb #chareidi    
    
    
    Anyone know when the Nokia N97 Mini will get LifeCasting? Price looks great http://qurl.com/yd2cs #Nokia #N97    
    
    
    Book fair of Beit Shemesh authors- very impressive number for small town! Here's list with links to books http://qurl.com/cy1wn #betshemesh    
    
    
    Check out Groupon's daily deal - huge discounts on the coolest stuff in your city. http://gr.pn/aMYg9L #groupon    
    
    
    #Groupon looks like good deals if you live in the States http://goo.gl/FnkDe and rumor says #Google is going to buy them #fb    
    
    
    Google on a patent rampage now bidding $2M for Modu's IP http://goo.gl/4wOY4 incl phones using contacts stored on other devices #google #fb    
    
    
    Google patent rampage now bidding $2M to buy Modu's IP http://goo.gl/4wOY4 incl phones using contacts stored on other devices #google    
    
    
    Anyone reading this use GroupOn? http://qurl.com/tw2yl Rumor says Google may buy them. Curious to hear feedback from users in USA. #fb    
    
    
    Survey: If u can find your WiFi net's MAC addr, can u check if its in http://samy.pl/androidmap/index.php let me know Y or N. Thanks! #fb    
    
    
    A 5-minute history of the Middle East problem: http://qurl.com/7zpkp As he says, simple to describe, impossible to solve. #israel #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth somehow this made me think of you... http://qurl.com/mrjdl    
    
    
    Fascinating article http://qurl.com/vqs5g and book by BGU prof http://qurl.com/95q74 #Torah #gematria #bgu #bengurion    
    
    
    Fascinating article on meaning in Hebrew words http://qurl.com/vqs5g and book by BGU prof http://qurl.com/95q74  #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth re yr tweet "80% min of haredim CHOOSE not to work" I thought so 2 but math sez 1 teacher per 3-4 families + admin & other jobs    
    
    
    Boruch Dayan Emes C'K Bostener Rebbe Levi Yitzchok Horowitz of Boston & Har Nof interesting history & thoughts in http://qurl.com/y7k84    
    
    
    @noahroth one teacher per 30-40 kids, all amortized    
    
    
    @noahroth ex-champions    
    
    
    @benDurham re Jewish wizards in HP some guess Anthony Goldstein is, note Avada Kedavra is hebrew/aramaic, also see http://qurl.com/qtqy4    
    
    
    @noahroth re Yosef and hishtadlus I think the midrash ba'mekor starts w/ "Yosef ish emuna haya" eg only for him as prototype of emuna    
    
    
    @noahroth I realized that I wrote here http://qurl.com/483r3 about why Yosef was held to this standard... #parsha #vayeshev #Torah    
    
    
    Still looking for Chanukah gifts? Teens & young adults like the book Harry Potter and Torah http://qurl.com/qtqy4 #Chanukah #hanukah #gift    
    
    
    I'm not a fan of Jews going on Har HaBayit but this is amazing: see how seriously the Arabs take Jewish prayer! http://qurl.com/wjw8h    
    
    
    Grizzly customers now know which cellphone co's are researching location-based song playing & location log analysis http://goo.gl/rR8gI #fb    
    
    
    Grizzly customers now know which cellphone co's are researching location-based song playing & location log analysis http://goo.gl/rR8gI    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics reports which cellphone co's are researching location-based song playing & location log analysis http://goo.gl/rR8gI    
    
    
    Hamas mourns Bin Laden same day they reconcile with Palestinian Authority http://goo.gl/CdT4d building blocks for peace? sure. #fb    
    
    
    @NaNplayer @mobiDevJC Any thought of NaNplayer on other platforms?    
    
    
    Enjoyed so many Beit Shemesh authors at book fair! List of books w/ links here: http://qurl.com/p68vl #betshemesh #beitshemesh    
    
    
    Anyone know where the tekes Zochrim in Israel is being streamed? #israel #zikaron #zochrim    
    
    
    @noahroth That's the kotel or zochrim?    
    
    
    The annual zochrim is a different, dati run, tekes, this year at Sultan's pool. I went last year it was very moving    
    
    
    @noahroth I would agree with you, but this one is not different for being dati, it's that it's grass roots bringing in families of fallen    
    
    
    @StryStry Harry Potter actor Jewish http://qurl.com/t772b and series has lots of connections to Jewish thought http://qurl.com/tfglc    
    
    
    really enjoying Android on my Samsung Galaxy http://qurl.com/7wmgr #android #samsung #cellphone #smartphone    
    
    
    Good article on #Gilad #Shalit negotiations http://qurl.com/gsnp2 - remember this is all caused by #Arabs choosing #terror over #peace    
    
    
    And I thought @noahroth tweets too much!  http://qurl.com/j3nqs    
    
    
    @noahroth @MarkSoFla @Gsix R David says 2 "goons" took him out by his arms when he wore talis over his head like only the Rav there does    
    
    
    Why I like Netanyahu: recent economic speech http://qurl.com/3kq2f     #Israel #economy #netanyahu #bibi    
    
    
    @noahroth You're not reading the right news sources...  http://qurl.com/svbhq    
    
    
        
    
    
    Anyone tried Nokia N900? Price is down to only $521 http://qurl.com/r87ny while N97 down to $492 http://qurl.com/36twl Comments? #nokia    
    
    
    One hour til coffee!   #fb    
    
    
    Coffee after a fast day -- life begins again....   #fb    
    
    
    Harry Potter and Torah Blog for VaYechi: Joseph, Egypt, and Magical Protection http://qurl.com/wh17r   - #Torah #Vayechi #Harry #Potter    
    
    
    Harry Potter and Torah Blog for VaYechi: Joseph, Egypt, and Magical Protection http://qurl.com/wh17r - #fb    
    
    
    Great high school math education by my brother in the Bronx http://qurl.com/chww3  #Bronx #math #education    
    
    
    This is a great one - what might the world's list of terrorists have in common?  http://qurl.com/v9jrf #israel #peace #islam #foxnews    
    
    
    Looks like a book that says it straight...  http://qurl.com/3sn9z - Strong Horse: Power, Politics & the Clash of Arab Civilizations    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great article comparing airport security in USA with that in Israel http://qurl.com/4swv8    #Israel #security #fb    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/HkMyDA    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/peKhYP    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/_7eU3w    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/Piyvfi    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/2Jt_Rz    
    
    
    Grizzly Analytics releases 155-page report on Next Generation Mobile Location Technologies http://goo.gl/r02bd    
    
    
    Read about location-based song playlists, location-based reminders, smartphone calendar navigation & more http://goo.gl/r02bd    
    
    
    What are Apple Google Microsoft & others really doing with logs of user locations? Read about research in their labs http://goo.gl/r02bd    
    
    
    Read about location-based song playlists, location-based reminders, smartphone calendar navigation, research in using …http://lnkd.in/3K6J-S    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/P_zGug    
    
    
    Letter I wrote to NY Times about terrorism reporting http://qurl.com/94hcv is quoted to defend Feng Shui! http://qurl.com/16cn3 #nyt #fb    
    
    
    @noahroth Never heard of PBH but to test my Googling I found http://qurl.com/dswqw original ref seems to be his book http://qurl.com/m6rpk    
    
    
    Just realized in vid Rav Elyashiv manipulated by askan RavElyashiv refers to Beit Din HaGadol ie Rabbanut BeitDin? http://qurl.com/4lm5m    
    
    
    @noahroth count your blessings they could be in the same part of the house....  advice: adults go to a third part of the house...    
    
    
    @noahroth When you get your Nokia you'll be able to "side-load" maps in Ovi Maps even w/o data roaming   #nokia #e72    
    
    
    Chareidi dad wants 2 sell kidney 2 pay 4 kids wedding, R Elyashiv says no http://qurl.com/pt3pn I say Torah gave us solution: work! #fb    
    
    
    Nokia N97 Mini smal and thin with slider keyboard but no new location/facebook app yet - only $460 unlocked http://qurl.com/t9zcy    
    
    
    Nokia N97 Mini smal and thin w/ slider keyboard but no new location/facebook app yet only $460 unlocked http://qurl.com/t9zcy #nokia #n97    
    
    
    @noahroth I tend to try to be conservative with these things, when I can afford it.    
    
    
    Just read that 6 out of 8 IDF Golani commanders are dati - http://qurl.com/ph2vn   #israel #idf    
    
    
    Location-based song playlists, location-based reminders, navigation integrated with cellphone calendar & contacts,...: http://lnkd.in/V7sBm6    
    
    
    Location-based song playlists, location-based reminders, navigation integrated with cellphone calendar & contacts,...: http://lnkd.in/xbtHet    
    
    
    Many phone log locations of Wi-Fi networks but Grizzly Analytics found what they'll do next with user location data http://goo.gl/8V77m    
    
    
    @noahroth re blood drive need to go once a year to keep family coverage (I really do it altruistically, but self-interest doesn't hurt)    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are developing new location technologies that will revolutionize smartphone use,...: http://lnkd.in/gu-BXP    
    
    
    @noahroth re greenlight - any word can be verbed    
    
    
    Being nice is back "in:" #WSJ writes of trend against gossip http://qurl.com/c5k9g - similar to #Jewish approach http://qurl.com/k9t9l    
    
    
    #NYT #Israel economy http://qurl.com/6vk3k cites StartUp Nation http://qurl.com/46fcy Golden Age of Jewish Achievement http://qurl.com/y32wt    
    
    
    @mayerreich Did you eat at the new place? How does it compare to Pinati? #beitshemesh #betshemesh Beit Shemesh #restaurant    
    
    
    Anyone eat at the new Beit Shemesh restaurant yesterday? How is it? How does it compare to say Pinati? #betshemesh #beitshemesh    
    
    
    @rabbiyhaber Tracking down mekoros from your "tachlis" shiur can't find right part of Rasisei Leila. Par 15 starting "2 minei hasagos"?    
    
    
    This is great: a PlayMobile airport security check toy http://qurl.com/2y9y4 next a suicide bomber Barbie? #israel #toy #terrorism    
    
    
    Another #book on #aliya to #israel: Settling for More http://qurl.com/sdv6d    
    
    
    Apple's iMessage - a threat to who? New blog message about iMessage, SMS, RIM, and more. http://goo.gl/R2emf #fb    
    
    
    Apple's iMessage - a threat to who? New blog message about iMessage, SMS, RIM, and more. http://goo.gl/R2emf    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/uXyG4J    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/itYbHy    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/PQNk26    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/CrzbRp    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/A9PMx6    
    
    
    Apple, Google, Microsoft & others are working on location-based media, social networks in navigation, location...: http://lnkd.in/GgVHss    
    
    
    Gotta say, great commercial from #Motorola for their #Android powered #Droid http://qurl.com/14zr2   @HilzFuld    
    
    
    RIM - Strong contender in next-generation mobile location technologies? New Grizzly Analytics blog message. http://goo.gl/OAcNr #lbs #fb    
    
    
    RIM - Strong contender in next-generation mobile location technologies? New Grizzly Analytics blog message. http://goo.gl/OAcNr    
    
    
    @cultofmac iMessage looks great http://goo.gl/Ep5QP  but Google can copy it in a heartbeat- integrating SMS w/ Google Talk & GMAIL chat    
    
    
    @BGR Eulogizing RIM may be premature, BBM is paid for by co's for the secure e-mail integration, not just sms'ing http://goo.gl/R2emf     
    
    
    @nokia You've been envisioning flexible phones around wrists since 888&Morph and researching lot too goo.gl/7uKAQ what's new here?    
    
    
    VMWare acquiring spree: SlideRocket cloud presentations, SocialCast microblogging, now DigitalFuel financial mgt SaaS http://goo.gl/HvvNe    
    
    
    @noahroth re E72 Hebrew not sure why req jailbreaking recommend not voiding warranty but should be downloadable? only guessing no experience    
    
    
    Superbus wants to hire Chareidim but Modiin&RBS Chareidim not interested (in Elad they are) http://qurl.com/drhpj #jobs #chareidim #israel    
    
    
    Finally a video that expresses what I think of #Farmville http://qurl.com/fhgcm  #fb    
    
    
    Haiti disaster: China sent 50 rescuers, UK sent 72, Arab countries sent none, Israel sent hundreds http://qurl.com/hbwv2 #haiti #israel #fb    
    
    
    Disproportionate response: China sent #Haiti 50 rescuers, Arab countries sent none, #Israel sent hundreds http://qurl.com/hbwv2 #fb    
    
    
    RIP Robert B Parker my favorite mystery author - books: http://qurl.com/5myq4 - obit: http://qurl.com/d8qb6 #fb    
    
    
    RIP Robert B Parker my favorite mystery author - books: http://qurl.com/5myq4 - obit: http://qurl.com/d8qb6   #robert #parker #spenser    
    
    
    @cultofmac great article on iPads & styluses: I reached the conclusion for tech reasons in Feb but noone believes it http://goo.gl/9aOIp     
    
    
    Great .@CultOfMac article on pen input & iPad http://goo.gl/mGxRI  fits a trend in tech Apple is researching http://goo.gl/9aOIp  #fb    
    
    
    Great CultOfMac article on pen input & iPad http://goo.gl/mGxRI  fits a trend in tech Apple is researching...: http://lnkd.in/TKW_F2    
    
    
    Great CultOfMac article on pen input & iPad http://goo.gl/mGxRI  fits a trend in tech Apple is researching...: http://lnkd.in/qx_JAx    
    
    
    @MikeElgan great cultofmac article on iPad stylus: I reached the conclusion 4 tech reasons in Feb but noone believes http://goo.gl/9aOIp     
    
    
    @ElianaBenador What gdud is your son in? Amazing tekes. I was curious if anyone tweeted about it and saw your comment. Mazal tov!    
    
    
    @hanitagal What gdud is your son in? Amazing tekes! (Sorry for English) Mazal tov to them all!    
    
    
    @ElianaBenador Sorry if I touched a nerve, but false public accusations are assur le'halacha and illegal.    
    
    
    Anyone able to loan me car battery jumper cables?  #beitshemesh #betshemesh    
    
    
    Is looking for jumper cables - anyone in Sheinfeld area that can loan me this evening?  #fb    
    
    
    Segula to say Parshat HaMon on Tuesday this week.  http://qurl.com/ltzd4  - Dov says working hard is also a segula for parnasa. #minhag    
    
    
    @RustyMikeRadio @google Google does have cities marked in regular maps, but some apps & web sites use older versions of Google maps    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HilzFuld Easy to delete dups in google contacts online. Note for past few months I've noticed delay in syncing contacts at least on WM    
    
    
    @HilzFuld shouldn't sync do a merge?    
    
    
    Google buys SageTV http://goo.gl/r5Dkf  for GoogleTV http://goo.gl/5AWqO  or Android http://goo.gl/8bGzv  Grizzly sez both http://goo.gl/GLKNm     
    
    
    AOL's hillarious response to Yahoo! using their app name http://goo.gl/B3mhe  Grizzly Analytics likes Yahoo! recent innovations anyway #fb    
    
    
    RE: @nokia Grizzly Analytics has an 85-page report analyzing Nokia's research on NanoTechnology for Mobile. http://go… http://disq.us/2bt4rk    
    
    
    Interesting thought on the Torah's killing curse and Rambam http://qurl.com/hw4r7  @noahroth #torah    
    
    
    Thus @noahroth dismisses supernatural stuff in the Torah that has both Rambam's and the Rav's buy-in....    
    
    
    Location-Based Reminders: 54-page report from Grizzly Analytics, from iOS5 Reminders to the future being researched http://goo.gl/0SJtq     
    
    
    Location-Based Reminders: from iOS5 to the future being researched http://goo.gl/0SJtq  - 54-page report from Grizzly Analytics    
    
    
    @HilzFuld gotta include Waze @waze    
    
    
    @HilzFuld nope @waze is GPS with RT traffic reports gen'ed from phone tracking plus police reports from users. I predict acquisition    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Sorry, you're right, I thought you were still after best apps in general.    
    
    
    Nokia promoting solar energy trial .@NokiaSolar energy harvesting is part of their nanotech research http://goo.gl/MtuYg     
    
    
    @noahroth thanks for conversation starters I've earned my $million for 2day & have nothing else to do but tweet #not http://goo.gl/0OIyK     
    
    
    Nokia soon to reveal solar energy tech in trial http://goo.gl/PczDS  is it silicon carbide nanoflowers? http://goo.gl/MtuYg  .@NokiaSolar    
    
    
    Best Buy launches cloud music service .@BGR http://goo.gl/7lRJ8  powered by Israeli Catch Media http://goo.gl/wp9aR  once Google target    
    
    
        
    
    
    In 2007 only iphone apps were in-browser! http://goo.gl/fSaBk  RT .@cultofmac Patent Confirms Apple Will Allow Third-Party Widgets in iOS5    
    
    
    Shortcomings in #iOS5 location-based reminders & existing mobile apps, & research addressing the shortcomings http://goo.gl/vXINq  #iphone    
    
    
    @askGayleShimoff Can you say more about the new school initiative?    
    
    
    Great El Al ad http://qurl.com/s6k8h and suggested ad http://qurl.com/rccg1 #elal #security #tefillin #israel #jewish    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mikeeisenberg there's no shortage of robotics research here, both theoretical (Weizmann) and practical (Technion). But most funding is EU    
    
    
        
    
    
    BLOG POST: Nokia's solar powered phone experiment, and the search for the next big thing. http://goo.gl/avMAq  .@NokiaSolar    
    
    
    BLOG POST: .@Nokia solar powered phone experiment, and the search for the next big thing. http://goo.gl/avMAq  .@NokiaSolar    
    
    
    iPhone iOS5 location reminders look great, but other companies are doing the research to make them really work! http://goo.gl/EwYNB     
    
    
    Re friends in circles .@cultofmac T-Mobile MyFaves in 2007 http://goo.gl/oZ1fX  and T-Mobile Wing w/ HTC in 2007 http://goo.gl/mBsTW     
    
    
    @HilzFuld How? Not working for me, still saying no....    
    
    
    Hey .@HilzFuld have you tried this g+ browser app on your iPhone? http://goo.gl/XreTs  Let me know what you think....    
    
    
        
    
    
    Key mobile trends in 2012 according to Strategy Analytics, Vision Mobile & Grizzly Analytics http://goo.gl/FG39W  .@visionmobile .@SA_Update    
    
    
    Blog post: The Google+ misdirection - things Google's wants you to ignore for now http://goo.gl/sVGok  with concrete predictions    
    
    
    Google+ mobile - things Google isn't talking about and future directions http://goo.gl/sVGok  and predictions about Facebook counterattach    
    
    
    @HilzFuld ... because iOS5 is fully integrated with iCloud (Google+ Mobile) and Twitter (+Circles)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HilzFuld ... re +Hangouts on mobile this is also their answer to FB/Skype etc    
    
    
    @HilzFuld you're 20 seconds behind my Tweets....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld actually twitter sez my tweet was 10 seconds earlier than yours... anyway, "great minds think alike"    
    
    
    @HilzFuld re msgs of accepted Linkedin invites - see: inbox / invitations / archived #notreallyfail but bad tab labels    
    
    
    Google Plus: Four points people aren't focusing on, and five predictions related to Google, Facebook & mobile http://goo.gl/sVGok     
    
    
    Would technology revolutions like #solar powered phones save #Nokia? http://goo.gl/gtPcD  Tweet replies or blog comments welcome    
    
    
    .@HilzFuld re Google+ traffic in 2-3mo I'll bet u a buck xmas referrals & traffic will have g+ only 25% of FB & that'll be called good    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Rounds    
    
    
    @HilzFuld also bobsled    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Nimbuzz    
    
    
    Now .@unwiredtweets reports evidence of #iPhone stylus plans http://goo.gl/acFT0  continues a trend I discussed here: http://goo.gl/cn9os     
    
    
    Google Plus: Four points people aren't focusing on, and five predictions related to Google, Facebook & mobile http://goo.gl/sVGok     
    
    
        
    
    
    Checking out Google Plus gplus.to/krulwich So far: interesting and well done but not enough to beat FB and Twitter's momentum #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld maybe google+ is your number 1 referrer because noone on g+ has any other content to click on besides yours? :-)    
    
    
    Test tweet wow    
    
    
    Test Tweet from another address    
    
    
    Test g+ update to Twitter You received this message because Bruce (Dov) Krulwich shared it with  
yh3nbn-l9lb34@twittermail.com.    
    
    
    Another test G+ Tweet    
    
    
    Now a test Tweet & FB update    
    
    
    Dilbert on Twitter    
    
    
        
    
    
    If there are so many millions of Google+ users, why does this Google query only have about 654,000 results?  http://goo.gl/FOW16     
    
    
        
    
    
    BLOG: Google+ users: 9 million or 657,000? http://goo.gl/un4l9  Reasons to doubt the hype, while still being impressed with Google Plus    
    
    
    BLOG: Google+ users: 9 million or 657,000? http://goo.gl/un4l9  Reasons to doubt the hype despite liking #GooglePlus .@GooglePlusTweet    
    
    
    RIM to split network & phone divisions says .@BGR http://goo.gl/NXpXi  Grizzly Analytics has predicted this since April http://goo.gl/QBx0A     
    
    
    RIM to split network&phone divisions says .@BGR http://goo.gl/NXpXi  Grizzly predicted this in April http://goo.gl/QBx0A  http://goo.gl/HlkkZ     
    
    
    O Twittermail tem me proporcionado momentos de muita alegria! O Twittermail tem me proporcionado momentos de muita alegria!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I don't care how many times it's retweeted, no way Google's buying GroupOn for $2.5B - the price must be under $300M    
    
    
    Israel the one country not hurt by wikileaks http://qurl.com/tprsq the truth is on our side!    #fb    
    
    
    MobileCommerceTrends quotes 3 analysts predictions for 2012....  http://goo.gl/bTht8     
    
    
    @dalmaer I'm analyzing next-gen mobile location tech http://goo.gl/G5SM5  can we talk sometime about retail interests in that area?    
    
    
    Beit Shemesh stabbing appears romantic motivated what a surprise! 4 arrested. http://qurl.com/vs7zp http://qurl.com/z26v1 #betshemesh #fb    
    
    
    Nesher factory is again negotiating on the air we breathe in Beit Shemesh http://qurl.com/6h65k #betshemesh #beitshemesh #fb    
    
    
    BLOG: The next wave of mobile location-based services http://goo.gl/w1pGC  like music, settings, calendar, indoor navigation, and more!    
    
    
    @noahroth Windows 7 pinning    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HilzFuld http://yfrog.com/kef1np Tell your techies to put HTML comments around the contents of their SCRIPT tags.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Your site's Javascript is in <script> tags but not <!-- --> comments. OK for modern browsers but not some text extractors    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Apple developer said #iOS5 to include face DETECTION not face recognition. http://goo.gl/0KPYG  Many seem 2 b confusing the two!    
    
    
    @geppyp Do you enjoy being misquoted? http://goo.gl/0KPYG     
    
    
    @HilzFuld Great article, great quote from the face.com founder....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Try to copy/paste it from WORD - not 100% sure, but it's worked for me in other systems    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Copy them into WORD, turn them into a table, copy the whole table and paste it back into WP.  Might not work, but worth a try    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Avoid everything that seems backwards and you'll never get anything done!    
    
    
    @noahroth why high unemployment? I'm thinking higher taxes, which will be the opposite of what will truly help the middle class here    
    
    
    .@digitimes says Apple & Samsung looking at tech for solar powered phones - Nokia & Alta Devices also groundbreaking http://goo.gl/FjF7g     
    
    
    .@MikeElgan Amazon rumored doing same. But NXP slashed 2011 #NFC projections, maybe they know no NFC in #iphone5 ?http://goo.gl/S4CZf     
    
    
        
    
    
    @HilzFuld @noahroth Noah the structure flipped in Jan b/c of new laws (Ya, Hillel, I see your discussion b/c I follow both of you)    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @noahroth ... used to be you'd pay for the phone and get the discount on service w/ hitchayvut, but ....    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @noahroth ... the govt made service hitchayvuyot illegal. so now they discount the phone w/ hitchayvut (which is legal) and...    
    
    
    @HilzFuld @noahroth ... charge for service. I'm in the market for a few phones now, and pelephone seems highest, Orange & cellcom better    
    
    
    @noahroth Sounds about right. Pelephone quoted me that for only 400 mins&smss. Depends also on which phone    
    
    
    @HilzFuld That's so 1990's.  Nowadays we just redefine the grammar rules for changing mediums of communication....    
    
    
    @noahroth In Israel, because we don't have Sundays, every day feels like a Monday    
    
    
    enjoying today's Dilbert....  http://qurl.com/3ls4h    
    
    
    enjoying today's Dilbert.... http://qurl.com/3ls4h   #fb    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Curious what you think: I'm deciding between Galaxy SII and Motorola Milestone 2 - M has QWERTY, SII has 2.3 & gyro. thoughts?    
    
    
    @HilzFuld no need, but when I used to have one (TyTN) I loved it. But the s2 is nice in every other way....    
    
    
        
    
    
    How PayPal and Amazon will quickly dominate mobile #NFC payments http://goo.gl/MYA5D  even on .@Nokia phones    
    
    
    Why PayPal or Amazon's NFC payment method will work on Nokia phones even w/o Secure Chip .@nokia .@nfc_hub http://goo.gl/MYA5D     
    
    
    Hey @paypal and @amazon you're on the right path with #nfc mobile payments! http://goo.gl/MYA5D  #grizzlyanalytics    
    
    
    How @PayPal and @Amazon will soon dominate mobile phone #NFC payments http://goo.gl/MYA5D     
    
    
    Great article by Alan Dershowitz on the #Dubai #terrorist assassination http://qurl.com/lpq9h    
    
    
    Show your support for the #Israeli #Mossad going against terrorists http://qurl.com/zndzt    
    
    
    WikiLeaks: Netanyahu willing 2 swap land 4 peace http://qurl.com/fj3mk why is this new? Said it 2yrs ago, Palestinians won't stop terror #fb    
    
    
    Amazon Local deals service now developing mobile app for iOS/Android/web http://goo.gl/8D8CO  arch built w/ AWS, RubyOnRails, SOA....    
    
    
    .@PayPal and .@Amazon poised to scoop up the #NFC payments market http://goo.gl/0V33M  will they succeed before the others catch up?    
    
    
    The next wave of cellphone location-based services http://goo.gl/916xo  location-based playlists and phone settings, and more....    
    
    
    Amazon Local deals service now developing mobile app for iOS/Android/web http://goo.gl/8D8CO   .@groupon look out! .@Amazon is coming....    
    
    
    @RotaryJerusalem can you post a map link (msg me to ask how) to kalaniot or other nice sites near Beit Shemesh and Emek HaEla? #beitshemesh    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Do you see the FB Messenger app? Android market on my new S2 on Orange doesn't seem to have it.    
    
    
    @HilzFuld Definitely awesome, still in the stage of playing and figuring out what's useful.    
    
    
    @orange_israel @orangeil Why can't I see the new Facebook Messenger app in Android market?    
    
    
    @rabbisedley Curious about the caffeine pill you mentioned taking before Tisha B'Av was it time-release? how didn't it effect you at night?    
    
    
    Great article on recent Jewish charity organizations - http://qurl.com/9mwd1 #fb    
    
    
    I know this happens in San Francisco but here too? RT @triskerrebbe: Big wedding tonight in bet shemesh reb motta frank with rav cheshin    
    
    
    @noahroth If someone's going to label chometz KFP on Passover, why not label it that way all year round?    
    
    
    Nokia researchers publish book on NanoTechnology for Future Mobile Devices - looks very cool...  http://qurl.com/w4gvg  #fb    
    
    
    Nokia researchers publish book on NanoTechnology for Future Mobile Devices - looks very cool... http://qurl.com/vy1zb #Nokia #nanotech    
    
    
    BLOG reply to .@cultofmac claim that Apple's done inventing new devices: Why he's wrong & inventions in the pipeline http://goo.gl/IXzLf     
    
    
    