@marenhogan your own, like usual    
    
    
    Are You One of Us? Applicants and Employment Branding http://www.recruiter.com/articles/applicants-employment-brand/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    This is great: Matt Kirshen: "I was playing chess with my friend and he said, 'Let's make this interesting'. So we stopped playing chess."    
    
    
    As a business owner or manager, which government initiative would most impact your decision to hire more people? http://linkd.in/n49VTR     
    
    
    Interesting npr interview, i guess authors of curious george escaped from nazis in france...    
    
    
    LinkedIn Stock Surges On Rumors Of A Big Partnership With Facebook http://www.businessinsider.com/linkedin-stock-surges-on-rumors-a-big-partnership-with-facebook-2011-9?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_term=&utm_content=&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    LinkedIn Poll: What Makes you Hire? http://lnkd.in/piFyfE     
    
    
    Female Talent Seen As Untapped Resource in Emerging Markets http://lnkd.in/gHC6YJ     
    
    
    India Sees Shortage of Top Talent http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/india-sees-shortage-of-top-talent/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Facebook Timeline & changes to profiles http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/facebook-timeline/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Not another social network profile to worry about! Here are some new Facebook profile tips... http://lnkd.in/ENaHHR     
    
    
    If Jobs were like School http://lnkd.in/vXVc8F     
    
    
    Who Not to Be in an Online Community http://lnkd.in/VSqNzW     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/kxJFTA  Hi Nicanor, I don't know of any free ones.. I think Basecamp is HTML5 compatible and works well with those devices....    
    
    
    Those Impossible to Find Newbies http://lnkd.in/mHpe7T     
    
    
    Recruiting the New Textistentialists http://lnkd.in/cnKxdB     
    
    
    Starbucks is teaming up with @Jobs_for_USA to help fund new job creation http://lnkd.in/7anTdc     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/imdezf  Thank you all for the nice notes, glad you like this week's features!    
    
    
    The Vision of Steve Jobs and Recruiting 201: http://lnkd.in/sxsrXv     
    
    
    @braingain interesting. Not sure. Lemme check    
    
    
    @braingain cool, what does it do?    
    
    
    The Apple Bisociative Approach to Recruiting http://lnkd.in/zuhWBm     
    
    
    The 147 Companies That Control Everything - Forbes http://onforb.es/ptQEiM     
    
    
    On the 7th day, there was power #clp    
    
    
    @SmartRecruiters No problem! Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    Good Headhunting with The Headhuntress http://lnkd.in/Vmkv7Y     
    
    
    @JohnSumser RE the list we have over 1000 networks, blogs,  - indexed for the search engine: http://tinyurl.com/aqohql    
    
    
    starting a blog - any reason NOT to choose Wordpress?    
    
    
    pretty cool.. FeedSquares - Supercharge your Google Reader - Google Chrome extension gallery http://bit.ly/cgvoBv    
    
    
    new tool for searching linkedin and other sites for candidates: Social Recruiting Tools | Social Media Recruiting http://bit.ly/aLHS0B    
    
    
    supposed to make your cpu light more natural, worth a shot- F.lux http://bit.ly/buXseL    
    
    
    edgr    
    
    
    @dmanaster looking forward to ERE!  hope to meet up with you there sometime. #ereexpo    
    
    
    Retiring at 80 http://lnkd.in/JfPkRQ     
    
    
    hotel key came with safety tips...a good sign?  love you hotwire    
    
    
    @Fishdogs post a discussion in TalentBar group on Linkedin and I'll feature it.  we all need that sort of help right now.    
    
    
    @Fishdogs your career branding group, might give it a boost..    
    
    
    @Fishdogs @animal are either of you at the ere?    
    
    
    @Fishdogs the next version of www.splits.org will put this one to shame...  ;)  yup, I'm at ERE...    
    
    
    @Animal haha    
    
    
    if you like beer and talking about geeky things like twitter, let me buy you a drink tonight... #ereexpo    
    
    
    @jasonwhitman I'm going to try to at least double my caloric intake from last ere...    
    
    
    @TimDineen and to eat, don't forget eating.    
    
    
    Top Five Reasons to Join LinkedIn Groups http://lnkd.in/23F__D     
    
    
    @Talk_Marketing @sirenf cool, glad you liked it!    
    
    
    Facebook Career Pages: How to Get Them Right http://lnkd.in/CaafTQ     
    
    
    @ryanleary barely. just got back from a week of vacation with 3 kids under 5.    
    
    
    great tool for @ning builders gets bought out.. Constant Contact Acquires Social Media Inbox Startup Nutshell Mail http://tcrn.ch/bQ3fwM    
    
    
    @marenhogan my sister lived there for a while and picked up an accent. watch out!    
    
    
    Style Matters. Management Style, that is http://lnkd.in/r2Z9FD     
    
    
    Oops meant to say it's a good day when you remember the people you worked with over what you worked on    
    
    
    more peanut butter and chocolate: http://blog.linkedin.com/2010/05/25/find-and-follow-your-linkedin-connections-on-twitter    
    
    
    @stantonmjones tx and I just included you in the @milesj/CIO list    
    
    
    @Jerry_Albright it's said to be more viralent than the black plague    
    
    
    You think you're a blackberry guy until you pick up an iPhone. It can be yr whole office. And you can be a cabbage farmer with it.    
    
    
    @ElaineERE that was the first time frozen tractor wheels were mentioned on twitter    
    
    
    @eddiearsyad I feel like a traitor..    
    
    
    How Resumes Get Read http://lnkd.in/_8ecmd     
    
    
    Just what I'm thinking about today... http://lnkd.in/ewHufF     
    
    
    @jdakers how about ice cubes? that's what the instructions told me.    
    
    
    @jdakers that's what i figured - an "idiot proof" way but probably not the best    
    
    
    Certain groups on Linkedin have an amazing new interface. Looks like Facebook stirred with Twitter.  Example: http://bit.ly/dDdf7A    
    
    
    @LouBonica oh no! is that right? I just asked everyone's input. Perhaps only a % see the new update?    
    
    
    @LouBonica oh thank goodness. I just love when I send out incorrect info to 20K people (you got me scared.) It happens often to me. ;)    
    
    
    @LouBonica no problem at all. and consider yourself listed!    
    
    
    @johnsantangelo thanks for the note! it's an exciting time for MPS of course and I wish everyone there the best.    
    
    
    @splits #needaguy test java developer in Hartford, CO United States in Technology #splits    
    
    
    @jasonwhitman check how twitterjobsearch is following through links to search the referenced job... Pretty cool    
    
    
    @TimDineen it's my real middle name    
    
    
    @ginab coming from you, that got me interested ;)    
    
    
    @splits #haveaguy test candidate in  Taiwan in Legal #splits    
    
    
    What Business Insider Does Right http://lnkd.in/rmXVrS     
    
    
    @marenhogan remember you don't have to choose    
    
    
    @splits #needaguy test candidate in San Diego, CA United States in Semiconductor #splits    
    
    
    @splits #wantodosplits java c# developers software in Hartford, CT United States #splits    
    
    
    Social Media Housekeeping Tips for 2012 http://lnkd.in/ycu7fV     
    
    
    No kids this weekend, I'll either get everything done that I've been trying to for the past year or just watch tv for 60 hours straight...    
    
    
    I like this cornerstone content principle “@chrisbrogan: Use WordPress pages like a pro from @willieljackson -  http://bit.ly/8Xcqmi”    
    
    
    @LinkedIn any plans to make a seperate iPhone app for linkedin groups or integration with your current app?    
    
    
    RE: @byosko That's a really great post... People hear over and over about the guys at Foursquare turning down $100m an… http://disq.us/do548    
    
    
    So there IS a way to make a movie about superhero robots completely boring    
    
    
    @marenhogan ok I'm talking about robots and you about star trek.. I think I'm with the right company    
    
    
    The Dangers of Startups http://www.recruiter.com/blog/dangers-of-startups/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer’s Job Hunt http://www.recruiter.com/articles/rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer%e2%80%99s-job-hunt/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    A Recruiter To-Do List for 2012 http://www.recruiter.com/articles/a-recruiter-to-do-list-for-2012/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    At 230am on a weekday, Twitter is pretty much a bunch of robots talking to each other    
    
    
    Recruiting Tech: 5 Game Changers for 2012 http://www.recruiter.com/articles/recruiting-tech-5-game-changers-for-2012/ … via @recruiterdotcom #recruiting #software    
    
    
    @justinpirie I'm going to try to not be so US-centric.. ;)    
    
    
    @brownpf trying to sleep, of course. ;)    
    
    
    this is incredible. M.I.T. Game-Changer: Free Online Education For All - Forbes http://onforb.es/vZZcDS     
    
    
    @marenation that name is too funny. I will follow you anywhere you go    
    
    
    @KerrySOMalley tx! hey btw, i added you to @milesj/cmo list, check it out    
    
    
    Congrats Indeed! RE: Indeed.com doubles its floor space - StamfordAdvocate http://bit.ly/99i0xg    
    
    
    Working from home ain't lonely when you talk to people for a living...    
    
    
    @ewmonster nice fortune mention! I go to my wife, hey I know that guy...    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin mexico i assume in your background.  beautiful.  hope to see you again in 09    
    
    
    @TaraRepucci thanks - interested to see where you end up!    
    
    
    this is a good against the grain piece about Microsoft vs. Google | Wired.com http://bit.ly/bfVqrQ    
    
    
    8:25am two weeks after starting new position, finally got through every email & Linkedin message. not bad right? ;) Sorry for any delays!    
    
    
    Why Recruiting Looks Easy http://www.recruiter.com/articles/why-recruiting-looks-easy/ … via @recruiterdotcom #recruiting    
    
    
    # java in ,  US #splits    
    
    
    checking out how #recruiters are using www.splits.org to do #splits.  yes, I'm hashtag crazy.    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin check out that www.splits.org when you have a sec.. would love to hear your comments. also, let's do some kind of event soon    
    
    
    @jjbuss check out Twitter for recruiters to do splits: www.splits.org  would love to hear your thoughts    
    
    
    @ahjobslist I would love to hear your thoughts on the splits site!    
    
    
    @recruiter123 nice pic!  if you enter in candidates like that, people should find them even with general twitter searches.  good luck!!    
    
    
    @donnafryer thanks for the splits mention!    
    
    
    Great to be back in Boston commons after maybe 10 or 15 years... Still don't know my way around...    
    
    
        
    
    
    What makes a good recruiting firm website? http://lnkd.in/GMunuU  #recruiting    
    
    
    Who Benefits from Facebook's $100B IPO? http://www.recruiter.com/blog/who-benefits-from-facebooks-100b-ipo/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Why Communities Matter http://wp.me/pkncT-et  via @marenhogan    
    
    
    had fun meeting with two very smart people today.. one said "do one thing very well and say no to everything else" and the other said..    
    
    
    "find someone doing just what you're doing and don't make the same mistakes"    
    
    
    @Craig_Silverman congrats! Look forward to hearing about your new venture.    
    
    
    @Animal einstein had less of a groove between the two halves of his brain.  he was pretty much beyond human.  just a fun fact.  or fiction.    
    
    
    thinking I need a new online picture.  my family just said my mouth is hanging open like I'm some kind of idiot.    
    
    
    made a new Google profile, man these guys are taking over the world. http://www.google.com/profiles/milesjennings    
    
    
    12 killer websites worth watching - David Clarke, BGT Partners - iMediaConnection.com

http://bit.ly/bGQQrk    
    
    
    @marenhogan did I pocket dial you? You purse dial me like every four days...    
    
    
    2012 Recruitment: What’s Behind the Buzzwords http://www.recruiter.com/articles/2012-recruitment-what%e2%80%99s-behind-the-buzzwords/ … via @Adam_InnovateCV    
    
    
    reading http://tinyurl.com/dxu2qs    
    
    
    just updated the passive candidate search to include google profiles: http://tinyurl.com/djmump    
    
    
    update from Twitter about OAuth api issue. http://tinyurl.com/ck8dgu - they say it'll be fixed later today #splits    
    
    
    @dmanaster sorry never got to meet at last ere.  but it was a great event.  let's talk sometime.    
    
    
    @dmanaster thanks!  I guess you're in NYC, do you want to meet up sometime in the next couple of months?    
    
    
    looking at some start ups on http://www.chubbybrain.com  pretty cool    
    
    
    Social Recruiting Trends in 2012 http://www.recruiter.com/articles/social-recruiting-trends-in-2012/ … via @job_magic    
    
    
    looking for the best c# / .NET developers for a hedge fund in Greenwich, CT #jobs #developer #software    
    
    
    #jobs won't be the end of monster.com.  might help them.    
    
    
    feeling hungry after a $9 whole foods lunch    
    
    
    @recruiterparker thanks!  glad you like it    
    
    
    vowing never to write "please retweet" again    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    Our wonderful hiring process... Here's How Jim Got a Job [Infographic] http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/how-jim-got-a-job-infographic/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    thinking how google profiles + twitter = web 3.0    
    
    
    gearing up to fold laundry.  do all kids wear 5 outfits a day?    
    
    
    @sparrowsmith it's about identity on the web + real time communication between those identities.  i'l have to write a blog...    
    
    
    my son just said "that's my unhappy smile" (for pictures only)    
    
    
    @sparrowsmith will do.  ah, now I see I'm talking to a pro.  i better do some research.  ;)   research a blog post, as if... ;)    
    
    
    when google profiles have RSS we'll be in business...  http://www.google.com/profiles/milesjennings    
    
    
    @Natallini there's a direct correlation between love of martial arts and beer    
    
    
    reading Suzanne Travers post on working with social media: http://www.talentbar.com/profiles/blogs/working-with-social-media-im    
    
    
    i want a 5 7 5 about being jealous of pesticided neighbors lawn. #haiku    
    
    
    getting slammed with Java jobs in CT.  We need people for contract roles and fulltime positions.  java j2ee software #jobs    
    
    
    endorsing all i do not know @animal    
    
    
    @Animal amen    
    
    
    @zxed not love, just acceptance of the inevitability of their ubiquity    
    
    
    @BristolCtNet love your site! would like to connect with you sometime about a couple of ideas    
    
    
    glad that 104.1 is back.  my musical tastes never budged since you were gone    
    
    
    my son says i look like a princess in my bathrobe    
    
    
    cursing Oauth!    
    
    
    tball and yardwork.  85 deg today  nice!    
    
    
    @totalcio consider yourself listed!    
    
    
    Putting Soldiers to Work http://www.recruiter.com/articles/putting-soldiers-to-work/ … via @recruiterdotcom #military #jobs    
    
    
    @byosko yup, 500. I was obsessed with them for perhaps 49 hours    
    
    
    Weekly round-up: Social Media, Recruiting Tech, Helping Soldiers  http://lnkd.in/Bgk-_R     
    
    
    @ImSoSarah I broke my toe 15 years ago and have never run since. ;)    
    
    
    looking for some asap twitter development work!!  contact me.  #oauth #twitter #software #developer #jobs authentication application api    
    
    
    glad that splits.org is up and running again. #splits    
    
    
    thinking would be hard to wake up at 4am to farm if farm land itself worth 13m. crzy world.    
    
    
    Heard about Talent Communities? http://www.recruiter.com/articles/heard-about-talent-communities/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    It's disgusting that Internet companies continue to support censorship. http://blog.twitter.com/2012/01/tweets-still-must-flow.html … via @twitter    
    
    
    this is pretty hilarious-  BP Spills Coffee: http://ucbt.net/v/6472    
    
    
    sending out weekly update on TalentBar - social media articles this time.  http://tinyurl.com/d7yl3u    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin how did I not know about CAPS?    
    
    
    thinking House is getting a little gratuitous for no particular reason    
    
    
    @slmcg we're going to get a lot of activity on splits.org in the next couple of days.  ping me if you have any questions!    
    
    
    reading about #TalentNet: http://tinyurl.com/dayrbd    
    
    
    @dmanaster my house smells like little kids.    
    
    
    my wife just tried to fast forward live tv.  we don't sleep much.    
    
    
    @SuzanneTravers thanks for writing! http://tinyurl.com/dxcdnu    
    
    
    somewhere it's time to be awake.  but not here.    
    
    
    @sengineland why would microsoft bother with vine when they already have a piece of facebook?    
    
    
    watching SDLC humor  http://tinyurl.com/c28w6v    
    
    
    that MSFT vine service seems pretty cool.  local is the new social.  but I don't think this is the killer local app yet.    
    
    
    @_McLaughlin cat herder?  that's what I do too.    
    
    
    @aplusk someday the quality of films will be so low we'll just call them movies    
    
    
    reading about social recruiting: http://tinyurl.com/c9xd9w    
    
    
    We must stand for universal human rights http://www.recruiter.com/blog/stand-universal-freedom/ … via @recruiterdotcom @twitter    
    
    
    @JasonCBlais looks ok, but slow...    
    
    
    elegantly stated like only an @animal could    
    
    
    is tori amosized a term?    
    
    
    @analogrecruiter you should connect with @abcase - he needs an electrical engineer for circuit boards #splits    
    
    
    @need a JBOSS ESB AJAX Java Developer in  CT US in Technology #splits    
    
    
    @liwright cool!  but mine was a rt.  just contact @abcase #splits    
    
    
    @abcase looks like @liwright has a candidate for you #splits    
    
    
    Too bad India's taking China's lead on freedom of speech... http://reut.rs/AoZgbX     
    
    
    The Danger of Joking at Work: The Rise and Fall of Workplace Humor http://www.recruiter.com/articles/joking-at-work/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    great you have a java candidate @sunilkjain we'll email you  #splits    
    
    
    feeling the temp rising and seeing s of border signs popping up off 95    
    
    
    wondering about a billboard: "pedro corny?"    
    
    
    From Jobs to Roles: Who We are at Work is Changing http://www.recruiter.com/articles/from-jobs-to-roles-who-we-are-at-work-is-changing/ … via @recruiterdotcom #jobs    
    
    
    Never a dull moment in this space: A Big Bet on Human Capital: Oracle Buys Taleo http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/a-big-bet-on-human-capital-oracle-buys-taleo/ …    
    
    
    This is just too funny. At Twitter, The Future is You!: http://youtu.be/vccZkELgEsU  via @youtube    
    
    
    @LinkedIn just merge already and get it over with. ;)    
    
    
    @need a Java ESB J2EE Web Developer in Stamford, CT US in Technology #splits    
    
    
    The Gamification of Work: Let's Have Some Fun http://www.recruiter.com/articles/the-gamification-of-work-lets-have-some-fun/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    @JenniferMcClure @RedBranch It's in the works! Someday we'll get really crazy and get byline images. We're super techie.  ;)    
    
    
    @CincyRecruiter #shrm10 strangely looks like a Poison concert    
    
    
    Fhju. G pic.twitter.com/HXwFqAig    
    
    
    Social Recruiting: Who's on First? http://www.recruiter.com/articles/social-recruiting-whos-on-first/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Thanks Chris - that post went crazy. @smashfly    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin I'm trying to take ugly as something of a compliment. I'll try to make it to that CAPS meeting.  I will look into it!    
    
    
    Just added myself to the http://wefollow.com twitter directory under:  #recruiter #recruiting #blog    
    
    
    good to see #hiring as a trending topic.    
    
    
    Graph of social media on Google Ngram http://ngrams.googlelabs.com/graph?content=social+media&year_start=2000&year_end=2008&corpus=0&smoothing=3 … via @orwant #socialmedia    
    
    
    Appears talk of the soul is on the upswing after 150 yrs of decline http://ngrams.googlelabs.com/graph?content=soul%252Cspirit&year_start=1800&year_end=2008&corpus=0&smoothing=3 … via @orwant    
    
    
    @SaifSiddiqui thanks for the note - sure will do.  I'll do it tonight    
    
    
    @TimDineen thanks Tim - nice to hear from you!  Hope all is well.    
    
    
    @lspearmanii I will correct by tomorrow - thanks for note!    
    
    
    amen!! RT @jerry_albright Are recruiters still reviewed based on their #s any more? Or is it all about branding, paying it forward...    
    
    
    @jerry_albright SM experts make an average of 7,223 placements/year.    
    
    
    Unemployment: It's Your Problem http://www.recruiter.com/articles/unemployment-its-your-problem/ via @recruiterdotcom #jobs    
    
    
    Late Adopters: When it Pays to be Old School http://www.recruiter.com/articles/late-adopters-when-it-pays-to-be-old-school/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    People who use @rescuetime should need it less and less, right? Wrong.    
    
    
    @need a Mid-level .NET Developer in Hartford, CT US in Financial #splits    
    
    
    needing someone to ban me from godaddy    
    
    
    @recruitingblogs just picking up some scraps.. you have left the recruiting domain landscape a cold and lonely desert    
    
    
    @recruitingblogs i had lost my voice when I met him so @jobing probably considers me half mute    
    
    
    @shawnvw #splits is a easy way for recruiters to identify that they want to partner on job requirements to make placements together.    
    
    
    enjoying local radio that they bought back from clearchannel. is radio de-consolidating?    
    
    
    my 3 year old is tweeting under my name again..    
    
    
    deciphering 2.5 year old dreams    
    
    
    oh wait it turns out she was talking about a dancing bird she saw on youtube.  whats the world coming to    
    
    
    @successsecret i would say you don't have to master IT language, but understand personalities and business  http://short.to/60bz    
    
    
    any good ideas on setting up niche job boards?    
    
    
    looking at the world's 2nd worst webpage.  hands down #1 is the first version of talentbar http://www.angelfire.com/super/badwebs/main.htm    
    
    
    but my kids love that webpage.  they are dancing to the music... http://www.angelfire.com/super/badwebs/main.htm    
    
    
    "again," they say, "again..." each time it ends    
    
    
    @zappos don't be a cow for obvious reasons    
    
    
    cool new publishing option from scribd.  now to get around to writing that book: http://tinyurl.com/qqmlct    
    
    
    adding #PM and #pmo related content to main twitter feed at www.ppmng.com    
    
    
    can anyone suggest any great web software or widget to mash up a whole bunch of twitter and RSS feeds and display it in a nice way?    
    
    
    where's the official list of day of week #hashtags like #musicmonday?    
    
    
    lunch with a #usability expert.  I have a lot to learn... here's their hashtag feed http://tinyurl.com/64gn8z    
    
    
    checking out everyzing.. "The Web's first Universal Search & Publishing Solution"  that's a big claim.  http://www.everyzing.com/    
    
    
    @michaelrawlins that figures!  and how could I not find you with a mysterious twitter name like firstnamelastname?  i need more sleep    
    
    
    Really amazing work here - An Easier Way to Grow your Professional Network http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/03/27/new-people-you-may-know/ …    
    
    
    Some Spiffy New Updates http://www.recruiter.com/i/some-spiffy-new-updates/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    checking out a really beautifully designed #twitter app: http://twistori.com/    
    
    
    what's so funny about a tomato stain on your shirt? we ask my daughter.  Because it's bad, she says. #kids    
    
    
    Google Glasses: The Cloud Comes to Earth http://www.recruiter.com/i/google-glasses-the-cloud-comes-to-earth/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    just a spoonful of sugar makes the medicine go down in a most delightful way. #quote mary poppins    
    
    
    What’s Wrong with Children Self-Publishing? Nothing - Publishing Perspectives http://publishingperspectives.com/2012/04/whats-wrong-with-children-self-publishing-nothing/#.T4MdxsPLbpE.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    feeling the burn... painting is way harder than recruiting    
    
    
    reading #job hunting tips on talentbar: http://bit.ly/uPV7F    
    
    
    Recruiting Babies http://www.recruiter.com/i/recruiting-babies/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    @al3x after an application and account is whitelisted by Twitter, should it still be getting posting rate limits?  thanks so much!    
    
    
    reading cheezhead's article on Twitter #job search and @hashjobs http://bit.ly/WRZrJ    
    
    
    my son just invented a mouse trap/water glass device.  hmmm.. (patent pending)    
    
    
    @mzsanford thanks for the note about the whitelisting issue - the account is @hashjobs    
    
    
    checking out yahoo pipes to aggregate #rss feeds.. any thoughts on the service? http://pipes.yahoo.com/pipes/    
    
    
    @jasonwhitman I'm trying to mashup a whole bunch of stuff and then share it in a widget.  thought i would give it a try...    
    
    
    @recruitingblogs yeah it's frying my brain right now    
    
    
    @SylvieDahl lol!  btw what is a movie poet?    
    
    
    @yahoo - RT @hashjobs Yahoo!: VP, User Experience and Design in Sunnyvale, CA in Media / Publishing #jobs #job http://tinyurl.com/q9zqvm    
    
    
    substitute pipes mashup tool for drugs: http://bit.ly/Fqge2    
    
    
    like adwords for twitter... had to happen. nice idea: http://featuredusers.com/    
    
    
    are there any great #twitter developers out there who aren't wrapped up in a big project?  #job #jobs    
    
    
    @al3x thanks for the note - it's been about 6 days...    
    
    
    thinking giving away green plastic car keys to promote your hybrid car giveaway is ridiculous    
    
    
    @jasonwhitman thanks Jason!  that's about a 100x easier..    
    
    
    Women Are Saying Goodbye http://www.recruiter.com/i/women-are-saying-goodbye/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    friend of mine's funny mac ad parody: http://bit.ly/pzYHu    
    
    
    Dumb Bloggers Make Better Lovers http://milesjennings.com/2010/12/28/dumb-bloggers/ …    
    
    
    @Animal is the prize heaven, never understood    
    
    
    "outsourced" is pretty good. I have to see India sometime soon. http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0425326/    
    
    
    New Linkedin polls could be great: http://j.mp/hMzB4k    
    
    
    Why Twitter Lists are Useless http://milesjennings.com/2010/12/why-twitter-lists-are-useless/ …    
    
    
    My wife can look at a blueprint and walk around it in her mind. I can barely navigate the real world.    
    
    
    Listening to a Stadium Full of People http://milesjennings.com/2010/12/listening-to-a-stadium/ …    
    
    
    @Vinkashyap thanks for the note!    
    
    
    @jriss2020 Tx! Glad you liked it, it's a neat product with a lot of interesting implications.    
    
    
    @bioitbob thanks for the note! that was just me questioning something I got involved in more than the value of the product itself    
    
    
    Now follow Sunday for people you love? Some day soon people will get really crazy and just go back to church #fs    
    
    
    What Other People Think of You http://bit.ly/9IMiEd    
    
    
    @jasoncblais gotta tell you though when me and fam were driving thru the Shenandoah valley recently, we were like why don't we live here?    
    
    
    Dear cobra administration, please stop trying to trick me into letting my policy lapse    
    
    
    @PeterBrayTweets you sir, have been listed    
    
    
    @chuckhall @jeffs_journey @affiliatemgt @businessgp @robpipe @tegly @socialgrow @GuyMansueto consider yourself listed ;)    
    
    
    @pvantees thanks so much for the note!! That list is only English tweets unfortunately... I should have mentioned that!    
    
    
    @DittmanRewards It's meant for more personal accounts - do you have someone who runs your company?    
    
    
    @davidgerzof Hi David, thanks for the note and consider yourself listed!    
    
    
    @jackieyeaney thanks for the note - done!    
    
    
    @TweetJohnLane Hi - what's your bio, do you have a link?    
    
    
    @ideasincmumbai it's more for individual executives versus company brands - do you have a marketing leader or CEO that is on Twitter?    
    
    
    @jasonpinto you got it!    
    
    
    @Phoenix_pdwnyc it's more for individual executives than brands. Do you have someone at your company to suggest?    
    
    
    @CharlieColeIMS done!    
    
    
    @johnlusk done! ;)    
    
    
    @JohnDigles John, thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    @DataGlam Hi - do you have a link to your profile somewhere?    
    
    
    @dgupta5150 done, sir. ;)    
    
    
    @mstrategiesCEO thanks for the mention, you're on the list!    
    
    
    @jgulvik done!    
    
    
    @kenbruno nice article http://bit.ly/aKL0yT. I'm very interested in niche communities and run a CMO group @milesj/cmo    
    
    
    @PaulTravis done!    
    
    
    @RobManger done!    
    
    
    @derickson done!    
    
    
    @hchimoff done!    
    
    
    @chris_craig done! Do you have a website, just curious as you're near my neck of the woods.    
    
    
    @EricPinckert done!    
    
    
    @zulkhernain thanks, what are you proposing?    
    
    
    @KelleyBriggs you fit the bill. you're in. ;)    
    
    
    @alfredo_gingin thanks for the note - the CMO list is only for English tweets however. sorry, I should have mentioned that!    
    
    
    @SaaSCMO consider yourself listed. ;)    
    
    
    @MENGonline done! would be interesting to talk sometime. dm me if you want to.    
    
    
    Managing Social Networks Hurts | http://bit.ly/bGYjpY #socialmedia #smm    
    
    
    @ColetteCote  consider yourself listed (and very well qualified.)    
    
    
    @MichaelFertman done!    
    
    
    I've never recruited someone to be an "agent of change." have you?    
    
    
    this is too funny not to RT. @thechive girl quits job by emailing funny pics http://bit.ly/9WpYXl    
    
    
    nice talking to you @tedkohnen! we'll be in touch.    
    
    
    Here's an awesome example of a niche industry social network that someone pointed out to me: http://activerain.com/ #smm    
    
    
    @WSJ isn't that a good thing? Americans now owe more on their student loans than their credit cards http://on.wsj.com/baTnOz    
    
    
    @ewmonster that's a cool article. congrats! http://bit.ly/cmNWl7    
    
    
    @jsways tsk!    
    
    
    @ChinaGorman now your comment has me thinking about philosophy. thanks China. philosophy is the reason I was a waiter after college. ;)    
    
    
    @MikeRamer I can't read words that aren't on radiation-transmitting devices anymore. Seriously.    
    
    
    Video Game Teamwork and Lego Batman http://milesjennings.com/2010/12/video-game-teamwork/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @lucapenati done! Good to follow you now too...    
    
    
    @patlovenhart I added you. did you mean that you ARE following the list? ;)    
    
    
    @Navigatepartner It's like 10,000 spoons when all you need is a knife. btw, I love complaining about my favorite things. ;)    
    
    
    @mikekumpf come on you told you her about that tweet.    
    
    
    "that's not very Canadian of you" just came up in conversation.    
    
    
    Were you awake at midnight on New Year's Eve? Be honest. http://linkd.in/gddikx    
    
    
    Temp Trends Around The World http://lnkd.in/kXyf6t     
    
    
    The my little ponies are just bizarre    
    
    
    Five Steps to Building a Resume that Gets Noticed http://lnkd.in/E9HAN8     
    
    
    Elliott smith never meant for his songs to be the background for ninjump. Love iPhones.    
    
    
    What New College Grads Look For http://lnkd.in/e9XNqs     
    
    
    @mashable N. Korea is more than just a "secretive regime." 3 million people have died under brutal dictatorship http://bit.ly/dtSbZ6    
    
    
    @catherinedavis1 no. Just kidding. Yes.    
    
    
    Who’s King Now? Content or Conversation? http://lnkd.in/YudGfn     
    
    
    I am officially the worst board secretary ever.    
    
    
    @MegFitz thanks for the list mention! for #followfriday!    
    
    
    Secret Twitter Power Users http://milesjennings.com/2011/01/secret-twitter-power-users/ …    
    
    
    @michaelwolfe thanks for the rt. happy new year!    
    
    
    good inc article with founder of wordpress: http://bit.ly/1fSiG    
    
    
    @RabbiIssamar this time, I suppose... ;)    
    
    
    @TimDineen Thanks Tim! but I wish I was this guy: http://bit.ly/bLsatS    
    
    
    @RecruiterCTO I'm stuck at world headquarters    
    
    
    @smashfly thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    @animal @MaureenSharib Sure, I'm out this morning - but my number is 860-748-4872 if you want to talk this afternoon. Maybe like 1?    
    
    
    @JennyDeVaughn should be interesting IPO... shares of Linkedin on Sharespost value it at around 2 billion    
    
    
    "A good percentage of men are colorblind." "No, I think you're just blind." - convo after i dressed the kids    
    
    
    @JennyDeVaughn terrific mostly! Happy new year!    
    
    
    @BillVick amen. prisons are the biggest issue that no one talks about. 2M people in the system.    
    
    
    setting up subgroups on the TalentBar Linkedin group for Recruiters and HR: http://bit.ly/GbTty    
    
    
    thank goodness.  http://bit.ly/YfEqU    
    
    
    the economy is bouncing back... just like this bear: http://bit.ly/tPJ9l    
    
    
    When the French call a movie dark, they really mean it...    
    
    
    if it seems too good to be true, I'm just going to keep at it. new rule of thumb.    
    
    
    just testing out @seesmic integration with the @recruitingblogs network. seems pretty cool.    
    
    
    amazing what one person can do. this guy made google instant search a year ago in "a couple hour's work" http://www.istartedsomething.com/20090821/the-real-live-search-bing-api-experiment/ …    
    
    
    @smashfly that's a lot shorter than recruiter.com took and recruiter doesn't do much yet. but stay tuned. ;)    
    
    
    @kbaumann was going to say I'm only #19 and I work there ;)    
    
    
    According to Hollywood, I was born in a very cheesy time    
    
    
    @RecruiterCTO it turns out I am a master soccer coach.    
    
    
    @kyleford what flavor is the future?    
    
    
    @michaellperry what's wrong with them? did it mess up the site for you?    
    
    
    You know who's also smart and funny, but a real jerk? The Devil.    
    
    
    On Sunday afternoon it's easy to make the stretch to call scooby-doo somehow educational    
    
    
    Modis: .Net Developer in Stamford, CT, US in Financial #jobs #job http://hashjobs.com/job/HJ3153287    
    
    
    featuring top influencers in HR & recruitment by Sumser: http://bit.ly/3YeWPH #recruiting #hr    
    
    
    thanks @Fishdogs for the #followfriday mention.  Hey you, call it #followmonday and follow @Fishdogs    
    
    
    watching house hunters.  the reason why is complicated.    
    
    
    I'm such a dork that I can't wait to see this movie http://sonypictures.com/u.php?a=25348    
    
    
    thanks for the follow @GoobleDGuck. you complete me.    
    
    
    @jheineck of course, have seen that too.  man, I'm a wild and crazy guy.    
    
    
    thinking 20 minutes of parent-teacher conference time per YEAR sounds a little low...    
    
    
    Today is one of those blues traveler solos frantic and beautiful    
    
    
    check out top100 HR/Recruiter influencers http://bit.ly/3YeWPH and @williamtincup profiled for the latest one: http://bit.ly/ldhkE    
    
    
    @Recruiter that is a killer twitter name you have there...    
    
    
    good to see #recruiters getting involved in niche social networks. RT @jasonbiser http://www.ppmng.com/profile/JasonBiser    
    
    
    @davemendoza my wife and I are obsessed with that show.  but not in a "buffy the vampire slayer" fan kind of way...    
    
    
    only 14% of #jobs tweets come from top 10 accounts, which means it's not all just robots and RSS feeds, it's real. stats:http://bit.ly/cGTEt    
    
    
    @andybeal I like your radically tech-centric posts mixed with Abraham Lincoln quotes.  not too many people do that...    
    
    
    @andybeal now just relate a Lincoln quote to a blog on pagerank theory, and I'll be really impressed  ;)    
    
    
    @JohnSumser I searched around for Hartford CT for a bit and then gave up   http://bit.ly/18KmfH    
    
    
    Interview with Gen Y Career Expert @lindseypollak by @SMarksRecruiter: http://www.recruiter.com/i/from-college-to-career-tips-from-gen-y-expert-lindsey-pollak/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    I'll try to make it next year! New HR Tech Trends: http://bit.ly/ULDZ8l  #HRTechConf    
    
    
    The vote to end the board meeting was particularly enthusiastic    
    
    
    #splits is like #recruiter morse code    
    
    
    @x415 thanks for the note, hope you enjoy the group!    
    
    
    Interesting to see @loukerner as the "First social media analyst on Wall Street"    
    
    
    the about menu may not go anywhere yet, but the jobs do @hashjobs    
    
    
    resting after a day at the circus. (a literal circus for once)    
    
    
    Apparently I'm crazy for mild syncopation and extensive vamping. Pandora knows things about me that I don't.    
    
    
    Twitter needs to find a way to monetize cliches    
    
    
    @tedmurphy how much for a slice of your idealism?    
    
    
    @MeghanMBiro a steel factory around me has a nap room + open salaries + profit sharing. Too bad I stink at forging steel...    
    
    
    featuring some new blogs on talentbar: http://www.talentbar.com/profiles/blog/list    
    
    
    how was I following a Kentucky wildcat fan profile?  I don't even like basketball.  don't drink and follow...    
    
    
    @Animal Cary Elwes is one of the distinguished alums from my wife's alma mater.  i mean, you can't beat "men in tights"    
    
    
    embarrassed I hadn't missed one @junkKi vote for: The Top 10 Social Media Stories You Might Have Missed http://bit.ly/16MPSL    
    
    
    @Animal seems like you & mr. savage are closer than one might assume...    
    
    
    winnie from the wonder year's real math thesis: http://danicamckellar.com/math/percolation.pdf    
    
    
    interesting idea, common word #twitter names: @TwiNames    
    
    
    why is the dmoz editor application process harder than most law schools?    
    
    
    @melanielloyd is that the car you have or want?  just curious    
    
    
    @melanielloyd oh so both have and want, that's nice. i used to have a ferrari poster in my room, never did get around to getting one... ;)    
    
    
    @melanielloyd i would first have to take the leap of selling my house, clothes, and possibly children.    
    
    
    @melanielloyd yup, it's one of the boards we use most and it's really good for technology.    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan do you capitalize he when referring to the devil?    
    
    
    @alanhill8 thanks for the note about that recruitingblogs article! http://bit.ly/RBLSs    
    
    
    @Kristen_Durkin im crazy about consumerreports, but im an old fogey.  let me know the model and I'll look it up for you.    
    
    
    @melanielloyd I don't know too much about the price, but I think the value is pretty good.  be sure to get yr jobs on indeed.com as well    
    
    
    my wife says oil-rubbed bronze is the new brushed nickel.  i think she may be on something.  i mean on to something.    
    
    
    updating @ppmng #pm    
    
    
    getting the Connecticut office of Modis on the Twitter map: @CTmodis.  We'll be posting #tech news, links, and of course #jobs    
    
    
    switched it around to @modisct... we're going to share tech links and the local CT technology jobs we're recruiting on.    
    
    
    john melloncamp is just as kitchy in person which is a good thIng    
    
    
    First #recruitfest, now today is chowderfest at mystic seaport!    
    
    
    @mysticseaport beautiful day for chowderfest!! http://plixi.com/p/49596325    
    
    
    on social networks, your profile can be an ad, but your real interactions like blogs and forum posts shouldn't be.  just a thought.    
    
    
    Taco bell is never a good idea, but kinda glad that I always forget this.    
    
    
    @WorkResults @incentintel @jasonlauritsen Some of my favorite sessions at #recruitfest were essentially panel discussions though...    
    
    
    The Starbucks folks are laying down some old school tracks today...    
    
    
    It's a great feeling to say, "Yes, we accept all major credit cards."    
    
    
    Another great post by track leader @TalentSynch: What was different and why it's important -> #Recruitfest 2010 http://ow.ly/2SSgz    
    
    
    Finally reading the outliers, not saying anything about the book but saying wow, I'm actually reading a book    
    
    
    @sjglynn thanks for the RT.  It's getting to be a personal gripe of mine.  ;)    
    
    
    seems like the last time i've been w/out email for two days was before they invented email.  feels kinda good.  but back to twitter now.    
    
    
    @callmeslouch "finest" is high praise indeed in this day and age.    
    
    
    @dianaejennings it can't be too close to coming out, they're still using the same free wordpress theme that i do.  nice last name btw.    
    
    
    will do so post haste @KlasO @ppmng I suggest changing the picture from the 'o_O' to the group logo or similar    
    
    
    @ryanendres thanks for your contributions to @ppmng!  Look forward to seeing more.    
    
    
    @Monster_WORKS @watsonlg man, do you guys sleep?    
    
    
    @marenhogan mine was today. and i do. ;)    
    
    
    RT job post by @TinaHancock ck this out http://hashjobs.com/job/HJ4101875 we'll see if it works    
    
    
    A New View for a New Year http://www.recruiter.com/i/a-new-view/  via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Trending in #Recruiting http://www.recruiter.com/i/trending-in-recruiting/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Thanks to the folks at @grammarly for contributing to @recruiterdotcom: The Comma and Your Career http://bit.ly/UV6koO     
    
    
    LinkedIn CEO: Site will become 'economic graph' over next decade | Internet & Media - CNET News http://cnet.co/YnSFLm     
    
    
    @glencathey  wow, that is really blatant...    
    
    
    4 Hiring Apps To Keep You in The Game in 2013 http://bit.ly/UZ4C5N  #recruiting    
    
    
    link: EDGAR Online: More than Just a 'Financial iPod'   http://seekingalpha.com/a/37lp #xbrl    
    
    
    LinkedIn Launches Ads API, Enabling Custom Tools For Large-Scale Campaigns | @TechCrunch http://tcrn.ch/X1M4FZ     
    
    
    Marissa Mayer on God, family and Yahoo - Fortune Tech http://bit.ly/V4H5QT     
    
    
    The Day Work Became a Choice http://bit.ly/V4KZJs     
    
    
    What’s the Score With Hiring Gamification? http://bit.ly/RoaI2c  #recruitment    
    
    
    You may not get benefits in a startup, but the gym sure is empty at 3pm on a Fri.    
    
    
    Is it the fast Jazz in the background or do I just get really excited by good CRM work? #salesgeek    
    
    
    @zapoint do you have a presentation or something on zapoint?    
    
    
    @marenhogan its fun to try    
    
    
    registering a twitter account for my hometown.  hyper local tweets are cool.  #twitter    
    
    
    @HartfordStage Christmas Carol yesterday was awesome. New family tradition for sure.    
    
    
    The Real Reasons your Employees are Leaving You http://bit.ly/SrQLVi     
    
    
    Is the .JOBS Domain the Future of #Job Search? http://bit.ly/RyRiaS     
    
    
    5 Key Hiring Metrics for 2013 http://bit.ly/SuGI1N  #recruiting    
    
    
    Smart people fix dumb problems.    
    
    
    Mary Meeker releases stunning data on the state of the Internet | via @VentureBeat http://bit.ly/RzXVcW     
    
    
    Outgoing SEC Chair Schapiro Delayed JOBS Act Rulemaking Over Legacy Worries http://bit.ly/RBXm2i  - about crowdfunding    
    
    
    Matchmaking Comes to #Jobs: @eHarmony to Launch Job Board? http://bit.ly/SAUmAe     
    
    
    Not to be a basher, but it's pretty amazing that the entire Windows8 metro ecosystem is unusable for real work. Tx @Stardock    
    
    
    Check out our brand new Google Plus community! Come join us! http://bit.ly/SDc4TO  #jobs #recruiting    
    
    
    I get way too excited about this stuff. Google+ Introduces “Communities” To Replace Old School Groups: http://tcrn.ch/SDewtu     
    
    
    The future of #LinkedIn and the economic graph | LinkedIn http://linkd.in/SReHCT     
    
    
    The Workforce in 2020 http://bit.ly/SLlZa1  (lack of robots notwithstanding)    
    
    
    This is exactly what we need: Steps to Entrepreneurship with Nonprofit @intersectfund Founder Joe Shure http://bit.ly/RWoSrt     
    
    
    Big Idea 2013: This Year, the War on Drugs Ends | LinkedIn http://linkd.in/S3LeY6     
    
    
    Sorry, zero hair & make-up expenses covered at our startup - How to Land a Celebrity Co-founder | http://bit.ly/S4tM5S     
    
    
    I'm sorry, how did our current administration save us 2.2 Trillion?  I just don't understand, not getting political.    
    
    
    Great - Catcher in the Rye dropped from US school curriculum - Telegraph http://bit.ly/T9d1mL     
    
    
    Sending out an update to the TalentBar group.  I just love messing up a link going out to 70,000 people.  ;)    
    
    
    Good Neighbors and Recruiting http://www.recruiter.com/blog/good-neighbors-recruiting/ …    
    
    
    @gefischer Thanks Greg, 'tis easier to blog than shovel...    
    
    
    Great post for startups and software vendors: A Postmortem Analysis of Standout Jobs http://www.instigatorblog.com/postmortem-analysis-of-standout-jobs/2010/10/05/ … via @byosko tx @slouch    
    
    
    Dr. Karie Willyerd (@angler) and 5 Ways to Stay Productive to Accelerate your #Career in 2013 http://bit.ly/SW3vnn     
    
    
    @marenhogan you are obsessed    
    
    
    Well put together article on LinkedIn by @PMInstitute that I contributed to recently: http://bit.ly/YTMqPU     
    
    
    @SylvieDahl haha! That looks much more like me than my neighbor.    
    
    
    What do people think of the name "Sawyer?    
    
    
    @Rickers42 Great, tx!    
    
    
    Real Networking with Linkedin http://bit.ly/hXLHVd     
    
    
    @chrisgtaylor nice..    
    
    
    "We all live the same lives as rockstars but no one is watching"    
    
    
    @babarkj it doesn't really. Yet. Watch out.    
    
    
    Internet Marketers are moving into the Recruiting Space | http://bit.ly/byicvx    
    
    
    Why 2010 Changing Internet Recruiting | http://bit.ly/by441u #recruiting    
    
    
    Like the new pic...    
    
    
    @somaJohn Not stars, that's for sure.    
    
    
    Tx for the RT @bullhornlive @StacyZapar @timdineen @smashfly @slouch #FF a little early    
    
    
    TX for the mention @smashfly: Recruitment Marketing Articles of the Week 10.23.10 to 10.29.10 - RecruitingBlogs.com http://bit.ly/bWjfpb    
    
    
    HR Vendors Don't Care about SEO | http://bit.ly/a05Qv3 #hr    
    
    
    Zoho + Google apps rocks    
    
    
        
    
    
    We used to have levers to vote; now we're back to pen and little bubbles. Thanks computers. #election    
    
    
    10 Critical Steps to Achieving Magnetic Leadership [Part 1] http://bit.ly/WVFFbF     
    
    
    Modis: Recruiter in Hartford, CT, US in Staffing #jobs #job http://hashjobs.com/job/HJ4979174    
    
    
    "Sleep well." "I will. I have planned what I want to dream." #kidquote    
    
    
    How to Be An Honest Recruiter http://bit.ly/gBjwic     
    
    
    @lelandv I guess they're kind of like leprechauns... ;)    
    
    
    Profile Search with Linkedin Instant Search http://bit.ly/fnKckD     
    
    
    An exclusive club of 2M!  ;)  I have one of the top 1% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. http://www.linkedin.com/pub/profile/0/029/920?trk=200tw …    
    
    
    Facebook Sponsored Stories for Recruiting http://bit.ly/gYgnj5     
    
    
    Top #Social Tools for 2013 http://bit.ly/13eFtv1     
    
    
    Ruckus Roundup: Marissa Mayer http://bit.ly/XGvQya     
    
    
        
    
    
    Should #Recruiting Without Resumes be Policy? http://bit.ly/15T7d87     
    
    
    Unique Card Game Creator Demonstrates Vast Possibilities of Entrepreneurship http://bit.ly/YaxUxF     
    
    
    New #Recruiting Technology Trends Report for 2013 http://bit.ly/12uoPrL     
    
    
    IT Hiring Lessons from Aziz Ansari http://bit.ly/YhrnkG     
    
    
    5 Signs of a Great Recruiter http://bit.ly/YnBq7Y     
    
    
    Nice story of how raising prices can pay off http://on.wsj.com/9ekexH via @AllenAlist    
    
    
    @animal I actually don't agree with most of that article either. @RecruiterDotCom is usually accused of praising recruiters...    
    
    
    @AlaRecruiter @animal I agree. We publish a lot of different views. Mine personally is http://bit.ly/YnBq7Y  & http://bit.ly/15w2WnW .    
    
    
    @Jerry_Albright @animal Still raising kids & building web stuff. I'm writing tool tips as we speak. It's all glamor all the time.    
    
    
    @AlaRecruiter Amy I guess she got a personal threat, so of course we're taking down that article.    
    
    
    @AlaRecruiter it's not your fault of course! Recruiters are a passionate bunch. I was one too.    
    
    
    "Looking for a lifeguard? Ours walks on water."  love those #churchsigns...    
    
    
    the futures bright in toronto gotta wear shades RT @recruitingblogs some recruiting advice - RecruitingBlogs.com http://bit.ly/44PYQm    
    
    
    Freelancers or Full-time Hires:  How to Grow Your Staff the Right Way http://mvb.me/index.php/s/baabb2t …    
    
    
    7 Essential Tools for Managing Teams, Time, and Projects http://mvb.me/s/ed72cft     
    
    
    @wrike A big +1 for a Wrike iPad app!    
    
    
    The Next 50 Ideas for Billion-Dollar Software Companies | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130408160410-5434591-the-next-50-ideas-for-billion-dollar-software-companies …    
    
    
    6 Ways to Make LinkedIn Endorsements Worthwhile http://bit.ly/Z8X4Bs     
    
    
    The Importance of Going Mobile http://bit.ly/Zr3Ylu     
    
    
    No one welcomes like Waterbury! pic.twitter.com/O4ximyuLP1    
    
    
    Online Outsourcing: A New Way to Manage Costs http://mvb.me/s/b9ed2dt     
    
    
    hello folks @modis, drop me a line if I can be of help    
    
    
    @cruiter nice twitter presentation    
    
    
    @Cruiter you sound like you're leaving.  or im leaving.  wait, do you know something i don't?    
    
    
    @wolfgugler thanks for RT.  The dean, eh?  I like it.    
    
    
    How To Attract Big Talent To Your Small Firm http://bit.ly/14P2hTX     
    
    
    The 4 Moments of Truth in the Hiring Process—and how to Handle Them http://bit.ly/ZmLumL     
    
    
    How to Write a Great Ad for your Next New Hire http://mvb.me/s/a80136     
    
    
    Our kids actually have "working snack" periods during school like the working lunches of adults. Like they won't have enough of that...    
    
    
    Scrappy PR: 5 Ways to Build Buzz for Small Business http://mvb.me/s/cdd6e2t     
    
    
    The Global Challenge: Recruiting and Your EVP http://bit.ly/15vGlh5     
    
    
    Screening Resumes – How to Find the Right Candidate for the Job: http://bit.ly/17Yw9xz     
    
    
    Great blog post @dcurtis - What a stupid idea http://bit.ly/10LRFgp     
    
    
    We have a new career advice section on Recruiter.com - here's a post about it! http://www.recruiter.com/blog/career-advice-job-experts/ …    
    
    
    Do Your Employees Like Working For You? http://mvb.me/s/cccb38t     
    
    
    EDGAR Online Is Running with the Elephants http://seekingalpha.com/a/3e6c #xbrl    
    
    
    @williamtincup Happy belated birthday! http://hluv.me/rm4z7n #williamtincupbday    
    
    
    BranchOut Announces New Connections Feature http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/?p=1585 …    
    
    
    'Wow, That Was Easy!' Said No Entrepreneur Ever | Robert Hatta http://huff.to/1dZU9Pk     
    
    
    .@guykawasaki Happy Birthday! Sending u some HashLove http://hluv.me/t3bfhb #guykawasakibday    
    
    
    @marenhogan ive seen the ad, not for me either. "P90x ab ripper is NOT for babies"    
    
    
    Linkedin Updates: The New Recruiter Magazine? http://bit.ly/eqbn1k  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    I just sent @byosko a Congratulations card. congrats on the upgrade!  this card makes me laugh Sign it too! http://hluv.me/c9i4xn #hashlove    
    
    
    Why You Need to Be a (Web) Publisher http://mvb.me/s/188748t     
    
    
    The Top 100 Websites For Your Career - Tx @Forbes http://onforb.es/1eZicE3  for including @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Newly relaunched job board for Recruiting Jobs and HR Jobs http://shar.es/1aVwL    
    
    
    got through my first 32 years without internet radio how i don't know    
    
    
    there's a lot of hot property deals here in ct.  anyone have like 2, maybe 3 hundred grand to loan?    
    
    
    @RecruitingH2H facebook was meant for a mind finer than mine    
    
    
    nice! @pmorrisongc    
    
    
    Glad to be getting my company involved with the CT Tech Council @cttech. CT needs more startups!    
    
    
    @Adams_Ideas @ApploiObserver Just saw this - we should put you in touch with our editor!    
    
    
    @Adams_Ideas @ApploiObserver I'm going to try to update 1x/day. Baby steps. Let's have a call next week.    
    
    
    No idea I could get Inc, Entrepreneur, Fortune, and Fast Company all in one app. Good work @NextIssue     
    
    
    @marenhogan Thanks for connecting the industry like no one else can!    
    
    
    It took them 20 years or so, but Apple finally got me. Windows 8 was the last straw.    
    
    
    @marenhogan I was being dead serious. You're around every corner in this little town (of recruiting/hr).    
    
    
    10 Things To Stop Doing To Yourself to Be Happier, Backed by Science http://zite.to/1a1uQ0Q     
    
    
    Developers are starting a complete responsive redesign project on http://Recruiter.com ! Responsive seems to be the new Y2k bug...    
    
    
    @AntonM_Ivanov Thanks for the note! It really takes a lot of time to do things 100% right - I try to do online moderation about 34% right ;)    
    
    
    Inbox zero - hooray! For the next 30 seconds.    
    
    
    LinkedIn and Pulse Mobile Integration: http://zite.to/HMBMnQ     
    
    
    Ouch. http://www.forbes.com/sites/kylesmith/2013/04/04/its-time-for-companies-to-fire-their-human-resource-departments/ …    
    
    
    Great post on programming @justpw http://fugit.co/post/29561430366/building-with-only-your-mind …    
    
    
    @TheSendOffMan ha!    
    
    
    I love @NPR but they tend to over-cover trout.    
    
    
    @Adams_Ideas good talking and will do!    
    
    
    In Q1 2014, @RecruiterDotCom is again putting out a Recruiting Tech Trends report - if you want to contribute a quote or content, ping me!    
    
    
    Great idea - A Scientific Journal For Kids, Edited By Kids http://zite.to/1avAJ5y     
    
    
    Reading @algore's "The Future" book this weekend. Really interesting. Esp that I'm actually reading a real book.    
    
    
    Looking forward to taking some online courses @GA - seems way more practical than mba classes.    
    
    
    @GA Thank @inc - I read about you guys there. Seems like just what I've been looking for.    
    
    
    Are You Ready for Generation Z? http://www.recruiter.com/i/are-you-ready-for-generation-z/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    100 Million Reasons to Hire for Character http://bit.ly/18MA9gT     
    
    
    Goals are the New Tweets: How to use Social Goals for Your Company http://bit.ly/HZqXPq     
    
    
    Twitter on mobile just got dumbed down - less esoteric symbols - good move as they try to scale.    
    
    
    Artists Are Job-Creating Entrepreneurs, Too. http://zite.to/19IwVKW     
    
    
    Smart post by @optimizely: 25 Ways A/B Testing Can Optimize The Wall Street Journal’s Paywall: http://bit.ly/1hZsjdu     
    
    
    @Optimizely it's also what company blogs should be - free advice!    
    
    
    The Kids in This Billboard Point at Actual Planes Flying Overhead http://zite.to/1cI1TWy  -amazing    
    
    
    @mlassoff great to meet you! #goctstartups    
    
    
    @CTBeertour What you do - now THAT's an idea.    
    
    
    @daveranno what a week!    
    
    
    Hope they make it, great site - Why Fab Is Bleeding http://zite.to/I8EdS0     
    
    
    @ellenhuerta just read your old article on leaving google - fantastic. Best of luck to you.    
    
    
    This is absolute marketing genius http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=UFpe3Up9T_g&autoplay=1&desktop_uri=%252Fwatch%253Fv%253DUFpe3Up9T_g%2526autoplay%253D1 …    
    
    
    @neilhimself @OnPointRadio loved the candystore analogy.    
    
    
    First CCSU and now Yale. Not CT's month. Hope this one's just a mistake too.    
    
    
    Why I Left Google by @ellenhuerta: http://bit.ly/1aSNKGx     
    
    
    good luck! love reading your blog! @penelopetrunk: Even though it's my fourth startup it's still so scary to launch http://bit.ly/1937KDm     
    
    
    I'm not sure why any of this "food" is legal to sell. RT @RyanEstis: 10 Foods Sold in the U.S. Banned Elsewhere: http://bit.ly/1cpYziT     
    
    
    Good blog by @danshipper http://danshipper.com/what-i-learned-bootstrapping-a-6-figure-business-from-school …    
    
    
    Recruiting Like Southwest http://bit.ly/1aYIIIQ     
    
    
    I'm Peterman @marenhogan. Incidentally, the actor went to my high school. What TV Boss are You? http://www.recruiter.com/i/what-tv-boss-are-you/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Oh oh, that's now! RT @weelund: 2:55pm - When productivity dies and what to do about it http://bit.ly/1887N5X  via @fastcompany    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm taping this to my wall: Next time I design a product, I vow not to be a complete moron.    
    
    
    How should a hiring manager evaluate an applicant? http://www.recruiter.com/milesjennings/advice/#7 … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    When are the High-Risk Times for Losing Talent? http://bit.ly/1911qQz     
    
    
    @chrisrussell Thanks! Just made questions live. If you want to do one, login to http://recruiter.com , then menu My Profile, then My Advice    
    
    
    The @RecruiterDotCom Network on LinkedIn just hit 500,000 members! http://linkd.in/1cXhB0r     
    
    
    How to Have Great Ideas More Often, According to Science http://zite.to/18ao3n2     
    
    
    @Wrike is my last and desperate hope for sanity.    
    
    
    @wrike oh no, it was just a compliment. Around here, we just say "Wrike me" all day about any task. It's what keeps us sane.    
    
    
    This is kind of mind blowing - Should Job Promotions Be Random? http://bit.ly/1gK4p1p  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    My @gmail dashboard says I get over 200 emails a day. Officially giving up the idea of inbox zero to pay attention to more important things.    
    
    
    Just sent @MJenningsJr a Congratulations card. Congrats on launching www.ownershipview.com! Sign it too! http://hluv.me/wbf8wc #hashlove    
    
    
    We Say We Like Creativity, but We Really Don’t http://zite.to/1gcMWRG     
    
    
    Here’s How Elizabeth Gilbert (Bestselling Author of Eat, Pray, Love) Writes http://zite.to/1gWtiab     
    
    
    What to Do When You Get to Work http://bit.ly/IRj1zL     
    
    
    The Self-Employed Recruiter: Chicken-Fox or Chicken? http://bit.ly/dQAWVY  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    20 Year-Old Designs A Better Windows Than Microsoft http://zite.to/1daIhdN     
    
    
    We usually think local and buy global.    
    
    
    Now if only blue collar workers could get some of this same flexibility... Flexible Workplace http://bit.ly/1gvGGEV     
    
    
    @dmanaster It's a directly related post from a couple of days ago, not anchor link seo spam (that I'm sure we both hate.) Big difference.    
    
    
    Haim is awesome. Haim derived iradio station is something a bit different than awesome.    
    
    
    Review 2013 sales item by item. What's selling? Put efforts there and double down.    
    
    
    Not sure if MSFT is best pick for help w/web services. Microsoft Executive to Oversee Health Website http://on.wsj.com/1bY15z3     
    
    
    Ask employees what they'll do differently next year and what you should be doing differently.    
    
    
    Saving money = making money. It's time to negotiate contracts & decide on essential services.    
    
    
    @ktvezeau welcome to twitter. Somehow it knew to tell me you joined.    
    
    
    My take on: How would you advise someone to get ahead and advance in their career? http://www.recruiter.com/milesjennings/advice/how-would-you-advise-someone-to-get-ahead-and-advance-in-their-career// … via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    @MarkAEvertz We're looking for help with raising interesting discussions and moderation. You have a great background! Love to have yr help!    
    
    
    @MarkAEvertz Ok, just emailed you through LI with a note and my contact info.    
    
    
    @donrua No problem! Thanks for participating in the group!    
    
    
    @markfidelman Helping with some moderation. Mostly contributing interesting discussions and comments. Would be great to have your help!    
    
    
    Tim Draper To Universities: This Is How You Teach People To Become Entrepreneurs  http://onforb.es/IFcQzq  via @forbes / @markfidelman    
    
    
    @krischronister wow thank you! Btw, we run this cmo group. Just looking for moderators.maybe interested? http://www.linkedin.com/groups?groupDashboard=&gid=51822 …    
    
    
    Thanks so much for including http://Recruiter.com  in that top 35 list @ken_sundheim. Just saw that now! http://onforb.es/1gjMij7     
    
    
    Tips to Becoming an Employer of Choice in 2014 http://www.recruiter.com/i/tips-to-becoming-an-employer-of-choice-in-2014/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    How to succeed at building your own product in 2014 http://zite.to/JwNcNN     
    
    
    Ok, so this is the 3rd time my identity has been stolen... Maybe I'll just find a new one...    
    
    
    @JennyDeVaughn that was a great talk on social media you did #recruitfest    
    
    
    @Sarahw79 wont tell me what pearl jam means    
    
    
    Insulting Recruiters? It Just Might Work. http://www.recruiter.com/blog/insulting-recruiters-work/ … @hackruiter    
    
    
    Karmic retribution from leaving #recruitfest early, hanging out in beamsville w flat tire    
    
    
    @BooleanBlackBlt would you want to invest a thousand in twitter at that valuation? i would jump at that    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ewmonster i have that today lemme tell you ;) nice pic and great meeting you    
    
    
    @andygregorycgp my customs guy asked if there were any "wayward canadians" in the trunk. He was punchy but had an actors delivery #recru ...    
    
    
    @shally congrats!    
    
    
    @AmyRenz great to meet you!!    
    
    
    @qc_lady nice meeting you too, look forward to again sometime!    
    
    
    @ewmonster i have an official man crush on you    
    
    
    Love that everyones tweeting about their drunken breakfast in beds and im up for the day with a brighteyed 2 yearold...    
    
    
    @marenhogan me too but ate dinner 3x last night should be backsoon  re @marenhogan I lost 6 pounds at #recruitfest    
    
    
    @cvitello you know sat morning all kids have a built in alarm    
    
    
    Turning into one of those crzy sports dads    
    
    
    @JeanetteMcLeod any tips for teaching kids to slur the sounds together once they know individual sounds of letters in a word?    
    
    
    @marenhogan yr way more fun than we are RE I got a can of whipped cream and I am chasing my kids around pretending I have rabies    
    
    
    @lruettimann great to meet you this week, you are even punkier in person    
    
    
    @marenhogan tx for telling me about ubertwitter and ruining my life    
    
    
    things are getting better, you can feel it RT @andygregorycgp Niceto know I will be starting offMonday with a candidate accepting an offer    
    
    
    moved around whole house today pretty much for fun and now cant move. stay up for madmen or not, hmmm.. what a wild and crazy life    
    
    
    cool profile of a guy with a lot of good ideas RT @recruitingblogs Top 100 Auren Hoffman http://bit.ly/1ybvUt    
    
    
    @sgordon70 i have no idea. but if your business grows any faster than it already is, you can just buy apple. the company.    
    
    
    @JasonCBlais wouldnt you die? Re  “Laugh as much as you breathe"    
    
    
    Just signed @seerysm's Happy Birthday card. Happy birthday! http://hluv.me/yoccbi #hashlove    
    
    
    @lruettimann what is his latest?    
    
    
    Making my salesperson eat 450 of expenses. Just kidding christine.    
    
    
    @lruettimann ah seth's finally bastardizing squidoo. Guess he has to make a buck, but hes giving u what u couldmake on blogger in 10min    
    
    
    help @ryanleary win 10K for a national charity for Multiple Sclerosis. please vote for his video here: http://bit.ly/17IjuB #charity    
    
    
    Auto DMs are, apparently, a felony in some states.    
    
    
    @CASanta according to a recent poll, u should never find out    
    
    
    Amen RT @jillelswick: All I ever wanted was to be a rich eccentric.    
    
    
    I see you've turned on big brother GPS @CASanta RE polls can mean anything. I spurn your recent poll. http://myloc.me/ODCf    
    
    
    @marenhogan jello with fruit and whipped cream    
    
    
    @Jerry_Albright but can you insert a verbal summary?    
    
    
    @lruettimann drinks alone. Me too.    
    
    
    @DorothyBeach i dont know but i wonder how google wave will be used for recruiting. Got waverecruiting.com just for fun    
    
    
    Classic @Jerry_Albright re google wave sucks. I also have jerryalbrightsucks.com    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just signed @JohnSumser's Happy Birthday card. Happy bday! Hope to talk to u sometime for more than 30 seconds ;) http://hluv.me/1xo3im  ...    
    
    
    starting to think @ewmonster is simply a professional socialite.    
    
    
    That just deserves a RT @Animal: Don't post horrific links 1st thing in the morning    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ten Questions for your Recruiting Career http://bit.ly/dHVh0C  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
        
    
    
    @CASanta would make a horrible journalist    
    
    
    @blogging4jobs - saw this late. Thanks so much for the mention! 7 Amazing Resources for HR, Recruitment http://jessicamillermerrell.com/2011/03/7-amazing-resources-for-hr-recruitment-training/ …    
    
    
    @MikeRamer Tx Mike! Hope all is well. Let's connect again soon.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Here's our overly official press release - Recruiter.com Launches Collaborative Platform with Social Integration http://bit.ly/ezsT8E    
    
    
    @CASanta im glad you still have 10 yr old placebo still on your ipod    
    
    
    U r john muir not glenn beck RT @Animal: the staff quietly morphed from stunning resting-between-jobs actresses into stu    
    
    
    LinkedIn Is About To Make Headlines http://tcrn.ch/edxdPN  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Unfiring: Re-Recruitment Models http://bit.ly/dH7YMt  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    @CincyRecruiter i saw that show. Zig is a cool guy, kept repeating home-court advantage over and over    
    
    
    Just signed @dmanaster's Thank You card. what is the sound of one neon hand clapping?congrats on the acquisition! http://hluv.me/t5fz3d  ...    
    
    
    Twitter Talking Separately to Microsoft and Google About Big Data-Mining Deals - http://shar.es/1e0mq    
    
    
    Top Influencers v1.34: Jason Davis the man the myth the legend http://retwt.me/JgA7    
    
    
    @marenhogan Congrats again Maren! Very interesting company - I know you will take them far. http://bit.ly/eLo3v5    
    
    
    if you have way too much free time... RT @sengineland Google Continues Crowdsourcing Its Map Data http://bit.ly/p76cz    
    
    
    this @kevinrose guy knows his stuff.. How to Go from 1 to 1,000,000 Users (or Readers) http://ff.im/-9C6u3    
    
    
    @JasonCBlais you are    
    
    
    Veterans Face Likely Unemployment http://bit.ly/ei1TJ6  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    Thats messed up RT @kevinrose: "if you wish to make an apple pie from scratch, you must first create the universe." ~carl sagan    
    
    
    @lruettimann pretend hes singing as hes talking. Its supposed to work, diff part of brain accessed    
    
    
    @SourcerKelly easy, anyone doing keyword searches. Search is usually more important than followers unless u are @chrisbrogan    
    
    
    @SourcerKelly Put a job out w few followers and then thru 1 with lots and track results.    
    
    
    @TimDineen the quick answer is no    
    
    
    off to punpkin parade... we're a buncha paegans in ct...    
    
    
    @sarahw79 dude there isnt mongolian food within 35 mi of hometown    
    
    
    Parallels with .Jobs and .XXX extensions http://bit.ly/i8uBlW  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    hashjobs on bing and now maybe google? what do you think? is this a huge deal for online job search or I am too into these things? #jobs    
    
    
    @BillBoorman cool, I was starting to feel crazy. and my wife tells me I am... ;)    
    
    
    Does Software Shape Talent Acquisition? http://bit.ly/dh68Kf #recruiting    
    
    
    @Jordan_Banks oh no not you too    
    
    
    @marenhogan careful he can hypnotise too    
    
    
    Ladybug infestation in ct... This is really serious    
    
    
    poor guy gets a bad username RT @angielim:The man largely responsible for inventing the internet @timberners_lee, is now on Twitter    
    
    
    @PennyGoodman haha!    
    
    
    @PennyGoodman laughing with you not at you. ;)    
    
    
    thanks @amoodyknapp, you guys @ning are doing great work. i would love to hear your thoughts once www.talentbar.com is done.    
    
    
    @CallmeSlouch are you the ghost writer?    
    
    
    thinking after the fact that writing self-effacing emails to 75,000 people just comes off insincere    
    
    
    summary for the week for the social network for project managers: http://bit.ly/uMtwM #pmot    
    
    
    @ginab ever thought about having some kind of ning conference? I'll bet a lot of people would be interested.    
    
    
    @B2BTOTY hmm.. ok. what's a good blog post about it?    
    
    
    @B2BTOTY i actually meant a blog post that you've done that was interesting and inform. about your business. but thanks for the info    
    
    
    http://www.heifer.org/ is a cool charity. our kids are going to buy rabbits. what do they do with the rabbits they ask. hmm not magic tricks    
    
    
    @marenhogan i was a painter. Tip with cofee and doughnuts    
    
    
    that ping service works pretty well on ning, but can't seem to update more than one network    
    
    
    @Animal they have to be coming from somewhere..maybe look at embed link and extract it from there. U should also get file access    
    
    
    @Ning thanks for the #ff mention - back at you @ning and @ginab    
    
    
    @animal no idea on that one. but if you request file access from ning, you might be able to see them in your actual file directory    
    
    
    google and the social web from twitter recruiter RT @RecruitingDiva Nice article from @om @gigaom http://bit.ly/28UHfq #ff    
    
    
    @Jason that youre really popular    
    
    
    Are You Done Building your Social Network? http://bit.ly/bb3aSF #socialmedia    
    
    
    Twitter lists are making me crazy and eating up all my free time. ;)    
    
    
    @IanGertler hey Ian, just added you!    
    
    
    great @stevenpdennis, just added you...    
    
    
    @patrickmoran done, sir    
    
    
    @fearlesscomp done, sir    
    
    
    @DigitalPopuli done, sir    
    
    
    @cbruemmer done!    
    
    
    consider yourself listed @JohnDigles ;)    
    
    
    @jglass8 you even included the hey at the beginning, so you have been accepted...    
    
    
    @SocialSteve you have a cool twitter name, so you have been accepted.  just kidding. ;)    
    
    
    @RichardTurcott you are listed!    
    
    
    @mvolpe you sir, are now listed.    
    
    
    @citymindful thanks for the nice words, and you are now listed    
    
    
    @stewartgandolf done!    
    
    
    @Perficient thanks for the nice note!    
    
    
    @mscordell looks like a new Twitter account, what do you do?    
    
    
    @billpoly with a face like that, how could i say no?    
    
    
    What Does Google +1 Equal? http://bit.ly/eapu4n  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    @mcarpenter21 thanks so much!    
    
    
    @RecruiterApp how would i know that?    
    
    
    checking out wefollow, strangely for the first time    
    
    
    @ginab you're at the world series and I'm thinking about ning networks. what's wrong with this picture? (your reply, of course, nothing!)    
    
    
    Twitter lists are kind of cool in their equality. @wefollow can only have 20, just like you. check theirs out at @wefollow/lists    
    
    
    drinking a mcd eggnog milkshake after 8pm prob not my best idea...    
    
    
    @princessbowie it's darn good, I'll tell you    
    
    
    @wylywade milkshake: no milk, plenty of shake    
    
    
    my dad should write for barrons RT @xbrlfeed: EDGAR's Online Q3 in the Black: Adjusted EBITDA Soars 728% http://bit.ly/3Hljc9    
    
    
    @BooleanBlackBlt best wishes!!    
    
    
    @JasonCBlais maine is full of straight stoners    
    
    
        
    
    
    that's really cool @dannysullivan made a google news custom search section about search engines http://bit.ly/4Eg8nS    
    
    
    Twitter, Linkedin, & Ning all have common investors, they should play well together @braingain Noticed new follow functionality in LinkedIn    
    
    
    @Ning thanks so much for the nice mention! Ning rocks - keep up the great work!!    
    
    
    but of course RT @listorious 11% of the Listorious most popular Twitter lists are created by traditional media sources http://bit.ly/V6xlE    
    
    
    @johnfoleyjr - thanks for the nice note!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @RodSloane you sir, are listed. Let me know if you have suggested users and what you think of the cmo twitter list.    
    
    
    @mcmilker you are listed on the CMO marketing executive Twitter List! Let me know your thoughts on the list and if you have suggested users!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @akiki i can't believe you're not on it already! will do.    
    
    
    @KatyMGallagher well that's something that's never been said before... ;)    
    
    
    What Do Open Linkedin Groups Mean for Jobs? | http://bit.ly/bs2XFn #linkedin #jobs    
    
    
    @Paris22 @Jerry_Albright Have you had to shave lately? (My guess is - no) Miles always looks baby faced -- its all the clean living guys..    
    
    
    @MikeOwcarz lets see if that hashtag catches on. ;)    
    
    
    @marenhogan i love kind of blue but not his straight jazz    
    
    
    Ok i personally know of 2 people hospitalized and 1 dead from swine flu. Get that vaccine folks.    
    
    
    Thanks! @smallbiztwit: @milesj/CIO http://ow.ly/BWgo Best CIO list on Twitter 171 CIO's on list and followed by 462....very impressive.    
    
    
    man google wave is about as much fun as a migraine.    
    
    
    @chuckwoo I can't wait until "returning to our startup roots" is something we kick around during a meeting...;)    
    
    
    @RecruiterStacy is that the world's easiest job to fill or what? ;) seems like everyone's dream job.    
    
    
    First time the word deer stand ever used on twitter RT @Jerry_Albright: Heading out to the deer stand...    
    
    
    @ArlineWall no problem! enjoy!    
    
    
    @kyleford that is just horrible. re: @kyleford Eating an ostrich burger.  but i could use one myself.    
    
    
    @jowyang creating jobs is not the dark side of the force...    
    
    
    Havent watched yet, but has to be good RT @RecruitingDiva: Claymation Twitter tutorials http://is.gd/4XAmv by @alexalee    
    
    
        
    
    
    @joegerstandt and many times, the only priority    
    
    
    It's my once every 5th Spring cleaning day today...    
    
    
    @genexerjv thanks so much, glad you like it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Brave New Soccer http://www.recruiter.com/blog/brave-new-soccer/ …    
    
    
    Our First Company Handbook http://www.recruiter.com/blog/first-company-handbook/ …    
    
    
    @stephmcdonald that contest should be called the absolute hardest way to make 40k ;)    
    
    
    Prove that You're the Best http://www.recruiter.com/blog/prove-that-youre-the-best/ …    
    
    
    How to protect your brand on Twitter http://www.recruiter.com/blog/protect-your-brand-twitter/ …    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan the last time that happened to me.. Wait thats never happened to me    
    
    
    Quick discussion on NYT selling partial stake in Indeed.com http://bit.ly/jsnV9Y  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    All the Recruiting News That's Fit to Print http://www.recruiter.com/blog/recruiting-news-thats-fit-to-print/ …    
    
    
    we now have to drive by the "singing house" every night for the kids, LED xmas lights set to what sounds like Metallica jinglebells    
    
    
    Employ Media Defends .jobs domains http://bit.ly/iphDU5  via @RecruiterDotCom #recruiting    
    
    
    @guyfriedman thanks Guy, good to work with you    
    
    
    Interview with Maren Hogan (@marenhogan) of BraveNewTalent http://bit.ly/iXj4ya  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
    @marenhogan a white lie of course. But I'm seriously considering ordering some Recruiter.com tee shirts...    
    
    
    @peopleshark mark this one down as should, but never get around to... at least me that is. http://ow.ly/4Njge    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @Jerry_Albright Hartford is a hotbed for recruiting talkshow hosts, I can see why he would want to break into this lucrative market.    
    
    
    “@TechCrunch: The Next 10 Years Will Be .. http://tcrn.ch/lEyyUH ” great article tho I wonder if it's a good development for the general public    
    
    
        
    
    
    @peopleshark thanks for the mention Carmen, have a great week.    
    
    
    @Chernesky you've probably had the busiest month of your life because the huge hiring!    
    
    
    That NASA app is a good hour of fun w the kids. Here's shaggy. http://yfrog.com/h4uf1srj     
    
    
    This is too cool, they need a screensaver- Visible Tweets – http://bit.ly/lycFEm    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TSpagnola I just came across your profile and see you're in ct. How have I not spoken to you yet?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Good article on college and startups http://mobile.syracuse.com/advsyra/article/Jg9dBzle …    
    
    
    Required Reading for Startups http://www.recruiter.com/blog/required-reading-startups/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Bears, Babies, and Why No One Remembers You http://lnkd.in/CbpwgP    
    
    
    Holy Social Networking! Linkedin Shares Pop http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/holy-social-networking-linkedin-shares-pop/ … via @recruiterdotcom LNKD #IPO    
    
    
    Good blog about valuing your employees http://lnkd.in/ymrSxf    
    
    
    @toddyeager thanks, but not by me, it's @recruitercto    
    
    
    Some weekend dumbness - A Lightbulb Goes Off http://www.recruiter.com/blog/lightbulb/  via @RecruiterDotCom    
    
    
        
    
    
    For Memorial Day - http://lnkd.in/bJAhj2    
    
    
    The new Linkedin Apply button has some really neat implications http://www.recruiter.com/recruiting-news/apply-with-linkedin-button/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
        
    
    
    Recruiter.com babywear? Now I'm impressed. Thanks @recruitercto, you rock.    
    
    
    "Write like you just got hit in the head with an axe. You’re not very smart and you have one minute to talk before you bleed out."    
    
    
    Hockey Workplace Invasions... http://www.recruiter.com/articles/hockey-and-alien-workplace-invasions-2/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Social Networks for Recruiters: The End of an Era? http://www.recruiter.com/blog/social-networks-for-recruiters-the-end-of-an-era/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    Wish me luck, I'll need it... http://lnkd.in/6dnwBu    
    
    
    Usual reason I use my iPhone: grill timer. Happy weekend!    
    
    
    @Becalynd btw thanks Becky!    
    
    
    @RobertFischer yes! Best game ever. That mysterious thief was so annoying...    
    
    
    @MikeRamer thanks Mike, hope you had a good one!    
    
    
    Making me smile - penciled in hearts from our kids in the margins of our design docs...    
    
    
    @jwnajarian Thanks so much for the mention!    
    
    
    Google Plus (Google+): Finally, A Recruiting Friendly Facebook http://www.recruiter.com/articles/google-plus-facebook-recruiting/ … via @recruiterdotcom    
    
    
    A discussion of how Google Plus can be used for jobs and hiring http://www.recruiter.com/articles/google-plus-jobs/ …    
    
    
    3 New Google Plus Resources http://lnkd.in/4i_VfF  - wrap up of a few recent articles on the new service.    
    
    
    @animal Tx animal, hope all is well    
    
    
    @marenhogan Free is the new black http://bit.ly/qkSmxJ     
    
    
    