fabrik 2.0b3 out - role on the next release candidate :)    
    
    
    been triangulated by 3 cats - one of which is not my own and cant talk, well you know miaww!    
    
    
    just joined diaspora - like the way you can follow tags    
    
    
    finally update fabrikar.com subscription code from AEC to Fabrik subscription system    
    
    
    what is it with cats and doors? Can't they leave them closed?    
    
    
    @testthetweeture sxsw coming up    
    
    
    La Rochelle badminton Tournament this weekend, lets see if i can win a singles match for a change    
    
    
    new javascript plugin architecture for Fabrik 2.0 - install the fabrikjs form plugin from the SVN to see an example    
    
    
    man whats with the euro pound exchange rate - it sucks!    
    
    
    merry christmas, special thanks to rich for the song - awesome    
    
    
    cosmos the cat is recovering after falling off the roof of our 3 story flats - shes ok we think!    
    
    
    new Fabrik 3 release for Joomla 1.6/1.7 - http://bit.ly/jzZUbb  fork us at https://github.com/Fabrik/fabrik     
    
    
    back at work - wishing everyone a balanced and productive year!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen I wonder if portablecontacts isn't going to be hugh this year    
    
    
    snowing at home - very rare sight!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen is the comment extension got to be purely for JPress or can other components use it?    
    
    
    started caching some Fabrik queries - speed imrpovements galore!    
    
    
    @cozimek openid: pretty darn massive, opensocial uses it so thats 700million users right there, microsoft use it as well i believe    
    
    
    loving general midi    
    
    
    new jfusion release out - checking out the vbulletin integration    
    
    
    thanks to barbara http://tinyurl.com/8bbnro new fabrik calendar option to grey out weekends    
    
    
    just watched the lazurus project - a ray of inspiration on an otherwise dready sunday    
    
    
    @hisyamadnan no current plans to use #jplatform. Fabrik 3 stable is the current goal then wysiwyg editor    
    
    
    #Fabrik buildscript running all js code through jshint, and then using YUI compressor to compress the js files. Builds run from hudson    
    
    
    Yummy - got JanRains RPX to work with Joomla - login to Joomla with your facebook/openid/flickr/myspace account!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen yes it will be part of a component - nothing really solid to show yet. RPX uses openid2 - https://rpxnow.com/    
    
    
    fail: french ffbad.org, half the links don't work, can't enter results or see them correctly !    
    
    
    @AmyStephen you could wash them hehe! :P    
    
    
    added simple FOAF support to com_fabble    
    
    
    working on a commenting plugin for fabrik    
    
    
    igfest (bristol uk) game on tonight sign up here http://simongames.co.uk/play    
    
    
    post on n:n relationships in fabrik http://tinyurl.com/ck978w    
    
    
    community builder / fabrik plugin out http://tinyurl.com/dzomxn    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/y9ksncq #joomla #fabrik site notstricktlydubstep - some nice open source samples    
    
    
    @yireo the vunerability is fixed in 2.0rc5    
    
    
    #fabrik #joomla - boolean full-text searches now available in the SVN    
    
    
    I earned the Addon Adhesive sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/aEQhO8    
    
    
    facebook joins openid foundation - http://tinyurl.com/daftls    
    
    
    New order - guitars still sounding fresh to me    
    
    
    fabrik table rendering just got a whopping speed increase - go Hugh!    
    
    
    I earned the Lone Wolf sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/ayNzsB    
    
    
    @AmyStephen youcan use hashtags: http://twitter.pbwiki.com/Hashtags    
    
    
    @mspanish saw you saw that Amy was interested in RPX for Joomla.    
    
    
    @mspanish saw you were interested in RPX for Joomla - I'm part way through making a login module which uses RPX    
    
    
    is currently posting from fabble    
    
    
    is currently listening to itunes in alphabetical order    
    
    
    press release - check, new icon set - check,    
    
    
    enter pressed by accident - check!    
    
    
    We've released Fabrik 2.0rc1! Yeah! http://tinyurl.com/b8fk8u    
    
    
    thanks pdemaers for the good fabrik review : http://tinyurl.com/7hd77d&-feedback/forms/1659/details#rev-39254    
    
    
    #hatgame is going to sxsw    
    
    
    test msg    
    
    
    #hatgame  http://www.umbrellagroup.org/hatmap    
    
    
    test    
    
    
    14    
    
    
    I've released a little gpl Joomla twitter component /module  http://pollen-8.co.uk/    
    
    
    picking up speed towards a fabrik3.0b release.....    
    
    
    wow highest visitor numbers ever to fabrikar.com 6680 last week - 75% up on last year    
    
    
    We have 2525 users signed up to our mailing list. Thanks for all the love!    
    
    
    good luck to simon for #SXSW and their #hatgame - site built on #Joomla and #Fabrik http://www.umbrellagroup.org    
    
    
    speed up ur #Joomla #coding by typing less - use texter http://tinyurl.com/2xwg7v awesome!    
    
    
    ooh AND #texter fixes your spelling mistakes as well! - no more 'teh' (had to type really slowly for it not to change the spelling!)    
    
    
    #hatgame using #joomla and #fabrik at #sxsw featured on bbc http://tinyurl.com/bm9jdw    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i fear that people wont use Jaiku - not enough users compared to twitter    
    
    
    backup your site with amazon s3 - http://www.secobackup.com/    
    
    
    new fabrik wiki page for auto-fill form plugin http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Form_plugin_autofill …, please add more information    
    
    
    @alledia @Evernote  I got lost for an hour and a half once - double checked every car in the car park before finding mine    
    
    
    Fabrik elements wiki page http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Element_Plug-ins … - please help fill in the missing artilces    
    
    
    yeah  - promoted to french badminton National Division 3 - congrats to all the team!    
    
    
    Want to explain an action you know too well to some one (eg a smash) try doing it left handed - you'll understand better the difficulty!    
    
    
    “Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!”    
    
    
    is currently getting back to fabble    
    
    
    post 1    
    
    
    #fabrik 2.0rc2 for #joomla 1.5.10 released http://tinyurl.com/d5x93w    
    
    
    rockin to the wildhearts    
    
    
    @cozimek iplotz is a pretty nice wireframing tool - I have to admit though that paper and pen can't be beaten    
    
    
    got rid of 5 ish fabrik bugs today - only 40 odd more to go !    
    
    
    great personal music server - http://sockso.pu-gh.com/    
    
    
    Fabrik CCK - embed custom content directly in you Joomla articles http://fabrikar.com/blog/55-cck-video    
    
    
    @AmyStephen thx Amy - looking for feedback on improving this - suggestions welcome :)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen have to say I was just a "little" bit inspired by Tamka's methodology :)    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/1L08YTH9EAZPR  #Kindle    
    
    
    omg! zoho release  a series of open social gadgets http://bit.ly/4EJXL8    
    
    
    @BusinessContent not too up on what sobi can or cant do - the cck button allows you to insert custom data into J articles    
    
    
    @AmyStephen but action without ideas is directionless ;)    
    
    
    finished The Black Prism: Lightbringer: Book One by Brent Weeks and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/kOnrbr  #Kindle    
    
    
    finished The Heroes by Joe Abercrombie http://amzn.to/mvn1TS  #Kindle    
    
    
    test live site    
    
    
    has fixed a horrid bug in fabrik subscriptions    
    
    
    alice is home - yeah!    
    
    
    not connected to facebook    
    
    
    scratching his head    
    
    
    fb connect disabled in module    
    
    
    is currently ola    
    
    
    is currently heyo    
    
    
    @cozimek heheh none - its perfect as it is :) - now if more people could supply bundles of J and components that would be cool    
    
    
    #fabrik admin pagination of table data should be working now - how did i miss that one!    
    
    
    consulting my #joomla #iching about serious questions in life and love    
    
    
    new #fabrik plugin download available  create #Joomla users from your forms http://bit.ly/Npcho    
    
    
    in #fabrik you can now opt to copy elements when you copy groups    
    
    
    anyone know of a 'forge' like #Joomla component? (No need to host SVN just allow users to host mini projects)    
    
    
    @cozimek not 100% sure if it will load all tweets but you could check out my #joomla #twitter component  http://bit.ly/sBajR    
    
    
    #fabrik file upload element now can store and retrieve documents to Amazon s3 storage    
    
    
    looks like hugh added an ip address element plug-in to the #fabrik svn - go Hugh :)    
    
    
    testing bumptop - neat 3d desktop app!
http://twitpic.com/4j8vr    
    
    
    @cozimek pc desktop or real one? for the desktop bumptop is quiet fun - http://bumptop.com/    
    
    
    #fabrik passwod element plugin now committed to SVN - has strength checker code and stores in J1.5 password format    
    
    
    finally added commenting plug-in to #fabrik downloads section (subscribers only) http://bit.ly/7i7og    
    
    
    happy with the new http://fabrikar.com/blog/74-fabrik-304-released … fabrik3.0.4 release for Joomla 2.5    
    
    
    added new subscriber tutorial on #fabrik releated data feature http://bit.ly/14UQ4M    
    
    
    @AmyStephen opensocial the future just you won;'' know its there (but you'll be using it - gmail, hi5,myspace, ning etc.......)    
    
    
    please vote for new fabrik features @ http://fabrik.uservoice.com    
    
    
    @AmyStephen not a small undertaking I've been working on a container for a while (using shindig)   can send you some alpha code if you want    
    
    
    @AmyStephen ah they've improved that since i last looked at it - seems a pretty good idea for Tamka :)    
    
    
    fabrikar.com visitor stats 32000 unique visitors in April - up 107% from last year - thanks everyone! #fabrik #joomla    
    
    
    fabrik 2.0rc3 released -  http://bit.ly/207H5O    
    
    
    just got back from teaching badminton - too darn hot for it    
    
    
    pet hate - people who just write "hi rob" in skype then dont say anything more - write a full  sentence darn it!    
    
    
    @Dean_IconWeb ok i was asking for that - big time    
    
    
    Reading: "European Parliament Now Within Grasp of the Pirate Party" (http://twitthis.com/knttjd)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen for subs I used AEC, JFusion and Paypal. On the accounting I use sage and tradebox cash manager to download and records subs    
    
    
    @AmyStephen for subs its all about creating value around your product, be that support, videos, docs extra code etc    
    
    
    new #fabrik subscriber tutorial up - describes using linkage tables to create multi-multi relationships    
    
    
    I'm watching Cowboys & Aliens http://bit.ly/IHz5Pn  @GetGlue #CowboysAliens    
    
    
    I'm watching Immortals (10 others checked-in) http://bit.ly/IvbWAw  @GetGlue @immortalsfilm    
    
    
    Fabrik Tutorial - Creating Joomla Forms Documentation - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/introduction-to-fabrik/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    anyone know why #Joomla 1.5.20 with the #mootools upgrade plugin will allow class.extends({}) in firefox but not in IE?    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan - Hi Ian got an odd inconsistency with the new Mootools 1.2 compat layer in J1.5.20 -  http://bit.ly/9IBWzv    
    
    
    Fabrik and Custom Joomla User Registration Form - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/fabrik-user-registration-form/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    Fabrik: Create a Custom Joomla User List - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/joomla-user-list/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    CSS / JS Auto Refreshing with Live.js http://zite.to/M5T8vt  via @zite    
    
    
    Introducing boxbox http://zite.to/LzHWEH  via @zite    
    
    
    xbox 360 human interaction - wayyyy more advanced than the wii  http://bit.ly/fhaei    
    
    
    working on wedding playlist - think I'll just put Chemical Brothers on repeat for a couple of hours:)    
    
    
    think if i put on 4 hours of electro I might make my guest ears bleed a little too much    
    
    
    finished badminton coaching for the season, sad to see some of the students leaving the fold - sigh    
    
    
    @cozimek  probably not exactly what you were looking for, but the #fabrik upload element lets you store and retrieve content from amazon s3    
    
    
    I have more requests for quotes that a human can possibly handle - anyone competent with creating forms in #fabrik who wants  $$$    
    
    
    @cozimek it uses adaptor classes, currenlty theres one for the filesystem and one for amazon s3,   s3 code based on http://bit.ly/HFTo7    
    
    
    20 Must-Have Massive GUI kits http://zite.to/LArwdi  via @zite    
    
    
    finished The Forever War by Joe Haldeman and gave it 2 stars http://amzn.to/LYuatv  #Kindle    
    
    
    need to render #pdfs in #Joomla ? see my Joomla wiki article http://docs.joomla.org/How_to_create_PDF_views#Download_the_domPDF_library …    
    
    
    fixed 20ish #fabrik #joomla bugs this am - things are looking pretty solid - each fix required  1 or two lines of code changes to fix !    
    
    
    working on in-line table editing for #fabrik - got the ajax up for injecting elements in table cells :)    
    
    
    got to love #mootools inheritance model - eat that #jQuery!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen click table cell, load content, save update cell, each cell data type has js classes which inherit from various super classes    
    
    
    @AmyStephen looks limited no? and why use yet another js lib in Joomla when theres a mootools version already  http://tinyurl.com/krjoh7.    
    
    
    @AmyStephen have i missed something with the jQuery one then? i saw ordering and highlighting - thats all no? Both libs are not ok for me    
    
    
    Do Joomla! have a future? Sure! its just not written yet- everyone grab your pens!    
    
    
    @Tigratrus you make it sound like a trip to the toilet! lol    
    
    
    finished White Tiger: Dark Heavens Book One by Kylie Chan and gave it 2 stars  pretty average http://amzn.to/Nd7PZi  #Kindle    
    
    
    fabrik 2.0.1 released - this is security update so please everyone upgrade! http://bit.ly/9wWJcs    
    
    
    Shell car servicing site implemented in #fabrik #joomla by softforge http://carservicing.shell.co.uk/  sweet!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i'm working on a Kaltura series of plugins for #Joomla and #Fabrik - its a very cool service!    
    
    
    anyone looking to buy a 1bed flat in London - my sister is selling hers    
    
    
    I'm meeting the termite man in an hours time    
    
    
    @neriv glad you like fabrik cck? whats the +/'- of the two systems?    
    
    
    1.5 hours till i sign for my new house :o    
    
    
    at the back of your head
 http://amzn.com/k/1A9P1FK6Q5J2N #Kindle    
    
    
    just submitted a  #Joomla 1.6 patch with a MVC refractored newsfeed admin component  and shift click to select multiple items    
    
    
    neat cypherinfo added fabrik to wikipedia http://tinyurl.com/lhe24c    
    
    
    @jprobinso have a beer for me!    
    
    
    finished The Cold Commands (Gollancz S.F.) by Richard Morgan and gave it 4 stars http://amzn.to/sX0aTA  #Kindle    
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/oIRgT  - I'm really stoked to announce that Fabrik 3.0.6 is now out!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen lol yeah - 'everyone' wants to be like ME (j/k) :)    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/cHCSgpr7TSO0DiETWooF5A … #Kindle    
    
    
    new subscriber #fabrik tutorial for using mySQL views as database join data sources - sounds complex but isn't :) http://fabrikar.com/help/tutorials/details/3/30 …    
    
    
    Neat hack for limiting #fabrik dropdown options based on the current users access level http://fabrikar.com/forums/showthread.php?t=27633 …    
    
    
    2 displaced vertebra - undeniably rather painful!    
    
    
    working on Twtiter/oAuth integration for fabrik    
    
    
    Want yours? Click to get an invite to build your graphical bio on Vizify. https://www.vizify.com?code=199964&km_source=invite_twitter&km_generation=0&km_orig_source=invite_twitter&km_orig_person=FsUSRRMKZ509PMsFUS7LO8MBCgk=&km_prev_person=FsUSRRMKZ509PMsFUS7LO8MBCgk=vizify.com/?code=199964&k … via @vizify    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    Analysis of 20 Bootstrapped Startup Landing Pages http://zite.to/OsAVqo  via @zite    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    25 Beautiful Examples of Pricing Tables http://zite.to/SAq18d  via @zite    
    
    
    Joomla 2.5.7 Released http://shar.es/u5E73  via @sharethis - contains my humble patch for duplicate db sessions errors when using ajax    
    
    
    @roblocke wrong, they've banned non GPL extensions - commercial GPL extensions ARE listed    
    
    
    added a subscriber #fabrik plug-in to limit the number of form submissions a user can make. #joomla    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    #Joomla 1.5.12 updated tinymce to v3 the old v2 methods will no longer work! This effects #fabrik - please update  http://tinyurl.com/qduxwp    
    
    
    finished Cloud Atlas by David Mitchell and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/itg8Gw  #Kindle    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    over at #fabrik we have released the latest version of Fabrik for #Joomla 1.5: http://bit.ly/gPf4zQ    
    
    
    31 years old and i still hate using the phone, especially in french    
    
    
    Créer une application Web pour le CMS joomla avec le constructeur d'application Fabrik http://www.betterliving.be/qf     
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/guPW4gV9RLS4T8BKD1j4Fg … #Kindle    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    Yeah #fabrik lists and forms now insert the menu items meta data and keywords, oh and you can use {placeholders} as well!    
    
    
    Just finished off adding some batch acl methods for #fabrik elements - saves you editing 100's of elements one by one!    
    
    
    @TessaFenwick glad you no longer have to wait :)    
    
    
    finished Best Served Cold by Joe Abercrombie and gave it 4 stars http://amzn.to/Anby94  #Kindle    
    
    
    anyone used http://www.joomlaads.com/ ? feedback as either a advertiser or publisher welcome    
    
    
    got my iphone - so what apps should I install?    
    
    
    anyone had experience with YQL?    
    
    
    slug dreams http://amzn.com/k/DLKQ0UK7Z7BA #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/kmxKK5HzTQivXOXEwAEOmQ … #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/ZQXmbhhiQKC1G8UpToInpQ … #Kindle    
    
    
    finished Red Country by Joe Abercrombie and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/R4Y5nA     
    
    
    dreaming http://amzn.com/k/EU3GUX7I5PAN #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/mnirn4JJTDGLIr9miKjQjg … “It’s the questions we can’t answer that teach us the most. They teach us how to think.    
    
    
    @jeandrelennox why do you ask? I quoted something front.a.book I was.reading.tonight. Did you think that was not.me?    
    
    
    @bloqhead reduce fabrik js files: go to admin ->tables->params-> 'yes' for 'Merged JS files ' report the js error on the fabrik forum    
    
    
    Want to learn to write #Fabrik plug-ins and get paid for it? We need an eWay payment plugin - contact me #Joomla    
    
    
    finished Wise Man's Fear: The Kingkiller Chronicle: Day Two by Patrick Rothfuss and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/eGmwHb     
    
    
    great line http://amzn.com/k/HPZKMN1P10W5 #Kindle    
    
    
    Please help us translate fabrik @ https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/fabrik/ …    
    
    
    Twitter oAuth for MSGE    
    
    
    The tweature will rise    
    
    
    Sorry it seems my twitter account was hacked - and Ive been Direct messaging spam - please ingore them!    
    
    
    Built a neat database schema comparison tool into #fabrik today, lets you manage and deploy changes across two databases via Joomla's admin    
    
    
    @danielrwoodward post your questions in the forum and we will try to help :)    
    
    
    just added in option to publish/unpublish fabrik element validations    
    
    
    oh and options to (un)publish fabrik element javascript events    
    
    
    @sanderpotjer great work Sander!    
    
    
    Oh wow - Fabrik's made it into Joomla's top 10 Community Choice Extensions Winners! 
http://magazine.joomla.org/issues/issue-dec-2012/item/1011-community-choice-extensions-december-2012 …    
    
    
    added a new #fabrik tsubscriber utorial - how to build charts visualizations from your table data #joomla #jos    
    
    
    We have a new Alphauserpoints form plug-in for #fabrik #joomla. Award users points for submitting forms!http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Form_plugin_alphauserpoints …    
    
    
    Support MooTools FTW, add a #twibbon to your avatar now! - http://twibbon.com/join/MooTools-FTW    
    
    
    Sweet! You can now style Fabrik google map elements - see our wiki docs for how!
http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Google_map …    
    
    
    @danielrwoodward cool :) - we're getting close to a final #fabrik 2.0 release WOOT!    
    
    
    Tom just released a #youtube plugin for #fabrik  http://tinyurl.com/l2o3le - nice work Tom! #joomla    
    
    
    http://imgur.com/elR6msH  via @imgur    
    
    
    responsive #Fabrik list layouts in Joomla3 https://github.com/Fabrik/fabrik/commit/8fd580fa9df267d411a82cdd276e40cc20703765 …    
    
    
    Bootstrap for Extension Developers JWC 2012 on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/andytarr/bootstrap-for-extension-developers-jwc-2012 …    
    
    
    Creating Animations and Transitions With D3 http://shar.es/CIkt5  via @visually    
    
    
    time for lunch!    
    
    
    improved #fabrik update column plugin, users can now mass apply updates to multiple columns    
    
    
    testers please for update for my #joomla #bootstrap calendar http://joomlacode.org/gf/project/joomla/tracker/?action=TrackerItemEdit&tracker_item_id=30040 …    
    
    
    Joomla 3.1 Beta2 Released http://shar.es/eI2kU  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @Tigratrus cool! - I tend to hashtag anything to do with fabrik with #fabrik so you can set up a filter in tweetdeck for that !    
    
    
    new http://2.8hourslater.com/  2.8hourslater asylum site up ! Ready for further #zombie carnage    
    
    
    had a great weekend!    
    
    
    new #fabrik video coming soon - using the twitter form plugin    
    
    
    good morning all #fabrik users!    
    
    
    going to start reading 'merde actually'    
    
    
    try to go for a run    
    
    
    Today I'm me    
    
    
    Today I'm reworking fabrik 2.0.x redirect code    
    
    
    Today I'm nothing to see here    
    
    
    Today I'm on fire!    
    
    
    why is mulitsite work such a head mangler?    
    
    
    Adham Shaikh - great electro artist    
    
    
    fabrik site down for an upgrade, sorry its taking longer than expected!    
    
    
    checking out #evernote on the pc    
    
    
    Sorry for the long delay, but the new http://fabrikar.com   site should now be up and running. Let us know if you have suggestions/issues    
    
    
    approaching 24 hours in front of the pc. oh dear    
    
    
    @pete_fry like to see you sprint for 1km pete :)    
    
    
    @pete_fry So would i lol.Did a 10k fun run last month in 55 mins so thats what 5.5 min / km (gosh my maths rocks)    
    
    
    Just added the option to add polylines to #fabrik #googlemap #visualizations    
    
    
    Get your  free #fabrik form template - each group rendered in its own tab  http://tinyurl.com/muwb8s #joomla    
    
    
    I just uploaded "Fabrik 3.1 - details template desgin" to Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/65639868     
    
    
    I just added "Fabrik 3.1 - details template desgin" to Fabrik: http://vimeo.com/channels/38129/65639868 …    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i set my own define : define( "COM_FABRIK_LIVESITE",  str_replace('/administrator', '', JURI::base()) );    
    
    
    buffer looks pretty cool    
    
    
    I used Shazam to discover The Promise by The Cure #shazam    
    
    
    changed my first car battery - I  feel like a man ! (one with very little manual skills of course)    
    
    
    yeah! woop woop - mortgage docs came through - *should* mean I move on the 15th - at last!    
    
    
    man #lastfm sucks now i have to pay for streaming. Minus 1 point for living in france    
    
    
    MooTools Roundup - August 2009 http://bit.ly/2Sgp6v    
    
    
    Want a Fabrik conference? Please fill in our questionnaire http://fabrikar.com/component/fabrik/form/45/ …    
    
    
    @NorviceSpartan yes pay for a subscription to get it    
    
    
    I earned the I Am Number Four Coming Soon sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/iebHfb    
    
    
    I earned the Opening Week sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/dPvoTc    
    
    
    @manishc  fabrik tutorials - http://fabrikar.com/help/tutorials    
    
    
    igfest in Bristol this weekend   http://tinyurl.com/q34o8m - street games, mass social interaction,  play and adventure.    
    
    
    #moosehunt is ON! - #Joomla powered street game for #igfest  http://tinyurl.com/pbha2m #bristol    
    
    
    @eworldhost yes you can get fabrik to pull data from a db table and display it in the front end - the db doesnt have to be the J db either    
    
    
    2 hours - 3 cups off coffee and i have most of #fabrik running in #Joomla1.6 - just have to think about the ACL changes    
    
    
    going to Tours tomorrow - first day of Badminton N3! woot!    
    
    
    tom added an awesome fusion charts viz to #Fabrik grab it in the svn    
    
    
    added a custom fabrik filter to output PDF's of activities per town for http://vrijenwillig.nl/activiteitenzoeker# …    
    
    
    @eworldhost yes    
    
    
    updated my #joomla tag cloud module for 1.5 - download here -  http://tinyurl.com/phcxkd    
    
    
    #Ryanair just cancelled my christmas flights - didn't suggest an alternative even if there's one from Poitieres - freaking USELESS COMPANY!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen HAPPY BIRTHDAY :)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen hi Amy the Fabrik team is going to the J dev conf in New York, love to do the talk on mt1.2 - how can I contact the organizers    
    
    
    @ElinWaring hi Elin - I'd love to do the talk on mt1.2 @ the Joomla dev conf at new york let me know if you are intrested    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/ma76zx    
    
    
    intresting debate on whether experienced J core devs should be coding or mentoring others http://tinyurl.com/ma76zx    
    
    
    tip use JArrayHelper::getValue() to get data from an array in Joomla - avoids warnings if no key found in the array #joomla    
    
    
    #fabrik subscribers - get the new 'digg' voting element from the downloads section #joomla    
    
    
    flexible #javascript #mootools method to clone an object with options to clone or pass by reference http://tinyurl.com/m2s3jl    
    
    
    I earned the Movie Buff(100) sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/hExoqk    
    
    
    new #joomla #fabrik subscriber #tutorial : one to many relationships: create tables/forms to store parent/child data and relationships    
    
    
    woops! url for #joomla #fabrik #tutorial is http://tinyurl.com/yjfurs8    
    
    
    @ElinWaring  any chance you can let me know if you are considering my proposal to do a talk at New York #Joomla dev conf ?    
    
    
    working on a #balsamiq xml importer into #fabrik - design mockups and create working #Joomla fabrik applications    
    
    
    @balsamiq - thanks, so far so good the xml structure is clear didn't even need to read the docs! will post a video when I'm done!    
    
    
    #fabrik placeholders can now accept {$their->var->uservalue} which allows you to load in a user from $_REQUST[var] and access its properties    
    
    
    dont suppose anyone's got a #googlewave invite?    
    
    
    2009 sucks - long live 2010    
    
    
    added a #ambrasubs plugin "afterstore: update database col " - http://tinyurl.com/ydqacv3 #joomla    
    
    
    Teaser video for our new #balsamiq to #fabrik #Joomla component - rapid prototyping :: rapid deployment http://vimeo.com/20926663    
    
    
    Amen ! RT @LouisLandry: Those using php with the suhosin patch be wary of session/cookie encryption settings with Joomla especially with IE8    
    
    
    pet hate - people asking you to quote for a job but tell you they don't have a lot of money - 'oh ok! I'll charge you less then!' :D    
    
    
    gotta love Neal Asher! http://bit.ly/fR4If5 (via @GetGlue) #TheVoyageOfTheSableKeech    
    
    
    capable of twisting the seemingly ordinary into something the twisted side of abnormal - great! http://bit.ly/hycNZ5 (via @GetGlue)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen gosh yes well just been too darn busy :D got engaged, and doing lots of fun stuff!    
    
    
    FB open social graph allows you to give a fax number - anyone still use those? When will the last person using one realze?    
    
    
    @AmyStephen should be doing #jab11 need to sort myself out for it first!    
    
    
    testing out twitter in google wave - nice but twitter avatars dont show    
    
    
    anyone want a #googlewave invite?    
    
    
    sorry must be going mad - swore i saw an option to send invites for googlewave - but now i dont see it - very sorry to have wasted ppls time    
    
    
    @kproductivity lol thanks so i wasn't going mad then!    
    
    
    great weekend with my parents, inspirational people!!    
    
    
    fail: artiosef free doesn't play nicely with ajax calls  - inserts an advert in the returned json - boo!    
    
    
    So funny http://bit.ly/fcwMfs @GetGlue #LeDnerDeCons    
    
    
    #fabrik subscriptions up 5% this month - thank you to everyone that makes it possible    
    
    
    wooh google just offered to translate a web page for me ?    
    
    
    wishing #simongames good luck in their crazy caravan gps game #joomla #fabrik powered game for #sohotheatre    
    
    
    just booked my ticket to #joomla dev conference new york - woot!    
    
    
    @ElinWaring just booked my ticket for new york! looking forward to it    
    
    
    I am watching Dirty Dancing http://bit.ly/eH0Zif @GetGlue #DirtyDancing    
    
    
    I am watching Trainspotting http://bit.ly/eWDizy @GetGlue #Trainspotting    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan yup use mootools heavily !    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan  fabrik has a #mootools switch for 1.1/1.2- prefer 1.2 but its hard to get it to play nicely with other 3d party stuff    
    
    
    playing wth mootools ART and a Joomla 1.6 system plugin to switch ART styles based on active J template. Wish  understood mt depender better    
    
    
    @andrewmilks nice to see your web site quoting site up! http://tinyurl.com/yagp4b9    
    
    
    Yeah made it to the airport new York joomla Dev conf here I come    
    
    
    #jdc09 rooms filling up - coffees poured - lets bring it on    
    
    
    getting ready to leave to see the guys at#futuron, then its off to #jab11 - will have a #fabrik stand - looking forward to it!!    
    
    
    @cozimek thanks for the OSM talk - truely you ROCK Ryan - the honestly in the way you communicate is an example to us all!    
    
    
    #fabrik Financial Viability form  http://tinyurl.com/ye5cjvw by @kproductivity @kproductivity    
    
    
    waiting for alice    
    
    
    test from sameplaces    
    
    
    ripping all my old cds from when i was 15 - thewildheats still rock - yeah yeah i know its not cool but f**k it    
    
    
    can invite people to twine.com if intrested?    
    
    
    fabrik ajax form validations are now kinda working - horay for my ego!    
    
    
    got a bare bones triplify configuration file wotrking in Joomla    
    
    
    finally won a badminton team match = still going down though    
    
    
    wheres the frickin sun gone ?    
    
    
    @emargee chill man - listen to some biosphere :)    
    
    
    @emargee the leg thing could be quiet cool - http://snurl.com/23s4p - or theres alwasy lastminute.com    
    
    
    how cool - flash based font creator http://fontstruct.fontshop.com    
    
    
    fabrik 2 - slightly more valid xhtml output than this morning!    
    
    
    @emargee hey steve id be up for checking out evernote ;)    
    
    
    @emargee duh yeah - rob@pollen-8.co.uk    
    
    
    gr why is PHP4 still here    
    
    
    5 active fabrik 2.0 tickets left    
    
    
    OMG! just figured out how to use Joomla view caching for logged in users for fabrik - 5x speed improvement !    
    
    
    new inkscape out    
    
    
    new fabrik site template coming along nicely    
    
    
    @S_Shot way to go guys!    
    
    
    the devil is Always in the details - damn him    
    
    
    mhhuahh friendfeed now available in twirl - v cool    
    
    
    finally after 5 months go my glasses fixed - blimy hadnt realised how blind i was getting    
    
    
    yeah my wrist now longer hurts - could actually smash the shuttle yesterday - I'm still an unfit slacker  but at least that can be fixed    
    
    
    @emargee yeah blind and no hands! - ergonomic keyboard and chair on order!    
    
    
    @emargee  its when you start feeling the 'drafts' when all the doors are closed that you have to really start worrying :O    
    
    
    ahhh at last the delicious addon for firefox 3    
    
    
    @emargee as you seem to love twitter the most out of my friends -- http://snurl.com/29qy9    
    
    
    new version of the #balsamiq to #fabrik component bug fixes plus allows you to create forms/tables by pasting in xmlhttp://bit.ly/jzZUbb    
    
    
    I love the evoluent mouse - their keyboard has a great idea to put the number pad on the left .. http://bit.ly/lYRH2b    
    
    
    just saw #futurons #fabrik designs for #podion - omg its going to be awesom!    
    
    
    Vizualize.Me is launching soon and I'm one of the first in line! Join me. #launch http://vizualize.me/30yb9  via @vizualizeme    
    
    
    just finish Fabrik presentation to JoomlaDay South Africa - great fun - shame about skype calls cutting out though!    
    
    
    trying out zenbe email with twitter integration    
    
    
    reducing queries - 200% gain. Now to reduce memory - banging head on wall will provide acceptable results    
    
    
    struggling with crappy xp machines networking    
    
    
    new card new cable - no go    
    
    
    going to bed - 23:30 and still 28  degrees    
    
    
    just realised that commuting sucks - hey just as well i work from home :)    
    
    
    releasing Fabrik 1.0.6....    
    
    
    hey everyone please help my lovely friend Marine by filling in her "tourism on the net" questionnaire http://tinyurl.com/y9jbbt9    
    
    
    just added #coverflow and #ganttchart  visualizations to the #fabrik svn (#joomla) More great ways to show your #fabrik data!    
    
    
    Hannes is asking for help with patches for Joomla1.6 http://tinyurl.com/yzwlgys - I've just done two, can you beat me? :)    
    
    
    woot some ones actually gone to the trouble of pirating my fabrik tutorials - thanks a lot I'm flattered!    
    
    
    buisness cards - check, flyers - check - We good to go!    
    
    
    grrr French printers - you'd think 5 days notice would be enough to get some crummy business cards printed! - But.. found one in the end    
    
    
    coded a nice html5 video annotation mootols/joomla content plugin working    
    
    
    @testthetweeture 123456    
    
    
    @testthetweeture  abc    
    
    
    @testthetweeture  tes6 from rob    
    
    
    fabrik 2.0b3 out - role on the next release candidate :)    
    
    
    been triangulated by 3 cats - one of which is not my own and cant talk, well you know miaww!    
    
    
    just joined diaspora - like the way you can follow tags    
    
    
    finally update fabrikar.com subscription code from AEC to Fabrik subscription system    
    
    
    what is it with cats and doors? Can't they leave them closed?    
    
    
    @testthetweeture sxsw coming up    
    
    
    La Rochelle badminton Tournament this weekend, lets see if i can win a singles match for a change    
    
    
    new javascript plugin architecture for Fabrik 2.0 - install the fabrikjs form plugin from the SVN to see an example    
    
    
    man whats with the euro pound exchange rate - it sucks!    
    
    
    merry christmas, special thanks to rich for the song - awesome    
    
    
    cosmos the cat is recovering after falling off the roof of our 3 story flats - shes ok we think!    
    
    
    new Fabrik 3 release for Joomla 1.6/1.7 - http://bit.ly/jzZUbb  fork us at https://github.com/Fabrik/fabrik     
    
    
    back at work - wishing everyone a balanced and productive year!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen I wonder if portablecontacts isn't going to be hugh this year    
    
    
    snowing at home - very rare sight!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen is the comment extension got to be purely for JPress or can other components use it?    
    
    
    started caching some Fabrik queries - speed imrpovements galore!    
    
    
    @cozimek openid: pretty darn massive, opensocial uses it so thats 700million users right there, microsoft use it as well i believe    
    
    
    loving general midi    
    
    
    new jfusion release out - checking out the vbulletin integration    
    
    
    thanks to barbara http://tinyurl.com/8bbnro new fabrik calendar option to grey out weekends    
    
    
    just watched the lazurus project - a ray of inspiration on an otherwise dready sunday    
    
    
    @hisyamadnan no current plans to use #jplatform. Fabrik 3 stable is the current goal then wysiwyg editor    
    
    
    #Fabrik buildscript running all js code through jshint, and then using YUI compressor to compress the js files. Builds run from hudson    
    
    
    Yummy - got JanRains RPX to work with Joomla - login to Joomla with your facebook/openid/flickr/myspace account!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen yes it will be part of a component - nothing really solid to show yet. RPX uses openid2 - https://rpxnow.com/    
    
    
    fail: french ffbad.org, half the links don't work, can't enter results or see them correctly !    
    
    
    @AmyStephen you could wash them hehe! :P    
    
    
    added simple FOAF support to com_fabble    
    
    
    working on a commenting plugin for fabrik    
    
    
    igfest (bristol uk) game on tonight sign up here http://simongames.co.uk/play    
    
    
    post on n:n relationships in fabrik http://tinyurl.com/ck978w    
    
    
    community builder / fabrik plugin out http://tinyurl.com/dzomxn    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/y9ksncq #joomla #fabrik site notstricktlydubstep - some nice open source samples    
    
    
    @yireo the vunerability is fixed in 2.0rc5    
    
    
    #fabrik #joomla - boolean full-text searches now available in the SVN    
    
    
    I earned the Addon Adhesive sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/aEQhO8    
    
    
    facebook joins openid foundation - http://tinyurl.com/daftls    
    
    
    New order - guitars still sounding fresh to me    
    
    
    fabrik table rendering just got a whopping speed increase - go Hugh!    
    
    
    I earned the Lone Wolf sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/ayNzsB    
    
    
    @AmyStephen youcan use hashtags: http://twitter.pbwiki.com/Hashtags    
    
    
    @mspanish saw you saw that Amy was interested in RPX for Joomla.    
    
    
    @mspanish saw you were interested in RPX for Joomla - I'm part way through making a login module which uses RPX    
    
    
    is currently posting from fabble    
    
    
    is currently listening to itunes in alphabetical order    
    
    
    press release - check, new icon set - check,    
    
    
    enter pressed by accident - check!    
    
    
    We've released Fabrik 2.0rc1! Yeah! http://tinyurl.com/b8fk8u    
    
    
    thanks pdemaers for the good fabrik review : http://tinyurl.com/7hd77d&-feedback/forms/1659/details#rev-39254    
    
    
    #hatgame is going to sxsw    
    
    
    test msg    
    
    
    #hatgame  http://www.umbrellagroup.org/hatmap    
    
    
    test    
    
    
    14    
    
    
    I've released a little gpl Joomla twitter component /module  http://pollen-8.co.uk/    
    
    
    picking up speed towards a fabrik3.0b release.....    
    
    
    wow highest visitor numbers ever to fabrikar.com 6680 last week - 75% up on last year    
    
    
    We have 2525 users signed up to our mailing list. Thanks for all the love!    
    
    
    good luck to simon for #SXSW and their #hatgame - site built on #Joomla and #Fabrik http://www.umbrellagroup.org    
    
    
    speed up ur #Joomla #coding by typing less - use texter http://tinyurl.com/2xwg7v awesome!    
    
    
    ooh AND #texter fixes your spelling mistakes as well! - no more 'teh' (had to type really slowly for it not to change the spelling!)    
    
    
    #hatgame using #joomla and #fabrik at #sxsw featured on bbc http://tinyurl.com/bm9jdw    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i fear that people wont use Jaiku - not enough users compared to twitter    
    
    
    backup your site with amazon s3 - http://www.secobackup.com/    
    
    
    new fabrik wiki page for auto-fill form plugin http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Form_plugin_autofill …, please add more information    
    
    
    @alledia @Evernote  I got lost for an hour and a half once - double checked every car in the car park before finding mine    
    
    
    Fabrik elements wiki page http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Element_Plug-ins … - please help fill in the missing artilces    
    
    
    yeah  - promoted to french badminton National Division 3 - congrats to all the team!    
    
    
    Want to explain an action you know too well to some one (eg a smash) try doing it left handed - you'll understand better the difficulty!    
    
    
    “Whatever you can do or dream you can, begin it. Boldness has genius, power and magic in it!”    
    
    
    is currently getting back to fabble    
    
    
    post 1    
    
    
    #fabrik 2.0rc2 for #joomla 1.5.10 released http://tinyurl.com/d5x93w    
    
    
    rockin to the wildhearts    
    
    
    @cozimek iplotz is a pretty nice wireframing tool - I have to admit though that paper and pen can't be beaten    
    
    
    got rid of 5 ish fabrik bugs today - only 40 odd more to go !    
    
    
    great personal music server - http://sockso.pu-gh.com/    
    
    
    Fabrik CCK - embed custom content directly in you Joomla articles http://fabrikar.com/blog/55-cck-video    
    
    
    @AmyStephen thx Amy - looking for feedback on improving this - suggestions welcome :)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen have to say I was just a "little" bit inspired by Tamka's methodology :)    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/1L08YTH9EAZPR  #Kindle    
    
    
    omg! zoho release  a series of open social gadgets http://bit.ly/4EJXL8    
    
    
    @BusinessContent not too up on what sobi can or cant do - the cck button allows you to insert custom data into J articles    
    
    
    @AmyStephen but action without ideas is directionless ;)    
    
    
    finished The Black Prism: Lightbringer: Book One by Brent Weeks and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/kOnrbr  #Kindle    
    
    
    finished The Heroes by Joe Abercrombie http://amzn.to/mvn1TS  #Kindle    
    
    
    test live site    
    
    
    has fixed a horrid bug in fabrik subscriptions    
    
    
    alice is home - yeah!    
    
    
    not connected to facebook    
    
    
    scratching his head    
    
    
    fb connect disabled in module    
    
    
    is currently ola    
    
    
    is currently heyo    
    
    
    @cozimek heheh none - its perfect as it is :) - now if more people could supply bundles of J and components that would be cool    
    
    
    #fabrik admin pagination of table data should be working now - how did i miss that one!    
    
    
    consulting my #joomla #iching about serious questions in life and love    
    
    
    new #fabrik plugin download available  create #Joomla users from your forms http://bit.ly/Npcho    
    
    
    in #fabrik you can now opt to copy elements when you copy groups    
    
    
    anyone know of a 'forge' like #Joomla component? (No need to host SVN just allow users to host mini projects)    
    
    
    @cozimek not 100% sure if it will load all tweets but you could check out my #joomla #twitter component  http://bit.ly/sBajR    
    
    
    #fabrik file upload element now can store and retrieve documents to Amazon s3 storage    
    
    
    looks like hugh added an ip address element plug-in to the #fabrik svn - go Hugh :)    
    
    
    testing bumptop - neat 3d desktop app!
http://twitpic.com/4j8vr    
    
    
    @cozimek pc desktop or real one? for the desktop bumptop is quiet fun - http://bumptop.com/    
    
    
    #fabrik passwod element plugin now committed to SVN - has strength checker code and stores in J1.5 password format    
    
    
    finally added commenting plug-in to #fabrik downloads section (subscribers only) http://bit.ly/7i7og    
    
    
    happy with the new http://fabrikar.com/blog/74-fabrik-304-released … fabrik3.0.4 release for Joomla 2.5    
    
    
    added new subscriber tutorial on #fabrik releated data feature http://bit.ly/14UQ4M    
    
    
    @AmyStephen opensocial the future just you won;'' know its there (but you'll be using it - gmail, hi5,myspace, ning etc.......)    
    
    
    please vote for new fabrik features @ http://fabrik.uservoice.com    
    
    
    @AmyStephen not a small undertaking I've been working on a container for a while (using shindig)   can send you some alpha code if you want    
    
    
    @AmyStephen ah they've improved that since i last looked at it - seems a pretty good idea for Tamka :)    
    
    
    fabrikar.com visitor stats 32000 unique visitors in April - up 107% from last year - thanks everyone! #fabrik #joomla    
    
    
    fabrik 2.0rc3 released -  http://bit.ly/207H5O    
    
    
    just got back from teaching badminton - too darn hot for it    
    
    
    pet hate - people who just write "hi rob" in skype then dont say anything more - write a full  sentence darn it!    
    
    
    @Dean_IconWeb ok i was asking for that - big time    
    
    
    Reading: "European Parliament Now Within Grasp of the Pirate Party" (http://twitthis.com/knttjd)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen for subs I used AEC, JFusion and Paypal. On the accounting I use sage and tradebox cash manager to download and records subs    
    
    
    @AmyStephen for subs its all about creating value around your product, be that support, videos, docs extra code etc    
    
    
    new #fabrik subscriber tutorial up - describes using linkage tables to create multi-multi relationships    
    
    
    I'm watching Cowboys & Aliens http://bit.ly/IHz5Pn  @GetGlue #CowboysAliens    
    
    
    I'm watching Immortals (10 others checked-in) http://bit.ly/IvbWAw  @GetGlue @immortalsfilm    
    
    
    Fabrik Tutorial - Creating Joomla Forms Documentation - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/introduction-to-fabrik/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    anyone know why #Joomla 1.5.20 with the #mootools upgrade plugin will allow class.extends({}) in firefox but not in IE?    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan - Hi Ian got an odd inconsistency with the new Mootools 1.2 compat layer in J1.5.20 -  http://bit.ly/9IBWzv    
    
    
    Fabrik and Custom Joomla User Registration Form - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/fabrik-user-registration-form/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    Fabrik: Create a Custom Joomla User List - OSTraining http://www.ostraining.com/blog/joomla/joomla-user-list/ … via @ostraining    
    
    
    CSS / JS Auto Refreshing with Live.js http://zite.to/M5T8vt  via @zite    
    
    
    Introducing boxbox http://zite.to/LzHWEH  via @zite    
    
    
    xbox 360 human interaction - wayyyy more advanced than the wii  http://bit.ly/fhaei    
    
    
    working on wedding playlist - think I'll just put Chemical Brothers on repeat for a couple of hours:)    
    
    
    think if i put on 4 hours of electro I might make my guest ears bleed a little too much    
    
    
    finished badminton coaching for the season, sad to see some of the students leaving the fold - sigh    
    
    
    @cozimek  probably not exactly what you were looking for, but the #fabrik upload element lets you store and retrieve content from amazon s3    
    
    
    I have more requests for quotes that a human can possibly handle - anyone competent with creating forms in #fabrik who wants  $$$    
    
    
    @cozimek it uses adaptor classes, currenlty theres one for the filesystem and one for amazon s3,   s3 code based on http://bit.ly/HFTo7    
    
    
    20 Must-Have Massive GUI kits http://zite.to/LArwdi  via @zite    
    
    
    finished The Forever War by Joe Haldeman and gave it 2 stars http://amzn.to/LYuatv  #Kindle    
    
    
    need to render #pdfs in #Joomla ? see my Joomla wiki article http://docs.joomla.org/How_to_create_PDF_views#Download_the_domPDF_library …    
    
    
    fixed 20ish #fabrik #joomla bugs this am - things are looking pretty solid - each fix required  1 or two lines of code changes to fix !    
    
    
    working on in-line table editing for #fabrik - got the ajax up for injecting elements in table cells :)    
    
    
    got to love #mootools inheritance model - eat that #jQuery!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen click table cell, load content, save update cell, each cell data type has js classes which inherit from various super classes    
    
    
    @AmyStephen looks limited no? and why use yet another js lib in Joomla when theres a mootools version already  http://tinyurl.com/krjoh7.    
    
    
    @AmyStephen have i missed something with the jQuery one then? i saw ordering and highlighting - thats all no? Both libs are not ok for me    
    
    
    Do Joomla! have a future? Sure! its just not written yet- everyone grab your pens!    
    
    
    @Tigratrus you make it sound like a trip to the toilet! lol    
    
    
    finished White Tiger: Dark Heavens Book One by Kylie Chan and gave it 2 stars  pretty average http://amzn.to/Nd7PZi  #Kindle    
    
    
    fabrik 2.0.1 released - this is security update so please everyone upgrade! http://bit.ly/9wWJcs    
    
    
    Shell car servicing site implemented in #fabrik #joomla by softforge http://carservicing.shell.co.uk/  sweet!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i'm working on a Kaltura series of plugins for #Joomla and #Fabrik - its a very cool service!    
    
    
    anyone looking to buy a 1bed flat in London - my sister is selling hers    
    
    
    I'm meeting the termite man in an hours time    
    
    
    @neriv glad you like fabrik cck? whats the +/'- of the two systems?    
    
    
    1.5 hours till i sign for my new house :o    
    
    
    at the back of your head
 http://amzn.com/k/1A9P1FK6Q5J2N #Kindle    
    
    
    just submitted a  #Joomla 1.6 patch with a MVC refractored newsfeed admin component  and shift click to select multiple items    
    
    
    neat cypherinfo added fabrik to wikipedia http://tinyurl.com/lhe24c    
    
    
    @jprobinso have a beer for me!    
    
    
    finished The Cold Commands (Gollancz S.F.) by Richard Morgan and gave it 4 stars http://amzn.to/sX0aTA  #Kindle    
    
    
    http://eepurl.com/oIRgT  - I'm really stoked to announce that Fabrik 3.0.6 is now out!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen lol yeah - 'everyone' wants to be like ME (j/k) :)    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/cHCSgpr7TSO0DiETWooF5A … #Kindle    
    
    
    new subscriber #fabrik tutorial for using mySQL views as database join data sources - sounds complex but isn't :) http://fabrikar.com/help/tutorials/details/3/30 …    
    
    
    Neat hack for limiting #fabrik dropdown options based on the current users access level http://fabrikar.com/forums/showthread.php?t=27633 …    
    
    
    2 displaced vertebra - undeniably rather painful!    
    
    
    working on Twtiter/oAuth integration for fabrik    
    
    
    Want yours? Click to get an invite to build your graphical bio on Vizify. https://www.vizify.com?code=199964&km_source=invite_twitter&km_generation=0&km_orig_source=invite_twitter&km_orig_person=FsUSRRMKZ509PMsFUS7LO8MBCgk=&km_prev_person=FsUSRRMKZ509PMsFUS7LO8MBCgk=vizify.com/?code=199964&k … via @vizify    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    Analysis of 20 Bootstrapped Startup Landing Pages http://zite.to/OsAVqo  via @zite    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    25 Beautiful Examples of Pricing Tables http://zite.to/SAq18d  via @zite    
    
    
    Joomla 2.5.7 Released http://shar.es/u5E73  via @sharethis - contains my humble patch for duplicate db sessions errors when using ajax    
    
    
    @roblocke wrong, they've banned non GPL extensions - commercial GPL extensions ARE listed    
    
    
    added a subscriber #fabrik plug-in to limit the number of form submissions a user can make. #joomla    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    #Joomla 1.5.12 updated tinymce to v3 the old v2 methods will no longer work! This effects #fabrik - please update  http://tinyurl.com/qduxwp    
    
    
    finished Cloud Atlas by David Mitchell and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/itg8Gw  #Kindle    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    over at #fabrik we have released the latest version of Fabrik for #Joomla 1.5: http://bit.ly/gPf4zQ    
    
    
    31 years old and i still hate using the phone, especially in french    
    
    
    Créer une application Web pour le CMS joomla avec le constructeur d'application Fabrik http://www.betterliving.be/qf     
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/guPW4gV9RLS4T8BKD1j4Fg … #Kindle    
    
    
    testing posting to individual accounts    
    
    
    Yeah #fabrik lists and forms now insert the menu items meta data and keywords, oh and you can use {placeholders} as well!    
    
    
    Just finished off adding some batch acl methods for #fabrik elements - saves you editing 100's of elements one by one!    
    
    
    @TessaFenwick glad you no longer have to wait :)    
    
    
    finished Best Served Cold by Joe Abercrombie and gave it 4 stars http://amzn.to/Anby94  #Kindle    
    
    
    anyone used http://www.joomlaads.com/ ? feedback as either a advertiser or publisher welcome    
    
    
    got my iphone - so what apps should I install?    
    
    
    anyone had experience with YQL?    
    
    
    slug dreams http://amzn.com/k/DLKQ0UK7Z7BA #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/kmxKK5HzTQivXOXEwAEOmQ … #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/ZQXmbhhiQKC1G8UpToInpQ … #Kindle    
    
    
    finished Red Country by Joe Abercrombie and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/R4Y5nA     
    
    
    dreaming http://amzn.com/k/EU3GUX7I5PAN #Kindle    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/mnirn4JJTDGLIr9miKjQjg … “It’s the questions we can’t answer that teach us the most. They teach us how to think.    
    
    
    @jeandrelennox why do you ask? I quoted something front.a.book I was.reading.tonight. Did you think that was not.me?    
    
    
    @bloqhead reduce fabrik js files: go to admin ->tables->params-> 'yes' for 'Merged JS files ' report the js error on the fabrik forum    
    
    
    Want to learn to write #Fabrik plug-ins and get paid for it? We need an eWay payment plugin - contact me #Joomla    
    
    
    finished Wise Man's Fear: The Kingkiller Chronicle: Day Two by Patrick Rothfuss and gave it 5 stars http://amzn.to/eGmwHb     
    
    
    great line http://amzn.com/k/HPZKMN1P10W5 #Kindle    
    
    
    Please help us translate fabrik @ https://www.transifex.com/projects/p/fabrik/ …    
    
    
    Twitter oAuth for MSGE    
    
    
    The tweature will rise    
    
    
    Sorry it seems my twitter account was hacked - and Ive been Direct messaging spam - please ingore them!    
    
    
    Built a neat database schema comparison tool into #fabrik today, lets you manage and deploy changes across two databases via Joomla's admin    
    
    
    @danielrwoodward post your questions in the forum and we will try to help :)    
    
    
    just added in option to publish/unpublish fabrik element validations    
    
    
    oh and options to (un)publish fabrik element javascript events    
    
    
    @sanderpotjer great work Sander!    
    
    
    Oh wow - Fabrik's made it into Joomla's top 10 Community Choice Extensions Winners! 
http://magazine.joomla.org/issues/issue-dec-2012/item/1011-community-choice-extensions-december-2012 …    
    
    
    added a new #fabrik tsubscriber utorial - how to build charts visualizations from your table data #joomla #jos    
    
    
    We have a new Alphauserpoints form plug-in for #fabrik #joomla. Award users points for submitting forms!http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Form_plugin_alphauserpoints …    
    
    
    Support MooTools FTW, add a #twibbon to your avatar now! - http://twibbon.com/join/MooTools-FTW    
    
    
    Sweet! You can now style Fabrik google map elements - see our wiki docs for how!
http://fabrikar.com/wiki/index.php/Google_map …    
    
    
    @danielrwoodward cool :) - we're getting close to a final #fabrik 2.0 release WOOT!    
    
    
    Tom just released a #youtube plugin for #fabrik  http://tinyurl.com/l2o3le - nice work Tom! #joomla    
    
    
    http://imgur.com/elR6msH  via @imgur    
    
    
    responsive #Fabrik list layouts in Joomla3 https://github.com/Fabrik/fabrik/commit/8fd580fa9df267d411a82cdd276e40cc20703765 …    
    
    
    Bootstrap for Extension Developers JWC 2012 on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/andytarr/bootstrap-for-extension-developers-jwc-2012 …    
    
    
    Creating Animations and Transitions With D3 http://shar.es/CIkt5  via @visually    
    
    
    time for lunch!    
    
    
    improved #fabrik update column plugin, users can now mass apply updates to multiple columns    
    
    
    testers please for update for my #joomla #bootstrap calendar http://joomlacode.org/gf/project/joomla/tracker/?action=TrackerItemEdit&tracker_item_id=30040 …    
    
    
    Joomla 3.1 Beta2 Released http://shar.es/eI2kU  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @Tigratrus cool! - I tend to hashtag anything to do with fabrik with #fabrik so you can set up a filter in tweetdeck for that !    
    
    
    new http://2.8hourslater.com/  2.8hourslater asylum site up ! Ready for further #zombie carnage    
    
    
    had a great weekend!    
    
    
    new #fabrik video coming soon - using the twitter form plugin    
    
    
    good morning all #fabrik users!    
    
    
    going to start reading 'merde actually'    
    
    
    try to go for a run    
    
    
    Today I'm me    
    
    
    Today I'm reworking fabrik 2.0.x redirect code    
    
    
    Today I'm nothing to see here    
    
    
    Today I'm on fire!    
    
    
    why is mulitsite work such a head mangler?    
    
    
    Adham Shaikh - great electro artist    
    
    
    fabrik site down for an upgrade, sorry its taking longer than expected!    
    
    
    checking out #evernote on the pc    
    
    
    Sorry for the long delay, but the new http://fabrikar.com   site should now be up and running. Let us know if you have suggestions/issues    
    
    
    approaching 24 hours in front of the pc. oh dear    
    
    
    @pete_fry like to see you sprint for 1km pete :)    
    
    
    @pete_fry So would i lol.Did a 10k fun run last month in 55 mins so thats what 5.5 min / km (gosh my maths rocks)    
    
    
    Just added the option to add polylines to #fabrik #googlemap #visualizations    
    
    
    Get your  free #fabrik form template - each group rendered in its own tab  http://tinyurl.com/muwb8s #joomla    
    
    
    I just uploaded "Fabrik 3.1 - details template desgin" to Vimeo: http://vimeo.com/65639868     
    
    
    I just added "Fabrik 3.1 - details template desgin" to Fabrik: http://vimeo.com/channels/38129/65639868 …    
    
    
    @AmyStephen i set my own define : define( "COM_FABRIK_LIVESITE",  str_replace('/administrator', '', JURI::base()) );    
    
    
    buffer looks pretty cool    
    
    
    I used Shazam to discover The Promise by The Cure #shazam    
    
    
    changed my first car battery - I  feel like a man ! (one with very little manual skills of course)    
    
    
    yeah! woop woop - mortgage docs came through - *should* mean I move on the 15th - at last!    
    
    
    man #lastfm sucks now i have to pay for streaming. Minus 1 point for living in france    
    
    
    MooTools Roundup - August 2009 http://bit.ly/2Sgp6v    
    
    
    Want a Fabrik conference? Please fill in our questionnaire http://fabrikar.com/component/fabrik/form/45/ …    
    
    
    @NorviceSpartan yes pay for a subscription to get it    
    
    
    I earned the I Am Number Four Coming Soon sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/iebHfb    
    
    
    I earned the Opening Week sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/dPvoTc    
    
    
    @manishc  fabrik tutorials - http://fabrikar.com/help/tutorials    
    
    
    igfest in Bristol this weekend   http://tinyurl.com/q34o8m - street games, mass social interaction,  play and adventure.    
    
    
    #moosehunt is ON! - #Joomla powered street game for #igfest  http://tinyurl.com/pbha2m #bristol    
    
    
    @eworldhost yes you can get fabrik to pull data from a db table and display it in the front end - the db doesnt have to be the J db either    
    
    
    2 hours - 3 cups off coffee and i have most of #fabrik running in #Joomla1.6 - just have to think about the ACL changes    
    
    
    going to Tours tomorrow - first day of Badminton N3! woot!    
    
    
    tom added an awesome fusion charts viz to #Fabrik grab it in the svn    
    
    
    added a custom fabrik filter to output PDF's of activities per town for http://vrijenwillig.nl/activiteitenzoeker# …    
    
    
    @eworldhost yes    
    
    
    updated my #joomla tag cloud module for 1.5 - download here -  http://tinyurl.com/phcxkd    
    
    
    #Ryanair just cancelled my christmas flights - didn't suggest an alternative even if there's one from Poitieres - freaking USELESS COMPANY!    
    
    
    @AmyStephen HAPPY BIRTHDAY :)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen hi Amy the Fabrik team is going to the J dev conf in New York, love to do the talk on mt1.2 - how can I contact the organizers    
    
    
    @ElinWaring hi Elin - I'd love to do the talk on mt1.2 @ the Joomla dev conf at new york let me know if you are intrested    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/ma76zx    
    
    
    intresting debate on whether experienced J core devs should be coding or mentoring others http://tinyurl.com/ma76zx    
    
    
    tip use JArrayHelper::getValue() to get data from an array in Joomla - avoids warnings if no key found in the array #joomla    
    
    
    #fabrik subscribers - get the new 'digg' voting element from the downloads section #joomla    
    
    
    flexible #javascript #mootools method to clone an object with options to clone or pass by reference http://tinyurl.com/m2s3jl    
    
    
    I earned the Movie Buff(100) sticker on @GetGlue! http://bit.ly/hExoqk    
    
    
    new #joomla #fabrik subscriber #tutorial : one to many relationships: create tables/forms to store parent/child data and relationships    
    
    
    woops! url for #joomla #fabrik #tutorial is http://tinyurl.com/yjfurs8    
    
    
    @ElinWaring  any chance you can let me know if you are considering my proposal to do a talk at New York #Joomla dev conf ?    
    
    
    working on a #balsamiq xml importer into #fabrik - design mockups and create working #Joomla fabrik applications    
    
    
    @balsamiq - thanks, so far so good the xml structure is clear didn't even need to read the docs! will post a video when I'm done!    
    
    
    #fabrik placeholders can now accept {$their->var->uservalue} which allows you to load in a user from $_REQUST[var] and access its properties    
    
    
    dont suppose anyone's got a #googlewave invite?    
    
    
    2009 sucks - long live 2010    
    
    
    added a #ambrasubs plugin "afterstore: update database col " - http://tinyurl.com/ydqacv3 #joomla    
    
    
    Teaser video for our new #balsamiq to #fabrik #Joomla component - rapid prototyping :: rapid deployment http://vimeo.com/20926663    
    
    
    Amen ! RT @LouisLandry: Those using php with the suhosin patch be wary of session/cookie encryption settings with Joomla especially with IE8    
    
    
    pet hate - people asking you to quote for a job but tell you they don't have a lot of money - 'oh ok! I'll charge you less then!' :D    
    
    
    gotta love Neal Asher! http://bit.ly/fR4If5 (via @GetGlue) #TheVoyageOfTheSableKeech    
    
    
    capable of twisting the seemingly ordinary into something the twisted side of abnormal - great! http://bit.ly/hycNZ5 (via @GetGlue)    
    
    
    @AmyStephen gosh yes well just been too darn busy :D got engaged, and doing lots of fun stuff!    
    
    
    FB open social graph allows you to give a fax number - anyone still use those? When will the last person using one realze?    
    
    
    @AmyStephen should be doing #jab11 need to sort myself out for it first!    
    
    
    testing out twitter in google wave - nice but twitter avatars dont show    
    
    
    anyone want a #googlewave invite?    
    
    
    sorry must be going mad - swore i saw an option to send invites for googlewave - but now i dont see it - very sorry to have wasted ppls time    
    
    
    @kproductivity lol thanks so i wasn't going mad then!    
    
    
    great weekend with my parents, inspirational people!!    
    
    
    fail: artiosef free doesn't play nicely with ajax calls  - inserts an advert in the returned json - boo!    
    
    
    So funny http://bit.ly/fcwMfs @GetGlue #LeDnerDeCons    
    
    
    #fabrik subscriptions up 5% this month - thank you to everyone that makes it possible    
    
    
    wooh google just offered to translate a web page for me ?    
    
    
    wishing #simongames good luck in their crazy caravan gps game #joomla #fabrik powered game for #sohotheatre    
    
    
    just booked my ticket to #joomla dev conference new york - woot!    
    
    
    @ElinWaring just booked my ticket for new york! looking forward to it    
    
    
    I am watching Dirty Dancing http://bit.ly/eH0Zif @GetGlue #DirtyDancing    
    
    
    I am watching Trainspotting http://bit.ly/eWDizy @GetGlue #Trainspotting    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan yup use mootools heavily !    
    
    
    @ian_maclennan  fabrik has a #mootools switch for 1.1/1.2- prefer 1.2 but its hard to get it to play nicely with other 3d party stuff    
    
    
    playing wth mootools ART and a Joomla 1.6 system plugin to switch ART styles based on active J template. Wish  understood mt depender better    
    
    
    @andrewmilks nice to see your web site quoting site up! http://tinyurl.com/yagp4b9    
    
    
    Yeah made it to the airport new York joomla Dev conf here I come    
    
    
    #jdc09 rooms filling up - coffees poured - lets bring it on    
    
    
    getting ready to leave to see the guys at#futuron, then its off to #jab11 - will have a #fabrik stand - looking forward to it!!    
    
    
    @cozimek thanks for the OSM talk - truely you ROCK Ryan - the honestly in the way you communicate is an example to us all!    
    
    
    #fabrik Financial Viability form  http://tinyurl.com/ye5cjvw by @kproductivity @kproductivity    
    
    
    waiting for alice    
    
    
    test from sameplaces    
    
    
    ripping all my old cds from when i was 15 - thewildheats still rock - yeah yeah i know its not cool but f**k it    
    
    
    can invite people to twine.com if intrested?    
    
    
    fabrik ajax form validations are now kinda working - horay for my ego!    
    
    
    got a bare bones triplify configuration file wotrking in Joomla    
    
    
    finally won a badminton team match = still going down though    
    
    
    wheres the frickin sun gone ?    
    
    
    @emargee chill man - listen to some biosphere :)    
    
    
    @emargee the leg thing could be quiet cool - http://snurl.com/23s4p - or theres alwasy lastminute.com    
    
    
    how cool - flash based font creator http://fontstruct.fontshop.com    
    
    
    fabrik 2 - slightly more valid xhtml output than this morning!    
    
    
    @emargee hey steve id be up for checking out evernote ;)    
    
    
    @emargee duh yeah - rob@pollen-8.co.uk    
    
    
    gr why is PHP4 still here    
    
    
    5 active fabrik 2.0 tickets left    
    
    
    OMG! just figured out how to use Joomla view caching for logged in users for fabrik - 5x speed improvement !    
    
    
    new inkscape out    
    
    
    new fabrik site template coming along nicely    
    
    
    @S_Shot way to go guys!    
    
    
    the devil is Always in the details - damn him    
    
    
    mhhuahh friendfeed now available in twirl - v cool    
    
    
    finally after 5 months go my glasses fixed - blimy hadnt realised how blind i was getting    
    
    
    yeah my wrist now longer hurts - could actually smash the shuttle yesterday - I'm still an unfit slacker  but at least that can be fixed    
    
    
    @emargee yeah blind and no hands! - ergonomic keyboard and chair on order!    
    
    
    @emargee  its when you start feeling the 'drafts' when all the doors are closed that you have to really start worrying :O    
    
    
    ahhh at last the delicious addon for firefox 3    
    
    
    @emargee as you seem to love twitter the most out of my friends -- http://snurl.com/29qy9    
    
    
    new version of the #balsamiq to #fabrik component bug fixes plus allows you to create forms/tables by pasting in xmlhttp://bit.ly/jzZUbb    
    
    
    I love the evoluent mouse - their keyboard has a great idea to put the number pad on the left .. http://bit.ly/lYRH2b    
    
    
    just saw #futurons #fabrik designs for #podion - omg its going to be awesom!    
    
    
    Vizualize.Me is launching soon and I'm one of the first in line! Join me. #launch http://vizualize.me/30yb9  via @vizualizeme    
    
    
    just finish Fabrik presentation to JoomlaDay South Africa - great fun - shame about skype calls cutting out though!    
    
    
    trying out zenbe email with twitter integration    
    
    
    reducing queries - 200% gain. Now to reduce memory - banging head on wall will provide acceptable results    
    
    
    struggling with crappy xp machines networking    
    
    
    new card new cable - no go    
    
    
    going to bed - 23:30 and still 28  degrees    
    
    
    just realised that commuting sucks - hey just as well i work from home :)    
    
    
    releasing Fabrik 1.0.6....    
    
    
    hey everyone please help my lovely friend Marine by filling in her "tourism on the net" questionnaire http://tinyurl.com/y9jbbt9    
    
    
    just added #coverflow and #ganttchart  visualizations to the #fabrik svn (#joomla) More great ways to show your #fabrik data!    
    
    
    Hannes is asking for help with patches for Joomla1.6 http://tinyurl.com/yzwlgys - I've just done two, can you beat me? :)    
    
    
    woot some ones actually gone to the trouble of pirating my fabrik tutorials - thanks a lot I'm flattered!    
    
    
    buisness cards - check, flyers - check - We good to go!    
    
    
    grrr French printers - you'd think 5 days notice would be enough to get some crummy business cards printed! - But.. found one in the end    
    
    
    coded a nice html5 video annotation mootols/joomla content plugin working    
    
    
    @testthetweeture 123456    
    
    
    @testthetweeture  abc    
    
    
    @testthetweeture  tes6 from rob    
    
    
    