Thinking that @dojotoolkit may find my dojo box and whisker plot interesting http://tinyurl.com/box-and-whisker    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/mscg - IMG00011.jpg    
    
    
    @brynn Hotwire for cars has been good to me. May not be good if your plans could change. If so, read fine print.    
    
    
    @peter_c_william @peteskomoroch Padrons are also great cigars.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang your just published tweets seem broken    
    
    
    @dtunkelang or perhaps the tweets are predicting the future ;-) ?    
    
    
    Thinking I may be able to adapt the committee perceptron to learn mixture model weights for search http://tinyurl.com/comittee-perceptron    
    
    
    Cold day for the bike ride in with a wind chill of 17.  Time to find the weak points in my cold weather gear.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/pmut - bike_outfit.jpg    
    
    
    Verdict: my toes were slightly cold and I would wear a slightly heavier windbreaker next time it is this cold.    
    
    
    Having a really slow start today for no good reason    
    
    
    I'm not convinced that the idea articles are not out there, but they certainly are dwarfed by other narratives. http://lnkd.in/uVvHk2     
    
    
    40 degrees makes for a nice ride in.  I'm expecting rain on the ride home.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/rrt9 - IMG00018.jpg    
    
    
    Hoping I'd be lucky enough to drink some of @ben_vandurme 's beer.    
    
    
    Want: http://tinyurl.com/kilott-wt5 (notice the Sturmey-Archer 5 speed hub)    
    
    
    Doing 4 WWW reviews this evening    
    
    
    @leejb one day to determine success or failure is cheap!    
    
    
    +1: false discovery rate, practical significance, and proper interpretation of p-values. -100: "Bayes Watch" pun. http://bit.ly/bRg0pW    
    
    
    MASH reminds me of Catch-22    
    
    
    Not knowing where my tire lever is makes it hard to change from my winter cross tires back to road slicks.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/zgb1 - dinner.jpg    
    
    
    putting off figuring out how to transform an Indri query network into its "gradient network" with respect to a parameter    
    
    
    Disappointed that Search Engines: Information Retrieval in Practice's covers sig tests but doesn't address multiple testing issues    
    
    
    @ben_vandurme wait, what?    
    
    
    Wishing @barsmart had an API so we could do a bar crawl mashup.    
    
    
    iRobot was nice enough to ship me a new battery because I killed it following their instructions.    
    
    
    @briancavalier have you tried construction junction?    
    
    
    @ej I've drawn a number of diagrams for my dissertation in Inkscape.  I generally like it, but have found the connectors to be a bit buggy.    
    
    
    Pittsburgh is gridlocked    
    
    
    @edibaise sort of.  I feel "nonbelievers" is very us vs. them.  Also, atheists very clearly have beliefs.    
    
    
    following @ealdent not just because his posts are of academic interest, but also that, like me, he posts pictures of beer.    
    
    
    I do not like bidding on papers to review.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/16eno - ten fidy    
    
    
    Debugging committee perceptron code for learning Indri mixture model parameters.    
    
    
    Digging tramp ( http://www.gnu.org/software/tramp/ ) for editing remote files.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Pittsburgh certainly inspires adopted hometown pride for me and a number of my friends in CMU and also some who have moved.    
    
    
    Done fighting with antlr for the evening.  Looking forward to more tomorrow.    
    
    
    As much as I hate bidding on papers to review, it seemed to work well for me with SIGIR.  Not bidding on WWW papers resulted in misery.    
    
    
    First success at gradient based optimization for mixture model parameters for known-item finding. Yes, it's maximizing mean-reciprocal rank.    
    
    
    Defogging at Big Dog Coffee    
    
    
    Sweet. Committee perceptron training on preference pairs confirmed to learn excellent parameters for held-out test set.    
    
    
    @brynn Despite official proclaimation, I doubt it will be PG.    
    
    
    @abdur ouch! glad everyone is okay.    
    
    
    My Amazon EC2 image reads user data on creation to run a batch of experiments, uploads the results to my server, then terminates itself. #in    
    
    
    Got a delinquent notice on a bill for $0.00.  Apparently American Education Services thinks I didn't pay nothing on time.    
    
    
    @jaykreps I'm in Santa Rosa    
    
    
    To breakfast, then to work at Big Dog Coffee.    
    
    
    @flurie we should meet over beer again to talk about close reading.    
    
    
    emacs will never die. Evidence: http://tinyurl.com/twit-el    
    
    
    The shredder I bought from Costco was so cheap because their contract with Fellowes explicitly excluded replacement parts.    
    
    
    @jelsas Yes, Costco's return policy is excellent, but doesn't cover my 2 year old device (not saying it should, just saying)    
    
    
    Lanbo Zhang: facet feedback for personalization indicates sufficiency or necessity, loss fn should handle separately #issdm    
    
    
    @nyyrajvggranhre @jaykreps magic of unstructured data can be  volume, but often must fight hard adding structure to use it effectively    
    
    
    @jaykreps Agree completely    
    
    
    @communicating Sutton & McCallum's CRF tutorial assumes some ML and stats knowledge, but is quite good http://tinyurl.com/afkq5m    
    
    
    @jelsas sounds like a great way to reduce review overload ;-)    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1zndl - Rogue Hazelnut Brown Nectar    
    
    
    http://www.csusummerarts.org/maf/index.shtml  so proud of my wife Christine and her award winning screenplay!    
    
    
    @Heewa @seancolombo Fred Flintstone might tell you a fixed gear car would be rough on your knees in San Francisco.    
    
    
    I have a feeling it is going to be hard to stay focused the rest of this week.    
    
    
    At Big Dog Coffee, writing about inverted indexes to support fast element parent/child query constraints.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson @briancavalier it's Chris' birthday too! Happy birthday b-funk!    
    
    
    Seems like every bus but the one I need has gone by twice.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff You need a client that supports the all of the Unicode characters http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chess_symbols_in_Unicode    
    
    
    @seancolombo Alas no, it's cut and paste all the way.    
    
    
    Just delivered a draft of my dissertation to my committee, working on scheduling my defense. #in    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries http://short.to/2ic8p but perhaps more boxes are search boxes than you thought?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries I make no claims about the result quality of @pogil search    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/2z8fq - IMG00047.jpg    
    
    
    @communicating That was my birthday swag.  Thanks!    
    
    
    @communicating wonder how it compares to ASSERT http://cemantix.org/assert.html (I used ASSERT for some diss. exps) nice to see alternatives    
    
    
    Long.bitCount(a^b) is a fast way to compute the Hamming distance of two binary strings. Challenge: pack as much into 64 bits as possible.    
    
    
    http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/138976/FPRF.pdf … and http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/120078/wfc0398-liPS.pdf … suggest one bit per hash function is enough in LSH. Are 64 hash functions enough?    
    
    
    Spectral hashing looks strong, but I won't build an affinity mx for millions of docs and run PCA. How big a sample is needed to beat LSH?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff yeah there are some  optimizations, but it's a bit amusing that the authors propose I do exactly what I hoped to avoid    
    
    
    @houndish pics or it didn't happen    
    
    
    @communicating @leejb curation can have value. Do influential humans following a (virtual) bot/retweeter indicate value?    
    
    
    @houndish glad things are safe again    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries the title and one sentence description is about all she's tools me, so I'm curious too. It's a romantic comedy    
    
    
    Downgrading to basic cable. Upgrading to netflix.    
    
    
    We're looking for interns on the recommendations engine team at LinkedIn. Let me know if you are interested!    
    
    
    Am I ready for my thesis defense tomorrow? Almost.    
    
    
    I held onto this bottle of wine since SIGIR 03 to celebrate my successful defense.  http://twitgoo.com/1466te    
    
    
    It takes around 1300 distinct email senders to make the top 3 most emailed articles of the day on the New York Times http://lnkd.in/eiMST8    
    
    
    @communicating Query language should be simple but unambiguous.  Could HOW MANY be valid query terms?  Might quotes be misleading (phrases)?    
    
    
    @communicating If possible, use the patterns from query languages that your users might know.    
    
    
    Interesting take on how tracking cookies benefit smaller publishers.  I just wonder how many people would actually opt…http://lnkd.in/aKzvAU    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ ML and IR grad students nearing graduation. If you're interested, send me your resume. We still have some open positions.    
    
    
    #lazyweb What's a typical value for Cohen's Kappa for relevance judgments?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Naturally :-) At what point do you typically consider revising the task or instructions (for the next year)?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @ian_soboroff My tweet was intentionally bait for Ian :-). I left it general to see if I get other responses.    
    
    
    @jonathankoren congratulations!    
    
    
    @JackGConrad and on a micro level, bike commuting saves me hundreds of dollars a year in gas and car maintenance, keeps me happy and healthy    
    
    
    Wikipedia is a social network. New mediawiki feature development makes this very clear http://www.mediawiki.org/wiki/Echo_(Notifications) …    
    
    
    @ej congratulations!    
    
    
    @ram Thanks!    
    
    
    Happy I can now update my profile http://techcrunch.com/2010/08/04/linkedin-mspoke/ #in    
    
    
    @andy_c did you bike up beechwood, or go some other route?    
    
    
    @andy_c Plenty of uphill on the way back, too. s/beacon/bartlett/;s/forbes/northumberland/ might have less traffic and be a bit shorter    
    
    
    Yes, Finds Pew Study, People Will (and Do) Pay For Digital Content http://lnkd.in/WPKJEs    
    
    
    @brendan642 Thanks! I'm pretty excited. Probably won't be working with @peteskomoroch right away, but could see it happening in the future.    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati awesome! Hope the ride went well    
    
    
    @strlen looks like a fun ride, but it's missing a rear rack for panniers ;-)    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/794f3 - No hope for Detroit    
    
    
    @peteskomoroch @mdreid @noahkagan invert the y axis    
    
    
    @CA_DMV what does the "system down statewide" sign at Santa Clara mean? I need to transfer my registration and license to CA.  can I?    
    
    
    expecting a long wait @CA_DMV despite arriving 30 mind before it opened. Miffed they put me back in the line after getting my car checked    
    
    
    Managed to survive the ca dmv. Worst dmv I've been to. Even pa, which also can't pass a budget, can manage to get you done in an hour    
    
    
    Using regularization to provide a prior.  Hoping it will reduce my parameter estimation woes.    
    
    
    @_mathur Sorry you didn't get a chance to ask your question regarding security. http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/06/09/an-update-on-taking-steps-to-protect-our-members/ … may answer your questions    
    
    
    Current status:  http://plixi.com/p/43495582    
    
    
    Decided not to sleep in the office but bike home instead. Gin and tonic, 4 Chimay, Mac and cheese demand it.    
    
    
    6 rabbits and 1 black cat.  What does it mean if a black turns and runs when it sees you coming?    
    
    
    3 days later. To the naysayers who felt standing in a creek for 30 minutes drinking beer wouldn't wash off the poison ivy: you were wrong.    
    
    
    Current status  http://plixi.com/p/44596402    
    
    
    @JtotheC tonic is probably the best place to have a beer and watch #anthrocon    
    
    
    I'll have good company in Moscow! RT @ecir2013: We're excited to announce another confirmed Industry Day speaker - Hilary Mason (@hmason)    
    
    
    OkCupid: an average rating isn't always a sufficient summary of a distribution for prediction http://lnkd.in/eF24wt    
    
    
    Apparently, it's national drink beer day! http://eatocracy.cnn.com/2012/09/28/national-drink-beer-day/ … Thanks, @prismatic! Intersected with election season: http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/09/in-which-i-reconsider-my-entire-political-outlook/262981/ …    
    
    
    @briancavalier on minimum viable product: just a feeling, but seems like viable is starting to mean bland. I think it should mean awesome    
    
    
    @IanPaterson This tweet clued me in that SnapRetail moved its offices. The strip district is a better place for a startup than Monroeville.    
    
    
    @briancavalier @JohnCampbellJr @IanPaterson LinkedIn blocks commits that don't compile and reverts your commit if the unit tests fail. CRAZY    
    
    
    @sharathrao Just glad I could finish and enjoy it before it turned into vinegar!    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Despite working in the guts of the payload structures, I never realized Index had real time indexing support!    
    
    
    Indri had "real time" support in 2004, earlier than Zoie or Solr. Shame we didn't make a bigger deal of it. @dmetzlerd @trevor_strohman    
    
    
    @pogil @CharlotteHase or I more likely, I had never payed much attention to its importance at the time    
    
    
    @Careerimp's resunate helps you adapt your resume from LinkedIn to a job -  http://careerimp.com/resunate/ #in /via @eengler #alphalab    
    
    
    @communicating analyzed    
    
    
    @IanPaterson ha! Perhaps you just hate yourself for living in the past?    
    
    
    @seanjtaylor @gappy3000 you get more miles out of a car if you understand how it works, but many are good drivers without that knowledge    
    
    
    Looking for company knowledge bases with descriptions & aliases. Must be more comprehensive than Wikipedia+Freebase. Need not be free.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @lintool now out of that context, I realize now that did not come across well our as I meant    
    
    
    @leifos @lintool makes a great point often overlooked. Powering and cooling data centers is expensive. Efficiency is a big deal.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @leifos @ecir2013 yes - Filip Radlinkski and Katja Hofmann's work is very related. I've enjoyed comparing notes with them    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @leifos @ecir2013 None yet, but we are building on work from Yahoo! http://arxiv.org/abs/1003.5956     
    
    
    Goodbye world, hello Paul!    
    
    
    @briancavalier @pbrumblay @bostonaholic so 5/08 would be like groundhog day, right? But that's in February. This is hurting my head    
    
    
    #ecir2013 keynotes by Diane Kelly & @informor, industry talks by @lintool @marc_najork @karenchurch me and others at http://events.yandex.ru/events/ecir2013     
    
    
    "@CheapEatsChick: Espresso! http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/05/09/espresso-chart_n_3247215.html?utm_hp_ref=@food123 …" I normally just have an espresso, but the affogato looks good to me.    
    
    
    Want to work with me to build compelling news products? Let me know http://lnkd.in/gWrK3G    
    
    
    "@vitroc Universities by Return of Invstmnt http://lnkd.in/pwk8TU  
" would these look different adjusted for cost of living where grads go?    
    
    
    Curse you Frasier Crane! I had not seen the Orient Express    
    
    
    @mancrates Hoppy hopstatic    
    
    
    @seancolombo or for if you freeze it    
    
    
    @adilaijaz that trick only works with non-final classes. Does that shake you to your core?    
    
    
    So apparently Excel doesn't like SUMIF if you have around 370,000 rows.    
    
    
    Just set up http://roksbox.com/ on my Roku to play mp3 files from my desktop. Nice! All I had to do was run a web server on my desktop...    
    
    
    Arrived in Denver. Looking forward to interam    
    
    
    @andy_c and then you ponder about sampling the world?    
    
    
    @andy_c doesn't stripping and sanding come first? Or is a new railing?    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell cross country would be more fun to watch if spectators could add obstacles to the course before the race.    
    
    
    Redis at Disqus | Brett Hoerner's blog http://lnkd.in/4TbEmW    
    
    
    @ladygaga You've got nothing to do with your birth, but being on the right track implies you've got something to do with it. I'm confused.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/hznfu - Sunset steak and beer    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/i5rg0 - People are turning Pittsburgh's parking spaces into parks    
    
    
    Just discovered horror and glory of Google Play Music. When did I give permission for albums I ripped? Reminders of http://Mp3.com     
    
    
    @pogil discovered this after an accidental click on the app on my android. Music not on phone, but on desktop...    
    
    
    I work with the guys on this team! Post by @adilaijaz: The Engineering behind LinkedIn Products “You May Like” http://bit.ly/fvdoNt #in    
    
    
    Left work a little early to get out of downtown.  To me, Pittsburgh felt more like a ghost town than a "police state" #g20    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/ivpoo - Weyerbacher imperial pumpkin ale    
    
    
    @JtotheC I bought a bag of the riceworks sweet chili chips a couple weeks ago. The bag barely lasted 24 hours.    
    
    
    #g20 downtown parking garages are closed.  Recommend parking legally on a side street in a neighborhood and busing downtown.    
    
    
    #g20 Parking: pay attention to street signs. Many neighborhoods have daytime restrictions. Each street that is restricted will have signs.    
    
    
    #g20 Public transit: http://www.portauthority.org    
    
    
    Disappointed more of @GATOR_313 's music isn't like change gonna come.    
    
    
    @brynn it can be hard to say no to those requesting reviews but doing it from time to time has greatly improved the quality of my life.    
    
    
    trying to understand how we get the right stuff into the db    
    
    
    cutting down on office expletives (moving on to a different task)    
    
    
    This is what I've been working on! LinkedIn Today Is Live: A Walkthrough http://tcrn.ch/gecPxZ  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @jelsas @dtunkelang The Onion comes at source #39 for  http://www.linkedin.com/today/higher_education    
    
    
    @jelsas @dtunkelang If you're lucky, you might catch one of their articles in the "Novel & Newsworthy" section of that page.    
    
    
    Twittering from my blackberry! And reading a friends dissertation to make sure I represent his work well    
    
    
    You'd think the fatty mcdonalds I ate at 2 would have lasted longer    
    
    
    Sounds like @andy_c needs some coffee    
    
    
    The 46 page single-spaced beast of a related work chapter is now Jamie's problem.    
    
    
    You'd think it is finals week or something.  The first two coffee shops I tried had no tables.  Curse you students!    
    
    
    putting the love-seat in the make-out room    
    
    
    @zach I haven't had a problem with the TOCs in Preview.  Do you want my preamble for comparison?    
    
    
    @zach http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~pto/Preamble.tex and http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~pto/Titlepage.tex    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell since IBM believes that services are the way to make money, they didn't like innovation that couldn't be sold as a service    
    
    
    disappointed that the steelers got back into the game, only to have their defense blow it.    
    
    
    Trying to find time for Dean and Einar between little bugs from QDAP.    
    
    
    Shopping    
    
    
    I've got to work on my timing. Thought I was running behind, but I still had to wait a few minutes at the gate.    
    
    
    LinkedIn Today coffee truck! http://plixi.com/p/88111952    
    
    
    Twice checking bags for a tool. 1st-hold still while I pinch you with this vice. 2nd-wait an hour while I sharpen this with my honing plane.    
    
    
    This is why I don't like checking luggage.    
    
    
    Impulse! Costco had wiis.    
    
    
    @mdreid my favorite: instant friend, just add beer    
    
    
    http://xkcd.com/882/ I wonder whether the scientists corrected for multiple testing #in    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati nice! cyclocross bikes rock!    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati Information retrieval's view circa 2003: http://tinyurl.com/2cmrdn    
    
    
    Makes me happy: RT @Sharp_Edge Great beer news for Pittsburgh! http://short.to/y56f    
    
    
    Just reread my thesis proposal.  Most of the goals remain the same, but the model/hypotheses/experiments have changed a lot since then!    
    
    
    Missing my beloved wireless at crazy mocha. Why do you fail? WHY?    
    
    
    The unexpected bonus 140GB on my new @westerndigital hard drive is more than 3x the size of my old drive all on its own.    
    
    
    @ianpaterson you can not has jameson. You has beam    
    
    
    @amazonaws where's my low-CPU high-memory ec2 instance?  Say, a large instance with 15GB?  #AWS    
    
    
    @communicating quality is very context sensitive, but basically yes    
    
    
    @briancavalier so is wire.js like spring for JavaScript?    
    
    
    @ealdent thank you!    
    
    
    Excited that elvis costello and the imposters open for the police show.    
    
    
    I've recently been thinking a lot about how to make pervasive split testing easy.  http://tinyurl.com/split-tests-pt1    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell but how long has it been there?    
    
    
    @javasoze Sensei demo was really easy to run, but how do I shut down a sensei node?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I've recently been getting invites for web meetings promising to [get rich quick scheme].  Seems like clever spam/scam to me.    
    
    
    http://www.botanicalls.com/twitter/    
    
    
    Relishing that I now have minions.    
    
    
    Enjoying my new neighborhood bar    
    
    
    @zach Did you do any speed tests on the stanford NER when you played with it?    
    
    
    Glad I don't work in an office of touchy feely drama people    
    
    
    Debugging custom c++ network messages not written by me = nightmare    
    
    
    taking my fixie to my "office" on the south side    
    
    
    I desire a longer brake lever.    
    
    
    @sammirati a good friend of mine is renting space at http://www.officenomads.com/ in Seattle    
    
    
    Ian FTW    
    
    
    @houndish I love my cyclocross. They're very versatile bikes    
    
    
    @houndish In 06 I got a Cannondale cyclocross disc. They doesn't make a cross with disc brakes anymore, but I love the bike    
    
    
    @houndish If you don't like the ride, there are a also lot of aggressive street bikes with flat bars that take fat tires /cc @briancavalier    
    
    
    @houndish for example: http://www.bikesdirect.com/products/motobecane/cafe_century_pro_xi.htm /cc @briancavalier    
    
    
    The diner coffee is actually decent when it is a fresh pot!    
    
    
    Heading to Hough's for dinner, beer, and pencil and paper statistics.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson happy birthday! I'll buy you a beer on saturday    
    
    
    People watching in Market Square.    
    
    
    @communicating business or pleasure? You could easily spend days talking to ppl in Pittsburgh if you take a broad definition of surrounding    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell you can has waaa...    
    
    
    @andy_c perhaps they are so poorly baked nobody wants to eat them    
    
    
    @Ian for the bump.    
    
    
    Reading how google news handles scale - http://www2007.org/paper570.php    
    
    
    Go ahead and jump!    
    
    
    I found the simple life ain't so simple.    
    
    
    Everybody wants some. Baby, how bout you?    
    
    
    I'll wait till your love comes down.    
    
    
    The cradle will rock:    
    
    
    Hot for teacher    
    
    
    @houndish Panama    
    
    
    @houndish you got the order wrong!    
    
    
    Getting Mariokart. Woot!    
    
    
    They just put a recliner on the fire.    
    
    
    Finally making it in to work after a detour to the Strip District to get my dad a birthday gift.    
    
    
    Waiting for the game to start    
    
    
    @jelsas beer? where?    
    
    
    @mdreid reminds me of the somewhat uncommon wisdom i first heard from my father "sometimes the best thing to say is nothing at all"    
    
    
    @mdreid along with "not every battle is worth fighting "    
    
    
    Texted result of Manchester v. Chelsea to @JohnnyCampbell.  Not exactly sure why.    
    
    
    Heading out to lay trail.    
    
    
    Realizing the benefits of keypad locks on my phone.    
    
    
    Back third of trail marked...    
    
    
    Out of flour with half a mile left to mark. Will finish tomorrow    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell mmm soysage    
    
    
    Pbj and box wine on my balcony.  Now that's what I call living.    
    
    
    After listening to http://is.gd/AvJ at Best Buy, I just had to order one.  The sound sparkled with my Grado SR80s.    
    
    
    It always amazes me how many fewer statistically significant differences we can detect after correcting for multiple testing.    
    
    
    That thing that you think is different? We can't be sure. Check back a few years from now we have better methods for mult. test correction.    
    
    
    @pghh3 it's only bc bad others still think there's a difference when we really can't tell. You'd think "scientists" would know better...    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell sorry I couldn't join you - was stuck in the office until 30 minutes ago.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson I'm pretty sure we should give @JohnnyCampbell 30 days or so to claim it.  Like lost-and-found boxes.    
    
    
    @edibiase Did you find the Vivo Barefoot shoes locally, or did you order them off of the internet?    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell you will have the option to create a real life Battlefield:Furries if you join us at Tonic tomorrow.    
    
    
    chop chop chopping the related work chapter down to less than 30 pages.    
    
    
    Today was simply wonderful    
    
    
    Amused that the only people who have bothered to port MINPACK to Java and release it is the US Forest Service.    
    
    
    feeling deflated    
    
    
    @briancavalier glad you enjoyed the dub chocolate.  It's one of my favorite stouts.    
    
    
    @zach Welcome to the world of text!    
    
    
    Thinking http://is.gd/RwP might be an interesting read.  Found via http://is.gd/RwS    
    
    
    Sitting in traffic    
    
    
    Landed in Pittsburgh.    
    
    
    Back at the dealer so they can put the tire on right this time.    
    
    
    @seancolombo you should check out http://short.to/1646z - they also include the code used to make the graphs    
    
    
    @briancavalier you may also like http://jott.com    
    
    
    I think lots of queries kill Cuil.  They claim to have a lot of pages, but return nothing for many queries they should.    
    
    
    Must be missed something about how Cuil works.  Would have been nice for them to let me know that there might be results for me Q later...    
    
    
    Wondering where Ian went.    
    
    
    @bmevans youtube, myspace, facebook, blogger. Measured by Alexa's top sites http://is.gd/18eq    
    
    
    Power went out.    
    
    
    Just saw a possum. Now watching the bats.    
    
    
    @edibiase are you doing the minor in lang. tech?  I see a couple of LTI courses in there...    
    
    
    @bmevans If your trip back East includes Pittsburgh, you should swing by mSpoke!    
    
    
    Congratulating Dr. Mahady    
    
    
    Walking to Hough's for lunch and some work to prevent onset of cabin fever #snowmageddon    
    
    
    Southside works is amazingly empty despite (because of?) the music festival.    
    
    
    After dropping a rental game off, I was stuck behind the bus I wanted.    
    
    
    @briancavalier hope you finished your chores - I'm thinking about riding my bike to the trail tonight it is so nice out    
    
    
    #roku + #pandora + @SlavicSoulParty = #nowplaying    
    
    
    Looking forward to Fallout 3. http://is.gd/1PBd    
    
    
    Jamie Callan (my advisor) now has the first complete draft of my dissertation.    
    
    
    @briancavalier hope you enjoy the work at @snapretail! It sounds like you'll be working on an interesting and challenging project.    
    
    
    @edibiase I always had the "what are all these people doing here" reaction when the semester started.    
    
    
    Love how the bread is "singing" as it cools http://twitpic.com/5ntxf8     
    
    
    @communicating isn't it always sobering how messy the real world (data) can be? Academics often take cleaned datasets for granted    
    
    
    The salad for lunch and amy's TV dinner has left me feeling calorie deprived. After checking the box, I found the dinner had only 260 cals!    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell this geek is only making it to crazy mocha now...    
    
    
    @IanPaterson also drinking coffee, but in South Side.   Weekend of coffee tweets?    
    
    
    @jelsas You got it! The book and dutch oven were a very thoughtful wedding gift from @lmariaschneider and @deansher    
    
    
    @bmevans what's a pirate's favorite statistical analysis program? But seriously, I do almost all of my data analysis in R.    
    
    
    Biking to south side for grins    
    
    
    trip delayed: thought light battery was charged, turned out not true    
    
    
    Mmm vanilla porter    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Is a TREC 2009 Blog Track overview available yet?    
    
    
    @briancavalier found at Rivertowne Pour House in Monroeville.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Was it taboo to use link count to the day's articles in the top stories task, or were there too few links to be useful?    
    
    
    @banksimple A bank with an API sounds cool and innovative, but does a myriad of apps gel with simple? Sounds like 'bankgeek.'    
    
    
    @banksimple Transparency rocks, but I'm having trouble finding an example where an API would be better than a clear TOS and UI. Help me pls?    
    
    
    @banksimple Okay, I think I get it now. For example, I could build an app that tracks and displays changes to the terms/conditions over time    
    
    
    @shamir_k @banksimple Thanks for the examples and clarifications - they were very helpful!    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Thanks! I missed U of Iowa's paper on my first pass through the proceedings.    
    
    
    My neighborhood bar Hough's now has 70 beers.    
    
    
    @seancolombo @deansher perhaps the goal should be the "Sean Colombo" or "Dean Thompson" everyone thinks of when your name is mentioned.    
    
    
    @bcavalier southern tier imperial pumking: mellow with rich tones of pumpkin and spice. Very warm and nutty.    
    
    
    Done laying trail in much less time than expected. Cool weather makes a big difference.    
    
    
    Awesome ad: http://www.youtube.com/experiencewii    
    
    
    hanging art between plays    
    
    
    Glad I have a month for ECIR reviews    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald thanks for the link. What would happen if you use linking documents as basis for expansion, rather than Wikipedia?    
    
    
    @edibiase how are you liking your vivo barefoot shoes?    
    
    
    @edibiase so that's a positive statement of comfort?    
    
    
    Resisting the pressure of the Leinenkugel beer reps at Hough's.  Choosing Great Lakes' Edmund Fitzgerald porter instead.    
    
    
    Wondering whether @ej still checks his ir.iit.edu email address.    
    
    
    @ej strange.  I'll resend.    
    
    
    Feeling enlighted about how people vote: http://www.kansas.com/205/story/565669.html    
    
    
    Feeling cabin feever after two days at home    
    
    
    @abdur I'm with you on no Facebook apps.  They always feel very invasive, are a hassle to set up, and they like to spam my friends.    
    
    
    Enjoyed discussing tagging, taxonomies, attention, and filtering over lunch with @danielabarbosa.    
    
    
    @ryanqnorth I'm too lazy to build an n-gram lang model of T-Rex's speech from http://tinyurl.com/qwantz-transcripts #qwantzle    
    
    
    @ryanqnorth #qwantzle = qwantz puzzle, because this totally needs its own hashtag.    
    
    
    @danielabarbosa I agree. Tweets demand attention.  It is our choice who receives our attention.    
    
    
    @danielabarbosa Not following does not imply a lack of interest, but rather a preference for a different mode of providing attention.    
    
    
    Digging stephanierooker.com at ava    
    
    
    Working on a journal paper on work done at the Reliable Information Access Workshop http://bit.ly/ria - seems like so long ago...    
    
    
    Thinking that @dojotoolkit may find my dojo box and whisker plot interesting http://tinyurl.com/box-and-whisker    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/mscg - IMG00011.jpg    
    
    
    @brynn Hotwire for cars has been good to me. May not be good if your plans could change. If so, read fine print.    
    
    
    @peter_c_william @peteskomoroch Padrons are also great cigars.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang your just published tweets seem broken    
    
    
    @dtunkelang or perhaps the tweets are predicting the future ;-) ?    
    
    
    Thinking I may be able to adapt the committee perceptron to learn mixture model weights for search http://tinyurl.com/comittee-perceptron    
    
    
    Cold day for the bike ride in with a wind chill of 17.  Time to find the weak points in my cold weather gear.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/pmut - bike_outfit.jpg    
    
    
    Verdict: my toes were slightly cold and I would wear a slightly heavier windbreaker next time it is this cold.    
    
    
    Having a really slow start today for no good reason    
    
    
    I'm not convinced that the idea articles are not out there, but they certainly are dwarfed by other narratives. http://lnkd.in/uVvHk2     
    
    
    40 degrees makes for a nice ride in.  I'm expecting rain on the ride home.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/rrt9 - IMG00018.jpg    
    
    
    Hoping I'd be lucky enough to drink some of @ben_vandurme 's beer.    
    
    
    Want: http://tinyurl.com/kilott-wt5 (notice the Sturmey-Archer 5 speed hub)    
    
    
    Doing 4 WWW reviews this evening    
    
    
    @leejb one day to determine success or failure is cheap!    
    
    
    +1: false discovery rate, practical significance, and proper interpretation of p-values. -100: "Bayes Watch" pun. http://bit.ly/bRg0pW    
    
    
    MASH reminds me of Catch-22    
    
    
    Not knowing where my tire lever is makes it hard to change from my winter cross tires back to road slicks.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/zgb1 - dinner.jpg    
    
    
    putting off figuring out how to transform an Indri query network into its "gradient network" with respect to a parameter    
    
    
    Disappointed that Search Engines: Information Retrieval in Practice's covers sig tests but doesn't address multiple testing issues    
    
    
    @ben_vandurme wait, what?    
    
    
    Wishing @barsmart had an API so we could do a bar crawl mashup.    
    
    
    iRobot was nice enough to ship me a new battery because I killed it following their instructions.    
    
    
    @briancavalier have you tried construction junction?    
    
    
    @ej I've drawn a number of diagrams for my dissertation in Inkscape.  I generally like it, but have found the connectors to be a bit buggy.    
    
    
    Pittsburgh is gridlocked    
    
    
    @edibaise sort of.  I feel "nonbelievers" is very us vs. them.  Also, atheists very clearly have beliefs.    
    
    
    following @ealdent not just because his posts are of academic interest, but also that, like me, he posts pictures of beer.    
    
    
    I do not like bidding on papers to review.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/16eno - ten fidy    
    
    
    Debugging committee perceptron code for learning Indri mixture model parameters.    
    
    
    Digging tramp ( http://www.gnu.org/software/tramp/ ) for editing remote files.    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Pittsburgh certainly inspires adopted hometown pride for me and a number of my friends in CMU and also some who have moved.    
    
    
    Done fighting with antlr for the evening.  Looking forward to more tomorrow.    
    
    
    As much as I hate bidding on papers to review, it seemed to work well for me with SIGIR.  Not bidding on WWW papers resulted in misery.    
    
    
    First success at gradient based optimization for mixture model parameters for known-item finding. Yes, it's maximizing mean-reciprocal rank.    
    
    
    Defogging at Big Dog Coffee    
    
    
    Sweet. Committee perceptron training on preference pairs confirmed to learn excellent parameters for held-out test set.    
    
    
    @brynn Despite official proclaimation, I doubt it will be PG.    
    
    
    @abdur ouch! glad everyone is okay.    
    
    
    My Amazon EC2 image reads user data on creation to run a batch of experiments, uploads the results to my server, then terminates itself. #in    
    
    
    Got a delinquent notice on a bill for $0.00.  Apparently American Education Services thinks I didn't pay nothing on time.    
    
    
    @jaykreps I'm in Santa Rosa    
    
    
    To breakfast, then to work at Big Dog Coffee.    
    
    
    @flurie we should meet over beer again to talk about close reading.    
    
    
    emacs will never die. Evidence: http://tinyurl.com/twit-el    
    
    
    The shredder I bought from Costco was so cheap because their contract with Fellowes explicitly excluded replacement parts.    
    
    
    @jelsas Yes, Costco's return policy is excellent, but doesn't cover my 2 year old device (not saying it should, just saying)    
    
    
    Lanbo Zhang: facet feedback for personalization indicates sufficiency or necessity, loss fn should handle separately #issdm    
    
    
    @nyyrajvggranhre @jaykreps magic of unstructured data can be  volume, but often must fight hard adding structure to use it effectively    
    
    
    @jaykreps Agree completely    
    
    
    @communicating Sutton & McCallum's CRF tutorial assumes some ML and stats knowledge, but is quite good http://tinyurl.com/afkq5m    
    
    
    @jelsas sounds like a great way to reduce review overload ;-)    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1zndl - Rogue Hazelnut Brown Nectar    
    
    
    http://www.csusummerarts.org/maf/index.shtml  so proud of my wife Christine and her award winning screenplay!    
    
    
    @Heewa @seancolombo Fred Flintstone might tell you a fixed gear car would be rough on your knees in San Francisco.    
    
    
    I have a feeling it is going to be hard to stay focused the rest of this week.    
    
    
    At Big Dog Coffee, writing about inverted indexes to support fast element parent/child query constraints.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson @briancavalier it's Chris' birthday too! Happy birthday b-funk!    
    
    
    Seems like every bus but the one I need has gone by twice.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff You need a client that supports the all of the Unicode characters http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chess_symbols_in_Unicode    
    
    
    @seancolombo Alas no, it's cut and paste all the way.    
    
    
    Just delivered a draft of my dissertation to my committee, working on scheduling my defense. #in    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries http://short.to/2ic8p but perhaps more boxes are search boxes than you thought?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries I make no claims about the result quality of @pogil search    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/2z8fq - IMG00047.jpg    
    
    
    @communicating That was my birthday swag.  Thanks!    
    
    
    @communicating wonder how it compares to ASSERT http://cemantix.org/assert.html (I used ASSERT for some diss. exps) nice to see alternatives    
    
    
    Long.bitCount(a^b) is a fast way to compute the Hamming distance of two binary strings. Challenge: pack as much into 64 bits as possible.    
    
    
    http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/138976/FPRF.pdf … and http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/120078/wfc0398-liPS.pdf … suggest one bit per hash function is enough in LSH. Are 64 hash functions enough?    
    
    
    Spectral hashing looks strong, but I won't build an affinity mx for millions of docs and run PCA. How big a sample is needed to beat LSH?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff yeah there are some  optimizations, but it's a bit amusing that the authors propose I do exactly what I hoped to avoid    
    
    
    @houndish pics or it didn't happen    
    
    
    @communicating @leejb curation can have value. Do influential humans following a (virtual) bot/retweeter indicate value?    
    
    
    @houndish glad things are safe again    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries the title and one sentence description is about all she's tools me, so I'm curious too. It's a romantic comedy    
    
    
    Downgrading to basic cable. Upgrading to netflix.    
    
    
    We're looking for interns on the recommendations engine team at LinkedIn. Let me know if you are interested!    
    
    
    Am I ready for my thesis defense tomorrow? Almost.    
    
    
    I held onto this bottle of wine since SIGIR 03 to celebrate my successful defense.  http://twitgoo.com/1466te    
    
    
    It takes around 1300 distinct email senders to make the top 3 most emailed articles of the day on the New York Times http://lnkd.in/eiMST8    
    
    
    @communicating Query language should be simple but unambiguous.  Could HOW MANY be valid query terms?  Might quotes be misleading (phrases)?    
    
    
    @communicating If possible, use the patterns from query languages that your users might know.    
    
    
    Interesting take on how tracking cookies benefit smaller publishers.  I just wonder how many people would actually opt…http://lnkd.in/aKzvAU    
    
    
    @francesco1986_ ML and IR grad students nearing graduation. If you're interested, send me your resume. We still have some open positions.    
    
    
    #lazyweb What's a typical value for Cohen's Kappa for relevance judgments?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Naturally :-) At what point do you typically consider revising the task or instructions (for the next year)?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @ian_soboroff My tweet was intentionally bait for Ian :-). I left it general to see if I get other responses.    
    
    
    @jonathankoren congratulations!    
    
    
    @JackGConrad and on a micro level, bike commuting saves me hundreds of dollars a year in gas and car maintenance, keeps me happy and healthy    
    
    
    Wikipedia is a social network. New mediawiki feature development makes this very clear http://www.mediawiki.org/wiki/Echo_(Notifications) …    
    
    
    @ej congratulations!    
    
    
    @ram Thanks!    
    
    
    Happy I can now update my profile http://techcrunch.com/2010/08/04/linkedin-mspoke/ #in    
    
    
    @andy_c did you bike up beechwood, or go some other route?    
    
    
    @andy_c Plenty of uphill on the way back, too. s/beacon/bartlett/;s/forbes/northumberland/ might have less traffic and be a bit shorter    
    
    
    Yes, Finds Pew Study, People Will (and Do) Pay For Digital Content http://lnkd.in/WPKJEs    
    
    
    @brendan642 Thanks! I'm pretty excited. Probably won't be working with @peteskomoroch right away, but could see it happening in the future.    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati awesome! Hope the ride went well    
    
    
    @strlen looks like a fun ride, but it's missing a rear rack for panniers ;-)    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/794f3 - No hope for Detroit    
    
    
    @peteskomoroch @mdreid @noahkagan invert the y axis    
    
    
    @CA_DMV what does the "system down statewide" sign at Santa Clara mean? I need to transfer my registration and license to CA.  can I?    
    
    
    expecting a long wait @CA_DMV despite arriving 30 mind before it opened. Miffed they put me back in the line after getting my car checked    
    
    
    Managed to survive the ca dmv. Worst dmv I've been to. Even pa, which also can't pass a budget, can manage to get you done in an hour    
    
    
    Using regularization to provide a prior.  Hoping it will reduce my parameter estimation woes.    
    
    
    @_mathur Sorry you didn't get a chance to ask your question regarding security. http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/06/09/an-update-on-taking-steps-to-protect-our-members/ … may answer your questions    
    
    
    Current status:  http://plixi.com/p/43495582    
    
    
    Decided not to sleep in the office but bike home instead. Gin and tonic, 4 Chimay, Mac and cheese demand it.    
    
    
    6 rabbits and 1 black cat.  What does it mean if a black turns and runs when it sees you coming?    
    
    
    3 days later. To the naysayers who felt standing in a creek for 30 minutes drinking beer wouldn't wash off the poison ivy: you were wrong.    
    
    
    Current status  http://plixi.com/p/44596402    
    
    
    @JtotheC tonic is probably the best place to have a beer and watch #anthrocon    
    
    
    I'll have good company in Moscow! RT @ecir2013: We're excited to announce another confirmed Industry Day speaker - Hilary Mason (@hmason)    
    
    
    OkCupid: an average rating isn't always a sufficient summary of a distribution for prediction http://lnkd.in/eF24wt    
    
    
    Apparently, it's national drink beer day! http://eatocracy.cnn.com/2012/09/28/national-drink-beer-day/ … Thanks, @prismatic! Intersected with election season: http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2012/09/in-which-i-reconsider-my-entire-political-outlook/262981/ …    
    
    
    @briancavalier on minimum viable product: just a feeling, but seems like viable is starting to mean bland. I think it should mean awesome    
    
    
    @IanPaterson This tweet clued me in that SnapRetail moved its offices. The strip district is a better place for a startup than Monroeville.    
    
    
    @briancavalier @JohnCampbellJr @IanPaterson LinkedIn blocks commits that don't compile and reverts your commit if the unit tests fail. CRAZY    
    
    
    @sharathrao Just glad I could finish and enjoy it before it turned into vinegar!    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Despite working in the guts of the payload structures, I never realized Index had real time indexing support!    
    
    
    Indri had "real time" support in 2004, earlier than Zoie or Solr. Shame we didn't make a bigger deal of it. @dmetzlerd @trevor_strohman    
    
    
    @pogil @CharlotteHase or I more likely, I had never payed much attention to its importance at the time    
    
    
    @Careerimp's resunate helps you adapt your resume from LinkedIn to a job -  http://careerimp.com/resunate/ #in /via @eengler #alphalab    
    
    
    @communicating analyzed    
    
    
    @IanPaterson ha! Perhaps you just hate yourself for living in the past?    
    
    
    @seanjtaylor @gappy3000 you get more miles out of a car if you understand how it works, but many are good drivers without that knowledge    
    
    
    Looking for company knowledge bases with descriptions & aliases. Must be more comprehensive than Wikipedia+Freebase. Need not be free.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @lintool now out of that context, I realize now that did not come across well our as I meant    
    
    
    @leifos @lintool makes a great point often overlooked. Powering and cooling data centers is expensive. Efficiency is a big deal.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @leifos @ecir2013 yes - Filip Radlinkski and Katja Hofmann's work is very related. I've enjoyed comparing notes with them    
    
    
    @IR_oldie @leifos @ecir2013 None yet, but we are building on work from Yahoo! http://arxiv.org/abs/1003.5956     
    
    
    Goodbye world, hello Paul!    
    
    
    @briancavalier @pbrumblay @bostonaholic so 5/08 would be like groundhog day, right? But that's in February. This is hurting my head    
    
    
    #ecir2013 keynotes by Diane Kelly & @informor, industry talks by @lintool @marc_najork @karenchurch me and others at http://events.yandex.ru/events/ecir2013     
    
    
    "@CheapEatsChick: Espresso! http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/05/09/espresso-chart_n_3247215.html?utm_hp_ref=@food123 …" I normally just have an espresso, but the affogato looks good to me.    
    
    
    Want to work with me to build compelling news products? Let me know http://lnkd.in/gWrK3G    
    
    
    "@vitroc Universities by Return of Invstmnt http://lnkd.in/pwk8TU  
" would these look different adjusted for cost of living where grads go?    
    
    
    Curse you Frasier Crane! I had not seen the Orient Express    
    
    
    @mancrates Hoppy hopstatic    
    
    
    @seancolombo or for if you freeze it    
    
    
    @adilaijaz that trick only works with non-final classes. Does that shake you to your core?    
    
    
    So apparently Excel doesn't like SUMIF if you have around 370,000 rows.    
    
    
    Just set up http://roksbox.com/ on my Roku to play mp3 files from my desktop. Nice! All I had to do was run a web server on my desktop...    
    
    
    Arrived in Denver. Looking forward to interam    
    
    
    @andy_c and then you ponder about sampling the world?    
    
    
    @andy_c doesn't stripping and sanding come first? Or is a new railing?    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell cross country would be more fun to watch if spectators could add obstacles to the course before the race.    
    
    
    Redis at Disqus | Brett Hoerner's blog http://lnkd.in/4TbEmW    
    
    
    @ladygaga You've got nothing to do with your birth, but being on the right track implies you've got something to do with it. I'm confused.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/hznfu - Sunset steak and beer    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/i5rg0 - People are turning Pittsburgh's parking spaces into parks    
    
    
    Just discovered horror and glory of Google Play Music. When did I give permission for albums I ripped? Reminders of http://Mp3.com     
    
    
    @pogil discovered this after an accidental click on the app on my android. Music not on phone, but on desktop...    
    
    
    I work with the guys on this team! Post by @adilaijaz: The Engineering behind LinkedIn Products “You May Like” http://bit.ly/fvdoNt #in    
    
    
    Left work a little early to get out of downtown.  To me, Pittsburgh felt more like a ghost town than a "police state" #g20    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/ivpoo - Weyerbacher imperial pumpkin ale    
    
    
    @JtotheC I bought a bag of the riceworks sweet chili chips a couple weeks ago. The bag barely lasted 24 hours.    
    
    
    #g20 downtown parking garages are closed.  Recommend parking legally on a side street in a neighborhood and busing downtown.    
    
    
    #g20 Parking: pay attention to street signs. Many neighborhoods have daytime restrictions. Each street that is restricted will have signs.    
    
    
    #g20 Public transit: http://www.portauthority.org    
    
    
    Disappointed more of @GATOR_313 's music isn't like change gonna come.    
    
    
    @brynn it can be hard to say no to those requesting reviews but doing it from time to time has greatly improved the quality of my life.    
    
    
    trying to understand how we get the right stuff into the db    
    
    
    cutting down on office expletives (moving on to a different task)    
    
    
    This is what I've been working on! LinkedIn Today Is Live: A Walkthrough http://tcrn.ch/gecPxZ  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @jelsas @dtunkelang The Onion comes at source #39 for  http://www.linkedin.com/today/higher_education    
    
    
    @jelsas @dtunkelang If you're lucky, you might catch one of their articles in the "Novel & Newsworthy" section of that page.    
    
    
    Twittering from my blackberry! And reading a friends dissertation to make sure I represent his work well    
    
    
    You'd think the fatty mcdonalds I ate at 2 would have lasted longer    
    
    
    Sounds like @andy_c needs some coffee    
    
    
    The 46 page single-spaced beast of a related work chapter is now Jamie's problem.    
    
    
    You'd think it is finals week or something.  The first two coffee shops I tried had no tables.  Curse you students!    
    
    
    putting the love-seat in the make-out room    
    
    
    @zach I haven't had a problem with the TOCs in Preview.  Do you want my preamble for comparison?    
    
    
    @zach http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~pto/Preamble.tex and http://www.cs.cmu.edu/~pto/Titlepage.tex    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell since IBM believes that services are the way to make money, they didn't like innovation that couldn't be sold as a service    
    
    
    disappointed that the steelers got back into the game, only to have their defense blow it.    
    
    
    Trying to find time for Dean and Einar between little bugs from QDAP.    
    
    
    Shopping    
    
    
    I've got to work on my timing. Thought I was running behind, but I still had to wait a few minutes at the gate.    
    
    
    LinkedIn Today coffee truck! http://plixi.com/p/88111952    
    
    
    Twice checking bags for a tool. 1st-hold still while I pinch you with this vice. 2nd-wait an hour while I sharpen this with my honing plane.    
    
    
    This is why I don't like checking luggage.    
    
    
    Impulse! Costco had wiis.    
    
    
    @mdreid my favorite: instant friend, just add beer    
    
    
    http://xkcd.com/882/ I wonder whether the scientists corrected for multiple testing #in    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati nice! cyclocross bikes rock!    
    
    
    @SeanAmmirati Information retrieval's view circa 2003: http://tinyurl.com/2cmrdn    
    
    
    Makes me happy: RT @Sharp_Edge Great beer news for Pittsburgh! http://short.to/y56f    
    
    
    Just reread my thesis proposal.  Most of the goals remain the same, but the model/hypotheses/experiments have changed a lot since then!    
    
    
    Missing my beloved wireless at crazy mocha. Why do you fail? WHY?    
    
    
    The unexpected bonus 140GB on my new @westerndigital hard drive is more than 3x the size of my old drive all on its own.    
    
    
    @ianpaterson you can not has jameson. You has beam    
    
    
    @amazonaws where's my low-CPU high-memory ec2 instance?  Say, a large instance with 15GB?  #AWS    
    
    
    @communicating quality is very context sensitive, but basically yes    
    
    
    @briancavalier so is wire.js like spring for JavaScript?    
    
    
    @ealdent thank you!    
    
    
    Excited that elvis costello and the imposters open for the police show.    
    
    
    I've recently been thinking a lot about how to make pervasive split testing easy.  http://tinyurl.com/split-tests-pt1    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell but how long has it been there?    
    
    
    @javasoze Sensei demo was really easy to run, but how do I shut down a sensei node?    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I've recently been getting invites for web meetings promising to [get rich quick scheme].  Seems like clever spam/scam to me.    
    
    
    http://www.botanicalls.com/twitter/    
    
    
    Relishing that I now have minions.    
    
    
    Enjoying my new neighborhood bar    
    
    
    @zach Did you do any speed tests on the stanford NER when you played with it?    
    
    
    Glad I don't work in an office of touchy feely drama people    
    
    
    Debugging custom c++ network messages not written by me = nightmare    
    
    
    taking my fixie to my "office" on the south side    
    
    
    I desire a longer brake lever.    
    
    
    @sammirati a good friend of mine is renting space at http://www.officenomads.com/ in Seattle    
    
    
    Ian FTW    
    
    
    @houndish I love my cyclocross. They're very versatile bikes    
    
    
    @houndish In 06 I got a Cannondale cyclocross disc. They doesn't make a cross with disc brakes anymore, but I love the bike    
    
    
    @houndish If you don't like the ride, there are a also lot of aggressive street bikes with flat bars that take fat tires /cc @briancavalier    
    
    
    @houndish for example: http://www.bikesdirect.com/products/motobecane/cafe_century_pro_xi.htm /cc @briancavalier    
    
    
    The diner coffee is actually decent when it is a fresh pot!    
    
    
    Heading to Hough's for dinner, beer, and pencil and paper statistics.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson happy birthday! I'll buy you a beer on saturday    
    
    
    People watching in Market Square.    
    
    
    @communicating business or pleasure? You could easily spend days talking to ppl in Pittsburgh if you take a broad definition of surrounding    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell you can has waaa...    
    
    
    @andy_c perhaps they are so poorly baked nobody wants to eat them    
    
    
    @Ian for the bump.    
    
    
    Reading how google news handles scale - http://www2007.org/paper570.php    
    
    
    Go ahead and jump!    
    
    
    I found the simple life ain't so simple.    
    
    
    Everybody wants some. Baby, how bout you?    
    
    
    I'll wait till your love comes down.    
    
    
    The cradle will rock:    
    
    
    Hot for teacher    
    
    
    @houndish Panama    
    
    
    @houndish you got the order wrong!    
    
    
    Getting Mariokart. Woot!    
    
    
    They just put a recliner on the fire.    
    
    
    Finally making it in to work after a detour to the Strip District to get my dad a birthday gift.    
    
    
    Waiting for the game to start    
    
    
    @jelsas beer? where?    
    
    
    @mdreid reminds me of the somewhat uncommon wisdom i first heard from my father "sometimes the best thing to say is nothing at all"    
    
    
    @mdreid along with "not every battle is worth fighting "    
    
    
    Texted result of Manchester v. Chelsea to @JohnnyCampbell.  Not exactly sure why.    
    
    
    Heading out to lay trail.    
    
    
    Realizing the benefits of keypad locks on my phone.    
    
    
    Back third of trail marked...    
    
    
    Out of flour with half a mile left to mark. Will finish tomorrow    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell mmm soysage    
    
    
    Pbj and box wine on my balcony.  Now that's what I call living.    
    
    
    After listening to http://is.gd/AvJ at Best Buy, I just had to order one.  The sound sparkled with my Grado SR80s.    
    
    
    It always amazes me how many fewer statistically significant differences we can detect after correcting for multiple testing.    
    
    
    That thing that you think is different? We can't be sure. Check back a few years from now we have better methods for mult. test correction.    
    
    
    @pghh3 it's only bc bad others still think there's a difference when we really can't tell. You'd think "scientists" would know better...    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell sorry I couldn't join you - was stuck in the office until 30 minutes ago.    
    
    
    @IanPaterson I'm pretty sure we should give @JohnnyCampbell 30 days or so to claim it.  Like lost-and-found boxes.    
    
    
    @edibiase Did you find the Vivo Barefoot shoes locally, or did you order them off of the internet?    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell you will have the option to create a real life Battlefield:Furries if you join us at Tonic tomorrow.    
    
    
    chop chop chopping the related work chapter down to less than 30 pages.    
    
    
    Today was simply wonderful    
    
    
    Amused that the only people who have bothered to port MINPACK to Java and release it is the US Forest Service.    
    
    
    feeling deflated    
    
    
    @briancavalier glad you enjoyed the dub chocolate.  It's one of my favorite stouts.    
    
    
    @zach Welcome to the world of text!    
    
    
    Thinking http://is.gd/RwP might be an interesting read.  Found via http://is.gd/RwS    
    
    
    Sitting in traffic    
    
    
    Landed in Pittsburgh.    
    
    
    Back at the dealer so they can put the tire on right this time.    
    
    
    @seancolombo you should check out http://short.to/1646z - they also include the code used to make the graphs    
    
    
    @briancavalier you may also like http://jott.com    
    
    
    I think lots of queries kill Cuil.  They claim to have a lot of pages, but return nothing for many queries they should.    
    
    
    Must be missed something about how Cuil works.  Would have been nice for them to let me know that there might be results for me Q later...    
    
    
    Wondering where Ian went.    
    
    
    @bmevans youtube, myspace, facebook, blogger. Measured by Alexa's top sites http://is.gd/18eq    
    
    
    Power went out.    
    
    
    Just saw a possum. Now watching the bats.    
    
    
    @edibiase are you doing the minor in lang. tech?  I see a couple of LTI courses in there...    
    
    
    @bmevans If your trip back East includes Pittsburgh, you should swing by mSpoke!    
    
    
    Congratulating Dr. Mahady    
    
    
    Walking to Hough's for lunch and some work to prevent onset of cabin fever #snowmageddon    
    
    
    Southside works is amazingly empty despite (because of?) the music festival.    
    
    
    After dropping a rental game off, I was stuck behind the bus I wanted.    
    
    
    @briancavalier hope you finished your chores - I'm thinking about riding my bike to the trail tonight it is so nice out    
    
    
    #roku + #pandora + @SlavicSoulParty = #nowplaying    
    
    
    Looking forward to Fallout 3. http://is.gd/1PBd    
    
    
    Jamie Callan (my advisor) now has the first complete draft of my dissertation.    
    
    
    @briancavalier hope you enjoy the work at @snapretail! It sounds like you'll be working on an interesting and challenging project.    
    
    
    @edibiase I always had the "what are all these people doing here" reaction when the semester started.    
    
    
    Love how the bread is "singing" as it cools http://twitpic.com/5ntxf8     
    
    
    @communicating isn't it always sobering how messy the real world (data) can be? Academics often take cleaned datasets for granted    
    
    
    The salad for lunch and amy's TV dinner has left me feeling calorie deprived. After checking the box, I found the dinner had only 260 cals!    
    
    
    @JohnnyCampbell this geek is only making it to crazy mocha now...    
    
    
    @IanPaterson also drinking coffee, but in South Side.   Weekend of coffee tweets?    
    
    
    @jelsas You got it! The book and dutch oven were a very thoughtful wedding gift from @lmariaschneider and @deansher    
    
    
    @bmevans what's a pirate's favorite statistical analysis program? But seriously, I do almost all of my data analysis in R.    
    
    
    Biking to south side for grins    
    
    
    trip delayed: thought light battery was charged, turned out not true    
    
    
    Mmm vanilla porter    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Is a TREC 2009 Blog Track overview available yet?    
    
    
    @briancavalier found at Rivertowne Pour House in Monroeville.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Was it taboo to use link count to the day's articles in the top stories task, or were there too few links to be useful?    
    
    
    @banksimple A bank with an API sounds cool and innovative, but does a myriad of apps gel with simple? Sounds like 'bankgeek.'    
    
    
    @banksimple Transparency rocks, but I'm having trouble finding an example where an API would be better than a clear TOS and UI. Help me pls?    
    
    
    @banksimple Okay, I think I get it now. For example, I could build an app that tracks and displays changes to the terms/conditions over time    
    
    
    @shamir_k @banksimple Thanks for the examples and clarifications - they were very helpful!    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Thanks! I missed U of Iowa's paper on my first pass through the proceedings.    
    
    
    My neighborhood bar Hough's now has 70 beers.    
    
    
    @seancolombo @deansher perhaps the goal should be the "Sean Colombo" or "Dean Thompson" everyone thinks of when your name is mentioned.    
    
    
    @bcavalier southern tier imperial pumking: mellow with rich tones of pumpkin and spice. Very warm and nutty.    
    
    
    Done laying trail in much less time than expected. Cool weather makes a big difference.    
    
    
    Awesome ad: http://www.youtube.com/experiencewii    
    
    
    hanging art between plays    
    
    
    Glad I have a month for ECIR reviews    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald thanks for the link. What would happen if you use linking documents as basis for expansion, rather than Wikipedia?    
    
    
    @edibiase how are you liking your vivo barefoot shoes?    
    
    
    @edibiase so that's a positive statement of comfort?    
    
    
    Resisting the pressure of the Leinenkugel beer reps at Hough's.  Choosing Great Lakes' Edmund Fitzgerald porter instead.    
    
    
    Wondering whether @ej still checks his ir.iit.edu email address.    
    
    
    @ej strange.  I'll resend.    
    
    
    Feeling enlighted about how people vote: http://www.kansas.com/205/story/565669.html    
    
    
    Feeling cabin feever after two days at home    
    
    
    @abdur I'm with you on no Facebook apps.  They always feel very invasive, are a hassle to set up, and they like to spam my friends.    
    
    
    Enjoyed discussing tagging, taxonomies, attention, and filtering over lunch with @danielabarbosa.    
    
    
    @ryanqnorth I'm too lazy to build an n-gram lang model of T-Rex's speech from http://tinyurl.com/qwantz-transcripts #qwantzle    
    
    
    @ryanqnorth #qwantzle = qwantz puzzle, because this totally needs its own hashtag.    
    
    
    @danielabarbosa I agree. Tweets demand attention.  It is our choice who receives our attention.    
    
    
    @danielabarbosa Not following does not imply a lack of interest, but rather a preference for a different mode of providing attention.    
    
    
    Digging stephanierooker.com at ava    
    
    
    Working on a journal paper on work done at the Reliable Information Access Workshop http://bit.ly/ria - seems like so long ago...    
    
    
    