Drinking a Dortmunder Gold by @GLBC_Cleveland @ Joey's Italian Grille — http://untp.it/1drzsAY     
    
    
    I just earned the 'Lager Jack (Level 3)' badge on @untappd! http://untp.it/140oleb     
    
    
    Today stats: 5 followers, 5 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @NathanLattanzi @JayGilmore @anyadowning    
    
    
    Today stats: 5 followers, 3 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @RobQuigley    
    
    
    NFL PHI - QB Nick Foles completed 6-of-17 passes for 63 yds in 1st half of preseason finale vs. Jets (ESPN) http://es.pn/14D8YJd     
    
    
    NFL PHI - Rookie QB Matt Barkley 13-of-27 for 134 yds with INT in 2nd half of preseason finale vs. Jets (ESPN) http://es.pn/14fcToB     
    
    
    NFL - Redskins QB Robert Griffin III tweets that he has been "cleared" to play season opener vs. Eagles (ESPN) http://es.pn/YYuzSj     
    
    
    Thanks @LaughNYC @afabbiano for being top new followers in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    NFL PHI - Eagles release 12 players, including Chip Kelly's former QB at Oregon Dennis Dixon (ESPN) http://es.pn/1dXFmHF     
    
    
    Drinking an Oberon Ale by @BellsBrewery @ Liberty Union Bar & Grille — http://untp.it/1dzfMLD     
    
    
    Drinking an IPA by @lagunitasT @ Liberty Union Bar & Grille — http://untp.it/18c3qlo     
    
    
    Today stats: 5 followers, 6 unfollowers and followed 2 people via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @madSMscientist    
    
    
    NFL PHI - Eagles release OL Danny Watkins, who was 1st-round pick in 2011 (ESPN) http://es.pn/XYvcho     
    
    
    Check out this great wine from Cristom. I'm giving it 4.5 of 5 stars with the Vivino app: http://www.vivino.com/s/52227c2c6a39f     
    
    
    Today stats: 4 followers, 3 unfollowers and followed one person via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    NFL DEN - LB Adrian Robinson assigned to Broncos off waivers from Eagles (ESPN) http://es.pn/10aCwuL     
    
    
    NFL PHI - Eagles claim CB Shaun Prater off waivers from Bengals; waive CB Curtis Marsh (ESPN) http://es.pn/17ASIZr     
    
    
    Drinking an India Pale Ale (IPA) by @YardsBrew — http://untp.it/14bHgTs     
    
    
    Target's Ticket video on-demand service launching soon http://lnkd.in/NzHYaS     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @natashavincent    
    
    
    Today stats: 2 followers, 5 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/14RlbIg  http://bit.ly/14RlbIg     
    
    
    Thanks @NatMoraisBR @FashionPennPal for being top engaged members in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/14RlbYC ? http://bit.ly/14RlbYC     
    
    
    NFL - Redskins coach Mike Shanahan says QB Robert Griffin III will start in season opener vs. Eagles (ESPN) http://es.pn/YYuzSj     
    
    
    I like to repost this in case some of you forgot your #grammar lessons! http://instagram.com/p/Xs6FnsCQSk/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @JoeBugBuster    
    
    
    Today stats: 3 followers, 4 unfollowers and followed one person via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    @nosefrida haha, thanks!!    
    
    
    @hamptonskiley yes, the end to "summer" now. :(    
    
    
    I want to win a ticket to Social Media Success Summit 2013 http://bit.ly/winSMSS13  via @smexaminer #winSMSS13    
    
    
    I want to win a ticket to Social Media Success Summit 2013 http://bit.ly/winSMSS13  via @smexaminer #winSMSS13    
    
    
    @robotlordpj haha, nope, still a Buckeye fan! how've you been?    
    
    
    NFL MIA - Dolphins agree to terms on 1-year contract with OG Danny Watkins (former Eagles 1st-rd draft pick) (ESPN) http://es.pn/15TyZ4U     
    
    
        
    
    
    @robotlordpj what weekend is the PSU/KSU game??  I have a lot going on with weekend soccer as i coach 2 teams this fall. haha but might work    
    
    
    Thanks @LaughNYC @ReachMktg for being top new followers in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    #LinkedIn Training Seminar "How to Optimize & Use Your LinkedIn Profile for Success!" 9/17 Exton PA http://ow.ly/ovS4B     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @Social_Ben @purplelover04 @theeMailguide    
    
    
    Today stats: 3 followers, 6 unfollowers and followed one person via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    I want to win a ticket to Social Media Success Summit 2013 http://bit.ly/winSMSS13  via @smexaminer #winSMSS13    
    
    
    Check out Waze - a free traffic & navigation app that I use all the time http://bit.ly/wtshare     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @andrew_ob @adigaskell @ngagecompany    
    
    
    Today stats: One follower, 2 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    I want to win a ticket to Social Media Success Summit 2013 http://bit.ly/winSMSS13  via @smexaminer #winSMSS13    
    
    
    Thanks @nikkisunstrum @ctmarcom for being top engaged members in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    Check out this article about Zack Swire and eGood! http://bit.ly/17zkUWB     
    
    
    NFL - Riley Cooper and Cary Williams, who was critical of WR for racial epithet, scuffle in practice (ESPN) http://es.pn/19m5kkO     
    
    
    They are getting the #DirtWolf ready!! cant wait much longer! via @victorybeer's video http://instagram.com/p/d4i0siS0iA/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @anniemal @cubanalaf @dallassinglemom    
    
    
    Today stats: 4 followers, 6 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    #smile it's #Friday!!  #tgif http://instagram.com/p/d6qjmkiQTO/     
    
    
    I want to win a ticket to Social Media Success Summit 2013 http://bit.ly/winSMSS13  via @smexaminer #winSMSS13    
    
    
    Thanks @LaughNYC @ReachMktg for being top new followers in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    NFL - Eagles coach Chip Kelly on Riley Cooper-Cary Williams fight: "No fallout whatever" (ESPN) http://es.pn/155ysNr     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @jlisak    
    
    
    Today stats: 9 followers, 3 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Enjoying our 11th Anniversary dinner. (@ Fiorello's Cafe) http://4sq.com/1cTqJDM     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Today stats: 2 followers, 3 unfollowers and followed one person via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    Giants are the lessor of two evils! #snf #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/19yI9Ug     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just got today's #Newsroom sticker. Get yours in the next 3h:1m. #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/17K6fMx  #Newsroom    
    
    
    Today stats: One follower, One unfollower via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    @ctomkiel @wendyscherer thank you for the anniversary wishes!    
    
    
    @rutherfordkris tweet away! :)    
    
    
    @stevekrohn Steve, thanks for the AboutMe compliment! have a great week!    
    
    
    Pinterest and Path battle over ‘P’ logos http://bit.ly/19BnGOM     
    
    
    NFL PHI - QB Matt Barkley, DE Vinny Curry, CB Shaun Prater, T Dennis Kelly among inactives for Monday opener (ESPN) http://es.pn/XYvcho     
    
    
    Pinterest and Path battle over ‘P’ logos http://bit.ly/19BnGOO  http://bit.ly/19BnGOO     
    
    
    #Philly area: Learn about #LinkedIn Profile Optimization & Best Practices at our seminar on 9/17! #EXTONPA http://ow.ly/oHm7c     
    
    
    "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013" a FREE Webinar on Sept 27 RSVP Now and Share --> http://bit.ly/13Cu9bi  #pmot #projectmanagement    
    
    
    Are you ready to Enable your PMO? Do you feel the need for better scheduling and collboration with the Project teams? check out this...    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @SarahLindsay @WendySLea    
    
    
    Today stats: One follower, 3 unfollowers via http://Unfollowers.me     
    
    
    @dadarocks i am trying to get that unfollower thing to stop sending. i don't even remember signing up :)    
    
    
    SEO for B2B Execs; A Lead Generation Strategy Guide. Download a copy today! via @nusparkmktg http://ow.ly/oJMod     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @theeMailguide @lisarocksSEM    
    
    
    Soccer practice tonight. Hot one out there! (@ Shamona Creek Elem. School) http://ow.ly/oMXV1     
    
    
    I just entered to win a FREE plant from http://givingplants.com ! #contest #sweepstakes Click here to enter - http://a.pgtb.me/Tc20jZ     
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/D9Awt3  #in    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @tracysestili @ahilliardm    
    
    
    I'm talking w @WilsonVA on the @ChescoMarketing #HOA show this morning. Speaking about our upcoming LinkedIn Seminar http://bit.ly/15ZgE2f     
    
    
    #Philly area: Learn about #LinkedIn Profile Optimization & Best Practices at our seminar on 9/17! #EXTONPA http://ow.ly/oHm7c     
    
    
    @lgreenberg haven't been to Taco Maya. So it's good? Will have to check it out.    
    
    
    @lgreenberg last night's GEYA soccer practice was brutal hot ! But nice to see fresh paint. Looking Fw to a cool wkend as I hv back-back gm    
    
    
    @CaraBarone did hear/see the news about twitter going public. Thx. Will have to search for that article.    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @JonahLupton @EileenOBrien @MommyBlogExpert    
    
    
    Twitter files for IPO, most highly anticipated public offering since Facebook http://ow.ly/oPynq     
    
    
    Happy Friday everyone!    
    
    
    Check out "How to Optimize & Use Your LinkedIn Profile for Success!" | Training Seminar 9/17 Exton PA …http://optimizing-your-linkedin-profile-workshop-estw.eventbrite.com     
    
    
    Working on my presentation for @ChescoMarketing LinkedIn Seminar next week. (at @Wegmans w/ @chescomarketing) http://4sq.com/17vVyMN     
    
    
    @laurenbeley i still have recruiters hit me up for job positions that i did 10 years ago!! i used to be in IT, not sure where pull info :)    
    
    
    Happy Friday shout out to @douglasPscott @fashionpennpal @NatMoraisBR @mmbizon @WilsonVA @CTMarcom @AManzellaPR Enjoy the weekend!    
    
    
    Check out and #FF these accounts and learn more about them & their products: @1holistichealer @RequestItaly @givingplants @ChesCoMarketing    
    
    
    Check out "How to Optimize & Use Your LinkedIn Profile for Success!" | Training Seminar 9/17 Exton PA …http://optimizing-your-linkedin-profile-workshop-estw.eventbrite.com     
    
    
    @laurenbeley nope, sure doesn't!  have a good weekend.  where are working now?    
    
    
    @ctmarcom will do! gorgeous weekend!    
    
    
    @laurenbeley oh that's right. i remember now.  :)  beautiful weekend ahead! enjoy too!    
    
    
    Talking About Google Voice and Google Hangouts - #ChesCoMG OnAir: http://bit.ly/13XyOVD  via @youtube    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Soccer soccer soccer (@ Shamona Creek Elem. School) http://4sq.com/1ecsFuc     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @spicydesign    
    
    
    Check out "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013" http://kwikpmo-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @RavenTools @OMum22    
    
    
    The definitive guide to homemade hummus http://pinterest.com/pin/242912973624878257/ …    
    
    
    I walked 0.70 mi with @mapmywalk. Check out my route in PA, United States! http://mmf.cc/18p6pFt  #walk #walking    
    
    
    You should join me at this Meetup. Bucks Mont Marketing meetup 9/25 Check it out and RSVP! http://meetu.ps/20g9hY     
    
    
    I'm an @Influenster and you can be too! Be a tastemaker for access to perks, products, and offers. http://bit.ly/Q7ZOvM  #trendsetting    
    
    
    @ctmarcom @WilsonVA thanks Coreen!    
    
    
    @AManzellaPR Thanks Angela! everyone have fun! @WilsonVA @douglasPscott @FashionPennPal @NatMoraisBR @mmbizon @ctmarcom @jamminpsu    
    
    
    @WilsonVA thanks for the monday morning shout out! just getting on twitter!    
    
    
    @christuttle thanks Chris.  We're planning on taking the 3 hr seminar and breaking into short webinars this fall. how are you?    
    
    
    @christuttle we should set some time for next week to catch up again and see what each is working on.    
    
    
    "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013" a FREE Webinar on Sept 27 RSVP-> http://bit.ly/13Cu9bi  #pmot #projectmanagement    
    
    
    @courtconigs what happened in #DC?    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @TheGiggleGuy @PavelNovel @mincedmedia    
    
    
    Speaking at the @ChescoMarketing LinkedIn Seminar. (@ Chester County Economic Development Council) [pic]: http://4sq.com/188PHwa     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @ColleenMPowers @nuviapp @Your_Say    
    
    
    Philly area marketing pros: check out Northern Chester County Marketing events calendar https://www.eventbrite.com/org/3091397356?ref=eotw … via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Check out "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013" http://kwikpmo-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    @courtconigs yes, i did check news sites after your tweet. so sad for all the innocent people :(  i hadn't seen news, twitter on monday :)    
    
    
    "How to Use Twitter for Your Business" Meetup on 9/25 in N Wales PA. Check it out and RSVP! http://bit.ly/189rs2J     
    
    
    I just used a handy email template to remind my friends to vote for our school in the #GiveWithTarget program. http://givewith.target.com/school/57655     
    
    
    BREAKING NEWS: Local police in Cleveland expect crime rates to increase by 33% on Sunday afternoons as football fans have nothing to do! ;-)    
    
    
    Could you please VOTE for my kid's school. each vote = $1 from Target to support to K-12 schools.  #GiveWithTarget http://tgt.biz/16oaolT     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @tmj_phl_adv @HandyMoms @larrykim    
    
    
    Check out my BrandYourself profile, do me a favor and let me know what you think! http://jefftincher.brandyourself.com     
    
    
    Arrrg matey, me kids arre gonna kick yer landlubber arse!! Happy Pirates Day! (@ Martial Arts Studio) http://4sq.com/19irDHm     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @CharityIdeas    
    
    
    @FireMom I think I need something to track my sleep patterns. Especially once my kids invade our bed in the middle of the night!    
    
    
    @jillianbmele yup. Chip will be a great change to the team. Just need ALL players to work as a team during the same game. Play smart & hard    
    
    
    @EricaDiamond cute. Have a great Friday!!    
    
    
    @EricaDiamond yes that is one annoyance with iOS 7, all unread email shows. Can turn Badge off in Settings>Notifications>mail.    
    
    
    Thanks @exploreB2B @ckw09 for being top new followers in my community this week :) | insight by http://commun.it     
    
    
    Check out "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013 - October 2013" http://bit.ly/18gfCUk  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Pretty cool to get this card in the mail today from @BluecoatGin #BluecoatGin. They took the time to… http://instagram.com/p/ef0bPJCQT1/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @DanStasiewski @joePRguy @Michael_Swart    
    
    
    Soccer, soccer and more soccer today!  9am and 10:30am games - and I'm coaching both! http://ow.ly/i/3bJud     
    
    
    After soccer lunch (@ Buffalo Wild Wings - @bwwings) http://4sq.com/19nQ4TH     
    
    
    I'm at Artisan Homebrew (Downingtown, PA) http://4sq.com/16ocd1a     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @pbkup    
    
    
    Happy first day of fall!! What do you love best about autumn? http://instagram.com/p/ekOkqxiQWj/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @natashavincent @_Karen    
    
    
    Twitter Analytics: 3 Tools that Measure and Track Your Success http://lnkd.in/bwBDKpv     
    
    
    Thanks @WilsonVA@jamminpsu for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Thanks @douglasPscott @AManzellaPR for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @DanStasiewski @SumAll @hannahchatmedia    
    
    
    Thanks @exploreB2B @Bri_Clark @ckw09 for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @nyike ah, haven't been on twitter much, saw you also coach soccer. hope it's going well for you! what ages? I have 1st and 2/3 grades    
    
    
    Did you have trouble with Gmail yesterday? Here's why -- http://bit.ly/16FOryF     
    
    
    Attending @chescomarketing event tonight. Come join us on porch. Talking Mobile & Web apps! (at @UnoChicagoGrill) http://4sq.com/1amkEhL     
    
    
    At the @Chescomarketing event tonight talking about mobile apps and web apps. http://bit.ly/1bE19EY     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @mincedmedia @boostctr @zoe_cairns    
    
    
    @jamminpsu @WilsonVA @douglasPscott @LeilaAnsart @Gazalla @johnlauber @PhillyAreaYoga same to everyone! thx for attending. #ChescoMG    
    
    
    Great place for tire damage. Fast repair and new tire installed. Friendly service and very honest. Highly recommend. http://4sq.com/170UnFO     
    
    
    @NatMoraisBR @mmbizon have a good time tonight at your Meetup and good luck with the Twitter preso!!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @tedprodromou @jmgagnon @Amoravick    
    
    
    Thanks @ChesCoMarketing @NatMoraisBR for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    can anyone help? Sharing an Eventrbrite event on LinkedIn and the event image NOT displaying on @LinkedIn. can anyone test on their end.    
    
    
    Discipline hour for kids. Thank God!! (@ Martial Arts Studio) http://4sq.com/1bfO2dT     
    
    
    @LinkedInHelp yes, same problem in chrome & FF. i sent email to @Eventbrite about it as well. try sharing this link. http://kwikpmo-oct4.eventbrite.com     
    
    
    @LinkedInHelp and thank you for the response!    
    
    
    FREE Project Management Webinar | October 4th 11am ET | Enable Your PMO with #KwikPMO and #ProjectServer2013! http://ow.ly/pg4wq     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @ShortStackLab @emilythousand    
    
    
    Take care of your Skin and Eyes - from @Holistic Healer & Wellness  http://blog.HolisticHealerOnline.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/242912973624947599/ …    
    
    
    What does Organic and Natural Really Mean? - @Holistic Healer & Wellness http://pinterest.com/pin/242912973624947606/ …    
    
    
    FREE Project Management Webinar | October 4th 11am ET | Enable Your PMO with #KwikPMO and #ProjectServer2013! http://ow.ly/pg4C9     
    
    
    Hey @BetaList, @NatMoraisBR, @ChesCoMarketing, @FashionPennPal, you're in my inner circle on Twitter: https://www.vizify.com/jefftincher/connections?s=twitter&u=35220&f=7303&t=connections_share_inner_circle … via @vizify    
    
    
    Are you in my inner circle on Twitter?  Find out here: https://www.vizify.com/jefftincher/connections?s=twitter&u=35220&f=7303&t=connections_share_everyone … then visualize your own with #Vizify    
    
    
    The right ad at the right time! --> Facebook Tweaks News Feed Algorithm to Show More Relevant Ads http://bit.ly/1bMNs6J     
    
    
    3 Essential Tips for Spying on PPC Competition http://bit.ly/1bMNLyC     
    
    
    Dinner and some meatballs tonight (@ Regal Downingtown 16 - @regalmovies for Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs 2) http://4sq.com/199Uewo     
    
    
    Thanks @Bri_Clark @ckw09 @TheGoToSite for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @jmgagnon @LaurenEHarper @highervis    
    
    
    Win a $500 Target Gift Card! Enter now! http://www.thesweetestplan.blogspot.com/2013/09/500-target-gift-card-giveaway.html …    
    
    
    Enter to win a $500 Target gift card http://is.gd/XM9gCO     
    
    
    @NatMoraisBR @douglasPscott i know. not sure why he's getting all those tweets, Doug do you have some Notification turned on that is new??    
    
    
    Enjoyed meeting (in person) this week! @LeilaAnsart @PhillyAreaYoga @ReferralPush (Justin) - See you at the next @ChesCoMarketing event!    
    
    
    Let #GoBuckeyes! 11 hours to game time. #breakingbadgers #ohiostatebuckeyes #buckeyes #buckeyenation http://instagram.com/p/ezftFuiQY8/     
    
    
    #BreakingBadgers airs tonight at 8pm when Ohio State Buckeyes take on Wisconsin Badgers. O-H http://instagram.com/p/ezgIaZiQZe/     
    
    
    Back to Back #soccer games today for Coach Dad. Kids are playing great!    
    
    
    Soccer soccer soccer (@ Shamona Creek Elem. School) http://4sq.com/1aymcp3     
    
    
    Family. Campfire. Pumpkins. And soon s'mores!! http://instagram.com/p/e0m22LCQd5/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Building Authority & Relevance with Your Keywords http://bit.ly/1haxT78  via @level343    
    
    
    FREE #ProjectManagement Webinar "Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013 - October 4 2013" http://kwikpmo-oct4-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Thank you #BryceBrown for great moves and #Eagles touchdown!    
    
    
    @LeilaAnsart sure, it's going to be Wed 10/23 this time for #ChescoMG. Will be focusing on WordPress sites.    
    
    
    @KHomnack @courtconigs need to stay off social media to not get spoilers! :)    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @Dannyschuit @ParentingAuthor    
    
    
    @jamminpsu nice bday gift for her!    
    
    
    Upgrade to HootSuite Pro - get 2 user access; manage multiple accounts/profiles. Starts at $9.99/mo http://ow.ly/pki80     
    
    
    New @MailChimp App In @HootSuite Brings Email and Social Media Marketing Together http://bit.ly/1hdR7ss     
    
    
    Rivalfox: Monitor competitors and create opportunities http://btl.st/1afy2or  via @BetaList    
    
    
    Thanks @Gazalla @BetaList for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Looking 2 get a Hangout panel of social media marketers to chat, Interested? @ChrisTuttle @jeffroach @nikkisunstrum @1ad_dad @goldiebrown78    
    
    
    @justkaela pick out some good fruit. Skip the laundry!! My $0.02!!    
    
    
    @JulieMPron you don't want to know my question for Siri!!! :) how've you been???    
    
    
    Definitely!! RT @liamdempsey: If Congress were a reality show, would it be possible to vote them all off in the first episode?    
    
    
    Looking 2 get a Hangout panel of social media marketers. Interested?? @NatMoraisBR @WilsonVA @ctmarcom @mastranj I'll send details later    
    
    
    Hundreds of baby spiders just born by our front door. Not happy. http://instagram.com/p/e5wlo1iQVZ/     
    
    
    @Coloredegghome yeah pretty creapy but amazed at how many spiders are in one egg sack!!    
    
    
    @ctmarcom yeah. Sometime! :) haven't thought that far ahead yet. Was just putting feelers out. I'll DM or email ideas later    
    
    
    @1ad_dad yes. I'll email you and others with ideas and we can all think about it. Been following good people for long, now next step :)    
    
    
    @Caleb_Mezzy not really sure yet. DM me your email as I was planning to touch base w people to think this through. Could be fun. U'd be good    
    
    
    Some great advice for your LinkedIn strategies when it comes to lead gen. 
http://lnkd.in/bdwDJrB     
    
    
    Thanks @Bri_Clark @ckw09 @TheGoToSite for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Are you a Buffer user yet? With this link we both get a bonus space for sharing Tweets and Facebook posts! http://bit.ly/17lJajw     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @evently    
    
    
    @jeffroach not really sure. was just getting some good people lined up. i plan on emailing you soon!    
    
    
    @nikkisunstrum that's ok. was just looking for some great people to all join in an open discussion, build connections. i see you are busy!    
    
    
    @JulieMPron yes, saw you updates from #TypeACon cool. i'm doing well. managing multiple clients, custom web analytics and some other work.    
    
    
    @jf_sheehan you can set the schedule of Buffer updates in the tool. Buffer is nice to not over tweet in a short time period.    
    
    
    @jf_sheehan if you have any questions, just tweet me.  I should write up a blog post about buffer :) if i do, i'll let you know.    
    
    
    Philly burbs: Building & Managing a #WordPress Site - Oct 23 6pm Pour House | Exton, PA more info/register at http://bit.ly/17lITNf     
    
    
    Heard someone is having a birthday today!! Everyone wish @NatMoraisBR a very #HappyBirthday!! (@mmbizon u should rt)    
    
    
    3 Essential Tips for Spying on #PPC Competition http://bit.ly/17lJ7Ec     
    
    
    Following &amp; following back on twitter is the first step of engagement, like a handshake. (Analogy borrowed from @ChrisTuttle) #sm4np    
    
    
    Checking out my "office coworkers" and what all are up to! (@ Barnes & Noble - @bnbuzz w/ @lgreenberg) http://4sq.com/19eRljU     
    
    
    Get Buffer to post with better timing to Twitter and Facebook. Sign up here and we both get extra features! http://bit.ly/1hgIdKN     
    
    
    Are you a Buffer user yet? With this link we both get a bonus space for sharing Tweets and Facebook posts! http://bit.ly/17lJdvq     
    
    
    Enable your #PMO with #ProjectServer 2013 - Webinar 10/4 11am ET http://www.vibrantfusion.com/wordpress/event/enable-pmo-project-server-2013-october-2013/ … #KwikPMO via @KwikPMO    
    
    
    The mother of all iOS 7 Tips and Tricks Guides. http://bit.ly/1dT7z1m  <-- great to read! lots of good tips!    
    
    
    Thanks @Bri_Clark @TheGoToSite @LoveMottos for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @KHomnack so.....coffee and chat later this week or next week? did you ever start a blog? and I know you're working a little now.    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @ckroks    
    
    
    Enable your PMO with Project Server 2013 (free webinar) – October 4th 2013 http://bit.ly/1731QkA  via @KwikPMO    
    
    
    #ChescoMG meeting of the minds! (at @PaneraBread w/ @chescomarketing) http://4sq.com/19ZaQcP     
    
    
    Attending @marketri seminar with @markwschaffer speaking. oct 9 Philly. http://marketri.ticketleap.com  http://tkt.ly/1bvUFFI  #ticketleap    
    
    
    @rutled17 i'll be at the event next week with @Marketri. see you there.    
    
    
    @WilsonVA woot woot!! #Sconda    
    
    
    @KHomnack yikes!! a naughty word hashtag from you! not sure i can have coffee with a person like that. f it, how's monday!? :)    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @highervis @RitasItalianIce @LisaStone    
    
    
    Thanks @WilsonVA @ctmarcom for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @h_nordlund @CjSkiLee @RPetrilloMktg    
    
    
    Taking my dad out for his bday lunch. (@ Victory Brewing Company w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/19pHUZj     
    
    
    Thanks @Bri_Clark @DaddyBookins @LoveMottos for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    An In-Depth look at Project Server 2013 and KwikPMO http://www.vibrantfusion.com/wordpress/event/in-depth-look-at-project-server-2013-kwikpmo/ … via @KwikPMO    
    
    
    Happy Friday!! Enjoy!!! @hamptonskiley @christuttle @KHomnack @pinkpearlpr @MarkkennedySEM @NikkiSunstrum @fashionpennpal @susie_parker    
    
    
    @hangonsloopyosu haha, yup.  McGahee bad in '03 National Title game, but as a new RB on Browns it's all good :)    
    
    
    An In-Depth look at Project Server 2013 and KwikPMO - Richmond, VA | Oct 16 9am-12pm FREE RSVP here: http://ow.ly/pvuMQ     
    
    
    Attending @Marketri Social Media Marketing Event with @markwschaffer speaking. #Philly Oct 9th | regsiter here --> http://marketri.ticketleap.com     
    
    
    Any fun Friday night plans??    
    
    
    It's Friday Happy Hour and I'm relaxing with a @BluecoatGin martini on the deck. Enjoyin the summer-like October evening in Philly burbs!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @mikejny @highervis @edwardnehls    
    
    
    It's time for #SaturdaySoccer!! I coach both of my kid's teams, games at 9 and 10:30am. Who else coaches soccer for their kids? #Dads    
    
    
    Soccer, sun and SWEAT! (@ Shamona Creek Elem. School) http://4sq.com/17FBRTW     
    
    
    Guys afternoon out!! (@ Victory Brewing Company) http://4sq.com/192a14D     
    
    
    Ice cream!!!!  Some of the best!!! (@ Chester Springs Creamery) http://4sq.com/17ataN0     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @MarcEnsign    
    
    
    @JasonFitch916 I did a few searches for soccer and found a few good drills for my 2/3 grade team. But a nice app is Soccer Dad!!    
    
    
    @mastranj haha. What is Denver up to now??    
    
    
    @aliphalen nice farm!    
    
    
    @mastranj wow. I'm missing a great game.    
    
    
    Check out these great infographics http://bit.ly/1fbmXcM  via @Ever_Post    
    
    
    An In-Depth look at Project Server 2013 & KwikPMO - Richmond, VA | Oct 16 9am-12pm FREE RSVP here: http://ow.ly/pvv4R  #ProjectServer    
    
    
    GA Experts: Google Content Experiments not tracking Transactions or Goals correctly. Any help??    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @Your_Say @savvybostonian @SHDickson    
    
    
    always cool to look at #TiltShift photos. http://bit.ly/1fbnOde  via @Ever_Post    
    
    
    @JeffTincher Make sure you you a PROFESSIONAL looking photo!! I've seen quite a few profile photos that loo... http://medl.it/eE2Xr     
    
    
    8 LinkedIn First-Time User Mistakes http://lnkd.in/bMeBjtE     
    
    
    @hootsuite_help i had email with 30 day trial of Hootsuite Univ and keep trying to apply it but never gets me past the billing screen    
    
    
    @HootSuite_Help i see the coupon showing -$21 and selected my name/account. but click Save Changes, says Success & takes to Dashboard.    
    
    
    @HootSuite_Help but if i go to the HSU url i can't seem to access.  I'll check later.    
    
    
    15 percent of Americans don't use the Internet at all!! [study] what do they do?? :) http://bit.ly/GE2Wxj     
    
    
    ✓ Read Internet Marketing Article(s): "Spent 30mins reading through Feedly. " https://www.lift.do/c/12415587     
    
    
    @douglasPscott exactly my point! :)  have a good night!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @ChesCoMarketing @mintblogger    
    
    
    Let your day be full of Victory! #victorybeer @ Victory Brewing Company http://instagram.com/p/fNLOPXiQUN/     
    
    
    Thanks @Bri_Clark @DaddyBookins @animationchefs for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Chrome just got a whole lot better (and more social) thanks to #hootlet: http://ow.ly/pD4iv     
    
    
    @tfurlong good parenting trick! i may have to use that on my kids :)    
    
    
    @PatsHoppedUp i once thought about mowing the lawn at night and then rescued a beer from the fridge instead ;-)    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @KeithKeller    
    
    
    Enough of boring presentations, bring on the animations with #powtoon! Create your own free animated PowToon http://bit.ly/19f3m58     
    
    
    @afmarcom Hi Angelique, it's been a while since we've last talked. I hope all is well! Have a great day :) (via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @FoundtheMarbles    
    
    
    @1ad_dad doing good.  hey, i still have to followup with you and a few other freelance/marketing pros about my Hangout idea! been busy :)    
    
    
    @1ad_dad i'm getting ready for my bi-weekly Google Hangout OnAir show for @ChesCoMarketing 1:30pm - http://bit.ly/ChescoMGOnAir  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    @1ad_dad yeah, today ET. in 30 mins.  it's about a local "Story Slam" and interviewing the founder of it. it's a great event he runs.    
    
    
    Thanks @ChesCoMarketing @FashionPennPal for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    She's finally giving me some #SweetAction tonight!! Whoop whoop! http://instagram.com/p/fTrTYfiQeb/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @CollectiveBias    
    
    
    Happy Friday! http://instagram.com/p/fUzwysiQW8/     
    
    
    @InTheKitchenKP haha. thanks! that image was going around a lot on instagram.  love it!!    
    
    
    An Interview with West Chester Story Slam founder, Jim Breslin http://bit.ly/15YV6cL  via @ChescoMarketing OnAir Show    
    
    
    Thanks @DaddyBookins @animationchefs @TheEricGraham for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.…    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @sdentrepreneur @pinkpearlpr @MsSonicFlare    
    
    
    Something is wrong with my wife, she won't let me cut her hair!! ;-)    
    
    
    I'm up to - Philadelphia at Tampa Bay (Oct 13, 5:00pm) http://upto.com/e/gLba     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @PaulDunay @DeniseWakeman    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @annagervai @simplystacienet    
    
    
    Thanks @nikkisunstrum @HamptonsKiley for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @marcusnelson    
    
    
    .@HamptonsKiley @nikkisunstrum glad to be in good company and top engaged on social :)  have a great week.    
    
    
    thx RT @LifeOfDadShow The Dads Know What's Up Daily is out! http://paper.li/lifeofdadshow/dads-ftw … ▸ Top stories today @benwakeling @tommyriles @JeffTincher    
    
    
    @HamptonsKiley sounds like a great and healthy way to start off the day! #Smoothies    
    
    
    In or near Chester Co., PA + want to learn about #WordPress? Come hear @liamdempsey speak to @ChesCoMarketing. http://bit.ly/19E4RtS     
    
    
    I'm at Barnes & Noble - @bnbuzz (Exton, PA) http://4sq.com/GPJkFX     
    
    
    Thanks @TheEricGraham @SuccessCoaching @CoziFamily for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.i…    
    
    
    Check out "Building & Managing Your #WordPress Site" Exton PA 10/23 $5 …http://wordpress-event-exton-pa-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @RecruitMoore @JennGHanford @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Upcoming #WordPress Event in Exton PA 10/23. Best Practices for Business, themes, plugins, tips & more!  #ChescoMG http://ow.ly/pS4IN     
    
    
    Morning meeting and planning (@ Barnes & Noble - @bnbuzz w/ @chescomarketing) http://4sq.com/1bWt83V     
    
    
    What is Considered a Low or High CTR by AdWords Professionals http://bit.ly/H3FHfc     
    
    
    Can Google+ for Businesses Compete with Facebook/Twitter? http://bit.ly/H3HyAT     
    
    
    Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, And YouTube Referrals Up 52%+ In Past Year [REPORT] http://bit.ly/H3I7KR     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @juliaserafina @evently @joePRguy    
    
    
    Thanks @douglasPscott @LifeOfDadShow for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    I just updated my Vizify bio. https://www.vizify.com/jefftincher     
    
    
    @JennGHanford thanks. i am having a great week!! hope yours is going well too!!    
    
    
    Get Ready for More 'Interest-Based' Facebook Ads in Your News Feed http://on.mash.to/16e02us   via @mashable #socialmedia     
    
    
    Exciting nighttime soccer game and in the rain. Kids rocked it!! (@ Fellowship Soccer Fields) http://4sq.com/1d0kKA9     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @jmgagnon    
    
    
    Thanks @TheEricGraham @The_Retro_Inc @SuccessCoaching for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commu…    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @KeithPunches    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Kids getting skylanders swap force with gift cards from bday. (@ Target w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/H5bRaP     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @storyspinner    
    
    
    Thanks @JennGHanford @BetaList for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Check out Building & Managing Your #WordPress Site this Wednesday in Exton PA. …http://wordpress-event-exton-pa-estw.eventbrite.com  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @iGoByDoc @bethanysimpson @BabySavers    
    
    
    @FashionPennPal hey there. wasn't sure if you could attend the ChescoMG event tmrw evening. thought I'd ask.    
    
    
    @douglasPscott see you out tomorrow evening.  should be a fun event and good times at the Pour House.    
    
    
    @NatMoraisBR @mmbizon just checking to see if you two were going to make the drive to Exton tomorrow evening. have 18 people signed up    
    
    
    Is Your Intern Or Your CEO the Most Influential Person in Your Company? http://sociallogical.com/blog/is-your-intern-or-your-ceo-the-most-influential-person-in-your-company/ … via @jeffroach    
    
    
    Thanks @ReachMktg @TopHRblog @TheEricGraham for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @NatMoraisBR yes maybe then :) I having a bucks mont meetup soon? I have 2 people in area that should attend. How r things?? Email me    
    
    
    @FashionPennPal well happy bday to both of them!!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @Barzhini    
    
    
    Upcoming Event in Exton: Build & Manage a WordPress Site | Oct 23 - http://eepurl.com/GZkg5     
    
    
    Pearl Jam gives Phily local kid best 'first concert' story ever!! http://po.st/lsnYfV  (so cool since he's a friend of ours!) #PearlJam    
    
    
    Building and Managing a WordPress Site tonight at 6pm in Exton PA - watch this --> http://youtu.be/BRRB1bJbKWg  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … ▸ Top stories today via @torbahax @AdobeSocial    
    
    
    @jamminpsu it's a great group and I really enjoy connecting people and giving advice. Thx for feedback :) @WilsonVA @ChesCoMarketing    
    
    
    @mmbizon yes it was a great event. I think 20 people and liams preso was great!    
    
    
    .@liamdempsey you're welcome. Good group and many people said it was great preso. Thx! @WilsonVA @ChesCoMarketing    
    
    
    Watch us LIVE & OnAir this morning at 10am (or so). We're talking about #WordPress and recapping our #ChescoMG event. http://bit.ly/ChescoMGOnAir     
    
    
    Thanks @ChesCoMarketing @liamdempsey for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @kevjkirkpatrick    
    
    
    Thanks @ReachMktg @TopHRblog @jmacofearth for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @PaulBiedermann @DebWeinstein    
    
    
    SOCCER SATURDAY! (@ Shamona Creek Elem. School w/ @lgreenberg) http://4sq.com/HnEXBY     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @GhostTweetings @RSVPPhilly    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @juliaserafina    
    
    
    Starbucks Wants You To Buy Your Friend A Coffee With A Tweet http://www.mediabistro.com/alltwitter/starbucks-tweet-a-coffee_b51017 … via @feedly    
    
    
    Eagles' Chip Kelly needs a reality check http://espn.go.com/blog/nfceast/post/_/id/58084/eagles-chip-kelly-needs-a-reality-check … via @feedly    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @netsuccess101 @DMurrow @locallylove    
    
    
    How to survey your site visitors with Google Consumer Surveys  via @justincutroni http://ow.ly/qgB2S     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @Navahk @ReachLocal @B2BMKTGInsider    
    
    
    @DreamHostCare i see that many sites having issues today. is the main Dreamhost . com site down as well?? can't access cpanel    
    
    
    @HollyChessman just getting back to twitter after a while away :) i'll take this survey    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @KYWNewsradio @prpeep    
    
    
    #Orion Free WordPress Theme: http://www.fabthemes.com/orion/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @SarahsBlogOfFun @iSocialTish    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @anyadowning @InfoSara @bullseyevideo    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @untappd    
    
    
    Here for a Marriott Timeshare event (@ Courtyard Marriott) http://4sq.com/1ax7OAJ     
    
    
    I'm at Victory Brewing Company (Downingtown, PA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/19qURGs     
    
    
    I thanked a veteran at Victory Brewing Co, Heinz donated to Wounded Warrior Project®. Learn more @ http://TurnToServe.com . #OurTurnToServe    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Thanks @WilsonVA @jamminpsu for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Thanks @TopHRblog @jmacofearth @The_Retro_Inc for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Thanks @douglasPscott @NatMoraisBR for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Thanks @TopHRblog @jmacofearth @Texasholly for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/D9Awt3  #in    
    
    
    http://bpt.me/511026  - Join us 11/21 at #ChescoMG event Exton PA "Learn How to Use Paid Search & PPC Advertising for your Small Business!"    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @ReachMktg @akstout18 @milesaustin    
    
    
    @davidianbrant Thank you for the RT earlier today! Have a good Tuesday.    
    
    
    Back to Season 3 of #TheTudors...2 epis left then final season.    
    
    
    How New Shopping Campaigns Are Giving PLAs A Jolt! http://bit.ly/1cJMB4d     
    
    
    Intro to #GoogleAdWords and #PPCMarketing on 11/21 in Exton PA  via @ChescoMarketing #ChescoMG http://ow.ly/quyVH     
    
    
    .@nikkisunstrum must be an exciting and nerve-wracking day. You have my support even though i can't #vote in MI. :)    
    
    
    Thanks @davidianbrant @BetaList for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    5 Google Analytics Updates that You Should Know About http://ow.ly/quD3A     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @jlisak @ckroks @CaddyMarketing    
    
    
    Thanks @FashionPennPal @ChesCoMarketing for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @douglasPscott thanks for the intro Mr Scott :)  @oboyorganic pls dm me and let's share email, etc to better communicate.    
    
    
    @douglasPscott @oboyorganic and hope you both can join us at the @ChesCoMarketing event on Thur Nov 21 at Unos in Exton/Lionville. AdWords!    
    
    
    @oboyorganic you can learn more at http://www.chescomarketing.com  or just ask me about #ChescoMG :)    
    
    
    it's already time to get the kids off the bus!?!  #WorkAtHomeDad #dads    
    
    
    Pre soccer pizza (@ Carmine's Parkside Pizza) http://4sq.com/1fn6D6m     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @techsavvymama    
    
    
    Thanks @katiesheadesign @TomReidy @lisabriercliffe for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.i…    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @PamelaJMyers @LaurenEHarper    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @TheBabyGuyNYC    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Thanks @nikkisunstrum @ctmarcom for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    You should join me at the #Philly #burbsWP Meetup in West Chester PA tonight. Check it out and RSVP! http://meetu.ps/22vXHn     
    
    
    @liamdempsey @JohnLauber @jamminpsu looking fw to seeing you at the #burbsWP event tonight.  where is a good place to park?    
    
    
    At the #burbsWP meetup for Wordpress (@ Ryan's Pub w/ @chescomarketing) http://4sq.com/1i2RvNL     
    
    
    Learning some great UI tips and "how to guide the eye" for web design and Wordpress sites. #wpBurbs #philly #wordpress.    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @LifeOfDadShow @PegFitzpatrick    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 34 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Thanks @katiesheadesign @TomReidy @gothamc for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Why Project Online? Or should we say “Why NOT”? FREE Webinar http://www.vibrantfusion.com/wordpress/event/why-project-online-or-should-we-say-why-not/ … via @KwikPMO    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @TheVAPassport @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Exton PA Event: Google AdWords 101 for Small Businesses + Business Neworking Happy Hour -- https://www.eventbrite.com/e/google-adwords-101-for-small-businesses-business-neworking-happy-hour-tickets-9282703817?ref=ecaltw …    
    
    
    @wcstoryslam appreciate the retweet!    
    
    
    @jamminpsu yes, i had to leave a little early. but it was good info at #burbsWP    
    
    
    ManageFlitter rocks at cleaning my Twitter account. Try it with this link and we both get 200 extra unfollows daily! http://bit.ly/18sHL8f     
    
    
    Localation: Monitor how your business is listed in online directories http://btl.st/18sK4I9  via @BetaList    
    
    
    Kid-less dinner. Some call it "date night dinner" (@ Umami Asian Bistro) http://4sq.com/HZ1JAt     
    
    
    If you'd like to save time managing contests & prize draws check this out & request your early-access invite http://bit.ly/1gKxU5Q     
    
    
        
    
    
    Exton PA Event: Google AdWords 101 for Small Businesses + Business Networking Happy Hour 11/21 6pm http://bit.ly/AdWordsExtonPA  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    @jetts31 hey there. Hope all is well. I really need to get back into these dad chats!! Every wed @ 10pm?? Can't do now.    
    
    
    @justkaela i know how much you like the flyers, so hope they turn things around soon. Hope you are well and feeling fine.    
    
    
    .@liamdempsey @Jimbrez @Ticketmaster first the high service charge, now an ad?? I'd be fine to watch an ad (or two) to NOT PAY service fee.    
    
    
    Fueling up. Gas and coffee (at @Wawa w/ @marchawkins) http://4sq.com/1icBS6m     
    
    
    Great hair salon on the mainline! (@ Tei Salon) [pic]: http://4sq.com/18wnVJ0     
    
    
    Thanks @LifeOfDadShow @jamminpsu for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Parent meeting about the new DASD math in focus program. What do you think about math in your child's school?? http://4sq.com/17Wo7ab     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @mikimarkovich    
    
    
    Exton PA Event: Google AdWords 101 for Small Businesses + Business Networking Happy Hour 11/21 6pm http://bit.ly/AdWordsExtonPA  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    @jetts31 great. thanks for that info! i hope to join in on #dadsrt next Wed!!  i'm doing ok. my soccer coaching season ended last saturday    
    
    
    @NotesFrom2Half hi there. thanks for asking the question about reader for blogs.  i have been using Feedly lately and really like    
    
    
    @oboyorganic recipe sounds great!!!    
    
    
    @jetts31 my 2-3 grade boys were undefeated :) League is more recreational and not about winning...but we did. just a good group of boys!!    
    
    
    @jetts31 you as well.  i'm adding to my calendar now :)    
    
    
    @jetts31 haha. i may have done that as well once or twice.    
    
    
    @emilylambert905 that is a good article about IG and what might work best.  it's all about "HOW" the image looks :)    
    
    
    always good to read how to optimize LinkedIn! RT @Marketri: 5 Easy Tips to Optimize Your #LinkedIn http://bit.ly/16MLqAn   via @SMMagic    
    
    
    @aswinn that's pretty cool. congrats on the book and in the mag.  i'm not flying American however.    
    
    
    Looking for a cool way to run viral contests and sweepstakes? Check out @comprized http://comprized.com/?lrRef=X29uRE     
    
    
    does your weekend include raking leaves?? I'm not looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @jmgagnon    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @ckroks @KeithPunches @NadiaGradwell    
    
    
    "Happy Birthday, Google Analytics!"  http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/PPCHero/~3/halj5nL3W8Q/ …    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @MalharBarai @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Check out the Chester County Marketing event on 11/21 in Exton, PA -- Google AdWords and Facebook Ads : https://google-adwords-exton-pa.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Thanks @JohnLauber @NatMoraisBR for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @aaronharclerode what are you doing on twitter??  :)  go away, lol    
    
    
    @oboyorganic thanks for the recipe.  i never got a chance to call you to catch up.  slammed today and tmrw. maybe later in week???    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @ckroks @emilythousand @jlisak    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @chrisfictoor @LovinDaLife    
    
    
    Hello, goobye...hello, goodbye...it's like a Beatles song with the constant FOLLOW me and UNFOLLOW 3 days later. too many tweetbots...    
    
    
    @jamminpsu just saw this and hope she gets well soon!!    
    
    
    @LifeOfDadShow yes. i stopped following people unless they are human :)  i have been swamped with client work that i don't tweet as much    
    
    
    @LifeOfDadShow going to try and join the #dadsrt chat tomorrow night at 9pm though!    
    
    
    @LeilaAnsart was checking in on twitter and saw your last tweet about Vella in exton! sounds excellent and this is NEWS to me :)    
    
    
    @LifeOfDadShow @dad2summit @NYCDadsGroup @homedadnet i may be down for that too!  i've got my 19 day beard going.  but started 10days ago    
    
    
    I'm at Starbucks (Exton, PA) http://4sq.com/17q0rIt     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Thanks @BetaList @billsebald for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    @mmbizon thanks for the tweets today!  are you going to try and make it? Have close to 20 people i think    
    
    
    @oboyorganic are you avail to call around 3pm?    
    
    
    @Gazalla thanks! will you be there?    
    
    
    @mmbizon well at least get a few strikes!!  i guess @NatMoraisBR won't make the drive by herself. :) see you both soon!! plan an event!    
    
    
    time for a 15 min #powernap  4 hours of sleep last night doesn't cut it!    
    
    
    @Gazalla you can pay at door the $5 if you want.  no worries    
    
    
    @mmbizon it sure is easier to say "strikes" than get one when bowling. good luck!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @mikejny @stephanies    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @CollectiveBias @CaddyMarketing    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @mikejny @JonMikelBailey    
    
    
    Dad/son lunch (at @Wendys) http://4sq.com/18zls4t     
    
    
    Poof! I just zapped 1 hr 43 mins off my daily tasks with @EasilyDo. You gotta check out this free app, too! http://ezly.do/Twtsaved     
    
    
    Join me on @untappd to discover new beers and locations! http://untappd.com/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @anyadowning @CollectiveBias    
    
    
    Thanks @WilsonVA @ChesCoMarketing for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 34 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @Shoutlet    
    
    
    Picking up our 25lb fresh turkey. 🍗🍗Gobble gobble (@ Loag's Corner Turkey Farm) http://4sq.com/1erbbrq     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 36 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just voted for @OhioStateFootball in @BigTenNetwork #Tiebreaker. Cast your vote now. http://www.btntiebreaker.com     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 30 F and Light Snow/Windy http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Opened my last bottle of Victory Dark Intrigue. Bought it 2 years ago and it has aged well, more… http://instagram.com/p/hRUJccCQY2/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @kevjkirkpatrick @TheResumeSmith    
    
    
    Here with Spider-Man a ninja and bomber pilot. (@ Liberty Union Bar & Grille) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1bvSo02     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @courtneyengle @BadRhinoINC    
    
    
    @theyearofelan haha, agree...you are a much better 'tweeter' than handwriter! thank you for the Thanksgiving Day humor. we all NEED it!!    
    
    
    @kirktim sounds like a great prediction! let do this, #GoBuckeyes #BuckeyeNation    
    
    
    Hi @liamdempsey thx for the thanksgiving tweet out! @ctmarcom @jamminpsu @WilsonVA @douglasPscott @yhurg @Jimbrez @PhillyMktgLabs    
    
    
    @ctmarcom thank you for the Thanksgiving tweet!! hope all is well and your dog enjoyed the day too :)    
    
    
    @NotesFrom2Half less than 2 hours! #GoBuckeyes #BuckeyeNation    
    
    
    @pjmccarthy63 hey PJ, hope your turkey turned out great again!  ours was fantastic!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @Jimbrez can't believe it's ONLY saturday! WOOT!!!  @liamdempsey @ctmarcom @jamminpsu @WilsonVA @douglasPscott @yhurg @PhillyMktgLabs    
    
    
        
    
    
    @NotesFrom2Half yup. heading to my Dad's house to watch with him. he's a 1968 #OSUAlum    
    
    
    3-Day #BlackFriday & #SmallBusinessSaturday Special - 50% OFF #CircuitOne Hands-on Driving Experience: http://eepurl.com/JFBlH     
    
    
    @mailchimp is the best way to mass edit a list to download, make changes in Excel and then upload again? Will it just overwrite members?    
    
    
    20 minutes to #Buckeyes game! Heading to watch with my Dad! #GoBuckeyes!    
    
    
    #ohiostate touchdown. #buckeyenation    
    
    
    63yd TD run by #BraxtonMiller #osu    
    
    
    %ichigan fu%ble turns into #ohiostate TD. Up 28-21.    
    
    
    @aswinn haha. For sure.    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @ADiSilvestro @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    24 and O-H http://instagram.com/p/hYTb2vCQQ0/     
    
    
    Circuit One Hands on Driving Experience Events http://www.circuit-1.com/upcoming-events/ … via @CircuitOne1    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @CollectiveBias @RigniteInc    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @daverosborough @amywhiggins    
    
    
    ChescoMG Holiday Gathering & Business Networking Event http://www.chescomarketing.com/event/chester-county-marketing-holiday-gathering-business-networking-event/ … via @ChescoMarketing    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @time2mrkt @guerrieo    
    
    
    Just got this Superfan sticker. Check out my 98 other stickers on #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1dPrFxf     
    
    
    Drool-worthy eats & real inspiration! #Chobani http://bit.ly/19gW7bY  #Chobani4Change    
    
    
    Chatting about our upcoming LinkedIn webinars (@ Cosi w/ @chescomarketing @prkinggarage) http://4sq.com/1g6KQCX     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @mikejny @SMMmagazine @MissyWard    
    
    
    Internet Marketing Dos and Donts during the holidays #hangoutonair w/ @ChesCoMarketing : http://youtu.be/OD9tVYDqEHs     
    
    
    @justkaela congrats!!!  have a great day!    
    
    
    @justkaela i bet! all the best!! Happy Holidays    
    
    
    Which do you prefer, Horse or Bull? http://on.fb.me/1d1bo3A  pic.twitter.com/74h8GIuuQ4    
    
    
    Afternoon luncheon and committee discussion about a great summer camp (@ ESF Winter Headquarters) http://4sq.com/1kfCo1B     
    
    
    #RIP Nelson Mandela -- dead at 95. http://bit.ly/1cdwF8d     
    
    
    @DadatworkNJ yup, i picked Bull and lamborghini as well :)    
    
    
    Putting Bigfoot to bed tonight! #dadsRT http://instagram.com/p/hj8MvjiQeg/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lunch meeting (@ Barnes & Noble - @bnbuzz) http://4sq.com/1eVDe2t     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 37 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @extoleinc    
    
    
    A few new #untappd badges this week. @ Grillin' & Chillin' http://instagram.com/p/hmrJ1siQXF/     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 36 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    O-H 12 hours until game time. Every game is a home game! #ohiostate #gobucks http://instagram.com/p/hnvNtJCQeJ/     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @aswinn my kids have dance parties every weekend with neighbor kids. Adults then have to watch their moves. Haha.    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 28 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @jeremarketer @tmj_phl_adv @UBtalkin    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 30 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks @mikejny @FashionPennPal for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 34 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @abonde @voziq    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Heavy Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Just updated my BrandYourself profile, do me a favor and let me know what you think! http://jefftincher.brandyourself.com/?utm_source=tsProfile …    
    
    
    Some good ideas for your Business Marketing plan in 2014 - http://klou.tt/1hi3f20u96d8x?n=1 …    
    
    
    Facebook vs Pinterest - which is top for sharing and ecomm? - http://klou.tt/17zxc88t21yjo?n=1 …    
    
    
    I gave @douglasPscott +K about Instagram on @klout http://klout.com/douglasPscott/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=17206 …    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    One fish, two fish, red fish, blue fish.  Thank you Dr Seuss for the great reminder! http://instagram.com/p/hwdn5wCQc0/     
    
    
    @Ommegangphilly sounds like a good time.    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @BigRyanPark @TinaCook @jdnorthwest    
    
    
    SAVE 50% on @CircuitOne1 Hands-on Driving Experience / Thompson International Speedway http://www.eventbrite.com/e/circuit-one-hands-on-driving-experience-thompson-international-speedway-registration-9446387399?aff=estw … via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Grow your business network next Wed at @ChescoMarketing's Holiday Event - it's FREE! 12/18 in Exton PA …http://chester-county-marketing-holiday-business-event.eventbrite.com/?aff=estw  #ChescoMG    
    
    
    Reform #ECPA: Tell the Government to Get a Warrant http://wh.gov/lBibY     
    
    
    @sharpbizopps sure does. How is your biz going? Happy holidays.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @DadsRoundTable A1 I volunteer as a youth soccer coach for both son/daughter teams. Great times & memories!! Also help at school #dadsRT    
    
    
    .@ThatJohnnyDude @vinzska I think #volunteer As coach is more about tchng kids respect, teamwrk & good sportsmanship. Than the game #dadsRT    
    
    
    Finally able to get a few tweets in during #dadsRT tonight. Haven't been on a chat in long time. Still in sons bedrm while he reads :)    
    
    
    @ThatJohnnyDude thanks john same to you. Been a long time!! #dadsRT    
    
    
        
    
    
    That's great!! RT @readbradthedad: A2: Volunteering gives me a chance to show mu #Kids what it means to serve and care for others.  #dadsrt    
    
    
    @DadsRoundTable hah that would be a good idea. #dadsrt    
    
    
    @TheJasonGreene same. I just finished coaching 15 2/3 graders. Biggest team and we did awesome. I enjoy teaching life skills THEN soccer :)    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @MelissaSChapman @Katadhin    
    
    
    @jillianbmele accident in upper Uwchlan Twp on little conestoga rd btwn Milford rd and Park Ln. Probably still closed; due to black ice.    
    
    
    Our #elfontheshelf just fell over and the kids noticed a tag on the elf! Probably should hv cut that off. But why hv tag in the 1st place?    
    
    
    SurveyMonkey donated $0.50 to Humane Society of the US when I took a survey. You can help too: http://contribute.surveymonkey.com/charity/humane-society … via @surveymonkey    
    
    
    @DavidsONDECK yep, heard some downed wires and accident this morning. wife had to detour around.    
    
    
    @DadsRoundTable @readbradthedad totally agree. saturday morning soccer fields are jammed in my area. sorry i had to drop off early last nt    
    
    
    @readbradthedad @vinzska i still coach 2/3 grade for my son's team. and asst with daughters 1st grade. lot of fun watching them learn & grow    
    
    
    Handwashing and Your Family's Health http://www.springtonmanorhsa.org/2013/12/handwashing-family-health/ …    
    
    
    #Orion Free WordPress Theme: http://www.fabthemes.com/orion/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @emilythousand @SteveHuff    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @BruceSallan @tmj_phl_adv @TOGOMedia    
    
    
    “@DanielSharkov: How to Increase Your Upload Speed for Hangouts http://goo.gl/bCOqiu  via @WebbyStation”. Going to give this a try. #hoa    
    
    
    @douglasPscott I hadn't been on Klout in a long time. Got an email about a few new things and checked it out. Btw u going to event on wed?    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 36 F and Wintry Mix http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
        
    
    
    How was your weekend?    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @DanielGHebert @FangFeng88    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    @NotesFrom2Half thanks, yes a fun weekend for us.    
    
    
    If anyone cares: my lips are SOOO chapped, i think rubbing with sandpaper would feel better!    
    
    
    @HamptonsKiley all good here! tackling many things this first 1/2 of day! crossing things off the "to do" list feels good    
    
    
    Did someone tweet that Tony Romo choked again during the final 5 mins of the game? haha, at least no change in NFC East standings #GoEagles!    
    
    
    @HamptonsKiley so hope you're day is going ok too.  we had a great weekend with family. celebrated early xmas with inlaws    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @LauraleeGuthrie @LinkedInExpert    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 27 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    @jamminpsu enjoy the wrestling meet. good luck to the team!    
    
    
    Snow covered roads in Chester springs / lionville area. Rt 100/rt 113  (@ Village of Eagle) http://ow.ly/293W7t     
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 30 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Redbox return (@ Acme) http://4sq.com/JEkACp     
    
    
    Holiday dinner event for client (@ M Restaurant - @mrestaurant_phl) http://4sq.com/J3zsJu     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @voziq    
    
    
    @MRestaurant_PHL yes, excellent dinner and service! great place.  Thank you. We were there for the Vibrant Fusion holiday dinner.    
    
    
    @AdriennFaklya @dad2summit @admrich thanks for the shout out Adrienn!    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @lightspanD @ariwinokur @tgwilson    
    
    
    I'm at @Wawa w/ @marchawkins http://4sq.com/19dYQc5     
    
    
        
    
    
    Dropping off $100 in food and cash donations raised at @ChescoMarketing Holiday event.Thanks to all that contributed! http://4sq.com/1dpbnWV     
    
    
    Thanks @AdriennFaklya @DadsRoundTable for being top engaged members in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Win $1000 in Facebook Ads! http://www.wishpond.com/sw/27085/reference?scid=64767&type=Merchant … via @Wishpond    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @voziq @soclogical @ReachLocal    
    
    
    Thanks @real7a for being top new follower in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Always have your stuff when you need it with @Dropbox. Sign up for free! https://db.tt/OFz6JfK     
    
    
        
    
    
    Real is crafted, authentic and simple. Just like yogurt should be. #Chobani http://cho.ba/1cbMAaZ  #Chobani4Change    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @AaronGoldman @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Loving @harvest for time tracking and invoicing! Try it out yourself and save $10 off your first month: http://try.hrv.st/2-71366?t     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @StevenRothberg    
    
    
    Thanks @KavalonThatsMe @G_Raab for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 32 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
    Have a Very Merry Christmas!! Santa came and kids enjoying the spirit of Christmas :) http://instagram.com/p/iWFpLHCQe7/     
    
    
    Santa did good, Brought the right Legos! #legochima #legofriends http://instagram.com/p/iWKTBWCQWW/     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @nathankievman @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 28 F and Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/D9Awt3  #in    
    
    
    @ctmarcom @WilsonVA @jamminpsu @douglasPscott @liamdempsey @Jimbrez @yhurg hope everyone had a great Xmas and good times!  we did. :)    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @StevenLJohnson @JonMikelBailey    
    
    
    Understanding Google Analytics Demographics & Interests Reports http://online-behavior.com/analytics/demographics … via @onbehavior    
    
    
    Thanks @TechUncensored @guidecentral for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @KeithPunches @sejournal    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @SocialMediaSean @tmj_phl_adv    
    
    
    Check out @chefsfeed, a food guide built by the best chefs in the country. DL the app free from iTunes: http://chefsfeed.com/app     
    
    
        
    
    
    Final: Eagles 24, Cowboys 22. K Orton (DAL) 30 of 46, 358yds, 2TD, 2INT L McCoy (PHI) 27 for 131yds. (ESPN) http://ift.tt/1cgdJVG  #Ph...    
    
    
    Thanks @liamdempsey for being top engaged member in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @Spredfast @McMurryTMG    
    
    
    @ColleenMook wow def a long time no tweet, haha. thanks for the tweet and touching base. I NEED to get blogging again!!    
    
    
    @ColleenMook what type of things were you "talking about me", with other bloggers, etc? I have a new site ready...but need to get writing.    
    
    
    @ColleenMook my plan is for http://TheHoppyDad.com  @TheHoppyDad  :) A mix of me -- a beer loving Dad that wants to be happy/hoppy :)    
    
    
    @ColleenMook oh and lastly...Have a Happy & Safe New Years! hope your enjoyed the holidays as well!    
    
    
    Have a Hoppy Brew Year!! #happybrewyear2014 #untappd #brew #beer #badge http://instagram.com/p/imUrp3iQQ5/     
    
    
    Bluehost, HostGator Among EIG Brands Hit by Massive New Year’s Eve Outage http://ow.ly/sbgYG     
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks @shop_philly @saramomof2 for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @B2BMKTGInsider    
    
    
    Check out "Circuit One Hands on Driving Experience/ Atlanta Motor Speedway" http://www.eventbrite.com/e/circuit-one-hands-on-driving-experience-atlanta-motor-speedway-registration-9537604231?aff=estw … via @CircuitOne1 #circuitone #Atlanta    
    
    
    Need more coffee (at @Wawa) http://4sq.com/1dWH7Db     
    
    
    Thanks @douglasPscott for being top engaged member in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 28 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @mPortray @courtneyengle    
    
    
    Is that #snow in Exton? #ChesterCounty // 14 F and Light Snow http://wxch.nl/Je1U5Z     
    
    
    Thanks @tinastullracing @BermudaScooter for being top new followers in my community this week (insight via http://commun.it )    
    
    
        
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @MeganLeap @jmgagnon @aknecht    
    
    
    This is definitely the time to head to target. No one is really here yet! (@ Target) http://4sq.com/1e4WZ6x     
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm at Birchrunville Store Cafe (PA) http://4sq.com/1dlowiL     
    
    
    Spreading Social News is out! http://paper.li/JeffTincher/1321284805 … Stories via @tuxmiller @guerrieo @KlaudiaJurewicz    
    
    
    