TCF: Playing with My Christmas Presents--Retrieving Nicaea: Times, they do not change that much! Here I ... http://bit.ly/YVgmqp  <--More    
    
    
    Anglikanische Nonnen treten zur katholischen Kirche über http://www.kath.net/detail.php?id=39516 … @KatholikenNet #newevangelization    
    
    
    Happy 10th day of #Christmas & feast of the Holy Name of Jesus, the name above every other name! (Philippians 2:5-11)    
    
    
    DYK: 2013 is the first year with four consecutive integers (not in any particular order) since 1432?    
    
    
    "Unnecessary and ill-advised"? http://dailycaller.com/2013/01/03/obama-calls-ndaa-conscience-clause-for-military-chaplains-unnecessary-and-ill-advised/ … After this from Feb. http://www.theblaze.com/stories/u-s-military-silences-catholic-chaplains-from-speaking-out-against-obama-admin-ruling/ … extra measures are necessary and well-advised.    
    
    
    @GRMcDermott Excellent article!    
    
    
    Intelligent commentary #FF @GRMcDermott @matthewschmitz @catholicthing @PublicDiscourse @DouthatNYT @MarkSteynOnline @fbeckwith @ericmetaxas    
    
    
    #FF (quite obviously) @Pontifex    
    
    
    Happy 11th day of #Christmas and feast of St. Elizabeth Ann Seton, who created the first free Catholic school in U.S. http://www.catholic.org/saints/saint.php?saint_id=180 …    
    
    
    Pouring milk in the cereal before praying the blessing. #CatholicProblems    
    
    
    TCF: New Look to the Blog; Sacred Music Playlist Returns: Happy 11th day of Christmas, dear readers!Well... http://bit.ly/ZlPxjW  <--More    
    
    
    @preachermancp Reconciliation is important because of the validity of their orders and because their pastors have led sheep from the fold.    
    
    
    Outrageous: Nurses Fired for Refusing Flu Shot - Yahoo! News http://news.yahoo.com/nurses-fired-refusing-flu-shot-224637902--abc-news-health.html …    
    
    
    Happy 12th day of #Christmas and feast of St. John Neumann, who was a priest in Buffalo and Pittsburgh in the 1800s. #Epiphany is tomorrow!    
    
    
    Child support claim rankles sperm donor to lesbian pair: http://www.ruthblog.org/2013/01/05/child-support-claim-rankles-sperm-donor-to-lesbian-couple/ … Can anyone else see that children are victims in this society?    
    
    
    TCF: Commercial: Notre Dame's Former Coach, Faithful Catholic Lou Holtz, with an Invitation: Something t... http://bit.ly/WlnTfX  <--More    
    
    
    TCF: Adopt a Twerp - A Prayer Project to Assist the Holy Father, @Pontifex, on Twitter: Here at The Char... http://bit.ly/V0olo0  <--More    
    
    
    10 surprising quotes from abortionists http://liveactionnews.org/10-surprising-quotes-from-abortionists/ … #cultureofdeath    
    
    
    Please consider sharing this, @alwayscatholic @CatholicLisa @tom_perna @AmericanPapist http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/adopt-twerp-prayer-project-to-assist.html#.UOrGvWx5Ns4.twitter … God bless!    
    
    
    @youne090864 Yes. I saw your message to the Pope, and I will pray for your discernment of the priesthood.    
    
    
    Our Lady of Victory, Pray for us! First Things Tribute to Our Lady and to Her Team http://www.firstthings.com/onthesquare/2013/01/notre-dame-our-lady …    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict with a Shout Out to Hobby Lobby?: With this latest Tweet, I think obviously of Hobby ... http://bit.ly/WqzZ7u  <--More    
    
    
    @tom_perna Congrats, Tom! Many blessings to you and your students!    
    
    
    TCF: More on the Twerps: They Might Be Searching for God: More on the Church-meets-Twitter phenomenon. D... http://bit.ly/XLj9Hr  <--More    
    
    
    @MCardaronella With you, bro! http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/adopt-twerp-prayer-project-to-assist.html …    
    
    
    TCF: The Twerps Are Quick, Can You Be Quicker?--Please Re-Tweet!: There is a lot of love being shown to ... http://bit.ly/ZtxzHy  <--More    
    
    
    MT @Newman_Society New CUA business school rooted in Catholic social doctrine , natural law http://wp.me/pVkso-4fZ     
    
    
    TCF: Ironic March for Life Promo Video: March for Life, 2013, how I wish I could be there! But I will be... http://bit.ly/ZE1U6l  <--More    
    
    
    If #Michigan loses to Ohio State, #Duke should retain its No. 1 ranking. Duke beat #Louisville head-to-head and has played tougher schedule.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx We are about to freeze here in Southern Cal. Pray that our strawberries and oranges survive. Could cause fruit prices to rise.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Yes, I have been keeping track. You are quite right about that.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Oh, no! Good thing for our healthy economy. Wait ... never mind.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx What's weird is that 30 miles down the coast, it's 15 degrees warmer right now.    
    
    
    Church Fathers answer question: "Why did Jesus insist on being baptized?" http://insightscoop.typepad.com/2004/2013/01/church-fathers-answer-the-question-why-did-jesus-insist-on-being-baptized.html … @ignatiusinsight Happy feast of the baptism!    
    
    
    Planned Parenthood quietly abandons ‘pro-choice’ http://goo.gl/HnJpI  Hmm. Will they keep "anti-choice zealots" in their rhetorical arsenal?    
    
    
    Deaf Twins Going Blind Euthanized: Yahoo http://news.yahoo.com/deaf-twins-going-blind-euthanized-165500992--abc-news-topstories.html … Next in state-sanctioned murder for Belgium: dementia patients and children    
    
    
    TCF: Speaking of Irony: "The Guardian" Challenges Moral Norms concerning Pedophilia - #dictatorshipofrel... http://bit.ly/103RWAa  <--More    
    
    
    TCF: Prayers and Help Needed for Continued Medical Care of Haitian Priest (Please Share and Re-Tweet): T... http://bit.ly/UpZnN7  <--More    
    
    
    6 Reasons Why Men Can Speak on #Abortion http://shar.es/49WFe     
    
    
    MT @PublicDiscourse “The rights of children trump the right to children”: Lessons from France on Defending #Marriage: http://www.thepublicdiscourse.com/2013/01/7601/     
    
    
    @OlafTyaransen Money feeds no one, only acts of service and love, i.e., the Church's constant mission. The Church is the wealth of the poor.    
    
    
    @atheistpunk Money feeds no one, only acts of service and love, i.e., the Church's constant mission. The Church is the wealth of the poor.    
    
    
    Advocating for the poor by trolling the Pope on Twitter? #logicfail    
    
    
    @atheistpunk False. Plus, if that's all you think the Pope does or says to Africa, then here is some assigned reading. http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&rct=j&q=&esrc=s&source=web&cd=1&cad=rja&ved=0CDUQFjAA&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vatican.va%2Fholy_father%2Fbenedict_xvi%2Fapost_exhortations%2Fdocuments%2Fhf_ben-xvi_exh_20111119_africae-munus_en.html&ei=-bn2UMX3CaqTiAL_sYD4DQ&usg=AFQjCNGIcr-w2FWP9-Q7M5G3yZJliwDspA&sig2=2H9i-mPbr9WF2ytZ9KiZOw&bvm=bv.41018144,d.cGE …    
    
    
    @HomefryDaddy @atheistpunk Buying food does not guarantee that bellies will be fed. (Thus, the Church's ministry of feeding the hungry.)    
    
    
    @atheistpunk @HomefryDaddy Your own bellies are bloated on the atheist narrative. Catholics feed more hungry than do any groups combined.    
    
    
    "Religious Freedom Day" today? 1 year after HHS mandate, will we celebrate Jan. 20 as take-away-religious-freedom-day? http://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2013/01/16/presidential-proclamation-religious-freedom-day#.UPdHGk7dC_g.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Twitter Habet Papam! Pope Opens Account for Tweeting in Latin: For a second there, I forgot it was ... http://bit.ly/SaXftQ  <--More    
    
    
    #FF #Catholic @Pontifex_ln    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns Unforgiven Debt    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns The Great Taxpayer Robbery    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns Young Guns, Old Guns, Knock, Knock, Give Us Your Guns    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns California Conquest (Actually, that's it's real name.)    
    
    
    TCF: St. Athanasius on the Self-Effacement of St. Anthony of the Desert: TCF Quoteboard: As I read the w... http://bit.ly/13QWWXS  <--More    
    
    
    Steyn: Trillion-Dollar-Coin Fever: Has America’s choo-choo jumped the tracks? http://www.nationalreview.com/articles/338110/trillion-dollar-coin-fever-mark-steyn … via @NRO @MarkSteynOnline    
    
    
    See? #Duke should have been #1. Now that #Louisville and #Indiana have gone down, that little polling error should be fixed. @dukeblueplanet    
    
    
    Do you have a garden, @DanielGarlandJr? RT @PhilosophyQuotz If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need. Cicero    
    
    
    @DanielGarlandJr Cicero was before scotch, so we can hardly fault him for the glaring omission.    
    
    
    Charities to boycott: Comic Relief, Eagles Clubs, Elks Clubs, Elton John AIDS Foundation, and the Red Cross http://www.lifenews.com/2011/09/12/pro-life-group-lists-companies-backing-planned-parenthood/ …    
    
    
    TCF: Viva Latina! First Papal Tweet in Angelic Tongue: @Pontifex_ln - first Latin Tweet! How cool is thi... http://bit.ly/T80oN0  <--More    
    
    
    Mandatory American reading: #MLK's Letter from a Birmingham Jail http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/02/patriotism-wrote-letter-patriotism.html#.UP11Nvmw5lM.twitter … #civildisobedience    
    
    
    Happy feast of St. Agnes, a lamb for Christ! Listen to Mike Aquilina on her life | St Paul Center for Biblical Theology http://www.salvationhistory.com/blog/st._agnes_a_lamb_for/#.UP13J0rdxme.twitter …    
    
    
    Obama Begins Inauguration Festivities With Ceremonial Drone Flyover http://onion.com/11MpnI7  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Viva la France! RT @TweetSmarter Should Google & Facebook be taxed for collecting your personal data? http://tnw.co/Vl772W     
    
    
    40 years of abortion on demand is not working. Time for a change:  Recognize the natural rights of the unborn today! Retweet if you agree.    
    
    
    MT @NCRegister Mother Teresa: "The greatest destroyer of peace today is #abortion because it is a war against the child." #prolife #Roe40    
    
    
    40  years of abortion on demand is 40 years too many. Be a #voiceforthevoiceless! Recognize the natural rights of the unborn today! #Roeat40    
    
    
    Two women are behind legalized #abortion in America: now both of them want it reversed: #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/two-women-legalized-abortion-in-america-now-both-of-them-want-it-reversed … #roeat40    
    
    
    Bishop Burbidge disallows EMHC’s from giving blessings during Communion http://www.splendoroftruth.com/curtjester/2013/01/bishop-burbidge-disallows-emhcs-from-giving-blessings-during-communion/ … via @curtjester    
    
    
    Mandatory viewing for #RoeAt40 http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/05/be-sufficiently-warned-but-you-must.html#.UP-XDSoqfR8.twitter … Some have done much wrong, others too little right; we all bear the guilt of our nation.    
    
    
    Reclaiming the Human Center of the Abortion Debate: http://youtu.be/dawFw_fPCw8  #RoeAt40    
    
    
    Recommended reading for #RoeAt40: Robert Spitzer's brilliant Ten Universal Principles  http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/05/strongly-recommended-ten-universal.html#.UP-cWE-J-MM.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Video:  New Evidences the Gospels were Based on Eyewitness Accounts (Dr. Peter Williams): Next time... http://bit.ly/UTzVzG  <--More    
    
    
    @tom_perna @StevenErtelt Tolerant to those who agree with them. Leftists (closet socialists) preach but do not practice democratic ideals.    
    
    
    My wife and I were talking about this last night. Glad to find this Moynihan article: Benedict Stands on the Ramparts http://catholicexchange.com/benedict-stands-on-the-ramparts/#.UQE0Tja3UJ8.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican celebrates 30 anniversary of Code of Canon Law, the work that "will never be complete" http://www.romereports.com/palio/vatican-celebrates-30-anniversary-of-code-of-canon-law-english-8816.html#.UQE2SIyGMJY.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Scuzziest Pro-Abortion Video Ever Brings the Exploitive Nature of Abortion into Sharp Relief: Kudos... http://bit.ly/10QJzZf  <--More    
    
    
    Scuzziest Pro-Abortion Video Ever Brings the Exploitive Nature of #Abortion into Sharp Relief http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/scuzziest-pro-abortion-video-ever.html#.UQKzqCddpMs.twitter … Today, #MarchforLife!    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ Seems an interesting testament to the role sanctifying grace plays in recognizing the gravity of the loss of innocent life.    
    
    
    I wish I were tweeting from the #MarchforLife! Instead, I'm offering work and prayers for the 500K+ marchers. Grace, peace, strength to you!    
    
    
    TCF: @Pontifex Joins #MarchforLife from Afar: Pope Benedict XVI Tweets to Marchers: No doubt a day in U.... http://bit.ly/TzBA0n  <--More    
    
    
    KC's Bishop Finn: National Catholic Reporter not a "Catholic" publication: The Catholic Key http://catholickey.org/2013/01/25/the-bishops-role-in-fostering-the-mission-of-the-catholic-media/ … Why no coverage by N_R?    
    
    
    More: @NCRonline not a 'Catholic' publication, says KC bishop: Catholic Culture http://shar.es/C61hm     
    
    
    1 More @NCRonline RT @fatherz Bp. Finn calls out the National Catholic Reporter: http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/01/bp-finn-calls-out-the-national-catholic-reporter/ … … #catholic #fishwrap #dissent #tcot    
    
    
    No bus stop in DC this time! MT @FatherZ #MarchforLife: Where was NCR? LCWR? Nuns on Bus? CHA? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/01/follow-up-march-for-life-where-was-ncr-lcwr-nuns-on-bus-cha/ … #abortion    
    
    
    Canonist Peters on His Excellency Finn's rebuke of N_R. Curious silence on the news from @NCRonline. http://canonlawblog.wordpress.com/2013/01/25/recognizing-the-national-catholic-reporter-for-what-it-is-actually-for-what-it-isnt/ … Hat tip @fatherz    
    
    
    Stan the Man - The True Face of Sportsmanship http://www.catholiceducation.org/articles/stories_of_faith_and_character/cs0585.htm …    
    
    
    Stopped in Taco Bell for first time in 4 years or so. Remembered why I have not gone to Taco Bell in 4 years or so.    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Gratias tibi, Sancte Pater, pro bona verba tuum. Oramus pro te quotidie. Ora pro nobis. Ora pro America.    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Thank you also for your many texts. My favorite was Behold the Pierced One. I also reviewed your Jesus of Nazareth for Zenit.    
    
    
    Happy feast day, @lukei4655!    
    
    
    Prayer of St. Thomas Aquinas Before Study http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/08/prayer-of-st-thomas-aquinas-before-study.html?spref=tw … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    TCF: St. Thomas Aquinas: True Liturgist: Happy feast day of St. Thomas Aquinas, particularly to all Domi... http://bit.ly/T0UtaY  <--More    
    
    
    Oregon Doctor Pushes Depressed Patient Into Assisted Suicide http://www.lifenews.com/2013/01/29/oregon-doctor-pushes-depressed-patient-into-assisted-suicide/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    Complaint: #Sebelius’ illegal campaign trip for Obama worse than we thought http://bit.ly/WBTtY6#.UQoT3ATOQ70.twitter … via @DCExaminer #HHS    
    
    
    Video: Why Can't Women Be Priests? An Explanation from the Theologian of the Papal Household http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/why-can.html#.UQvXoMqg1M0.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    @alwayscatholic Thank you for sharing! God bless you!    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln "... melior est enim obedientia quam victimæ, et auscultare magis quam offerre adipem arietum."    
    
    
    #WSJ: America's Baby Bust http://on.wsj.com/WJex1Q  via @WSJ #demographics #contraception #parenting #economics FYI: Parenting makes me happy!    
    
    
    @ericmetaxas I was disappointed to see that they have unfortunately taken a polemical turn of late. http://blog.abolishhumanabortion.com/2013/01/an-open-letter-to-pro-life-roman.html …    
    
    
    @ericmetaxas follow-up on prvs: We should unite in our common pursuit for the sake of life, and not pick at centuries-old doctrinal wounds.    
    
    
    TCF: Update on Haitian Priest: Fr. Dumas and a Request for Prayers: Fr. Dumas, whose story was shared he... http://bit.ly/VIhSwO  <--More    
    
    
    @Peets_Tweets 49ers: 29, Ravens: 24    
    
    
    @TinoTarango @CatholicLisa @RJGrigaitis Excellent!    
    
    
    Observations from tonight: Harbaugh has great meltdowns, Kaepernick looks like Megamind, hid children's eyes from Beyonce's soft porn show.    
    
    
    More observations: Commercials are making the #Superbowl an adults-only affair. The demonic and sexually explicit more in-the-face than ever    
    
    
    Oh the rows of days past over this or that religious ad! Tonight: voodoo curses, soul-selling (w/ Latin contract), and lots of fornication.    
    
    
    @TeDeumBlog She became a stumbling block for young women everywhere. Very disappointing.    
    
    
    @friarpark Bud Light's Voodoo commercials (I think there were at least three different ones) and Mercedes-Benz's string of commercials.    
    
    
    Was very impressed by #Kaepernick's play and the #49ers heart. Too much #Flacco. Congrats to the #Ravens and to #Birk, #Lewis, #Reed & crew!    
    
    
    Schoolboy, 7, playing imaginary game gets suspended http://on.kdvr.com/WPQ3FRS  An era without common sense. Save our world, little man! Save on!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MarcelLeJeune Preach! Adult entertainment = good scotch, good cigar, good conversation    
    
    
    #Jesuit high school's beautiful chapel renovation! http://seeingtheform.wordpress.com/2013/01/09/sacred-heart-chapel-tampa-fl/ … #sacredart #sacredarchitecture #newevangelization    
    
    
    Opinion on the services to bury Richard III "he must now be given a Catholic funeral Mass" | http://CatholicHerald.co.uk  http://www.catholicherald.co.uk/commentandblogs/2013/02/06/i-dont-mind-where-they-bury-richard-iii-but-having-been-denied-christian-burial-by-henry-tudor-he-must-now-be-given-a-catholic-funeral-mass/#.UROrNaNSOXo.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican's Head of Family Council, says his words about homosexuals were manipulated http://www.romereports.com/palio/vaticans-head-of-family-council-says-his-words-about-homosexuals-were-manipulated-english-8942.html#.URPbBwQE3o4.twitter …    
    
    
    Kardinal Meisner übt schwere Kritik an 'Katholikenphobie' http://www.kath.net/detail.php?id=39997 … via @KatholikenNet    
    
    
    Historic #canonization! Pope to announce elevation of 800+ #saints http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-will-announce-on-monday-date-for-canonization-for-over-800-saints-english-8965.html#.URZ7P0K4-9I.twitter … Best line: "John Paul II ... elevated 'only' 482"    
    
    
    #Prayers requested for a sick loved one and caretakers. Thank you!    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father, for your service to Holy Mother Church. Please count on our prayers.    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict Announces He is Resigning Effective Feb. 28: I am in shock, still hoping I am going t... http://bit.ly/126LnxG  <--More    
    
    
    I would encourage everyone, out of reverence to our current Holy Father, to wait for all the "next pope" talk until his seat is vacant.    
    
    
    Cardinal Dolan on Benedict’s Resignation http://shar.es/YG01g  via @firstthingsmag    
    
    
    Conclave apparently will be on March 18.    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father, for your service. When you retreat into prayer next month will you please pray for me and for my family?    
    
    
    No delay in hostility expressed against the Pope by media, spinning according to their narrative. #unsurprising #insensitive #ignoringthem    
    
    
    This is not the end of the world--maybe. Good article on St. Malachy And The Papal Prophecies by @DanielGarlandJr http://irishanddangerous.blogspot.com/2007/10/st-malachy-and-papal-prophecies.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The Sacred Page: Scott Hahn on the Pope's Resignation http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/02/scott-hahn-on-popes-resignation.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    CNS: Professor-Pope Resigns http://bsfurl.com/10X8K/1RsU/Sl0  "Champion of Catholic Education Renewal"    
    
    
    The unexpected announcement that rang out in the Concistory Hall via L'Osservatore Romano http://shar.es/Y6v4h     
    
    
    A sign that we should pray for the Church: Lightning strikes St. Peter's this afternoon via ANSA.it http://www.ansa.it/web/notizie/rubriche/politica/2013/02/11/Benedetto-XVI-lascia-pontificato-Papa-dimette-28-febbraio_8225601.html?idPhoto=1 … via @ansa_topnews    
    
    
    MT Germany's banning homeschooling doesn't violate rights: U.S. Attorney General’s office: LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/banning-homeschooling-does-not-violate-rights-u.s.-attorney-generals-office … #socialism    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln We are praying for you, Holy Father. May God reward you abundantly for your humble service to the Church.    
    
    
    More on the #lightning strike(s): Lightning bolt hit Vatican not once but TWICE hours after Pope's resignation http://mirr.im/X92PuJ     
    
    
    The reality of the end of the papacy of Pope Benedict XVI is starting to sink in. Until Christ comes, there will never be another like him.    
    
    
    Must-read: The Reluctant Pope http://amsp.ec/1Sbw6V  #dictatorshipofrelativism    
    
    
    Must-must read from Dr. Hahn: Benedict Will Still Be There for Us: http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/benedict-will-still-be-there-for-us …    
    
    
    "The Lord is victorious" - Pope Benedict chats about Second Vatican Council with priests of Rome http://en.radiovaticana.va/news/2013/02/14/pope_to_rome%27s_priests:_the_second_vatican_council,_as_i_saw_it/en1-664858 …    
    
    
    Will there be an encyclical on faith as had been planned? http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/1300685.htm?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Rutler: Benedict’s Decision in the Light of Eternity | Crisis Magazine http://www.crisismagazine.com/2013/benedicts-decision-in-the-light-of-eternity#.UR6HqQaHPEA.twitter …    
    
    
    Cardinals will cease tweeting during the sacred Vatican conclave http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/1300682.htm?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Just started studying French a few weeks ago and am enjoying it much! Using the book "French for Reading" http://www.amazon.com/French-Reading-Karl-C-Sandberg/dp/0133316033/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&qid=1361044108&sr=8-1&keywords=french+for+reading …    
    
    
    Braut des Lammes: Ad completorium –  noch zum Rücktritt Papst Benedi... http://brautdeslammes.blogspot.com/2013/02/ad-completorium-noch-zum-rucktritt.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    De Ratzinger à Benoît XVI, itinéraire en images | http://La-Croix.com  http://www.la-croix.com/Religion/Actualite/De-Ratzinger-a-Benoit-XVI-itineraire-en-images-_NG_-2013-02-12-497073#.USBphRF1Ahw.twitter …    
    
    
    Benoît XVI, le pontificat en images | http://La-Croix.com  http://www.la-croix.com/Religion/Actualite/Benoit-XVI-le-pontificat-en-images-_NG_-2013-02-12-496969#.USBsQY4iy1I.twitter …    
    
    
    Catholic-bashers have embellished the truth about abuse in Catholic institutions. Time to put the record straight http://soc.li/8AVmfmS     
    
    
    MT St. Alphonsus Ligouri's letter prior to election of new pope: Fr. Z's Blog http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/a-saint-on-the-wretched-condition-of-the-church-while-waiting-for-a-new-pope-to-be-elected/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    6 Liturgical No-No's During Lent |Blogs | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/blog/jimmy-akin/6-liturgical-no-nos-during-lent …    
    
    
    Jesuit expert calls Benedict 'great reformer' on sex abuse | National _ Reporter: http://ncronline.org/blogs/ncr-today/jesuit-expert-calls-benedict-great-reformer-sex-abuse#.USJgXffJAZc.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict Comments on Resignation from Light of the World: It is difficult to comprehend that t... http://bit.ly/UAgRsz  <--More    
    
    
    POLL: What name will the next Pope choose? | Fr. Z's Blog – What Does The Prayer Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/poll-what-name-will-the-next-pope-choose/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Web surfing for long periods of time can cause withdrawal symptoms 'similar to people on a comedown from ecstasy' http://bit.ly/XTbXqw     
    
    
    RT Wherein Fr. Z makes a suggestion to Cardinal Electors http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/wherein-fr-z-makes-a-suggestion-to-cardinal-electors/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    #2BXVI Thank you for your constant service to the Church! God has made a great name for you, and you will always be our Papa Benedetto!    
    
    
    More on #Benedict’s revolutionary act: his astonishing predictions | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/blog/more-on-benedicts-revolutionary-act-his-astonishing-predictions …    
    
    
    Get some rest, says @roccopalmo. Big week ahead. "The Calm Before..." http://whispersintheloggia.blogspot.com/2013/02/the-calm-before.html …    
    
    
    "He is the hand that God stretches out to man" - The Holy Father's Angelus on Jesus' temptations. http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/benedict_xvi/angelus/2013/documents/hf_ben-xvi_ang_20130217_en.html …    
    
    
    TCF: For Your Lenten Motivation: Words On Penance from Pope Benedict: This is from Light of the World,... http://bit.ly/XFMvDG  <--More    
    
    
    #SongsThatWillNeverGetOld Te Deum. Pange Lingua. Veni Creator Spiritus. Ave Maria. #tRCot    
    
    
    Just watched Food Inc. Never eating again.    
    
    
    God, after Food Inc, in night's Divine Office: "You have put into my heart a greater joy than they have from abundance of corn and new wine"    
    
    
    Colorado bishop: National Catholic Reporter ‘is an embarrassment to the #Catholic Church’ | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/colorado-bishop-national-catholic-reporter-is-an-embarrassment-to-the-catho …    
    
    
    Pope's last Angelus: "The Lord is calling me 'out to the mountain' ... this does not mean I'm abandoning the Church." http://www.romereports.com/palio/popes-last-angelus-i-will-not-abandon-the-church-i-will-serve-in-a-different-way-english-9145.html#.USo7XDoNc9I.twitter …    
    
    
    Pope's Address At Conclusion of Lenten Spiritual Exercises | ZENIT http://www.zenit.org/en/articles/pope-s-address-at-conclusion-of-lenten-spiritual-exercises … #λογος #verbum #ars #beauty    
    
    
    Extraordinary Ministers of Communion giving blessings as if they were priests http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/quaeritur-extraordinary-ministers-of-communion-giving-blessings-as-if-they-were-priests/ … via @FatherZ See also Vatican letter    
    
    
    My #AdoptACardinal - His Eminence Anthony Olubunmi Cardinal Okogie, Archbishop Emeritus of Lagos, Nigeria http://adoptacardinal.org     
    
    
    The Pope's final general audience address to the English-speaking pilgrims http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/benedict_xvi/audiences/2013/documents/hf_ben-xvi_aud_20130227_en.html …    
    
    
    Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--English http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of.html#.US5CIT5_E-U.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--Latin http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of_27.html#.US5CO-fkBQY.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    Benedict XVI's most memorable moments with world leaders http://www.romereports.com/palio/benedict-xvis-most-memorable-moments-with-world-leaders-english-9183.html?utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=twitterfeed#.US5aEGa5fCY.twitter …    
    
    
    Partial Indulgence: Let us pray for our Pontiff, Pope Benedict http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/v-let-us-pray-for-our-pontiff-pope-benedict/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    "Anyone who has discovered Christ must lead others to him. A great joy cannot be kept to oneself. It has to be passed on." Pope Benedict XVI    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father. You will always be my Pope! God grant you your well-deserved peace for the remainder of your days!    
    
    
    #THANKSPONTIFEX In a couple of hours, he may no longer be the Holy Father, but he will always be our Pope!    
    
    
    #ThanksPontifex for your leadership and faithfulness to Him who calls. #Interregnum Come Holy Spirit!    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--Latin: Since the Vatican says that his Twitter ... http://bit.ly/YKqtBc  <--More    
    
    
    RT, please. Pope Benedict XVI, Complete List of Latin Papal Tweets http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of_27.html#.US_bsB4dldE.twitter …    
    
    
    RT, please. Glad I saved these-His tweets are deleted already! Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Eng. Papal Tweets http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of.html#.US_dUnezW7k.twitter …    
    
    
    From Castel Gandolfo, Pope's Final Farewell | ZENIT - The World Seen From Rome http://www.zenit.org/en/articles/from-castel-gandolfo-pope-s-final-farewell …    
    
    
    The Death of Liberal Catholicism | Catholic Teacher Education http://beingcatholic.com.au/the-death-of-liberal-catholicism/ … It may take a bit longer than a quarter of a century.    
    
    
    CNA: Cardinals set date - March 4 - for meetings about next Pope; Conclave date not yet determined http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/cardinals-set-date-for-meetings-about-next-pope/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+catholicnewsagency%2Fdailynews+%28CNA+Daily+News%29&utm_term=daily+news#.UTC9dNrSqlE.twitter …    
    
    
    Bishop asks Catholics to affirm Church teaching. Catholics freak out. | Catholic World Report http://www.catholicworldreport.com/Blog/2032/bishop_asks_catholics_to_affirm_church_teaching_catholics_freak_out.aspx#.UTC-099zI9E.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican's tribute book to #PopeBenedictXVI: beautiful images and quotes http://www.vatican.va/bxvi/omaggio/index_en.html …    
    
    
    Bishop enforces Catholic doctrine; press goes, ‘Wha …?’  http://www.patheos.com/blogs/getreligion/2013/03/bishop-enforces-catholic-doctrine-press-goes-wha/#sthash.ed5Mjosv.dpuf … Request "consistent with the right of all private schools"    
    
    
    Reno: Staying Home from the Conclave http://shar.es/jZmX7  via @firstthingsmag    
    
    
    @RichardDawkins It is very simple. If we are dying, priests come to our side for sacraments and strength as we make our final journey.    
    
    
    Pruden: White House under siege by reality - Washington Times: http://wtim.es/YGl0aB  via @washtimes    
    
    
    Interesting via @DeaconsBench: We've had African popes, but a black pope? Well, perhaps... http://shar.es/jxYe3     
    
    
    10 Reasons Cardinal Burke Will Be Next Pope ~ Dr. Taylor Marshall | Canterbury Tales http://shar.es/jKtwy  via @taylorrmarshall    
    
    
    #WeAllHaveThatOneFriend Who died for us on a Cross. Let us follow Him today.    
    
    
    @tom_perna There are a lot of exciting possibilities--not the least of which might be another Italian pope. Whoever he is, let him be holy.    
    
    
    @tom_perna I think this is going to be a longer conclave.    
    
    
    Interesting article on the papabili, the buzz around Rome, and the reliability of the "insiders." http://moynihanreport.itvworking.com/from-the-desk-of/letter-30-the-next-and-the-last … @RobertMoynihan    
    
    
    @tom_perna Who knows? Maybe they'll figure out who they will vote for quickly, even before the conclave. Complicating factors at play.    
    
    
    #InitialsOfSomeoneYouCareAbout ΜΡ ΘΥ #tRCot    
    
    
    Catholic school children hold a CONCLAVE! PHOTOS! What Does The Prayer Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/just-too-cool-catholic-school-children-hold-a-conclave-photos/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Cardinal Burke as Pope: Answering Two Common Objections ~ Dr. Taylor Marshall | Canterbury Tales http://shar.es/jOl2c  via @taylorrmarshall    
    
    
    @DanOnRadio Great job, @JamesMartinSJ! I disagree with this headline "almost goes ballistic." I thought you were quite well-spoken.    
    
    
    @DanOnRadio @JamesMartinSJ Ah. Well, I could not tell. Grace prevailed! Thanks for sharing.    
    
    
    @CardinalNapier Thank you, your eminence! We are glad to have more time to pray for you and for all the Cardinal-electors.    
    
    
    #WeAllHaveThatOneFriend Who suffered to give meaning to our own, Who died to save us from sin & death, Who rose to fill us with life & hope.    
    
    
    Right on. The Sacred Page: The next pope should be an "administrator"? "Reform" is more than managing bureaucracies! http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/03/the-next-pope-should-be-administrator.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    CNA: Hugo Chavez died 'in the bosom of the Church.' Died 'clinging to Christ' http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/hugo-chavez-died-in-the-bosom-of-the-church/#.UTeb55ovEwU.twitter … infinite #divinemercy > anyone's sins    
    
    
    Malcolm Ranjith, the Cardinal who lived through the 2004 Tsunami http://www.romereports.com/palio/malcolm-ranjith-the-cardinal-who-lived-through-the-2004-tsunami-english-9281.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter#.UTiPhkEY8hA.twitter …    
    
    
    All of my students today seemed quite excited to adopt their #cardinals. Adopt your own for prayer: http://www.adoptacardinal.org/adoption  #conclave #tRCot    
    
    
    It must be confusing to sort between the St. Louis #Cardinals and the Vatican City #Cardinals on Twitter these days. #Catholic #conclave    
    
    
    #GodsPraiseRoom "Worthy is the Lamb who was slain, to receive power and wealth and wisdom and might and honor and glory and blessing!"    
    
    
    #GodsPraiseRoom You gave us your own flesh as our true food, our bread from heaven, and your blood as true drink, just as you said. #John6    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ I do not think they foresaw that some cardinals would take so long to arrive when the retirement was announced Feb. 10.    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ Plus, throughout the course of salvation history, momentous events have occurred over the course of 3 days.    
    
    
    #Conclave: March 12. Saints, come to our aid: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CKWRuFjIRFo&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    @lukei4655 I have good kids and supportive colleagues. Makes all the difference in the world. I'm sure your trials were quite meritorious.    
    
    
    #FF @CardinalBertone @CardinalDolan @CardinalSean @Cardinal_Wuerl @CardinalNapier @CardRavasi_en @TurksonCardinal @DomOdiloScherer @Pontifex    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Papal Projection #1--The Name: What name will the next Holy Father select? We all have our g... http://bit.ly/VRR4Ng  <--More    
    
    
    Bold Papal Projection #1--The Name: I think the next pope will be Paul VII. Why? Read more: http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-papal-projection-1-name.html#.UTq5i_6t4BE.twitter … What do you think?    
    
    
    Get a text alert when the new #pope is elected! http://www.popealarm.com     
    
    
    I predict the new Pope will pick the name Paul VII Make a guess: http://catholicvote.org/NameThePope.php  My prediction: http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-papal-projection-1-name.html …    
    
    
    "Aujourd'hui, c'est la journée de la femme! Mais quelle place pour la femme si on nie toutes les différences?" http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=593725493990935&set=a.514044101959075.134429.513639495332869&type=1 …    
    
    
    The 3 C's: Avoid these things the night before an exam via @wyzant Any friends interested in joining this tutoring network, I'll invite you.    
    
    
    "Kevin, yes, your Porsche is ready!" said the ebullient tire salesman to the theology teacher. #awkwardsocialclassmixup, just 5 minutes ago    
    
    
        
    
    
    Video: A look inside the Papal conclave | http://CatholicVote.org : http://www.catholicvote.org/video-a-look-inside-the-papal-conclave/#.UTvhyw8j1A0.twitter …    
    
    
    1 man, 1 woman, 2 girls, 2 alarm clocks, 2 cellphones, 1 epic 8- to 12-week battle against the unrelenting passage of time. Bring on DST!    
    
    
    @LHuizenga @dakotapastor As it is in Luke 22:32, another set of verses that deals with Peter and the Twelve.    
    
    
    Congrats, @SalemSpartans! State titles for boys and girls hoops!    
    
    
    @dakotapastor @LHuizenga There is no mention of keys in that episode; rather, it refers to the power of forgiveness/retention of sins.    
    
    
    Ruse: Dare we hope for Burke? http://www.thecatholicthing.org/columns/2013/dare-we-hope-for-burke.html#.UT12bcQsLCQ.twitter …    
    
    
    9 things you need to know about how cardinals actually vote in conclaves |Blogs | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/blog/jimmy-akin/9-things-you-need-to-know-about-how-cardinals-actually-vote-in-conclaves … #NCRegister    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Prediction No. 2—Where the Pope Will Not Be From: With the conclave just about 24 hours away... http://bit.ly/14NHkmJ  <--More    
    
    
    Rome Reports: A look at the History of the Conclave http://www.romereports.com/palio/a-look-at-the-history-of-the-conclave-english-9343.html#.UT37Qqrr8_g.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Projection #3—The Pope Will Be Catholic: You can take this last one to the bank. What? Did y... http://bit.ly/14QoV8T  <--More    
    
    
    The Charcoal Fire: Bold Projection #3—The Pope Will Be Catholic http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-projection-3the-pope-will-be.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @TeDeumBlog @EWTN They are doing a good job. It's not the same, however, without Fr. Neuhaus. Requiescat in pace!    
    
    
    If Michael Jordan were a cardinal, would he vote for André Cardinal Vingt-Trois? #tRCot #conclave    
    
    
    @disciple96 @TeDeumBlog @EWTN Yes. I will never forget him or his coverage of the 2005 conclave.    
    
    
    @TaylorRMarshall I read recently that it was four. http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/0505401.htm …    
    
    
    "The Church does not need a general manager, but a man of faith" - Vatican Insider http://vaticaninsider.lastampa.it/en/world-news/detail/articolo/conclave-23168/ …    
    
    
    Wow! If at first you don't succeed, try, try again! http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/0505401.htm … #HabemusPapam #conclave #FrancisI    
    
    
    History today! 1st non-European Pope since 700s! 1st Latin American Pope! 1st Pope West of Atlantic! 1st Jesuit Pope! Francis the 1st! Wow!    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Hey, thanks for reading! I guess my "hunch" made me doubly wrong, though! God always gives the extra effort to humble me!    
    
    
    Pope Francis I #AMDG    
    
    
    Feel like a kid again! Pope Francis takes the bus? So do I! Hey, Francis was my confirmation name! Woah! #tRCot #Catholic #PopeFrancis    
    
    
    Yes! Domino's delivers! #Dominos Pizza Wins Court Order Stopping #HHS Abortion Mandate http://shar.es/euznD  via @BreitbartNews    
    
    
    Excellent article from Sandro Magister on Pope Francis I. http://chiesa.espresso.repubblica.it/articolo/1350465?eng=y …    
    
    
    New video celebrating the election of Pope Francis. http://www.catholicvote.org/     
    
    
    Apparently, one only needs one lung to be filled with the Holy Spirit. #PopeFrancis #tRCot http://ti.me/13WSXfb  via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Pope Francis and St. Francis: Preach the Gospel Always. And for the Love of God, Use Words. | http://CatholicVote.org : http://www.catholicvote.org/pope-francis-and-st-francis-preach-the-gospel-always-and-for-the-love-of-god-use-words/#.UUNJSNGyIME.twitter …    
    
    
    That viral photo with 3 popes? No, that's not Pope Francis, but Edouard Card. Gagnon http://m.aciprensa.com/noticia.php?n=40142 … 3 saints, 1 picture. Impressive!    
    
    
    @MatthewWarner FYI: Went to see if any more cardinals had joined TweetCatholic and it looks like the site is down.    
    
    
    @PopeAlarm How do you unsubscribe from text alerts? Thanks!    
    
    
    By George! Benedict XVI's brother? Georg Ratzinger. His prefect of papal household? Archb. Georg Gänswein. Successor? Jorge Card. Bergoglio.    
    
    
    @CardinalMahony Your Eminence, we love both Francis and Benedict. Many believers, including Orthodox, encounter Jesus in liturgical majesty.    
    
    
    St. Francis and liturgical abuse.  What Did St. Francis Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/what-did-st-francis-really-say-02/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    More interesting material from St. Francis on the Liturgy: What Did St. Francis Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/what-did-st-francis-really-say/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Be not afraid! The Holy Spirit builds in continuity & makes new whether shoes are red or black. Both Popes' gifts to the Church will endure!    
    
    
    How is this information public? Conclave should be under the oath of secrecy. The Vatican needs to investigate. http://life.nationalpost.com/2013/03/15/canadas-ouellet-beat-pope-francis-in-first-rounds-of-voting-reports/ …    
    
    
    TCF: Breathing with Both Lungs:  Saturday of the Akathist: I stumbled upon this iconography site last ... http://bit.ly/113wcW4  <--More    
    
    
    Powerful! Card. Bergoglio's Lenten letter to the faithful of Buenos Aires http://jmgarciaiii.blogspot.com/2013/02/cdl-bergoglios-lenten-letter-2013.html … #PopeFrancis    
    
    
    @AbbyJohnson This is truly one of those days.    
    
    
    @Sacerdotus @lindagaboardi @prolifejoan Our Lady of Akita, Oct. 13, 1973 http://www.ewtn.com/library/mary/akita.htm …    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Count on our prayers, Holy Father Francis! Ad Maiorem Dei Gloriam!    
    
    
    Rome Reports: Pope greets pilgrims after celebrating Mass in Vatican parish http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-greets-pilgrims-after-celebrating-mass-in-vatican-parish-english-9457.html#.UUXbiDIlYDs.twitter …    
    
    
    Οὐδὲ ἐγώ σε κρίνω· πορεύου καὶ μηκέτι ἁμάρτανε.    
    
    
    My 4-year-old: "I want pizza!" [Introspective pause] "... I don't know why I could just eat pizza all the time."    
    
    
    #Cultureofdeath horrors! Doctors in China Have Performed 336 Million Abortions, 196 Million Sterilizations Since 1971 http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2013/03/16/china_performed_336_million_abortions_since_1971.html?utm_source=tw&utm_medium=sm&utm_campaign=button_toolbar …    
    
    
    The swallows returned to St. Michael's Norbertine Abbey as I was playing with my daughters outside after Mass today. God is good! #Catholic    
    
    
    Liberals will soon turn on Pope Francis | Fr. Z's Blog (olim: What Does The Prayer Really Say?) http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/liberals-will-soon-turn-on-pope-francis/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Pope Francis continues Benedict XVI's Twitter momentum; over 2 million followers on @pontifex English account; Spanish followers near 1M.    
    
    
    WDTPRS: Those red shoes http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/i-am-thinking-about-those-red-shoes/ … via @FatherZ Seems not so much directed at Francis, but at those taking shots at Benedict XVI    
    
    
    This is well-stated by @amywelborn2:  A word http://wp.me/p53if-2iF     
    
    
    It is St. Joseph's feast day in Rome! Greatful for pontificate of our Holy Father Pope Francis! How many jokes during homily? I'd guess 3.5.    
    
    
    Χαιρετε! The Sacred Page: The Gospel Will Be Read in Greek at the Papal Inst... http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/03/the-gospel-will-be-read-in-greek-at.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines I could see you homeschooling our many children.    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines My spiritual director doesn't think I have a vocation to the priesthood after all!    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines Your modesty is unparalleled.    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines You are beautiful! I am referring, of course, to the Thomistic definition of beauty.    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines What's your favorite encyclical?    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines I see we attend the same daily Mass. Don't you love how Father's excellent homilies complement his liturgical piety?    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines How's your Latin? Aquae multae non potuerunt extinguere caritatem.    
    
    
    Akin: Should We Be Concerned About Pope Francis's Inaugural Mass? #NCRegister http://www.ncregister.com/blog/jimmy-akin/should-we-be-concerned-about-pope-franciss-inaugural-mass …    
    
    
    Inauguration homily of Pope Francis (@Pontifex)  http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/francesco/homilies/2013/documents/papa-francesco_20130319_omelia-inizio-pontificato_en.html … #Catholic #StJoseph #BenedictXVI    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ That article is filled with false dichotomy and forgetful of the real Benedict XVI, the stone which the [media] rejected.    
    
    
    WDTPRS: Bp. Vasa (Santa Rosa) getting blow-back for requiring Catholic teachers to adhere to Catholic ways http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/bp-vasa-d-santa-rosa-getting-blow-back-for-requiring-catholic-teachers-to-adhere-to-catholic-ways/ … @FatherZ    
    
    
    Far too much dichotomous thinking comparing pontificates. Benedict was XVI one of the greatest popes of modern era. How quickly some forget!    
    
    
    How sad that some, rather than rejoice over Francis's papacy, focus on the continued persecution of Benedict! Those who do so need prayer!    
    
    
    Who is using Eucharist for politics? MT @charliespiering Biden's office releases news that he & Pelosi received Communion during papal Mass    
    
    
    I had forgotten that the Gospel was in Greek at Pope Benedict's installation Mass too. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m31JYp1SGt4 … Looking for today's video...    
    
    
    He is the Vicar of Christ! If you haven't seen this yet, watch! Pope gets out of Popemobile to bless disabled man. http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-gets-out-of-popemobile-to-bless-disabled-man-before-inaugural-mass-english-9476.html#.UUkTXyuP0tE.twitter …    
    
    
    @JulieBorowski The state has an interest in marriage for obvious reasons. The real enemy is "no fault divorce" (i.e., divorce on demand).    
    
    
    Syria's Christians in peril, Melkite Catholic leader warns Pontiff http://shar.es/eK9J9  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Biden: We almost had US pope, "chance at power" http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/ticket/biden-almost-had-american-pope-203143228--politics.html … Not strange to me that Biden would frame this in rhetoric of "power."    
    
    
    All you catechumens: if you are being tempted, the prayers of the saints (and sinners) are with you. Hang in there! See you at The Vigil!    
    
    
    @JulieBorowski As is evident, this is fundamental flaw in libertarianism: inability or unwillingness to distinguish b/w liberty and license.    
    
    
    Great interview with His Excellency, Archbishop Cordileone, on gay marriage http://www.freep.com/usatoday/article/2001085 … @ArchdioceseSF    
    
    
    Pope Francis Affirms there is “Dictatorship of Relativism” http://shar.es/eUbOl  via @TheAnchoress    
    
    
    North Dakota moves to ban #abortion http://news.msn.com/politics/north-dakota-lawmakers-move-to-ban-abortion#tscptmt … I'm hoping N. Dakotans have as much good sense as their lawmakers. #humanrights    
    
    
    Catholics, it's not an infidelity to the Church to continue to express your love for Benedict XVI even now. Please remember him in prayer.    
    
    
    This is moving! RT @roccopalmo Video of unprecedented Meeting of Popes #PopeBenedictXVI #PopeFrancis #Catholic    
    
    
    @BobJabro @CardinalMahony She will also be pleased to know that Pope Benedict XVI celebrated Mass here as well: http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/03/dont-forget-benedict-xvi-said-mass-at.html …    
    
    
    Feast of the Annunciation on March 25? Not in 2013--transferred because of Holy Week to April 8 http://shar.es/eBcwe     
    
    
    Holy Week approacheth! Last lap of the Lenten race. Forget all the falls along the way; let us strengthen our mortification for Christ.    
    
    
    Look for my article on Marian devotion in the May/June issue of Lay Witness. http://www.cuf.org/  It will also be online. #trcot #Catholic    
    
    
    It's Twitter official: Pope Francis is going to Brazil this summer for #WYD! I wish I were going! @pontifex @Pontifex_es @Pontifex_pt    
    
    
    Ὡσαννὰ τῷ υἱῷ Δαυίδ· Εὐλογημένος ὁ ἐρχόμενος ἐν ὀνόματι κυρίου· Ὡσαννὰ ἐν τοῖς ὑψίστοις.    
    
    
    Last year on #PalmSunday, the priest turned his handful of hyssop into a veritable supersoaker, drenching me and my infant head to foot.    
    
    
    Allen: Debunking three 'urban legends' about Pope Francis http://ncronline.org/blogs/ncr-today/debunking-three-urban-legends-about-pope-francis#.UU9xEtUMTzm.twitter … From whom, I wonder, did the media got those false quotes?    
    
    
    Obama gaffe: "Passover is a celebration of the freedom our ancestors dreamed of, fought for..." http://www.southbendtribune.com/news/sbt-rabbi-anyone-can-appreciate-passover-meaning-20130325,0,4929834.story … God did the fighting.    
    
    
    @JulieBorowski That's quite an oversimplification. Marriage isn't just about tax cuts, divorce. It's about the health of children & society.    
    
    
    LSN: 1.4 million march against gay marriage in France; police gas crowd, including children http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/1.4-million-march-against-gay-marriage-in-france-police-tear-gas-crowd-chil … Follow: @LaManifPourTous    
    
    
    US bishops cite Pope Francis in urging marriage rally prayers: Catholic News Agency http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/us-bishops-cite-pope-francis-in-urging-marriage-rally-prayers/#.UVEqnD-ygMM.twitter …    
    
    
    Granted, some are uncharitable (as is true with any group). But if we say "no" to gay marriage, it is because of love. #trcot #Catholic    
    
    
    to the recognition of the dignity and inalienable value of every single and unique human being called into existence. (2/2)    
    
    
    Dignitas Personae (CDF): Behind every “no” in the difficult task of  discerning between good and evil, there shines a great “yes” ... (1/2)    
    
    
    @TylerDyer2 @LarrySabato Also, consider France. The traditional family movement there is both young and large. More: @LaManifPourTous    
    
    
    Required reading for libertarians:  Privatizing Marriage Is Impossible | Public Discourse http://www.thepublicdiscourse.com/2012/04/5069/  by @DrJrobackmorse    
    
    
    Great post: How Not to Have a Debate about Gay Marriage: http://www.dennyburk.com/how-not-to-have-a-debate-about-gay-marriage/ … Piers Morgan out to publicly shame SSM detractors?    
    
    
    TCF: Something You Might Not Expect from the Canticle of the Sun: TCF Quoteboard: With the Holy Father... http://bit.ly/10Qc33N  <--More    
    
    
    Spy Wednesday and "the impiety of the traitor" via @RorateCaeli http://rorate-caeli.blogspot.com/2013/03/holy-week-jesus-betrayed-and-sold.html … #Judas #betrayal #Passion #trcot #Catholic #holyweek    
    
    
    @TaylorRMarshall "Lord, do you want us to bid fire come down from heaven and consume them?" #askandyoushallreceive    
    
    
    A blessed Triduum and watchful Holy Thursday to all! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U-AsvDn87fo&feature=player_embedded&list=PLD8RZBdrhQ4gAtvpT2eO5bNSF5LkNmISM … #priesthood #Church #Eucharist #LastSupper #PangeLingua    
    
    
    There is no Easter without #GoodFriday. Remember the One who died today that you might live forever. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XppXi_jZKWk&feature=player_embedded&list=PLD8RZBdrhQ4gAtvpT2eO5bNSF5LkNmISM … #Catholic #trcot    
    
    
    "I opened the sea before you, but you opened my side with a spear." #GoodFriday, Improperia (The Reproaches) http://youtu.be/wTZqJlyK5qU     
    
    
    Aquinas on the Eternal Son's Union with the Entombed Flesh & with Christ's Soul among the Dead http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/04/tcf-quoteboard-eternal-son-united-to.html#.UVX8x54RPBg.twitter … #GoodFriday #Catholic    
    
    
    Book: Pope Bl. John Paul II Self-Flagellated http://www.cnn.com/2010/WORLD/europe/01/27/pope.flagellate/index.html … Who else will suffer penance for the unrepentant? #gospelofsuffering    
    
    
    Benedict XVI’s Theology of Holy Saturday: First Things http://shar.es/dtBeB  “God incarnate entered absolute & extreme solitude of mankind”    
    
    
    The labor of the Church is coming to a close. Will you be there tonight to witness the birth of her sons & daughters? #EasterVigil #Catholic    
    
    
    Juvenile prisoners from LA County write to Pope Francis: "I know the same youth feet that you wash are like me." http://en.radiovaticana.va/m_articolo.asp?c=677778 …    
    
    
    "My mom was aborted." A truly Satanic irony: Science eager to harvest eggs from aborted babies to be used in IVF http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-186802/Should-eggs-aborted-babies.html …    
    
    
    RT ‏@dlongenecker1 Ten Questions for Shroud Skeptics http://shar.es/dvBiF     
    
    
    @jksoren82 Such a non sequitur is obviously a mischaracterization of BXVI's thought. Christianity is a priori true b4 any existential crises    
    
    
    Christ is risen, alleluia! He is risen indeed, alleluia! Happy Easter!    
    
    
    Hey Google, next year Easter won't fall on Cesar Chavez's birthday. #culturefail    
    
    
    Bishop Vasa: Delay in implementing Catholic identity pledge presents "an opportunity to teach" http://cal-catholic.com/wordpress/2013/03/30/bishop-vasa-stands-firm-on-catholic-identity-in-schools/ … via @Calcatholic    
    
    
    No April Fools: the Astros are in first place. http://espn.go.com/mlb/standings     
    
    
    Background of antinomianism: Some thoughts on the VPO statement regarding the Mandatum rite controversy http://canonlawblog.wordpress.com/2013/04/01/some-thoughts-on-the-vpo-statement-regarding-the-mandadtum-rite-controversy/ … via @canonlaw    
    
    
    @tom_perna - I thought you might appreciate this http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/04/if-church-fathers-had-been-on-twitter.html#.UVnggM4drz0.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: If the Church Fathers Had Been on Twitter: Top 10 Most Memorable April Fools Day Moments: If Twit... http://bit.ly/127fENJ  <--More    
    
    
    @tom_perna Thanks! Glad baseball is back!    
    
    
    Going to be a long season for the Padres, the Twins, the Yankees (yes), the Rockies' pen, and the Angels' opponents.    
    
    
    @tom_perna @greglamatrice Nice one, Tom! You should explain to him the 4/1 custom in the U.S. so he can retweet you and prove it!    
    
    
    Will the Brewers have the only walk-off win for the day? I hope not. Let's pick up where we left off. Go #Athletics!    
    
    
    @CardinalNapier Your eminence, this season will pass. Benedict was the most theologically erudite pope in modern era. He won't be forgotten.    
    
    
    @CardinalNapier Generations yet to be born will be those who will measure the greatness of his pontificate. God bless you and happy Easter!    
    
    
    NOM's Thomas Peters: Kids are Central to Marriage Debate http://shar.es/dY6tU  He's absolutely right. Who is unnecessary? a mommy or daddy?    
    
    
    Pope Blessed John Paul II, pray for us!    
    
    
    Gearing up for a new quarter teaching κοινή Greek at JP Catholic! Excited to welcome my students, both those in class and those online!    
    
    
    It's still early, but this phlegmatic #Athletics offense is reminiscent of un-offensive Aprils and Mays of a decade ago.    
    
    
    Please pray for my friends' son, who is 9 days old and having open heart surgery today. For the parents, family, doctors, and staff.    
    
    
    Immediate Action Requested for Romeikes—Grant Permanent Legal Status to Persecuted German Homeschool Family http://wh.gov/sd2U     
    
    
    Study shows African Americans reject civil, gay rights equation: CNA http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/study-shows-african-americans-reject-civil-gay-rights-equation/#.UV3jgzP8Zy0.twitter …    
    
    
    Disturbing! Abortion worker at trial: It was ’literally a beheading’ http://nbcnews.to/10EPVpv  #cultureofdeath    
    
    
    Abstinence and Friday of the Easter Octave …http://the-hermeneutic-of-continuity.blogspot.com/2013/04/abstinence-and-friday-of-easter-octave.html … Short answer: Yes, some sort of abstinence is good today.    
    
    
    After judge tells arrested pro-life activist ‘your God’s wrong,’ lawyers file appeal http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/after-judge-tells-arrested-pro-life-activist-your-gods-wrong-lawyers-file-a … #civildisobedience Hebrews 13:3    
    
    
    Delayed thanks for the occasional RT's, @lukei4655, @DanielGarlandJr, @jksoren82, and @prolifejoan! Happy Easter to you all! Χρίστος ἀνέστη!    
    
    
    Pray for the Warrens and repose of the soul of his son. Saddleback Church Says Rick Warren’s Son Committed Suicide http://cbsloc.al/ZGdzRa     
    
    
    TCF: Mother Teresa on Mercy and Forgiveness: A most blessed Divine Mercy Sunday to you all!
 
 http://bit.ly/Y5JbVv  <--More    
    
    
    χαῖρε κεχαριτωμένη!  #thingsarchangelssay #OurLady #Gabriel #Annunciation #Catholic    
    
    
    Disturbing video. http://chicksontheright.com/posts/item/24056-this-really-can-t-be-shown-too-much … One would have thought these ideas to have died with the dictatorships of the 20th century.    
    
    
    The "collective" is better off when families take charge of their children.    
    
    
    Pray for Pope Emeritus Benedict XVI http://soa.li/yRWDtzk  Spanish paper: "we won't have us with him for very much longer" via @Telegraph    
    
    
        
    
    
    RT please and vote "Absolutely!" - Benedict XVI: Who should be on the 2013 #TIME100 list? http://ti.me/YKfkg5     
    
    
    The Atlantic: Why Dr. Kermit Gosnell's Trial Should Be a Front-Page Story - Conor Friedersdorf http://www.theatlantic.com/national/archive/2013/04/why-dr-kermit-gosnells-trial-should-be-a-front-page-story/274944/ … #FF @conor64    
    
    
    ‘Pro-choice’ reporter apologizes for not covering #Gosnell, calls it ‘trial of the century’ | LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/pro-choice-reporter-apologizes-for-not-covering-gosnell-calls-it-trial-of-t …    
    
    
    Seriously, ESPN? A's win 9th in a row on a 12th inning walk-off against their 2012 ALDS foes and not a word? http://espn.go.com/mlb/     
    
    
    Gosnell might be the worst serial killer in history, says … “Nightline” anchor « Hot Air http://hotair.com/archives/2013/04/12/gosnell-might-be-the-worst-serial-killer-in-history-says-nightline-anchor/ … via @hotairblog    
    
    
    Signs of renewal in Europe: Human embryo is "One of Us": help us to protect and respect its dignity and integrity - http://www.oneofus.eu/     
    
    
    This is good news indeed. RT @FatherZ HUGE! CDF to LCWR http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/04/huge-cdf-to-lcwr/ …    
    
    
    Congress, defund abortion NOW!  Delaware Planned Parenthood clinic facing charges of unsafe, unsanitary conditions http://abclocal.go.com/wpvi/story?section=news/local&id=9059172 …    
    
    
    Horror RT @jmattbarber "Gay" adoptive "father" rapes & prostitutes five year-old "son." like I said: get used to this http://www.rpvnetwork.org/m/blogpost?id=2548153%3ABlogPost%3A51335 …    
    
    
    Happy birthday, Benedict XVI! RT @ASchwibach Ad multos annos: Benedikt XVI. feiert 86. Geburtstag in aller Stille http://www.kath.net/news/40923     
    
    
    Cannon: The Problem with the Press, Pt1 Religion http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/04/15/the_problem_with_the_press_part_1_religion_117948.html#.UW3VAHoxTv0.twitter … Avoid embarrassment: Hire Catholic experts to cover Catholicism beat    
    
    
    Family of dead Gosnell patient tearfully testify: repairman tells of drains clogged with body parts | LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/family-of-dead-gosnell-patient-tearfully-testify-repairman-tells-of-drains …    
    
    
    Post-Reformation Catholic Thought and Piety (27 vols.) is now available from @Logos Bible Software  http://www.logos.com/product/15707/post-reformation-catholic-thought-and-piety …    
    
    
    One suspect in custody, another remains on the loose
 http://www.bostonglobe.com/metro/2013/04/18/mit-police-officer-hit-gunfire-cambridge-police-dispatcher-says/4UeCClOVeLr8PHLvDa99zK/story.html?s_campaign=sm_tw … via @BostonGlobe    
    
    
    The pontificate of Pope Benedict XVI began 8 years ago today. Pray for him today. #Catholic #trcot    
    
    
    @tom_perna Thanks, Tom! God continue to bless your work!    
    
    
    Video: Police Release Incredible Thermal Images of Boston Bombing Suspect in His Last Hiding Place http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/04/20/mass-police-release-incredible-thermal-images-of-boston-bombing-suspect-in-his-last-hiding-place/?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=Share%20Buttons&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=Share%20Buttons … Wow!    
    
    
    Born of water and spirit, I ceased to be a pagan 33 years ago today. Thanks, Mom & Dad! And thanks be to God for His glorious gift of grace!    
    
    
    "The way humanity treats the environment influences the way it treats itself, and vice versa"--Pope BXVI. On Earth Day, consider the unborn.    
    
    
    That quote is from Caritas in Veritate, 51. http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/benedict_xvi/encyclicals/documents/hf_ben-xvi_enc_20090629_caritas-in-veritate_en.html … Whole chapter on human development and the environment. #Catholic #trcot    
    
    
    On Earth Day, quit your contraceptives. Bad for your soul, bad for the environment, bad for species. http://www.ncregister.com/site/article/contracepting_the_environment …    
    
    
    Sadness and prayers for the people of France and for her children today. @LaManifPourTous, keep up the good fight for families and children.    
    
    
    French police assault priest protesting gay marriage. This debate is bigger, uglier than the mainstream media admits http://soa.li/0S865Db     
    
    
    #Gosnell effect? President Obama Backs Out of Planned Parenthood Fundraiser Speech http://www.lifenews.com/2013/04/24/president-obama-backs-out-of-planned-parenthood-fundraiser-speech/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    Are You Part of the Great Catholic Migration of the 21st Century? | Canterbury Tales http://shar.es/JTbN4  via @taylorrmarshall    
    
    
    This is excellent--really good advice, too. "The Contraceptive Sanctuary: Why you SHOULD Bring Baby to Church" http://shar.es/JTWgT     
    
    
    Wow! One can vote 25 times per email address for the MLB all-star game. Time to rock the vote like a dead pet in a swing state!    
    
    
    Religious ignorance or religious indifference? Sad. "At Boston's bombing scene: Catholic priests need not apply" http://shar.es/l10h0     
    
    
    @jksoren82 Where are you guys thinking of moving?    
    
    
    Who would have thought a 1-hit shutout might be the second-best-pitched game today? Tigers' Sanchez: 17 K's through 8 innings.    
    
    
    @jksoren82 Awesome! Best of luck with your applications! God bless!    
    
    
    Starting to wonder if my Athletics are going to escape April with a winning record. They need Cespedes healthy and Straily in Oakland now!    
    
    
    Dangerously fashionable! -- Eponymous Flower: French Police Go Berserk: Arrest Everyone Who Wears Pink Hoodies http://eponymousflower.blogspot.com/2013/04/french-police-go-berserk-arrest.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @MatthewWarner I, for one, spent too many hours cutting linings out of my hats. Curved, worn-in, perhaps even a little stained = high style    
    
    
    @MatthewWarner Good method! These days, clothing retailers make lame-looking hats pre-broken in. In our day, we did it ourselves.    
    
    
    TCF: Blogging Break: Writing rests sort of come upon me with varying degrees of workflow. I will be ba... http://bit.ly/16dpvlZ  <--More    
    
    
    Outrage: Parents seek 2nd medical opinion, cops barge into Cali. home and take their baby - Blaze http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/04/29/im-going-to-grab-your-baby-and-dont-resist-cops-barge-into-cali-parents-home-take-their-baby-after-they-seek-2nd-medical-opinion-and-its-on-video/?utm_source=facebook&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=Share+Buttons&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=Share%20Buttons …    
    
    
    Gotta love a game in which the hero got 3 hits (2 HRs) but struck out four times http://mlb.mlb.com/mlb/gameday/index.jsp?gid=2013_04_29_anamlb_oakmlb_1&mode=recap&c_id=oak … Glad I didn't stay up for this one!    
    
    
    What’s Killing American Catholicism, by @dlongenecker1 http://shar.es/ltikN  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Urge Pentagon to scrub plans to court-martial Christians who share faith: Sign petition, protect relig freedom @FRCdc http://www.frc.org/alert/pentagon-consultant-no-gospel-witness-for-chaplains …    
    
    
    St. Joseph the worker, pray for us! Protect our work and our families! Help us to follow your example of trust in the Father's providence.    
    
    
    Happy feast day of St. Athanasius, who, though he lived many years in exile, was the great victor over the heresy of Arianism!    
    
    
    Pope told Argentine Bishops in March to use doc restricting communion for pro-aborts | http://LifeSiteNews.com  http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/pope-tells-argentine-bishops-to-use-doc-restricting-communion-for-pro-abort …    
    
    
    Feeling the love on teacher appreciation week! God bless my students' parents!    
    
    
    Thankful for all the great teachers in my life! Especially my Mom and Dad, grandparents, family, and many memorable professors and teachers!    
    
    
    Prayers needed! Wyoming Catholic College Freshman Dies in Hiking Accident with Family http://shar.es/l8p3Z     
    
    
    @michellemalkin @washingtonpost Far from rich, 33, but I confess I love ChickFilA. Maybe it's the sauce talking, but #Benghazi > #Watergate    
    
    
    Pro-choice reporter covering Gosnell trial changes mind on abortion: LSN http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/pro-choice-reporter-covering-gosnell-trial-changes-mind-on-abortion … #LifeSiteNews    
    
    
    Wow! Oh, that there were more professional athletes like Matt Kemp of the Dodgers. http://shar.es/lDPNv     
    
    
    ‘This baby won’t stop breathing!’: Abortionist strangled baby born alive while nurses watched: LSN http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/this-baby-wont-stop-breathing-abortionist-strangled-baby-born-alive-while-n … #LifeSiteNews    
    
    
    The Sacred Page: Ascension Day Readings http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/05/ascension-day-readings.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @NewsBreaker Failure to defend Americans abroad, lying to the people, altering documents, suppressing the truth. These are the key issues.    
    
    
    Steyn: "For the American people to accept the Obama-Clinton lie is to be complicit in it." The Benghazi Lie: NRO http://www.nationalreview.com/node/347980     
    
    
    @whitehouse Um, I think you don't really understand Mother's Day. You must be thinking of Promiscuous Co-Ed Day.    
    
    
    W.H. Marks Mother's Day By Celebrating Free Birth Control http://shar.es/lVv9Y  via @sharethis    
    
    
    More federal corruption: IRS Admits Targeting Conservative Groups, Apologizes http://aclj.us/59jw  via @ACLJ    
    
    
    Top GOP Senator Says Obama Could Be Impeached Over ‘Most Egregious Cover-Up in American History’ http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/05/10/top-gop-senator-says-obama-could-be-impeached-over-most-egregious-cover-up-in-american-history/?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=Share%20Buttons …    
    
    
    Obama administration: "Stand down." #benghaziinfourwords    
    
    
    One wonders if things could be worse off in the DOJ with Al Capone or Billy the Kid calling the shots. I think not. http://www.ap.org/Images/Letter-to-Eric-Holder_tcm28-12896.pdf …    
    
    
    Senior tax officials knew of extra Tea Party scrutiny http://reut.rs/12vOQCI  ... some knew from 2011!    
    
    
    #Benghazi, #IRS, #DOJ -- What a combo! And for only--what?--$6 trillion! Can we have an impeachment smoothie on the side for free?    
    
    
    Isaac Newton tried to Invent New Language http://usat.ly/13RrtFm  via @USATODAY In this regard, Tolkien>Newton. Nonetheless, kudos to Newton.    
    
    
    BREAKING: ABC SAYS WHITE HOUSE AUTHORIZED IRS-GATE POLITICAL ENEMY SCANDAL http://shar.es/ZgvDb  via @liberty #impeach    
    
    
    Steyn: The Autocrat Accountants | National Review Online http://www.nationalreview.com/node/348687  @MarkSteynOnline fears not the audit!    
    
    
    Obama Supporter Has Perfectly Improbable Explanation Absolving President From Blame For Scandals http://onion.com/18NY0zm  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Kathtube: Veni Creator Spiritus http://www.kathtube.com/player.php?id=31380 … A blessed feast of Pentecost to all! #newevangelization    
    
    
    Daughter of author of The Color Purple: How my mother's fanatical feminist views tore us apart http://www.dailymail.co.uk/femail/article-1021293/How-mothers-fanatical-feminist-views-tore-apart-daughter-The-Color-Purple-author.html … #feminism #abortion    
    
    
    @Pontifex Happy Pentecost, Holy Father! May the Holy Spirit continue to guide you and abide in you per omnia saecula saeculorum!    
    
    
    Veni Creator Spiritus! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cDhYGdK0KQg&list=PLD8RZBdrhQ4gAtvpT2eO5bNSF5LkNmISM&index=3 … Happy feast of #Pentecost! Happy birthday, Catholic Church!    
    
    
    Lord, have mercy! CBS News: Monstrous Tornado Kills More Than 50 People, destroys elementary school http://cbsloc.al/10LH6xJ  #PrayforOklahoma    
    
    
    31-year-old man takes preteen girl to Planned Parenthood after raping her http://s.shr.lc/11Vvko5  How many rapes are covered up by abortion?    
    
    
    #DOJ: Employees must affirm homosexuality - #LifeSiteNews.com http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/justice-department-employees-must-affirm-homosexuality … DOJ corrupt to core, no longer about justice but agenda    
    
    
    #IRS Audited 69% of Adoptive Families While Defending Planned Parenthood http://shar.es/ZygU8  #corruption #impeach!    
    
    
    @PPact Not all they were up to. http://www.chron.com/news/article/Okla-lawmakers-to-take-up-tornado-recovery-bill-4538376.php … Money going toward baby-killing is a waste of needed taxpayer resources.    
    
    
    Please RT: Imagine Sisters Movement to make a "Fishers of Men"-like video to promote religious life vocations http://lightoflovefilm.com/  #trcot    
    
    
    Ouch! #Astros are 7-5 against #Angels & #Mariners, 7-28 against everyone else.    
    
    
    Meanwhile, the #Marlins are like the cicadas, emerging from the darkness for a moment of glory before returning into the earth.    
    
    
    Famous exorcist says Pope's simple prayer cast out demon :: Catholic News Agency (CNA): http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/famous-exorcist-says-popes-simple-prayer-cast-out-demon/#.UZ-EvHePQYh.twitter …    
    
    
    #ObamaScandalMovies Hunt for October Surprise    
    
    
    #ObamaScandalMovies Catch Me If You Can    
    
    
    #ObamaScandalMovies All the President's Men II--a sequel that has the critics raving, "Outdoes the original!" "Put Nixon up for sainthood!"    
    
    
    #ObamaScandalMovies Vegas Vacation (feat. Beyonce and Jay-Z)    
    
    
    #memorialday Requiescant in pace, Tyrone Woods, Glen Doherty. #benghazi    
    
    
    Pope: Open Door to Faith http://shar.es/ZUThs  @Pontifex makes me think of the customs delaying confirmation in the U.S. into teen years...    
    
    
    Polling Expert: Survey on priests' dislike of Missal may be inaccurate - Catholic News Agency http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/survey-on-priests-dislike-of-missal-may-be-inaccurate/#.UaGbbgIbQ5A.twitter …    
    
    
    τί ἐστιν ἄνθρωπος, ὅτι μιμνῄσκῃ αὐτοῦ, ἢ υἱὸς ἀνθρώπου, ὅτι ἐπισκέπτῃ αὐτόν;    
    
    
    Happy #MemorialDay to all, particularly to my family members who have served, and especially to those who have died for love of country.    
    
    
    I am happy to see many stores closed today. If stores can close on #MemorialDay to honor those who died for us, why not also on Sundays?    
    
    
    Congrats to my former students graduating today! God bless you, keep you, show His face to you, have mercy on you, and give you His peace!    
    
    
    @tom_perna Glutton for punishment? Looks like they wanted to switch to a half-way interesting game!    
    
    
    Call Your Mother! The Why, What, and How of Marian Piety | CUF http://www.cuf.org/2013/05/call-your-mother-the-why-what-and-how-of-marian-piety/ …    
    
    
    @tom_perna Feel free to share on one of your Mondays with Mary. http://www.cuf.org/2013/05/call-your-mother-the-why-what-and-how-of-marian-piety/ … God continue to bless your work!    
    
    
    @tom_perna Sorry for confusion. Just wanted to share an article I wrote.    
    
    
    Not only are #Athletics on 15-2 run, but they have also beaten quality pitchers in the process: Shields, Sale, Darvish, Lincecum, Bumgarner    
    
    
    The 4th shoe drops: Email scandal rocks administration http://www.examiner.com/article/the-4th-shoe-drops-email-scandal-rocks-administration … via @examinercom When will there be accountability?    
    
    
    Lessons from France on the Myths of Same-Sex Marriage | Public Discourse: http://www.thepublicdiscourse.com/2013/06/10293/     
    
    
    Bishop tells hostile crowd at gay marriage debate: my secretary was murdered by a gay activist | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/bishop-tells-hostile-crowd-at-gay-marriage-debate-my-secretary-was-killed-b …    
    
    
    Two-Year-Old Emerges From “Vegetative State” After Adult Stem Cell Treatment http://www.lifenews.com/2013/06/05/two-year-old-emerges-from-vegetative-state-after-adult-stem-cell-treatment/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    NCR: Lesbian Teacher Wins $170K Court Award from Cinci Archdiocese http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/lesbian-teacher-wins-170000-court-award-from-cincinnati-archdiocese … Your excellencies, bring back the mandatum!    
    
    
    KUHNER: The betrayal of the Navy's SEAL Team 6 - Washington Times: http://wtim.es/11KWZkk  via @washtimes    
    
    
    TCF: Solzhenitzyn: Harvard Commencement Address 35 Years Later: I discovered this speech when a friend... http://bit.ly/199mGUC  <--More    
    
    
    #dictatorshipofrelativism: Bill: Every Scottish child to have a state-appointed overseer | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/every-scottish-child-to-have-a-state-appointed-overseer-new-bill …    
    
    
    Three double-headers in the MLB today, two of which seem to have been unscheduled. Too bad Wolf takes a loss for his relief outing.    
    
    
    Many congratulations to all my former Saint Joseph Academy students! I wish I could have attended graduation, but my prayers are with you!    
    
    
    Edward Snowden: The whistleblower behind NSA revelations http://gu.com/p/3gec7/tw  "I understand that I will be made to suffer for my actions"    
    
    
    Another scandal. At what point do we give up searching for the remains of a camel under so much straw? http://washington.cbslocal.com/2013/06/10/cbs-news-u-s-state-department-cover-ups-range-from-prostitution-charges-to-drug-rings/ …    
    
    
    Along the same lines... IRS Caught on Tape Telling Nonprofit: “Keep Your Faith to Yourself” http://www.lifenews.com/2013/06/10/irs-caught-on-tape-telling-nonprofit-keep-your-faith-to-yourself/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    Thankful for my sweet and loving wife and my wonderful daughters! Time 4 family, time 4 personal study, time 4 rest! Let there be summer!    
    
    
    Pope acknowledges 'gay lobby' influence in Vatican http://shar.es/wVJjA  Also notable citation of Pelagian and Gnostic/pantheism trends...    
    
    
    Chen Guangcheng abruptly ordered to leave NY University: human rights leaders call for investigation http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/chen-guangcheng-abruptly-ordered-to-leave-ny-university-pro-life-activists … #LifeSiteNews    
    
    
    Tweet    
    
    
    The Evolution of the Swimsuit by Jessica Rey http://www.qideas.org/video/the-evolution-of-the-swimsuit.aspx …  How every girl in Southern California needs to watch this!    
    
    
    Looking forward to the new encyclical. Here is a brief intro to its composition from Sandro Magister. http://chiesa.espresso.repubblica.it/articolo/1350539?eng=y …    
    
    
    @olivegarden I will return to OG when Darden stops giving $$ to Planned Parenthood. http://www.lifenews.com/2011/09/12/pro-life-group-lists-companies-backing-planned-parenthood/ …    
    
    
    Judge: Teacher Who Punished Student 4 Catholic Belief abt Homosexuality Violated Student’s 1st Amendment Rights--TMLC http://www.thomasmore.org/press-releases/2013/06/federal-judge-teacher-who-punished-student-expressing-catholic-belief-against#.UcSjwvQ_RPk.twitter …    
    
    
    #PornStruggles trending on Twitter? Here is a video to solve those problems: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tvo0OCcp600 …    
    
    
    This should be good. A friend from childhood who is quite a writer! http://frontporchphilosopher.wordpress.com/  #Catholic    
    
    
    Supreme Court Decision on Marriage: “Tragic Day for Marriage and our Nation” http://www.hprweb.com/2013/06/supreme-court-decisions-on-marriage-tragic-day-for-marriage-and-our-nation/#.Uc8UXopu0_E.twitter …    
    
    
    Obamas fly chef 860 miles to the White House... just to make pizza http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1168940/Obamas-fly-chef-860-miles-White-House--just-make-pizza.html … via @DailyMailUS I make excellent sausage gravy...    
    
    
    Rome Reports: Pope Francis' first Encyclical - Lumen Fidei - to be released on July 5th http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-francis-first-encyclical-to-be-released-on-july-5th-english-10436.html#.UdHHo46xBD5.twitter … Yes! #summerreading    
    
    
    Dear America, have a happy holiday this coming #4thofjuly! 
Love, #relativism    
    
    
    Obama cancels July 4th celebration for troops, but not his safari for himself. http://americanoverlook.com/obama-cancels-4th-of-july-for-our-troops/10770 … #presidentofthepeople #letthemeatcake    
    
    
    God Bless America! Happy birthday, USA! May true freedom be restored. http://youtu.be/1HqskmrpiuY  Sung by Irish tenor Ronan Tynan via @youtube    
    
    
    Lumen Fidei: Initial Observations | The Charcoal Fire http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/07/initial-observations-lumen-fidei.html#.Udc0vDFxbK4.twitter …    
    
    
    @DanielGarlandJr And all four of Benedict's encyclicals? ;)    
    
    
    TCF: Initial Observations: Lumen Fidei: Well, I know it's been a while since I've written anything, so... http://bit.ly/13zfYoO  <--More    
    
    
    @DanielGarlandJr Being that Benedict wrote three of his own and one of Francis's. ;)    
    
    
    Watched my wife turn a cloudy evening over the Pacific into a beautiful painting. Wow is she so talented and am I very blessed!    
    
    
    DMV:  2 hours to get in, 2 hours to get out. Not bad. Enjoyed baptism conversation with G50.    
    
    
    Lopez: Same-Sex Parenting: Child Abuse? | The Public Discourse http://www.thepublicdiscourse.com/2013/07/10474/     
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Dang! Has anyone started building an ark yet?    
    
    
    TCF: Vocation, Saints, the Beauty of the Church:  An Interview with Cardinal Schönborn:  Cardinal Schö... http://bit.ly/1avfRy8  <--More    
    
    
    TCF: The Charcoal Fire: New Direction: You may have noticed I took a break for a while. This proved ve... http://bit.ly/1avRRuQ  <--More    
    
    
    This NYT article by Ma Jian is an important read on China’s one-child policy http://nyti.ms/16LXUK6     
    
    
    TCF: Fasting or Hospitality? The Desert Fathers Weigh In: As I work on my Greek translation skills, I ... http://bit.ly/15z5Aud  <--More    
    
    
    The Thomistic Doctrine of God and Dominican Spiritual Life - Fr. Gilles Emery, O.P. http://youtu.be/TOM-wOTa46E  via @youtube    
    
    
    Was a Yoenis Cespedes fan before it was cool. http://www.csnbayarea.com/blog/casey-pratt/still-wearing-bat-weight-cespedes-homers-bp …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Good news! I have a future article forthcoming in the theology journal Nova et Vetera. No publication date yet.    
    
    
    @sullijo Thank you!    
    
    
    @jbarooah Thank you!    
    
    
    Interesting discussion on my candles article today in FT http://shar.es/kYmOA  Always glad for both the RTs and for the criticism.    
    
    
    @jjredick Do not listen to those spewing hate at you, Roanoke Valley brother. Christ is now calling you to be a voice for the voiceless.    
    
    
    @JJRedick And if it seems being a Christian and being pro-abortion are compatible, see Didache 2.2 (c. 50-100 A.D.). http://www.earlychristianwritings.com/text/didache-lake.html …    
    
    
    @VVenustas Thank you!    
    
    
    Rezac: Poem Pope Francis never wrote--CNA http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/blog/the-poem-pope-francis-never-wrote/ … Reminds me of Seneca quote: "Believe them not in the absence of a hotlink."    
    
    
    Pray for Mrs. Cordoba & her family! http://www.bishopoconnell.org/page.cfm?p=676&newsid=826 … I interviewed here a few years ago. She would have been one of my colleagues.    
    
    
    @tom_perna Thanks for the #FF. Nice article on St. James. Keep up the good work.    
    
    
    North Carolina Governor Signs Pro-Life Bill Stopping Abortions http://www.lifenews.com/2013/07/26/north-carolina-governor-signs-pro-life-bill-stopping-abortions/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    North Carolina Eugenics: Sterilization Program Victims Offered Funds http://huff.to/1dZLXyH  31 states involved in this crime vs humanity.    
    
    
    @Pontifex Count on our constant prayers, your Holiness!    
    
    
    Looking forward to delving more deeply into Maximus's Greek. French is calling, too! pic.twitter.com/0euIAGa697    
    
    
    @directorsilk @gallicho Couple points: Re:Church dogma, as in the Assumption, a Pope does not change Church doctrine; rather, he defines it.    
    
    
    @directorsilk @gallicho 2nd: Assumption was not unprecedented, as Immaculate Conception was similarly defined in 1854 (albeit before Vat1).    
    
    
    @directorsilk @gallicho 3rd: In both instances (1854 & 1950), there was massive collaboration with the will of the bishops of the world.    
    
    
    #Royals: Most disheartening 9-game winning streak ever? In that time, the Tigers are 7-1, and the Indians, 8-1.    
    
    
    Whistleblowers: Intimidation, cover-up, weapons. #CIA apparently has much to hide in #Benghazi #scandal. http://thelead.blogs.cnn.com/2013/08/01/exclusive-dozens-of-cia-operatives-on-the-ground-during-benghazi-attack/ …    
    
    
    Interesting look at what the research is showing ... The Injustices of the Surrogacy Industry | CWR http://www.catholicworldreport.com/Item/2475/the_injustices_of_the_surrogacy_industry.aspx#.UfvdI0nsEu8.twitter …    
    
    
    Criminal serving sentence with monks pleads to be sent back to prison http://bit.ly/v0xydv  One man's heaven, another's hell. #Ascesis FTW    
    
    
    Cal Catholic: Archbishop Gomez urges action on CA state senate bill, SB131 - http://s.shr.lc/11HB9mq     
    
    
    10 Quotes That Prove The Pope Is A Liberal | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/blog/pat-archbold/10-quotes-that-prove-the-pope-is-a-liberal …    
    
    
    Media That Clamored Against Komen Skips Planned Parenthood Paying $4.3 Million in Medicaid Fraud Case | NewsBusters http://shar.es/ytZYd     
    
    
    I hope to access Migne's Patrologiae Cursus Completus: Series Graeca (167 vols.) on my @Logos Bible Software http://www.logos.com/product/28903/patrologiae-cursus-completus-series-graeca …    
    
    
    Technology at the service of humanity... http://www.upworthy.com/omg-best-use-of-a-billboard-i-have-ever-seen?g=2 … #socialjustice #subsidiarity #solidarity #CaritasinVeritate    
    
    
    Sacramento alert for next week: Bad bills! Bathroom bill and gender bill. - http://s.shr.lc/14EAOEX     
    
    
    TCF: Samples from Centuries on Love: Maximus the Confessor: Maximus the Confessor's Centuries on Love ... http://bit.ly/1413fql  <--More    
    
    
    Pope Francis to Consecrate the World to Mary’s Immaculate Heart | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.registerticket.com/eedaily-news/pope-francis-to-consecrate-the-world-to-marys-immaculate-heart … Yes!    
    
    
    TCF: JP Catholic Students' Production of Redline Featured in LA Times: On the feast of St. Maximilian ... http://bit.ly/1a5MuSs  <--More    
    
    
    Reminder, Catholics: Tomorrow is a Holy Day of Obligation. Don't forget to attend morning or evening Mass of the #Assumption at your parish.    
    
    
    Reading assignment for today: Munificentissimus Deus http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/pius_xii/apost_constitutions/documents/hf_p-xii_apc_19501101_munificentissimus-deus_en.html … Happy Feast of the #Assumption! Don't forget to go to Mass.    
    
    
    Pray for Christians in Egypt. Brothers and sisters in the One Body are suffering and need our prayers as they watch church and home burn.    
    
    
    British medical journal: 16-year-old girl became infertile from Gardasil vaccine - http://s.shr.lc/1cS5xAJ     
    
    
    @tom_perna Nicely done! Attending the Eastern rite Masses is quite a breath of fresh air!    
    
    
    Wow! This perfect throw reminds me of that one from Ichiro back when he was with the M's... http://atmlb.com/16XbtUT     
    
    
    Horror! Muslim Brotherhood Torches Christian Orphanage, 100-Year-Old Catholic School, and more http://shar.es/z1IEU  via @gatewaypundit    
    
    
    TCF: Oremus: For Egypt and Our Brothers and Sisters Suffering in the Body: Upon seeing this image of a... http://bit.ly/16BbDTs  <--More    
    
    
    Filming Begins in 2014: Nicea – following The Passion of Christ - http://s.shr.lc/176Kt5e  Lots of drama in church history! Should be good.    
    
    
    California lawmaker pulls son from class over transgender law - http://s.shr.lc/18aCb9A  via @CalCatholic    
    
    
    Archbishop Gänswein: Zenit article completely false that "God told" Benedict to resign - „Von A bis Z erfunden“ http://www.kath.net/news/42560     
    
    
    ... and if anyone knows the intimate truth of the matter, it's Gänswein.    
    
    
    New California Law Forces Parishes To Switch To E-Thuribles  http://www.eyeofthetiber.com/2013/08/22/new-california-law-forces-parishes-to-switch-to-e-thuribles/ … #Catholic Wouldn't be surprised if it became true 1 day!    
    
    
    At least something is right in the world. This is a happy photo. http://40daysforlife.com/blog/?p=4625     
    
    
    A new secretary of state for the Vatican, and Gänswein to remain prefect of the papal household. http://www.kath.net/news/42629     
    
    
    @susanslusser And 4th straight year with a winning record at home.    
    
    
    What is this, home run day? 40(+?) in 15 games. Seems quite unusual.    
    
    
    One of my favorite classroom interruptions is when a former student drops in for a surprise visit.    
    
    
    You can't tell me there's no such thing as a guardian angel after seeing this mudslide clip! http://www.weather.com/news/incredible-weather-gifs-20130905?cm_ven=Twitter … via @weatherchannel    
    
    
    Whatever fasting, prayer, sufferings you have today, offer it to God for peace, especially in Syria. #prayforpeace #PrayForSyria    
    
    
    Still a mystery. Why? #NeverForget #september11 2012, #benghazi    
    
    
    #wherewereyou I was a college senior, and broke the news to everyone in my psychology class that a.m. When the buildings fell, we went home.    
    
    
    America, #Remember911, when we stopped honking horns at each other and became neighbors again, when we returned to God and united in prayer.    
    
    
    Putin publishes must-read op-ed in NYT: A Plea for Caution From Russia http://nyti.ms/1eFFMCQ     
    
    
    @tom_perna @theologyteach I enjoyed reading this. Thanks, Tom!    
    
    
    #ThanksPontifex for being the advocate for peace and for leading the world into prayer for our brothers and sisters in Syria!    
    
    
    @frbmcgrath Very interesting! Thank you!    
    
    
    #BeingAChristian "...that they may all be one..." When one member suffers, the whole body suffers. Pray for Christians in Syria and Egypt!    
    
    
    TCF: Becoming Marian--The Beloved Disciple Takes Her "Into His Reality" (εἰς τὰ ἴδια):  Michelangelo's... http://bit.ly/1gjG54g  <--More    
    
    
    Prayers for the repose of the souls killed and consolation of the families of those who serve our country. #NavyYardShooting    
    
    
    Requiem aeternam dona eis, Domine, et lux perpetua luceat eis. Requiescant in pace. Amen. #NavyYardShooting    
    
    
    @MichaelPBarber Congrats to all the Barbers! Good name! He looks like he is already engaged in deep, Scriptural contemplation.    
    
    
    Unlikely, but if the #Royals can sweep the #Rangers and if the #Orioles win 3 of 4 from the #Rays, this may be one crazy last week of #MLB.    
    
    
    RT Atom Bomb Nearly Exploded Over North Carolina in 1961: UK Paper http://www.theblaze.com/stories/2013/09/20/atom-bomb-nearly-exploded-over-north-carolina-in-1961-uk-paper/?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=ShareButtons&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=story&utm_campaign=ShareButtons … Wow. How many of us wouldn't be here?    
    
    
    @badgercatholic Why, that'd be Benedict XVI, of course!    
    
    
    DThmpsn: Suicide bombers kill 60-200 Christians in Pakistan. NOW will world wake up to Islamist war on Christianity? http://fw.to/06I6gwa     
    
    
    Hosmer double, no outs, bottom 10th. Go, #Royals! #Athletics    
    
    
        
    
    
    #ALWestChamps! #Athletics! Congrats to #Royals on a winning season!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @pdawg17 @susanslusser We tied Boston 3-3. Next is intradivision. http://mlb.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20130904&content_id=59527184&c_id=mlb …    
    
    
    @susanslusser Wow--tied intradivision. So we have a .591 winning % against the AL West, the Sox a .589 against the AL East.    
    
    
    @RaysBaseball While the Rangers and Indians are still in pursuit, the Royals with 74 losses can only chase after the Indians, not the Rays.    
    
    
    Cal Catholic: Pope Francis excommunicates Australian priest - http://s.shr.lc/15VWdIe     
    
    
    American Spectator: When Paul Corrected Peter http://ow.ly/23Juto     
    
    
    Benedict XVI Publicly Responds to Atheist’s Critique: NCRegister http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/pope-benedict-publicly-responds-to-atheists-critique … Looking forward to reading this letter in full!    
    
    
    Twitter trends sure are perplexing. #badassconfessions - #sluttyconfessions Why, people? You are worth so much more.    
    
    
    #badassconfessions "Bless me, Father, for I have sinned. I wish no longer to be a 'badass,' as they say, but a worthy son of the Most High."    
    
    
    #sluttyconfessions "Bless me, Father, for I have sinned. I repent and wish to live like a daughter of the Most High."    
    
    
    Yeah. I'm never leaving America again. "Giant Hornets Killing Dozens" http://wxch.nl/1bdOzcU  Warning: Do not watch. Stay indoors forever.    
    
    
    Comments from Germain Grisez to @RobertMoynihan regarding Pope Francis's language in recent interviews. http://themoynihanletters.com/from-the-desk-of/letter-90-editorial-on-popes-interview …    
    
    
    Lost In Translation … http://shar.es/KKfFc  via @the_crescat    
    
    
    Pope Francis interview in La Repubblica, or, “Is This Now My Fate?” http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/10/pope-francis-interview-in-la-repubblica-or-is-this-now-my-fate/ … via @fatherz    
    
    
    Shameful. Honor Flight to World War II Memorial in jeopardy due to shutdown http://www.northwestohio.com/news/story.aspx?id=953619 … via @wnwotv    
    
    
    R.I.P., Tom Clancy    
    
    
    People talk religion all the time and publicly. Are you grown yet? Enter the conversation. Talk to strangers. #newevangelization    
    
    
    Requesting prayers for a special intention. Thank you!    
    
    
    Unfortunately, this game reminds me a lot of Game 5 of last year. Hopefully, different result. #Athletics    
    
    
    @dnowaczewski2 Hard to win when striking out 16 times. This series could be over in a hurry.    
    
    
    @lukei4655 Was there this summer. Utterly breath-taking mosaic work!    
    
    
    @JaneMLB Let's hope they have neither the chance to extend nor to break their 5-game Game 5 losing streak in ALDS play.    
    
    
    Enjoyed watching the #Athletics with my 5-year-old. Good company numbs the sting. Congrats on a great season.    
    
    
    Powerful: Pope Francis speaks about the Faith of Mary http://shar.es/E5V05  Very relevant in light of his comments to women's conference.    
    
    
    A Married Mom and Dad Really Do Matter: New Evidence from Canada | Public Discourse http://bit.ly/GJKh3d     
    
    
    Christmas in October as Fr. Daley's translation of Transfiguration homilies arrives. Wow! http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0881414670?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=0881414670&linkCode=shr&tag=thechafir-20&qid=1381612032&sr=8-1&keywords=light+on+the+mountain …    
    
    
    Pope consecrates the world to Immaculate Heart of Mary | CNA http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/pope-entrusts-world-to-immaculate-heart-of-mary/#.UlsbJVcRHIM.twitter … #Fatima    
    
    
    Wow. No hits again for a #Tigers pitcher through 5? Apparently, the best thing to do after clinching is to be no-hit in game 162. #ALCS    
    
    
    Transgender Boy Harassing Girls in the Bathroom Gets No Punishment [but harassment victims are threatened] http://shar.es/E4okQ     
    
    
    @bettnet @TheAnchoress A MLB pitcher throws 110 pitches as hard as he can and takes 5 days off. Don't really hear of QBs having TJ surgery.    
    
    
    French bishops restore Lord's Prayer to a less misleading form: "Et ne nous laisse pas entrer en tentation" http://news.yahoo.com/french-church-reword-blasphemous-lords-prayer-173309950.html …    
    
    
    Very little denouement left in this #NLCS: the Cardinals are going to the World Series.    
    
    
    CalCatholic: Let's spit and create perfect baby http://s.shr.lc/1cGrnot  Would that these evils had remained in the genre of science fiction!    
    
    
    An important read - Federalist: Can We Finally Start Talking About The Global Persecution Of Christians?  http://thefederalist.com/2013/09/25/can-we-finally-start-talking-about-the-global-persecution-of-christians/ … via @FDRLST    
    
    
    Is Evangelical Liberalism an Oxymoron? | First Things http://shar.es/EUpeq  @firstthingsmag An enlightening read from @GRMcDermott.    
    
    
    @TomCrowe The teams that are left are all "Yankees Lite." I wish they both could lose. Too bad that didn't happen in the ALDS.    
    
    
    @roccopalmo Wasn't the 2005 Series White Sox vs. Astros?    
    
    
    @PhilosophyQuotz ἀρχὴ σοφίας φόβος κυρίου (Initium sapientiae timor Domini)    
    
    
    Happy feast day, Pope Bl. John Paul II (soon to be "St."!) Ora pro nobis! Totus tuus, Maria!    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Cards in 7 - that's my prediction.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Pitchers fare better in cold weather. Should be a big series for Big Papi, however; he is well-insulated.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Speaking as one with a cold-weather build, of course...    
    
    
    LMU nearly drops abortion coverage, then renounces Catholic teachings as shackles and praises dissent. Confused much? http://www.cardinalnewmansociety.org/CatholicEducationDaily/DetailsPage/tabid/102/ArticleID/2635/Loyola-Marymount-President-Sending-Mixed-Signals-on-Abortion-and-Catholic-Identity.aspx …    
    
    
    Report on theology society both 'encouraging, saddening' | Catholic News Agency http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/report-on-theology-society-both-encouraging-saddening/#.UmitY_U5-B0.twitter …    
    
    
    Good job, Jim Joyce. Made the right call.    
    
    
    @dschoenfield Seems like near-perfect justice to me. http://espn.go.com/mlb/recap?gameId=231004102 …    
    
    
    Tonight wasn't the 1st #obstruction call involving the #redsox in the playoffs. In fact, they were the beneficiaries: http://espn.go.com/mlb/recap?gameId=231004102 …    
    
    
    #redsox were once the beneficiaries of 2 questionable #obstruction calls in the same playoff game: http://espn.go.com/mlb/recap?gameId=231004102 … Me: #schadenfreude    
    
    
    @DanielGarlandJr I've seen more ridiculous obstruction calls. The one in 2003 against Tejada was a worse call. At least this one was correct    
    
    
    Action Needed As Kidnapping Of Syrian Archbishops Reaches 180 Days http://huff.to/1d76rHs  via @HuffPostRelig    
    
    
    @MarcelLeJeune Both equally horrible for different reasons.    
    
    
    Western eyewitness of #Benghazi goes public: http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2013/10/27/report-first-western-eyewitness-in-benghazi-to-go-public-gives-account-attack/ …    
    
    
    "The Most High knew that Adam wanted to become a god, so He sent His Son who put him on in order to grant him his desire." St. Ephrem    
    
    
    Reading St. Ephrem makes me want to go to heaven immediately.    
    
    
    "I learned how, compared to Paradise, 
our abode is a dungeon; 
yet the prisoners within it 
weep when they leave it!"
~ St. Ephrem    
    
    
    @twitter, I don't like the change with the photos! Be less like Facebook; that's a good plan.    
    
    
    David Ortiz: Best World Series performance ever?    
    
    
    @becs_315 I always miss Virginia in the fall! California is great, but there are only two seasons here: sunny and 65-75, sunny and 75-85.    
    
    
    #embarassingstorytime That time you started a trend on Twitter with a misspelled word in it.    
    
    
    Required reading: Thomas Peters: Reflections On My Time Away | CatholicVote http://www.catholicvote.org/reflections-on-my-time-away/#.UnZJx1NyCjc.twitter … #suffering #problemofevil #providence    
    
    
    Some say Daylight Savings Time is all about economics. I say it is a conspiracy to purge the job market of narcoleptics in the springtime.    
    
    
    Agreed. @JulieBorowski The real question is more like, why did the GOP fail to support its man? That's the difference-maker.    
    
    
    I paid $3.49/gal for gas today. It was like I entered into a time warp back to the middle of Obama’s first term.    
    
    
    What does the U.S. & Canada have in common with N.Korea & China? Abortion for any reason: http://s.shr.lc/192nLIM     
    
    
    Exploring the possibilities--more high-tech bellwork coming to the classroom!  #tech13oc #tRCot    
    
    
    #ff @Pontifex    
    
    
    Catholic scholars blast Common Core in letter to U.S. bishops http://wapo.st/1faa0gC  #commoncore #Catholic    
    
    
    @technomaven Thank you for your keynote presentation. Lots of great resources.    
    
    
    CNS: NCEA gets Gates Foundation grant to promote ‘Common Core’ in Catholic schools http://shar.es/8mfsc  #Catholic #commoncore    
    
    
    A shout out to Hankook Tires. I missed by 4 days the deadline for an $80 rebate, but after writing them a letter, they sent me one anyway.    
    
    
    @tom_perna Congrats!    
    
    
    @jksoren82 Sometimes, love for the customer prevails over the bottom dollar--a nice contrast from the more common experience these days.    
    
    
    @jksoren82 but you are quite punny. Let's catch up soon.    
    
    
    That was some exciting football! Big plays on offense and defense. Congrats, JSerra!    
    
    
    Disturbing realities from Austin Ruse:  Quotas for Transsexuals: What ENDA Portends | Crisis Magazine http://www.crisismagazine.com/2013/quotas-for-transsexuals-what-enda-portends#.Un6xEEBSG6Q.twitter …    
    
    
    Savage bully is at it again. This time, "mandatory" abortion. How does that work? Pro-choice, or pro-compulsion? http://dailycaller.com/2013/11/06/dan-savage-abortion-should-be-mandatory-for-30-years/ …    
    
    
    Prayers to all in the Philippines, where the death toll may be as high as 10,000. http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Peace/2013/11/09/PHILIPPINE-TYPHOON-DEATH-TOLL-COULD-REACH-10k?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter … Comparable to Cat-4 hurricane.    
    
    
    Philippines: a way for you to help: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OxDDQ9PR4SU … Above all, please pray for them.    
    
    
    Bl. Junipero Serra biography ignores priest's heroism, critic says | CNA http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/bl-junipero-serra-biography-ignores-priests-heroism-critic-says/#.Un_6__1fTzI.twitter …    
    
    
    #ObamacareRockAndRolloutHits Love Will Keep Us Alive    
    
    
    Thankful for all the veterans in my family and all who have served our country. May God richly reward them all for their sacrifices.    
    
    
    Cardinal Castrillon says Pope Francis has "no problem" with Extraordinary Form or with groups promoting it http://shar.es/8rXAP     
    
    
    On the phenomena surrounding the increased practice of cremation and the importance of burying the dead: http://www.catholicuniversebulletin.org/THEOLOGY13/theology1.php …    
    
    
    Requiem aeternam dona eis, Domine, et lux perpetua luceat eis. Requiescant in pace. #VeteransDay    
    
    
    Picked up Thanksgiving turkey today. By my estimation, the fairest of all the fowl.    
    
    
    NCRegister | Cardinal O’Malley on Vatican Reform and Other Key Church Issues http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/cardinal-omalley-on-vatican-reform-and-major-issues-facing-the-u.s.-church …    
    
    
    Congrats to my friend @BetsyK1 on co-publishing this book with @DrJrobackmorse. Looking forward to reading! http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1594714460?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=1594714460&linkCode=shr&tag=thechafir-20&f_rd_m=ATVPDKIKX0DER&pf_rd_s=center-2&pf_rd_r=0C5T9JXY40DYT0F045MW&pf_rd_t=101&pf_rd_p=1630083502&pf_rd_i=507846 … #marriage    
    
    
    When the Obama Magic Died http://www.realclearpolitics.com/articles/2013/11/16/when_the_obama_magic_died_120680.html#.UomUTNdfTq0.twitter …    
    
    
    MT @AHMalcolm Census faked 2012 unemployment data to help Obama's reelection http://bit.ly/19Bnpcm     
    
    
    @AHMalcolm @TomCrowe And the more scandals there were, the less any one of them seemed scandalous...    
    
    
    Haha! IJ Review: "SNL's Hilarious 'Presidential Depression' Fake Ad is About the Hardest-Hitting Obama Satire Yet" http://www.ijreview.com/2013/11/95715-snls-hilarious-presidential-depression-fake-ad-hardest-hitting-satire-yet/ …    
    
    
    A lot of people don't get why Catholics are so fixated on abortion, but understanding Catholics' passion for the issue is very simple.    
    
    
    What if Catholics are actually right? What if every abortion actually takes the life of a unique and unrepeatable human person?    
    
    
    @stvsmith2009 Jesus' authority trumps here (Lk 6:30: παντὶ αἰτοῦντί σε δίδου).    
    
    
    @stvsmith2009 Chrysostom is also very clear: "Why dost thou neither take pity thyself, and dissuadest those who would? ...    
    
    
    @stvsmith2009 If we spend upon all indifferently, we shall always have compassion."    
    
    
    @DaveArmstrong58 Thanks for the discussion in the commentary. I used to agree with you, btw. Luke 6:30 and John Chrysostom changed my mind.    
    
    
    Enjoying dramatic and glorious Pacific sunsets the past couple of days. Just a small reminder that we are created to be fulfilled by beauty.    
    
    
    Thank you, Pope Benedict XVI, for the #YearOfFaith.    
    
    
    We've been through a lot as a Church since the #YearofFaith began in October 2012. The light of faith shines into this world's darkness!    
    
    
    @lukei4655 What an awesome piece! That makes me want to pick up the tambourine and sing "Lord of the Dance." http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PEAIJV6CmtA …    
    
    
    ὃς ἐρρύσατο ἡμᾶς ἐκ τῆς ἐξουσίας τοῦ σκότους καὶ μετέστησεν εἰς τὴν βασιλείαν τοῦ υἱοῦ τῆς ἀγάπης αὐτοῦ #YearofFaith    
    
    
    Prayers requested for a friend whose newborn is fighting for her life.    
    
    
    "The Most High knew that Adam had wanted to become a god, so He sent His Son who clothed Himself in Adam to grant him his desire." ~Ephrem    
    
    
    If one plans to listen to the media regarding Evangelii Gaudium, instead use the time to read it (in sum or in part) http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/francesco/apost_exhortations/documents/papa-francesco_esortazione-ap_20131124_evangelii-gaudium_en.html …    
    
    
    My 2 year old, with quivering lip: "I need chocolate." Me: "Why?" Her answer: "Because I might cry."    
    
    
    Please pray for my friends' newborn baby, Lily. Please also read about her and offer your prayers with faith: http://prayforlily.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    #GoSpartans! MT @SalemSpartans Sherando beat Courtland. On to Sherando next Sat. for the state semifinal/4A North championship.    
    
    
    "...by deification the saints are gods ..." St. John of Damascus, Defense Against Those Who Attack the Holy Images http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/0881412457?ie=UTF8&camp=213733&creative=393185&creativeASIN=0881412457&linkCode=shr&tag=thechafir-20&qid=1386210022&sr=8-1&keywords=treatises+images+damascus …    
    
    
    Obama admin, Matthews' tingly leg kicks ballerinas off the stage http://www.foxnews.com/opinion/2013/12/05/young-ballerinas-kicked-out-theater-for-msnbc-obama-interview/ …    
    
    
    Fr. Edward Oakes, 65, passes http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/jesuit-theologian-remembered-for-scholarship-joyfulness/#.UqKjZOJIL0U.twitter … Requiem aeternam dona ei, Domine, et lux perpetua luceat ei. Requiescat in pace. Amen.    
    
    
    How can anyone support abortion? It still numbs the mind. "Father, forgive them; for they know not what they do."    
    
    
    Prayers for Stephen Ray's grandson who was rushed to the hospital http://shar.es/O0KE5     
    
    
    Pray For Lily: Good News, Bad News http://prayforlily.blogspot.com/2013/12/good-news-bad-news.html?spref=tw … Please keep praying for our friends' little girl!    
    
    
    MT @TwitchyTeam ESPN reportedly refuses Catholic hospital ad: ‘problematic’ mention of Jesus [video] http://twitchy.com/2013/12/11/espn-blasted-after-reportedly-refusing-catholic-hospital-ad-due-to-problematic-mention-of-jesus-video/#.UqlCEVTXe3M.twitter …    
    
    
    Note to aspiring professionals: When a doctor says "crap" and "that sucks" it does not inspire patience confidence.    
    
    
    Prayers, please! Thank you!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Right to life, liberty, pursuit of happiness. The order mattered to the founding fathers. Which one is listed first? #PraytoEndAbortion    
    
    
    @reneejulene I am sorry for your loss, Renee. To God, your sons are most precious, and still are.    
    
    
    Death is not the end. All the dead will rise from their tombs on the last day when Christ comes in glory. #PraytoEndAbortion    
    
    
    @PhilosophyQuotz So cartesian! So easily refuted! This was not Locke's brightest statement.    
    
    
    @reneejulene Do you know of the coming resurrection? All the dead will be raised. Death does not have the final word. http://www.vatican.va/archive/ENG0015/__P2G.HTM …    
    
    
    @reneejulene Renee, you initiated the conversation. Take care and God bless you.    
    
    
    Strange that there is no news coverage of the freight train derailment in Oceanside. Lots of commuters would be interested in that story!    
    
    
    Picked the wrong day to ride the train. This is a good reminder that no mode of travel is perfectly safe.    
    
    
    Yellowstone supervolcano magma chamber 2.5 times bigger than previously thought. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-25312674 …    
    
    
    Set copier to print finals. Forgot to select "staple." #teacherproblems    
    
    
    Manila envelope nearly took off my thumb. May need transfusion. #teacherproblems    
    
    
    TCF: Gaudete! Some Voices Bid You Rejoice! Happy Gaudete Sunday: For more on Gaudete Sunday, read what... http://bit.ly/JsT0Ij  <--More    
    
    
    Snowden vindicated? Either way: NSA ruling makes for a bad day for Obama. http://www.forbes.com/sites/kashmirhill/2013/12/16/federal-judge-writes-epic-smackdown-of-unconstitutional-nsa-phone-record-collection/?utm_source=dlvr.it&utm_medium=twitter … Good day for freedom...    
    
    
    Tomorrow, my students will darken nearly 10,000 bubbles on their finals. Say a little prayer for those saints-in-the-making.    
    
    
    Very difficult to follow the logic here. "Feds: #Harvard bomb threat was made by student trying to avoid final" http://abc13.co/1hizlWX     
    
    
    Karl Marx trending on Twitter. Hopefully everyone is discussing how bad his ideas were for humanity. Remember, the dead tweet no tweets.    
    
    
    Apparently, Marx devotees know how to bring the animus. Folks throwing anti-Catholic slurs at me. People to pray for + Jn. 15:18 = win/win    
    
    
    Anderson: Penalizing Those Who Hold Biblical Views of Marriage http://natl.re/JI2z5D  via @NRO #DuckDynasty    
    
    
    Cardinal Newman Society: ‘Catholic Is Our Core’ Launched to Address Concerns about Common Core in Catholic Schools http://shar.es/Ozmhu     
    
    
    Pray for our Navy, and for all those exposed to Fukushima radiation. Wow is this story disturbing! http://nypost.com/2013/12/22/70-navy-sailors-left-sickened-by-radiation-after-japan-rescue/ …    
    
    
    Ecce enim evangelizo vobis gaudium magnum, quod erit omni populo: quia natus est vobis hodie Salvator, qui est Christus Dominus.    
    
    
    "Chains shall He break for the slave is our brother; And in His name all oppression shall cease..."    
    
    
    "Sweet hymns of joy in grateful chorus raise we,
Let all within us praise His holy name..."    
    
    
    "Christ is the Lord! O praise His Name forever,
His power and glory evermore proclaim."    
    
    
    Happy Christmas and feast of St. Stephen! If you've not read his epic "last words" from his trial, read Acts 6:2-8:1 http://quod.lib.umich.edu/cgi/r/rsv/rsv-idx?type=DIV1&byte=5033832 …    
    
    
    The evil one cannot win. He is without hope for a reason: Christ has come to destroy his work. Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    Verbum is giving away a FREE copy of Foundations Plus! http://bit.ly/18H9vM4  Enter to win your copy on Epiphany.  http://ptab.it/22GKY     
    
    
    Click to help me win! Verbum is giving away a FREE copy of Foundations Plus! Enter to win your copy on Epiphany. http://ptab.it/22GKY     
    
    
    Could be your daughter, could be mine. We need to rally in prayer for this little girl and her family. http://www.lifenews.com/2013/12/27/hospital-yanking-jahi-mcmaths-life-support-refuses-to-transfer-her-to-new-facility/ …    
    
    
    Chargers! Bring on the Bengals!    
    
    
    Reminder: January 1 is a holy day of obligation for all Catholics (even for those traveling). Find a Church near you http://masstimes.org/     
    
    
    St. Andrew of Crete on the Θεοτόκος: "All things are made holy by your myrrh-like fragrance. ...    
    
    
    "... Because of you, sin's aggression is over; the curse of our first mother has been turned to grace."    
    
    
    St. Andrew: "O holy one, holier than all the saints, supremely holy treasury of all that makes us holy. ..."    
    
    
    "O woman who as one individual, without division or dissolution, united humanity to God!"    
    
    
    Breitbart: Rose Parade Same-Sex Marriage Condemned by LGBT Community http://shar.es/9v3uK     
    
    
    For the twenty-somethings at the coffee shop last night... Not OMG, but GGM http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/05/not-omg-but-ggm.html#.UsbxOXYs0As.twitter … Blessed be God. Blessed be his holy name.    
    
    
    Industry, not environmentalists, killed traditional bulbs http://bit.ly/KhSSvE#.UsbwNY_8o1A.twitter … via @DCExaminer    
    
    
    True and False Witness on the Abortion-Pill Mandate | http://CatholicVote.org : http://www.catholicvote.org/true-and-false-witness-on-the-abortion-pill-mandate/#.UsciRL1oieM.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Playing with My Christmas Presents--Retrieving Nicaea: Times, they do not change that much! Here I ... http://bit.ly/YVgmqp  <--More    
    
    
    Anglikanische Nonnen treten zur katholischen Kirche über http://www.kath.net/detail.php?id=39516 … @KatholikenNet #newevangelization    
    
    
    Happy 10th day of #Christmas & feast of the Holy Name of Jesus, the name above every other name! (Philippians 2:5-11)    
    
    
    DYK: 2013 is the first year with four consecutive integers (not in any particular order) since 1432?    
    
    
    "Unnecessary and ill-advised"? http://dailycaller.com/2013/01/03/obama-calls-ndaa-conscience-clause-for-military-chaplains-unnecessary-and-ill-advised/ … After this from Feb. http://www.theblaze.com/stories/u-s-military-silences-catholic-chaplains-from-speaking-out-against-obama-admin-ruling/ … extra measures are necessary and well-advised.    
    
    
    @GRMcDermott Excellent article!    
    
    
    Intelligent commentary #FF @GRMcDermott @matthewschmitz @catholicthing @PublicDiscourse @DouthatNYT @MarkSteynOnline @fbeckwith @ericmetaxas    
    
    
    #FF (quite obviously) @Pontifex    
    
    
    Happy 11th day of #Christmas and feast of St. Elizabeth Ann Seton, who created the first free Catholic school in U.S. http://www.catholic.org/saints/saint.php?saint_id=180 …    
    
    
    Pouring milk in the cereal before praying the blessing. #CatholicProblems    
    
    
    TCF: New Look to the Blog; Sacred Music Playlist Returns: Happy 11th day of Christmas, dear readers!Well... http://bit.ly/ZlPxjW  <--More    
    
    
    @preachermancp Reconciliation is important because of the validity of their orders and because their pastors have led sheep from the fold.    
    
    
    Outrageous: Nurses Fired for Refusing Flu Shot - Yahoo! News http://news.yahoo.com/nurses-fired-refusing-flu-shot-224637902--abc-news-health.html …    
    
    
    Happy 12th day of #Christmas and feast of St. John Neumann, who was a priest in Buffalo and Pittsburgh in the 1800s. #Epiphany is tomorrow!    
    
    
    Child support claim rankles sperm donor to lesbian pair: http://www.ruthblog.org/2013/01/05/child-support-claim-rankles-sperm-donor-to-lesbian-couple/ … Can anyone else see that children are victims in this society?    
    
    
    TCF: Commercial: Notre Dame's Former Coach, Faithful Catholic Lou Holtz, with an Invitation: Something t... http://bit.ly/WlnTfX  <--More    
    
    
    TCF: Adopt a Twerp - A Prayer Project to Assist the Holy Father, @Pontifex, on Twitter: Here at The Char... http://bit.ly/V0olo0  <--More    
    
    
    10 surprising quotes from abortionists http://liveactionnews.org/10-surprising-quotes-from-abortionists/ … #cultureofdeath    
    
    
    Please consider sharing this, @alwayscatholic @CatholicLisa @tom_perna @AmericanPapist http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/adopt-twerp-prayer-project-to-assist.html#.UOrGvWx5Ns4.twitter … God bless!    
    
    
    @youne090864 Yes. I saw your message to the Pope, and I will pray for your discernment of the priesthood.    
    
    
    Our Lady of Victory, Pray for us! First Things Tribute to Our Lady and to Her Team http://www.firstthings.com/onthesquare/2013/01/notre-dame-our-lady …    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict with a Shout Out to Hobby Lobby?: With this latest Tweet, I think obviously of Hobby ... http://bit.ly/WqzZ7u  <--More    
    
    
    @tom_perna Congrats, Tom! Many blessings to you and your students!    
    
    
    TCF: More on the Twerps: They Might Be Searching for God: More on the Church-meets-Twitter phenomenon. D... http://bit.ly/XLj9Hr  <--More    
    
    
    @MCardaronella With you, bro! http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/adopt-twerp-prayer-project-to-assist.html …    
    
    
    TCF: The Twerps Are Quick, Can You Be Quicker?--Please Re-Tweet!: There is a lot of love being shown to ... http://bit.ly/ZtxzHy  <--More    
    
    
    MT @Newman_Society New CUA business school rooted in Catholic social doctrine , natural law http://wp.me/pVkso-4fZ     
    
    
    TCF: Ironic March for Life Promo Video: March for Life, 2013, how I wish I could be there! But I will be... http://bit.ly/ZE1U6l  <--More    
    
    
    If #Michigan loses to Ohio State, #Duke should retain its No. 1 ranking. Duke beat #Louisville head-to-head and has played tougher schedule.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx We are about to freeze here in Southern Cal. Pray that our strawberries and oranges survive. Could cause fruit prices to rise.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Yes, I have been keeping track. You are quite right about that.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Oh, no! Good thing for our healthy economy. Wait ... never mind.    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx What's weird is that 30 miles down the coast, it's 15 degrees warmer right now.    
    
    
    Church Fathers answer question: "Why did Jesus insist on being baptized?" http://insightscoop.typepad.com/2004/2013/01/church-fathers-answer-the-question-why-did-jesus-insist-on-being-baptized.html … @ignatiusinsight Happy feast of the baptism!    
    
    
    Planned Parenthood quietly abandons ‘pro-choice’ http://goo.gl/HnJpI  Hmm. Will they keep "anti-choice zealots" in their rhetorical arsenal?    
    
    
    Deaf Twins Going Blind Euthanized: Yahoo http://news.yahoo.com/deaf-twins-going-blind-euthanized-165500992--abc-news-topstories.html … Next in state-sanctioned murder for Belgium: dementia patients and children    
    
    
    TCF: Speaking of Irony: "The Guardian" Challenges Moral Norms concerning Pedophilia - #dictatorshipofrel... http://bit.ly/103RWAa  <--More    
    
    
    TCF: Prayers and Help Needed for Continued Medical Care of Haitian Priest (Please Share and Re-Tweet): T... http://bit.ly/UpZnN7  <--More    
    
    
    6 Reasons Why Men Can Speak on #Abortion http://shar.es/49WFe     
    
    
    MT @PublicDiscourse “The rights of children trump the right to children”: Lessons from France on Defending #Marriage: http://www.thepublicdiscourse.com/2013/01/7601/     
    
    
    @OlafTyaransen Money feeds no one, only acts of service and love, i.e., the Church's constant mission. The Church is the wealth of the poor.    
    
    
    @atheistpunk Money feeds no one, only acts of service and love, i.e., the Church's constant mission. The Church is the wealth of the poor.    
    
    
    Advocating for the poor by trolling the Pope on Twitter? #logicfail    
    
    
    @atheistpunk False. Plus, if that's all you think the Pope does or says to Africa, then here is some assigned reading. http://www.google.com/url?sa=t&rct=j&q=&esrc=s&source=web&cd=1&cad=rja&ved=0CDUQFjAA&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vatican.va%2Fholy_father%2Fbenedict_xvi%2Fapost_exhortations%2Fdocuments%2Fhf_ben-xvi_exh_20111119_africae-munus_en.html&ei=-bn2UMX3CaqTiAL_sYD4DQ&usg=AFQjCNGIcr-w2FWP9-Q7M5G3yZJliwDspA&sig2=2H9i-mPbr9WF2ytZ9KiZOw&bvm=bv.41018144,d.cGE …    
    
    
    @HomefryDaddy @atheistpunk Buying food does not guarantee that bellies will be fed. (Thus, the Church's ministry of feeding the hungry.)    
    
    
    @atheistpunk @HomefryDaddy Your own bellies are bloated on the atheist narrative. Catholics feed more hungry than do any groups combined.    
    
    
    "Religious Freedom Day" today? 1 year after HHS mandate, will we celebrate Jan. 20 as take-away-religious-freedom-day? http://www.whitehouse.gov/the-press-office/2013/01/16/presidential-proclamation-religious-freedom-day#.UPdHGk7dC_g.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Twitter Habet Papam! Pope Opens Account for Tweeting in Latin: For a second there, I forgot it was ... http://bit.ly/SaXftQ  <--More    
    
    
    #FF #Catholic @Pontifex_ln    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns Unforgiven Debt    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns The Great Taxpayer Robbery    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns Young Guns, Old Guns, Knock, Knock, Give Us Your Guns    
    
    
    #LiberalWesterns California Conquest (Actually, that's it's real name.)    
    
    
    TCF: St. Athanasius on the Self-Effacement of St. Anthony of the Desert: TCF Quoteboard: As I read the w... http://bit.ly/13QWWXS  <--More    
    
    
    Steyn: Trillion-Dollar-Coin Fever: Has America’s choo-choo jumped the tracks? http://www.nationalreview.com/articles/338110/trillion-dollar-coin-fever-mark-steyn … via @NRO @MarkSteynOnline    
    
    
    See? #Duke should have been #1. Now that #Louisville and #Indiana have gone down, that little polling error should be fixed. @dukeblueplanet    
    
    
    Do you have a garden, @DanielGarlandJr? RT @PhilosophyQuotz If you have a garden and a library, you have everything you need. Cicero    
    
    
    @DanielGarlandJr Cicero was before scotch, so we can hardly fault him for the glaring omission.    
    
    
    Charities to boycott: Comic Relief, Eagles Clubs, Elks Clubs, Elton John AIDS Foundation, and the Red Cross http://www.lifenews.com/2011/09/12/pro-life-group-lists-companies-backing-planned-parenthood/ …    
    
    
    TCF: Viva Latina! First Papal Tweet in Angelic Tongue: @Pontifex_ln - first Latin Tweet! How cool is thi... http://bit.ly/T80oN0  <--More    
    
    
    Mandatory American reading: #MLK's Letter from a Birmingham Jail http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/02/patriotism-wrote-letter-patriotism.html#.UP11Nvmw5lM.twitter … #civildisobedience    
    
    
    Happy feast of St. Agnes, a lamb for Christ! Listen to Mike Aquilina on her life | St Paul Center for Biblical Theology http://www.salvationhistory.com/blog/st._agnes_a_lamb_for/#.UP13J0rdxme.twitter …    
    
    
    Obama Begins Inauguration Festivities With Ceremonial Drone Flyover http://onion.com/11MpnI7  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Viva la France! RT @TweetSmarter Should Google & Facebook be taxed for collecting your personal data? http://tnw.co/Vl772W     
    
    
    40 years of abortion on demand is not working. Time for a change:  Recognize the natural rights of the unborn today! Retweet if you agree.    
    
    
    MT @NCRegister Mother Teresa: "The greatest destroyer of peace today is #abortion because it is a war against the child." #prolife #Roe40    
    
    
    40  years of abortion on demand is 40 years too many. Be a #voiceforthevoiceless! Recognize the natural rights of the unborn today! #Roeat40    
    
    
    Two women are behind legalized #abortion in America: now both of them want it reversed: #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/two-women-legalized-abortion-in-america-now-both-of-them-want-it-reversed … #roeat40    
    
    
    Bishop Burbidge disallows EMHC’s from giving blessings during Communion http://www.splendoroftruth.com/curtjester/2013/01/bishop-burbidge-disallows-emhcs-from-giving-blessings-during-communion/ … via @curtjester    
    
    
    Mandatory viewing for #RoeAt40 http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/05/be-sufficiently-warned-but-you-must.html#.UP-XDSoqfR8.twitter … Some have done much wrong, others too little right; we all bear the guilt of our nation.    
    
    
    Reclaiming the Human Center of the Abortion Debate: http://youtu.be/dawFw_fPCw8  #RoeAt40    
    
    
    Recommended reading for #RoeAt40: Robert Spitzer's brilliant Ten Universal Principles  http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/05/strongly-recommended-ten-universal.html#.UP-cWE-J-MM.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Video:  New Evidences the Gospels were Based on Eyewitness Accounts (Dr. Peter Williams): Next time... http://bit.ly/UTzVzG  <--More    
    
    
    @tom_perna @StevenErtelt Tolerant to those who agree with them. Leftists (closet socialists) preach but do not practice democratic ideals.    
    
    
    My wife and I were talking about this last night. Glad to find this Moynihan article: Benedict Stands on the Ramparts http://catholicexchange.com/benedict-stands-on-the-ramparts/#.UQE0Tja3UJ8.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican celebrates 30 anniversary of Code of Canon Law, the work that "will never be complete" http://www.romereports.com/palio/vatican-celebrates-30-anniversary-of-code-of-canon-law-english-8816.html#.UQE2SIyGMJY.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Scuzziest Pro-Abortion Video Ever Brings the Exploitive Nature of Abortion into Sharp Relief: Kudos... http://bit.ly/10QJzZf  <--More    
    
    
    Scuzziest Pro-Abortion Video Ever Brings the Exploitive Nature of #Abortion into Sharp Relief http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/01/scuzziest-pro-abortion-video-ever.html#.UQKzqCddpMs.twitter … Today, #MarchforLife!    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ Seems an interesting testament to the role sanctifying grace plays in recognizing the gravity of the loss of innocent life.    
    
    
    I wish I were tweeting from the #MarchforLife! Instead, I'm offering work and prayers for the 500K+ marchers. Grace, peace, strength to you!    
    
    
    TCF: @Pontifex Joins #MarchforLife from Afar: Pope Benedict XVI Tweets to Marchers: No doubt a day in U.... http://bit.ly/TzBA0n  <--More    
    
    
    KC's Bishop Finn: National Catholic Reporter not a "Catholic" publication: The Catholic Key http://catholickey.org/2013/01/25/the-bishops-role-in-fostering-the-mission-of-the-catholic-media/ … Why no coverage by N_R?    
    
    
    More: @NCRonline not a 'Catholic' publication, says KC bishop: Catholic Culture http://shar.es/C61hm     
    
    
    1 More @NCRonline RT @fatherz Bp. Finn calls out the National Catholic Reporter: http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/01/bp-finn-calls-out-the-national-catholic-reporter/ … … #catholic #fishwrap #dissent #tcot    
    
    
    No bus stop in DC this time! MT @FatherZ #MarchforLife: Where was NCR? LCWR? Nuns on Bus? CHA? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/01/follow-up-march-for-life-where-was-ncr-lcwr-nuns-on-bus-cha/ … #abortion    
    
    
    Canonist Peters on His Excellency Finn's rebuke of N_R. Curious silence on the news from @NCRonline. http://canonlawblog.wordpress.com/2013/01/25/recognizing-the-national-catholic-reporter-for-what-it-is-actually-for-what-it-isnt/ … Hat tip @fatherz    
    
    
    Stan the Man - The True Face of Sportsmanship http://www.catholiceducation.org/articles/stories_of_faith_and_character/cs0585.htm …    
    
    
    Stopped in Taco Bell for first time in 4 years or so. Remembered why I have not gone to Taco Bell in 4 years or so.    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Gratias tibi, Sancte Pater, pro bona verba tuum. Oramus pro te quotidie. Ora pro nobis. Ora pro America.    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Thank you also for your many texts. My favorite was Behold the Pierced One. I also reviewed your Jesus of Nazareth for Zenit.    
    
    
    Happy feast day, @lukei4655!    
    
    
    Prayer of St. Thomas Aquinas Before Study http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2012/08/prayer-of-st-thomas-aquinas-before-study.html?spref=tw … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    TCF: St. Thomas Aquinas: True Liturgist: Happy feast day of St. Thomas Aquinas, particularly to all Domi... http://bit.ly/T0UtaY  <--More    
    
    
    Oregon Doctor Pushes Depressed Patient Into Assisted Suicide http://www.lifenews.com/2013/01/29/oregon-doctor-pushes-depressed-patient-into-assisted-suicide/ … via @StevenErtelt    
    
    
    Complaint: #Sebelius’ illegal campaign trip for Obama worse than we thought http://bit.ly/WBTtY6#.UQoT3ATOQ70.twitter … via @DCExaminer #HHS    
    
    
    Video: Why Can't Women Be Priests? An Explanation from the Theologian of the Papal Household http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/why-can.html#.UQvXoMqg1M0.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    @alwayscatholic Thank you for sharing! God bless you!    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln "... melior est enim obedientia quam victimæ, et auscultare magis quam offerre adipem arietum."    
    
    
    #WSJ: America's Baby Bust http://on.wsj.com/WJex1Q  via @WSJ #demographics #contraception #parenting #economics FYI: Parenting makes me happy!    
    
    
    @ericmetaxas I was disappointed to see that they have unfortunately taken a polemical turn of late. http://blog.abolishhumanabortion.com/2013/01/an-open-letter-to-pro-life-roman.html …    
    
    
    @ericmetaxas follow-up on prvs: We should unite in our common pursuit for the sake of life, and not pick at centuries-old doctrinal wounds.    
    
    
    TCF: Update on Haitian Priest: Fr. Dumas and a Request for Prayers: Fr. Dumas, whose story was shared he... http://bit.ly/VIhSwO  <--More    
    
    
    @Peets_Tweets 49ers: 29, Ravens: 24    
    
    
    @TinoTarango @CatholicLisa @RJGrigaitis Excellent!    
    
    
    Observations from tonight: Harbaugh has great meltdowns, Kaepernick looks like Megamind, hid children's eyes from Beyonce's soft porn show.    
    
    
    More observations: Commercials are making the #Superbowl an adults-only affair. The demonic and sexually explicit more in-the-face than ever    
    
    
    Oh the rows of days past over this or that religious ad! Tonight: voodoo curses, soul-selling (w/ Latin contract), and lots of fornication.    
    
    
    @TeDeumBlog She became a stumbling block for young women everywhere. Very disappointing.    
    
    
    @friarpark Bud Light's Voodoo commercials (I think there were at least three different ones) and Mercedes-Benz's string of commercials.    
    
    
    Was very impressed by #Kaepernick's play and the #49ers heart. Too much #Flacco. Congrats to the #Ravens and to #Birk, #Lewis, #Reed & crew!    
    
    
    Schoolboy, 7, playing imaginary game gets suspended http://on.kdvr.com/WPQ3FRS  An era without common sense. Save our world, little man! Save on!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MarcelLeJeune Preach! Adult entertainment = good scotch, good cigar, good conversation    
    
    
    #Jesuit high school's beautiful chapel renovation! http://seeingtheform.wordpress.com/2013/01/09/sacred-heart-chapel-tampa-fl/ … #sacredart #sacredarchitecture #newevangelization    
    
    
    Opinion on the services to bury Richard III "he must now be given a Catholic funeral Mass" | http://CatholicHerald.co.uk  http://www.catholicherald.co.uk/commentandblogs/2013/02/06/i-dont-mind-where-they-bury-richard-iii-but-having-been-denied-christian-burial-by-henry-tudor-he-must-now-be-given-a-catholic-funeral-mass/#.UROrNaNSOXo.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican's Head of Family Council, says his words about homosexuals were manipulated http://www.romereports.com/palio/vaticans-head-of-family-council-says-his-words-about-homosexuals-were-manipulated-english-8942.html#.URPbBwQE3o4.twitter …    
    
    
    Kardinal Meisner übt schwere Kritik an 'Katholikenphobie' http://www.kath.net/detail.php?id=39997 … via @KatholikenNet    
    
    
    Historic #canonization! Pope to announce elevation of 800+ #saints http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-will-announce-on-monday-date-for-canonization-for-over-800-saints-english-8965.html#.URZ7P0K4-9I.twitter … Best line: "John Paul II ... elevated 'only' 482"    
    
    
    #Prayers requested for a sick loved one and caretakers. Thank you!    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father, for your service to Holy Mother Church. Please count on our prayers.    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict Announces He is Resigning Effective Feb. 28: I am in shock, still hoping I am going t... http://bit.ly/126LnxG  <--More    
    
    
    I would encourage everyone, out of reverence to our current Holy Father, to wait for all the "next pope" talk until his seat is vacant.    
    
    
    Cardinal Dolan on Benedict’s Resignation http://shar.es/YG01g  via @firstthingsmag    
    
    
    Conclave apparently will be on March 18.    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father, for your service. When you retreat into prayer next month will you please pray for me and for my family?    
    
    
    No delay in hostility expressed against the Pope by media, spinning according to their narrative. #unsurprising #insensitive #ignoringthem    
    
    
    This is not the end of the world--maybe. Good article on St. Malachy And The Papal Prophecies by @DanielGarlandJr http://irishanddangerous.blogspot.com/2007/10/st-malachy-and-papal-prophecies.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The Sacred Page: Scott Hahn on the Pope's Resignation http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/02/scott-hahn-on-popes-resignation.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    CNS: Professor-Pope Resigns http://bsfurl.com/10X8K/1RsU/Sl0  "Champion of Catholic Education Renewal"    
    
    
    The unexpected announcement that rang out in the Concistory Hall via L'Osservatore Romano http://shar.es/Y6v4h     
    
    
    A sign that we should pray for the Church: Lightning strikes St. Peter's this afternoon via ANSA.it http://www.ansa.it/web/notizie/rubriche/politica/2013/02/11/Benedetto-XVI-lascia-pontificato-Papa-dimette-28-febbraio_8225601.html?idPhoto=1 … via @ansa_topnews    
    
    
    MT Germany's banning homeschooling doesn't violate rights: U.S. Attorney General’s office: LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/banning-homeschooling-does-not-violate-rights-u.s.-attorney-generals-office … #socialism    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln We are praying for you, Holy Father. May God reward you abundantly for your humble service to the Church.    
    
    
    More on the #lightning strike(s): Lightning bolt hit Vatican not once but TWICE hours after Pope's resignation http://mirr.im/X92PuJ     
    
    
    The reality of the end of the papacy of Pope Benedict XVI is starting to sink in. Until Christ comes, there will never be another like him.    
    
    
    Must-read: The Reluctant Pope http://amsp.ec/1Sbw6V  #dictatorshipofrelativism    
    
    
    Must-must read from Dr. Hahn: Benedict Will Still Be There for Us: http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/daily-news/benedict-will-still-be-there-for-us …    
    
    
    "The Lord is victorious" - Pope Benedict chats about Second Vatican Council with priests of Rome http://en.radiovaticana.va/news/2013/02/14/pope_to_rome%27s_priests:_the_second_vatican_council,_as_i_saw_it/en1-664858 …    
    
    
    Will there be an encyclical on faith as had been planned? http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/1300685.htm?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Rutler: Benedict’s Decision in the Light of Eternity | Crisis Magazine http://www.crisismagazine.com/2013/benedicts-decision-in-the-light-of-eternity#.UR6HqQaHPEA.twitter …    
    
    
    Cardinals will cease tweeting during the sacred Vatican conclave http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/1300682.htm?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Just started studying French a few weeks ago and am enjoying it much! Using the book "French for Reading" http://www.amazon.com/French-Reading-Karl-C-Sandberg/dp/0133316033/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&qid=1361044108&sr=8-1&keywords=french+for+reading …    
    
    
    Braut des Lammes: Ad completorium –  noch zum Rücktritt Papst Benedi... http://brautdeslammes.blogspot.com/2013/02/ad-completorium-noch-zum-rucktritt.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    De Ratzinger à Benoît XVI, itinéraire en images | http://La-Croix.com  http://www.la-croix.com/Religion/Actualite/De-Ratzinger-a-Benoit-XVI-itineraire-en-images-_NG_-2013-02-12-497073#.USBphRF1Ahw.twitter …    
    
    
    Benoît XVI, le pontificat en images | http://La-Croix.com  http://www.la-croix.com/Religion/Actualite/Benoit-XVI-le-pontificat-en-images-_NG_-2013-02-12-496969#.USBsQY4iy1I.twitter …    
    
    
    Catholic-bashers have embellished the truth about abuse in Catholic institutions. Time to put the record straight http://soc.li/8AVmfmS     
    
    
    MT St. Alphonsus Ligouri's letter prior to election of new pope: Fr. Z's Blog http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/a-saint-on-the-wretched-condition-of-the-church-while-waiting-for-a-new-pope-to-be-elected/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    6 Liturgical No-No's During Lent |Blogs | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/blog/jimmy-akin/6-liturgical-no-nos-during-lent …    
    
    
    Jesuit expert calls Benedict 'great reformer' on sex abuse | National _ Reporter: http://ncronline.org/blogs/ncr-today/jesuit-expert-calls-benedict-great-reformer-sex-abuse#.USJgXffJAZc.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict Comments on Resignation from Light of the World: It is difficult to comprehend that t... http://bit.ly/UAgRsz  <--More    
    
    
    POLL: What name will the next Pope choose? | Fr. Z's Blog – What Does The Prayer Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/poll-what-name-will-the-next-pope-choose/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Web surfing for long periods of time can cause withdrawal symptoms 'similar to people on a comedown from ecstasy' http://bit.ly/XTbXqw     
    
    
    RT Wherein Fr. Z makes a suggestion to Cardinal Electors http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/wherein-fr-z-makes-a-suggestion-to-cardinal-electors/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    #2BXVI Thank you for your constant service to the Church! God has made a great name for you, and you will always be our Papa Benedetto!    
    
    
    More on #Benedict’s revolutionary act: his astonishing predictions | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/blog/more-on-benedicts-revolutionary-act-his-astonishing-predictions …    
    
    
    Get some rest, says @roccopalmo. Big week ahead. "The Calm Before..." http://whispersintheloggia.blogspot.com/2013/02/the-calm-before.html …    
    
    
    "He is the hand that God stretches out to man" - The Holy Father's Angelus on Jesus' temptations. http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/benedict_xvi/angelus/2013/documents/hf_ben-xvi_ang_20130217_en.html …    
    
    
    TCF: For Your Lenten Motivation: Words On Penance from Pope Benedict: This is from Light of the World,... http://bit.ly/XFMvDG  <--More    
    
    
    #SongsThatWillNeverGetOld Te Deum. Pange Lingua. Veni Creator Spiritus. Ave Maria. #tRCot    
    
    
    Just watched Food Inc. Never eating again.    
    
    
    God, after Food Inc, in night's Divine Office: "You have put into my heart a greater joy than they have from abundance of corn and new wine"    
    
    
    Colorado bishop: National Catholic Reporter ‘is an embarrassment to the #Catholic Church’ | #LifeSiteNews http://www.lifesitenews.com/news/colorado-bishop-national-catholic-reporter-is-an-embarrassment-to-the-catho …    
    
    
    Pope's last Angelus: "The Lord is calling me 'out to the mountain' ... this does not mean I'm abandoning the Church." http://www.romereports.com/palio/popes-last-angelus-i-will-not-abandon-the-church-i-will-serve-in-a-different-way-english-9145.html#.USo7XDoNc9I.twitter …    
    
    
    Pope's Address At Conclusion of Lenten Spiritual Exercises | ZENIT http://www.zenit.org/en/articles/pope-s-address-at-conclusion-of-lenten-spiritual-exercises … #λογος #verbum #ars #beauty    
    
    
    Extraordinary Ministers of Communion giving blessings as if they were priests http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/quaeritur-extraordinary-ministers-of-communion-giving-blessings-as-if-they-were-priests/ … via @FatherZ See also Vatican letter    
    
    
    My #AdoptACardinal - His Eminence Anthony Olubunmi Cardinal Okogie, Archbishop Emeritus of Lagos, Nigeria http://adoptacardinal.org     
    
    
    The Pope's final general audience address to the English-speaking pilgrims http://www.vatican.va/holy_father/benedict_xvi/audiences/2013/documents/hf_ben-xvi_aud_20130227_en.html …    
    
    
    Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--English http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of.html#.US5CIT5_E-U.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--Latin http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of_27.html#.US5CO-fkBQY.twitter … via @kevinmclarke    
    
    
    Benedict XVI's most memorable moments with world leaders http://www.romereports.com/palio/benedict-xvis-most-memorable-moments-with-world-leaders-english-9183.html?utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=twitterfeed#.US5aEGa5fCY.twitter …    
    
    
    Partial Indulgence: Let us pray for our Pontiff, Pope Benedict http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/02/v-let-us-pray-for-our-pontiff-pope-benedict/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    "Anyone who has discovered Christ must lead others to him. A great joy cannot be kept to oneself. It has to be passed on." Pope Benedict XVI    
    
    
    @Pontifex Thank you, Holy Father. You will always be my Pope! God grant you your well-deserved peace for the remainder of your days!    
    
    
    #THANKSPONTIFEX In a couple of hours, he may no longer be the Holy Father, but he will always be our Pope!    
    
    
    #ThanksPontifex for your leadership and faithfulness to Him who calls. #Interregnum Come Holy Spirit!    
    
    
    TCF: Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Papal Tweets--Latin: Since the Vatican says that his Twitter ... http://bit.ly/YKqtBc  <--More    
    
    
    RT, please. Pope Benedict XVI, Complete List of Latin Papal Tweets http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of_27.html#.US_bsB4dldE.twitter …    
    
    
    RT, please. Glad I saved these-His tweets are deleted already! Pope Benedict XVI--Complete List of Eng. Papal Tweets http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/02/pope-benedict-xvi-complete-list-of.html#.US_dUnezW7k.twitter …    
    
    
    From Castel Gandolfo, Pope's Final Farewell | ZENIT - The World Seen From Rome http://www.zenit.org/en/articles/from-castel-gandolfo-pope-s-final-farewell …    
    
    
    The Death of Liberal Catholicism | Catholic Teacher Education http://beingcatholic.com.au/the-death-of-liberal-catholicism/ … It may take a bit longer than a quarter of a century.    
    
    
    CNA: Cardinals set date - March 4 - for meetings about next Pope; Conclave date not yet determined http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/cardinals-set-date-for-meetings-about-next-pope/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+catholicnewsagency%2Fdailynews+%28CNA+Daily+News%29&utm_term=daily+news#.UTC9dNrSqlE.twitter …    
    
    
    Bishop asks Catholics to affirm Church teaching. Catholics freak out. | Catholic World Report http://www.catholicworldreport.com/Blog/2032/bishop_asks_catholics_to_affirm_church_teaching_catholics_freak_out.aspx#.UTC-099zI9E.twitter …    
    
    
    Vatican's tribute book to #PopeBenedictXVI: beautiful images and quotes http://www.vatican.va/bxvi/omaggio/index_en.html …    
    
    
    Bishop enforces Catholic doctrine; press goes, ‘Wha …?’  http://www.patheos.com/blogs/getreligion/2013/03/bishop-enforces-catholic-doctrine-press-goes-wha/#sthash.ed5Mjosv.dpuf … Request "consistent with the right of all private schools"    
    
    
    Reno: Staying Home from the Conclave http://shar.es/jZmX7  via @firstthingsmag    
    
    
    @RichardDawkins It is very simple. If we are dying, priests come to our side for sacraments and strength as we make our final journey.    
    
    
    Pruden: White House under siege by reality - Washington Times: http://wtim.es/YGl0aB  via @washtimes    
    
    
    Interesting via @DeaconsBench: We've had African popes, but a black pope? Well, perhaps... http://shar.es/jxYe3     
    
    
    10 Reasons Cardinal Burke Will Be Next Pope ~ Dr. Taylor Marshall | Canterbury Tales http://shar.es/jKtwy  via @taylorrmarshall    
    
    
    #WeAllHaveThatOneFriend Who died for us on a Cross. Let us follow Him today.    
    
    
    @tom_perna There are a lot of exciting possibilities--not the least of which might be another Italian pope. Whoever he is, let him be holy.    
    
    
    @tom_perna I think this is going to be a longer conclave.    
    
    
    Interesting article on the papabili, the buzz around Rome, and the reliability of the "insiders." http://moynihanreport.itvworking.com/from-the-desk-of/letter-30-the-next-and-the-last … @RobertMoynihan    
    
    
    @tom_perna Who knows? Maybe they'll figure out who they will vote for quickly, even before the conclave. Complicating factors at play.    
    
    
    #InitialsOfSomeoneYouCareAbout ΜΡ ΘΥ #tRCot    
    
    
    Catholic school children hold a CONCLAVE! PHOTOS! What Does The Prayer Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/just-too-cool-catholic-school-children-hold-a-conclave-photos/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Cardinal Burke as Pope: Answering Two Common Objections ~ Dr. Taylor Marshall | Canterbury Tales http://shar.es/jOl2c  via @taylorrmarshall    
    
    
    @DanOnRadio Great job, @JamesMartinSJ! I disagree with this headline "almost goes ballistic." I thought you were quite well-spoken.    
    
    
    @DanOnRadio @JamesMartinSJ Ah. Well, I could not tell. Grace prevailed! Thanks for sharing.    
    
    
    @CardinalNapier Thank you, your eminence! We are glad to have more time to pray for you and for all the Cardinal-electors.    
    
    
    #WeAllHaveThatOneFriend Who suffered to give meaning to our own, Who died to save us from sin & death, Who rose to fill us with life & hope.    
    
    
    Right on. The Sacred Page: The next pope should be an "administrator"? "Reform" is more than managing bureaucracies! http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/03/the-next-pope-should-be-administrator.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    CNA: Hugo Chavez died 'in the bosom of the Church.' Died 'clinging to Christ' http://www.catholicnewsagency.com/news/hugo-chavez-died-in-the-bosom-of-the-church/#.UTeb55ovEwU.twitter … infinite #divinemercy > anyone's sins    
    
    
    Malcolm Ranjith, the Cardinal who lived through the 2004 Tsunami http://www.romereports.com/palio/malcolm-ranjith-the-cardinal-who-lived-through-the-2004-tsunami-english-9281.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter#.UTiPhkEY8hA.twitter …    
    
    
    All of my students today seemed quite excited to adopt their #cardinals. Adopt your own for prayer: http://www.adoptacardinal.org/adoption  #conclave #tRCot    
    
    
    It must be confusing to sort between the St. Louis #Cardinals and the Vatican City #Cardinals on Twitter these days. #Catholic #conclave    
    
    
    #GodsPraiseRoom "Worthy is the Lamb who was slain, to receive power and wealth and wisdom and might and honor and glory and blessing!"    
    
    
    #GodsPraiseRoom You gave us your own flesh as our true food, our bread from heaven, and your blood as true drink, just as you said. #John6    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ I do not think they foresaw that some cardinals would take so long to arrive when the retirement was announced Feb. 10.    
    
    
    @ThomasReeseSJ Plus, throughout the course of salvation history, momentous events have occurred over the course of 3 days.    
    
    
    #Conclave: March 12. Saints, come to our aid: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CKWRuFjIRFo&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    @lukei4655 I have good kids and supportive colleagues. Makes all the difference in the world. I'm sure your trials were quite meritorious.    
    
    
    #FF @CardinalBertone @CardinalDolan @CardinalSean @Cardinal_Wuerl @CardinalNapier @CardRavasi_en @TurksonCardinal @DomOdiloScherer @Pontifex    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Papal Projection #1--The Name: What name will the next Holy Father select? We all have our g... http://bit.ly/VRR4Ng  <--More    
    
    
    Bold Papal Projection #1--The Name: I think the next pope will be Paul VII. Why? Read more: http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-papal-projection-1-name.html#.UTq5i_6t4BE.twitter … What do you think?    
    
    
    Get a text alert when the new #pope is elected! http://www.popealarm.com     
    
    
    I predict the new Pope will pick the name Paul VII Make a guess: http://catholicvote.org/NameThePope.php  My prediction: http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-papal-projection-1-name.html …    
    
    
    "Aujourd'hui, c'est la journée de la femme! Mais quelle place pour la femme si on nie toutes les différences?" http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=593725493990935&set=a.514044101959075.134429.513639495332869&type=1 …    
    
    
    The 3 C's: Avoid these things the night before an exam via @wyzant Any friends interested in joining this tutoring network, I'll invite you.    
    
    
    "Kevin, yes, your Porsche is ready!" said the ebullient tire salesman to the theology teacher. #awkwardsocialclassmixup, just 5 minutes ago    
    
    
        
    
    
    Video: A look inside the Papal conclave | http://CatholicVote.org : http://www.catholicvote.org/video-a-look-inside-the-papal-conclave/#.UTvhyw8j1A0.twitter …    
    
    
    1 man, 1 woman, 2 girls, 2 alarm clocks, 2 cellphones, 1 epic 8- to 12-week battle against the unrelenting passage of time. Bring on DST!    
    
    
    @LHuizenga @dakotapastor As it is in Luke 22:32, another set of verses that deals with Peter and the Twelve.    
    
    
    Congrats, @SalemSpartans! State titles for boys and girls hoops!    
    
    
    @dakotapastor @LHuizenga There is no mention of keys in that episode; rather, it refers to the power of forgiveness/retention of sins.    
    
    
    Ruse: Dare we hope for Burke? http://www.thecatholicthing.org/columns/2013/dare-we-hope-for-burke.html#.UT12bcQsLCQ.twitter …    
    
    
    9 things you need to know about how cardinals actually vote in conclaves |Blogs | http://NCRegister.com  http://www.ncregister.com/blog/jimmy-akin/9-things-you-need-to-know-about-how-cardinals-actually-vote-in-conclaves … #NCRegister    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Prediction No. 2—Where the Pope Will Not Be From: With the conclave just about 24 hours away... http://bit.ly/14NHkmJ  <--More    
    
    
    Rome Reports: A look at the History of the Conclave http://www.romereports.com/palio/a-look-at-the-history-of-the-conclave-english-9343.html#.UT37Qqrr8_g.twitter …    
    
    
    TCF: Bold Projection #3—The Pope Will Be Catholic: You can take this last one to the bank. What? Did y... http://bit.ly/14QoV8T  <--More    
    
    
    The Charcoal Fire: Bold Projection #3—The Pope Will Be Catholic http://kevinmclarke.blogspot.com/2013/03/bold-projection-3the-pope-will-be.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @TeDeumBlog @EWTN They are doing a good job. It's not the same, however, without Fr. Neuhaus. Requiescat in pace!    
    
    
    If Michael Jordan were a cardinal, would he vote for André Cardinal Vingt-Trois? #tRCot #conclave    
    
    
    @disciple96 @TeDeumBlog @EWTN Yes. I will never forget him or his coverage of the 2005 conclave.    
    
    
    @TaylorRMarshall I read recently that it was four. http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/0505401.htm …    
    
    
    "The Church does not need a general manager, but a man of faith" - Vatican Insider http://vaticaninsider.lastampa.it/en/world-news/detail/articolo/conclave-23168/ …    
    
    
    Wow! If at first you don't succeed, try, try again! http://www.catholicnews.com/data/stories/cns/0505401.htm … #HabemusPapam #conclave #FrancisI    
    
    
    History today! 1st non-European Pope since 700s! 1st Latin American Pope! 1st Pope West of Atlantic! 1st Jesuit Pope! Francis the 1st! Wow!    
    
    
    @KevinMyattWx Hey, thanks for reading! I guess my "hunch" made me doubly wrong, though! God always gives the extra effort to humble me!    
    
    
    Pope Francis I #AMDG    
    
    
    Feel like a kid again! Pope Francis takes the bus? So do I! Hey, Francis was my confirmation name! Woah! #tRCot #Catholic #PopeFrancis    
    
    
    Yes! Domino's delivers! #Dominos Pizza Wins Court Order Stopping #HHS Abortion Mandate http://shar.es/euznD  via @BreitbartNews    
    
    
    Excellent article from Sandro Magister on Pope Francis I. http://chiesa.espresso.repubblica.it/articolo/1350465?eng=y …    
    
    
    New video celebrating the election of Pope Francis. http://www.catholicvote.org/     
    
    
    Apparently, one only needs one lung to be filled with the Holy Spirit. #PopeFrancis #tRCot http://ti.me/13WSXfb  via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    Pope Francis and St. Francis: Preach the Gospel Always. And for the Love of God, Use Words. | http://CatholicVote.org : http://www.catholicvote.org/pope-francis-and-st-francis-preach-the-gospel-always-and-for-the-love-of-god-use-words/#.UUNJSNGyIME.twitter …    
    
    
    That viral photo with 3 popes? No, that's not Pope Francis, but Edouard Card. Gagnon http://m.aciprensa.com/noticia.php?n=40142 … 3 saints, 1 picture. Impressive!    
    
    
    @MatthewWarner FYI: Went to see if any more cardinals had joined TweetCatholic and it looks like the site is down.    
    
    
    @PopeAlarm How do you unsubscribe from text alerts? Thanks!    
    
    
    By George! Benedict XVI's brother? Georg Ratzinger. His prefect of papal household? Archb. Georg Gänswein. Successor? Jorge Card. Bergoglio.    
    
    
    @CardinalMahony Your Eminence, we love both Francis and Benedict. Many believers, including Orthodox, encounter Jesus in liturgical majesty.    
    
    
    St. Francis and liturgical abuse.  What Did St. Francis Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/what-did-st-francis-really-say-02/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    More interesting material from St. Francis on the Liturgy: What Did St. Francis Really Say? http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/what-did-st-francis-really-say/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Be not afraid! The Holy Spirit builds in continuity & makes new whether shoes are red or black. Both Popes' gifts to the Church will endure!    
    
    
    How is this information public? Conclave should be under the oath of secrecy. The Vatican needs to investigate. http://life.nationalpost.com/2013/03/15/canadas-ouellet-beat-pope-francis-in-first-rounds-of-voting-reports/ …    
    
    
    TCF: Breathing with Both Lungs:  Saturday of the Akathist: I stumbled upon this iconography site last ... http://bit.ly/113wcW4  <--More    
    
    
    Powerful! Card. Bergoglio's Lenten letter to the faithful of Buenos Aires http://jmgarciaiii.blogspot.com/2013/02/cdl-bergoglios-lenten-letter-2013.html … #PopeFrancis    
    
    
    @AbbyJohnson This is truly one of those days.    
    
    
    @Sacerdotus @lindagaboardi @prolifejoan Our Lady of Akita, Oct. 13, 1973 http://www.ewtn.com/library/mary/akita.htm …    
    
    
    @Pontifex_ln Count on our prayers, Holy Father Francis! Ad Maiorem Dei Gloriam!    
    
    
    Rome Reports: Pope greets pilgrims after celebrating Mass in Vatican parish http://www.romereports.com/palio/pope-greets-pilgrims-after-celebrating-mass-in-vatican-parish-english-9457.html#.UUXbiDIlYDs.twitter …    
    
    
    Οὐδὲ ἐγώ σε κρίνω· πορεύου καὶ μηκέτι ἁμάρτανε.    
    
    
    My 4-year-old: "I want pizza!" [Introspective pause] "... I don't know why I could just eat pizza all the time."    
    
    
    #Cultureofdeath horrors! Doctors in China Have Performed 336 Million Abortions, 196 Million Sterilizations Since 1971 http://www.slate.com/blogs/the_slatest/2013/03/16/china_performed_336_million_abortions_since_1971.html?utm_source=tw&utm_medium=sm&utm_campaign=button_toolbar …    
    
    
    The swallows returned to St. Michael's Norbertine Abbey as I was playing with my daughters outside after Mass today. God is good! #Catholic    
    
    
    Liberals will soon turn on Pope Francis | Fr. Z's Blog (olim: What Does The Prayer Really Say?) http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/liberals-will-soon-turn-on-pope-francis/ … via @FatherZ    
    
    
    Pope Francis continues Benedict XVI's Twitter momentum; over 2 million followers on @pontifex English account; Spanish followers near 1M.    
    
    
    WDTPRS: Those red shoes http://wdtprs.com/blog/2013/03/i-am-thinking-about-those-red-shoes/ … via @FatherZ Seems not so much directed at Francis, but at those taking shots at Benedict XVI    
    
    
    This is well-stated by @amywelborn2:  A word http://wp.me/p53if-2iF     
    
    
    It is St. Joseph's feast day in Rome! Greatful for pontificate of our Holy Father Pope Francis! How many jokes during homily? I'd guess 3.5.    
    
    
    Χαιρετε! The Sacred Page: The Gospel Will Be Read in Greek at the Papal Inst... http://www.thesacredpage.com/2013/03/the-gospel-will-be-read-in-greek-at.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines I could see you homeschooling our many children.    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines My spiritual director doesn't think I have a vocation to the priesthood after all!    
    
    
    #CatholicPickUpLines Your modesty is unparalleled.    
    
    
    