#Jotakeirabaziarte @minte1974    
    
    
    Zorionak! @IbaizabalST    
    
    
    @Eil82 @LukaBassin I believe in your project and you have my full support man! Looking forward for your stuff!!!    
    
    
    IMO Begic is being a big pain in the ass for Maccabi all along the series. Are they too focused on him? @sJacas    
    
    
    @dejangod @sjacas Agree. + forcing them to double team in low post every time he gets the ball    
    
    
    @robscott33 Begic is posting up today...    
    
    
    IMO Pascual is making a huge effort to bring Lorbek back to earth. Not many coaches would. I like it.    
    
    
    of course he can do it because Lorbek has a lot of well deserved credit from past seasons. Earned credit.    
    
    
    @rodhig7 Maybe. But we'll read your live blogging during Athens game's halftime.    
    
    
    Agree! "Reyes spent a couple of minutes during the 2nd 4er laughing at the whole concept of stretch four" by @rodhig7 http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864     
    
    
    @sannti @robscott33 Azerbajanish airlines? WOW    
    
    
    Is it thursday already? And now? And now? #devotion    
    
    
    "I am a Celtic.  We are Boston http://sbn.to/ZnmR8R   via @LukaBassin  via @celticsblog #Boston #Celtics #NBA”    
    
    
    @TikotDeRoa Ya. Ha habido cruce...    
    
    
    @rodhig7 @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rafael_uehara @DONbblog @sJacas OK just followed those of you I wasn't following. We'll have fun    
    
    
    FCB's zone is really serious stuff... Not easy to beat    
    
    
    “@robscott33: you get the feeling PAO really, really need those corner 3s to drop” or they'll struggle big time    
    
    
    FCB's three guys switching action on P&R defense keeps working. Defensive Execution close to perfection    
    
    
    @sannti There are zones and Zones... I'd say this is one of the latters. Activity, big guys moving their feet... Not many off rebs...    
    
    
    FCB is closing 3rd 4er with Sada at the PF and Lorbek at SF    
    
    
    @georgerowland @sannti Agree    
    
    
    @DONbblog @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rodhig7 @rafael_uehara @sjacas And giving (more and more) confidence to Lorbek    
    
    
    @DONbblog @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rodhig7 @rafael_uehara @sjacas Hell yeah    
    
    
    I have an hypothesis, CSKA give more passes per game (not assists) than any other team in TOP 16. I wonder what @sJacas and the guys think    
    
    
    Please @rodhig7 @DONbblog @pistolpete_osfp @rafael_uehara check my last tweet and let me know what you think...    
    
    
    Knicks and Celtics playing a little bit of D... #NBAPlayoffs #playoffstime    
    
    
    J.Van Gundy "Pau and Howard are the best 4&5 combination in the League when they're happy, healthy and engaged"    
    
    
    Spurs, Bonner, Duncan: "You lead we follow..." pic.twitter.com/zZaGZiWTdQ    
    
    
    Spurs, Duncan, Bonner (II): sin palabras pic.twitter.com/RN3LwBj9a2    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd What's up Sherlock, I'm sending you a DM    
    
    
    @tomasvds You'll do it great! BTW it's nice when you can listen to the coaches during time outs... so please... you know.    
    
    
    Calentando / warm up: @rodhig7 http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864  ; @rafael_uehara http://thebasketballpost.com/2013/04/24/barcelona-panathinaikos-game-five-preview.aspx … ; @sannti http://euro-step.net/barcelona-panathinaikos-a-rivalry-at-its-peak/ … #devotion    
    
    
    @tomasvds Feeling the pressure? We'll be watching! Have a good game!    
    
    
    @robscott33 @euro_adventures Banks for a chair #justkidding    
    
    
    @robscott33 @euro_adventures That would only help PAO though #stillkidding    
    
    
    3 fouls in first not the same as 3 fouls in third so... We've got game    
    
    
    “@rodhig7: 2nd 4er recap http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864  I hope it remains close, I don't want to tweet about Pique and Shakira.”Hope u don't have to    
    
    
    A small player cutting baseline to the short corner is a good option vs. zone. Messina started doing it years ago with Papaloukas in CSKA    
    
    
    @sJacas Is the ball screen towards baseline working better than towards the middle for PAO or is it just my imagination?    
    
    
    @sJacas I'll take a look at it anyway. Some better looks but again I'm not 100% sure    
    
    
    P&R con V-Span, ajustes a zonas Mahmuti,parejas interiores diversas (Hines-Antic-Sermadini-Printezis / Barac-Erden-Savanovic-Gonlum) Farmar!    
    
    
    @Blue_LB Oly o Efes    
    
    
    @sJacas I really really really need to know if V-Span was injured and that's why he didn't play the last minutes - seconds! of G4 (really)    
    
    
    Let's see. My colleague @brianmccormick needs to know: Is there a reliable source for injury data for the top european leagues?    
    
    
    Sometimes with players it is like the slower the shooter's release (Printezis e.g.) the slower the defender's close out.    
    
    
    Spanoulis Sada-ing Shipp    
    
    
    Best minutes for EFES offense so far in the playoffs... Finding so many wide open shots, they aren't even taking all of them...    
    
    
    “@sannti: Tunçeri brought a different dimension to Efes offense. 3 assists...forcing the defense into tough situations.” Old School PG!    
    
    
    @sannti LOL    
    
    
    @sannti Not left! Right! Right!    
    
    
    @Euro_Adventures Star Wars Imperial March music, lasers... Frightening isn't it?    
    
    
    Hines guarding Erden is quite something... http://rjmbasket-english.blogspot.com.es/2013/04/balance-kyle-hines.html …    
    
    
    @Gus_bball @Eurohopes They had a private scrimmage for those scouts without tickets for today's game. LOL    
    
    
    @sannti Maybe not LOL    
    
    
    @sannti You can say you were talking about 80 minutes    
    
    
    @Gus_bball He is the kind of player every coach loves. O & D. Continuous effort. Unselfish.    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 Yes you are. I know the reason is you're focused on your team though. #1moreforthefinals    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 actually: “@CoachFinamore: OT in Boston. Carmelo is 9-31 from field. 14-18 FT 6 rebounds. 2 assists 7 turnovers”    
    
    
    C's giving Terry the ball because he is, you know, O-N-F-I-R-E    
    
    
    WOW! Basketball way of life! via “@LithuaniaBasket: Zalgiris Arena. #basketball #finals http://Instagram.com/p/YvRQEGyp2h/ ”    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Thx man, I'll be waiting for the interview's next pieces. Found it really interesting. We Spanish coaches should feel proud    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore #foulordefend alarm in Spanish ACB. Obradoiro-Unicaja. Seems like Unicaja will defend    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore Obradoiro missed a contested three pointer. Unicaja's game.    
    
    
    Alguien sabe algo sobre "Basketball Capitals"?  http://www.managingsport.com/espn_deportes_y_turkish_airlines_hacen_p%C3%BAblico_el_calendario_y_acuerdos_televisivos_para_la_nueva_se?utm_source=feedly&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+managingsport+%28ManagingSport.com%29 … cc @ganchetto    
    
    
    2" para final de 2º4º, Fondo Bulls (I) @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/XcuwBKuG83    
    
    
    2" para final de 2º4º, Fondo Bulls (II) @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/3kcEBbFglI    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore Excuse me, they need some time off so they will be ready to play the Eurobasket for Spain. Stop hacking our team. LOL    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket @ganchetto Cool! Thank you!    
    
    
    1 of the best F4 previews we'll read @rafael_uehara doing his thing http://thebasketballpost.com/2013/05/06/2013-euroleague-final-four-preview.aspx … Interesting approach to the Tomic-Slaughter issue    
    
    
    I check @sJacas - @ChristopheEPcom - @Eurohopes work so often that I feel it would be unfair not to support them: http://www.in-the-game.org/open-letter-to-jordi-bertomeu/ …    
    
    
    "Kent Bazemore, Manu Ginobili, and the defensive closeout to end game 1" the blanket theory via @brianmccormick http://feedly.com/k/13lJ2y8     
    
    
    @sJacas Is it sunny outside or what are those londoners doing man?    
    
    
    @sJacas LOL #bigfans    
    
    
    Spanoulis loves to "reject" ballscreens, specially on transition, Jackson should be aware...    
    
    
    Weems' D on V-Span is no joke... CSKA's use of high post (not only with big men) just amazing. Guess you all know about Hines' balance...    
    
    
    CSKA's notpickbutslip situation for Jackson's three... By now the best way to avoid OLY's hedging @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/smetzhe16U    
    
    
    @Gus_bball Agree... If I'm not wrong they did it only once during the first half...    
    
    
    This OLY's set is great for V-Span, Sloukas should be more patient if he plays the 2 role. @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/KKIybeKL2A    
    
    
    Definitly ball screen is not the way for CSKA today. Not even if they mix it with hand offs or any other situation...    
    
    
    So, no post up and no pick&roll/pop... tough game for CSKA    
    
    
    @CoachPerkins @robscott33 Vorontsevich's was their 2nd FG in 2nd half. Yes. Beyond scary.    
    
    
    @wardjdim @HoopLikeDrazen You know if it ain't broken why should u change it?    
    
    
    Kyle who? Too small for what? http://www.rjmbasket.blogspot.com.es/2013/04/equilibrio-kyle-hines.html … #devotion #notyourheightbutyourheart (and more)    
    
    
    Watch FCB's mismatch D... Double team and ready to rotate.    
    
    
    Will RMA change their mid ball screen D vs Marcelinho? Or will they expect him to start missing those mid range J's? Interesting    
    
    
    I believe in @sJacas lineups. You should too: http://www.in-the-game.org/stats.php?team=Real%20Madrid&level=team&sub=lineup&stage=all …    
    
    
    Not the first time Laso draws that set to finish a quarter. Nice execution and wide open shot from the corner.    
    
    
    How is Jawai going to defend ball screens? Help? Defend at all? We'll see. Interesting.    
    
    
    @sJacas Indeed!    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara There was one really painful, the one Wallace missed and was followed by Reyes' and1. It was a 6 points play.    
    
    
    @robscott33 I'll be watching them live this week during the Spanish championship... Obviously they're favourite to win it...    
    
    
    @robscott33 You saw them beat Barça... RMA has some good players, Sevilla is a good team... As the tournament goes on I'll let you know    
    
    
    Real's weak side activity is working...Plus Llull intensity on Spanoulis... Plus Begic...  Oly 7 points in 7 minutes, WOW    
    
    
    @robscott33 Agree, if they let him shoot that easily he'll end up hitting a couple of daggers and...    
    
    
    Notice that Serrod, today, is a much better p&r player than Teodosic, much harder to stop him...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen @sJacas Guess this was the situation, am I right? pic.twitter.com/GuJtKzNzS4    
    
    
    Slaughter has been underrated all season long. All that intensity... They knew well what they were signing last summer    
    
    
    @robscott33 It´s not a joke. Not the first time I see it    
    
    
    @brianmccormick Don´t know if you're being ironic pal... Anyway, the answer is yes    
    
    
    Nice RS,very good Top16,amazing playoffs,awsome F4. Finally the best team won.Respect for OLY, well deserved. RMA will fight 4 it again soon    
    
    
    @robscott33 First Joventut's game in Spanish Championship was easy. Next two appear to be to cool down after NIJT. We'll see in top 16 - 8    
    
    
    @robscott33 Spanish U18 championship SF Barça-Cornella (tournament underdogs) and Joventut-Real M. (RMA beat Unicaja in QF)    
    
    
    @robscott33 He scored 48 yesterday in QF against Estudiantes. Amazing performance    
    
    
    Contraataque (I): Usando La Calle Lateral http://bit.ly/176A7Vf     
    
    
    Ese último triple de Vasileiadis? Qué barbaridad técnica...    
    
    
    Plenty of #foulordefend situations in the ACB playoffs G2s... @CoachFinamore Amazing games!    
    
    
    @sannti That makes 34/34 in the season...    
    
    
    @pedroma2014 "If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster, and treat those two impostors just the same...";"If" de Rudyard Kipling.Enhorabuena    
    
    
    @robscott33 What do you think about CAI's stretch 4 with Rudez & Aguilar? ain't it cool?    
    
    
    @rafjuc @Lassomania He looked good during preseason with RMA vs ACB teams. Skilled, talented, smart and as you said, huge frame. Nice future    
    
    
    Que maravilla de finta Mirotic...    
    
    
    @Eil82 Have a nice flight and great work days there... Good luck    
    
    
    #drazenpetrovic pic.twitter.com/CnNyezSaAz    
    
    
    @Blue_LB Estamos todos aparcando. Dramático. Transporte público.    
    
    
    If they want to tie the series tonight, Miami need to work against Spurs 3x1 defense against Lebron's isolations pic.twitter.com/0wUcaQ48XK    
    
    
    One of the Spurs' transition sets:The side P&R is not easy to defend at all after the off ball screen for Splitter pic.twitter.com/mCK29c7gpg    
    
    
    ...and creates the space for Parker to finish with an easy jumper... pic.twitter.com/VmR9WX6hEk    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara @robscott33 IMO he's far from being a better fit than Huertas!    
    
    
    @robscott33 @rafael_uehara I guess you're right. IMO it won't be easy to find a better option though. I'd be really cautious    
    
    
    @DjordjevicStef @robscott33 @rafael_uehara I'd like to know what do they think in Barcelona.    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara @robscott33 I have to agree again. IMHO Dusko's "go to the basket" style in Vitoria was quite different than Barça's way    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Check your cellphone, don't risk malfunctioning... Is the signal ok? sure?    
    
    
    @davidgomezm89 Muchas gracias, lo leeré - veré detenidamente.    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt Thank you very much. We worked on it during the season, so it's first hand stuff. Again, I appreciate the feedback.    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt I want to push the ball,sometimes through passes (hopefully) but if there's no pass, why not dribbling if you have the skills?    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt First run (pass or dribble) then, if there's no option to finish in 4-6 seconds, we'll see what to do...    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt "depending on situation" That's the key. React to the situation trying to follow your phylosophy. Mine is: push the ball...    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt ...and we'll stop later if we have to    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt Well, I like to have clear rules (without them, there's no way to play) but words like "allways" or "never"... are dangerous    
    
    
    @monchofdez Qué te parece el close out de Draper...    
    
    
    I was missing @sJacas lineups. RMA to finish the game with Rodríguez, Llull, Rudy, Mirotic, Reyes    
    
    
    @SportandoBasket They were resourceful :-)    
    
    
    @sannti Million dollar question... I think Barça will give up anything but Carroll if you know what I mean...    
    
    
    @sannti Isolate off ball screens to avoid easy switching? Mirotic on the opposite corner to punish rotation with the kick out pass?    
    
    
    @sannti It won't be easy, they've (FCB) been working on this since the Copa del Rey... I'm excited to watch how Real is going to fix it    
    
    
    @sannti Agree. Just like here and we'll see if FCB bigs can rotate! Again, I think it is a key issue in the finals pic.twitter.com/N19Zup1kh2    
    
    
    @sannti Agree! Just like the old song: http://www.songsforteaching.com/folk/dembones.php … Mirotic connected to Carroll, who is connected to Sergio, who is... Synergies!    
    
    
    Envidia eterna a @sergiogm83 por haber podido entrenar a Niko Mirotic. Vaya jugador...    
    
    
    POPOVICH:Get them on a bus, it arrives at the ramp over here, we get off the bus, we get on the court and we play. That's how we get ready.    
    
    
    @LukaBassin Really glad for you coach! Wish you a lot of success!    
    
    
    Van Gundy "You can forget sometimes just how good Wade is" (ya se encarga el de recordártelo, Coach)    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara You know I'm kind of a true lineups believer... So I guess you're right!    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore European punks...    
    
    
    Let the game flow Danny... #shotselection    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore So, when is Ivan Drago coming? 2016?    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd Too late. 5:06 a.m. In Spain    
    
    
    Battier moneyfrickingball    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd And no way to celebrate if Pop wins this one... But I'll survive    
    
    
    Tim #youleadwefollow    
    
    
    @ganchetto 100% Agree    
    
    
    I do love this game. G'night!    
    
    
    @CCortesR44 Felicidades!    
    
    
    Otro aeropuerto con wifi abierta, Tánger. SXXI. #wifiaeropuerto    
    
    
    #laiarules    
    
    
    @tomasvds A new life ahead, go for it! You've had a great career and you have all the respect from bball people.    
    
    
    @streetball Only with our women's NT (they won Eurobasket yesterday evening) on the court...    
    
    
    Proud to be Ivory Coast NT Asisstant Coach. We start our stage. On our way to the Afrobasket '13 pic.twitter.com/g7gbt3syrJ    
    
    
    Glad to see how three players I worked with last season in Prievidza made it to the Slovak U20 & U18 squads. Masiar, Brodziansky & Sturcel    
    
    
    First practice of the day in Monastir (Tunisia) #afrobasket2013 Cote d'Ivoire getting ready. Nice gym. pic.twitter.com/oDLPmmbYct    
    
    
    The stage goes on in Monastir. Beautiful gym. #afrobasket2013 Cote d'Ivoire Basketball pic.twitter.com/lPkZYqMzn3    
    
    
    @NaoufalUariachi @basketcamino THX my friend! I missed you guys too. Done thing. We'll be in touch. Where are u heading now?    
    
    
    Cincinnati Bengals - Oklahoma drill #wow #hardknocks Si no lo habéis visto, recomendable... pic.twitter.com/d1xyN9gxYP    
    
    
    @CoachReveno I saw your game against Angola. I like your team and the way you play (BTW the 3pointer was way beyond the 24") Good luck!    
    
    
    Preparados... #Afrobasket2013 pic.twitter.com/PUBifJfH0U    
    
    
    Ben Romdhane 19 pts en primer cuarto contra Burkina. WOW.  #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Big respect for #Egypt Basketball Team. They play hard, smart and with their heart all game long #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    #Egypt #Egipto #Afrobasket2013 pic.twitter.com/fqCiAAKGA3    
    
    
    OMG Egipto!!!! #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Excelente Mike Mokongo, 11 ptos en primer cuarto y Centroafrica ganando a Nigeria 27-24 #wheresurpriseshappen #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Un paso más. One more step #RoadToSpain2014 #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    I believe #RoadToSpain2014 pic.twitter.com/TCoBFaXoxf    
    
    
    Afrobasket 2013 http://bit.ly/1342zUe     
    
    
    You'd have much more fun watching the game with the Spanish broadcasters @Euro_Adventures @sannti @TalkBasket Hilarious    
    
    
    Leo newsletters llenas de "steve nash drill" - "stephen curry drill" - "reggie miller drill" que enseñan a dar la vuelta (botando) a un cono    
    
    
    Top 10 Afrobasket 2013 “@REVERSEMAGAZINE: #Afrobasket2013: Le Top 10 ultra spectaculaire http://bit.ly/1dSpRSX  @FIBA #roadtospain2014”    
    
    
    Not the best decision making from Perperoglu in that last D against Belinelli… Going under the screen with almost no time to go...    
    
    
    "Perdimos porque..." http://amzn.com/k/AAgovjKmQSOjA031x6QgAA … we have a natural tendency to look for instances that confirm our story and our vision of...    
    
    
    And now, Eurobasket stats by @sJacas Amazing work. Endless. He should be hired by now by an EL power house to work on advanced stats...    
    
    
    @sannti @Lipko2013 No, no. We won.    
    
    
    Aquiles?????    
    
    
    How many times will Ukraine run this set for Jeter until the end of the game? #basketeditor @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/tDqkuWfHJy    
    
    
    Or,without him, this one: Small/big off ball screen followed by a ball screen #basketeditor @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/PR2hCQUnI4    
    
    
    So you want more basketball stats... check @TeamTextbook work, they're growing... http://t-book.co/     
    
    
    That, Kavvadas, is exactly what I talk about when I talk about setting a ball screen.    
    
    
    Bourousis short roll... Punishes help and creates a wide open shot #basketeditor @basketeditor pic.twitter.com/J2OARLsfpb    
    
    
    @sJacas VSpan % from BEKO during the EB??    
    
    
    Clásico partido que resuelve Bramos    
    
    
    @sJacas Would you show us Spain's shots creation distribution?    
    
    
    @sJacas Interesting. I guess is not that easy to reach conclusions in short tournaments like this one. Nice job anyway!    
    
    
    Thanks to @RunKeeper & @UnderArmour 1st run with my #UASpeedForm for being top 10 in the #FastestCity competition! pic.twitter.com/iC8cPE6ZVY    
    
    
    @lloydgar He has Euroleague level for sure. Talented, physical, patient, game knowledge, terrific shot creation skills, and his shooting...    
    
    
    Amazing amount of interesting data (shot creation) from @sJacas: a bunch of shot creation/possession usage graphs http://www.in-the-game.org/eurobasket-2013-shot-creationpossession-usage/ …”    
    
    
    “@sannti: El Chacho's throwing a "welcome to European ball" party for Micic.” He's been on fire for three years now. OMG    
    
    
    @sJacas France +/- with De Colo + Parker opposed to Parker at PG + a regular SG? Maybe I ask too many questions I know...    
    
    
    @sJacas ...and I guess you get what I'm suggesting with my last question...    
    
    
    @sJacas They need you at FIBA too... Do You have the same feeling? FRA playing better with T.P. off the PG spot?    
    
    
    I love flat screens. So do Tony Parker pic.twitter.com/ADBeJMlXPu    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Puerto Rico tried that against Brazil with Cheney on Marcelinho Huertas on the last FIBA Américas.    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Yes. But with more and more teams playing small ball nowadays... good D option for a couple of minutes    
    
    
    @Eil82 I'm in too pal!    
    
    
    @Eil82 I'm Fratello's big fan since he said the best of coaching Spudd Webb was that they could share suits if they needed to    
    
    
    Ukraine should stop the sloppy passing specially when Draper is around...    
    
    
    @Eil82 "it ain't over till it's over"    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket That would help    
    
    
    @UgurYilmazz_ Haha... Was talking about Aradori's dribbling hand. Should've placed it forward and on the inside to be able to...    
    
    
    @UgurYilmazz_ ...change direction avoiding Lavrinovic. Ball screen fundamentals. I'll try to use English more often LOL    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Yeah, I'm thinking about the African 4th best, to begin with...    
    
    
    @Lipko2013 We want YOU for Spain2014!    
    
    
    LIT need no more against CRO zone... corner and BOOM @basketeditor #basketeditor pic.twitter.com/6yXxmNXEIa    
    
    
    The zone won't work for Croatia today pic.twitter.com/aiclD3OnC2    
    
    
    @TeamTextbook So defense gives championships? Well, if you can score too, it does...    
    
    
    And they keep biting on the corner back door...    
    
    
    @sannti I'm not the "funny" kind of guy but I was gonna say FRA is a Parker oriented team while SPA is a Beard oriented...    
    
    
    Feeding Marc: SG curl+read Marc's defender. Behind: straight pass In front: high/low with 4 @basketeditor pic.twitter.com/f0mIMFrVgk    
    
    
    “@sannti: NBA'ers, stay away from El Chacho. This is an order, not a request.” We're not joking now. Seriously.    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I remember that Zalgiris with Kazlauskas & Sabonis. There were off. sets I keep using now. Pretty interesting basketball    
    
    
    And by the way, best announcer EVER, @LiamCanny on SER-ITA FIBATV right now. This guy does his job all around the globe    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I guess many Spanish fans will support Lietuva tonight... Good luck!    
    
    
    France's big men mid range shots (or help-reading) is the key for them in the  p&r battle    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen He needs to keep an eye on Parker to box him out though...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Keep an eye on Fran Guerra ('92)    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen I think he will. Saw him a week ago and he was better than I expected… It will be interesting to follow his development    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara As you said, his performance was great at FIBA Americas… No European team giving him a try?    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara He appeared to be under control all along the FIBA Americas… Understandable though.    
    
    
    It's early, but Banvit looked good against EFES… It is a team to follow for many reasons this season, isn't it? pic.twitter.com/Liubo2OBlD    
    
    
    @Glarusa @Euro_E_Row Pretty well. I'm sure he'll have a very good season (again)    
    
    
    Bird vs. Dr.J  http://amzn.com/k/CACGJL5ESbqntmDlNWW_5Q … Whenever he gets close to Doc, he kinda whispers, “Thirty to eight, Doc, thirty to eight, Doc.”...    
    
    
    Did I see it right? Banvit asisstant Coach watching last play on his cellphone?    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Some would send the big guy to the bench for allowing a shot instead of forcing the penetration    
    
    
    Third game I watch Banvit so far this season (and pre-season)and  it's clear they want to be aggressive when defending ball screens    
    
    
    @brianmccormick @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen It varies a lot depending on level. I'd say it goes from around 30 to maybe 50-60 (top teams)    
    
    
    @brianmccormick @GalenHarkness Agree with more games=better development but too many games + not enough practice wouldn't work... Balance    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick BTW in Hungary there's the U23 league (with many U18 players) with 22 RS games + F8...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick ...that means an U18-U17 could play those 30 plus another 30 or so with his age team, plus...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick Once a week. Maybe twice a week a couple or three times during the season...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick …then by the end of the season there are national tournaments w the best teams in the country    
    
    
    Banvit-Ostend both teams showing pretty good spacing. It's going to be a tough game.    
    
    
    Banvit, looking for the middle screen from the very beginning of their offense #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/EYItBEnyC2    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen what is Mejia doing??!! Man...    
    
    
    @redhoopsgr @LithuaniaBasket They're pretty resilient aren't they?    
    
    
    I didn't catch the new time out rules... @LithuaniaBasket @redhoopsgr @HoopLikeDrazen Can you help me?    
    
    
    @tomasvds And I need to say they deserve it 100%    
    
    
    "Evaluating coaches based on the process or the result" Another MUST read from @brianmccormick http://feedly.com/k/18WX1LE     
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Do you? Oostende showed pretty solid basketball. They're tough, with good spacing, share the ball… They're a nice surprise    
    
    
    Excelente post-game    
    
    
    @sJacas I think Mejri will get more minutes as the season goes on. You?    
    
    
    @sJacas IMO Slaughter has been one of RMA's best signings in years.    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Do u think it could be a balance thing more than a weight thing? I mean,he will never be a J.Dorsey if u know what I mean    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Agree    
    
    
    You're so picky :-D “@brianmccormick: Looking at YouTube: throwing the ball off the glass and jumping to get it is not a "rebounding drill"    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara To me it's clear that he's getting stronger. And faster. And I'd say he keeps working on his skills. Looks really good    
    
    
    RT: "@rafael_uehara: I think what might determine how soon he becomes a contriutor at NBA level is his level of readiness on defense. (2)”    
    
    
    @sJacas He looks good. Guess after scouting every team will try to deny his left hand... We'll see    
    
    
    @sJacas Not that Bemerhaven looked like the best PnR defenders, which helped him a couple of times...    
    
    
    @sJacas :-) whenever I can I like to watch games from different leagues. Germany is more and more interesting. That game was good (not only    
    
    
    @sJacas ...him but also Stojic, Echenique...    
    
    
    @redglove12 @sJacas Done    
    
    
    @redglove12 Can't DM you back...    
    
    
    My last tweet show there are some good basketball analysis out there… Aún se hacen buenos análisis de básket… THX to @robscott33    
    
    
    Think about this. Pensad en esto: http://amzn.com/k/kjrm1JglToikVQMWS3SCgg … basketball’s past is its future.    
    
    
    Eurobasket - Afrobasket http://bit.ly/19enXbM     
    
    
    So @sJacas with the new off.reb. 14" rule, how many more quick-isolation ball screens per game are we going to see? An average of...+20?    
    
    
    “@sJacas: I'd assume a little less: there's ca. 20 orb/game in average,4 of them converted for direct putbacks.Maybe 12-14?” Sounds accurate    
    
    
    Michael Jordan on being late to practice: http://amzn.com/k/aszdrS4kT2C7kXphVWDECA … Early in the season, Burrell was late for practice because he had be...    
    
    
    Interesante http://www.grantland.com/story/_/id/8719297/how-kobe-bryant-missed-shots-translate-new-nba-statistic-kobe-assist … "crediting a wide-open corner 3 solely to  Matt Bonner, Kawhi Leonard, or Danny Green...    
    
    
    ...is akin to giving Javier Bardem sole credit for No Country for Old Men" Son los tiros fallados por Kobe buenos para los Lakers?    
    
    
    "...the analytical "baseball-ification" of our fluid sport too often neglects this basic tenet of basketball ecology."    
    
    
    @IbaizabalST Zorionak! Oso ondo neskak!    
    
    
    Realmente OA se ha caído, verdad?    
    
    
    @DjordjevicStef I followed him closely when he played Eurochallenge F4 in Debrecen 2 seasons ago. Amazing player.    
    
    
    BB en 14" tras rebote ofensivo. Posteando rápido a Mumbrú #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/wBOT9AKrUJ    
    
    
    @sJacas You'll love to check Gran Canaria and the "double stretch 4" with Nacho Martín + Eulis Báez    
    
    
    @cagriturhan @rodhig7 He's struggling against the Martín + Baez combo, he's mobile but not that mobile to go beyond the line to play D…    
    
    
    @sJacas @robscott33 @cagriturhan @rodhig7 Did you see that? WOW    
    
    
    @cagriturhan @sJacas @robscott33 @rodhig7 I meant the fastbreak after free throw...    
    
    
    @rodhig7 IMO every team needs post ups... Even if they're not successful at first sight    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara + he can shoot. He's living a second youth, better than the first one IMHO    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 Are you skipping practices or what?    
    
    
    If you're going to follow @Euroleague this season, you can celebrate its tip off with @sJacas and his charts: WHERE ADVANCED STATS HAPPEN    
    
    
    Jelinek reads well the 2 vs. 1 in fastbreak situation and finishes straight instead of giving the useless pass many players give so often    
    
    
    @quiquevich @jondelapresa Some would say he needs to gain weight I think he needs to improve his balance to use his strenght properly    
    
    
    @quiquevich @jondelapresa But clearly he is on his way to be if not the best one of the best inside players in Europe    
    
    
    Corner threes in LBO-MAC... Danger!    
    
    
    As Mirotic gets better and better, RMA bigs get harder to defend. Plus defensive solidness (without Mejri!)... they look real good again    
    
    
    “@rafael_uehara: If Bourousis hits 3s well RM's making the dream come true: every guy needs to be defended at every spot on the floor.” HOT!    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara You were talking about it... Two threes in a row by Mirotic and Bourousis... Unstoppable    
    
    
    Nice way to end the third quarter... RMA's SOOB #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/1RToxjaVp4    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara …not many teams can reach that goal… and that means a fast paced game, which Real loves… Tough...    
    
    
    "Where SportVU...can truly help is in ensuring that repetition is thoughtful..." http://hardwoodparoxysm.com/2013/10/02/shane-battiers-take-on-the-sportvu-revolution-might-surprise-you/ …    
    
    
    100% Agree RT @brianmccormick: also, the data will help with training, preventing injury, fatigue monitoring, etc.    
    
    
    @sJacas And now, are we supposed to sleep tonight? LOL. Amazing stuff as usual. THX    
    
    
    @LiveBBall_TV If only I could login… something is not working properly. Waiting for the customer services representative to contact...    
    
    
    My last RT shows you how wrong a coach can be, never mind his level, league, experience… Amazing.    
    
    
    @LiveBBall_TV customer service fixed my problem quickly. Thanks guys. I really want to enjoy tonight's EL games!    
    
    
    Mirotic being able to finish towards his right shoulder that quick... How can you guard him in mid/low post???    
    
    
    I think Lamonica was telling the coaches, hey guys, a 30" time out is a 30" time out, cut the talking…    
    
    
    @TikotDeRoa IMO Ike Diogu es Euroliga sin ninguna duda    
    
    
    Tomic's short rolls create plenty of passing options (e.g. K-Pap's last back door) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/RW53utNyXa    
    
    
    “@HoopLikeDrazen: Almost had it again, Tomic to K-Pap backdoor. Defense just converges on Tomic & opens up all those options.Great cutter.”    
    
    
    FBU looking for Bogdanovic in low post... (I) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/jE5HhshsqF    
    
    
    ...and FBU counter once the defense is expecting for the same situation (and II) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/t6G8c471yR    
    
    
    “@sJacas: One day we'll have nightmares from this: http://twitter.com/sJacas/status/393829659877470208/photo/1pic.twitter.com/5NpTbli1af ” WOW a picture from Málaga! Nice!    
    
    
    Seth's Blog: When to speak up http://pinterest.com/pin/390194755186505371/ …    
    
    
    @SAnalyticsBlog @CatapultSports @TeamTextbook No way    
    
    
    LBO in off. transition, Nocioni pick & pops #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/kTShIbhu6R    
    
    
    With so many injuries, LBO is relying on spacing (p&r, p&p, stretch 4, ISO) and it's working so far... We'll see after half time adjustments    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland I'd like you to think what's better, riding the hot hand, or letting the defense think you're going to…    
    
    
    CSKA struggling to find the mismatches... Even with all the FBUs switching... Bad passing... Huge problems    
    
    
    @luis_cristovao I hope it will be useful! Don't hesitate to contact for questions or feedback. Thank you, enjoy!    
    
    
    Bourussis' fastbreaks on their way to become a classic in RMA offense...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen That would be great, but no TV tonight.    
    
    
    SIG almost managed to stop RMA's alley oop (almost) pic.twitter.com/N7jxwA0SmI    
    
    
    I'd really like to (once in a while) shoot some Questions For Advanced Analytics Guys #QFAAG I wonder what @sJacas thinks about it...    
    
    
    Slightly better spacing FCB & CSKA during the last minutes... Some good looks. Expecting something else though...    
    
    
    Messina's call was: "foul the roller on the catch"    
    
    
    Is there a better PG than S.Rodriguez right now? And I mean all around the world...    
    
    
    “@sJacas: Efes PnR D vulnerable to lobs (strong in other areas). Wrote about it last yr (http://bit.ly/1gKHC8c )" Really interesting post    
    
    
    @rodhig7 Watching a game which I already read before... Your Partizan's spacing article is really accurate.    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland Bayern trying to ride Staiger's hot hand… almost worked… except for his last airball...    
    
    
    @sJacas #QFAAG what do you think about eFG% related to number of passes + shotclock seconds spent? Does it make sense for you?    
    
    
    @sJacas "v" for "very" now I get it... I'll have to review the Harvard Statistics110 lectures first...    
    
    
    @sannti Let's get a link to watch that game live! #teamwork    
    
    
    @lloydgar I wouldn't hesitate to sign him. He's top level IMO. Euroleague level I'd say. He's got the whole package. We'll see...    
    
    
    Euroleague handball? Smh    
    
    
    CSKA managed pretty well team fouls to close the second quarter. Which by the way was way better than the first.    
    
    
    Thinking about a pts per ball screen (made/allowed) stat @sJacas #QFAAG    
    
    
    @georgerowland @sJacas Points off 0 - 1 - 2 passes after a ball screen is set?    
    
    
    “@georgerowland: @sannti @rjmbasket08 @sJacas New system, called GeorgeVU,I watch the game and note down with a pencil" HIRED.Right attitude    
    
    
    @rodhig7 @georgerowland @sJacas That's up to the coach, but related to lineups to begin with: This two guys running a P&R whitin lineup X...    
    
    
    @georgerowland @rodhig7 @sJacas How hot it would be to know what's better, pick and pop or pick and roll within different sets/lineups...    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland @rodhig7 Let's keep them off the equation… What do you think?    
    
    
    As I said, hot RT @sJacas: @rjmbasket08 "you'd be splitting it up to dozens of lineups/positions/locations @georgerowland @rodhig7    
    
    
    LBK, nice start... Offense flowing and tough defense. I liked Mainoldi's first foul. Nice sign    
    
    
    How many teams follow the "offensive rebound + three point shot" rule?    
    
    
    @sJacas Barcelona used to do it back in the day with Ndong, Vázquez... It was really hard to score against them...    
    
    
    @agustijulbe @sJacas Against that FCB you had to dunk or hit "nothing but net" or you wouldn't score at all. Right players+practice I guess    
    
    
    @sJacas Does he wear yellow jersey?    
    
    
    Even if I'm obviously (slightly) biased, Konate's dunk is the best... Best Alley-oops of #RoadToSpain2014: http://youtu.be/9O2OXYh8K4Y     
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Very good game. I'm posting something about it in a while    
    
    
    It's quite clear, Brose coaches are against cameras during time-outs... pic.twitter.com/5v7YiLvfmP    
    
    
    RMA baseline OOB, post up situation with Darden… plus high low option when the defender overplays… #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/exsw7wX4cP    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara IMO it's all about avoiding scouting…The thing is, are there rules about cam/mic? then every team should respect the rules...    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara And to answer your question, cam & mics are not that annoying. Everyone is used to them, c'mon!    
    
    
    100% agree RT @sJacas: RMB & Fener don't just stretch the defense to the 3pt arc, but often to NBA 3pt distance.    
    
    
    .@sJacas Maybe teams could try giving up the mid-range shots... Bulls style... Not easy anyway    
    
    
    I'd like them to answer but I guess their answer would be "not likely" @sJacas We need FG% data for 0-8" 8-16" 16-24" shotclock periods    
    
    
    Is PAO experimenting on giving up corner threes? Not working    
    
    
    UNI and a different way to screen the screener... then hand off situation on top #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/dws1kfznN2    
    
    
    BTW with the 14" "rule" the offensive rebound three pointer makes (still) much more sense... Don't u think so @sJacas ?    
    
    
    @sJacas Yes... You coined the concept... Once they start using it, they should give you a cent each time    
    
    
    Exactly "@sJacas: Get a quick open shot off the off-rebound? Right ... probably difficult to get better shot value later down the clock.”    
    
    
    Not easy to play offense with non - stretch bigs... pic.twitter.com/WcxoKRf3Zk    
    
    
    IMO @luis_cristovao @Lukas_Kuc You know more, but you realize there are many different answers for each situation...    
    
    
    Nice signing... "@sportando: Ike Diogu to play in D-League http://www.sportando.net/eng/usa/d-league/69310/ike-diogu-to-play-in-d-league.html …”    
    
    
    Hines doing his thing... Amazing energy. Whatever he does. A+    
    
    
    Sada: post up + two penetrations. Strategy not working for cska? Defenders' effort?    
    
    
    Hines' shot creation numbers, please @sJacas    
    
    
    @sJacas I didn't catch it, but that's the way (some people might consider it irony, but you know it's not)    
    
    
    Nice situation, SIG looking for the high/low after diagonal cuts and big2big screen #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/gackRmaqZj    
    
    
    Which they can run after the PG gives the pass and goes to the corner, too. #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/LCYgYhMwjF    
    
    
    @nandoblanco I'd say you won't be seeing it in a while buddie… And it's kind of sad, yes.    
    
    
    Great player & hard worker RT @BBLofficial: ICYMI Paul Gause headlines our Team of the Week this week #BBLCupFinal! pic.twitter.com/9D6rtNjvUh    
    
    
    Real Quick: Liberar Tiros - Kyle Hines http://bit.ly/1dKnG0E     
    
    
    @nandoblanco It's all about reward / risk. At least at the highest level. Also, I guess the work (or lack of) with youngsters is important    
    
    
    And you'd think, "another easy W for RMA" but it wasn't! Which is still more amazing.    
    
    
    Ball screen defense KEY: arms & hands action pic.twitter.com/h3KbOSXHm2    
    
    
    One of the best game endings I've watched in a while... Those three sideline inboundings in a row, plus the coast to coast... #devotion    
    
    
    MPS sideline OOB set. They did it twice to play the hand off with Hackett... #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/EBClZuryCh    
    
    
    ...and the third time, Hunter with the backdoor cut to score! #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/OSIuIyGcjA    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Funny how some players like that kind of talking.    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket IMHO everyone has his share of responsibility when things go wrong.He takes it from his shoulders to put it on someone else    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I think you get my point. It's his opinion, OK. I still think no one should avoid responsibility.And to me,smells like that    
    
    
    Ever noticed Draper's screens quality? Nice thing for a small player to set good screens    
    
    
    V-Span show has started… again #devotion pic.twitter.com/inndVTEdTU    
    
    
    Not many teams can make proper use of this hand off situation. OLY and FBU can. pic.twitter.com/it9KqkK9mD    
    
    
    @gonzalobedia IMO passer-receiver coord. Plus pass technique (hands position, body position, ball protection) plus pass angle...    
    
    
    @RomainDsDz My point is, what's its use if you can't shoot off that hand off pass? Spanoulis and Bogdanovic can.    
    
    
    @RomainDsDz That's it. Of course, there will be a repick right after the hand off, but then, that's a different story.    
    
    
    V-Span and mismatch decision making. Stay tunned...    
    
    
    Defensa De Desajuste / Mismatch Defense http://rjmbasket.blogspot.com.es/2014/01/defensa-de-desajuste-ideas-basicas.html#.UsfVG0REOxM.twitter …    
    
    
    @georgerowland Coach Plaza keeps doing it in Malaga. They do it on a regular basis+specially against that kind of player (see vs. Navarro)    
    
    
    Agree @robscott33 @luis_cristovao Team defense. You need good organization or it will be wide open shot after wide open shot    
    
    
    Yes @luis_cristovao @robscott33 the main idea (for me) is to force him to drive to the basket. That's the first goal for the defense    
    
    
    #Jotakeirabaziarte @minte1974    
    
    
    Zorionak! @IbaizabalST    
    
    
    @Eil82 @LukaBassin I believe in your project and you have my full support man! Looking forward for your stuff!!!    
    
    
    IMO Begic is being a big pain in the ass for Maccabi all along the series. Are they too focused on him? @sJacas    
    
    
    @dejangod @sjacas Agree. + forcing them to double team in low post every time he gets the ball    
    
    
    @robscott33 Begic is posting up today...    
    
    
    IMO Pascual is making a huge effort to bring Lorbek back to earth. Not many coaches would. I like it.    
    
    
    of course he can do it because Lorbek has a lot of well deserved credit from past seasons. Earned credit.    
    
    
    @rodhig7 Maybe. But we'll read your live blogging during Athens game's halftime.    
    
    
    Agree! "Reyes spent a couple of minutes during the 2nd 4er laughing at the whole concept of stretch four" by @rodhig7 http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864     
    
    
    @sannti @robscott33 Azerbajanish airlines? WOW    
    
    
    Is it thursday already? And now? And now? #devotion    
    
    
    "I am a Celtic.  We are Boston http://sbn.to/ZnmR8R   via @LukaBassin  via @celticsblog #Boston #Celtics #NBA”    
    
    
    @TikotDeRoa Ya. Ha habido cruce...    
    
    
    @rodhig7 @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rafael_uehara @DONbblog @sJacas OK just followed those of you I wasn't following. We'll have fun    
    
    
    FCB's zone is really serious stuff... Not easy to beat    
    
    
    “@robscott33: you get the feeling PAO really, really need those corner 3s to drop” or they'll struggle big time    
    
    
    FCB's three guys switching action on P&R defense keeps working. Defensive Execution close to perfection    
    
    
    @sannti There are zones and Zones... I'd say this is one of the latters. Activity, big guys moving their feet... Not many off rebs...    
    
    
    FCB is closing 3rd 4er with Sada at the PF and Lorbek at SF    
    
    
    @georgerowland @sannti Agree    
    
    
    @DONbblog @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rodhig7 @rafael_uehara @sjacas And giving (more and more) confidence to Lorbek    
    
    
    @DONbblog @robscott33 @pistolpete_osfp @rodhig7 @rafael_uehara @sjacas Hell yeah    
    
    
    I have an hypothesis, CSKA give more passes per game (not assists) than any other team in TOP 16. I wonder what @sJacas and the guys think    
    
    
    Please @rodhig7 @DONbblog @pistolpete_osfp @rafael_uehara check my last tweet and let me know what you think...    
    
    
    Knicks and Celtics playing a little bit of D... #NBAPlayoffs #playoffstime    
    
    
    J.Van Gundy "Pau and Howard are the best 4&5 combination in the League when they're happy, healthy and engaged"    
    
    
    Spurs, Bonner, Duncan: "You lead we follow..." pic.twitter.com/zZaGZiWTdQ    
    
    
    Spurs, Duncan, Bonner (II): sin palabras pic.twitter.com/RN3LwBj9a2    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd What's up Sherlock, I'm sending you a DM    
    
    
    @tomasvds You'll do it great! BTW it's nice when you can listen to the coaches during time outs... so please... you know.    
    
    
    Calentando / warm up: @rodhig7 http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864  ; @rafael_uehara http://thebasketballpost.com/2013/04/24/barcelona-panathinaikos-game-five-preview.aspx … ; @sannti http://euro-step.net/barcelona-panathinaikos-a-rivalry-at-its-peak/ … #devotion    
    
    
    @tomasvds Feeling the pressure? We'll be watching! Have a good game!    
    
    
    @robscott33 @euro_adventures Banks for a chair #justkidding    
    
    
    @robscott33 @euro_adventures That would only help PAO though #stillkidding    
    
    
    3 fouls in first not the same as 3 fouls in third so... We've got game    
    
    
    “@rodhig7: 2nd 4er recap http://www.in-the-game.org/?p=22864  I hope it remains close, I don't want to tweet about Pique and Shakira.”Hope u don't have to    
    
    
    A small player cutting baseline to the short corner is a good option vs. zone. Messina started doing it years ago with Papaloukas in CSKA    
    
    
    @sJacas Is the ball screen towards baseline working better than towards the middle for PAO or is it just my imagination?    
    
    
    @sJacas I'll take a look at it anyway. Some better looks but again I'm not 100% sure    
    
    
    P&R con V-Span, ajustes a zonas Mahmuti,parejas interiores diversas (Hines-Antic-Sermadini-Printezis / Barac-Erden-Savanovic-Gonlum) Farmar!    
    
    
    @Blue_LB Oly o Efes    
    
    
    @sJacas I really really really need to know if V-Span was injured and that's why he didn't play the last minutes - seconds! of G4 (really)    
    
    
    Let's see. My colleague @brianmccormick needs to know: Is there a reliable source for injury data for the top european leagues?    
    
    
    Sometimes with players it is like the slower the shooter's release (Printezis e.g.) the slower the defender's close out.    
    
    
    Spanoulis Sada-ing Shipp    
    
    
    Best minutes for EFES offense so far in the playoffs... Finding so many wide open shots, they aren't even taking all of them...    
    
    
    “@sannti: Tunçeri brought a different dimension to Efes offense. 3 assists...forcing the defense into tough situations.” Old School PG!    
    
    
    @sannti LOL    
    
    
    @sannti Not left! Right! Right!    
    
    
    @Euro_Adventures Star Wars Imperial March music, lasers... Frightening isn't it?    
    
    
    Hines guarding Erden is quite something... http://rjmbasket-english.blogspot.com.es/2013/04/balance-kyle-hines.html …    
    
    
    @Gus_bball @Eurohopes They had a private scrimmage for those scouts without tickets for today's game. LOL    
    
    
    @sannti Maybe not LOL    
    
    
    @sannti You can say you were talking about 80 minutes    
    
    
    @Gus_bball He is the kind of player every coach loves. O & D. Continuous effort. Unselfish.    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 Yes you are. I know the reason is you're focused on your team though. #1moreforthefinals    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 actually: “@CoachFinamore: OT in Boston. Carmelo is 9-31 from field. 14-18 FT 6 rebounds. 2 assists 7 turnovers”    
    
    
    C's giving Terry the ball because he is, you know, O-N-F-I-R-E    
    
    
    WOW! Basketball way of life! via “@LithuaniaBasket: Zalgiris Arena. #basketball #finals http://Instagram.com/p/YvRQEGyp2h/ ”    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Thx man, I'll be waiting for the interview's next pieces. Found it really interesting. We Spanish coaches should feel proud    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore #foulordefend alarm in Spanish ACB. Obradoiro-Unicaja. Seems like Unicaja will defend    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore Obradoiro missed a contested three pointer. Unicaja's game.    
    
    
    Alguien sabe algo sobre "Basketball Capitals"?  http://www.managingsport.com/espn_deportes_y_turkish_airlines_hacen_p%C3%BAblico_el_calendario_y_acuerdos_televisivos_para_la_nueva_se?utm_source=feedly&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+managingsport+%28ManagingSport.com%29 … cc @ganchetto    
    
    
    2" para final de 2º4º, Fondo Bulls (I) @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/XcuwBKuG83    
    
    
    2" para final de 2º4º, Fondo Bulls (II) @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/3kcEBbFglI    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore Excuse me, they need some time off so they will be ready to play the Eurobasket for Spain. Stop hacking our team. LOL    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket @ganchetto Cool! Thank you!    
    
    
    1 of the best F4 previews we'll read @rafael_uehara doing his thing http://thebasketballpost.com/2013/05/06/2013-euroleague-final-four-preview.aspx … Interesting approach to the Tomic-Slaughter issue    
    
    
    I check @sJacas - @ChristopheEPcom - @Eurohopes work so often that I feel it would be unfair not to support them: http://www.in-the-game.org/open-letter-to-jordi-bertomeu/ …    
    
    
    "Kent Bazemore, Manu Ginobili, and the defensive closeout to end game 1" the blanket theory via @brianmccormick http://feedly.com/k/13lJ2y8     
    
    
    @sJacas Is it sunny outside or what are those londoners doing man?    
    
    
    @sJacas LOL #bigfans    
    
    
    Spanoulis loves to "reject" ballscreens, specially on transition, Jackson should be aware...    
    
    
    Weems' D on V-Span is no joke... CSKA's use of high post (not only with big men) just amazing. Guess you all know about Hines' balance...    
    
    
    CSKA's notpickbutslip situation for Jackson's three... By now the best way to avoid OLY's hedging @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/smetzhe16U    
    
    
    @Gus_bball Agree... If I'm not wrong they did it only once during the first half...    
    
    
    This OLY's set is great for V-Span, Sloukas should be more patient if he plays the 2 role. @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/KKIybeKL2A    
    
    
    Definitly ball screen is not the way for CSKA today. Not even if they mix it with hand offs or any other situation...    
    
    
    So, no post up and no pick&roll/pop... tough game for CSKA    
    
    
    @CoachPerkins @robscott33 Vorontsevich's was their 2nd FG in 2nd half. Yes. Beyond scary.    
    
    
    @wardjdim @HoopLikeDrazen You know if it ain't broken why should u change it?    
    
    
    Kyle who? Too small for what? http://www.rjmbasket.blogspot.com.es/2013/04/equilibrio-kyle-hines.html … #devotion #notyourheightbutyourheart (and more)    
    
    
    Watch FCB's mismatch D... Double team and ready to rotate.    
    
    
    Will RMA change their mid ball screen D vs Marcelinho? Or will they expect him to start missing those mid range J's? Interesting    
    
    
    I believe in @sJacas lineups. You should too: http://www.in-the-game.org/stats.php?team=Real%20Madrid&level=team&sub=lineup&stage=all …    
    
    
    Not the first time Laso draws that set to finish a quarter. Nice execution and wide open shot from the corner.    
    
    
    How is Jawai going to defend ball screens? Help? Defend at all? We'll see. Interesting.    
    
    
    @sJacas Indeed!    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara There was one really painful, the one Wallace missed and was followed by Reyes' and1. It was a 6 points play.    
    
    
    @robscott33 I'll be watching them live this week during the Spanish championship... Obviously they're favourite to win it...    
    
    
    @robscott33 You saw them beat Barça... RMA has some good players, Sevilla is a good team... As the tournament goes on I'll let you know    
    
    
    Real's weak side activity is working...Plus Llull intensity on Spanoulis... Plus Begic...  Oly 7 points in 7 minutes, WOW    
    
    
    @robscott33 Agree, if they let him shoot that easily he'll end up hitting a couple of daggers and...    
    
    
    Notice that Serrod, today, is a much better p&r player than Teodosic, much harder to stop him...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen @sJacas Guess this was the situation, am I right? pic.twitter.com/GuJtKzNzS4    
    
    
    Slaughter has been underrated all season long. All that intensity... They knew well what they were signing last summer    
    
    
    @robscott33 It´s not a joke. Not the first time I see it    
    
    
    @brianmccormick Don´t know if you're being ironic pal... Anyway, the answer is yes    
    
    
    Nice RS,very good Top16,amazing playoffs,awsome F4. Finally the best team won.Respect for OLY, well deserved. RMA will fight 4 it again soon    
    
    
    @robscott33 First Joventut's game in Spanish Championship was easy. Next two appear to be to cool down after NIJT. We'll see in top 16 - 8    
    
    
    @robscott33 Spanish U18 championship SF Barça-Cornella (tournament underdogs) and Joventut-Real M. (RMA beat Unicaja in QF)    
    
    
    @robscott33 He scored 48 yesterday in QF against Estudiantes. Amazing performance    
    
    
    Contraataque (I): Usando La Calle Lateral http://bit.ly/176A7Vf     
    
    
    Ese último triple de Vasileiadis? Qué barbaridad técnica...    
    
    
    Plenty of #foulordefend situations in the ACB playoffs G2s... @CoachFinamore Amazing games!    
    
    
    @sannti That makes 34/34 in the season...    
    
    
    @pedroma2014 "If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster, and treat those two impostors just the same...";"If" de Rudyard Kipling.Enhorabuena    
    
    
    @robscott33 What do you think about CAI's stretch 4 with Rudez & Aguilar? ain't it cool?    
    
    
    @rafjuc @Lassomania He looked good during preseason with RMA vs ACB teams. Skilled, talented, smart and as you said, huge frame. Nice future    
    
    
    Que maravilla de finta Mirotic...    
    
    
    @Eil82 Have a nice flight and great work days there... Good luck    
    
    
    #drazenpetrovic pic.twitter.com/CnNyezSaAz    
    
    
    @Blue_LB Estamos todos aparcando. Dramático. Transporte público.    
    
    
    If they want to tie the series tonight, Miami need to work against Spurs 3x1 defense against Lebron's isolations pic.twitter.com/0wUcaQ48XK    
    
    
    One of the Spurs' transition sets:The side P&R is not easy to defend at all after the off ball screen for Splitter pic.twitter.com/mCK29c7gpg    
    
    
    ...and creates the space for Parker to finish with an easy jumper... pic.twitter.com/VmR9WX6hEk    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara @robscott33 IMO he's far from being a better fit than Huertas!    
    
    
    @robscott33 @rafael_uehara I guess you're right. IMO it won't be easy to find a better option though. I'd be really cautious    
    
    
    @DjordjevicStef @robscott33 @rafael_uehara I'd like to know what do they think in Barcelona.    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara @robscott33 I have to agree again. IMHO Dusko's "go to the basket" style in Vitoria was quite different than Barça's way    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Check your cellphone, don't risk malfunctioning... Is the signal ok? sure?    
    
    
    @davidgomezm89 Muchas gracias, lo leeré - veré detenidamente.    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt Thank you very much. We worked on it during the season, so it's first hand stuff. Again, I appreciate the feedback.    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt I want to push the ball,sometimes through passes (hopefully) but if there's no pass, why not dribbling if you have the skills?    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt First run (pass or dribble) then, if there's no option to finish in 4-6 seconds, we'll see what to do...    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt "depending on situation" That's the key. React to the situation trying to follow your phylosophy. Mine is: push the ball...    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt ...and we'll stop later if we have to    
    
    
    @GreenHoopsLt Well, I like to have clear rules (without them, there's no way to play) but words like "allways" or "never"... are dangerous    
    
    
    @monchofdez Qué te parece el close out de Draper...    
    
    
    I was missing @sJacas lineups. RMA to finish the game with Rodríguez, Llull, Rudy, Mirotic, Reyes    
    
    
    @SportandoBasket They were resourceful :-)    
    
    
    @sannti Million dollar question... I think Barça will give up anything but Carroll if you know what I mean...    
    
    
    @sannti Isolate off ball screens to avoid easy switching? Mirotic on the opposite corner to punish rotation with the kick out pass?    
    
    
    @sannti It won't be easy, they've (FCB) been working on this since the Copa del Rey... I'm excited to watch how Real is going to fix it    
    
    
    @sannti Agree. Just like here and we'll see if FCB bigs can rotate! Again, I think it is a key issue in the finals pic.twitter.com/N19Zup1kh2    
    
    
    @sannti Agree! Just like the old song: http://www.songsforteaching.com/folk/dembones.php … Mirotic connected to Carroll, who is connected to Sergio, who is... Synergies!    
    
    
    Envidia eterna a @sergiogm83 por haber podido entrenar a Niko Mirotic. Vaya jugador...    
    
    
    POPOVICH:Get them on a bus, it arrives at the ramp over here, we get off the bus, we get on the court and we play. That's how we get ready.    
    
    
    @LukaBassin Really glad for you coach! Wish you a lot of success!    
    
    
    Van Gundy "You can forget sometimes just how good Wade is" (ya se encarga el de recordártelo, Coach)    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara You know I'm kind of a true lineups believer... So I guess you're right!    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore European punks...    
    
    
    Let the game flow Danny... #shotselection    
    
    
    @CoachFinamore So, when is Ivan Drago coming? 2016?    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd Too late. 5:06 a.m. In Spain    
    
    
    Battier moneyfrickingball    
    
    
    @FlinderBoyd And no way to celebrate if Pop wins this one... But I'll survive    
    
    
    Tim #youleadwefollow    
    
    
    @ganchetto 100% Agree    
    
    
    I do love this game. G'night!    
    
    
    @CCortesR44 Felicidades!    
    
    
    Otro aeropuerto con wifi abierta, Tánger. SXXI. #wifiaeropuerto    
    
    
    #laiarules    
    
    
    @tomasvds A new life ahead, go for it! You've had a great career and you have all the respect from bball people.    
    
    
    @streetball Only with our women's NT (they won Eurobasket yesterday evening) on the court...    
    
    
    Proud to be Ivory Coast NT Asisstant Coach. We start our stage. On our way to the Afrobasket '13 pic.twitter.com/g7gbt3syrJ    
    
    
    Glad to see how three players I worked with last season in Prievidza made it to the Slovak U20 & U18 squads. Masiar, Brodziansky & Sturcel    
    
    
    First practice of the day in Monastir (Tunisia) #afrobasket2013 Cote d'Ivoire getting ready. Nice gym. pic.twitter.com/oDLPmmbYct    
    
    
    The stage goes on in Monastir. Beautiful gym. #afrobasket2013 Cote d'Ivoire Basketball pic.twitter.com/lPkZYqMzn3    
    
    
    @NaoufalUariachi @basketcamino THX my friend! I missed you guys too. Done thing. We'll be in touch. Where are u heading now?    
    
    
    Cincinnati Bengals - Oklahoma drill #wow #hardknocks Si no lo habéis visto, recomendable... pic.twitter.com/d1xyN9gxYP    
    
    
    @CoachReveno I saw your game against Angola. I like your team and the way you play (BTW the 3pointer was way beyond the 24") Good luck!    
    
    
    Preparados... #Afrobasket2013 pic.twitter.com/PUBifJfH0U    
    
    
    Ben Romdhane 19 pts en primer cuarto contra Burkina. WOW.  #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Big respect for #Egypt Basketball Team. They play hard, smart and with their heart all game long #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    #Egypt #Egipto #Afrobasket2013 pic.twitter.com/fqCiAAKGA3    
    
    
    OMG Egipto!!!! #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Excelente Mike Mokongo, 11 ptos en primer cuarto y Centroafrica ganando a Nigeria 27-24 #wheresurpriseshappen #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    Un paso más. One more step #RoadToSpain2014 #Afrobasket2013    
    
    
    I believe #RoadToSpain2014 pic.twitter.com/TCoBFaXoxf    
    
    
    Afrobasket 2013 http://bit.ly/1342zUe     
    
    
    You'd have much more fun watching the game with the Spanish broadcasters @Euro_Adventures @sannti @TalkBasket Hilarious    
    
    
    Leo newsletters llenas de "steve nash drill" - "stephen curry drill" - "reggie miller drill" que enseñan a dar la vuelta (botando) a un cono    
    
    
    Top 10 Afrobasket 2013 “@REVERSEMAGAZINE: #Afrobasket2013: Le Top 10 ultra spectaculaire http://bit.ly/1dSpRSX  @FIBA #roadtospain2014”    
    
    
    Not the best decision making from Perperoglu in that last D against Belinelli… Going under the screen with almost no time to go...    
    
    
    "Perdimos porque..." http://amzn.com/k/AAgovjKmQSOjA031x6QgAA … we have a natural tendency to look for instances that confirm our story and our vision of...    
    
    
    And now, Eurobasket stats by @sJacas Amazing work. Endless. He should be hired by now by an EL power house to work on advanced stats...    
    
    
    @sannti @Lipko2013 No, no. We won.    
    
    
    Aquiles?????    
    
    
    How many times will Ukraine run this set for Jeter until the end of the game? #basketeditor @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/tDqkuWfHJy    
    
    
    Or,without him, this one: Small/big off ball screen followed by a ball screen #basketeditor @BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/PR2hCQUnI4    
    
    
    So you want more basketball stats... check @TeamTextbook work, they're growing... http://t-book.co/     
    
    
    That, Kavvadas, is exactly what I talk about when I talk about setting a ball screen.    
    
    
    Bourousis short roll... Punishes help and creates a wide open shot #basketeditor @basketeditor pic.twitter.com/J2OARLsfpb    
    
    
    @sJacas VSpan % from BEKO during the EB??    
    
    
    Clásico partido que resuelve Bramos    
    
    
    @sJacas Would you show us Spain's shots creation distribution?    
    
    
    @sJacas Interesting. I guess is not that easy to reach conclusions in short tournaments like this one. Nice job anyway!    
    
    
    Thanks to @RunKeeper & @UnderArmour 1st run with my #UASpeedForm for being top 10 in the #FastestCity competition! pic.twitter.com/iC8cPE6ZVY    
    
    
    @lloydgar He has Euroleague level for sure. Talented, physical, patient, game knowledge, terrific shot creation skills, and his shooting...    
    
    
    Amazing amount of interesting data (shot creation) from @sJacas: a bunch of shot creation/possession usage graphs http://www.in-the-game.org/eurobasket-2013-shot-creationpossession-usage/ …”    
    
    
    “@sannti: El Chacho's throwing a "welcome to European ball" party for Micic.” He's been on fire for three years now. OMG    
    
    
    @sJacas France +/- with De Colo + Parker opposed to Parker at PG + a regular SG? Maybe I ask too many questions I know...    
    
    
    @sJacas ...and I guess you get what I'm suggesting with my last question...    
    
    
    @sJacas They need you at FIBA too... Do You have the same feeling? FRA playing better with T.P. off the PG spot?    
    
    
    I love flat screens. So do Tony Parker pic.twitter.com/ADBeJMlXPu    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Puerto Rico tried that against Brazil with Cheney on Marcelinho Huertas on the last FIBA Américas.    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Yes. But with more and more teams playing small ball nowadays... good D option for a couple of minutes    
    
    
    @Eil82 I'm in too pal!    
    
    
    @Eil82 I'm Fratello's big fan since he said the best of coaching Spudd Webb was that they could share suits if they needed to    
    
    
    Ukraine should stop the sloppy passing specially when Draper is around...    
    
    
    @Eil82 "it ain't over till it's over"    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket That would help    
    
    
    @UgurYilmazz_ Haha... Was talking about Aradori's dribbling hand. Should've placed it forward and on the inside to be able to...    
    
    
    @UgurYilmazz_ ...change direction avoiding Lavrinovic. Ball screen fundamentals. I'll try to use English more often LOL    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Yeah, I'm thinking about the African 4th best, to begin with...    
    
    
    @Lipko2013 We want YOU for Spain2014!    
    
    
    LIT need no more against CRO zone... corner and BOOM @basketeditor #basketeditor pic.twitter.com/6yXxmNXEIa    
    
    
    The zone won't work for Croatia today pic.twitter.com/aiclD3OnC2    
    
    
    @TeamTextbook So defense gives championships? Well, if you can score too, it does...    
    
    
    And they keep biting on the corner back door...    
    
    
    @sannti I'm not the "funny" kind of guy but I was gonna say FRA is a Parker oriented team while SPA is a Beard oriented...    
    
    
    Feeding Marc: SG curl+read Marc's defender. Behind: straight pass In front: high/low with 4 @basketeditor pic.twitter.com/f0mIMFrVgk    
    
    
    “@sannti: NBA'ers, stay away from El Chacho. This is an order, not a request.” We're not joking now. Seriously.    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I remember that Zalgiris with Kazlauskas & Sabonis. There were off. sets I keep using now. Pretty interesting basketball    
    
    
    And by the way, best announcer EVER, @LiamCanny on SER-ITA FIBATV right now. This guy does his job all around the globe    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I guess many Spanish fans will support Lietuva tonight... Good luck!    
    
    
    France's big men mid range shots (or help-reading) is the key for them in the  p&r battle    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen He needs to keep an eye on Parker to box him out though...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Keep an eye on Fran Guerra ('92)    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen I think he will. Saw him a week ago and he was better than I expected… It will be interesting to follow his development    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara As you said, his performance was great at FIBA Americas… No European team giving him a try?    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara He appeared to be under control all along the FIBA Americas… Understandable though.    
    
    
    It's early, but Banvit looked good against EFES… It is a team to follow for many reasons this season, isn't it? pic.twitter.com/Liubo2OBlD    
    
    
    @Glarusa @Euro_E_Row Pretty well. I'm sure he'll have a very good season (again)    
    
    
    Bird vs. Dr.J  http://amzn.com/k/CACGJL5ESbqntmDlNWW_5Q … Whenever he gets close to Doc, he kinda whispers, “Thirty to eight, Doc, thirty to eight, Doc.”...    
    
    
    Did I see it right? Banvit asisstant Coach watching last play on his cellphone?    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen Some would send the big guy to the bench for allowing a shot instead of forcing the penetration    
    
    
    Third game I watch Banvit so far this season (and pre-season)and  it's clear they want to be aggressive when defending ball screens    
    
    
    @brianmccormick @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen It varies a lot depending on level. I'd say it goes from around 30 to maybe 50-60 (top teams)    
    
    
    @brianmccormick @GalenHarkness Agree with more games=better development but too many games + not enough practice wouldn't work... Balance    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick BTW in Hungary there's the U23 league (with many U18 players) with 22 RS games + F8...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick ...that means an U18-U17 could play those 30 plus another 30 or so with his age team, plus...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick Once a week. Maybe twice a week a couple or three times during the season...    
    
    
    @GalenHarkness @harrimannonen @brianmccormick …then by the end of the season there are national tournaments w the best teams in the country    
    
    
    Banvit-Ostend both teams showing pretty good spacing. It's going to be a tough game.    
    
    
    Banvit, looking for the middle screen from the very beginning of their offense #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/EYItBEnyC2    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen what is Mejia doing??!! Man...    
    
    
    @redhoopsgr @LithuaniaBasket They're pretty resilient aren't they?    
    
    
    I didn't catch the new time out rules... @LithuaniaBasket @redhoopsgr @HoopLikeDrazen Can you help me?    
    
    
    @tomasvds And I need to say they deserve it 100%    
    
    
    "Evaluating coaches based on the process or the result" Another MUST read from @brianmccormick http://feedly.com/k/18WX1LE     
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Do you? Oostende showed pretty solid basketball. They're tough, with good spacing, share the ball… They're a nice surprise    
    
    
    Excelente post-game    
    
    
    @sJacas I think Mejri will get more minutes as the season goes on. You?    
    
    
    @sJacas IMO Slaughter has been one of RMA's best signings in years.    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Do u think it could be a balance thing more than a weight thing? I mean,he will never be a J.Dorsey if u know what I mean    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Agree    
    
    
    You're so picky :-D “@brianmccormick: Looking at YouTube: throwing the ball off the glass and jumping to get it is not a "rebounding drill"    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara To me it's clear that he's getting stronger. And faster. And I'd say he keeps working on his skills. Looks really good    
    
    
    RT: "@rafael_uehara: I think what might determine how soon he becomes a contriutor at NBA level is his level of readiness on defense. (2)”    
    
    
    @sJacas He looks good. Guess after scouting every team will try to deny his left hand... We'll see    
    
    
    @sJacas Not that Bemerhaven looked like the best PnR defenders, which helped him a couple of times...    
    
    
    @sJacas :-) whenever I can I like to watch games from different leagues. Germany is more and more interesting. That game was good (not only    
    
    
    @sJacas ...him but also Stojic, Echenique...    
    
    
    @redglove12 @sJacas Done    
    
    
    @redglove12 Can't DM you back...    
    
    
    My last tweet show there are some good basketball analysis out there… Aún se hacen buenos análisis de básket… THX to @robscott33    
    
    
    Think about this. Pensad en esto: http://amzn.com/k/kjrm1JglToikVQMWS3SCgg … basketball’s past is its future.    
    
    
    Eurobasket - Afrobasket http://bit.ly/19enXbM     
    
    
    So @sJacas with the new off.reb. 14" rule, how many more quick-isolation ball screens per game are we going to see? An average of...+20?    
    
    
    “@sJacas: I'd assume a little less: there's ca. 20 orb/game in average,4 of them converted for direct putbacks.Maybe 12-14?” Sounds accurate    
    
    
    Michael Jordan on being late to practice: http://amzn.com/k/aszdrS4kT2C7kXphVWDECA … Early in the season, Burrell was late for practice because he had be...    
    
    
    Interesante http://www.grantland.com/story/_/id/8719297/how-kobe-bryant-missed-shots-translate-new-nba-statistic-kobe-assist … "crediting a wide-open corner 3 solely to  Matt Bonner, Kawhi Leonard, or Danny Green...    
    
    
    ...is akin to giving Javier Bardem sole credit for No Country for Old Men" Son los tiros fallados por Kobe buenos para los Lakers?    
    
    
    "...the analytical "baseball-ification" of our fluid sport too often neglects this basic tenet of basketball ecology."    
    
    
    @IbaizabalST Zorionak! Oso ondo neskak!    
    
    
    Realmente OA se ha caído, verdad?    
    
    
    @DjordjevicStef I followed him closely when he played Eurochallenge F4 in Debrecen 2 seasons ago. Amazing player.    
    
    
    BB en 14" tras rebote ofensivo. Posteando rápido a Mumbrú #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/wBOT9AKrUJ    
    
    
    @sJacas You'll love to check Gran Canaria and the "double stretch 4" with Nacho Martín + Eulis Báez    
    
    
    @cagriturhan @rodhig7 He's struggling against the Martín + Baez combo, he's mobile but not that mobile to go beyond the line to play D…    
    
    
    @sJacas @robscott33 @cagriturhan @rodhig7 Did you see that? WOW    
    
    
    @cagriturhan @sJacas @robscott33 @rodhig7 I meant the fastbreak after free throw...    
    
    
    @rodhig7 IMO every team needs post ups... Even if they're not successful at first sight    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara + he can shoot. He's living a second youth, better than the first one IMHO    
    
    
    @Justin_Ingram20 Are you skipping practices or what?    
    
    
    If you're going to follow @Euroleague this season, you can celebrate its tip off with @sJacas and his charts: WHERE ADVANCED STATS HAPPEN    
    
    
    Jelinek reads well the 2 vs. 1 in fastbreak situation and finishes straight instead of giving the useless pass many players give so often    
    
    
    @quiquevich @jondelapresa Some would say he needs to gain weight I think he needs to improve his balance to use his strenght properly    
    
    
    @quiquevich @jondelapresa But clearly he is on his way to be if not the best one of the best inside players in Europe    
    
    
    Corner threes in LBO-MAC... Danger!    
    
    
    As Mirotic gets better and better, RMA bigs get harder to defend. Plus defensive solidness (without Mejri!)... they look real good again    
    
    
    “@rafael_uehara: If Bourousis hits 3s well RM's making the dream come true: every guy needs to be defended at every spot on the floor.” HOT!    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara You were talking about it... Two threes in a row by Mirotic and Bourousis... Unstoppable    
    
    
    Nice way to end the third quarter... RMA's SOOB #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/1RToxjaVp4    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara …not many teams can reach that goal… and that means a fast paced game, which Real loves… Tough...    
    
    
    "Where SportVU...can truly help is in ensuring that repetition is thoughtful..." http://hardwoodparoxysm.com/2013/10/02/shane-battiers-take-on-the-sportvu-revolution-might-surprise-you/ …    
    
    
    100% Agree RT @brianmccormick: also, the data will help with training, preventing injury, fatigue monitoring, etc.    
    
    
    @sJacas And now, are we supposed to sleep tonight? LOL. Amazing stuff as usual. THX    
    
    
    @LiveBBall_TV If only I could login… something is not working properly. Waiting for the customer services representative to contact...    
    
    
    My last RT shows you how wrong a coach can be, never mind his level, league, experience… Amazing.    
    
    
    @LiveBBall_TV customer service fixed my problem quickly. Thanks guys. I really want to enjoy tonight's EL games!    
    
    
    Mirotic being able to finish towards his right shoulder that quick... How can you guard him in mid/low post???    
    
    
    I think Lamonica was telling the coaches, hey guys, a 30" time out is a 30" time out, cut the talking…    
    
    
    @TikotDeRoa IMO Ike Diogu es Euroliga sin ninguna duda    
    
    
    Tomic's short rolls create plenty of passing options (e.g. K-Pap's last back door) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/RW53utNyXa    
    
    
    “@HoopLikeDrazen: Almost had it again, Tomic to K-Pap backdoor. Defense just converges on Tomic & opens up all those options.Great cutter.”    
    
    
    FBU looking for Bogdanovic in low post... (I) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/jE5HhshsqF    
    
    
    ...and FBU counter once the defense is expecting for the same situation (and II) #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/t6G8c471yR    
    
    
    “@sJacas: One day we'll have nightmares from this: http://twitter.com/sJacas/status/393829659877470208/photo/1pic.twitter.com/5NpTbli1af ” WOW a picture from Málaga! Nice!    
    
    
    Seth's Blog: When to speak up http://pinterest.com/pin/390194755186505371/ …    
    
    
    @SAnalyticsBlog @CatapultSports @TeamTextbook No way    
    
    
    LBO in off. transition, Nocioni pick & pops #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/kTShIbhu6R    
    
    
    With so many injuries, LBO is relying on spacing (p&r, p&p, stretch 4, ISO) and it's working so far... We'll see after half time adjustments    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland I'd like you to think what's better, riding the hot hand, or letting the defense think you're going to…    
    
    
    CSKA struggling to find the mismatches... Even with all the FBUs switching... Bad passing... Huge problems    
    
    
    @luis_cristovao I hope it will be useful! Don't hesitate to contact for questions or feedback. Thank you, enjoy!    
    
    
    Bourussis' fastbreaks on their way to become a classic in RMA offense...    
    
    
    @HoopLikeDrazen That would be great, but no TV tonight.    
    
    
    SIG almost managed to stop RMA's alley oop (almost) pic.twitter.com/N7jxwA0SmI    
    
    
    I'd really like to (once in a while) shoot some Questions For Advanced Analytics Guys #QFAAG I wonder what @sJacas thinks about it...    
    
    
    Slightly better spacing FCB & CSKA during the last minutes... Some good looks. Expecting something else though...    
    
    
    Messina's call was: "foul the roller on the catch"    
    
    
    Is there a better PG than S.Rodriguez right now? And I mean all around the world...    
    
    
    “@sJacas: Efes PnR D vulnerable to lobs (strong in other areas). Wrote about it last yr (http://bit.ly/1gKHC8c )" Really interesting post    
    
    
    @rodhig7 Watching a game which I already read before... Your Partizan's spacing article is really accurate.    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland Bayern trying to ride Staiger's hot hand… almost worked… except for his last airball...    
    
    
    @sJacas #QFAAG what do you think about eFG% related to number of passes + shotclock seconds spent? Does it make sense for you?    
    
    
    @sJacas "v" for "very" now I get it... I'll have to review the Harvard Statistics110 lectures first...    
    
    
    @sannti Let's get a link to watch that game live! #teamwork    
    
    
    @lloydgar I wouldn't hesitate to sign him. He's top level IMO. Euroleague level I'd say. He's got the whole package. We'll see...    
    
    
    Euroleague handball? Smh    
    
    
    CSKA managed pretty well team fouls to close the second quarter. Which by the way was way better than the first.    
    
    
    Thinking about a pts per ball screen (made/allowed) stat @sJacas #QFAAG    
    
    
    @georgerowland @sJacas Points off 0 - 1 - 2 passes after a ball screen is set?    
    
    
    “@georgerowland: @sannti @rjmbasket08 @sJacas New system, called GeorgeVU,I watch the game and note down with a pencil" HIRED.Right attitude    
    
    
    @rodhig7 @georgerowland @sJacas That's up to the coach, but related to lineups to begin with: This two guys running a P&R whitin lineup X...    
    
    
    @georgerowland @rodhig7 @sJacas How hot it would be to know what's better, pick and pop or pick and roll within different sets/lineups...    
    
    
    @sJacas @georgerowland @rodhig7 Let's keep them off the equation… What do you think?    
    
    
    As I said, hot RT @sJacas: @rjmbasket08 "you'd be splitting it up to dozens of lineups/positions/locations @georgerowland @rodhig7    
    
    
    LBK, nice start... Offense flowing and tough defense. I liked Mainoldi's first foul. Nice sign    
    
    
    How many teams follow the "offensive rebound + three point shot" rule?    
    
    
    @sJacas Barcelona used to do it back in the day with Ndong, Vázquez... It was really hard to score against them...    
    
    
    @agustijulbe @sJacas Against that FCB you had to dunk or hit "nothing but net" or you wouldn't score at all. Right players+practice I guess    
    
    
    @sJacas Does he wear yellow jersey?    
    
    
    Even if I'm obviously (slightly) biased, Konate's dunk is the best... Best Alley-oops of #RoadToSpain2014: http://youtu.be/9O2OXYh8K4Y     
    
    
    @rafael_uehara Very good game. I'm posting something about it in a while    
    
    
    It's quite clear, Brose coaches are against cameras during time-outs... pic.twitter.com/5v7YiLvfmP    
    
    
    RMA baseline OOB, post up situation with Darden… plus high low option when the defender overplays… #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/exsw7wX4cP    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara IMO it's all about avoiding scouting…The thing is, are there rules about cam/mic? then every team should respect the rules...    
    
    
    @rafael_uehara And to answer your question, cam & mics are not that annoying. Everyone is used to them, c'mon!    
    
    
    100% agree RT @sJacas: RMB & Fener don't just stretch the defense to the 3pt arc, but often to NBA 3pt distance.    
    
    
    .@sJacas Maybe teams could try giving up the mid-range shots... Bulls style... Not easy anyway    
    
    
    I'd like them to answer but I guess their answer would be "not likely" @sJacas We need FG% data for 0-8" 8-16" 16-24" shotclock periods    
    
    
    Is PAO experimenting on giving up corner threes? Not working    
    
    
    UNI and a different way to screen the screener... then hand off situation on top #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/dws1kfznN2    
    
    
    BTW with the 14" "rule" the offensive rebound three pointer makes (still) much more sense... Don't u think so @sJacas ?    
    
    
    @sJacas Yes... You coined the concept... Once they start using it, they should give you a cent each time    
    
    
    Exactly "@sJacas: Get a quick open shot off the off-rebound? Right ... probably difficult to get better shot value later down the clock.”    
    
    
    Not easy to play offense with non - stretch bigs... pic.twitter.com/WcxoKRf3Zk    
    
    
    IMO @luis_cristovao @Lukas_Kuc You know more, but you realize there are many different answers for each situation...    
    
    
    Nice signing... "@sportando: Ike Diogu to play in D-League http://www.sportando.net/eng/usa/d-league/69310/ike-diogu-to-play-in-d-league.html …”    
    
    
    Hines doing his thing... Amazing energy. Whatever he does. A+    
    
    
    Sada: post up + two penetrations. Strategy not working for cska? Defenders' effort?    
    
    
    Hines' shot creation numbers, please @sJacas    
    
    
    @sJacas I didn't catch it, but that's the way (some people might consider it irony, but you know it's not)    
    
    
    Nice situation, SIG looking for the high/low after diagonal cuts and big2big screen #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/gackRmaqZj    
    
    
    Which they can run after the PG gives the pass and goes to the corner, too. #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/LCYgYhMwjF    
    
    
    @nandoblanco I'd say you won't be seeing it in a while buddie… And it's kind of sad, yes.    
    
    
    Great player & hard worker RT @BBLofficial: ICYMI Paul Gause headlines our Team of the Week this week #BBLCupFinal! pic.twitter.com/9D6rtNjvUh    
    
    
    Real Quick: Liberar Tiros - Kyle Hines http://bit.ly/1dKnG0E     
    
    
    @nandoblanco It's all about reward / risk. At least at the highest level. Also, I guess the work (or lack of) with youngsters is important    
    
    
    And you'd think, "another easy W for RMA" but it wasn't! Which is still more amazing.    
    
    
    Ball screen defense KEY: arms & hands action pic.twitter.com/h3KbOSXHm2    
    
    
    One of the best game endings I've watched in a while... Those three sideline inboundings in a row, plus the coast to coast... #devotion    
    
    
    MPS sideline OOB set. They did it twice to play the hand off with Hackett... #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/EBClZuryCh    
    
    
    ...and the third time, Hunter with the backdoor cut to score! #BasketEditor pic.twitter.com/OSIuIyGcjA    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket Funny how some players like that kind of talking.    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket IMHO everyone has his share of responsibility when things go wrong.He takes it from his shoulders to put it on someone else    
    
    
    @LithuaniaBasket I think you get my point. It's his opinion, OK. I still think no one should avoid responsibility.And to me,smells like that    
    
    
    Ever noticed Draper's screens quality? Nice thing for a small player to set good screens    
    
    
    V-Span show has started… again #devotion pic.twitter.com/inndVTEdTU    
    
    
    Not many teams can make proper use of this hand off situation. OLY and FBU can. pic.twitter.com/it9KqkK9mD    
    
    
    @gonzalobedia IMO passer-receiver coord. Plus pass technique (hands position, body position, ball protection) plus pass angle...    
    
    
    @RomainDsDz My point is, what's its use if you can't shoot off that hand off pass? Spanoulis and Bogdanovic can.    
    
    
    @RomainDsDz That's it. Of course, there will be a repick right after the hand off, but then, that's a different story.    
    
    
    V-Span and mismatch decision making. Stay tunned...    
    
    
    Defensa De Desajuste / Mismatch Defense http://rjmbasket.blogspot.com.es/2014/01/defensa-de-desajuste-ideas-basicas.html#.UsfVG0REOxM.twitter …    
    
    
    @georgerowland Coach Plaza keeps doing it in Malaga. They do it on a regular basis+specially against that kind of player (see vs. Navarro)    
    
    
    Agree @robscott33 @luis_cristovao Team defense. You need good organization or it will be wide open shot after wide open shot    
    
    
    Yes @luis_cristovao @robscott33 the main idea (for me) is to force him to drive to the basket. That's the first goal for the defense    
    
    
    