@michaelmiraflor congrats this trumps the Adidas Jeezy sneaker as the realest sponsorship in the game    
    
    
    Excited to learn about mind reading from @hc http://shar.es/72iUs     
    
    
    @robbievitrano heading into town tonight, mad I'm missing #IdeaInstitute, but I would like to connect with the Trumpet team..    
    
    
    @ischafer @adfreak can't wait to see him kill some vampires    
    
    
    When I was young, I bought  a Honda Scooter for what these new Lebron sneakers are going to cost.    
    
    
    White folks just love to crip walk    
    
    
    Shout outs to my Korean brother who just owned the floor for Gangam Style    
    
    
    @thegasHole snacks on snacks on snacks    
    
    
    @DukeHoopBlog hey Rowe, drop me an email robert(at)http://blogads.com  and I'll put u in touch    
    
    
    @brittontaylor amazing!!! can you petition apple to forever change the "a" key to "sausages"    
    
    
    @barnapkins http://vimeo.com/47875656     
    
    
    @aburtch @barnapkins did you make your own song at the end? that functionality is crazy...    
    
    
    Wow @donaldhughes just told me we've reached an age where previous stars of MTV's Real World are in office and speaking at the RNC    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor think you would enjoy this book http://www.amazon.com/The-Big-Payback-History-Business/dp/0451229290 … had some good stories on cover diversity in Vibe's early days    
    
    
    @Jbrown523 you can still follow the old tech advice of shutdown + reboot    
    
    
    Do you make more money by giving away great content ?http://blog.aweissman.com/2012/06/what-if-we-give-it-away-lessons-from.html …    
    
    
    @carmenboca x100 when they use a bluetooh    
    
    
    @jl_weber thats the hard part....    
    
    
    @baratunde did Romney really just throw a party on a Yacht named "Cracker Bay" ? http://abcnews.go.com/Blotter/romney-party-yacht-flies-cayman-islands-flag/story?id=17105028#.UD5ugWie4mw …    
    
    
    Taylor Hicks is the perfect performer for the RNC #soulpatrol    
    
    
    @arilevine and we just pay the rent    
    
    
    Mitt just knocked over the asian cameraman did anybody else see that?    
    
    
    Promoted Mitt Tweet just popped up, I wish it was for President Dwayne Elizondo Mountain Dew Herbert Camacho instead    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U sorry about that cous, I'll make the $30kl back, I can feel a hot streak coming in black jack    
    
    
    @Scaroline27 amazing...    
    
    
    @SocialDivo wanted to connect on twitter too, keep in touch    
    
    
    I guess this crowd ain't up on Hot Cheetos    
    
    
    @angelinadarling amazing, dirt loves the kids    
    
    
    Who knows more about sleeping with dogs than this guy. #petsmart http://instagr.am/p/PH8q9TKDaT/     
    
    
    Cine: Hey Girl http://cinemagr.am/show/14693855  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    Cine: Chain Reaction http://cinemagr.am/show/14697728  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    Awfully tired boss, dog tired #RipJonCoffee    
    
    
    Nothing says #4ever like Nick & Jessica http://instagr.am/p/PKpG2QKDdn/     
    
    
    Content is the 7th Weapon of influence - @markwschaefer #CMWorld    
    
    
    Sorry Raleigh can't make Hopscotch, too busy seeing Rick Springfield in Ohio http://instagr.am/p/PNsn1LKDXB/     
    
    
    Rick Springfield is trying to get the crowd to sing the lyrics to songs other than Jesse's Girl. #nothappening    
    
    
    @teacheyd great meeting you, lets clear an afternoon for Chicken & Waffles some time soon    
    
    
    Best of the Wurst http://instagr.am/p/PPdZxjKDbv/     
    
    
    Chevy Ok Go Video got a billion impressions online... after their Super Bowl spot used "We Are Young" song topped ITunes #CMWorld    
    
    
    Making someone fill out a form to get your content is like asking for sex before the first date @giladdevries #CMWorld    
    
    
    Jack Hanna in the house http://instagr.am/p/PP0Nw7qDbT/     
    
    
    When the gorillas weren't breeding Jack Hanna hired his wife's gynecologist    
    
    
    @allimooney  Think Quarterly just won something at theseContent Marketing Awards, let me know if I need to rep the family name    
    
    
    Shout outs to @donaldhughes for representing NC to the fullest at the DNC #huges2016    
    
    
    @allimooney yes I think so, it was at the end of this content marketing world conference.... Congrats    
    
    
    @ableparris is that a Bourbon tasting? Can I send you my resume?    
    
    
    @richiecruz Fania got me when I heard the Dave Cortez "Happy Soul with a Hook" that DJ Premo flipped for Christina Aguilera of all people    
    
    
    3D Printing Plastic Fisher-Price Records http://www.core77.com/blog/digital_fabrication/3d_printing_plastic_fisher-price_records_23358.asp … via @Core77    
    
    
    Best Nature Trail Ever http://instagr.am/p/PcePwpKDXT/     
    
    
    @barnapkins did you see these http://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccinemacamera/ …    
    
    
    @barnapkins just saw this too http://trifilmsept12.eventbrite.com/  you shoukd submit  Tinsel Town    
    
    
    Damn this Ninjatune Beastie Boys Paul's Boutique tribute mix is amazing http://soundcloud.com/ninja-tune/solid-steel-radio-show-31-8-1?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=wtshare&utm_medium=twitter&utm_content=http://soundcloud.com/ninja-tune/solid-steel-radio-show-31-8-1 …    
    
    
    @allnick great meeting you in Columbus, lets chat more soon, love to hear what you have planned for @startupstats and future blogs    
    
    
    @ableparris What? Bill Nye is still alive? ha ha    
    
    
    Is anyone's suggested Facebook friends showing you just eye candy, instead of people you might actually know?    
    
    
    @ischafer please order up an @InvisibleObama case study video, @InvisibleObama deserves to win this year too    
    
    
    #TweetToShoot It's duck season http://tweettoshoot.neimanlabs.com/     
    
    
    @zipplockbag sinde we're both insanley handsome men, so we might need someone else to experience this problem, before drawing a conclusion    
    
    
    Shout outs to amc for playing The Green Mile all day everyday    
    
    
    @HaniHamma @colleenbrea Optimus Prime is the greatest leader    
    
    
    @arilevine amazing mix! that album was huge inspiration to dig in the crates, and this brought it all together for me...    
    
    
    If you played college ball before me, you got no business in the club. I'm looking at you Jeremy Hyatt    
    
    
    My Gangam Style My Pony mix is so conceptual    
    
    
    @barnapkins @colleenbrea @benaffleck amazing bring that back home    
    
    
    @arilevine are you in NC this weekend?    
    
    
    Air Celek #flyeaglesfly    
    
    
    Best headline of the day goes to @adage : Can the McRib Save Christmas? http://adage.com/u/7A8Sdb     
    
    
    @saneel the lowline founders will be speaking at this http://influencerconnyc-eorg.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    @bmorrissey is one gif enough to start  a Buzzfeed for us Eagles Fans : Birdfeed?http://gifrific.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/Brent-Celek-Jumps-Over-Ed-Reed.gif …    
    
    
    Do ad agencies have a job number for fantasy football?    
    
    
    @calebkramer @kylecameron we've got a polling feature some of our blogs, let me know next time, hopefully we can get a ton of free responses    
    
    
    @mzmelissa should have known a smart producer has it all figured out    
    
    
    @Gejashiku damn ravers    
    
    
    Hoops with @Khoadini @mikeppc99 and @chavisheughts tonight, I was Mr. 1 Run and Done    
    
    
    @beneckerson that negative attitude is clearly why you need this app ha ha, they got more investors than devs    
    
    
    @PaulGelb congrats Paul, great news    
    
    
    @erictullis Kenny Dope Produced it under The Bucket Heads name.. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K2vLaCElhP8 … samples Chicago Street Player http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_trFuBGPQho …    
    
    
    @erictullis man I'm  bummed I have to miss Kenny's set... let me know if you have any new favorite disco edits you're liking    
    
    
    Guest reviewers @immaculateinfat are killing it again, getting buck on purple drank amongst Gen X'ers http://goo.gl/dDI6V     
    
    
    Based on early reviews, seems you could easily improve IOS 6 buy institution Emojicon based maps    
    
    
    Props to @fakeshoredrive on building brands and musical movement at the same time #dewyou    
    
    
    @cpanetta77 I think he played the republican national convention?    
    
    
    So @Gejashiku played Blues Traveller tonight..    
    
    
    @shaunstripling lets hope it catches on in advertising http://adage.com/article/adages/ad-agency-creates-nap-rooms-employees/227475/ …    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands good luck, I'm sure you'll crush it    
    
    
    @darrylohrt @aburtch so a new Myspace = Pinstagram?    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor I bought some bike stuff at the beach and saw Walmart's "Fixie" Bike first hand http://www.walmart.com/ip/Thruster-700c-Men-s-Fixie-Bike/17206771 …    
    
    
    I never would have guessed Myspace would takover my day    
    
    
    @haveboard @duanebrown I feel like the slow loading choppy about to crash vimeo video gave me an accurate feel of the real Myspace    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller you weren't on Myspace before, how did you find out about my gigs at White Collar Crime?    
    
    
    Monday Night Hoops http://instagr.am/p/P-tXerKDZX/     
    
    
    @bradbeejay you know your old when going for 20 means minutes, not points    
    
    
    I hope this will be discussed in a Obama Romney Debate: Bacon, pork shortage "now unavoidable" http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/breaking/la-fi-mo-pork-bacon-shortage-20120924,0,6240960.story …    
    
    
    @barnapkins isn't that near a salami shop?    
    
    
    Clicked a banner that offered classic Atari games, prompts you to download MS Explorer for ad free gaming http://www.beautyoftheweb.com/amazing#/atari     
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic those look perfect for the evening wear competition, fancy sneakers    
    
    
    @richiecruz @RobMarkman I heard the saddest radio spot down south recently for Amil "1st lady of the Roc" hosting some hood club night    
    
    
    @barnapkins that's literally epic news, congrats    
    
    
    Checkpoint on capital blvd    
    
    
    @Buie i just landed at JFK, let's link up if you're around    
    
    
    Authenticity for brands, we know it when we don't see it,  are you a likeable person or soulless corporation? @tim_leake #AWIX    
    
    
    @tim_leake great presentation, really enjoyed your part    
    
    
    Didn't win the @advertisingweek Dj battle, but retiring to the Waldorf Astoria for the night makes me feel like a winner.    
    
    
    @TMorgz congrats on the big move and new gig, I'll be back in 2 weeks for a Perez Hilton, party and you have to come    
    
    
    @wjessewright congrats Jesse, awesome work    
    
    
    @advertisingweek thank you, your team is amazing, awesome week    
    
    
    Most retweeted tweet of last year came from a marketer #AWIX    
    
    
    CNN Breaking News: Romney just finished eating at the Cheesecake Factory    
    
    
    Anybody else get a sponsored facebook post from a political candidate tonight?    
    
    
    @steveESPOpowers A hand written cease and desist letter for the unauthorized use of your likeness, is the classy way to thank them    
    
    
    @nckfbr are we still on for lunch today?    
    
    
    @nckfbr yeah, send a text, tweet or rock a t the window when you are heading up this way    
    
    
    Lady in my building just told me my outfit was cute, as a 6 foot tall man in seersucker shorts, I'm going to take that as a win    
    
    
    @RaleighRockstar In the south no one ever goes to jail in a seersucker suit    
    
    
    @bmcd67 hey brian, do you manage the sci quest events looking to get some feedback on a wordpress plugin that it looks like you are using?    
    
    
    @bmcd67 yes thats the one, thinking it might be a good solution for some music / event blogs we work with... might need to get some feedback    
    
    
    Hey @Buie it was great seeing you in NYC, I was just talking to my friend @donaldhughes about @mgproject lets all grab lunch soon    
    
    
    @Buie @donaldhughes I'm going to try and take tomorrow off, lets do next week    
    
    
    I went shopping for normal headphones  tonight, not as easy as it sounds in a post Beats by Dre world    
    
    
    Party ain't a party til your guest is sitting in a Piñata  http://instagr.am/p/QfwLp5qDdX/     
    
    
    @saracobaugh the DewDriver?    
    
    
    @jnorthen hey Janet, great seeing you in NYC, still blown away by your mental telepathy pr powers    
    
    
    Someone in purchasing got a little too excited by the Ruff Ryders 10 years ago http://instagr.am/p/Qh-s7LqDZP/     
    
    
    Love that Jack Dorsey confirms his scaled down involvement at Twitter by posting it on Tumblr http://tnw.to/g5xr     
    
    
    @ableparris but will it tell me to buy collages and photo prints from the Parris family, if not they have some bugs to fix    
    
    
    @benblackmer @rapportive I'm seeing it on reply emails, but no longer see rapportive when i compose new emails    
    
    
    @mq5 Happy Birthday!!!!    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive Is this part of your plot to bring No Limit back?    
    
    
    @narrowd congrats on the FWA, huge!! but that client must have been real pain to deal with right?    
    
    
    @voiceOrezin didn't know if you caught this article: The Responsive Design Myth http://www.digiday.com/publishers/the-responsive-design-myth/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    Video dream team @barnapkins @thegasHole @Napwright collab w/ @NewRaleigh on the Cooke Street Carnival Video featuring @4toon    
    
    
    Has any designer done their own versions of the ebay logo? Can you really update zany dot com era logos?    
    
    
    Walmart finally realizes what we've all known: people don't want to go inside their stores... http://www.wired.com/business/2012/10/walmart-wishes-amazon-unhappy-holidays-with-same-day-delivery-launch/ …    
    
    
    Innovation or PR?: The Lexus iPad Print Ad | Digiday http://www.digiday.com/brands/innovation-or-pr-the-lexus-ipad-print-ad/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    @bmorrissey @funkmastabaker I'm mailing in the check for my @digiday print subscription right now, CinePrint is the future    
    
    
    Paul Ryan Has Already Lost the Debate Based on These Workout Photos - @Gawker http://gawker.com/5950879/paul-ryan-has-already-lost-the-debate-based-on-these-workout-photos …    
    
    
    @Malbonnington @iaintait this dj's rendition of Trans Europe Express is Ridiculous (minute and a half mark)  http://youtu.be/SiqIlW1IvlE     
    
    
    Poor Lance, he  had no choice but to dope http://ti.me/Ot2e7s     
    
    
    Dude just pulled out his harmonica and confirmed what key the record I'm playing is in. Bout to get real in here    
    
    
    @barnapkins bring your accordion it's on now    
    
    
    Quora Digest for the day http://www.quora.com/Wealth/Is-getting-rich-worth-it …    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller it looks like miserable multimillionaires still love the site.    
    
    
    @Chapinc we can only hope that Dishwasher Pete gets added to tonight's broadcast as a dishwashing strategist...    
    
    
    Why did I learn about the Hoagie Trail after my Philly trip? http://historictaconyrevitalization.com/hoagie-trail/     
    
    
    @djforge man, I just had to buy new headphones... and the Beats By Dre success has ruined headphones, thank god Sony still makes monitors    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U when you live in the south, a Wawa hoagie taste like heaven    
    
    
    @dougkleeman by ad people for ad people http://bbh-labs.com/while-you-were-off-an-iphone-web-app-for-the-connected-set …    
    
    
    @ableparris I'm getting ready to head out to Bk, how's your schedule looking    
    
    
    @ableparris I leave Friday, I'm up all the time, but needed to catch up with some  bk peeps, so I wanted to give a shout    
    
    
    @TMorgz I keep forgetting you are a New Yorker now... are you around tonight?    
    
    
    @TMorgz Perez Hilton Party at Highline Balroom, can you dm me your email    
    
    
    @TMorgz did u get in ok?    
    
    
    congrats @accarrino @annetteshade great seeing you last night    
    
    
    @beatrizv520 Great catching up with you..    
    
    
    Murdered out matte black Pontiac was the talk of the auto parts store http://instagr.am/p/Q-w3tRqDZb/     
    
    
    Dropping fresh copies of classic riddims courtesy of @MissLilysChat    
    
    
    We about to take it up from 2chainz to 3chainz    
    
    
    Girl with Honey Boo Boo Accent just asked for We No Speak Americano    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller jerk    
    
    
    Enjoying a soulful set by the amazing Keith Ward @calaveraraleigh    
    
    
    @barnapkins the new philly Wawa was baking bread in store, I think the bread distribution was the only thing holding them back...    
    
    
    I'm used to getting flyered at my Dj gigs, but not my day job http://instagr.am/p/RGZQ8ZKDdl/     
    
    
    Denny's to Launch Middle-Earth Inspired Menu http://adage.com/u/WvAwba     
    
    
    Woman Posts Boyfriend Request on GitHub, Requires Access to His Server http://betabeat.com/?p=67389  via @betabeat    
    
    
    The Quora Digest has become a highlight of my week, http://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-to-be-incredibly-funny …    
    
    
    Elmo Piñata got worked  blogads http://instagr.am/p/RIzAzBKDch/     
    
    
    @aburtch are you in this mellow mushroom video crossing the street or is it an Anson look a like ? http://creativity-online.com/work/mellow-mushroom-follow-us-well-follow-you/29591 …    
    
    
    @aburtch too funny saw Mitch share it, and it was on Creativity too, time to get your Sag card..    
    
    
    @djforge @DJSK1 do you guys know any good Charleston SC dj's ? A friend is getting married there, wants an old school party rocker    
    
    
    @djforge thanks Forge, @NattyHeavy what up, let me know your email or best way to refer a friend for a gig...    
    
    
    Dyskograf an optical based turntable, make your own beats with a marker http://vimeo.com/51700038     
    
    
    @megsterr mush Cali mush    
    
    
    @soundboy love what you guys are doing at songkick, detour is amazing...    
    
    
    @RickWebb ahhhh the Ikea Expedit, that 5x5 will hold over 2000 vinyl LP's, don't ask me how I know    
    
    
    @soundboy just signed up for your API too, looking forward to seeing what that data can do for local and event blogs I work with...    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller how many beignets did you eat before that presentation    
    
    
    Art of the Q http://instagr.am/p/ROgXn2KDfW/     
    
    
    Stop When Swinging http://instagr.am/p/ROgsI_KDf0/     
    
    
    The future sounds better in the Queens English RT @bmorrissey what percentage of planners are british? 60%?    
    
    
    @funkmastabaker what was the tumblr he ripped off, I want to check the og    
    
    
    @JasonHirschhorn I was just talking to my friend from http://areyouahuman.com/  today, I love their solution for bad CAPTCHAS, check them out    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield @jasonhirschhorn I like @solvemedia too, big problem, I'm glad multiple companies are bringing change    
    
    
    Do girls put pink monograms on their Suv's in other places, or just the south?    
    
    
    This nice southern lady just gave me a glow stick, and offered to feed me, am I dj'n a rave for Paula Dean?    
    
    
    @zipplockbag I can't wait for @thegasHole to be Guy Fieri    
    
    
    @patricec bumba clot hurricane    
    
    
    Obama and Gov Christie focus on working together to help the people..  http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/10/30/christie-praises-obama-doesnt-give-a-damn-about-romney-photo-op/#.UI_e-O4LfYM.twitter …    
    
    
    This is the White House I'm most concerned about right now pic.twitter.com/qEcylgAb    
    
    
    Can a 10 year old make better advertising than you? via @agencyspy http://www.mediabistro.com/agencyspy/toronto-agency-celebrates-ten-years-by-handing-creative-reins-over-to-10-year-olds_b40479 …    
    
    
    @scottforshay amazing to see the little one's giving creative direction to the editors    
    
    
    Thank You @jermainelandon for the term "Twerkers Comp"    
    
    
    Wow, thanks to @arilevine for sharing http://furby.tumblr.com/  and #HSUchat    
    
    
    Genius Bar - "yeah a bar without alcohol is not genius"    
    
    
    Do you think the right player is on the wrong team? @mcuban "I Would Vote for Romney if He Was a Democrat" http://wp.me/pk3mX-wp  via    
    
    
    Like pops always said, it doesn't matter if you win or lose, just cover the spread http://espn.go.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/8568724/nine-south-florida-youth-football-coaches-face-gambling-charges …    
    
    
    @denglander is that the one staring the Fat Boys?    
    
    
    @denglander classic    
    
    
    Turn the Epcot Dome into a Death Star and start building Ewok Village Orlando ASAP    
    
    
    @DevinPK10 no need to shave, furry applicants are encouraged    
    
    
    @RickWebb glad Lucy is safe, family is not too far on the shore... hope home and clubhouse were unaffected    
    
    
    @RickWebb family all down the shore and all are safe.. inlaws are year-round residents in Cape May, sounded bad early, but good reports now    
    
    
    Im ready for the return of the High Top Fade and Norris Cole on the Miami Heat is really helping the cause    
    
    
    @allnick I was amazed too, was wondered who actually hosts in NY    
    
    
    @holaolah he needs to design new Septa uniforms    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive Philly!!!!!    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor your instagram pics are crazy, lord of the flies hunger games stylee, hope you are well, and that was just documentary..    
    
    
    My man the @thegashole just killed the Halloween Game, all in with the Guy Fieri frosted tips http://instagr.am/p/Rd4B0eKDX4/     
    
    
    @cool_pond I highly suggest doing some back reading on Philebrity for the crazy tale that is Arthur Kade http://www.philebrity.com/index.php?s=arthur+kade …    
    
    
    When your kid has fangs, its best just to run with it http://dj-mooney.tumblr.com/post/34774319882/when-your-kid-has-fangs-its-best-just-to-run-with … via    
    
    
    Pumped to check out @davidchoe 's AMA on Reddit.. But I'll have to wait until I get home, you know its NSFW http://www.giantrobot.com/news/david-choe-ama-on-reddit/ …    
    
    
    @RyanNewYork thanks you for the awesome work on @TheFour2012    
    
    
    @thegasHole http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U5y9O20h9r8&feature=colike&utm_source=buffer&buffer_share=c1500 …    
    
    
    Who says Obama's not putting people back to work, Rasheed Wallace is playing for the Knicks    
    
    
    @Gejashiku I'm more Asian than you    
    
    
    @Khoadini been eating romantic dinners with Badu glad he has time to respond to @gejashiku    
    
    
    Dj Spclgst goes Bond http://instagr.am/p/RlapckqDWk/     
    
    
    Dude just had to rock his marathon medal for us fatties to see http://instagr.am/p/RncWPQKDYc/     
    
    
    Too much Middle Class talk, check @mike_palma for what tomorrow means for the Creative Class http://wp.me/pNb8n-WI     
    
    
    Help yourself to good food while helping others  join @immaculateinfat for a #sandy #EatDowntown Meetup - http://goo.gl/TLC69     
    
    
    @immaculateinfat thanks for organizing, great idea    
    
    
    @barnapkins I bought the domain, but @LilScrappy11 is making soup for tonight, thats all you need to know    
    
    
    @paulbz awesome: digging Tapestry, excited to see where it goes visually, once the @barnapkins start making stop motion + animations    
    
    
    Agencies: You Need Makeable Ideas Before You Can Make Things by @RickLiebling http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1681876  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    The Boston Globe called Nate Silver the Kurt Cobain of Statistics http://goo.gl/Lr54y  Who is the Courtney Love of stats?    
    
    
    @JasonHirschhorn check http://www.radiolily.com/  it's my new go to source for reggae...    
    
    
    @accarrino sorry to hear your family got hit by #Sandy , hope things are starting to look up    
    
    
    The @f_letter 's sharpie marketing at work http://instagr.am/p/RyVy_9KDft/     
    
    
    @raleighfelton get live...    
    
    
    @barnapkins great man date this morning, just saw your friend @paulbz quoted today.. http://goo.gl/mjtzA   cranking out some cool apps    
    
    
    If I had to pick a highlight for this historic political week  it would be picking up the Linkedin endorsement of @dinov    
    
    
    Duke University creates perfect invisibility cloak http://www.extremetech.com/extreme/140106-duke-university-creates-perfect-centimeter-scale-invisibility-cloak … via @christuff    
    
    
    KInd of ironic that Microsoft is sponsoring a new TV show based on 90's nostalgia http://shar.es/G6Uv8     
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor ha ha... I hope they have product placements for Windows 95    
    
    
    Have you ever wished the minds at MIT would create an infinite version of R Kelly's Ignition Remix? http://labs.echonest.com/Uploader/index.html?trid=TRWYIXL11C8A419FDE …    
    
    
    Michigan is going to allow betting on past horse races? Think I'll just bet on the winner http://www.mlive.com/newsflash/index.ssf/story/legislation-aims-to-boost-horse-racing-industry/f490c382d9004af8817da71eb2387f1b …    
    
    
    Thankful that @therosebuds properly honored Sade's Love Deluxe 20th Anniversary.. shouts to @Mr_JYU http://therosebuds.bandcamp.com/album/love-deluxe-the-rosebuds-perform-sade …    
    
    
    @steveESPOpowers Is ICY Signs opening a Detroit office? http://dj-mooney.tumblr.com/image/35861097933 …    
    
    
    @steveESPOpowers 2100 Michigan Ave, neighboring a BBQ joint, Bar and an Irish Social Club, I'll reduce my commission #KeepingItRealestate    
    
    
    The girl from Tennessee wearing sunglasses at night wants to hear the Pitbull Hotel Song because she's staying at the Marriot    
    
    
    Embarrassing white folk date spotted , your girl knows the lyrics to Biggie Juicy but you don't    
    
    
    Only in the south: Monster Donk in the parade http://instagr.am/p/SI_FnfqDZ-/     
    
    
    85 year old Olive Garden reviewer Marilyn Hagerty thinks NY Times Was Too Hard on Guy Fieri by @rupalparekh
http://adage.com/u/K9XS6b     
    
    
    Important Lessons you can learn from John Clayton's professional pony tail by @dougkleeman http://bit.ly/UIKe6W     
    
    
    @beneckerson so you can identify with that $500k a year    
    
    
    New chapters on TV this Friday, but R. Kelly's Trapped in the Closet is also coming to Broadway? -  http://gawker.com/5962038/no-but-seriously-this-is-awesome-r-kellys-fantastically-absurd-trapped-in-the-closet-is-coming-to-broadway …    
    
    
    @holaolah so excited for the new chapters, I love that low budget Theater groups have been performing this for years https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TpPHnJjzFqg …    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U it should be a blast, @LilScrappy11 is more excited than you can imagine..    
    
    
    Great write up by @erictullis on the new @therosebuds Sade cover project http://is.gd/YgICQd   cc @Mr_JYU    
    
    
    @benblackmer great seeing you last week, happy to see the TNW write up today.. Happy Thanksgiving    
    
    
    @will_yum oh my, the pre-party has started    
    
    
    @will_yum we drive up tonight, we can't wait to see you on Saturday    
    
    
    Cine: The hound house http://cinemagr.am/show/52416148  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    100th annual Cheshire Foxhunt aka the whitest event i've ever been to http://instagr.am/p/SVuJ10KDf-/     
    
    
    @Scaroline27 old school hunting hounds, their hound house is nicer than my home    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor I never understand the free wifi promotion, everyone trying it at once always chokes the bandwidth    
    
    
    Nothing says ladies night like the sexy sounds of a keytar http://instagr.am/p/SYnGX3KDYa/     
    
    
    Philly girls at my cousins wedding... Shot Luge http://instagr.am/p/SbyeVgKDdL/     
    
    
    @holaolah thanks for the warning, wifey and I grabbed a slice at the Fishtown Pizza Museum today, neighborhood is looking great    
    
    
    @cb3 most beautiful place in the world, have you met @holaolah at work? I'll be back soon we'll all have to grab lunch    
    
    
    Seaside Ghost Town: The Abandoned Millionaire Resort http://www.messynessychic.com/2012/07/19/seaside-ghost-town-the-abandoned-millionaires-resort/ … via @taraduveanu    
    
    
    I hereby declare that copyright is attached to all of my Tweets. Twitter gets the first 140 characters, Facebook can have the rest    
    
    
    @benblackmer I have no idea, urban legend.. that you can post something and some how retain rights I was just making fun of them    
    
    
    And brought back Mutombo? How a team of game developers help Old Spice save the world every five days http://sbn.to/ThEKjL     
    
    
    @Buie was just there, @benblackmer 's company is in that building..
we still need to grab lunch Jamil....    
    
    
    @Buie Friday should work great, give me a shout and we can meet up in downtown Durham    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive no surprise, cargo short post coming soon http://wtfismikewearing.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    @djforge wow thanks for the #throwbackthursday    
    
    
    @djforge for sure, can't believe that was close to 10 years ago    
    
    
    Saturday Night @FiveStarRes Disco Circus http://dj-mooney.tumblr.com/post/36879042303/in-recognition-of-world-aids-day-saturday-dec-1st … w/  @Mr_JYU @djmooney & Flowjo Family Circus #WAD12    
    
    
    @methodshop so sad I remember paying a ton of money for one of those #400mhzG4rip    
    
    
    @Mr_JYU were going to try, I'm more scarred to set it up, that ceiling is 40ft up, the trapeze hangs lower lol....    
    
    
    @littlejlovesu @Gejashiku Is put some wings on it the new motto at the auto shop? I better see y'all at the disco tomorrow...    
    
    
    The trapeze is ready, are you?  #discocircus http://instagr.am/p/StInZ3KDXg/     
    
    
    Tom Brady is such a beef cake http://instagr.am/p/StMsPhqDci/     
    
    
    #discocircus Tonight @FiveStarRes @Mr_JYU @DJMooney for #WAD2012 - http://twitpic.com/bhvt6i     
    
    
    @ischafer is he on your fantasy team?    
    
    
    @ischafer I have Dangelo so i know how frustrating that can be, especially when the other guy gets the td..    
    
    
    I love every thing about this http://skrillexquest.com/  game but Skrillex's music via @mzmelissa    
    
    
    @mzmelissa The kids love him, but Skrillex and Dubstep is the only music I'll forbid my child from listening to...    
    
    
    Nothing says Happy Holidays quite like DMX singing Rudolph the Red Nosed Reindeer http://www.egotripland.com/dmx-rudolph-the-red-nosed-reindeer-video/ …    
    
    
    @ischafer but suicide doors and Abe Lincoln are so hot right now    
    
    
    @NasherGirl I'm so jealous, have fun at Basel    
    
    
    @djforge my last 2 places were downwind from Kripsy Kreme, and Chargrill... no its Mami Nora's #fatboyproblems    
    
    
    The new Mashable design is further proof that no one really reads Mashable    
    
    
    @zipplockbag agreed... I'm kind of missing old blog formats that let me preview some text    
    
    
    Why did Newscorps "The Daily" fail? Not to many mentions of the obvious, Ipad comes with a free web browser..    
    
    
    UGG the maker of your favorite boots, now makes headphones  http://shop.nordstrom.com/s/ugg-australia-headphone-earmuffs-nordstrom-exclusive/3209189 …    
    
    
    happy ether day everyone rt “@fakeshoredrive: http://www.urbandictionary.com/define.php?term=ether%20day …”    
    
    
    Historic Dix Vote Paves way for Raleigh’s Central Park http://ra.ly/Vxf70j 
 via @NewRaleigh    
    
    
    @richiecruz might I suggest http://www.radiolily.com/     
    
    
    Can we do a kickstarter to buy the billboard next to this one? I want an official response from @steveESPOpowers http://www.philly.com/philly/blogs/inq-blinq/Saying-something-nice-about-Camden.html …    
    
    
    @mzmelissa did you check out http://bluekai.com/registry/  to see your cookies profile? I'm surprised Qwest banners aren't still following me    
    
    
    @mzmelissa I love chrome too much right now, but I can see why http://duckduckgo.com/  and IE's new "no track" are appealing, damn advertisers    
    
    
    @voiceOrezin wow probably old news to you, but this would be big http://allthingsd.com/20121206/facebook-in-talks-to-buy-microsofts-atlas-ad-platform/?mod=atdtweet …    
    
    
    @Buie come on by Blogads HQ...    
    
    
    Save the Pastrami: There are only 150 Jewish Delis left in North America https://vimeo.com/53381762  via @barnapkins    
    
    
    @dviens best ideas can come at the worst times    
    
    
    @SWeissman @ThoughtCatalog my burrito ordering experience is forever changed...    
    
    
    @barnapkins bring us some breadsticks    
    
    
    @kenwheaton Barclays probably bought naming right just so they could the email addresses of crazy rich people who buy these type tickets    
    
    
    @haveboard that's just wrong... why didn't Twitter buy them    
    
    
    @haveboard yeah it's surprising how many of the dominant social platforms actually lose money, I always need a reminder.    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U I can see playing air drums for that one, but air guitar?    
    
    
    Now playing at Mami Nora's Peruvian Chicken El General "pum pum" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NNWRCWkRr84 …    
    
    
    @beneckerson what are you cooking up?#jinglebots    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mikeppc99 Jackson Heights own "Randy Watson'    
    
    
    @AarthiD its been a crazy day on gmail, I use the biz version too, stay strong    
    
    
    @AarthiD ha ha, its amazing how solid Gmail has been for years, first buggy day I can remember... how is everything at Stack Exchange?    
    
    
    @AarthiD its been a great year, Blogads just had its 10th anniversary, we're like internet dinosaurs    
    
    
    AOL wants to remind you how great blinged out rap videos and AOL were in the 90's  http://adage.com/u/hdnwta   by @delrey via @natives    
    
    
    @erictullis @Blogads Hey eric, that tool is made for publishers or bloggers to install, so readers can easily quote you in a tweet..    
    
    
    @erictullis @Blogads Its installed on http://web.blogads.com/blog  just highlight some text on our blog... let me know what u think as a writer    
    
    
    @erictullis let us know if any of the pubs you write for are interested, its free, + love to make it easier for readers to share your work    
    
    
    My audience: Politically apathetic cupcake bakers. Find yours at http://targetron5000.com/?p=75&d=109&a=61 …    
    
    
    @saracobaugh awesome job...    
    
    
    @barnapkins seriously?    
    
    
    @barnapkins amazing, are we having a party to watch it live?    
    
    
    Charging $30 for a USB cord is why Radio Shack is still in business, but it's also why they will be going out of business    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller thx, my amazon prime has me covered on the basics, that looks good for my advanced geekery    
    
    
    Who wants to open a Chuck E Cheese for adults with this guy http://vimeo.com/52766487     
    
    
    @barnapkins smart move, I need to remember that    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor the bull jumping one had me wishing the bull didn't miss    
    
    
    @oneduran great seeing you tonight, let's link up soon    
    
    
    This is what happens when u check your chinchilla with the Dj http://instagr.am/p/TSbgw3KDYN/     
    
    
    @mtsthelen how about some color http://design-seeds.com/     
    
    
    Will the next generation of kids believe in Santa and his reindeer or Amazon Prime and his UPS men?    
    
    
    Did anybody give out blank Mayan Calendars for holiday swag this year #missedopportunity    
    
    
    @saracobaugh agreed, once got yelled at for calling Harris Teeter's to ask if they had Girls Scouts peddling cookies #onlycookiesplease    
    
    
    If you thought Trindad James was Golden, you have to see the Martin Lawrence "Jerome" edit http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mb9sVTvS5gw … via @richiecruz    
    
    
    Might not be the end of the world, but maybe Raleigh? @newraleigh http://www.wral.com/80s-themed-bar-downtown-raleigh/11893669/ … via @LuxePosh    
    
    
    @MeganDWade ha ha "lil chldrens"... merry 1st x-mad to baby wade, hope the brown truck brings much joy    
    
    
    @powershour I think Chris London is opening a 90's bar, where only girls born in the 90's are allowed entrance    
    
    
    I want to thank you all for you automated holiday email greetings today    
    
    
    The Beef Obradys Bowl is a real college football game    
    
    
    @ghoulianna gold is ok, but the puppy just wins it    
    
    
    @hueypriest give me a shout if you're around Raleigh    
    
    
    @will_yum @lilscrappy11 amazing... Thank you for the Mayfair postcard    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic congrats    
    
    
    @barnapkins lunch? http://youtu.be/FOjAb81ffgE     
    
    
    Tonights view, come see me at Busy Bee http://instagr.am/p/T7K704qDTS/     
    
    
    Unclear if NC Possum Drop used live marsupial -  http://www.newsobserver.com/2013/01/02/2579192/unclear-whether-live-marsupial.html …    
    
    
    Put inventive souls in an isolated place, give them resources, and leave them alone - @Grant27 http://www.psfk.com/2013/01/grant-mccraken-popular-innovation.html … via @psfk    
    
    
    @DevinPK10 @methodsavvy congrats or condolences? you seem to be further away form Chicken & Waffles...    
    
    
    @DelRey ha ha I like @kirbywinfield 's solution best, but also https://www.shoeboxed.com/     
    
    
    @tweetenhagen @Mr_JYU @camraleigh starting with a Swedish Death Metal power hour?    
    
    
    Love that @NixxedEW and @Mr_JYU got the Dj booth knocking louder than a packed @NeptunesParlour dance floor    
    
    
    Cassidy and Chingy back 2 back where r they now selections by @SPCLGST    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands happy new year Dre    
    
    
    Cine: Worst Dancers Of the night http://cinemagr.am/show/93901840  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    @thegasHole nothing says classy like amputee jokes    
    
    
    Happy to see I'm not alone in my battle with Time Warner Cable http://www.reddit.com/r/triangle/comments/164f62/are_you_sick_of_time_warner_nc_lessons_learned/ …    
    
    
    @LuxePosh I was looking forward to cutting the cord, but couldn't say no once they sweetened the deal    
    
    
    @saracobaugh hoping to ween myself off tv eventually and get a roku or something, so hard to quit    
    
    
    The Voice of The Ravens is Baltimore Sportscaster Gerry Sandusky #yourname gotruined http://www.wbaltv.com/WBAL-TV-Sports-Director-Voice-of-the-Ravens/-/9380084/10412934/-/jfnphrz/-/index.html …    
    
    
    @BobKnorpp are you back in NC?    
    
    
    Just got my first suspicious friend request since watching a bunch of Catfish episodes over the weekend    
    
    
    @BobKnorpp impressed that you squeezed in some Bo Time    
    
    
    @BobKnorpp ha ha Wawa is my first stop on I95 trips... soft pretzel and a hoagie everytime    
    
    
    @matt_hisamoto great seeing you, I'll shot you a text when I meet up with Will, maybe we'll meet some fake online girls    
    
    
    Mind Blown: homemade soap opera edit video for the go-go version of Ashley Simpson's Pieces Of Me thing,http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RkPKKmiHFm4 …    
    
    
    @ghoulianna cup o amazing    
    
    
    Where's the beef? @barnapkins birthday at The Angus Barn tonight, followed by tomorrow's 50% sale at Omaha Steaks    
    
    
    @barnapkins we'll have to ask the waiter for his finest bottle of Lipitor    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic his eddie munster look is killing it    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor I was shocked to go buy headphones after the Beats by Dre takeover, it was so hard to find normal $100 headphones    
    
    
    People I grew up with are asking if Jodie Foster is gay on Facebook    
    
    
    @LuxePosh somebody needs to do an edit or remix pronto.... I thought that intro was a joke.....    
    
    
    @benkunz great article.... nice to see a holistic media perspective for once    
    
    
    @mzmelissa smart move by that bank, have you ever watched the mandatory videos the writers have to do for that site?    
    
    
    @mzmelissa no its just clear that the editor makes them post a video for every story, saddest videos ever, almost a guilty pleasure    
    
    
    @C2Next So true, He's been calling out Lance for a long time, hope he gets the first apology    
    
    
    Twitter also announces their new search partnership http://bit.ly/sqxhVv     
    
    
    If you enjoyed The Atlantic's Scientology Sponsored Post, than this is a must read via @steketee http://www.theonion.com/articles/sponsored-the-taliban-is-a-vibrant-and-thriving-po,30910/ …    
    
    
    Can we give it up for Nerlens Noel's High Top Fade    
    
    
    @Scaroline27 I hardly recognize them..... with out their clothes on backwards    
    
    
    "The issue is the style of writing. The MTA wants nothing that looks like graffiti."” http://qote.me/1dxX0D     
    
    
    “IBM, which calls steampunk a “New Retail Trend in the Making.”” http://qote.me/PFzPEs     
    
    
    @katiebrauer I've been having fun prepping our Gif Panel.. I like that we can be so familiar with a concept but not know how to pronounce it    
    
    
    @katiebrauer agreed, pronounce it like the great gift that it is    
    
    
    “unlock your mind-reading mojo" in 15 minutes or less @sxsw with @hc 's neuroscience mind-reading magic http://qote.me/nINLrH     
    
    
    @bmorrissey I've all ready seen the hash tag #SuperBaugh    
    
    
    Quan    
    
    
    Who else is pumped for the 2nd annual NFL honors?    
    
    
    “Spotted: Sergey Brin wearing Google Glass specs as he blends in on NYC subway” http://qote.me/1fjlw4     
    
    
    @gputman I suddenly feel old..    
    
    
    “What did Te’o know...? How were so many top journalists caught so flat-footed?” How a College broke the story http://qote.me/2z4lIC     
    
    
    @barnapkins I'm so stoked for lunch now bro    
    
    
    Some guy trademarked the Harbaugh super bowl last year? http://m.espn.go.com/nfl/story?storyId=8873809&i=TWT&w=1cjo5 …    
    
    
    @funkmastabaker and I had to watch a Microsoft Surface pre-roll in order to view the clip    
    
    
    @megancarriker great idea, they had me at Donut    
    
    
    Lesson from Vine: Long videos suck, most of the Vine videos just suck less    
    
    
    What storm? We still going http://instagr.am/p/U76mTVqDfb/     
    
    
    Yo I need some of them DJ Puffs yo http://instagr.am/p/U90pcqqDbg/     
    
    
    ““Disruption is overrated,” ... “If you tell good stories, the platforms are sort of beside the point. -Matt Stone    
    
    
    “There will be exceptions, but the islands won’t prosper like the oceans.” http://qote.me/ScRSey     
    
    
    @HerHeels front runner for best campaign of the year... genius    
    
    
    @davesch7 crazy.. todays market is more concerned with expectations than performance... Apple's stock just tanked, Yahoo is up?    
    
    
    @paulbz thanks for sharing that Betaworks 2012 report... long read, but so insightful    
    
    
    @DevinPK10 wow    
    
    
    Starwood Hotels offer lets you pay your birth year for your rate, born in 1970=$70 How long until a young law student files suit?    
    
    
    @davesch7 ha ha awesome.... sounds about right to me....    
    
    
    VW is Fakin the Jamiacan? Is this use of Patois a Faux Pas? via @cb3 http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/why-cries-racism-wont-sink-volkswagens-super-bowl-ad-146866 …    
    
    
    @LilScrappy11 Smize http://bit.ly/WNsYzQ  via @barnapkins    
    
    
    @rossgrady Hi Ross, I'm working on a project to help bloggers with event calendars, love to chat about your experience with Trianglerock    
    
    
    @rossgrady thank you    
    
    
    @RyanNewYork I think these guys are your best shot... http://unionmetrics.com/     
    
    
    @RyanNewYork my pleasure, we made some free and interesting twitter tools  http://twiangulate.com/search/  and http://www.distillry.net/ 
check them out    
    
    
    @theRab really digging the new IBM Tumblr    
    
    
    In NY for #SMWNY come check out The Gif That Keeps on Giving  #smwgif http://socialmediaweek.org/newyork/events/?id=53538#.UQrUbZmpuPI.twitter …    
    
    
    @barnapkins I knew I stole the name, but had no idea form where or how close to home it came from... lolz    
    
    
    @steketee thanks for sharing    
    
    
    @steketee Office Hours at Fanellis sounds great, I'll give you a shout    
    
    
    @davidburn @DanGoldgeier looking forward to an Ad Pulp story on agencies billing by the word    
    
    
    @aburtch love the @davidlbaldwin quote in there...    
    
    
    I'm going to start ordering my Mocochino with 3 pumps of Dear Antler Spray    
    
    
    This Harden & Humphries entourage spot is so great... http://youtu.be/MkvByvL1YBc     
    
    
    Ed Koch on "Quality of life" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UZG31AbARSc …    
    
    
    ‘Miller, a tall, beefy guy of 32’ http://qote.me/3bLjdV  Forgets to mention @imjustinmiller is single ladies..    
    
    
    @Buie did you move up there?    
    
    
    @Buie congrats, was born there, now I have a reason to get back and visit.... check out http://deeplocal.com/  if you haven't all ready    
    
    
    @aburtch @adfreak gyrating isn't a trade off    
    
    
    If you have Oprah voice over a spot, everybody better win a jeep at the end of it    
    
    
    Save the Post Office http://wh.gov/yXzj     
    
    
    Tech-Savvy Baruch College Students Get in trouble for automating their course registration? http://nyti.ms/XT0MKf     
    
    
    New Hold Music for Yahoo 'one-hit wonder Snow, the Canadian rapper known for "Informer," to perform the song’ http://qote.me/vkWNhD     
    
    
    Just when you think life is good, @immaculateinfat shows you another level, its called "Sponsored Bourbon Tour" 
http://gizmodo.com/5969028/heres-how-you-turn-san-francisco-into-a-bourbon+fueled-gorgefest/gallery/ …    
    
    
    ‘Mr. Armstrong wanted to incorporate dancers and have the spot take cues from the 1990s rap hit "Mo Money Mo Problems’ http://qote.me/gjbb7A     
    
    
    N.J. judge orders local blogger to defend journalist status  http://shar.es/YH9b8  via @DanielHonigman    
    
    
    but isn't Facebook the catfish pond? ‘Let’s Date uses Facebook Connect to ... avoid having a Manti Te’o moment’ http://qote.me/duooLn     
    
    
    @JamieMS I'll send you the client job # for Reddit    
    
    
    Wonderful Together: @McKinney 's Beercade | Digiday http://www.digiday.com/agencies/wonderful-together-mckinneys-beercade/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    I guess the trailer is 11'5" http://instagr.am/p/VeU_NXKDWs/     
    
    
    @Mr_JYU downtown Durham, have you seen this before? http://11foot8.com/     
    
    
    @Scaroline27 @Mr_JYU thats the greatest hits mixtape I was looking for    
    
    
    @barnapkins these are the dvr's I couldn't remember last night https://www.aereo.com/  and http://www.boxee.tv/  which will come to NC 1st?    
    
    
    @bfuj919 I suggested 200 lbs of butter    
    
    
    The Gif that keeps Giving http://blogads.me/11POl50  Feb 21st #smwnyc with @SWeissman @MisterGIF @mpostal @kevinburg @amandalynferri #smwgif    
    
    
    Artisanal Social Media Marketing: great advice from @christuff http://www.adweek.com/news/technology/artisanal-social-media-marketing-147173 …    
    
    
    Pullquotes: Save time picking passages http://www.examiner.com/article/pullquotes-pass-time-picking-passages … via    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U charge me more, but don't change my favorite Bourbon...    
    
    
    Who else thinks Makers Mark should use the tears of grown men to water down its bourbon?    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands oh man,  have fun tonight    
    
    
    @RickLiebling Hey Rick we're doing a SMW panel on Gifs in advertising this year
http://web.blogads.com/social-media-week-new-york-2013#thegifthatkeepsongiving … join us if you can..    
    
    
    @eyevariety have you seen the new N&O design?    
    
    
    @RickLiebling great, look forward to seeing you and catching up...    
    
    
    @eyevariety I like the cleaner direction they went, but it feels like they started minimal and had to keep adding mandatory sections...    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor wow meet the new focus groups..    
    
    
    @dancharnas ad agency @WiedenKennedy has some actual Harlem Shake in theirs.. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cd8Fmh7nIrQ …    
    
    
    @DevinPK10 I might know the perfect person for this... @NixxedEW give my man Devin a shout...    
    
    
    Those who forget the Unitard are doomed to repeat it: ‘Adidas has unveiled a new type of shirt for NBA ’ http://qote.me/rYYRKY     
    
    
    Animated Gifs In Ads? http://blogads.me/11POl50   Feb 21st #smwnycwith @SWeissman @MisterGIF @mpostal @kevinburg @amandalynferri #smwgif    
    
    
    @theRab one of my favorite artist painter their stairs, skip the elevator ha ha http://joshualinergallery.com/gallery/newsarticle/stephen_powers_flights_of_genius_murals_at_ogilvy_and_mather …    
    
    
    Lets not forget the guy who used to have the #1 Video for "Harlem Shake" before this recent meme https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bDk_D-lUFcI …    
    
    
    @kicksNcoffee thats the crazy part, no one really does the Harlem shake in these viral videos, but this one http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cd8Fmh7nIrQ …    
    
    
    Check NYT's @AlexwilliamsNYC  piece on Gifs  http://nyti.ms/15dgkjv  and learn more next week w/ @MisterGIF http://blogads.me/11POl50     
    
    
    I can't wait until someone makes a music video from Russian Dashboard camera footage.    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller Dash Cam Greatest Hits http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hlxHPJAONpE …    
    
    
    @mikeppc99 what was the over under on ne-yo songs    
    
    
    Conspiracy Theory: @johnsteinberg thinks the Banner industry is the biggest critic of native ads #smwnative    
    
    
    @oohlarock I want to come check out your panel, but I forgot to register :(    
    
    
    Tomorrow at 12:30 @digiday 's @SWeissman talks with the best in Animated Gifs @MisterGIF @kevinburg http://blogads.me/11POl50  #smwgif    
    
    
    @oohlarock great see you soon..    
    
    
    @ableparris I'm in town, I actually organized a panel on Gifs in Advertising, you should come  http://blogads.me/11POl50     
    
    
    @rosiesiman great job on the content marketing presentation yesterday, is the deck posted online?    
    
    
    @bsokic did you eat yet? my phone died had to hit the hotel for a charge...    
    
    
    @bsokic sounds great, where is your session, I can head that way after I charge..    
    
    
    @beatrizv520 I forgot to give you a shout, we've got some great panels tomorrow, and Suxorz tomorrow night http://web.blogads.com/social-media-week-new-york-2013 … hollar    
    
    
    @oohlarock great job tonight, look forward to seeing you tomorrow, I'll dm you a vip code...    
    
    
    @sandershearne Congrats on your Yankee Son.    
    
    
    Instagram is like look at this Hummus, Vine is like watch me dunk my face in hummus @mopostal #smwgif    
    
    
    Wikipedia is volunteer  run, you will get a reply, but might be a 1 month delay #smwwiki    
    
    
    Great question Is it ok for Jimmy Wales to edit his own wiki, but not a brand? #smwwiki    
    
    
    There was a debate early in Ke$ha's career if she was notable enough for a Wikipedia entry #smwwiki cc @kenissomewhere    
    
    
    catify yourself by @dberkowitz  may have just won #suxorz pic.twitter.com/dWLpua1pnm    
    
    
    @MisterGIF @sweissman @mpostal @kevinburg @amandalynferri don't think so, did anyone live gif the panel? Thanks everybody    
    
    
    @SPhillyRaleigh Just rolled up for the first time and you guys were closed before 8?    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor I remember reading that she went crazy on Mark Ronson while he was dj'n back in the day, your instincts are probably right    
    
    
    @will_yum she can still kill it    
    
    
    Wow.. Searching For Sugarman ran out of money so they finished filming it with an iPhone app    
    
    
    @lizmorgan5 great meeting you at SMW in NYC, hope to see you around Raleigh    
    
    
    Hey Designers @methodsavvy is hiring http://linkd.in/ZuZyby  via @DevinPK10    
    
    
    @saracobaugh it's so punderful I love it    
    
    
    @AarthiD it was great seeing you at SMW, if we don't speak before, safe travels on your trip to India    
    
    
    @AarthiD it was as good as the worst social media can be :) good times, I'll give you a shout next time I'm up in NYC    
    
    
    Tweens Now Hoarding Tumblr URLs for 'Status and Power' http://betabeat.com/?p=80426  via @betabeat & @rickliebling    
    
    
    @aburtch good seeing you at RDU, I'll give you a shout for BBQ when thing settle down    
    
    
    ‘Coach K promptly broke wind upon getting in my car’ http://qote.me/vSHN9i     
    
    
    @hueypriest @teddyfaley I'm loving the pixelated mobb deep artwork as well    
    
    
    only blogads in the theater http://instagr.am/p/WSjgyoKDQH/     
    
    
    @nettaP Side Effects... Rooney Mara is my new hero    
    
    
    Love reliving this party I dj'd ‘not too long after.. Professor Griff had freaked his way through a Soul Train line’ http://qote.me/Vaninn     
    
    
    Forget Vine.... Emojis with sound are the next big thing.. http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/readiymate/telesound-the-sound-messenger?ref=category …    
    
    
    Wow... Giorgio Moroder Dj set? http://www.factmag.com/2013/03/04/rbma-new-york-announces/ …    
    
    
    ‘Local newspapers that deliver reliable information to
“tightly-bound communities” will stay viable’ -Warren Buffett http://qote.me/mNPX66     
    
    
    How do you top a bourbon tour? whole hog experience @immaculateinfat & @PaigeDenim #SmokeAndDenim @ForeignDomestic http://bit.ly/XmKkH3     
    
    
    ‘Publishers are starting to realise that the game is now “out there” and not inside their walled gardens.’ - @HC http://qote.me/DVoAJU     
    
    
    Japanese encourage naps on the job ‘It's called inemuri, which literally means "to be asleep while present"’ http://qote.me/73UWCZ     
    
    
    @SWeissman living in the south, I can attest to the fact that plenty of americans live in overalls all year, dudes even rock them shirtless    
    
    
    @marcman I won't watch that game... go pack, but glad to know I might see you in ATX    
    
    
    @kamerondotcom @ITSJEREMYSCOTT @lovehateinc congrats, you guys crushed it with the new site... looks amazing    
    
    
    @dberkowitz #yes    
    
    
    Shout outs to @fakeshoredrive for making this real http://vine.co/v/bHtzUMpanJI     
    
    
    @SWeissman but you would have to give up good pizza and bagels... tough trade off    
    
    
    @chrbutler make a video, and turn up the frame rate so it looks like the fastest loading site ever:)    
    
    
    White House Petition change the national anthem to R. Kelly's Ignition Remix http://wh.gov/f8vi     
    
    
    @sandershearne please use the term "Al Rokered" the D train instead    
    
    
    @Miss_MEW_  not everyone should relax    
    
    
    @donsteele I'm sad to miss LaQuintas Texas shaped waffle maker this year... Air BnB only provided a panini press    
    
    
    @oohlarock busted... Secret wrestling fan    
    
    
    Like a backwards Tom Shoes?: Harry Potter Chocolate uses child slavery @andrewslack and fans fighting for change #frenemy #SXSW    
    
    
    Never react to anything right away. 99% of the time fan communities self correct - @mikemonello #frenemy #SXSW #sxswsweet    
    
    
    Wordpress 1st 5 users were friends of @photomatt, artist musicians, nob tech users, helped ensure it was easy to use #sxswwp #SXSW    
    
    
    Haters gonna hate creators gonna create - @photomatt #sxswwp #sxswsweet    
    
    
    @theRab Blogads BBQ at Stubbs 7pm, I'll put you on the list    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor not sure if I emailed you, we're doing the Blogads BBQ again this year at Stubbs 7pm, come through    
    
    
    @jjones are you still in Austin?  Looks like a great party... Sad to have missed you and the MCK Alumni..    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor yeah i put you on but just send me some names, I'll dm you my # too    
    
    
    @mlelynn sorry sold it. Stella Mooney college fund    
    
    
    90% of content on Tumblr are reblogs #growtumblr #SXSW #sxswsweet    
    
    
    @theRab I'm up here too, have to say hello after    
    
    
    Awesome to hear @davidkarp mention @kevinburg and @_frommetoyou 's cinemagraphs as his favorite work #growtumblr #sxswi    
    
    
    @Cream_Wallabees great meeting you at Stubbs...glad to see @DrePowersBrands is a friend too.. Dre give a shout if you're around Austin    
    
    
    Packed house for @lisastone #brandblog with @nckfbr #sxswsweet #SXSW    
    
    
    Don't invite m#brandblog    
    
    
    Don't invite me over for drinks if its really a tupperware party, disclose it, same with ads  #brandblog #SXSW    
    
    
    @nckfbr tweeting the same thing as you 16 sec too late    
    
    
    @yolunia @nckfbr Great meeting you. Borscht lunch next time    
    
    
    Great seeing you @strle & @arilevine :)    
    
    
    My American Airlines Bronze Status assures me a window seat any time http://instagr.am/p/WxNsZqqDcd/     
    
    
    @Cream_Wallabees I'm out too... Great meeting... Should be in Atlanta soon, I'll give u a shout    
    
    
    that's my dog, no really it is “@barnapkins: Leica can't catch treats because she closes her eyes   . http://instagr.am/p/WxW2vzG2tW/ ”    
    
    
    ‘"When you have a crayon-carver in your midst, you use every opportunity to harness that creativity,"’ http://qote.me/w9QQi1     
    
    
    @DarrenSpedale great meeting you in Austin, best of luck with Family By Design, give a shout if you ever come back to NC    
    
    
    @eyevariety have you tried join.me ?    
    
    
    @eyevariety haven't used the audio or pro features... just like the ease of use and quickness... Goto more robust but features I never need    
    
    
    You know @bigdaddykane brings the heat "Night & Day" https://soundcloud.com/macmediapromo/marco-polo-f-big-daddy-kane … via @phontigallo    
    
    
    @KristinTaber great meeting you in texas.. hopefully I'll see you around Raleigh    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic congrats.. That's a grown ass man celebration right there #primo    
    
    
    We about to celebrate Trey Songz entire catalog    
    
    
    @hc hope you had a great b-day, thought u might enjoy this article http://science.nbcnews.com/_news/2013/02/28/17123686-two-rats-thousands-of-miles-apart-cooperate-telepathically-via-brain-implant?lite …    
    
    
    Congrats @hankleber For Four Notable Startups, This Was SXSW http://adweek.it/112xv3Y     
    
    
    NC Rat, communicates telepathically via brain implant with a rat thousands of miles away,  http://nbcnews.to/135iGCX   via @johnshankman    
    
    
    @Aerocles @caro @allnick you can keep the $$ even when you don't reach 100% of goal with Indiegogo right?    
    
    
    True Story: Armani designed movie sets on American Gigalow to match the clothes. #monochromemondays http://instagr.am/p/XAwcWEKDak/     
    
    
    Ridonkulous RT @DevinPK10 #durham style. pic.twitter.com/zeiKmptetf”    
    
    
    @arilevine @strle just letting y'all know, that this is officially melting the southern internets http://officialdollyparton.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    @arilevine my twitter stream was filled with so much genuine southern enthusiasm, they killed it with that page    
    
    
    @yolunia @nckfbr I'm glad we are officially a part of your nerd heard, high fives all around    
    
    
    @brittontaylor might I suggest this version http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=t5Rn7S2zLWE …    
    
    
    @barnapkins damn $$$$$ homey    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller proud of you son #USA    
    
    
    @donsteele kevin bacon or the pork product?    
    
    
    Alwaleed has the dwarves dive for $100 bills in bonfires, as the Business Insider story also alleged.’ http://qote.me/KLTABc     
    
    
    @funkmastabaker we donate.. to an organization that supports our mission of helping people to look and feel great???    
    
    
    @thegasHole blame the cool ranch dorito takeover    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor  cue your idea for the Jacob the Jeweler of wearable tech? or at least his etsy counterpart    
    
    
    Town changes name to for Dish Network sponsorship, citizen says “I wished Jack Daniel’s would have looked us up.”’ http://qote.me/motWEt     
    
    
    @barnapkins thinking of making a switch?    
    
    
    Congrats to @ImJustinMiller for not being called beefy by the New York Times http://www.nytimes.com/2013/03/24/fashion/weddings/start-ups-vie-for-a-slice-of-the-wedding-photo-cake.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    @barnapkins I too have been tempted... the Iphone 5 is not my next phone, but I'm willing to wait and see what comes next    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U a battle where everyone is a winner :)    
    
    
    ‘Release early, often and with rap music. This is Notorious R&D." —F.A.T. Lab’ http://qote.me/rP2cHL     
    
    
    ‘digital music is evolving in Africa... hits blow up strictly from bluetooth swapping’ http://qote.me/Eo9rlQ     
    
    
    @Pomennedy do you have any more camera prints for sale?    
    
    
    @Pomennedy that would be amazing.. thank you so much, let me know the best way to get the file    
    
    
    @Pomennedy thank you so much :)    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor are there networks now specializing in just mens fashion?    
    
    
    So this must be the real reason @blogads @katiebrauer is in LA for agency meetings http://adage.com/article/the-media-guy/agency-startup-hold-kitten-races-offices/240574/ … #KittenRaces    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor gotcha I saw details had a network but didn't know what it entailed.. makes sense, thx    
    
    
    Have they ever seen People of Walmart? Walmart considers using customers to deliver packages http://www.theverge.com/2013/3/28/4155914/walmart-considers-online-order-delivery-crowdsourcing …    
    
    
    @jessamason amazing... you should start using that as your resume    
    
    
    This party graduated high school in 2007??    
    
    
    @AarthiD so jealous.. Have fun    
    
    
    @raleighbarfly changing my name to Dj AARP    
    
    
    "money ain't a thing don't hate the player hate the game" -parked  in an old age home parking lot http://instagram.com/p/Xh_i6zqDaB/     
    
    
    Princeton Mom to All Female Students: ‘Find a Husband’ -  commenter advises them to just moisturize http://nymag.com/thecut/2013/03/princeton-mom-to-all-students-find-a-husband.html …    
    
    
    @Scaroline27 I would never joke about moisturizing... its just too important    
    
    
    @phontigallo Danny Ray is still working gigs, book him    
    
    
    Damn @dynamixif2 took it to the next level on @VH1 #MasteroftheMix    
    
    
    Texas Student, Tweets 'YOLO' During Test and Gets Suspended  http://huff.to/16jVrkk     
    
    
    @MisterGIF don't Yolo "The Man"    
    
    
    @C2Next I wonder what the NCAA is going to say about this, I hope they can keep it classy    
    
    
    @C2Next you're right, they do whats best for the brand and business    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic @karlistein @bexsilver Amazing... she's totally carbing out on some pizza in that video too    
    
    
    @SpaceBarZ Dennis Rodman is our only hope at a peaceful resolution.    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic @bexsilver @karlistjustice hmm are they really even friends, maybe they are just carb eating extras?    
    
    
    @aburtch just buy one here for $30 http://www.harborfreight.com/catalogsearch/result?q=Reciprocating+Saws … the tools are cheap quality, but usually less expensive than renting...    
    
    
    @aburtch stores in Ral & Dur , I've owned 2 of those saws..if the warranty is $5 or less its a good deal, they just swap it out instore    
    
    
    @DanGoldgeier some of the same tools that big publisher use are cheap to free... get Quantcast, and try Chartbeat for free    
    
    
    @barnapkins #highspeedbaptism    
    
    
    @nettaP r u downtown tonight?    
    
    
    @donsteele congrats!    
    
    
    Did Pitino think he was getting shot at? Don't piss off Vegas https://vine.co/v/bt7hwpuK9vT     
    
    
    The Winlevii twins have so much boring "real money" that they've decided to invest in Bitcoins instead http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2013/04/11/as-big-investors-emerge-bitcoin-gets-ready-for-its-close-up/ …    
    
    
    ‘the first ad blocker; a piece of plastic affixed to the bottom of monitors to obscure the dreaded advertising’ http://qote.me/apwQKJ     
    
    
    I'm ready for the Iverson follow up story: The Secret History of Kobe Bryant's Rap Career http://www.grantland.com/story/_/id/9161188/the-secret-history-kobe-bryant-failed-attempt-rap-career …    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor crazy read, I never knew he started off as a back pack rapper before that horrible song with Tyra    
    
    
    Your compliment means so much more when you're wearing an Affliction Tshirt    
    
    
    #WWRLDPic http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-7aLVgJdgfw0/UEZ8sxNxptI/AAAAAAAACqg/GSa5rW_iS00/s1600/lochte.jpg … Jeah    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands does Waffle House cite Drake lyrics on the regular? Amazing    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands im my experience, every trip to the Waffle House was started by a whole night full of bad ideas lolz...    
    
    
    @mikeso1omon wow so Chip Kelly pulled a Pete Carroll?    
    
    
    @angelinadarling before the kids adopted the term, we would call free brand stuff swag, that dude has swag swag    
    
    
    @ableparris @chrbutler agreed on the GF1, I bought my wife one , same size as a point an shoot, but many detachable lens options    
    
    
    Come on @steketee you need to head out to the Gold Coast of Long Island for the proper @GatsbyMovie  hisitorical viewing context    
    
    
    @arilevine upnorthtrips is such a treasure trove,  growing up, would you have believed there would be Ivy League hip-hop classes & archives?    
    
    
    @thegasHole I would have gone with the Charlotte Hairnets work, but I'm sure the design snobs will like this too    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic I like that you quote Bryan Adams and not Ryan Adams    
    
    
    http://Will.i.am . Wins Honorary Clio http://adweek.it/ZHylRR  I guess its for his work as an honorary creative director?    
    
    
    I've never been so excited by direct mail. Thank you Spanish Ham Catalog http://instagram.com/p/YbQDS0qDdM/     
    
    
    So.... Punky Brewster just raised $2.5 Million for her start up http://www.fastcompany.com/3008847/fast-feed/parenting-startup-moonfrye-raises-25-million …    
    
    
    Great to see Pepsico raise the stakes again on branded content. Congrats @richiecruz http://www.nytimes.com/2013/04/26/business/media/mountain-dew-to-introduce-a-sponsored-web-site.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    @richiecruz much respect, excited to see where you guys take it    
    
    
    Real talk... The I'm about to leave, play my song.. Is the worst request strategy ever... Just Leave    
    
    
    @bexsilver @karlistein DJ Rabbi Highkicks does not go gentile in to that good night    
    
    
    Late to bed and early to rise makes me???    
    
    
    Greetings from above http://instagram.com/p/Yqa4ekqDXm/     
    
    
    Hey Science Lets figure out stinky humans 1st RT @michaelmiraflor Why is this No Wash Shirt getting crazy press? It sounds disgusting.    
    
    
    @katiebrauer I love it when real news is better than The Onion    
    
    
    Congrats to @davidlbaldwin and everybody at Baldwin& on their continued success http://www.newsobserver.com/2013/04/29/2859051/baldwin-ad-agency-is-on-a-roll.html …    
    
    
    Wow thanks @DevinPK10 ...  @_FloridaMan is genius    
    
    
    @beneckerson @missjenny @girlnamedstevie @thegasHole Is it m eor is this idea Twerrible? http://www.weather.com/tv/tvshows/tornado-week/TWCintern …    
    
    
    @benblackmer just saw this in my timeline, thought you might enjoy it https://twitter.com/edhadley/status/329962897935572992 …    
    
    
    @PittsburghScene what is the best way to contact you for advertising?    
    
    
    7 uses of Pullquote, My 8th would be it is the fastest way for me to tweet a story form any site http://web.blogads.com/blog/2013/05/03/pullquote-styles/#axzz2SWQzsW8e …    
    
    
    @SWeissman what's the deal with the toothpick?    
    
    
    @SWeissman stick with the floss Jack    
    
    
    @zipplockbag that is amazing    
    
    
    @richiecruz I'm watching a different JR right now, but is that a Jose "ease" Parla show?    
    
    
    I have a hard time cheering for Felton, but that off the glass dish? Oh my    
    
    
    Little Italy is going crazy right now #Knicks    
    
    
    Is Battier French for Flopping?    
    
    
    How did one of Pacino's worst movies inspire multiple ad campaigns? http://adweek.it/15IEe9q     
    
    
    “Teens aren’t abandoning “social.” They’re just using the word correctly. ” by @cwthethird https://medium.com/understandings-epiphanies/aae8d5f880cc?utm_source=buffer&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Buffer&utm_content=buffer91703 …    
    
    
    @HaniHamma @barnapkins what a title    
    
    
    @hueypriest I met a Urologist with vanity car plates "C Me 2 Pee" those guys just have to have a great sense of humor    
    
    
    How many creative teams on cereal brands are thinking of ways they can get Ryan Gosling to film a spot?    
    
    
    White people are stomping like they are Lord of the Riverdance    
    
    
    @barnapkins damn lobster boy, I got an old pair of white Stan Smiths you can have to wear at the beach    
    
    
    @SpaceBarZ They are tearing our building apart, working form Raleigh today, how long r u in NC?    
    
    
    Do you need anymore reason for extra IRS scrutiny than naming your group after a historic protest against paying taxes?    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor yes, we use Parallax Scrolling to describe that type of design, even though technically not 100% correct use of that term    
    
    
    I just ran into Ghostface Killah at my Jerk Chicken spot, good start to the weekend    
    
    
    shump    
    
    
    Amazing!!! Meet San Diego's Worst Rapper, Real Estate Agent Rafael A. Perez http://adweek.it/12PgkU4     
    
    
    @donsteele We might need a count Action Bronson is obsessed with the word too http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rare_Chandeliers …    
    
    
    @ericsmithrocks are you going to be at BEA next week? Somebody just dropped off a blogger panel I'm on wednesday    
    
    
    @ericsmithrocks I just sent a note to the organizers suggesting you as a  panelist, are you available Wed at 3pm?    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic RG3 is on ESPN live right now, on the field throwing    
    
    
    This club has everything https://vine.co/v/bVZWO3pD2zD     
    
    
    @SWeissman can this be a Maury Povich style DNA test to reveal if @MisterGIF is the father?    
    
    
    #BEA & Bloggers join @MalleVallik @WellReadWife @ericsmithrocks @djmooney for Expanding The Reach of Your Blog http://goo.gl/wwDrv     
    
    
    @paulbz I met Mattias last week, smart guy + great product, amazed by their growth with fashion blogs    
    
    
    @paulbz left NY for the Shelley Family beach house, but I'll give you a shout next time up, love to hear more about Betaworks    
    
    
    Believe https://vine.co/v/bYY7wnqmX27     
    
    
    @patricec missed branding opportunity    
    
    
    If only they had built the Khaki Bar, it would have been the hottest pick up scene in town http://adage.com/u/1NSbeb     
    
    
    @arilevine congrats on the big Tumblr deal! Can you believe its been 20 years fro Wu-Tang?    
    
    
    @arilevine yes, the definition of old-school sure has changed on us ha ha    
    
    
    I would totally buy this bed so my kid could wake up in a New Bugatti http://dj-mooney.tumblr.com/post/52156195576/i-would-totally-buy-this-bed-so-my-kid-could-wake …    
    
    
    @HUBRaleigh @ImJustinMiller grand re-opening with food by http://www.chubbystacos.com/  and music by http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SwJM78j-5Rc … ?    
    
    
    @christuff don't hate the player, hate the game.. he doesn't even do weather anymore, he just wishes old people happy birthday    
    
    
    best bartender @BUSYBEECAFE and best Dj @spclgst and tater tots with yours truly    
    
    
    Just hanging @FiveStarRes , Pete Rock, Primo, and Rasheed Wallace at the bar    
    
    
    Ball Don't Lie    
    
    
    I always enjoy how @barnapkins videos can easily explain any topic or client http://vimeo.com/67857078     
    
    
    Great story in @digiday on how the Reddit team helped turn Crisis into Opportunity. Kudos @IamMikeCole @hueypriest http://www.digiday.com/brands/fathead-turns-crisis-into-opportunity/ …    
    
    
    I feel like I should be wearing Lederhosen at half mast. http://www.newsobserver.com/2013/06/09/2949500/renaldo-gillet-kuhler.html …    
    
    
    ‘Apple is about polish. Google is about scale. Microsoft is about, well, 30 years old’ http://qote.me/K7wMBc     
    
    
    "I want to hear myself Think Louder" -Robert Mooney 2013    
    
    
    SkyMall: "we’ve officially run out not only of things we need, but even of things we might plausibly desire" http://priceonomics.com/skymalls-skyfall/ …    
    
    
    @amandalynferri I hope he plays himself in it    
    
    
    @hc wall street loves Snapchat http://buff.ly/14Y7eDS     
    
    
    Nothing makes me feel older than seeing a Beastie Boys townhouse and thinking I really like that custom wallpaper http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/13/greathomesanddestinations/licensed-to-grill-mike-ds-brooklyn-town-house.html …    
    
    
    Rio's New Dance Craze: The Passinho Via @nprnews: http://n.pr/13dqf5C     
    
    
    The rise of Bro Media - 'We try to do as much as we can on BroBible to combat that by celebrating what ‘bro’ is’ http://qote.me/jFtXP6     
    
    
    @aburtch the judges office is on the 23rd floor, and he made Mike appear in person? hmmm might not be too impartial    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor also I would be more concerned about video killing Instagram than it killing Vine... What do you think?    
    
    
    LL & Ztrip https://vine.co/v/hBQJl0enjUh     
    
    
    @EventJoe @ztrip Thanks again for the hospitality. Great seeing you guys. The show is ridiculous, good luck with the rest of the tour.    
    
    
    wow @hillaryj did @paulaabdul have the cartoon Mc Scat Kat on the screen?    
    
    
    @DJMikeMorse great seeing you Sunday night, let's link up again soon    
    
    
    @hillaryj "opposites attract" was my jam. I can totally remember wearing bad cologne for the 1st time and dancing my ass off to Paula.    
    
    
    @steketee holly crap r u at the game ?    
    
    
    @hillaryj "I wanna sex u up" is kind of risqué for elementary school? You are so much cooler, Phil Collins was my 1st concert    
    
    
    @steketee did u ever know you're my hero?    
    
    
    @JamieMS in Spanish it's Señor Eva Longoria    
    
    
    @narrowd are you on Reddit? Peopl on the Triangle Subreddit have connected me with good people before    
    
    
    @barnapkins is it me or does @paulbz look like he is all ready signing autographs in the 2nd pic? 
http://www.theverge.com/2013/6/20/4447920/betaworks-a-startup-studio-doubles-down-on-creating-a-company-of …    
    
    
    Is Instagram now too big too fail? Am I the only one who hates the idea of adding video?    
    
    
    @ableparris I hated the idea of video Instagram until I saw this    
    
    
    @missjenny Its the only place people ask me if I want to supersize my beer    
    
    
    @johnshankman as added value just for HOV, maybe you autoplay audio for his song "Takeover" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2nfcKfVYCok …    
    
    
    The 5-Year-Old Boy Who Became an Instagram Style Icon | Fashion - Yahoo! Shine http://shine.yahoo.com/fashion/5-old-boy-8217-become-instagram-style-icon-155800006.html …    
    
    
    @marcman I used that years ago, and couldn't remember the name... awesome tool, thanks for reminding me    
    
    
    @HaniHamma I'm sure CJ's attitude helped more with that, you cant sit out all of your work outs    
    
    
    @donsteele maybe Mikhail Prokhorov is just lining up prospects for his 40 and over russian rec league team?    
    
    
    Dude rocking the scarf and Ed Hardy shirt in 80 degree heat, might just be ahead of a fashion come back    
    
    
    So summer stylish http://instagram.com/p/bIOwi8KDch/     
    
    
        
    
    
    "He respectfully requests six Cleveland Browns pall bearers so the Browns can let him down one last time" http://pllqt.it/1LcAH4     
    
    
    @barnapkins chain check ins only #BahamaBreezeBirthdays    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield Myrtle Beach = Redneck Riviera    
    
    
    I go to the beach for 1 weekend and the New York Public Library puts vinyl archive up for sale, http://bit.ly/11SfIz6 ”    
    
    
    Moving crowds? @Jpmartzel of @digitas on the similarities between dj'ing and strategic planning. English version here http://goo.gl/vtdqhv     
    
    
    I'm leaving all my money in the Bronx http://instagram.com/p/dIbH65qDXE/     
    
    
    @aburtch @michaelmiraflor NFC & QR = firts world pipe dreams, while Bluetooth File transfer is 3rd world reality http://motherboard.vice.com/blog/inside-the-cell-phone-file-sharing-networks-of-western-africa-q-a …    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor @aburtch its crazy when our hip-hop dj promo mixtape backgrounds better prepares us to understand the ad & tech world    
    
    
    Great people and an Amazing home! Check out @joanhiller @mattlemay 's BK digs via @AptTherapy http://goo.gl/E00wJF     
    
    
    @SWeissman Great read, did you know his lessons would be applicable to readers, or did you just know that you had to meet the Cronut King?    
    
    
    @SWeissman succeeded on all levels, fresh angle and most interesting piece I've seen on it, had no idea about the chraitable aspect either    
    
    
    @tim_nolan @ischafer he was in front of a giant boom box LL Cool J Radio style too    
    
    
    I'm buying for any of my friends who will go the barbershop tomorrow and order a Macklemore    
    
    
    I hope Stallone's attorneys are filing a cease and desist to Katy Perry as we speak    
    
    
    @hc http://bostinno.streetwise.co/2013/08/26/how-a-simple-inquiry-constant-feedback-from-reddit-launched-a-crowd-sourced-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Wow, I got a screen grab of the NYT Hack in case you didn't get to see it pic.twitter.com/TfoO4l3OCd    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor oh man, I'm not going to SXSW, but I really want to go to Marfa, best Prada store in the US, right?    
    
    
    All this Miley vs Syria commentary just shows we need to #Twerk4Peace    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor you should go check out Cameron NC some time, painted barns by Espo, Doze Green, Swoon & more
http://clclt.com/WayfaringTechNomad/archives/2013/04/10/barnstormers-street-art-gone-barn-around-cameron-nc …    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic I think RG1 is making a comeback this year    
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic hell yeah Rex Grossman is the original    
    
    
    Harper Says He Twerks Occasionally -- Thinks It Means Tweeting http://thelapine.ca/harper-says-he-twerks-occasionally-thinks-it-means-tweeting/ … via @TheLapine    
    
    
    @donsteele are we including Hall & Oates?    
    
    
    @bmorrissey @donsteele The Oates last minute sub for Hall at the 08 World Series was amazing  http://goo.gl/7ZOyIj     
    
    
    Over under on Dr James Andrews mentions during tonight's game?    
    
    
    @DJMikeMorse how is their new music? I need to check it out, been a while    
    
    
    Etsy Pages just launched with curation partners & tastemakers like Apartment Therapy, Lucky, West Elm http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/follow-us-on-the-brand-new-just-launched-etsy-pages-194971 …    
    
    
    “I don’t want your life- Recording James Van Der Beek and the famous line from Varsity Blues.” by @mrtbrls https://medium.com/p/d4564a050e9a     
    
    
    Are giant inflatable rats available for kids parties? Or should I just send invites to non union kids… http://instagram.com/p/ep-I5vqDQ0/     
    
    
    “The most shocking part of the story was learning that there is a vegan strip club in Portland.” http://nyti.ms/1foNPa3     
    
    
    No one teaches bike riding like Grandpa Carl. Great video by @rblumes http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/how-to-teach-a-kid-to-ride-a-bike-apartment-therapy-videos-195374 …    
    
    
    Confirmed that David Bowie has an office in my building? Time to start working on my Ziggy Stardust Halloween outfit, just to be that guy    
    
    
    @TMorgz I owe you some drinks, next week?    
    
    
    @TMorgz I'll give you a shout    
    
    
    Banksy on Village Voice "feels an affinity with people who provide quality content for free on street corners." http://goo.gl/IxKgHD     
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic did u skip the skins avatar and go straight to the caps twitter avatar this year? #NfcLeast    
    
    
    These Men Are Now Charging People to Look at Banksy's Latest Stencil http://gawker.com/these-men-are-now-charging-people-to-look-at-banksys-l-1443562694 …    
    
    
    If you haven't seen it yet, Ikea Or Death http://ikeaordeath.com  is the greatest thing from this weeks internet. Kudos @Buie    
    
    
    The Underbelly Project - Walk Through  - MOCAtv - Ep 19: http://youtu.be/bJuCHsYhmf0  via @youtube    
    
    
    Win: Luxury Mosaic Tile from Mission Stone and Tile Giveaway http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/win-luxury-mosaic-tile-from-mission-stone-and-tile-giveaway-195874 … via @AptTherapy    
    
    
    @zipplockbag earthlink uses same infrastructure, but different prices, you can switch back and forth for better prices, but not service    
    
    
    I'm booked for X-mas Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues Trailer #2: http://youtu.be/6VdGI5-z_hg     
    
    
    @RickWebb great seeing you, safe travels down south, which reminds me your guy from Supply Hog has renewed my faith in the internets    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield @Dwellable Congrats!    
    
    
    @thegasHole @barnapkins that would be my first stop too    
    
    
    @oohlarock congrats Mary, lets grab a drink to celebrate soon!    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor coming out of dj retirement?    
    
    
    @barnapkins ask your man @thegasHole about how hard the hair is    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor is this a private affair?, you need to hollar if its a public performance    
    
    
    @MIKEBMCD @djforge cat scratch fever    
    
    
    @pllqt @hc @bsokic screw-morphic design?    
    
    
    @MisterGIF are they the one's with Tribe Called Quest playing, I just learned these are their last shows?    
    
    
    @MisterGIF shows how old I am, only want to see Tribe, and falling for Internet Scams    
    
    
    @hillaryj don't forget Chinatown, Yo Bus is the best bus brand name ever, but I guess that's not saying much    
    
    
    I need reports on tonight's  A Tribe Called Quest show, or as you kids might call it Kanye Concert    
    
    
    Who do you think are the top Innovators and Icons of Design? http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/innovators-icons-of-design-tournament-presented-by-dyson-197161 … video by the amazing @rblumes    
    
    
    Yes! Fila Sweats are the future of advertsing - Digiday http://shar.es/8SbXY  via @bmorrisey @digiday    
    
    
    Congrats @mckinney “@PSFK: Homeless Campaign Lets Participants Rename Ordinary Household Products http://bit.ly/1hdf7Ac ”    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller you need diplomat plates for the firebird #DiplomaticImmunity    
    
    
    @mzmelissa @zipplockbag I'm watching more ads as a cordcutter than I ever did as a cable subscriber. I can't dvr and fast forward anymore    
    
    
    Happy Brown Friday http://on.digg.com/18Nl6qV     
    
    
    #Brawlmart is the best hashtag ever    
    
    
    Help Wanted: We're Hiring Apartment Therapy Editorial Contributors http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/were-hiring-apartment-therapy-editorial-contributors-196686 … via @AptTherapy    
    
    
    @AarthiD Thank You! I've been meaning to catch up. New job plus moving family up was crazy. Did you find a new full time gig?    
    
    
    @AarthiD congrats to you! finding good people is the hard part.    
    
    
    First successful use of a QR Code? College kid makes $24k in bitcoins by waving a sign on ESPN http://www.businessinsider.com/someone-holding-bitcoin-sign-on-college-gameday-receives-over-22-bitcoins-2013-12 … via    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor so true, I love that Reddit users had to photoshop enhance the image, they still couldn't scan it ha ha    
    
    
    Ron Burgundy hosts entire local Bismarck North Dakota newscast http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Fpj4uM1ruvs#t=85 …    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive I think you should just invest in this http://www.ebay.com/itm/I-GOT-THE-HOOK-UP-No-Limit-Films-Records-MASTER-P-Leather-Crew-Jacket-L-50-XL-/281218921091?pt=LH_DefaultDomain_0&hash=item4179f43283 …    
    
    
    @donaldhughes @PaigeWilcox how is @donaldhughes working during this Beyonce holiday?    
    
    
    @SWeissman I don't know if I needed more evidence after this http://weheartkanye.tumblr.com/post/37139703579 …    
    
    
    Casey Neistat Spent $25,000 Of 20th Century Fox's Money On Philippines Typhoon Relief http://huff.to/1cP7qgk     
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands what up dre?    
    
    
    Handmade Holidays: Renée's Hand-Poured Soy Candles Inspired Giving from Nikon http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/handmade-holidays-renes-handpoured-soy-candles-inspired-giving-from-nikon-197901 … via @AptTherapy    
    
    
    How A Paris Graffiti Mecca Was Transformed Into An Immersive Digital Experience By @jeffcbeer http://www.fastcocreate.com/3023680/how-a-paris-graffiti-mecca-was-transformed-into-an-immersive-digital-experience … via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    Final Round Jeans vs. Eames Lounge.. Vote Now!   

Innovators & Icons of Design: Presented by Dyson http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/innovators-icons-of-design-the-championship-round-presented-by-dyson-197851 … via @AptTherapy    
    
    
    @Aerocles @bmorrissey so Jerry just fired his play clock operator?    
    
    
    @Aerocles @bmorrissey Dez saved somebody's job with that td    
    
    
    I need to see more Foles and less Folds to bring home this win! #FlyEaglesFly    
    
    
    @jjones amazing happy new year JJ!    
    
    
    @averyj glad to know you are still alive RIP Uncle Phil    
    
    
    @ableparris the troposphere!    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Delorean Website is live and offering matching luggage for your futuristic car? http://www.delorean.com/     
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor congrats this trumps the Adidas Jeezy sneaker as the realest sponsorship in the game    
    
    
    Excited to learn about mind reading from @hc http://shar.es/72iUs     
    
    
    @robbievitrano heading into town tonight, mad I'm missing #IdeaInstitute, but I would like to connect with the Trumpet team..    
    
    
    @ischafer @adfreak can't wait to see him kill some vampires    
    
    
    When I was young, I bought  a Honda Scooter for what these new Lebron sneakers are going to cost.    
    
    
    White folks just love to crip walk    
    
    
    Shout outs to my Korean brother who just owned the floor for Gangam Style    
    
    
    @thegasHole snacks on snacks on snacks    
    
    
    @DukeHoopBlog hey Rowe, drop me an email robert(at)http://blogads.com  and I'll put u in touch    
    
    
    @brittontaylor amazing!!! can you petition apple to forever change the "a" key to "sausages"    
    
    
    @barnapkins http://vimeo.com/47875656     
    
    
    @aburtch @barnapkins did you make your own song at the end? that functionality is crazy...    
    
    
    Wow @donaldhughes just told me we've reached an age where previous stars of MTV's Real World are in office and speaking at the RNC    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor think you would enjoy this book http://www.amazon.com/The-Big-Payback-History-Business/dp/0451229290 … had some good stories on cover diversity in Vibe's early days    
    
    
    @Jbrown523 you can still follow the old tech advice of shutdown + reboot    
    
    
    Do you make more money by giving away great content ?http://blog.aweissman.com/2012/06/what-if-we-give-it-away-lessons-from.html …    
    
    
    @carmenboca x100 when they use a bluetooh    
    
    
    @jl_weber thats the hard part....    
    
    
    @baratunde did Romney really just throw a party on a Yacht named "Cracker Bay" ? http://abcnews.go.com/Blotter/romney-party-yacht-flies-cayman-islands-flag/story?id=17105028#.UD5ugWie4mw …    
    
    
    Taylor Hicks is the perfect performer for the RNC #soulpatrol    
    
    
    @arilevine and we just pay the rent    
    
    
    Mitt just knocked over the asian cameraman did anybody else see that?    
    
    
    Promoted Mitt Tweet just popped up, I wish it was for President Dwayne Elizondo Mountain Dew Herbert Camacho instead    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U sorry about that cous, I'll make the $30kl back, I can feel a hot streak coming in black jack    
    
    
    @Scaroline27 amazing...    
    
    
    @SocialDivo wanted to connect on twitter too, keep in touch    
    
    
    I guess this crowd ain't up on Hot Cheetos    
    
    
    @angelinadarling amazing, dirt loves the kids    
    
    
    Who knows more about sleeping with dogs than this guy. #petsmart http://instagr.am/p/PH8q9TKDaT/     
    
    
    Cine: Hey Girl http://cinemagr.am/show/14693855  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    Cine: Chain Reaction http://cinemagr.am/show/14697728  #cinemagraph #gif    
    
    
    Awfully tired boss, dog tired #RipJonCoffee    
    
    
    Nothing says #4ever like Nick & Jessica http://instagr.am/p/PKpG2QKDdn/     
    
    
    Content is the 7th Weapon of influence - @markwschaefer #CMWorld    
    
    
    Sorry Raleigh can't make Hopscotch, too busy seeing Rick Springfield in Ohio http://instagr.am/p/PNsn1LKDXB/     
    
    
    Rick Springfield is trying to get the crowd to sing the lyrics to songs other than Jesse's Girl. #nothappening    
    
    
    @teacheyd great meeting you, lets clear an afternoon for Chicken & Waffles some time soon    
    
    
    Best of the Wurst http://instagr.am/p/PPdZxjKDbv/     
    
    
    Chevy Ok Go Video got a billion impressions online... after their Super Bowl spot used "We Are Young" song topped ITunes #CMWorld    
    
    
    Making someone fill out a form to get your content is like asking for sex before the first date @giladdevries #CMWorld    
    
    
    Jack Hanna in the house http://instagr.am/p/PP0Nw7qDbT/     
    
    
    When the gorillas weren't breeding Jack Hanna hired his wife's gynecologist    
    
    
    @allimooney  Think Quarterly just won something at theseContent Marketing Awards, let me know if I need to rep the family name    
    
    
    Shout outs to @donaldhughes for representing NC to the fullest at the DNC #huges2016    
    
    
    @allimooney yes I think so, it was at the end of this content marketing world conference.... Congrats    
    
    
    @ableparris is that a Bourbon tasting? Can I send you my resume?    
    
    
    @richiecruz Fania got me when I heard the Dave Cortez "Happy Soul with a Hook" that DJ Premo flipped for Christina Aguilera of all people    
    
    
    3D Printing Plastic Fisher-Price Records http://www.core77.com/blog/digital_fabrication/3d_printing_plastic_fisher-price_records_23358.asp … via @Core77    
    
    
    Best Nature Trail Ever http://instagr.am/p/PcePwpKDXT/     
    
    
    @barnapkins did you see these http://www.blackmagicdesign.com/products/blackmagiccinemacamera/ …    
    
    
    @barnapkins just saw this too http://trifilmsept12.eventbrite.com/  you shoukd submit  Tinsel Town    
    
    
    Damn this Ninjatune Beastie Boys Paul's Boutique tribute mix is amazing http://soundcloud.com/ninja-tune/solid-steel-radio-show-31-8-1?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=wtshare&utm_medium=twitter&utm_content=http://soundcloud.com/ninja-tune/solid-steel-radio-show-31-8-1 …    
    
    
    @allnick great meeting you in Columbus, lets chat more soon, love to hear what you have planned for @startupstats and future blogs    
    
    
    @ableparris What? Bill Nye is still alive? ha ha    
    
    
    Is anyone's suggested Facebook friends showing you just eye candy, instead of people you might actually know?    
    
    
    @ischafer please order up an @InvisibleObama case study video, @InvisibleObama deserves to win this year too    
    
    
    #TweetToShoot It's duck season http://tweettoshoot.neimanlabs.com/     
    
    
    @zipplockbag sinde we're both insanley handsome men, so we might need someone else to experience this problem, before drawing a conclusion    
    
    
    Shout outs to amc for playing The Green Mile all day everyday    
    
    
    @HaniHamma @colleenbrea Optimus Prime is the greatest leader    
    
    
    @arilevine amazing mix! that album was huge inspiration to dig in the crates, and this brought it all together for me...    
    
    
    If you played college ball before me, you got no business in the club. I'm looking at you Jeremy Hyatt    
    
    
    My Gangam Style My Pony mix is so conceptual    
    
    
    @barnapkins @colleenbrea @benaffleck amazing bring that back home    
    
    
    @arilevine are you in NC this weekend?    
    
    
    Air Celek #flyeaglesfly    
    
    
    Best headline of the day goes to @adage : Can the McRib Save Christmas? http://adage.com/u/7A8Sdb     
    
    
    @saneel the lowline founders will be speaking at this http://influencerconnyc-eorg.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    @bmorrissey is one gif enough to start  a Buzzfeed for us Eagles Fans : Birdfeed?http://gifrific.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/Brent-Celek-Jumps-Over-Ed-Reed.gif …    
    
    
    Do ad agencies have a job number for fantasy football?    
    
    
    @calebkramer @kylecameron we've got a polling feature some of our blogs, let me know next time, hopefully we can get a ton of free responses    
    
    
    @mzmelissa should have known a smart producer has it all figured out    
    
    
    @Gejashiku damn ravers    
    
    
    Hoops with @Khoadini @mikeppc99 and @chavisheughts tonight, I was Mr. 1 Run and Done    
    
    
    @beneckerson that negative attitude is clearly why you need this app ha ha, they got more investors than devs    
    
    
    @PaulGelb congrats Paul, great news    
    
    
    @erictullis Kenny Dope Produced it under The Bucket Heads name.. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K2vLaCElhP8 … samples Chicago Street Player http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_trFuBGPQho …    
    
    
    @erictullis man I'm  bummed I have to miss Kenny's set... let me know if you have any new favorite disco edits you're liking    
    
    
    Guest reviewers @immaculateinfat are killing it again, getting buck on purple drank amongst Gen X'ers http://goo.gl/dDI6V     
    
    
    Based on early reviews, seems you could easily improve IOS 6 buy institution Emojicon based maps    
    
    
    Props to @fakeshoredrive on building brands and musical movement at the same time #dewyou    
    
    
    @cpanetta77 I think he played the republican national convention?    
    
    
    So @Gejashiku played Blues Traveller tonight..    
    
    
    @shaunstripling lets hope it catches on in advertising http://adage.com/article/adages/ad-agency-creates-nap-rooms-employees/227475/ …    
    
    
    @DrePowersBrands good luck, I'm sure you'll crush it    
    
    
    @darrylohrt @aburtch so a new Myspace = Pinstagram?    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor I bought some bike stuff at the beach and saw Walmart's "Fixie" Bike first hand http://www.walmart.com/ip/Thruster-700c-Men-s-Fixie-Bike/17206771 …    
    
    
    I never would have guessed Myspace would takover my day    
    
    
    @haveboard @duanebrown I feel like the slow loading choppy about to crash vimeo video gave me an accurate feel of the real Myspace    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller you weren't on Myspace before, how did you find out about my gigs at White Collar Crime?    
    
    
    Monday Night Hoops http://instagr.am/p/P-tXerKDZX/     
    
    
    @bradbeejay you know your old when going for 20 means minutes, not points    
    
    
    I hope this will be discussed in a Obama Romney Debate: Bacon, pork shortage "now unavoidable" http://www.chicagotribune.com/business/breaking/la-fi-mo-pork-bacon-shortage-20120924,0,6240960.story …    
    
    
    @barnapkins isn't that near a salami shop?    
    
    
    Clicked a banner that offered classic Atari games, prompts you to download MS Explorer for ad free gaming http://www.beautyoftheweb.com/amazing#/atari     
    
    
    @JrawlsMusic those look perfect for the evening wear competition, fancy sneakers    
    
    
    @richiecruz @RobMarkman I heard the saddest radio spot down south recently for Amil "1st lady of the Roc" hosting some hood club night    
    
    
    @barnapkins that's literally epic news, congrats    
    
    
    Checkpoint on capital blvd    
    
    
    @Buie i just landed at JFK, let's link up if you're around    
    
    
    Authenticity for brands, we know it when we don't see it,  are you a likeable person or soulless corporation? @tim_leake #AWIX    
    
    
    @tim_leake great presentation, really enjoyed your part    
    
    
    Didn't win the @advertisingweek Dj battle, but retiring to the Waldorf Astoria for the night makes me feel like a winner.    
    
    
    @TMorgz congrats on the big move and new gig, I'll be back in 2 weeks for a Perez Hilton, party and you have to come    
    
    
    @wjessewright congrats Jesse, awesome work    
    
    
    @advertisingweek thank you, your team is amazing, awesome week    
    
    
    Most retweeted tweet of last year came from a marketer #AWIX    
    
    
    CNN Breaking News: Romney just finished eating at the Cheesecake Factory    
    
    
    Anybody else get a sponsored facebook post from a political candidate tonight?    
    
    
    @steveESPOpowers A hand written cease and desist letter for the unauthorized use of your likeness, is the classy way to thank them    
    
    
    @nckfbr are we still on for lunch today?    
    
    
    @nckfbr yeah, send a text, tweet or rock a t the window when you are heading up this way    
    
    
    Lady in my building just told me my outfit was cute, as a 6 foot tall man in seersucker shorts, I'm going to take that as a win    
    
    
    @RaleighRockstar In the south no one ever goes to jail in a seersucker suit    
    
    
    @bmcd67 hey brian, do you manage the sci quest events looking to get some feedback on a wordpress plugin that it looks like you are using?    
    
    
    @bmcd67 yes thats the one, thinking it might be a good solution for some music / event blogs we work with... might need to get some feedback    
    
    
    Hey @Buie it was great seeing you in NYC, I was just talking to my friend @donaldhughes about @mgproject lets all grab lunch soon    
    
    
    @Buie @donaldhughes I'm going to try and take tomorrow off, lets do next week    
    
    
    I went shopping for normal headphones  tonight, not as easy as it sounds in a post Beats by Dre world    
    
    
    Party ain't a party til your guest is sitting in a Piñata  http://instagr.am/p/QfwLp5qDdX/     
    
    
    @saracobaugh the DewDriver?    
    
    
    @jnorthen hey Janet, great seeing you in NYC, still blown away by your mental telepathy pr powers    
    
    
    Someone in purchasing got a little too excited by the Ruff Ryders 10 years ago http://instagr.am/p/Qh-s7LqDZP/     
    
    
    Love that Jack Dorsey confirms his scaled down involvement at Twitter by posting it on Tumblr http://tnw.to/g5xr     
    
    
    @ableparris but will it tell me to buy collages and photo prints from the Parris family, if not they have some bugs to fix    
    
    
    @benblackmer @rapportive I'm seeing it on reply emails, but no longer see rapportive when i compose new emails    
    
    
    @mq5 Happy Birthday!!!!    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive Is this part of your plot to bring No Limit back?    
    
    
    @narrowd congrats on the FWA, huge!! but that client must have been real pain to deal with right?    
    
    
    @voiceOrezin didn't know if you caught this article: The Responsive Design Myth http://www.digiday.com/publishers/the-responsive-design-myth/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    Video dream team @barnapkins @thegasHole @Napwright collab w/ @NewRaleigh on the Cooke Street Carnival Video featuring @4toon    
    
    
    Has any designer done their own versions of the ebay logo? Can you really update zany dot com era logos?    
    
    
    Walmart finally realizes what we've all known: people don't want to go inside their stores... http://www.wired.com/business/2012/10/walmart-wishes-amazon-unhappy-holidays-with-same-day-delivery-launch/ …    
    
    
    Innovation or PR?: The Lexus iPad Print Ad | Digiday http://www.digiday.com/brands/innovation-or-pr-the-lexus-ipad-print-ad/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    @bmorrissey @funkmastabaker I'm mailing in the check for my @digiday print subscription right now, CinePrint is the future    
    
    
    Paul Ryan Has Already Lost the Debate Based on These Workout Photos - @Gawker http://gawker.com/5950879/paul-ryan-has-already-lost-the-debate-based-on-these-workout-photos …    
    
    
    @Malbonnington @iaintait this dj's rendition of Trans Europe Express is Ridiculous (minute and a half mark)  http://youtu.be/SiqIlW1IvlE     
    
    
    Poor Lance, he  had no choice but to dope http://ti.me/Ot2e7s     
    
    
    Dude just pulled out his harmonica and confirmed what key the record I'm playing is in. Bout to get real in here    
    
    
    @barnapkins bring your accordion it's on now    
    
    
    Quora Digest for the day http://www.quora.com/Wealth/Is-getting-rich-worth-it …    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller it looks like miserable multimillionaires still love the site.    
    
    
    @Chapinc we can only hope that Dishwasher Pete gets added to tonight's broadcast as a dishwashing strategist...    
    
    
    Why did I learn about the Hoagie Trail after my Philly trip? http://historictaconyrevitalization.com/hoagie-trail/     
    
    
    @djforge man, I just had to buy new headphones... and the Beats By Dre success has ruined headphones, thank god Sony still makes monitors    
    
    
    @ChiChiRules4U when you live in the south, a Wawa hoagie taste like heaven    
    
    
    @dougkleeman by ad people for ad people http://bbh-labs.com/while-you-were-off-an-iphone-web-app-for-the-connected-set …    
    
    
    @ableparris I'm getting ready to head out to Bk, how's your schedule looking    
    
    
    @ableparris I leave Friday, I'm up all the time, but needed to catch up with some  bk peeps, so I wanted to give a shout    
    
    
    @TMorgz I keep forgetting you are a New Yorker now... are you around tonight?    
    
    
    @TMorgz Perez Hilton Party at Highline Balroom, can you dm me your email    
    
    
    @TMorgz did u get in ok?    
    
    
    congrats @accarrino @annetteshade great seeing you last night    
    
    
    @beatrizv520 Great catching up with you..    
    
    
    Murdered out matte black Pontiac was the talk of the auto parts store http://instagr.am/p/Q-w3tRqDZb/     
    
    
    Dropping fresh copies of classic riddims courtesy of @MissLilysChat    
    
    
    We about to take it up from 2chainz to 3chainz    
    
    
    Girl with Honey Boo Boo Accent just asked for We No Speak Americano    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller jerk    
    
    
    Enjoying a soulful set by the amazing Keith Ward @calaveraraleigh    
    
    
    @barnapkins the new philly Wawa was baking bread in store, I think the bread distribution was the only thing holding them back...    
    
    
    I'm used to getting flyered at my Dj gigs, but not my day job http://instagr.am/p/RGZQ8ZKDdl/     
    
    
    Denny's to Launch Middle-Earth Inspired Menu http://adage.com/u/WvAwba     
    
    
    Woman Posts Boyfriend Request on GitHub, Requires Access to His Server http://betabeat.com/?p=67389  via @betabeat    
    
    
    The Quora Digest has become a highlight of my week, http://www.quora.com/What-is-it-like-to-be-incredibly-funny …    
    
    
    Elmo Piñata got worked  blogads http://instagr.am/p/RIzAzBKDch/     
    
    
    @aburtch are you in this mellow mushroom video crossing the street or is it an Anson look a like ? http://creativity-online.com/work/mellow-mushroom-follow-us-well-follow-you/29591 …    
    
    
    @aburtch too funny saw Mitch share it, and it was on Creativity too, time to get your Sag card..    
    
    
    @djforge @DJSK1 do you guys know any good Charleston SC dj's ? A friend is getting married there, wants an old school party rocker    
    
    
    @djforge thanks Forge, @NattyHeavy what up, let me know your email or best way to refer a friend for a gig...    
    
    
    Dyskograf an optical based turntable, make your own beats with a marker http://vimeo.com/51700038     
    
    
    @megsterr mush Cali mush    
    
    
    @soundboy love what you guys are doing at songkick, detour is amazing...    
    
    
    @RickWebb ahhhh the Ikea Expedit, that 5x5 will hold over 2000 vinyl LP's, don't ask me how I know    
    
    
    @soundboy just signed up for your API too, looking forward to seeing what that data can do for local and event blogs I work with...    
    
    
    @ImJustinMiller how many beignets did you eat before that presentation    
    
    
    Art of the Q http://instagr.am/p/ROgXn2KDfW/     
    
    
    Stop When Swinging http://instagr.am/p/ROgsI_KDf0/     
    
    
    The future sounds better in the Queens English RT @bmorrissey what percentage of planners are british? 60%?    
    
    
    @funkmastabaker what was the tumblr he ripped off, I want to check the og    
    
    
    @JasonHirschhorn I was just talking to my friend from http://areyouahuman.com/  today, I love their solution for bad CAPTCHAS, check them out    
    
    
    @kirbywinfield @jasonhirschhorn I like @solvemedia too, big problem, I'm glad multiple companies are bringing change    
    
    
    Do girls put pink monograms on their Suv's in other places, or just the south?    
    
    
    This nice southern lady just gave me a glow stick, and offered to feed me, am I dj'n a rave for Paula Dean?    
    
    
    @zipplockbag I can't wait for @thegasHole to be Guy Fieri    
    
    
    @patricec bumba clot hurricane    
    
    
    Obama and Gov Christie focus on working together to help the people..  http://www.rawstory.com/rs/2012/10/30/christie-praises-obama-doesnt-give-a-damn-about-romney-photo-op/#.UI_e-O4LfYM.twitter …    
    
    
    This is the White House I'm most concerned about right now pic.twitter.com/qEcylgAb    
    
    
    Can a 10 year old make better advertising than you? via @agencyspy http://www.mediabistro.com/agencyspy/toronto-agency-celebrates-ten-years-by-handing-creative-reins-over-to-10-year-olds_b40479 …    
    
    
    @scottforshay amazing to see the little one's giving creative direction to the editors    
    
    
    Thank You @jermainelandon for the term "Twerkers Comp"    
    
    
    Wow, thanks to @arilevine for sharing http://furby.tumblr.com/  and #HSUchat    
    
    
    Genius Bar - "yeah a bar without alcohol is not genius"    
    
    
    Do you think the right player is on the wrong team? @mcuban "I Would Vote for Romney if He Was a Democrat" http://wp.me/pk3mX-wp  via    
    
    
    Like pops always said, it doesn't matter if you win or lose, just cover the spread http://espn.go.com/espn/otl/story/_/id/8568724/nine-south-florida-youth-football-coaches-face-gambling-charges …    
    
    
    @denglander is that the one staring the Fat Boys?    
    
    
    @denglander classic    
    
    
    Turn the Epcot Dome into a Death Star and start building Ewok Village Orlando ASAP    
    
    
    @DevinPK10 no need to shave, furry applicants are encouraged    
    
    
    @RickWebb glad Lucy is safe, family is not too far on the shore... hope home and clubhouse were unaffected    
    
    
    @RickWebb family all down the shore and all are safe.. inlaws are year-round residents in Cape May, sounded bad early, but good reports now    
    
    
    Im ready for the return of the High Top Fade and Norris Cole on the Miami Heat is really helping the cause    
    
    
    @allnick I was amazed too, was wondered who actually hosts in NY    
    
    
    @holaolah he needs to design new Septa uniforms    
    
    
    @fakeshoredrive Philly!!!!!    
    
    
    @michaelmiraflor your instagram pics are crazy, lord of the flies hunger games stylee, hope you are well, and that was just documentary..    
    
    
    My man the @thegashole just killed the Halloween Game, all in with the Guy Fieri frosted tips http://instagr.am/p/Rd4B0eKDX4/     
    
    
    @cool_pond I highly suggest doing some back reading on Philebrity for the crazy tale that is Arthur Kade http://www.philebrity.com/index.php?s=arthur+kade …    
    
    
    When your kid has fangs, its best just to run with it http://dj-mooney.tumblr.com/post/34774319882/when-your-kid-has-fangs-its-best-just-to-run-with … via    
    
    
    Pumped to check out @davidchoe 's AMA on Reddit.. But I'll have to wait until I get home, you know its NSFW http://www.giantrobot.com/news/david-choe-ama-on-reddit/ …    
    
    
    @RyanNewYork thanks you for the awesome work on @TheFour2012    
    
    
    @thegasHole http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U5y9O20h9r8&feature=colike&utm_source=buffer&buffer_share=c1500 …    
    
    
    Who says Obama's not putting people back to work, Rasheed Wallace is playing for the Knicks    
    
    
    @Gejashiku I'm more Asian than you    
    
    
    @Khoadini been eating romantic dinners with Badu glad he has time to respond to @gejashiku    
    
    
    