About to get on an exciting panel at Grow 2011 in Vancouver    
    
    
    I'm proud of @soniaarrison on her book launch today ! "100+ How Longevity Will Change Everything" - amzn.to/rmX0mJ    
    
    
    As I'm trying to parse the 1000s of Steve Jobs news hits, so many gems in his quotes (by Wired): http://bit.ly/qQplC6     
    
    
    500+ people at Berkeley Entrepreneur Forum, awesome crowd, looking forward to my panel shortly w @jkraus @howardh & @samangus    
    
    
    Latest PWC MoneyTree survey: 15 largest co's have $300B cash, Google bought 48 co's in 2010, 97% of venture profits come from 15 co's / yr    
    
    
    Emailing with founders this time of the night is akin to a super broadband while email volume in the morning is like dial up...    
    
    
    Congrats to @soniaarrison on being on the cover of WSJ today ! http://bit.ly/qaHUVh     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/qI2pjQ     
    
    
    En route to JFK - longest security line I've seen... (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 143 others) http://4sq.com/pLIcg9     
    
    
    Congrats to the @breezy team: The @Breezy Partner Network launches w/1k printing locations - http://techcrunch.com/2011/09/07/breezy-launches-partner-network-lets-you-print-on-the-go-at-1000-locations/ …    
    
    
    @Soniaarrison - the security guard at Bloomberg knew about your book 100plus - and waved me out saying "to a great 2030 !" - just #awesome    
    
    
    Android (1.4B in '10 to 8.1B in '11) might overtake Apple (2.7B in '10 to 6B in '11) in app downloads via CNET - http://cnet.co/nYWc7s     
    
    
    Want VCs to invest in Concordes ? Would need a $100B fund: Est. cost $150M, ended up at $1.7B w/o equal benefits - http://bit.ly/nM4zj0     
    
    
    @simeons Agreed (also I use an iPhone 4 :) - still interesting numbers    
    
    
    @emilychangtv also lesson learned from Google: thou shall take care of your employees    
    
    
    Agree with @Fredwilson that less is more: Six Slides, Three Slides, or No Slides http://www.avc.com/a_vc/2011/09/six-slides-three-slides-or-no-slides.html …    
    
    
    Excited about Disrupt panel "@lanyrdalert: @Angels, 11:45am @ronconway @jeff @joshmedia @davemcclure @shervin @asenkut http://lanyrd.com/shgrh "    
    
    
    CNN Gallup poll: 58% of Americans feel they're worse off vs a year ago compared to half who feel they're better off; SV doesn't = US    
    
    
    Highlights from Nielsen's Top 20 Android Apps in US: 18% use the Amazon Android App Store via @businessinsider - http://read.bi/qTG579     
    
    
    Nielsen's Top 20 US Android Apps: 14% play Angry Birds Rio AND 26% play Angry Birds via @businessinsider - read.bi/qTG579 cc #roviomobile    
    
    
    Nielsen's Top 20 US Android Apps: 26% play Angry Birds vs 15% use Twitter via @businessinsider - read.bi/qTG579 cc #roviomobile    
    
    
    Congrats @adwane and @Zinch team: @Chegg buys @Zinch -  dthin.gs/neR05X    
    
    
    @aweissman - congrats on the news - look forward to doing more together    
    
    
    Via @cape: Mobile now accounts for over 10% of all sales in eBay UK - http://tnw.to/1ArHH  - #mobilecommerce    
    
    
    "@ttunguz Email Marketing Benchmarks by Industry http://ow.ly/6z1pr " lowest open rate: PR, Politics, highest: construction, other    
    
    
    our genes respond to the foods we eat (>40% carbs trigger metabolic inflammation)  http://bit.ly/oJ7FED  via @soniaarrison cc @tferriss    
    
    
    Ad in WSJ:&quot;We regrow bone. Yes, you read that right&quot; by Cleveland Clinic - how cool is that ? Cc @soniaarrison    
    
    
    PayPal Now Processing $315 M In Payments Per Day on upward of 5M transactions / day via @techcrunch http://techcrunch.com/2011/09/25/paypal-now-processing-315-million-in-payments-per-day/ …    
    
    
    Goldman: Microsoft Is Getting $444 Million Annually From Android Patent Licenses http://read.bi/qYrXJj     
    
    
    175 Founders 60+ companies in 6 countries on 4 continents, nearly 3k jobs created, 1 awesome community - http://www.felicis.com/founders/     
    
    
    Comparing revenues of Apple & Microsoft side by side (iphone + ipad now equals virtually all MSFT revenues !) - http://pulse.me/s/1VpE8     
    
    
    @pmarca on WSJ re "Why SW is Eating the World" - 40x increase in broadband users, 100x decrease in app costs - http://on.wsj.com/o6yIeE     
    
    
    Via Bloomberg and CIBC, tech industry as a whole may be sitting on more than $700B in cash this year - causing tech to fall less than SP500    
    
    
    @dcian Roger that fixing ASAP :)    
    
    
    Recent research: '11 smartphone userbase 627M ww (270M new shipped vs 194M notebooks) by '15 userbase -> 1.5B ww (449M new shipped)    
    
    
    "@hunterwalk: Honor Steve Jobs by building things which matter & lead from your heart." Hope we honor him beating cancer too    
    
    
    @sacca @naval @davemcclure @cdixon - @RovioMobile or @Shopify isn't SV; our job isn't rehashing present it's looking into future (b4 crowds)    
    
    
    Global e-commerce approaching $1 Trillion in 2013; By 2014: mobile app spend to hit $40B, US education spend $80B, Health IT spend $76B    
    
    
    Great take on the state of the market, angels and LPs by @fredwilson http://lnkd.in/msQrbY     
    
    
    Angry Birds Creator Rovio Eyes $1B IPO in 2012 http://lnkd.in/ZMz96y     
    
    
    Google has 4 of the Top 10 Greatest U.S. Dig. Media M&A Deals (YouTube & Android #1 & #2) Of All Time via @techcrunch http://techcrunch.com/2011/10/15/top-10-greatest-u-s-digital-media-ma-deals-of-all-time/ …    
    
    
    Congrats to @shopify on the announcement of its Series B to fuel its growth (we are excited to be part of it) - http://bit.ly/qlm6sy     
    
    
    100-year-old marathoner finishes race http://lnkd.in/E528Ca     
    
    
    @AngryBirds : 400M+ downloads, 130M monthly users, 30M DAU, 300M min of gameplay / day; marketing spend = 0 - http://tcrn.ch/osBndv  #awesome    
    
    
    En route to Dublin for F.ounders conference - looking forward to it    
    
    
    Love the vibe from Dublin Web Summit - finished a great panel    
    
    
    Great review of @jtimberlake's 'In Time' in Slate Magazine by @soniaarrison - http://slate.me/uGRML8     
    
    
    @gmc "Ireland is seriously pulling out all the stops tonight" - understatement of the night. Best."un"conference.ever.  #founders    
    
    
    Amazing dinner in Dublin Castle - #Founders pic.twitter.com/uhu3MGhI    
    
    
    Nicely done ! "@brianp: Great review of our new app @batch on the The Next Web: http://thenextweb.com/apps/2011/10/28/batch-for-iphone-lets-you-share-a-ton-of-photos-quickly/ …"    
    
    
    Congrats to the @massivehealth team on the launch of such a beautiful iOS app: Eatery (great reviews already) - http://tnw.co/rPNkWs     
    
    
    5 Felicis companies featured by Apple at the same time today: @soundhound, @massivehealth, @fitbit, @batch, @1000memories - super #awesome    
    
    
    Via @TheEconomist  immigrants make up 1/8th of US population but founded a quarter of tech companies    
    
    
    @BigDataCloud thanks for the invite - in NY this week, ccing @speechu    
    
    
    Look forward to speaking on investing and media panel @businessinsider #ignition conference shortly w @borthwick @nichcarlson moderating    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Level 6 "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare! Huzzah! http://4sq.com/sOcwbQ     
    
    
    Starting the morning with great coffee (@ Ground Support w/ 3 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/te95z7     
    
    
    I'm at United 0642 JFK -> SFO http://4sq.com/uuWmst     
    
    
    @erdogan @studios @ozgrrl09 @mat_vdp @jadlerb - thank you for the retweet on the immigration quote from Economist, much appreciated    
    
    
    @DealmakerMedia - Excited to see you in LA next week at http://dealmakermedia.com/events/66  - looking forward to it    
    
    
    The seismic shift in enterprise to cloud computing accelerates with SAP's purchase of Successfactors for $3.4B in cash: http://reut.rs/szEYJK     
    
    
    Looking forward to an exciting panel this morning with @billmaris, @howardh and Ian Sobieski at #FTStanford2011 cc @ftconferences    
    
    
    Congrats ! Hearsay Social CEO @ClaraShih Joins @Starbucks Board of Directors - @LeenaRao via @TechCrunch -  http://lnkd.in/KPUCw9     
    
    
    @JulesMaltz belated Thanks ! Great meeting you !    
    
    
    Congratulations @haroon @shervin and team @websdotcom on the Vistaprint acquisition (117.5M) - http://bit.ly/vEQlxF  - great memories    
    
    
    Michael Moritz: The best advice I ever got http://lnkd.in/8dfa7u     
    
    
    Ditto: "@Baris: congrats @auren! - Founders Fund Gains Serial Entrepreneur Auren Hoffman As Venture Partner http://me.lt/05ww0 "    
    
    
    3 out of 4 US firms w fewer than 1000 employees plan to spend $21,000 (ave) on tablets next year - http://pulse.me/s/4sF6m     
    
    
    Flurry estimates weekly app downloads reached 1.2B during holiday week, first time passing 1B mark (#2 country is CN) - http://tcrn.ch/sAaWCV     
    
    
    Some 6.5 Million People Found Angry Birds in Their Stockings on Christmas day alone - http://pulse.me/s/4CF3U     
    
    
    Great piece on the emergence of #socialcuration by @eladgil - http://bit.ly/AgXjnB     
    
    
    It's not even the end of first quarter, 49ers leading 14-0 #awesome    
    
    
    "@daslee: What I Learned Building the Apple Store - Ron Johnson - HBR http://j.mp/sGOe67  " payment another big differentiator    
    
    
    @rfradin @@peterpham @@asenkut roger that    
    
    
    @dkhare @@asenkut @@eladgil agreed - hence mobile is our largest focus at Felicis    
    
    
    "@paulg: Schlep Blindness: http://paulgraham.com/schlep.html " exactly why we like education & health, back founders globally who pursue audacious goals    
    
    
    Uh-oh, PC: Half of computing device sales are mobile http://gigaom.com/mobile/uh-oh-pc-half-of-computing-device-sales-are-mobile/ …    
    
    
    Packed house at Rocketspace - about to give a talk on exits pic.twitter.com/AzZAVINV    
    
    
    @agoldfisher @jenniferlum @bingbooster @boonspoon thanks for the tweets from @startupexits - incredible event last night !    
    
    
    @rmb great to run into you - look forward to connecting on @datasift    
    
    
    “@johnolilly: Tips for Entrepreneurs from a First Year VC - from PandoDaily  http://tmblr.co/ZUAZbyF28HqI ” awesome piece :)    
    
    
    Just landed in a snowy Munich for #DLD12 pic.twitter.com/pUelnOi8    
    
    
    @chrija me too ! Looking forward to it    
    
    
    Electric car ad from (!) 1912 pic.twitter.com/KkxSXD2r    
    
    
    Kung Hei Fat Coy - Happy Chinese New Year (of the Dragon) - an amazing Start so far - wishing everyone a prosperous and joyous year !    
    
    
    Congrats @garrytan and @aaroniba on becoming new YC partners - http://bit.ly/yinh92  (proud to have backed both @Posterous and @Appjet)    
    
    
    Wow @sebastianthrun congrats on Udacity - giving up Stanford tenure to teach hundreds of thousands online: http://reut.rs/xlzwmC     
    
    
    Great dinner with @jasonrapp (@ Prinz Myshkin) http://4sq.com/z7S8Io     
    
    
    Talk about change of guards $MSFT admits no longer ruling workplace http://read.bi/xBEldP  and Haliburton dumps $RIMM - http://read.bi/xBEldP     
    
    
    Via @gigaom / technet: App Economy Rocks: since '07, 311K direct app related jobs & 155K indirect app mkt related jobs created (466K tot.)    
    
    
    @btkisacik tesekkurler :)    
    
    
    @davemcclure @chudson really awesome panel tonight - tremendously enjoyed it - very glad to be working along with both of you !    
    
    
    Silicon Valley's Secret Sauce - great review of @quixotic and @bencasnocha new book "Startup of You" by @soniaarrison - http://bit.ly/xbxnBB     
    
    
    "@hunterwalk: Pinterest data: ... 80% of pins are re-pins,... http://bit.ly/zqPS3u " curating other content is the new creation    
    
    
    Congrats: "@TechCrunch: Groupon On A Buying Spree: Buys Mobile Payment Specialist Kima Labs http://tcrn.ch/xiRj95  by @ingridlunden"    
    
    
    Facebook Messenger, Apple's iMessage and Twitter estimated to result in $13.9B SMS revenue loss for carriers - http://bit.ly/yWpvHT     
    
    
    20GB in '80 cost nearly $1M and disk cluster weighed 2000kg ; 32GB microSD card in '10 cost $100 and weighed 0.5 grams    
    
    
    Lord of the Files: How GitHub Tamed Free Software (And More) (Robert McMillan/Wired.com) http://pulse.me/s/6kqjR     
    
    
    @angellist @@asenkut Thank you - cant wait for more cool new features from Angellist    
    
    
    Zaarly Celebrates Its Birthday W A New Reputation System (I wish I were at SXSW to try it out) - http://techcrunch.com/2012/03/08/zaarly-20/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    Tablet Adoption Surging in Enterprise - 22% of corp buyers planning to purchase tablets of those 84% iPad - http://pulse.me/s/6WiXN     
    
    
    “@pkedrosky: Luxury brands (up 2.7x since '01) vs the S&P 500 -  http://twitpic.com/8xlw46 ” excellence -> aspiring cust. -> high margins -> $$$    
    
    
    Happy St Patrick Day ! Remembering #F.ounders in Dublin & mtg w Irish Prime Minister Enda Kenny cc @paddycosgrave pic.twitter.com/urm81yNC    
    
    
    @Johnulawrence - thx for setting up the talk this morning; @sfgoodlife @Elliotcohen @BetoIII @Straforel @hoolieg thx for the tweets #mitsvst    
    
    
    @speechu - Love the new Felicis homepage :) http://www.felicis.com/     
    
    
    @shervin exactly - great conversation today    
    
    
    Angry Birds Space Is Out And It's Amazing! http://www.businessinsider.com/angry-birds-space-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=tools … via @sai_tools    
    
    
    @bencasnocha @shervin not only that; in careers the path to success often is not straight, the dots connect (Steve Jobs) afterwards    
    
    
    @Joi I watched Battle Royale before Hunger Games, cant believe the similarities    
    
    
    @azumio Love the continued innovation - Sleep Time is a gorgeous app - http://bit.ly/GPO3Ua  cc @speechu    
    
    
    “@andray: The Appoday Effect pic.twitter.com/GRBIM4Ds” that's impact :)    
    
    
    @sacca @johnolilly true that - just say no to fomo    
    
    
    @gbrockway hope to team up next time    
    
    
    Smartphones Account for Half of all Mobile Phones, Dominate New Phone Purchases in the US (Matth/Nielsen Wire) http://pulse.me/s/7wH72     
    
    
    China surpasses 1B mobile subs - http://www.google.com/hostednews/afp/article/ALeqM5jhpFZrHwD9qqSZ2pfh9WxJuDwE8A …    
    
    
    Angry Birds animated TV series to premiere in Autumn 2012 (Stuart Dredge/Guardian) http://pulse.me/s/7JgBB     
    
    
    @DollarShaveClub great mention by @theeconomist - Blade runners http://econ.st/GZbGM0  cc @peterpham @mjones    
    
    
    @tbuttolph we're bullish on Canada ! Ottawa for sure :) (cc @Shopify @hfizzle), Toronto next & def. spending time on Vancouver (cc @bwertz)    
    
    
    "@mhelft: Munster: How Apple becomes the first $1T co - Fortune Tech http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2012/04/03/munster-how-apple-becomes-the-first-1-trillion-company/ …" ->Apple could represent 26% of tech mkt from 17%    
    
    
    @joshu another brilliant founder like you needs to attack Business Intelligence with a deceptively simple UI and cloud service :)    
    
    
    3-D Printing Is So Last Year: MIT’s “Self-Assembling Sand” Builds Objects Instantly http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1669426  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    @zach_inc it's the mobile edu co @inkling we backed :) We think it's much cooler tech and founding team compared to wacom ;) cc @stanine    
    
    
    Finally pushed into blue level in Nike Plus, after 176 runs and 1016km; now on to conquer the next 1483km to get into purple    
    
    
    @davemcclure @500startups nicely done :) “@Visually: 500 Startups: Blowing Up Startups Since 2010 #infographic http://bit.ly/HeKAgL ””    
    
    
    @davemcclure it's all you and your team, tremendous job building the mentor network & scaling - getting closer to 500 :) (only 243 to go)    
    
    
    @speechu thanks for the tip - enjoying reading: The Power of Habit by Charles Duhigg http://www.amazon.com/dp/B0055PGUYU/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_g18Fpb19A9DTH …    
    
    
    @tferriss inspiring post especially the quote about being bold by Scottish explorer Murray  http://www.fourhourworkweek.com/blog/2012/04/04/playing-b-ball-with-obama-6-steps-to-crossing-anything-off-your-bucket-list/ …    
    
    
    Did everybody see what just happened? The pendulum has swung. http://42floors.com/blog/posts/did-everybody-see-what-just-happened-the-pendulum-has-swung … via @42floors    
    
    
    @fitbit and how data + social + UI can affect behavior change: "How the fitbit got me to walk more.."  http://arst.ch/t8k  via @Brett603    
    
    
    @cdixon agreed. In fact, why don't we have Nest like tech on all aspects of home, not just locks ?    
    
    
    Commodore 64 Pioneer Dies at 83 http://pulse.me/s/7ZwCp  - C64 was my first computer, basic my first foray into programming    
    
    
    @cdixon - incredible to look back, $599 retail for 64kb ram and NTSC output (320x200) - http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Commodore_64 …    
    
    
    @cdixon me too, best gift ever; now I get to see my son eat, watch a kid show & browse YouTube on an iPad, all at the same time, at age 2.5    
    
    
    @johnolilly what do we do most on mobile ? Photos, but also gaming. Look at Rovios growth, in also about 2 yrs, close to 1B downloads    
    
    
    Ice Cream, Taxes, and Hunger Games: How Seasons Affect Buying Behavior by @zaarly - http://bit.ly/HGHjZn     
    
    
    Computing's next milestone is "thinking" http://pulse.me/s/83mE9  (biggest take away is need for solutions working out of the box)    
    
    
    "@vkhosla: I disagree, success isn't dangerous b/c you don't know why but b/c it's fleeting, you need to be adaptable http://buswk.co/I9oJs3 "    
    
    
    “@johnolilly: people keep talking about phone & tablets as the "2nd screen". But they're not. They're now screen #1.” Agreed !    
    
    
    US Student Loans at ~$1Trillion > credit card debt while youth unemployment is highest in 60 yrs - http://huff.to/wLPZiT  (via Steve Loeb)    
    
    
    Creativity is the residue of time wasted - Albert Einstein    
    
    
    Internet Ad Revenue at $31B In 2011, Mobile [grew fastest] 149% from [$0.6B to $1.6B] (IAB Report) http://techcrunch.com/2012/04/18/iab-revenue-report-2011/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @bfeld @sacca @davemcclure couldn't agree more - "Simplify ^ 3" - Perfection is attained when there is nothing left to take away    
    
    
    Alt 12 Apps is our first @angellist investment, we are really proud to be backing them ! cc @jennwong4Alt12 @speechu @naval    
    
    
    Interesting take on recruiting against Google from Palantir cofounder Stephen Cohen - http://is.gd/S3OsAJ  via @garrytan    
    
    
    Amazon AWS represents 1% of all internet traffic - their top 40 users ? Lots of surprises: http://blog.deepfield.net/2012/04/18/how-big-is-amazons-cloud/ … (Thx @stanine for the tip)    
    
    
    Angry Birds & Angry Birds Space Bandages in Walgreens - awesome brand reach cc @RovioMobile @pvesterbacka pic.twitter.com/vArTxzeH    
    
    
    @davemcclure "Gunaydin Istanbul" (Good morning Istanbul in Turkish) - say hi to my hometown :)    
    
    
    @OrganicJOOS Thank you for the +K on @Klout    
    
    
    @8en great story of @pinterest on @sai - http://read.bi/JmK8Qg     
    
    
    Quattrone gems on M&A - top 73 tech companies have  $466B in cash, top 10 of those $34B EACH - http://www.pehub.com/147028/quattrone-offers-take-on-brave-new-ma-world/ …    
    
    
    Another awesome, super productive day - following words come to mind: Gratitude, HUSTLE, Labor of Love    
    
    
    @arjunsethi @VCMike no time to waste, its fun to make things happen    
    
    
    @ssubo @mcmorranmurray @BrettLaffel @awasti @CarrieAWalsh @jbeldock thx for the tweets - great panel & dialog today    
    
    
    Such an amazing day that I'm pulling a @shervin - Happiness comes when your work and words are of benefit to yourself and others - Buddha    
    
    
    Intelligence (IQ) Is (important but not sufficient): What You Really Need To Succeed (EQ, MQ and BQ) - Forbes http://pulse.me/s/8yMqZ     
    
    
    At SF Zoo    
    
    
    DNA Sequencing Is Improving Faster Than Moore's Law! - Forbes http://onforb.es/wA4y7B  - full human genome in 1d for $1K from $3.8B in 13yrs '03    
    
    
    China Leads Q1-12 in Smartphone activations (11x growth in 1yr) and the other 9 fastest growing countries - http://blog.flurry.com/bid/83261/China-Now-Leads-the-World-in-New-iOS-and-Android-Device-Activations …    
    
    
    The Most Influential Angel Investors On AngelList - Forbes - http://onforb.es/IjMUSL     
    
    
    Congrats on a well deserved piece: @Weebly CEO David Rusenko (@drusenko): It’s Time to Take Us Seriously http://dthin.gs/In3RNm     
    
    
    Cool: Dr Oz talking @Fitbit Ultra on his show in the context of tracking steps & calories - path to greater longevity http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K440HlblzUY&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    @cdixon do it - it was an awesome movie, definitely worth it    
    
    
    “@andefred: I know I'm late, but huge congrats to @slideshare team and investors (@davemcclure @cape @robinklein) among others.” +1    
    
    
    “@levie: 5 simple things America should 10X: math/science education, immigration, next-gen manufacturing, R&D funding, startups” Ditto    
    
    
    Awesome @roviomobile Rovio's Big Year: Angry Birds Helps Company Soar To $106M In Sales, 648M Downloads http://techcrunch.com/2012/05/07/rovios-big-year-angry-birds-helps-gaming-company-soar-to-106m-in-sales648m-downloads/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Apple linked with $113 million acquisition of German television manufacturer Loewe http://zite.to/J8ySTZ  via @zite    
    
    
    3,997 Models: Android Fragmentation As Seen By The Developers Of OpenSignalMaps http://techcrunch.com/2012/05/15/3997-models-android-fragmentation-as-seen-by-the-developers-of-opensignalmaps/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    New @Newsweek cover: "when I grow up I'm going to weigh 300 lbs - help !" pic.twitter.com/MoYpRqsV    
    
    
    @appnation:  mobile time spent: apps almost same as web, 73% on top 50 apps, 50% users on smartphones (up from 38%) - http://tcrn.ch/KlYHBU     
    
    
    @danprimack Thanks :) We are still under quiet period - It's a team effort with @speechu and @rquintini    
    
    
    Google Chrome (32.8%) Passed Internet Explorer (31.9%) as World's Most Popular Browser - Mozilla third (25%) - http://www.businessinsider.com/google-overtakes-internet-explorer-as-most-popular-browser-2012-5?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Great panel tonight w @shulygalili @UpWestLabs @naval @jeff discussing int'l investments http://bit.ly/IZnFFg     
    
    
    @msuster @karaswisher excited about DX2012 - that's a great hat :)    
    
    
    @msuster: The Seven Signs the Tech Industry is Poised for Major Innovation - http://bothsid.es/Ltw  + new technologies still in infancy    
    
    
    "faced w impossible, no harm in trying" German teen Shouryya Ray solves 300-yr mathematical riddle by Newton - http://zite.to/KVdljl  @zite    
    
    
    @rojajimmy I was just reporting the article as is - other lessons are importance of disregard for status quo, math, education & immigration    
    
    
    Tim Cook at D10 - double down on secrecy but more transparent on social responsibility    
    
    
    Tim Cook highlights: focus, culture of excellence, joy is in the journey, never follow the herd, can a product change someone's behavior    
    
    
    Spot on: RT @lindaavey: Larry Ellison "we need an enlightened immigration policy". #atd10    
    
    
    Ellison highlights on Jobs #atd10 "work on a solution until its insanely great" "liked intense debate b/c passion is measure of commitment"    
    
    
    More on Jobs #atd10 adaptability, single mindedness, inspire great performance, making a point w action vs mere words    
    
    
    Cool Jobs comment today: rather than just saying "talent matters" he designs a monument in new Pixar bldg 2 show appreciation #atd10    
    
    
    @saadventures say hi to my hometown, would love to debrief when you return :)    
    
    
    Remain humble - success must be earned; luck is always some part of it (though it's never obvious how much no matter how we rationalize it)    
    
    
    @jackabraham @emilyolson @hnshah thank you for the retweet - I was inspired by Mike Lewis commencement speech at Princeton    
    
    
    @rohit_x_ absolutely agreed    
    
    
    @jellyfishbloom @dylan20 @jay_jamison @joshelman pleasure was mutual - awesome panel & audience (I wish I took a photo) #glimpseconf    
    
    
    @Heart-felt Thank you ! @jackabraham @peterpham @akothari @erineturner @joshelman @ManuKumar @rohit_x @shulygalili cc @speechu @rquintini    
    
    
    @arijacoby @currypacker @imcharliegraham @mickhagen - grateful to work with great founders like yourselves :)    
    
    
    @rydonahue Thanks again - real pleasure to be in your syndicate and have a chance to work with you - much appreciated    
    
    
    @jamiequint @bwertz @ssubo - thank you ! really appreciate it    
    
    
    @firatdemirel Yerel kurucularda @SinaAfra ve @demetsmutlu - yatirimcilarda da @csertoglu ve @baris a saygim var. Olur mu degil ne zaman :)    
    
    
    Really humbled by our amazing team, friends, founders and my family's support - the bar is set so much higher now...back to work    
    
    
    @infoarbitrage Thank you !    
    
    
    @satyap thank you - exciting times, looking forward to the journey ahead - would love to connect    
    
    
    @rashmi thank you and belated congrats to you as well !    
    
    
    @adsiegel @howardlinzon @neerajarora @izhararmony - Thanks !    
    
    
    Doubling down on innovation with a boutique approach: http://bit.ly/Lxbm7N     
    
    
    Looking forward to a great VC roundtable panel tomorrow night at Churchill Club: http://bit.ly/HIexYO  with @billmaris @timechange & others    
    
    
    @jimscheinman @shobeir @royrod - belated thanks - appreciate the tweet !    
    
    
    @jasonmok @andrewspoeth @jwein75 thanks for the tweets, nice dialog / panel last night at @churchillclub    
    
    
    To the winner go the spoils: Apple & Samsung account for 90% of smartphone profits and 55% market share: http://news.cnet.com/8301-13579_3-57453949-37/apple-samsung-again-swallow-all-the-smartphone-profits/ …    
    
    
    Interview w @SebastianThrun: What's Next for SV - "Question all the rules, break all the rules"- http://on.wsj.com/KO7POz  via @WSJ    
    
    
    Happy fathers day !    
    
    
    “@arstechnica: With 16 petaflops & 1.6M cores, DOE supercomputer is world’s fastest http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/06/with-16-petaflops-and-1-6m-cores-doe-supercomputer-is-worlds-fastest/ …” 1st time for US since '09    
    
    
    @karaswisher @lizgannes felt like a natural on the red chair, clearly it's inspiring :)    
    
    
    @massivehealth Eatery app shows promise for hacking eating behavior http://www.technologyreview.com/news/428272/app-shows-promise-for-hacking-eating-behavior/ … cc @aza    
    
    
    Cool insights in @AppAnnie s great new infographic - http://www.appannie.com/media/pictures/marketing/infographic_game_of_phones.png … (US, UK, JP revenue champs, iOS & Googleplay tied for rev growth)    
    
    
    “@soniaarrison: Alzheimer's, Parkinson's, more -- due to infectious proteins? http://www.latimes.com/health/boostershots/la-heb-alzheimers-parkinsons-infectious-proteins-20120622,0,7835124.story …” could a different cure be found this way    
    
    
    Barrage of announcements today, Project Glass & 1M Android activations / day - Glad to see more innovation and solid stats from Google    
    
    
    Congrats to @gmail - largest email service in the world w 425M active users; great memories as an early alpha user - http://venturebeat.com/2012/06/28/gmail-hotmail-yahoo-email-users/ …    
    
    
    LinkedIn seems to be down... pic.twitter.com/ZidFiYSX    
    
    
    @levie I was wondering what's going on, thx for the clarification :)    
    
    
    Deeply grateful to the US for a grt education, 1st big break, the chance to start a company & the sweetest family ever - Happy 4th of July !    
    
    
    Amazon crafting an iPhone competitor? According to people w knowledge of plans at work at Foxconn - http://pulse.me/s/aZatk     
    
    
    "A 'no' uttered from the deepest conviction is better than a 'yes' merely uttered to please, or worse, to avoid trouble." - Mahatma Gandhi    
    
    
    George Bernard Shaw: "Some people see things as they are and say, why ? I dream things that never were and say, why not ?" - So true    
    
    
    Meraki Plans To Conquer Enterprise Wi-Fi, Hire Like Crazy With $40M In New Funding http://techcrunch.com/2012/07/10/meraki-40-million/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Rovio’s Amazing Alex has already hit the #1 paid spot on Apple’s App Store http://tnw.to/c1j6  via @TNWapps    
    
    
    Spool is joining Facebook http://wp.me/p20JJz-4d  - congrats @avichal @spool ! Cc @speechu    
    
    
    Good luck Marissa ! @marissamayer - [on becoming] Yahoo's new CEO: http://ow.ly/chhPY     
    
    
    “@FortuneMagazine: Thiel vs. Schmidt: The fireworks fly http://bit.ly/Mrvg3F ” I would have loved to see this one live    
    
    
    @mwseibel @socialcamapp team congrats on the acquisition by Autodesk; it's been an incredible journey since early days of Justin.tv    
    
    
    After 2 days in the hospital & having a 2nd son, I really appreciate doctors & nurses. They make what we do look like a walk in the park.    
    
    
    @todsacerdoti nice job on reach and ads served with Brightroll - http://tod.ly/NWxPw1     
    
    
    @shervin @akothari Thanks !    
    
    
    @satyap Thanks - we are overdue    
    
    
    @mickhagen @stalbs @eileentso @rfradin really appreciate the tweets - feeling truly blessed :)    
    
    
    Congrats to the @outright team: GoDaddy Acquires Cloud-Based, Financial Management Application Company Outright - http://tcrn.ch/NO1XpH     
    
    
    Wine Site Lot18 Downsizes Again: UK Operations To Shut Down This Week http://lnkd.in/bZ2Qqh     
    
    
    The World Will Soon Have More Phones Than Humans http://lnkd.in/E9b64u     
    
    
    Nicely done: @PeHub: @ManuKumar Raises $40M @K9 Ventures Fund II http://www.pehub.com/159774/manu-kumar-raises-40-million-k9-ventures-second-fund/ …    
    
    
    This looks amazing - impossible not to want one, just add a jet ski: http://jetovator.com/     
    
    
    Nicely done @bwertz - Canadian Angel Boris Wertz Raises $15 Million To Launch Micro-VC Fund Version One Ventures http://tcrn.ch/LLdzhI     
    
    
    McDonald's Jobs Taught Bezos, Leno And Others 7 Big Lessons - Forbes http://onforb.es/MUlFRp     
    
    
    Talent management insights by @stanine : Want to hire the right team? Exhaust your interviewees http://dlvr.it/1wG5q1  via @gigaom    
    
    
    A Cautionary Tale (striking stat: iPhone Revs > all MSFT revenues in Q1-2012): Microsoft's Lost Decade  http://www.vanityfair.com/business/2012/08/microsoft-lost-mojo-steve-ballmer … via @VanityFair    
    
    
    Huge congrats to @victoria_ransom & @wildfireapp team ! Well deserved: Google [acquires] Wildfire - http://www.pehub.com/161367/google-catches-wildfire/ … cc @davemcclure    
    
    
    Congrats to our largest education investment: @MindSnacks Nabs $6.5M From Sequoia To Bring Educational Games To Mobile http://techcrunch.com/2012/08/02/mindsnacks-series-a/ …    
    
    
    @bwertz @chrija @bigs @ivospigel @stevejang @manukumar - thank you ! really appreciate it !    
    
    
    Via @quixotic Why our school system isn't geared to produce innovators, yet a few standouts show what needs to change: http://lnkd.in/UkYYY6     
    
    
    MIT Robotics Lab, self flying model plane in tight confined spaces via @gigaom - http://gigaom.com/2012/08/09/its-a-bird-its-a-plane-its-an-mit-self-guided-robot/?utm_source=pulsenews&utm_medium=referral&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+OmMalik+%28GigaOM%3A+Tech%29 …    
    
    
    mhealth future in India & China, huge potential but also sizeable challenges: http://digital-medicine.blogspot.in/2012/08/indians-expect-to-lead-mhealth.html?m=1 … cc @speechu    
    
    
    Where do olympians go after their olympic career is over ? Cirque du Soleil (it already has 50 ex Olympians) - http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10000872396390443477104577550890871154880.html …    
    
    
    Great piece by @insightio - "Fear of Money" - http://influencehacks.com/fear-of-money     
    
    
    Why I'm so bullish on @cardspring: "Payment Data (& tracking it to web source) Is More Valuable Than Payment Fees" http://techcrunch.com/2012/08/18/payment-data-is-more-valuable-than-payment-fees/ …    
    
    
    US government invests $30M in a new 3D printing center - http://m.smartplanet.com/blog/business-brains/us-government-invests-30-million-in-new-3d-printing-center/25817 … thx to @soniaarrison for the tip    
    
    
    (With its market cap hitting $623B today) Apple overtakes Microsoft as most valuable stock of all time http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2012/08/20/apple-overtakes-microsoft-as-most-valuable-stock-of-all-time/ … @Fortunemagazine    
    
    
    Excited to be on board: " @vicariousinc Raises $15M Led By Dustin Moskovitz To Build SW That ‘Learns Like A Human’" -  http://tcrn.ch/RdmCcE     
    
    
    @roviohq opens new Santa Monica office, adds vets from Tumblr & MM http://tnw.to/k399  also teams up w Green Day http://rov.io/RbFDfs     
    
    
    Why wheat is so addictive (raises blood sugar higher than candy) and should be avoided - http://www2.macleans.ca/2011/09/20/on-the-evils-of-wheat-why-it-is-so-addictive-and-how-shunning-it-will-make-you-skinny/ … via @soniaarrison    
    
    
    Fascinating: The Nokia effect (9 companies whose revenues exceed 20% of resident country's GDP) - http://econ.st/SZtXtz  via @theeconomist    
    
    
    Exciting ! "@hfizzle: Introducing the New @Shopify for iPhone — eCommerce Blog by @Shopify http://bit.ly/PeFHaP "    
    
    
    Really excited about team Tynker is building: "@currypacker: We are hiring at our new startup Tynker (http://tynker.com/jobs )"    
    
    
    Scientists invent micro particles that oxygenate blood without breathing for up to 30 mins: http://www.techwench.com/scientists-invent-oxygen-particle-that-if-injected-allows-you-to-live-without-breathing/ …    
    
    
    from a book by navy seal sniper @brandontwebb: "Whatever it is that you do, you're making a stand, either for mediocrity or for excellence"    
    
    
    Really proud of the @clearslide team: ClearSlide Lands $28 Million in Round Led by Bessemer http://dthin.gs/RlrsR6     
    
    
    Really proud of @soniaarrison today: her book 100+ has won the 4th annual Living Now book award in aging: http://www.independentpublisher.com/article.php?page=1577 …    
    
    
    "Do things that have never been done before" - inspiring quote for Labor Day - via @joelrunyon (thx @pdurlej) http://bit.ly/MLK4OD     
    
    
    Nice ! @venturebeat:  @Shopify teams up with ShipStation to shave hours off delivery time - http://tinyurl.com/d9ssmxl  cc @tobi @hfizzle    
    
    
    @jack at TC Disrupt "Life happens at the intersections"    
    
    
        
    
    
    Awesome piece on http://Baby.com.br  in Forbes - Brazil's Dot-Com Gold Rush - http://onforb.es/O4n5cw  cc @kimballthomas @davismsmith    
    
    
    Researchers Turn Book Into DNA Code [potential for storing the whole internet on a drive the size of thumb] - http://on.wsj.com/P12jeP  via @WSJ    
    
    
    Congrats to @abitlucky team ! (Felicis Exit #35) - Zynga Buys A Bit Lucky To Break Into Mid-Core Gaming http://techcrunch.com/2012/09/17/zynga-acquisition-a-bit-lucky/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @RobK the whole 35 listed here: http://www.felicis.com/portfolio-acquired/ …    
    
    
    Congrats to the @SoundHound  team on passing the 100 million user mark ! - http://thenextweb.com/apps/2012/09/20/soundhound-passes-100-million-user-milestone/ …    
    
    
    Clearly one of PG's best essays, a must read: http://paulgraham.com/growth.html  via @paulg    
    
    
    Google market cap tops Microsoft's http://edition.cnn.com/2012/10/01/business/google-microsoft/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    @ardakutsal guclu program, bu kadar sene sonra Istanbul'a gelip, gelismeleri gorup, yarin karsilikli notlari paylasmak cok guzel :)    
    
    
    @ericmigi so nice to see you in Istanbul and get a glimpse of first Pebble in the wild :) pic.twitter.com/y12fgDxb    
    
    
    Congrats to @1000memories team, another exit for @felicisventures: http://Ancestry.com  acquires 1000 Memories - http://blog.1000memories.com/170-ancestry-acquires-1000memories …    
    
    
    really excited about the awesome fireside chat this morning with @ardakutsal at #webrazzi12 - http://summit.webrazzi.com/2012/en     
    
    
    @nesetdereli @sevnurm @fulyakim @TK_TR Super, tesekkurler - bunu yapalim (let's make it happen ;)    
    
    
    Great way to wrap up an awesome Istanbul trip, with a panel including @jeff @pkedrosky - burgeoning entrepreneurship & tech investing scene    
    
    
    I cant wait ! Nice gallery of shots from the #AngryBirdsStarWars event in Times Sq. http://bit.ly/RqGXZI  via @angrybirds    
    
    
    Lovely Goes From Craigslist Target To The Kayak Of Apartment Rentals As It Launches Nationwide http://techcrunch.com/2012/10/09/lovely-goes-from-craigslist-target-to-the-kayak-of-apartment-rentals-as-it-launches-nationwide/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    @shopify: over 35K active stores, $1B+ in products sold across 13M+ orders in 100+ countries cc @hfizzle @tobi - http://www.shopify.com/blog/6695662-1-billion …    
    
    
    @baris @ozantatar @numan @elbruzyilmaz @evrenertunc @sevnurm @cagricy @fatmagulguzel @selinkurtbilek & others tweets icin tesekkurler !    
    
    
    @pvesterbacka can't wait for new announcements - you guys are killing it :) See you in Helsinki in November ! #Slush12 cc @slushhq    
    
    
    Great piece on why employment matters by @adamlashinsky (&why we must fight over regulation and invest in education) - http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2012/10/12/work/ …    
    
    
    I wish I could see this live - Felix Baumgartners record breaking sky dive (Redbull Stratos), 128K ft, 706mph WOW - http://m.cnet.com/photos/felix-baumgartners-historic-skydive-pictures/10014153 …    
    
    
    "@stalbs: Not at all. RT @coolmomtech: Is it wrong that we have our calendars marked for Angry Birds Star Wars? http://ow.ly/esBEN " Agreed    
    
    
    @davetisch - you're fast, I'm right behind you: proud to back Romo - The Smartphone Robot for Everyone on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/RzTgGc     
    
    
    Romotive turns all iPhones into Robots http://www.businessinsider.com/romotive-turns-iphones-into-robots-and-raises-5-million-2012-10?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    “@RMB: Once again, the biggest winner of the Presidential debate was...@twitter. The tweet flow volume was insane!” agreed    
    
    
    So many reasons to be grateful and happy today: world's best family, two big smiles by my sons + most awesome companies in our portfolio    
    
    
    @johnolilly thank you ! Definitely agreed - their smiles & love are priceless    
    
    
    Correlation btw a country's level of chocolate consumption and its total number of Nobel laureates per capita? http://www.nejm.org/doi/full/10.1056/NEJMon1211064 …    
    
    
    Jeff Bezos: The Smart People Change Their Minds -  http://techcrunch.com/2012/10/19/jeff-bezos-the-smart-people-change-their-minds/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    Happy Halloween ! pic.twitter.com/wpdNYzix    
    
    
    Really excited to be on board: @DollarShaveClub Raises $9.8M, Launches In Canada http://techcrunch.com/2012/11/01/dollar-shave-club-funding/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "I Voted 2012" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/SL7xzm     
    
    
    Feels great to vote (@ Voting at 299 Alameda De Las Pulgas) http://4sq.com/SL7xzo     
    
    
    Incredible speech by Obama - graceful and moving speech by Romney; I couldn't be prouder to be a citizen of this country today...    
    
    
    Felicis portfolio company @wildfireapp mentioned in El Erian's letter to the President on how to fix the economy - http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2012/11/07/mohamed-el-erian/ …    
    
    
    @peterpham @karl still buzzing from the high bandwidth conversations - always a blast.    
    
    
    Feel The Force: Angry Birds Star Wars Tops U.S. App Store In Record 2.5 Hours, Says Rovio http://techcrunch.com/2012/11/09/feel-the-force-angry-birds-star-wars-tops-u-s-app-store-in-record-2-5-hours-says-rovio/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @ardakutsal @baris @fisbecer @TK_TR THY'a cok tesekkur borcluyum - hakkaten cok etkileyici SF seferini bu kisa zamanda gerceklestirmeleri    
    
    
    thank you @SVB_Financial really psyched to meet chess prodigy @magnuscarlsen    
    
    
    Awesome meeting chess prodigy @magnuscarlsen tonight in support of chess for 2nd & 3rd graders / cc @af4c_Firstmove    
    
    
    Congrats to @lovely for their new iPhone app that was featured by Apple - http://itun.es/us/VJGvI.i  #lovelyapp    
    
    
    AWESOME: Angry Birds Star Wars joins forces with Lotus F1 team during inaugural US GP: http://bit.ly/T51kfv  cc #pvesterbacka #roviohq    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/zQ6Zl6jr    
    
    
    Congrats to the @meraki team ! http://techcrunch.com/2012/11/18/cisco-acquires-enterprise-wi-fi-startup-meraki-for-1-2-billion-in-cash/ … - so proud to be an investor from the very beginning & proud of our 37th exit to date    
    
    
    @pvesterbacka great seeing you @startupsauna, @RovioHQ and at Aito tonight. You are the best marketer in the world & a gracious host to boot    
    
    
    @deekay @bwertz @Baris @dpatil thank you !    
    
    
    @MikiKuusi @andynosebone thanks for the hospitality, great dinner ! Looking forward to an awesome #slush12 tomorrow - on stage & off stage !    
    
    
    Congrats @alt12apps on the launch: integrated mobile store for moms - http://tnw.to/i0YSc  via @thenextweb cc @speechu #babybump #pinkpad    
    
    
    @speechu: Go Shopify! @techvibes: Shopify Tops List of Cyber Monday Destinations Behind Only Amazon & eBay http://ht.ly/fAj5P  cc @hfizzle    
    
    
    Let me know what's on your mind... Looking forward to Ask A VC today with @leenarao - http://techcrunch.com/2012/12/03/ask-a-vc-is-back-with-felicis-ventures-aydin-senkut/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @tobi @hfizzle congrats on reaching the 40K mark ! That is truly awesome ! cc @speechu    
    
    
    @hnshah @mishachellam @nowentrepreneur - Thanks ! @leenarao rocked it on TCTV - it was awesome to be her guest    
    
    
    @ryantate federated mobile apps & universal access (ie all mobile platforms) is plain good strategy - no big success w/o breaking some rules    
    
    
    Inspiring news amidst a tough weekend given the CT news: BBC News - Paralysed woman's thoughts control robotic arm http://bbc.in/V2iQVf     
    
    
    Congrats to Jesse, Ooshma, Emmett, Sujay, Jack, Alex, David, Dan and Adam ! 9 Felicis Founders in Forbes 30 Under 30 - http://onforb.es/Th1v8Q     
    
    
    We measure our success by one successful founder at a time, by each great portfolio company built and by founder dreams realized - Rock on !    
    
    
    Merry Christmas & Happy Holidays ! Wishing everyone more love, peace, success and happiness along with more health to enjoy for many years !    
    
    
    “@davidhornik: Pretty impressive -- 10% of Sundance films this year were Kickstarter funded: http://www.kickstarter.com/year/2012 ” surprising    
    
    
    @johnolilly happy birthday ! Keep up the good micro habits :)    
    
    
    Angry Birds-Maker Rovio Crossed 263M Monthly Active Users Last Month http://techcrunch.com/2013/01/11/rovio-263-million-users-december/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Dept of Homeland Security recommends disabling java in browsers (half of '12 vulnerabilities were related to Java) - http://nyti.ms/VGBBi2     
    
    
    I stand w/ @SandyHook. I'm making the #SandyHookPromise to keep my communitynity & country safer from violence: http://www.sandyhookpromise.org/promise?recruiter_id=37858 …    
    
    
    Top Hat Monocle Adds $1.1M Follow-On from Felicis to Reimagine The Lecture Hall Experience - http://tcrn.ch/SgRECw  cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    1.6 billion mobile phones shipped in 2012: Samsung ships 396.5M, Apple ships 135.8M | VentureBeat http://venturebeat.com/2013/01/25/1-6-billion-mobile-phones-shipped-in-2012-samsung-ships-396-5m-apple-ships-135-8m/#BkM5oziG5FKliR0r.02 … via @VentureBeat    
    
    
    Congrats @tivli on being in NY Times - we think you are the future of TV - http://www.nytimes.com/2013/01/28/business/media/tivli-puts-streaming-tv-on-campus.html?_r=1& …    
    
    
    @henniemartens @ichevan - the main surprise of the global shipment # was that Samsung number represented ~25% of the total...    
    
    
    Congrats to @PracticeFusion on an IxD award winning #iPad design for 2013 w @cooper ! http://youtu.be/r_XQvOWRadw  cc @felicisventures @speechu    
    
    
    Ambitious Startup Wish Aims to Outsmart the Business of Online Shopping http://dthin.gs/11naPKi  cc @contextlogic @felicisventures @speechu    
    
    
    Excited to see @PracticeFusion on this 101 billboard near #SFO via @NetSuite - pic.twitter.com/AjnHAdqZ cc @felicisventures @speechu    
    
    
    @eladgil on key qualities of BD people; add 1 ability to figure out key targets/customers & relentless prioritization - http://blog.eladgil.com/2013/02/hiring-great-business-people-is-hard.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    “If you want something you’ve never had, you must be willing to do something you’ve never done.” Thomas Jefferson - via @azumioinc    
    
    
    @3DersOrg: Startup Matterport's low-cost 3D scanner raises nearly $4M http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130202-startup-matterports-low-cost-3d-scanner-project-raises-nearly-$4m.html … #3dscanning cc @speechu @greylockvc @eisenberg    
    
    
    @mcgd @levie or math ?    
    
    
    $ZNGA (3K employees -> 200M cashflow) vs @minecraft (29 employees -> half of that) + resilient to copycats - http://on.wsj.com/W9UacR  via @WSJ    
    
    
    Rovio as poster child of innovation in Nordics via @Economist http://econ.st/14eBMUV  cc @felicisventures @rwong @roviohq    
    
    
    Congrats @aza - Massive Health has been acquired by Jawbone. Here's to revolutionizing health! http://gigaom.com/2013/02/04/jawbone-buys-visera-massivehealth-to-marry-data-design-with-wearable-computing/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    @lheron: Globally, ave. time spent on Facebook dropped 2% last year. In Brazil, it grew 208%! (Via @wsj) http://on.wsj.com/UVwBp0  cc @rquintini    
    
    
    Force is strong(er) in ESPN: according to WSJ, Disneys 80% stake values ESPN at $40B, 10x what it paid for Lucasfilm http://www.studiobriefing.net/2013/02/report-espn-is-disneys-biggest-asset-by-far/ …    
    
    
    Nice job @brightroll - BrightRoll Wins SIIA CODiE Award for Best Advertising Management Platform: http://www.brightroll.com/press-release/brightroll-wins-siia-codie-award-for-best-advertising-management-platform/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    @hunterwalk and @satyap congrats on Homebrew ! - http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2013/02/06/google-twitter-vc-fund/ …    
    
    
    This is really cool: check startup salaries / equity by job, department, focus, geo, etc - nice job @angellist: http://ow.ly/hrB1X     
    
    
    Celebrating the 100th birthday of my wife @soniaarrison's grandfather tonight - his secret ? be positive & physically active #centenarian    
    
    
    #Microsoft must be getting really desperate - "Google going through every word of every Gmail ?" on a WSJ ad pic.twitter.com/v0lcHyUf    
    
    
    @azumioinc named in the World's Top 10 Most Innovative Companies in Mobile at #4 - http://www.fastcompany.com/most-innovative-companies/2013/industry/mobile … cc @felicisventures @speechu    
    
    
    @todsacerdoti: Fast Company names @BrightRoll as one of its 2013 Most Innovative Companies - http://tod.ly/YmYST8 ” cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    120M people visited Apple Stores almost as many as 125M Visitors at Disney's Theme Parks in 2011 - http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/02/the-real-tomorrowland-apple-stores-get-almost-as-many-visitors-as-disneys-theme-parks/273093/ …    
    
    
    @inkling crushing it with Habitat launch: Bloomberg @BW "Building a better ebook than Amazon and Apple" http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-02-12/building-a-better-e-book-than-amazon-and-apple … cc @stanine    
    
    
    @OguzSerdar that 1 question is key for both how well a skill is mastered and if 1 can also explain it w equal ease - http://bit.ly/15cF5wl     
    
    
    Nothing speaks louder than a CEO doubling down: Mark Zuckerberg ups stake in Facebook http://mashable.com/2013/02/14/mark-zuckerberg-facebook-shares/ … via @mashable @MattGoldenVP    
    
    
    @sacca neither math nor all the books in the world can make you good in delivering those awesome stories; that's where charisma comes in...    
    
    
    This awesome Larry Page Q&A reminded me of early Google days - 10x is a philosophy to live by - http://www.wired.com/business/2013/01/ff-qa-larry-page/all/ …    
    
    
    Congrats @jackabraham: 1 yr later our work is shipping to 10s of millions as eBay's new home page - http://m.techcrunch.com/2013/02/18/pulling-from-more-than-400m-listings-ebays-pinterest-like-new-personalized-home-page-experience-rolls-out-tomorrow/ …    
    
    
    Felicis Ventures #2 for most exits among VCs in 2012 according to new PrivCo study: http://www.privco.com/top-20-venture-capital-firms-with-the-most-private-tech-company-exits-in-2012 … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    China becomes the world’s largest smartphone market in Feb '13 (246M devices vs 230M in US) - http://venturebeat.com/2013/02/18/china-becomes-the-worlds-largest-smartphone-market/#uVcKVJPqDke76MK2.02 … via @VentureBeat    
    
    
    Staying Competitive, the @GoogleVentures Way (excited to be co-investors in exciting projects !) -  http://on.mktw.net/XC5aRR   cc @kraneland    
    
    
    @prismatic @mikequity @fevzigungor @RMB @sraney @pejmannozad Thank you ! cc @speechu @rquintini    
    
    
    @sachinrekhi nice post: 1 of the Most Underrated Product Management Skills period: Influence Without Authority - http://bit.ly/YCBlhg     
    
    
    Congrats: Online Art Seller [@Artspace] Eyes Wider Market http://on.wsj.com/135s046  via @WSJ cc @alex01 @rquintini @felicisventures    
    
    
    Congrats to the winners of Breakthrough Prize for Life Sciences - full speed ahead to cure major diseases http://www.forbes.com/sites/matthewherper/2013/02/20/billionaires-anoint-biogeeks/ … @Forbes    
    
    
    @naval love the new @angellist office and really enjoyed catching up today - pure awesomeness pic.twitter.com/RXUDmIkjfc    
    
    
    Congrats @ajaykam @himani - @wedding party seed announced today (glad to be part of it) - http://techcrunch.com/2013/02/21/wedding-party-the-mobile-app-that-lets-guests-contribute-photos-to-gorgeous-shared-albums-scores-a-million-dollar-seed-round/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    @davismsmith cool piece on the origins of @Babynaweb & entrepreneurial advice on @whartonjournal - http://whartonjournal.com/?p=348  cc @rquintini    
    
    
    @dnanexus on @wired DNA Crunchers Ditch Hadoop for Homegrown Software - http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/02/genetic-data-glut/ … via @ManuKumar cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Great piece on When to Sell Your Company [or not] — by @ev — Medium http://bit.ly/12Oswry  via @loic    
    
    
        
    
    
    @danprimack Come on, don't trivialize Google Glass [from the same group as Google driverless cars;] the other 2 lag by far on innovation    
    
    
    @Romotive nice coverage on @USATODAY ! You're so unique in the robotics space - http://www.usatoday.com/story/tech/2012/11/12/robots-irobot-romotive-bossa-nova/1695383/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    By end '13, US deportations under Mr. Obama to reach 2M nearly same as from 1892 to 1997 on @nytimes http://www.nytimes.com/2013/02/23/us/advocates-push-obama-to-halt-aggressive-deportation-efforts.html …  via @MParekh    
    
    
    Mozilla launches with 18 carriers its Firefox OS for mobile at #MWC - http://blog.mozilla.org/blog/2013/02/24/mozilla-unlocks-the-power-of-the-web-on-mobile-with-firefox-os/ … http://www.techmeme.com/130224/p13#a130224p13 … via @Techmeme    
    
    
    World's oldest (101 !) marathon runner runs last race - what an inspiration for living beyond 100 http://us.cnn.com/2013/02/25/world/marathon-man-retires/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter … cc @soniaarrison    
    
    
    Looking forward 2 c @KellerRinaudo: Excited & a little nervous to be starting off TED 2013 by talking about robots... http://wp.me/p10512-htp     
    
    
    My first time meeting someone whose relatives founded a country - pretty cool - it's so key to just show up and spread good karma...    
    
    
    @cdixon interesting stat - 350M global PC shipment vs 215M smartphones Samsung shipped alone - 5th horseman ?    
    
    
    @cdixon plus they're innovating increasingly more on the product front    
    
    
    @KellerRinaudo awesome job on stage with @romotive - very inspiring ! #TED2013 cc @felicisventures - the future of personal robotics !    
    
    
    Bono: "we are going to win because the power of people is stronger than the people in power" #TED2013 pic.twitter.com/iWxTCjqPoq    
    
    
    @PracticeFusion Buys Predictive Modeling Start-Up 100Plus - via @Forbes http://onforb.es/XG5qfZ  cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    @garrytan or turn them into lemonades :)    
    
    
    +1 @sonnyvu @PracticeFusion @cwhogg we are very proud to be backers of both @ryanhoward and @cwhogg cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Looking forward to an awesome panel shortly on venture innovation trends at @morganstanley Tech conf. w @peterthiel @RonConway & @chamath    
    
    
    @MattRosoff thank you !    
    
    
    @bauhausvc @jgrankvist @aronsolomon thank you - appreciate the support :)    
    
    
    Psyched about the new @felicisventures website & branding; aspiring for a new level of design & transparency in VC http://www.felicis.com     
    
    
    @robin_solis check out our portfolio section - we are the first to indicate stage of investment for every company ;)    
    
    
    @mnshah absolutely    
    
    
    @tedesign @gniting @mikequity @bwertz @eileentso @leonnyc419 thank you ! Really appreciate the feedback & comments :)    
    
    
    @mamoonha @draaliya equally important a mans choice of wife - lucky to be married to my better half for almost 7 years now :) @soniaarrison    
    
    
    @mattcutts - remember when the index size was in billions ? info-graphic on Google search (30 Trillion pgs indexed) http://goo.gl/VNRXR ”    
    
    
    @BryanKChang @eileentso @nickbaum is doing an amazing job working with our founders, the site design is our own ;) as is our interior design    
    
    
    @bryankchang @eileentso @nickbaum however we did have a great team help us build the new site, icons & typography - colors match our office    
    
    
    Africa's consumer spending to double in 10 yrs & is fastest growing continent via @rellimluap @TheEconomist  - http://www.economist.com/news/leaders/21572773-pride-africas-achievements-should-be-coupled-determination-make-even-faster …    
    
    
    @todsacerdoti nice article on @brightroll in @peHUB 220 people now, remember when it was 4 http://dlvr.it/30bXlb  cc @jeff @felicisventures    
    
    
    Fascinating: @ramez A wireless, free-roaming, implantable 100-neuron brain-computer-interface at @brownuniversity http://ow.ly/ibn14     
    
    
    @clairecmc working on "getting the ban on using in-flight portable electronic devices lifted" via @TheEconomist http://www.economist.com/blogs/gulliver/2013/02/electronic-devices-planes?fb_ref=activity …    
    
    
    Huge thanks to @stanine @tobi and the indefatigable @pvesterbacka for inspiring us with great branding & design cc @hfizzle @stalbs    
    
    
    Apps economy grows by 62% to hit $25B - prompting @WSJ to launch dedicated site - @Jessicalessin: Announcing, http://WSJ.com/Apps     
    
    
    At an awesome intl entrepreneurship dinner hosted by @burtonlee with guests of honor Prezi's @peterarvai and @pvesterbacka of @RovioHQ    
    
    
    Congrats to @Clearslide on its first acquisition @sliderocket from VMware http://techcrunch.com/2013/03/05/vmware-exits-collaboration-market-with-sale-of-sliderocket-to-clearslide/ … via@techcrunch cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Another gorgeous app, Applauze (for events) from @955dreams and passing 4.6M downloads by @allthingsd http://dthin.gs/Z7dYQv  cc @smalldozes    
    
    
    @davemorin @path great job bringing on Kim Jabal as CFO - http://allthingsd.com/20130306/path-hires-ex-google-lytro-finance-head-as-new-cfo/ … via @allthingsd cc @dylancasey    
    
    
    Radio Gets Its 'Second Screen' in @SoundHound (130M+ downloads) with Dial Global Partnership - http://adage.com/article/media/radio-screen-soundhound-dial-pact/240153/ … va @adage    
    
    
    @FareedZakaria: Washington spends $73B on defense research, $31B on healthcare & just $3B on energy http://ti.me/15zGR9P  via @ramez    
    
    
    Via @danmartell: Don't Launch by @ericries http://buff.ly/YfMRyq  (some great insights that are not obvious - great post)    
    
    
    Excited to see future of 3D both @matterport @Floored3D in the @WSJ http://blogs.wsj.com/venturecapital/2013/03/07/matterports-3-d-scanner-faces-marketing-challenge/ … via @Eisenberg cc @felicisventures @speechu    
    
    
    Intl Womens Day honoring our founders @victoria_ransom @adwane @ladylexy @clarashih @ilana_stern @poojanathsankar @sandraohlin @emilyolson..    
    
    
    Coffee nirvana - meeting with @tonysphere at @bluebottleroast at mint plaza - about to experience a surprise ciphon creation    
    
    
    Sharing Economy (is here to stay) on the cover of Economist this week with quotes from @mill at @wheelz & @davidlee pic.twitter.com/oiYdHecfxE    
    
    
    @brandWendy: @elonmusk takeaway: you can have great achievement but if you aren’t having fun… life sucks. Agreed.    
    
    
    @dmac1 agree with main premise here but predicting 100 yrs doesn't take into account generational leadership change effects    
    
    
    Fascinating: 10 oldest companies still in existence 1 Beretta (gun maker) 1526, 2 Grolsch (beer), 3 Haig (whiskey) http://listverse.com/2011/08/12/10-oldest-still-operating-companies/ …    
    
    
    Angry Birds at H&M cc @pvesterbacka @RovioHQ @felicisventures pic.twitter.com/nV9HpwC8Qr    
    
    
    Awesome Sunday hike with gorgeous views of the bay - lucky to live here pic.twitter.com/5aU5olSTMV    
    
    
    @ericschmidt : Internet now accounts for 8% of UK GDP, more than any other European country - http://www.standard.co.uk/lifestyle/london-life/could-this-be-londons-moment--when-the-tech-scene-is-really-about-to-explode-8528837.html …    
    
    
    @adamlashinsky just when I was missing out on Homeland, I discovered The Americans - it rocks - http://www.fxnetworks.com/theamericans     
    
    
    “@pkedrosky: Most valuable companies in history, adjusted for inflation (top 2 are trading companies) - http://ca.finance.yahoo.com/photos/most-valuable-companies-ever-adjusted-for-inflation-1351801906-slideshow/most-valuable-companies-in-history-adjusted-for-inflation-photo--1113431046.html …”    
    
    
    MIT @techreview names @factual one of 50 most disruptive companies in 2013 kudos to @gilelbaz & team cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Can't wait: @RidScott of BladeRunner, Alien & Gladiator fame to direct 12 scifi shorts with @Machinima_com http://thenextweb.com/media/2013/03/12/ridley-scott-teams-up-with-machinima-to-produce-12-original-science-fiction-short-films/ …    
    
    
    China building national nextgen Internet - ironically with IP verification for enhanced security http://bit.ly/W5imzU  via @KurzweilAINews    
    
    
    37% of teens use internet via smartphone (up sharply frm '12); 23% mainly do so eschewing a PC - http://www.businessinsider.com/almost-a-quarter-of-us-teens-mainly-use-their-smartphones-to-go-online-2013-3 … via @businessinsider    
    
    
    @CoryBooker at #F.ounders: "see things not as what they are but for they could be" pic.twitter.com/5emVUoXPIM    
    
    
    Google Android's Sundar Pichai - nice profile on WSJ @sundarpichai - http://blogs.wsj.com/digits/2013/03/14/who-is-google-androids-sundar-pichai/ …    
    
    
    F.ounders in NYC @NASDAQ - should be an awesome day pic.twitter.com/zJwdGik0CN    
    
    
    Croods in Times Square - can't wait for the new @AngryBirds game ! cc @pvesterbacka @stalbs @RovioHQ pic.twitter.com/NEYa19pbkw    
    
    
    @smjasmin thank you !    
    
    
    @cathlevene awesome catching up; loved the Peter Doig work on @artspace - didn't know he's from Edinburgh, Scotland pic.twitter.com/pDxqrnLCkb    
    
    
    @startupcfo really excited about the first #F1 race in Melbourne this weekend !    
    
    
    @glassdoor Top 50 CEO survey, #1 is Zuckerberg, only 1 female CEO on list, @VictoriasSecret CEO Sharon Turney - http://www.glassdoor.com/50-Highest-Rated-CEOs.htm …    
    
    
    @bryce @eladgil @erickschonfeld @naval key for $goog is vast resources ie ~billion users & $$$, ability to work w amazing people, still    
    
    
    @gentry @saarsaar congrats - cant wait to see awesome new products as a result: Dropbox acquiring Orchestra - http://gigaom.com/2013/03/15/how-much-did-dropbox-pay-for-mailbox/ …    
    
    
    Happy St Patricks Day ! pic.twitter.com/Tjm3fXSaeu    
    
    
    @moleskine is going public on Mar 18 in Italian stock exchange - 25% EBITDA margins http://econ.st/10ahU3z  via @ttunguz  cc @tobi @hfizzle    
    
    
    @fdestin @lazerow - I couldn't agree more, focusing on right things is absolutely critical -  http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130320211727-1714080-the-1-mistake-entrepreneurs-make …    
    
    
    Youtube passes 1B MAU mark, assumes a lead role on 3 fronts -http://pandodaily.com/2013/03/21/so-much-for-laser-like-focus-how-youtube-is-casually-beating-other-social-networks-on-multiple-fronts/ …”    
    
    
    @IdrisCin @GirisimHaber @emreguzer tesekkurler    
    
    
    @RonDuke @evdemon @dspector much appreciated    
    
    
    @peterpham @sarahcuda expertise is useless unless it can be translated into effective action re http://pandodaily.com/2013/03/22/you-dont-want-experts-you-want-jacks-of-all-trades/ … latest by @bgoldberg    
    
    
    1st @ycombinator d day I've been in '06; ~12 cos, ~60 investors & @justinkan presenting Justin.tv with a gopro like camera attached to him    
    
    
    At @ycombinator Demo Day    
    
    
    Landgrab for messaging apps (users spend more time) like @WhatsApp and Line http://m.us.wsj.com/articles/a/SB10001424127887323466204578382733261211950?mg=reno64-wsj … by @EvelynRusli    
    
    
    @skonnard I signed up for @pluralsight and also super excited about kids programming courses - really nice job !    
    
    
    @ChelseaClinton: Why aren't more women in STEM jobs? How to reframe the debate http://huff.to/YLst9N  - I think it boils down to role models    
    
    
    @VentureBeat: SEC recognizes
@fundersClub as first ever online VC 
http://wp.me/p1re2-2Y1j     
    
    
    @HowardGwin @startupcfo on the contrary, we only focus on partnering w iconic companies not optimizing returns cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Glad to be on board again: @creditkarma raises $30M Series B, for expansion beyond credit monitoring - http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/02/credit-karma-raises-30-million-series-b-becomes-more-like-mint-as-it-expands-beyond-credit-monitoring/ …    
    
    
    Wall Street Journal Turkce - WSJ launches Turkish as its 8th language at http://wsj.com.tr  - http://www.webrazzi.com/2013/04/02/wall-street-journal-turkce/ … via @webrazzi    
    
    
    @maurar: Canada's ‘startup visa’ program (with immediate residency) could cost U.S. in war for talent http://ow.ly/jGH2R  cc @startupcfo    
    
    
    Most ridiculous startup ideas which eventually became successful? http://qr.ae/TiBrL  by @michaelrwolfe via @triketora (1800+ upvotes)    
    
    
    @LeoWid how about skipping ladders altogether and inventing a rocket instead ? Real success never comes from following rules or std quo    
    
    
    @nickbaum congrats on the launch today (http://allthingsd.com/20130403/storyworth-aims-to-elicit-and-record-family-stories/ …): @StoryWorth makes it easy to record family stories. https://www.storyworth.com     
    
    
    @cdixon @sai glad that Sergey hasn't lost any of his pizzazz from the early days    
    
    
    @felicisventures: @RovioHQ  doubles revenues ($195M) and significantly increases profits ($98.5M) in 2012 - http://venturebeat.com/2013/04/03/rovio-doubles-its-revenue-in-2012-on-strong-game-releases-and-consumer-product-sales/ …    
    
    
    @mwseibel @chudson @basevc congrats: http://www.businessinsider.com/most-influential-blacks-in-technology-2013-4?op=1 …    
    
    
    @loic I especially like "le Zidane du web" :) via @SiliconValleyfr - pic.twitter.com/1iVRZhFzi9    
    
    
    Super excited about our 1st piano - a 1962 Rippen Harp upright - it's never too late to learn... pic.twitter.com/gm9ff4pPAn    
    
    
    @cdixon: "Internet is overhyped" Newsweek '95. Shows how hard prediction is. http://www.thedailybeast.com/newsweek/1995/02/26/the-internet-bah.html … - cant think ahead by looking back    
    
    
    @loic it has been too long - we'll fix that :)    
    
    
    @mattcutts that's epic - congrats ! Inspiring    
    
    
    The buffer / scheduling nothing to create time to think & recharge - https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130403215758-22330283-the-importance-of-scheduling-nothing?_mSplash=1 … by @jeffweiner    
    
    
    Great to be in SF - I miss the unique sights - need to spend more time up here pic.twitter.com/EJQkyIfmO8    
    
    
    @Bill_Gross IPhone has 2M times more memory than Apollo 11 computer, yet >250M times people play Angry Birds than astronauts on that mission    
    
    
    @jasonrapp congrats on the move to @scienceinc - http://allthingsd.com/20130408/startup-studio-science-hires-digital-veteran-jason-rapp/?mod=tweet … cc @peterpham @mjones    
    
    
    AWESOME @PatientFusion is live: Book an appointment online with 27,000 doctors based on 1.5M reviews at http://www.patientfusion.com  starting now    
    
    
    @dsiroker @koomen congrats on the big @Optimizely funding & dominating Alexa top 10K chart for website optimization - http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/10/optimizely-series-a/ …    
    
    
    Excited to be on the venture panel today at @Xconomy Conference on Robotics at SRI in Menlo Park - http://www.xconomy.com/san-francisco/2013/02/05/debating-robots-jobs-and-the-changing-nature-of-work-on-april-11-at-sri/ … cc @lemnoslabs    
    
    
    @nilofer ability to learn is critical but so is the ability to put that into action, get things done (including newly learned ones)    
    
    
    @LeenaRao: Unfazed By Bitcoin’s Wild Swings ..., Silicon Valley VCs Place Their Bets http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/11/bitcoin/ … great piece by @kimmaicutler    
    
    
    +1 @brezina: You can tell @om just got back from some vacay (I'm guessing) because he is killing it this week. http://gigaom.com/2013/04/11/dennis-crowley-and-the-cycle-of-second-guessing/ …    
    
    
    Via @cjc: So happy for the team at @pulsepad and excited to see what they do next at @linkedin http://blog.pulse.me/post/47721164686/pulse-joins-the-linkedin-family … cc @akothari    
    
    
    I want one: @markoff: Holy Mackerel! Dutch Flying Cars?! http://pal-v.com/the-pal-v-one/the-pal-v-one-experience/ …    
    
    
    Nicely done @erply @kristjanh & team: profitable operations and passing 100K stores: http://m.techcrunch.com/2013/04/11/erply-milestone-profitability/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    @davemcclure roger that - really nice to see you - reconvene on ACA panel Thursday :)    
    
    
    @msuster scary stat - for sure related to sky high costs of education which is diverging fast from (currently) needed skills & job training    
    
    
    Immigrants founded 40% of Fortune500 & behind 7 of 10 firms w most valuable brands in the world: http://www.economist.com/news/business/21576101-start-ups-founded-immigrants-are-creating-jobs-all-over-america-jobs-machine … via @TheEconomist    
    
    
    Tilted :) @Crowdtilt: This Crowdtilt wants to do amazing things for #military children @Scherrology https://www.crowdtilt.com/campaigns/help-support-the-children-of-active-duty-us-military-service-members …    
    
    
    Major less important @WSJ: 95% of employers say they prioritize skills that contribute to innovation http://on.wsj.com/XHWoEG  via @EllenLevy    
    
    
    Excited to be here in Scottsdale for #eisummit - 1500+ attendees; should be a great day and a half full of #edtech innovation    
    
    
    Stunning stats at #eisummit by KIPP founder  @kippbigdog: by age 24, 82% top quartile income kids finish 4 yr college vs 8% bottom quartile    
    
    
    ACA Summit keynote panel on angel investing - @davemcclure will be adding the color - I'm going for the ride pic.twitter.com/XPKh6ucogM    
    
    
    @CarrieAWalsh thank you !    
    
    
    @KenHayesLA @irwin_brenda @AdamWinter appreciate it - that was really a blast up there w @davemcclure    
    
    
    Larry Page "w ambitious goals..There's not much competition, because no one else is crazy enough to try"
http://lat.ms/11GbxVn  via @jguynn    
    
    
    Really excited & proud to be at @foodspotting celebration dinner w @ladylexy @TeddyG @joshcook at @flourandwater    
    
    
    Really cool: @ChelseaClinton: @Worldreader offers 1400 books for free to anyone w a 2G mobile, anywhere in the world http://on.mash.to/YVgFGL     
    
    
    A look at the Mars desert research station in Utah: http://science.time.com/2013/03/12/mars-on-earth-a-look-at-the-mars-desert-research-station-in-utah/?iid=sci-main-belt … via @TIME pic.twitter.com/7rrryubnae    
    
    
    Via @snoble: @tobi talent isn't the unexplained ability to do something; it's the unexplained desire to willingly practice it    
    
    
    Exercise improves cognitive function (especially at older age), but weights & running do so differently via @stanine http://well.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/04/10/how-exercise-may-boost-the-brain/ …    
    
    
    Self experiment on sleep quality testing diff factors: reading iPad for 1 hour or more right before sleep cut my deep sleep time as much 30%    
    
    
    Proud to be a customer & investor: "Counsyl Is Pioneering A New Bioinformatics Wave" http://tcrn.ch/15FhOFb  by @kimmaicutler    
    
    
    Wow @felicisventures on fire this week: exits, lots of great news and our team getting bigger - super proud: @speechu @rquintini @fergiesk    
    
    
        
    
    
    Awesome piece on @zefrinc today - we are proud backers of @RichRaddon @ZachJames http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/26/as-it-focuses-on-content-id-and-monetization-zefr-signs-umg-sony-music-ultra-music-and-nascar/ … by @ryanlawler    
    
    
    Proud to be early backers of @wavii and @adrianaoun - congrats on joining the Google family and being our 46th exit - http://allthingsd.com/20130426/wavii-shuts-down-as-its-officially-acquired-by-google/ …    
    
    
    @barneyp @tedr Thank you ! Means much to me to work w amazing founders like yourselves, @Michels @adrianaoun & share the journey    
    
    
    At Ramen Dojo line w @eladgil pic.twitter.com/UiCwYRRVHR    
    
    
    @blackstone s Stephen Schwarzman endows $300M for scholarships to study at @Tsinghua_China "Rhodes East" http://m.newyorker.com/online/blogs/evanosnos/2013/04/rhodes-east-why-is-the-schwarzman-scholarship-in-china.html …    
    
    
    @gharik @cjhahn congratulations ! Big news :) super happy for you guys cc @soniaarrison    
    
    
    Super excited to welcome Guergana Tomova (@gbtomova) as our new CFO to the @felicisventures team !    
    
    
    Scientists Invent Oxygen Particle That Allows You To Live w/o Breathing ~30 mins http://www.techwench.com/scientists-invent-oxygen-particle-that-if-injected-allows-you-to-live-without-breathing/ … via @techwenchcom & @MissDestructo    
    
    
    Very exciting: 3 @felicisventures companies win a 2013 Webby: @Rovio, @DollarShaveClub and @Artspace via @speechu cc @rquintini    
    
    
    Up from 15M sites & 100M users, @weebly aims for creation of 100M new websites: http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/05/02/planning-for-another-100-million-web-sites/ … via @nytimesbits cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Really excited to welcome @dbarannik to @felicisventures ! http://www.felicis.com/team/dasha-barannik/ … I can't believe we are now 6 people :)    
    
    
    Top paid app of *all* time released by Apple: @RovioHQ s Angry Birds - http://venturebeat.com/2013/05/02/apple-announces-countdown-to-50-billion-apps-served-reveals-top-50-apps-of-all-time/ … via @speechu cc @pvesterbacka @stalbs    
    
    
    @dbarannik I love this chart - need to put it up in our kitchen !    
    
    
    9 out of 10 mobile searches lead to an action & 50%+ lead to a purchase:  http://socialmediatoday.com/brianna5mith/1373106/50-mobile-marketing-facts-will-blow-you-away … based on @HubSpot prezo via @Bill_Gross    
    
    
    @parislemon @GoogleVentures Congrats ! Great move    
    
    
    Data from @FlurryMobile: mobile war is over & the App has won: 80% of mobile time spent in apps http://bit.ly/10kH7Wa  via @flytip @stalbs    
    
    
    @firatdemirel @ihsanelgin @serkanunsal tesekkurler - basarimizi sadece calistigimiz kurucularin basarisiyla olcuyoruz. Bizi vareden onlar    
    
    
    When you get to work with amazing founders and a stellar team like the one we have @felicisventures; happiness is the norm not the exception    
    
    
    2 year old, Korean born toddler is youngest to ever get lab-made windpipe in Chicago - http://bigstory.ap.org/article/2-year-old-girl-gets-windpipe-made-stem-cells …  via @soniaarrison    
    
    
    Happy Mothers Day !    
    
    
    @dylancasey @marissamayer Congrats !    
    
    
    Loving the new @AnyDO app for iOS - it's incredible how far the app has come @OmerPerchik !    
    
    
    Want to reverse aging ? it might just become a matter of simple blood transfusion - http://science.slashdot.org/story/13/05/10/1515252/transfusions-reverse-aging-effects-on-hearts-in-mice … via @soniaarrison @slashdot    
    
    
    Android at 900M installs up from 400M last year via @jowyang yet Android penetration still ~10% most parts of the world via @MattRosoff    
    
    
    Most awesome birthday cake pic.twitter.com/0e1Ka827dS    
    
    
    Google’s Greatest Strength May Be the Luxury of Failure - http://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2013/05/17/googles-greatest-strength-may-be-the-luxury-of-failure/ … via @dcancel    
    
    
    How Retail is Being Disrupted; including big innovators like @shopify targeting $8B in GMV by '15 - http://bit.ly/12Jyfvp  via @CNBC    
    
    
    From my favorite trance DJ @arminvanbuuren: ‘’It's about living life intensely... & finding your own road" - http://armada.dj/rhqo90     
    
    
    Biggest gift of SV: thinking of how to make things happen in unique ways rather than wasting time worrying about how something might fail    
    
    
    Nikola Tesla pitches a VC firm caricature (hilarious) - 'nothing is funnier than the truth' - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zngK13FMgXM … via @om    
    
    
    Immigration Reform would save US $410B over 10 yrs, adding 1.6% to GDP by conservative estimate: http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/05/15/immigration-reform-save-billions_n_3280145.html?utm_hp_ref=business … via @HuffingtonPost    
    
    
    Its really key to succinctly describe what a startup does - by @ansanelli "the 10-second test" 
http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130521153813-1915923-passing-the-10-second-test … via @eileentso    
    
    
    History in the making: BREAKING: Senate Judiciary Committee approves landmark immigration bill offering citizenship to millions via @ap    
    
    
    How An Age-Old Chart Is Redefining Health Care (& reinventing that same chart) http://trib.al/B45qh6wm  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Corp. tax rates by S&P 500 '07-'12; Exxon, Chevron & ConocoPhillips paid $291B, Amazon was 6% - 
http://nyti.ms/127CSnO  via @justinwolfers    
    
    
    @gregbettinelli I focused on the outliers, Amazon was among the lowest overall rates, while the oil companies paid sizeable absolute amt    
    
    
    @amac @kevaldesai @timarmstrongaol then we need to make it happen more often :)    
    
    
    A Memorial Day Thank You (~18M veterans since WW II) Infographic via @MarketingPilgrm http://hub.am/18n6b74  via @HubSpot    
    
    
    Socratic wisdom, happiness as a choice and finding our spiritual harness -  http://lnkd.in/CS8-vr  via @reidhoffman    
    
    
    HBR article on innovation: healthy paranoia, intellectual curiosity, drive to innovate & fix things - http://lnkd.in/XsqvaT  via @Raminibar    
    
    
    Great funding announcement for @appurify @ManishLachwani @jay_srinivasan - http://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/mobile-testing--debugging-platform-appurify-raises-45m-series-a-financing-led-by-google-ventures-209197471.html … proud that @speechu was an early investor    
    
    
    "Going to Mars is difficult but achievable (3-6 months per trip)" "we can warm Mars up w greenhouse gases" @elonmusk #d11 via @TEDchris    
    
    
    This is really funny - http://incubatorincubator.com/  thanks  @ManuKumar @eladgil    
    
    
    @rsarver best of luck ! Look forward to finding out about the next adventure !    
    
    
    Never take democracy for granted; I'm proud of the people of Istanbul who stood up - http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/05/protests-show-turks-cant-tolerate-erdogan-anymore/276447/ … via @demirkapi @melotones    
    
    
    Artificial kidneys moving closer to reality (another step in a golden age of innovation) - http://www.economist.com/news/technology-quarterly/21578526-medical-technology-artificial-kidneys-are-getting-closer-becoming-clinical … via @TheEconomist    
    
    
    Front page of New York Times today - pic.twitter.com/tesp2FS9O2 via @linkibol @seanxyu    
    
    
    By @andrewchen: Great advice for new college grads: Don't sell your time for a living http://andrewchen.co/2013/06/03/new-college-grads-dont-sell-your-time-for-a-living/ … via @JulesMaltz    
    
    
    "Most important political office is that of the private citizen; sunlight the best disinfectant" - Justice L. Brandeis    
    
    
    H1B problems ? US immigration too tough ? Billboard on Hwy 101 for Canadian immigration - brilliant - http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/06/technology/wishing-you-and-your-start-up-were-here.html … via @nytimes    
    
    
    Eye opening @WSJ piece on caffeine addiction: http://on.wsj.com/19iWuqF  then cross ref here for caffeine content: http://bit.ly/eD61     
    
    
    @lindaavey @missavey looking forward to it    
    
    
    @MikeMcDerment great book & even greater response - agree with @speechu on the talent side but hard to imagine "post @freshbooks" for u :)    
    
    
    Really inspired by @nntaleb Antifragile - especially the parts on natures strategy of overcompensation / redundancy    
    
    
    Potential game changer in bioinformatics: Supreme Court rules isolated human genes cannot be patented - http://online.wsj.com/article/BT-CO-20130613-707026.html … via @speechu    
    
    
    “@GtownAngels: @asenkut Looking forward to having you on the panel tonight. @GtownAngels” Thank you ! Looking forward to it    
    
    
    Don’t Take Your Vitamins (pills) - http://nyti.ms/1bhK2Eg  via @soniaarrison on @nytimes    
    
    
    Three Things I’ve Learned From Warren Buffett (framework of thinking, use your platform, incredible value of time) - http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130612065727-251749025-three-things-i-ve-learned-from-warren-buffett …    
    
    
    @lindaavey @atulbutte @biotechfounder @eperlste @soniaarrison - it was a blast ! Here's to the scientists and inventors !    
    
    
    Best Father's Day present this weekend: my 4 year old son telling me: "Daddy, I like you !" while we are reading books together    
    
    
    48% of US GDP variation tracked to top firms; sales of top 100 companies = 35% GDP, other stats via @TheEconomist - http://www.economist.com/news/finance-and-economics/21579808-fate-large-firms-helps-explain-economic-volatility-goliaths?fsrc=scn/tw/te/pe/thegoliaths …    
    
    
    Love the @aetherapparel store in Hayes Valley - timeless design pic.twitter.com/jbMmmk5PUV    
    
    
    I had to try the "first case to protect you (& reduces radiation exposure)" after reading: http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2009/10/cellphone-radiation-testing/ … pic.twitter.com/VJ52heuvlq    
    
    
    Great line up :) @davemcclure: starting #PreMoney 5m -- morning speakers @paulg @msuster @naval @joshk @kbmdv @jeff @annimaniac @asenkut    
    
    
    Awesome day at #PreMoney and great organization by @davemcclure and @500startups - #hustle #marketing    
    
    
    @samanthassiow @rohit_x_ @tugceergul @andytangvc @mlstotts @daniellemorrill @ucete @gregraiten thanks for the feedback on the panel today    
    
    
    .@tomiogeron we focus on the success of our founders & alignment so that all our 47 exits from $10M to $1B+ matter cc @felicisventures    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great comments on #premoney panel today @sjacobsohn @__tosh @bedy @marcusogawa @LFlanagan @christine @desireedawns cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Big move: @gokulr - Square Hires AdSense "Godfather" Gokul Rajaram Away From Facebook http://techcrunch.com/2013/06/27/gokul-rajaram-square/ … … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Congrats to @scanscout team merged w @TremorVideo - big day - another secondary IPO for @felicisventures pic.twitter.com/f7SmYASOm1    
    
    
    Azumio (@azumioinc) launches Argus, a meta quantified self app and gets featured by Apple - http://gigaom.com/2013/07/03/the-meta-quantified-self-argus-app-for-ios-tracks-all-your-health-tracking-apps/ …    
    
    
    Happy 4th July US - you're a country where anything's possible so I hope 1 day that includes background checks on gun sales for my sons sake    
    
    
    @Eunner thank God you're OK - hope everyone else from the plane are doing better; surreal indeed    
    
    
    @emilyolson @roblafave congrats ! Really happy for both of you !    
    
    
    Nice mention of @roviohq: How @Dropbox Will Remake Itself (And Your Angry Birds) http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/07/dropbox … by @bobmcmillan cc @pvesterbacka    
    
    
    This is cool: AT&T is advertising @SoundHound in a TV spot: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=h5Pp05dWD5E … via @Bagelturf    
    
    
    Amazing tent, testament to ingenuity (one click set-up, withstand 75mph winds, gorgeous)  http://link.ahalife.com/view/4dd72c4e52366d356329f61212rj2.g8k/0c75c23c … via @soniaarrison @AHAlife    
    
    
    Nice piece on @GrowConf by @andrewdsouza on @techvibes great mention of @speechu cc @felicisventures - http://www.techvibes.com/blog/how-grow-changed-our-company-trajectory-2013-07-15 …    
    
    
    Agreed w @speechu: Love this job posting from @hfizzle - http://blog.harleyf.com/hustle-your-way-into-shopify … (cool, out of box thinking)    
    
    
    Inspiring: @GirlsWhoCode:..our #girlswhocode at @gecapital have already programmed their robots to draw masterpieces! pic.twitter.com/ugVV9QapEw    
    
    
    Frank post: @bhorowitz abt dreaded "downrounds", shifting markets, "eating s*** better than suicide" http://finance.fortune.cnn.com/2013/07/15/capital-market-climate-change/ … via @MattRosoff    
    
    
    Grand Canyon from tens of thousands of feet high, courtesy of in flight wifi -  breathtaking pic.twitter.com/FchbBilYc8    
    
    
    Congrats: @Inkling picks up powerful publishing partners (in Pearson & Elsevier) http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2013/07/17/inkling-picks-up-powerful-publishing-partners/ … via @mhelft cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    A chart that shows why Microsoft lost 30B in market cap today "PC, what PC ?" #denial http://www.businessinsider.com/chart-of-the-day-microsofts-big-problem-in-one-chart-2013-7 … via @msuster    
    
    
    "Tennis ball, circle & number 30,000" Great commencement speech by @drewhouston at MIT '13 - thanks to @schreier for the tip    
    
    
    @joshelman congrats :) http://allthingsd.com/20130724/former-twitter-facebook-product-pro-josh-elman-becomes-partner-at-greylock/ …    
    
    
    "entrepreneurs are contrarian value creators" via @TheEconomist: True entrepreneurs find possibility in .. impossible http://econ.st/12LzA45     
    
    
        
    
    
    Super excited for @felicisventures  to join @crunchbase Venture Program along w  @500startups http://bit.ly/10Z5AUK     
    
    
    Coolest presentation of mint tea I've yet seen; taking freshness to a new level... pic.twitter.com/ha9b8Fjyel    
    
    
    Great advice from @paulg on convincing: stick to truth & most pertinent facts, look at story thru other side's lens - http://paulgraham.com/convince.html     
    
    
    In @businessweek interview "just from one letter being wrong out of 1.1 million, it made the difference between life and no life" @JCVenter    
    
    
    A cool post by @abrydon in @TechCrunch describing how he used @ClearSlide in fundraising - http://tcrn.ch/139H06V     
    
    
    Shichi Hon Yari (Seven Spearmen) from Shiga prefecture - Sake Nirvana pic.twitter.com/HmCdyVrApn    
    
    
    From 0% to dominant browser in less than 5 years, Google's Chrome now 43% of desktop web traffic http://econ.st/1cNFZ62  via @TheEconomist    
    
    
    .@davidlee @triketora remember the days of browser extensions and toolbars ? Kudos to @sundarpichai and his team...    
    
    
    Roses from our garden, the colors look unreal, time to pause and appreciate Mother Nature and our good fortune pic.twitter.com/nEPBYK4w5s    
    
    
    From fringe to Las Vegas' savior: Electronic Dance Music (along w world's top paid DJs) http://onforb.es/14bHQLm  @forbes @zachtratar @seth    
    
    
    Next frontier on computing - your brain (nice @InteraXon mention) on @Forbes - http://www.forbes.com/sites/reuvencohen/2013/08/20/the-next-frontier-in-computing-your-brain/ … cc @ariel_garten via @felicisventures    
    
    
    Really proud of 2 @felicisventures founders making MITs 35 under 35 list: @pindrop s Vijay Balasubramanian & @counsyl s Balaji Srinivasan    
    
    
    Congrats @adammcnamara @tobi @hfizzle on the launch of @shopify POS - you guys are on fire ! http://techcrunch.com/2013/08/28/shopify-launches-point-of-sale-system-to-unify-online-and-brick-and-mortar-retail/ …    
    
    
    Scientists grow a 3D, self-organizing model of a developing human brain using stem cells http://pops.ci/18l45Qi  via @popsci @soniaarrison    
    
    
    Inspiring: On 5th try, (64 yr old) Diana Nyad becomes 1st person to complete (110 mile) Cuba-to-Florida swim without a shark cage via @AP    
    
    
    Congrats @viki @davemcclure @saarsaar @Joi site came such a long way from Wiikii days...    
    
    
    I like this piece by @hamishmckenzie: "Let's start a fight on the Internet": http://pandodaily.com/2013/09/02/lets-start-a-fight-on-the-internet/ … cc @naval    
    
    
    Microsoft To Buy Nokia's Device Biz & patents for 7.17B (all in overseas cash) http://allthingsd.com/20130902/microsoft-to-buy-nokias-device-business-for-7-17-billion-euros/ … via @johnolilly & @allthingsd    
    
    
    @firatdemirel @webrazzi aynen oyle @mobilike ilk yatirimimiz Turkiye'de - hayirli olsun :) cc @sekip @volkanbicer @TeamEurope @PointNineCap    
    
    
    Excited about the Friday #Beglobal panel w @davidlee @jeff @christine_tsai moderated by @sarahcuda cc @besuccess http://beglobal.co/agenda/     
    
    
    Excited to discuss innovation in early stage VC at @fundersclub #Upround conference tomorrow with @joshk and fireside chat w @feliciacurcuru    
    
    
    Well said @marissamayer "Make a few decisions, but make them perfectly"    
    
    
    Fantastic panel & awesome audience today @FundersClub's #Upround - Thanks @Marketing_Sage @CMBechs @emilybest @BrunoFonzi    
    
    
    Really proud of @Distill on their quest to make technical hiring dead simple and the first raise: http://tcrn.ch/1506hBi  via @kimmaicutler    
    
    
    So proud: @TIMEIdeas: @soniaarrison on Google's announcement, broken by TIME: Will You Still Love Me When I’m 164? http://ti.me/1f6ZkQO     
    
    
    Wow - this is uber cool: @TIME: Google vs. Death: TIME's cover story on Google's new initiative to solve death | http://ti.me/18biUq8     
    
    
    Qt"Last week Apple announced a gold iPhone; what did you do this week, Google? We founded a company that might one day defeat death itself."    
    
    
    @arampell totally agreed and that's why I'm so proud to be an alumni and early Xoogler - very inspiring    
    
    
    Thank you @FundersClub it was a really awesome event - cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    What to Know About the General Solicitation Law That Goes Into Effect Today http://fw.to/kUPHH2  via @emilyolson & Alex M of @FundersClub    
    
    
    Proud to be an early believer: With $70M raise, @practicefusion [goes after] Health Care Data http://onforb.es/1gVQaoo  by @tomiogeron    
    
    
    Embodiment of resilience and perseverance in a founder: @RyanHowardCEO building @practicefusion to be the next iconic healthcare company    
    
    
    @Tonyrides1 @Caroline_Pugh @Under30CEO thank you - we are working hard every day to earn our reputation, one founder at a time    
    
    
    Can't believe it's been 15 years: @mattcutts: To celebrate Google's 15th birthday ... how Google used to look: https://www.google.com/#q=google+in+1998 …    
    
    
    Good move: @HireArt, Job Applicant Screening Service Used By Airbnb, Cisco, eBay & Others, Gets More Affordable: http://tcrn.ch/16ZbMLV     
    
    
    Apple (replacing Coca Cola) & Google take over #1 and #2 spots on top global brands; 6 out of top 10 are tech cos: http://www.interbrand.com/en/best-global-brands/2013/Best-Global-Brands-2013.aspx …    
    
    
    @azumio totally dominating health & fitness on AppStore with 3 of the top 3 grossing apps pic.twitter.com/rmxJEwNMzf    
    
    
    Good catch @mamoonha; @stopman @jeremys stop by @felicisventures when you're in Palo Alto    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats to David Friedberg & @climatecorp team: Monsanto Acquires Climate Corporation For $930M http://techcrunch.com/2013/10/02/monsanto-acquires-weather-big-data-company-climate-corporation-for-930m/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats @Eisenberg & team @Floored3D for winning the GREATtech award for #hardware cc @rquintini    
    
    
    Is it the end of Paid Apps ? (Free apps 90% in appstore, & 6% at $.99 price point) http://techcrunch.com/2013/10/02/its-over-for-paid-apps-with-a-few-exceptions/ … by @SarahPerezTC via @ksegerstrale    
    
    
        
    
    
    According to emarketer Turkey now has highest Twitter penetration (31.1%) in the world: pic.twitter.com/OQ9MfsApo6 via @mszgn cc @KatieS @sacca    
    
    
    @sacca @MSZGN @KatieS smart enough to appreciate that talent is universal but without hustle, it's also of not much value...    
    
    
    So much said about the start, but finishing is equally important & much harder - http://bit.ly/19scAyS  from @avc via @VCMike    
    
    
    @zachtratar true    
    
    
    Millennials prefer “access to ownership” to ownership, except owning their own business http://buff.ly/1e6hP6v  on @forbes via @mtarun    
    
    
    Congrats @tworetzky on joining @Udacity as VP Product. Exciting days ahead in advancing education through technology http://dthin.gs/19kqyAR     
    
    
    Really proud of @pvesterbacka the recipient of 2013 #nordicaward by @siliconvikings - well deserved ! cc @RovioHQ pic.twitter.com/5eDfvhD2K0    
    
    
    Congrats @jwelde and the @smartling team on the big $24M raise & to being the globalization company - http://blogs.wsj.com/venturecapital/2013/10/09/smartling-raises-24-million-to-translate-everything-online/ … via @WSJ    
    
    
    Must read by @gregbettinelli: New Blog Post: My reaction to Zulily's IPO filing and Flash Sales explained http://wp.me/p3OTHu-1f     
    
    
    Big day for @MindSnacks, passing 8M downloads and launch of an awesome U.S. Geography app - https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/u.s.-geography-by-mindsnacks/id690162481?mt=8 …    
    
    
    Mobile Ad Spending Rises Sharply (145%) from $1.2B in 1H12 to $3B in 1H13 via @wsj http://on.wsj.com/1e8Jq7j     
    
    
    It's Tell All Book Season in Silicon Valley by @adamlashinsky http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2013/10/11/twitter-amazon-apple-books/ … lots exciting reads coming up @nickbilton @BradStone    
    
    
    So cool via @jeremys: @elonmusk: Rocket flight to 744m, hover & return to launch pad (shot from hexacopter drone) http://youtu.be/9ZDkItO-0a4     
    
    
    Tech rules: @msuster & @mmurph: iPhone sales last year exceeded rev of Coca-Cola & McDonald's http://m.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2013/09/the-iphone-is-a-bigger-business-than-coca-cola-and-mcdonalds-combined/280023/ … pic.twitter.com/wXyJi1Jkl4    
    
    
    @arampell iPhone got there in a little over 6 years versus decades it took Coke; @msuster @mmurph    
    
    
    Apple hires Burberry CEO @AngelaAhrendts as SVP of retail & stores - amazing hire - http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052702304561004579136642448489128.html … on @WSJ via @rjhang    
    
    
    Angry Birds Go! to launch Dec 11; exciting to see first video of @roviohq s kart-style racing game http://tnw.to/a0c9E  via @TheNextWeb    
    
    
    Interesting read: @satyap: so many nuggets of wisdom - LinkedIn’s Series B Pitch to Greylock: http://reidhoffman.org/linkedin-pitch-to-greylock/ …    
    
    
    It was fun to back @habibh & @yamli early in '09 w @gharik - most interesting & original middle eastern startup we invested cc @davemcclure    
    
    
    Amazing job on the new @Dropcam Pro, @gduffy and team - amazing resolution & new features - http://gigaom.com/2013/10/10/dropcams-new-camera-is-crystal-clear-and-its-learning-too/ …    
    
    
    Cool Analysis by @CBinsights on microVC funds including @felicisventures & how their syndicates change over time - http://www.cbinsights.com/blog/trends/felicis-ventures-floodgate-fund-investment-syndicate …    
    
    
    3 Reasons Why the Canadian Startup Tech Scene Rocks - nice shout out to @Shopify @deblanda http://prsm.tc/XNV1Cp  via @RMB cc @hfizzle    
    
    
    With its recent stock price gains, Google replaces Microsoft for 3rd most valuable ($336B) company in the world - http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2013/10/19/google-apple-exxon-microsoft/ …    
    
    
    Excited about the new @CrunchBase venture program tools to manage investors public data -  http://techcrunch.com/2013/10/22/crunchbase-venture-program-hits-400-and-launches-tools-to-help-investors-manage-their-public-data/ … via @ripemp    
    
    
    My first time checking out an actual Xiaomi phone (gen 2) at @theGMIC conference right before a panel pic.twitter.com/eO7pnZHSJu    
    
    
    So meta - photo of your photo on a smart watch... Thanks @philosophygeek ! pic.twitter.com/l9ExFoTGip    
    
    
    @MaxWendkos it seems to be a total copy of iOS and Android - crazy    
    
    
    Grt post @ttunguz: Remove the logo from the website, could customers still identify the experience ?
http://tomtunguz.com/the-simplest-brand-health-question-for-your-startup/ … via @hunterwalk    
    
    
    Proud of @Vicariousinc AI claims cracking 90% of CAPTCHAs offered by Google, Yahoo and PayPal http://tnw.to/j0j9F  via @felicisventures    
    
    
    Congrats @agarwal @posterous incredible journey indeed. Proud to be an early investor & here is to the next chapter post @twitter IPO    
    
    
    Ron Burgundy (@_Anchorman) + Dodge, best commercials ever: http://m.youtube.com/user/dodge/durango … Apparently consumers agree, sales went up 50%    
    
    
    This isn't new but true @brianalvey: "The VC game has become about branding yourself so you can get into a handful of hot deals." @Naval    
    
    
    Looking forward to #Helsinki's biggest #startup event @SlushHQ on Nov 13 (sold out) Waiting list: http://bit.ly/17hqDC7  #innovation    
    
    
    Thank you @hfizzle congrats again and keep inspiring #loveandhustle  cc @dbarannik pic.twitter.com/QxCx1fE7xr    
    
    
    @ceonyc @infoarbitrage @brianalvey @naval it's not mutually exclusive - the early bold bets build reputation & is the key asset for any VC    
    
    
    Fun panel @robinwauters at @SlushHQ thx for comments @lavas @Sarpanilkki @contactsven @eevakiuru @byarja @brkytskn pic.twitter.com/vTUsGFPZzq    
    
    
    Need to unlearn the urge to find answers - "the best answer to almost any question is another question" - Robert Rubin via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    Apple (reportedly) buys Xbox Kinect motion capture provider Primesense for $345M - http://www.slashgear.com/apple-reportedly-buys-kinect-tech-creator-primesense-17305684/ …    
    
    
    Nice to meet today @cynthiag - look forward to comparing more notes    
    
    
    Excited to see @siberianfruit @mrdubin @walterdriver - fantastic group of founders & companies at @GoldmanSachs  Tech Conf    
    
    
    SV is unique in the world b/c it accepts people for who they are, where anything's truly possible & where ideas & people really matter.    
    
    
    So thankful for my wonderful family, my awesome team, the incredible founders I work with & lucky 2 b at the right place at the right time    
    
    
    Awesome real time visualization: @tobi: look at what's going on at Shopify right now: http://incoming.shopify.com/     
    
    
    @sinatraj @wharton thanks again for the awesome dialogue - our biggest luxury @felicisventures is to be unconventional & unorthodox    
    
    
    @FrederikFischer @updatesfromSV - thanks to @SVOD_club #svod13 fireside chat w @advornikova was one of the best - awesome audience    
    
    
    So cool: @AstroKatie: Milky Way over South Africa - Photo by Stephen Potter. http://www.saao.ac.za/sutherland-by-night/ … pic.twitter.com/uG41tDAozr    
    
    
    Great company, Thx @chraynaud: Top 5 angel investors by @EntMagazine http://entm.ag/1d19zDv  @davemcclure @RonConway @davidlee & Esther Dyson    
    
    
    Lots of robotics, machine vision & 3D printing @LisaOstrikoff: Top 10 Tech of 2013 According to Tumblr http://on.mash.to/18cHU5a  @mashabletech    
    
    
    Awesome win (19-17) @sf49ers over #seahawks ! 4 field goals by Dawson - http://www.usatoday.com/story/sports/nfl/2013/12/08/seahawks-49ers-week14/3911827/ …    
    
    
    So proud of @tobi, @hfizzle & team: @Shopify Raises $100M to bridge clicks & bricks - http://blogs.wsj.com/venturecapital/2013/12/12/on-road-to-ipo-shopify-raises-100m-to-bridge-clicks-and-bricks/ … cc @felicisventures    
    
    
    Wow: Google just bought Boston Dynamics, maker of various animal like robots & military supplier -  http://www.nytimes.com/2013/12/14/technology/google-adds-to-its-menagerie-of-robots.html …    
    
    
    Apple's iOS 76% of small/medium business activations in 2013 based on Intermedia data http://appleinsider.com/articles/13/12/12/apples-ios-nabbed-76-of-small-medium-business-device-activations-in-2013-study-says … via @Techmeme @appleinsider    
    
    
    Well done @speechu, @felicisventures 1 of top drones/robotics VCs - http://m.bizjournals.com/sanjose/news/2013/12/19/vcs-step-up-funding-for-future-drone.html … proud of our founders @helengreiner @jbdowney83    
    
    
    Amazing: from closing 2 big pivotal deals Christmas Eve to seeing my sons great grandfather drive a Tesla at 102 yr pic.twitter.com/s7zGtQYtG0    
    
    
    Awesome post ski mocha @Coffeebar96161 - loving downtown Truckee - happy 2014 ! cc @sacca    
    
    
    @sacca roger that    
    
    
    Great guest post by @aileenlee (that's why I'm proud of our dozen female Founder / CEOs) Why Women Rule The Internet http://tcrn.ch/fDNJoj    
    
    
    @satyap belated congrats on @jointheflock @twitter - really excited for you    
    
    
    Via @bobmetcalfe Top 10 Industries dying - WSJ http://on.wsj.com/hSZAJz - Next to be disrupted by Internet: Energy, Healthcare, Education    
    
    
    Via @michaelpollan - infographic on food spending by country (US spends less than 7% of income, lowest of any country) - http://p2.to/19RU    
    
    
    Accidental Find May Lead to a Cure For Baldness http://singularityhub.com/2011/04/02/accidental-find-may-lead-to-a-cure-for-baldness-2/ …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/f5k9XS    
    
    
    Elite 8: Who to Watch for in Venture Capital - G. Doriot, TrueBridge Capital - Forbes (I'm humbled by the company) http://bit.ly/gtyB4e    
    
    
    I'm at Bloomberg (731 Lexington Ave, 59th St, New York) w/ 8 others http://4sq.com/g1pRC0    
    
    
    Best meeting in NYC w @cdixon - inspired and pumped. Ready to blog again...    
    
    
    @margbrennan great segment on Bloomberg today - thanks again for the opportunity    
    
    
    @donnawells @mirceapasoi @bwertz @rydonahue thx so much for the kind tweets ! Really appreciate it    
    
    
    Via @johnbattelle Google’s Biggest Advertisers (Top 10 - Amazon, 3 insurers, 1 credit card co, 1 retailer, 1 travel co) http://bit.ly/h8Xn4A    
    
    
    Awesome: Angry Birds (@rovio) to soon sync score across devices | Crave - CNET http://cnet.co/edSpRU    
    
    
    iPad, tablets take a bite out of PC shipments (-1% vs expected 3% growth) via CNET - http://cnet.co/dLtL5v    
    
    
    Tech's Top Women Under 30 - Great compilation of exciting new talent -  http://bit.ly/eNgoMB    
    
    
    @loic great seeing you tonight - love the new @seismic strategic direction    
    
    
        
    
    
    @yvesbehar @pocarles re Angry Birds vs Mickey Mouse, check this out: http://bit.ly/gTN3Rg / also check the Appstore, Rovio has 3 in top 10    
    
    
    @yvesbehar @pocarles agreed on the points / still a super exciting ride, more chapters waiting to be written    
    
    
    “@medialab: MIT Announces Joi Ito as Next Media Lab Director:  http://bit.ly/eE73sf ” - Congrats @Joi !    
    
    
    US Mobile Apps: All About Android and Apple iOS: they collectively represent 74% of mobile app downloaders | Nielsen - http://bit.ly/mL5xUm    
    
    
    Apple spends less than 3% of revenues on R&D, whereas Microsoft about 14-15% striking contrast in amount spent vs innovative products - WSJ    
    
    
    "Don't be evil" Google tops US brand reputation rankings, financial services firms (GS / AIG) at bottom - CNET News http://cnet.co/mBLJBe    
    
    
    Bin Laden news causes “bigger traffic spike than royal wedding” | VentureBeat http://bit.ly/jYzV3k    
    
    
    Congratulations to Founders of @bumptech, @disqus, @hearsaysocial, @meraki, named to @BW Best Young Tech Entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/mR4hxB    
    
    
    Another digital gold rush | The Economist (mention of Super Angels & Felicis) - http://econ.st/iKZvhR    
    
    
    Inspirational piece: @Octopart, The Little Startup That Hung In There (kudos to Andres, Harish & Sam) - http://tcrn.ch/kb8sCS    
    
    
    Excited about the first Felicis IPO: LinkedIn stock surges after  IPO - http://on.ft.com/iWLGNL    
    
    
    @rabois March 2010    
    
    
    @rabois they didn't - it was a private transaction (and not in the secondary markets)    
    
    
    Nice job @imoim @gharik @ralphimo - Best IM client on Android: the super sleek, easy-to-use Imo: http://lifehac.kr/mS9Enm    
    
    
    First Felicis Founder event just wrapped up - super cool to see so many of our incredible founders in one room for the first time - awesome    
    
    
    @mickhagen and @tedr thanks again for your support - awesome seeing you today    
    
    
    Congrats to @jackabraham and Mikael Hed of @Roviomobile on making the Most Creative People 2011 | Fast Company http://bit.ly/iUxquO    
    
    
    Istanbul tops Financial Times most livable cities readers poll (SF #4) - http://goo.gl/Hwdws     
    
    
    “@davestone: @loic on that: http://bit.ly/lRdXSx ” great iPad stats (40% now use it as primary comp., 29% have more than 50 apps, most paid)    
    
    
    Great post by @danprimack on VC/PE fund performance data from UTIMCO. Top funds: USV '04, Foundry '07, Spark II - http://bit.ly/krE2p2    
    
    
    I'm at Trump Soho - The Library (246 Spring Street, New York) http://4sq.com/kRS0Zj    
    
    
    Excited about the Churchill Club -  VC Roundtable tonight with co-panelists @joshk @billmaris @howardh @rayrothrock  - http://bit.ly/jTqiSI    
    
    
    Forrester: U.S. Mobile Commerce To Reach $31 Billion By 2016 (growing from 1% to 7% of e-commerce) http://pulse.me/s/fk86    
    
    
    Walmart vs Amazon (the only stat that matters is the customer service ranking [W#10, A#1]) [INFOGRAPHIC] http://on.mash.to/isS0pe    
    
    
    Most interesting referral bonus I've seen: $20K + your full genome sequenced: @DNANexus - hiring SW Engineers ! http://bit.ly/kAQvMg     
    
    
    I’m nominating Inkling for “The FASTech 50″ list of most innovative companies! http://on.wsj.com/lc42MJ  #FASTech50 cc/ @inkling @stanine    
    
    
    I’m nominating Practice Fusion for “The FASTech 50″ list of most innovative companies! http://on.wsj.com/lc42MJ  #FASTech50 cc/ @PracticeFusion    
    
    
    Congrats to @plotwatt &  @lfishback on winning the @ecomagination challenge -  http://fb.me/HDMDUtTP  #awesome    
    
    
    Why Peter Thiel Likes Electronic Health Record Provider Practice Fusion - Zina Moukheiber / Forbes http://onforb.es/jDMckD  @PracticeFusion    
    
    
    The Current State of Venture Capital http://zite.to/mdVCg3 via @Ziteapp    
    
    
    Jeff Bezos on Embracing Failure at Amazon via @alleyinsider - http://read.bi/kJI4XV     
    
    
    IDC Predicts 183 B Mobile App Downloads By 2015 (17x increase over 10.7B in '10) & More In-App Purchasing http://tinyurl.com/3wh6bsx    
    
    
    Q&A with @Mattrosoff from @BusinessInsider - http://read.bi/mTN95r    
    
    
    Congrats @Poojanath @piazza on NY Times ! http://www.nytimes.com/2011/07/04/technology/04piazza.html …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Atlanta Teacher Uses Angry Birds for Physics Lessons #Awesome cc @Roviomobile - http://bit.ly/nublbM    
    
    
    6 Major Mobile App Stores Compared [Infographic] | by Bit Rebels via @ugurkaner - http://bit.ly/nUmlVF    
    
    
    Mobile industry to reach 2% of global GDP ($1.3 Trillion), 6B subs in 2011 via @VentureBeat - http://bit.ly/rcBWqP    
    
    
    Congrats @Sinaafra - Naspers values Turkish ecommerce giant markafoni at $200 million, buys 70% stake http://bit.ly/nq0SBk  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Crazy but true - so much for direct fiber connection at work: City of Palo Alto: "squirrels ate the cable" - our internet's down...    
    
    
    Look forward to being a judge & seeing the 5 great startups at FORTUNE Brainstorm TECH Startup Idol tomorrow ! - http://bit.ly/oqRsnt    
    
    
        
    
    
    Via @shaig - top 10 tech companies' aggregate cash horde: $240 Billion #opportunity #M&A - http://bit.ly/oja1Jr     
    
    
    @DanaBrunetti @naywilliams @dpatil @subes01 @randizuckerberg @rbucks @speechu For sure - there'll be more action coming up :)    
    
    
    "A team that's constantly learning and evolving their skill sets is more powerful than experts afraid to leave their comfort zone" M Lipton    
    
    
    