My second monitor's been blinking on and off, and my main monitor just stopped working. I feel like Otto from Sons of Anarchy.    
    
    
    @AmberCadabra The gravitational sucking of rock stardom on the wane? ;)    
    
    
    @logosmith I wish. Time to get a better bag.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs I read #LeanIn and really enjoyed it. I had a few issues w/ the structure, but got a lot out of it.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs One of our execs hated the name-dropping, but can't say it bothered me. Enjoyed reading the VIP acknowledgements    
    
    
    @arikhanson Guess it just didn't bother me. I'm very proud of my mentor, even though he wasn't famous. I'd praise him to the skies.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs 2nd half of #LeanIn is a bit slower to read because it becomes a series of essays, not one consistent narrative.    
    
    
    @arikhanson But she's a chief exec at Facebook and married to the CEO of SurveyMonkey. I didn't really expect direct relatability.    
    
    
    @arikhanson Don't get me wrong, not discounting your take. I did worry that many women would find it too isolated a case to learn from.    
    
    
    @KatFrench Because we're guys or because we're nitpicking? @arikhanson    
    
    
    @KatFrench What, you don't think of me and @arikhanson as Rawhide men? Wait, don't answer that.    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan Probably when I lost my newspaper job back in 2005. A scary, optimistic, limitless time for reflection.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @mrdolson My favorite is still "Steak," the email marketing firm. "Rare medium, well done."    
    
    
    @arikhanson @mrdolson Don't forget this valuable chart of agency naming protocols: http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/infographic-taxonomy-advertising-agency-names-146517 …    
    
    
    Having dinner with this little charmer. http://instagram.com/p/Y0_r7dP4rA/     
    
    
    Feel like I blinked and these appeared. http://instagram.com/p/Y1D3YPP4hG/     
    
    
    Kid at grocery store told his mom, "Buy me something, and I'll stop being annoying!" I double dog dare my kids to try this approach.    
    
    
    @bretttmw Once is right.    
    
    
    Secret political message in my casserole pan. #99percent http://instagram.com/p/Y5xUdqP4vP/     
    
    
    Like bay leaves? Took a few years to mature, but our bay plant is exploding now. http://instagram.com/p/Y5xp4Yv4v1/     
    
    
    Email segmentation done wrong: Forrester sent me a note w/ a subject line that says "Second Blast to Unopens."    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Better than "uninterested party," I suppose.    
    
    
    Big thanks to @Mashable's @ToddWasserman for including me as a consulting expert in the "Social Makeover" series: http://on.mash.to/12PqaUn     
    
    
    @ESPN_ProdGirl Hey thanks, KR. Might jeopardize my precious under-the-radar status. :)    
    
    
    @girllostincity Hey thanks!    
    
    
    My team at @LuckieAndCo has an opening for a Digital Content Writer. Only 1 year exp required. http://bit.ly/11T520h     
    
    
    @cebsilver On-site. We've got a good stable of freelance topic experts all over, but this one's in Bham full-time.    
    
    
    @hushamanda Great to hear! I'll float your idea past HR....    
    
    
    Today's road snack: "rolled to explode with flavor"! http://instagram.com/p/ZEII7zv4rw/     
    
    
    @hushamanda No, that one's "Charlie Tango Crapflush." Totally different.    
    
    
    You keep tools in a gauntlet? RT @SBarnes: #FB is quickly becoming the most expensive, less effective, irrelevant tool in your #smm gauntlet    
    
    
    @SBarnes Well there's your problem right there.    
    
    
    Spain. #CountriesThatStillHaveKingsForNoRealReason    
    
    
    @CaptainAnnoying Love the scene where he punched out Goebbels and blew up the Luftwaffe factory while making love to Maria.    
    
    
    Have you watched "This Is Water" yet? (1.6M have.) Here's my Q&A with the creators: http://adweek.it/12gXjLn     
    
    
    @girllostincity Probably depends how well you curate your sponsors. If they're supporting content you already had planned, it's a win-win    
    
    
    @girllostincity Sponsors always want to be in the content well, not the ad sidebar, but it's definitely rare they bring much of worth.    
    
    
    One of my favorite pics of my daughter (http://i.imgur.com/CbHplu4.jpg ) got a nice upgrade via Reddit: http://i.imgur.com/W98Vkrt.jpg     
    
    
    @ourmaninchicago Just when you start to hate the Internet....    
    
    
    How great is it that the iPhone names every sent photo "Photo.jpg"? Zero great. None great.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 For now, the 30- or 60-second spot is still the core product of advertising.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 In this case, I think the goal is for the Top 10 to have a clear identity & not just feel like a recap of everything we cover.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 Originally, our "Freakiest Ads of the Year" was "Freakiest Advertising Moments" to be more inclusive, but it was just clunky.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 But yeah, good idea on the good ideas. Would probably be a totally different list, too.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 "5-10 good things from the past week or so" <- Finally, a pace we can all maintain.    
    
    
    Running a wide range of FB pages is surreal. Stoked about 50 new fans on one, disappointed by 10,000 new fans on another.    
    
    
    @sree Thanks for sharing my Q&A with @seetheglossary. Felt bad my editor, DFW megafan @nudd, was away and didn't get to write it himself.    
    
    
    My niece caught a 5-pound bass off my parents' pier. Biggest fish ever caught at the lakehouse! http://instagram.com/p/ZOM7J7v4o5/     
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk Tiny grub lure. No idea how it held fast.    
    
    
    @jelenawoehr Well, we definitely let this one go. My parents live right next to a nuclear power plant. :)    
    
    
    @megprpr Thanks so much. Really appreciate you coming out to the event.    
    
    
    Chuck E Cheese has a Tro-Lo-Lo parody. Solid. https://vine.co/v/bEa2YrAOK07     
    
    
    @omarg When I read your poor man's Don Draper, all I hear is GOB from Arrested Development.    
    
    
    @megprpr Was not familiar with @FORKology, but it sounds interesting. Could be a good fit for our work on @AlabamaFood.    
    
    
    Email webinar just showed pic of baboons to illustrate acronym APES. Those are monkeys, buddy. I question all your facts now!    
    
    
    @cebsilver I'll retweet that if you retweet this.    
    
    
    Email webinar just corrected baboons as monkeys not apes. Thank you, equally nerdy participant who actually put it in as Q&A feedback.    
    
    
    @mattplanet Everyone in the room seems convinced it was me.    
    
    
    @scottschablow My wife also likes to correct every reference where Curious George is called a "monkey." He has no tail, so must be an ape.    
    
    
    @armano HulkArmano in T minus 3....2...    
    
    
    @armano We don't choose how the gamma radiation affects us.    
    
    
    @SadieAwesome I like my women like I like my alternative-history fiction: Dubious of U.S. exceptionalism & obsessed w/ WWII. #PickupMetaphor    
    
    
    I find the intro of the He-Man remake hilarious. https://vine.co/v/bEUU365WjTA     
    
    
    People who've seen both: Iron Man 3 or Star Trek? Need to make the most of date night.    
    
    
    @bengreenman Good to know someone prospered during the Depression.    
    
    
    @HPippen3 My dad and I were just talking about what a perfect day it is for a movie theater. Muggy as all getout.    
    
    
    Selling my Sega Genesis + Sega CD, both in great working condition. http://bham.craigslist.org/vgm/3813804661.html …    
    
    
    @CamilleTGipson One of the best tweets ever. Could probably become a book deal. @etbowser    
    
    
    So....why are so many people leaving Tumblr? Do we hate Yahoo now?    
    
    
    @Techevarr My mortgage has been sold five times and I've never even cared who bought it. Hard to muster the energy over a tumblog.    
    
    
    @Techevarr It settled down eventually. Re-fi'd 2 years ago, and only one transfer since. Bounced around a lot during the '08 crazies.    
    
    
    @Techevarr I guess a 15-year fixed w/ reliable payment history became a hot commodity after the subprime freakout.    
    
    
    @Boldface My feed is nothing but Oklahoma tornados. Wishing you the best of luck, from one tornado state to another.    
    
    
    Nutella lawyers shut down World Nutella Day, a fan tradition since 2007: http://adweek.it/16M9cx2     
    
    
    @jbarbush Worth checking out this one too, apparently: http://bit.ly/18fAJoD     
    
    
    Apparently video game controller design hit its theoretical limit in 2005. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    Skype / group video chat integration into the Xbox One might finally make sci-fi video calling seem legit. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @katykelley When that day comes, I'll pay you $7 to dress like Princess Leia and repeat the same line over and over.    
    
    
    Xbox One won't have a CD tray, so I guess I'll have to find something else to stab with a paper clip every third night. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    Wait, what? For reals? Re the new Kinect: "When you're exercising it can read your heartbeat." #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @katykelley Shiiiit, I was gonna do that anyway.    
    
    
    @meggerz04 That's some Continuum tech right there. Can it tell if you're pregnant? #xboxreveal    
    
    
    But can the new Kinect make me sweat til I bleed? Because THAT would be dope enough, indeed. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @ElmntsofMadness @meggerz04 I'm sure the Open MRI add-on will be ready for holiday 2014.    
    
    
    First Xbox One sports titles are soccer, football, basketball & ultimate fighting. Baseball joins hockey in the cultural gutter. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @erniebufflo Crazy, but neat.    
    
    
    How was I not already following my longtime friend, transportation guru and Nat'l Press Club president @agreilingkeane? Fixed.    
    
    
    Good reminder. RT @lmerricks: If you’re sending relief supplies to OK, I learned in AL that manual can openers are always needed. #OKNeeds    
    
    
    Looking gift cookies in the mouth. https://vine.co/v/bVublJwEYK5     
    
    
    @NikiDoyle Not sure how we haven't crossed paths (until @MollyFolse mentioned you to me today). Are you a Huntsville native? (I am.)    
    
    
    @MeghanHoyer Well, you shouldn't crowd the pan. But yeah, not too shabby.    
    
    
    If Nikola Tesla had to ask for money from today's venture capitalists: http://adweek.it/13NyTdB     
    
    
    @thenoodleator Sorry, they want you to be a what? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8668AcOoEpY …    
    
    
    I like the optimism of the vendor who emailed me "Can we connect this week?" on the Friday afternoon before a holiday.    
    
    
    Just learned I've written 427 blog posts for @AdFreak since April 2007. Random Friday stat courtesy of @Nudd.    
    
    
    Never heard of this, but apparently it's quite popular. Last one! http://instagram.com/p/Ztl4ttv4mO/     
    
    
    @NikiDoyle Wow, the phrase "an hour west of Huntsville" is not something you hear often. Let's grab coffee sometime soon.    
    
    
    The Birmingham subreddit is having a Rogue Tavern meetup tonight at 8:30. Details: http://www.reddit.com/r/Birmingham/comments/1f1j4r/meetup_tonight_at_rogue_tavern/ …    
    
    
    Just met a double-jointed guy. It's uh... https://vine.co/v/bVweQqLJ6F1     
    
    
    Capoeira lessons from mommy. https://vine.co/v/bVFljughw7J     
    
    
    Got the peas and hot peppers set up in the #Earthbox. Obviously the cucumbers behind them have a head… http://instagram.com/p/ZyneOQv4my/     
    
    
    He died a noble death. https://vine.co/v/bVU9MEm6Im3     
    
    
    @megprpr Never hurts to ask for case studies or references so you can see what they've actually accomplished vs. just numbers.    
    
    
    Funny how Facebook has turned childbirth into a real-time spectator sport. Watching a friend get peppered w/ update requests by the minute.    
    
    
    @americopywriter Great point. It's a pointless distraction. People need to learn to just wait.    
    
    
    @jsandford I'm sure you can yell for Siri to take care of all that.    
    
    
    @ToddWasserman Tilt your head, and it's Pol Pot drinking from a human skull.    
    
    
    Wisdom from my 5-year-old daughter: "Daddy, let's build a Death Star. But without a hole for good guys to blow it up through."    
    
    
    Copywriter leaves agency after 16 years, and his first solo ad hits the front page of Reddit: http://adweek.it/1aDOSew     
    
    
    @Mister_Wang Only thing Reddit likes better than DIY is DIYWSITTM. Do It Yourself While Sticking It To The Man.    
    
    
    @sssemester Seems like everyone's first or second tweet is "trying to figure out Twitter" or something like "Is this thing on?"    
    
    
    Super excited about finally getting to see Superman's origin story. No idea where that guy came from.    
    
    
    Anyone grow up with Drake's snacks?    
    
    
    @SarahWCaron DMIng you now.... :)    
    
    
    I'm about 6 episodes deep in the new season of Arrested Development. Does it bother to get funny at some point?    
    
    
    @soapnana Good to hear. Watched that one last night.    
    
    
    @adamostrow Hope it's Reddit's turn now.    
    
    
    @Andy_Aspirin Classiness side, I didn't say anything negative about the ad. Said it cut through the clutter by using dubstep. It's fine.    
    
    
    This is amazing: Children's cancer center rebrands chemo treatment as "Superformula" - http://bit.ly/15yjPAJ  By @davegian    
    
    
    @cebsilver Lo, and on the sixth day he pivoted the tables, and it was good.    
    
    
    With SalesForce and ExactTarget merging, my vendor roster will have gone from 4 to 2 to 1 in the course of two years. #MergerMania    
    
    
    @michaeldamboldt And a prestige class.    
    
    
    @patrickklepek Very cool that he's being honored and doubly great that you could accept it in his name.    
    
    
    @mattplanet Your rich uncle, rich father AND rich great-aunt will love it. #MtBrookFamilyFriendly    
    
    
    Asked daughter if she wanted to try someplace "new and exciting for dinner." "Yes!" "Wait, what do you consider exciting?" "A playground!"    
    
    
    @gsalinas I was going to try taking her to that Persian place by Guitar Center. I canceled the plan, then learned later it's closed    
    
    
    @desaraev The random "helpful guy" in the yoga vid was hilarious.    
    
    
    @gsalinas I think it's straight-up closed for good. Haven't driven by, but Urban Spoon says it's gone.    
    
    
    I didn't plant any of these squash. They all grew out if the compost. http://instagram.com/p/aPHgP9P4qO/     
    
    
    @YoungbloodJoe Good idea.    
    
    
    @RealSheree I got one cantaloupe plant last year, but nothing really came out of it. At least this year I'll have something to show for it.    
    
    
    Please take a moment today to vote for my agency, @LuckieAndCo, in the Medium category of #SocialMadness: http://bit.ly/19CIJBR     
    
    
    @JessicaDonlon Researchers plan to first test the invisibility cloak by sneaking past Professor Snape and into Hogsmeade.    
    
    
    @RowdyBowden Edward Burns.    
    
    
    "This video contains adult content. Please enter a completely fake birthday so we can pretend we tried to stop you."    
    
    
    Gamers growing increasingly incensed with Microsoft's #XboxOne: http://bit.ly/14lXyGB     
    
    
    Shrine of the Most Glorious Future, an exhibit by John Lytle Wilson. https://vine.co/v/bLn2dXYHXAd     
    
    
    @natbro Wanted to send you a few questions for an article I'm working on. Can you DM me a good email address to hit you at?    
    
    
    Live blogs are great for some things, but not the Mac Pro reveal. It's like listening to 10 drunk bats describe an elephant. #wwdc    
    
    
    There have been 7.4 trillion iOS push notifications? That's a truly sprawling amount of annoyance. #WWDC    
    
    
    Xbox One will be $499. http://www.engadget.com/2013/06/10/microsoft-xbox-one-price-availability/ …    
    
    
    @LadySnarksalot Oh good, I was just looking for offhanded ways to improve us.    
    
    
    I have no idea why she's reading Lovecraft in the dark, but I'm very proud. http://instagram.com/p/aZmNgiv4gu/     
    
    
    @jenbarnett It is known.    
    
    
    Any guesses on what's growing out of my compost? Butternut? Pumpkin? http://instagram.com/p/acFjSov4i_/     
    
    
    @jasonhmartin That might be more manageable at this point.    
    
    
    @jenbarnett I've never eaten an acorn squash, so doubtful it'd be in my compost. I'm terrified I might have 35 pumpkin plants.    
    
    
    @jenbarnett Zero, but I did throw a whole one into the compost bin after Halloween. Never again.    
    
    
    The 11 grossest fast food abominations from around the world: http://adweek.it/11vU2nU  My collaboration w/ @EpicMealTime    
    
    
    What are you doing in Tennessee, my old Midwestern friend? @ Culver's http://instagram.com/p/aeaA_ev4vw/     
    
    
    Ron Burgundy said it best: http://bit.ly/XrEzDr  RT @jonmbauer: Today's traffic jam gold: a guy eating corn on the cob for breakfast.    
    
    
    Who are some little-known but awesomely talented crafty bloggers?    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Crafty, like in the Beastie Boys way. Gets around, always down.    
    
    
    .@Mashable connected me w/ a photog for free social consulting. He built audience, but struggling to build sales: http://on.mash.to/1bzNN8a     
    
    
    @lmerricks Awesome, thanks!    
    
    
    POP TART TRUCK! https://vine.co/v/blFngL5pOZP     
    
    
    Just visited a site that lets you close its page-covering pop-up ad, but then makes you wait out the 15 seconds of blank screen anyway.    
    
    
    Our midcentury modern house just got a bit more modern. http://instagram.com/p/alJXigP4t0/     
    
    
    And so it begins: Pickle Season! http://instagram.com/p/aoDSmAP4g_/     
    
    
    @hanniespice It's incredibly easy and fun in a zen, crafty way. First few batches can be stressful, but I can send you tips if you go for it    
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk @elizarde Pickling on the stove top kinda wrecks the joy of an air conditioned house, but totally worth it.    
    
    
    @hanniespice Wow, that's super gross. Thanks for the extra motivation to keep up my DIY approach to pickles.    
    
    
    Bham folks, what's up with 31 traffic in Hoover/ Vestavia this morning?  Crawling to work.    
    
    
    Go home, Excel. You're drunk. pic.twitter.com/sk5HfyS7Cn    
    
    
    @digitaldamsel I should just file it and see what happens.    
    
    
    @jvreeland It was all going so well, too, until.... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZWrv3l_2tGQ …    
    
    
    Great Twitter promoted content feature: target non-mobile users. FB needs this, since its apps don't work in mobile. pic.twitter.com/sdjerwbFEM    
    
    
    In case you thought you were having a rough morning... http://instagram.com/p/ax_We9P4kN/     
    
    
    @LaraIsNatasha Overturned semi.    
    
    
    If you have to start a message with "I'm following up on the earlier emails and voicemails I left you," your sales prospects are slim.    
    
    
    Just discovered the "My Imaginary Well-Dressed Toddler Daughter" Pinterest Board. A. Mazing. http://pinterest.com/tiffanywbwg/my-imaginary-well-dressed-toddler-daughter/ …    
    
    
    @SouthernDrawlll There are so few handy resources for us parents of wealthy waspy fashion-forward toddlers.    
    
    
    Thousands of pre-written brand tweets and FB posts congratulating the Spurs were today donated to needy children in third-world nations.    
    
    
    @cebsilver But thanks to YouSendIt, the shipping is much faster.    
    
    
    End of an era: @dberkowitz leaving @360i to become CMO for agency MRY. http://www.marketersstudio.com/2013/06/thank-you-360i.html …    
    
    
    "Sloths are like a mixture of opossums and monkeys." - @aprilwilson_    
    
    
    Earning his keep at the farmers market. @ Pepper Place Saturday Market http://instagram.com/p/a3bs9Ev4sq/     
    
    
    Cold AC inside, cold beer outside. Good day for a hot afternoon. http://instagram.com/p/a4JV0uv4kE/     
    
    
    I find it darkly entertaining that a hotel's hold music is "I'm On Fire."    
    
    
    New SnapChat for kids, "SnapKidz", doesn't actually send any messages. That's one way to keep it safe, I guess. http://mashable.com/2013/06/24/snapchat-kidz/ …    
    
    
    @MarshaCollier I like to think I'm still years away from having to make these parenting decisions, but it's coming up scary fast.    
    
    
    At a public utilities conference, and proud to see an analysis of social media use ranked our client, @alabamapower, in the nation's Top 10.    
    
    
    @alanjones19 I'm a fan of working for change within the system. But that's a conversation best had over beer, not over Twitter.    
    
    
    @JasonChupick Strange times.    
    
    
    Samsung S4 users, what are your favorite apps?    
    
    
    Vaguebooking makes me irrationally frustrated. It's like someone walking into your office, sitting down and saying "Life, you know?"    
    
    
    Recently hired folks, what job listing sites did you use to keep an eye on openings?    
    
    
    @KatieKMundy Great, thanks. Specifically posting a PR/social media position, so your feedback's extra valuable.    
    
    
    We're all so proud. RT @LuckieAndCo: April Wilson started as a @LuckieAndCo intern, and now... https://vine.co/v/haajTEIjq12     
    
    
    @sewlovedshop I don't know what any of that means...    
    
    
    Party I was at last night had a guy playing a log. http://instagram.com/p/bJXoRoP4nx/     
    
    
    Excited to announce @KatieStrasser has joined @LuckieAndCo as a Digital Content Writer. Katie, congrats on surviving your first day!    
    
    
    Massive #job opening on my team at @LuckieAndCo in Bham: Social Media/PR Specialist - http://bit.ly/1cMTG2s     
    
    
    My boss traded me a dozen of his chickens' eggs for a jar of my homemade pickles. #PostApocalypseEconomy http://instagram.com/p/bSA97Yv4hc/     
    
    
    @Charter I'm a customer getting daily sales calls from your reps on my cell, trying to upsell me. How do I make it stop?    
    
    
    @Charter Thanks! Unrelated: We set up autopay months ago, but no payments ever went through. Saw similar complaints online. Thoughts?    
    
    
    @Charter Great, thanks again.    
    
    
    Texters are the new drunk drivers, and cell talkers are the new stoned drivers. Soooo sloooow.    
    
    
    If you could fight crime by making omelets, I would, because it's pretty much my only super power. http://instagram.com/p/bWbDTEP4np/     
    
    
    I'm in Publix savings beast mode. http://instagram.com/p/bW5OF6P4v5/     
    
    
    @Leslie_Wiggins $1,798. ... Just kidding, it was a pretty normal one-cart trip, but I bought tons of cherries on sale $4/off per pound.    
    
    
    Informational cooler labeling. http://instagram.com/p/bbyULav4tA/     
    
    
    Heartbroken to hear about the death (at age 34) of my favorite podcast host, Ryan Davis from @GiantBomb: http://bit.ly/11vREE5     
    
    
    @JustinMcElroy Nice piece on Remembering Ryan.    
    
    
    2,400+ comments on @GiantBomb's podcast remembering @taswell. Amazing how many people he had an impact on. http://bit.ly/15d5S9Q     
    
    
    @jthrashr Yeah, I guess that's part of the benefit of waiting a few days to announce. And definitely fitting. Cracked me up several times.    
    
    
    #FollowFriday shoutout to the planet's best Digital Content team: @MollyFolse, @KatieStrasser, @Caetee, @aprilwilson_, @loisk    
    
    
    Spotify thanks user @jelenawoehr by creating a playlist with a secret message just for her: http://bit.ly/16yE9Qv     
    
    
    Catching up on all the back orders for spicy pickles and okra. http://instagram.com/p/bwNxPBv4sZ/     
    
    
    @kenisajerk Oh I see how it is...turn down a job on my team and then ask for @AdFreak coverage?! ;)    
    
    
    @kenisajerk Noticed your toothpaste project last week. Fun stuff.    
    
    
    @kenisajerk Ha, just giving you shit. Peter Mayer's a great shop.    
    
    
    Or laptops/tablets. RT @askRegions: Take advantage of your hotel’s safe. Don’t leave extra cash or duplicate cards out in your room.    
    
    
    Epic tweet RT @washingtonpost: Old worry: Falling asleep on top of the train and slipping off.
New worry: Kidnappers. http://wapo.st/18jAuZW     
    
    
    @evantravers As someone who collected baseball cards for years, I knew what to do: sell those things the second I could. @yanisvaroufakis    
    
    
    Anyone who's seen the @Adweek traffic stats knows it should really be called Nuddweek. Happy #FF to marketing's master journalist, @Nudd.    
    
    
    Just realized I recently posted my 15,000th tweet. That's 2,500 tweets a year since joining in 2008. Now I feel like a chatterbox.    
    
    
    @tsh Every time I bust out the canoe at the lake, my nephews and nieces pile in like a clown car. Maybe someday one of them will paddle.    
    
    
    @ktannerdesigns I would totally retweet that if your account wasn't private. Great shot. #PicklePride    
    
    
    Cobbler time. http://instagram.com/p/cAENdjv4im/     
    
    
    Manhunt in Shelby County, Ala., for an escaped inmate, last seen in a tan Chevy Malibu: http://www.myfoxal.com/story/22899068/manhunt-underway-for-escaped-inmate-in-shelby-county …    
    
    
    My wife's in the top .0001% of meticulous household budgeters, so the fact that she loves @YNAB is high praise indeed. Great software.    
    
    
    @matt_bart We jumped right to ver. 4, so I can't speak to how it's improved. Took her a few days to learn the ins and outs, but works great.    
    
    
    @sewlovedshop If you have any questions on budgeting, let me know. My wife's always happy to share her secrets. @ynab    
    
    
    @ShaunChavis Happy to help. Email me at griner (at) gmail. Also, @cturnip is pickle maven in her own right, in case you need another.    
    
    
    @ShaunChavis My references: http://instagram.com/p/bwNxPBv4sZ/  :)    
    
    
    "Don't worry, I won't sell you or kill you." #ModernChivalry http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/07/22/blind-date-_n_3635648.html?utm_hp_ref=tw …    
    
    
    @NoMeatballs But what if the doorbell is ringing from INSIDE THE HOUSE?    
    
    
    My pick for ad of the day: Vodafone's well-made modernization of lovesick teens "waiting by the phone" - http://adweek.it/14QItyU     
    
    
    @crushtoronto Have you guys done #SadieCam before? Hope to do it again?    
    
    
    @CrushToronto Did you guys record any of the livestream? I'd love to embed it in our @AdFreak writeup.    
    
    
    @CrushToronto Sounds great. If you can get it to me over the weekend, I'll get it added in. griner at gmail.    
    
    
    @CrushToronto Also, belated props to @glossyinc for posting the Sadie project on FB early enough that I could watch it in action.    
    
    
    Love seeing all the #AlabamaFood pride at Pepper Place. @ Pepper Place Saturday Market http://instagram.com/p/cRqMGIv4gL/     
    
    
    Recognized @BitterOldPunk and @Elizarde from Twitter last night and crashed their anniversary date. Great time! pic.twitter.com/lkRVhNvGVn    
    
    
    Hey Pope....I like your style.    
    
    
    @elizarde Definitely! When you get a second, follow my account so I can DM you my personal contact info. cc @BitterOldPunk    
    
    
    @katyawachtel @abeaujon Somewhere, Ned Flanders is stammering out his objection to such foul-diddly-doggone language.    
    
    
    @DylanByers I thought BOOM RT meant "Bitter Orator Of Missouri Real Talk." Or "Blast Orphan Onto Moon, Relax Tonight." #NowIKnow    
    
    
    @JusticeMitchell The last time I saw that much meat in a bottle, a doctor had to get involved. HEYOOOO    
    
    
    #ContentCocktails night with the team. @ Little Savannah Restaurant http://instagram.com/p/cfYOtkv4gr/     
    
    
    In time out, channeling Steve McQueen from the Great Escape. https://vine.co/v/hbrD6YLE2tO     
    
    
    Time to go terrify Scooby-Doo. http://instagram.com/p/c2HzHTv4qK/     
    
    
    I obviously liked this house in Fort Morgan. http://instagram.com/p/c2l3WNP4im/     
    
    
    DOUBLE RAINBOW. http://instagram.com/p/c5EPmLP4oM/     
    
    
    @adakevms I'll write a very detailed note on my Final Jeopardy answer screen.    
    
    
    A talking dog for a dad. A black son from America. Meet Japan's most popular ad family: http://adweek.it/169kMlY     
    
    
    @EvanBenner Thanks. I was shocked to learn how huge the campaign was. Just don't run across such things much over here.    
    
    
    Good Q. Seinfeld maybe? RT @caff: Where did "Is this a thing?" and "This should be a thing" come from? I'm missing the context.    
    
    
    @ginidietrich No. 7: Wear jeans.    
    
    
    This is awesome: San Pellegrino lets you take control of a robot to tour Sicily and talk to the locals - http://adweek.it/17L6u6F     
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary There's only room for one self-centered jerk in my department. @LuckieAndCo    
    
    
    @jsandford I'm apparently feeling troll-y today. @ginidietrich    
    
    
    @caff I also saw mentions that Joss Whedon and Aaron Sorkin shows popularized it in the 90s. I can picture Josh from West Wing saying it.    
    
    
    @WadeOnTweets Thanks, Wade!    
    
    
    @zacksyl Thanks, man!    
    
    
    @wagnerlk I stand by it. But admittedly, the bar for funniest Jell-O ad is quite low. @bobbbyg @AdFreak    
    
    
    My mother-in-law found a phonebox lantern and painted it #Tardis blue for my birthday! http://instagram.com/p/dCShnCv4s7/     
    
    
    I think I just got followed by the Da Vinci Code. http://instagram.com/p/dDN87Uv4gO/     
    
    
    @TroyBakerVA It's like a reverse version of Taken. Teenage girl doesn't know who you are, but she will find you.    
    
    
    @mareejones Ours is starting kindergarten too. It's....quite different than when I was a kid. But looks awesome.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sushi Village was sending me mixed signals at lunch yesterday. http://instagram.com/p/dPKIk6P4ll/     
    
    
    Great piece on one of the nicest guys in the corporate social media world, @JasonEng_ - http://bit.ly/1cTgTp2  Thanks, @ricdragon    
    
    
    My new piece for @Polygon - http://sbn.to/15dRe4F  - is worth it just for @sleeptest's design and @steve_courtney's illustrations.    
    
    
    @tec2030 Hey thanks!    
    
    
    @MossTweet Ha, thanks, Thomas. Great getting some actual in-person time yesterday.    
    
    
    What will happen to your Xbox 360, PS3 or Wii over the next 30 years? My new piece for @Polygon: http://sbn.to/15dRe4F     
    
    
    Some holes in your life can never be filled. I have questions only my mentor could answer, but he passed away in 2008.    
    
    
    Samsung's laughably horrible promo: When amateur talent and awkward creative direction collide - http://adweek.it/13W8SXd     
    
    
    @sarahpressler Agreed. It's just begging for a send-up.    
    
    
    @Techevarr Thanks for the feedback! I tend to sell every game the minute I'm done with it, but I might hang on to a few favorites.    
    
    
    Join my team? RT @LuckieAndCo: Our #Bham office is looking for a Digital Content #Intern: http://bit.ly/188OoeS     
    
    
    @AdamSinger First the honey and syrup, now the tuna?!    
    
    
    Apparently in Miley's world, "growing up" means twerking and doing ecstasy. In my day, it meant getting LESS stupid.    
    
    
    @TheNextMartha You can hit up @MollyFolse for Google Drive tips. She built out our agency's shared-doc system on there.    
    
    
    @PRJessicaC I'm sure the Internet can make that happen.    
    
    
    @jenbshaw Aw, that's rough. Hope it passes quickly!    
    
    
    @TheNextMartha While @MollyFolse is out lollygagging, I'm happy to try to help on your Drive issue.    
    
    
    Anyone know how to access the old Google Docs Templates directly from Google Drive?    
    
    
    @cebsilver Holding out hope for Mel Gibson as Darkseid.    
    
    
    Wow, huge influx of DM spam this morning. You'd think Twitter would have a handle on this by now.    
    
    
    @ericaendicott @mareejones Syrian hackers at it again, getting the word out about weight-loss secrets.    
    
    
    @AudreyRuns Yep! Check http://luckierethinktank.com  @LuckieAndCo    
    
    
    @mattsingley There should be a bingo card. Dibs on the square for T-shirts referencing Atari controllers and/or the phrase "old school"    
    
    
    @SadieAwesome Awesome, Sadie! #palindromictweets    
    
    
    Honored to be named one of the @BhamBizJrnl's #40toFollow: http://bit.ly/164RbZt  Some awesome folks in there.    
    
    
    @fiPlanPartners Thanks! And thanks, @ChrisCreates!    
    
    
    My request for a public Q&A with "Head of Potatoes" @SarahDurdinR has vaulted to the front page of Reddit: http://bit.ly/15M5LRf     
    
    
    The guy with chairs was literally closing a place while I filmed this. https://vine.co/v/hJEd7Qizxva     
    
    
    @SarahDurdinR Great! Just go here - http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/  - and click "Submit an AMA" on the right. (You'll need a Reddit account)    
    
    
    @SarahDurdinR Title can be something like "I am Head of Potatoes Sarah Durdin Robertson. AMA!"  Then just answer as many as you can. :)    
    
    
    @SarahDurdinR You'll need to post "Proof" that you're the real you. Usually a pic holding a sign that says "Hi Reddit" or somesuch.    
    
    
    @adakevms @gsalinas City Center's been sad for a while, but now it's an absolute ghost town. Such a great location, too.    
    
    
    @BenBloodworth Carmike cinema now, but yeah, same one.    
    
    
    Just invented "The Mason-Dixon Shandy." Michigan and Georgia, together at last. http://instagram.com/p/eBDfyqv4qa/     
    
    
    @Free_Burge @MaryColurso You guys started a cover band?!    
    
    
    @lmerricks Thanks, Lori!    
    
    
    @mcclain2224 Thanks, Melissa!    
    
    
    Brands are really being pounded today for daring to mention 9/11. Most "fail" examples I've seen are shrug-worthy at best/worst.    
    
    
    Looking for bar recommendations on Yelp, and top review for one says it's "comfortable like grandma's fat lap." Uhh...    
    
    
    @adakevms Oh man, so many hours of hard drinking on that fat, comfortable knee.    
    
    
    Just presented to a medical conference on managing online reviews. They key? Make it easy to share feedback, online and off.    
    
    
    @jamiebeckman Congrats!    
    
    
    Seen in L.A. I declined. http://instagram.com/p/eV_NGfv4gX/     
    
    
    @RoisinB "Glad you asked! It's human skin!"    
    
    
    A map of the nation's top agencies by state: http://adweek.it/1eJ12KI  Great work by @Nudd for @Adweek    
    
    
    Can't believe Facebook graph search still doesn't support post search. Searching public content seems pretty cost-of-admission.    
    
    
    Anyone else going to see Phosphorescent tonight in Bham?    
    
    
    @tessa That's a "Napoleon in Russia" level retreat.    
    
    
    Hard root beer float. Let's do this. http://instagram.com/p/ekm6rPv4rN/     
    
    
    Thanks for the book, @angengland! Time to put it to good use! http://instagram.com/p/ek-6Bav4sp/     
    
    
    Just another dinner in the South. https://vine.co/v/hrb1ZrxhP1H     
    
    
    @AngEngland At least they all apply to my lifestyle!    
    
    
    @AngEngland Just the butchery.    
    
    
    @adakevms You handle the bloodletting and I'll do the rest. @AngEngland    
    
    
    Today is National Check Your 'Other' Inbox on Facebook Day! How will YOU be celebrating?    
    
    
    @LotusCarroll So I take it "Our Lady of the Bathroom Selfie" never got its IRS exemption?    
    
    
    Fake Apple landing page touts iOS7 as waterproof; shenanigans ensue.  http://adweek.it/19ATl0W     
    
    
    Just realized my slideshares have been viewed 554,000 times. Never really think about that site, but maybe I should.    
    
    
    Yay, another book from @angengland! Stoked for next planting season. http://instagram.com/p/etIFlVP4ip/     
    
    
    Finally getting to see @ambercadabra speak after years of being "social media friends." #typeacon    
    
    
    "If something scares the pants off of you, it's probably something you should pursue. " - @AmberCadabra #exceptclowns #typeacon    
    
    
    @ikepigott Will do! @AmberCadabra    
    
    
    How is it so many amazing women face "impostor syndrome"? How do we teach our daughters to value affirmation but not depend on it? #typeacon    
    
    
    .@AmberCadabra warns not to envy bloggers who seem to have it all together. "People are showing you what they want you to see." #typeacon    
    
    
    @allthingsfadra It's a short drive... @MackCollier could b3 here by lunch. @KerryGorgone @RobynsWorld    
    
    
    Hard to follow a class act like @AmberCadabra, but I'll be speaking at #typeacon on building your Facebook audience at 10. Should be fun!    
    
    
    @chilihead It's kinda sad that "faking it" has become synonymous w/ being confident in your own opinions, you know?    
    
    
    @chilihead And even sadder that many of those who believe they're faking it will never accomplish enough to convince themselves otherwise.    
    
    
    Man, what an awesome crowd for my session on FB growth at #TypeACon today. Great questions, super nice/smart people. Posting slides soon.    
    
    
    @MyGOMOM Thanks for the great tweets today from #TypeACon!    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden @goodgirlgonered Thanks for coming out to my session today and sharing some of the info!    
    
    
    @UrbanMooCow Thanks for the feedback on my session! Glad you enjoyed it. Had a great time.    
    
    
    @centsiblelife Thanks for the awesome and helpful tweeting during y session, Kelly!    
    
    
    @JameeTMiller Thanks for coming out to my session today! Glad to hear it was helpful.    
    
    
    @BeginToCraft Thanks for coming out to the session! Hope your Facebook experimentations go well.    
    
    
    @mommyswishlist Thanks for the feedback! Really enjoyed the crowd today.    
    
    
    @westoftheloop So glad to hear it was a helpful session this morning! Looking forward to more chats while we're at #TypeACon    
    
    
    Here are my slides from today's #TypeACon session on building your Facebook audience: http://slidesha.re/18w7Iom     
    
    
    @thesimplerweb Thank YOU! Had a great time today.    
    
    
    Ha, @ResourcefulMom just got applause for telling #TypeACon audience how to disable Google calendar invites unless you RSVP'd.    
    
    
    @Jennifer_Bilbro Can never have enough things!    
    
    
    Just about dropped my phone when I saw this notification. http://instagram.com/p/ex1kJYv4hM/     
    
    
    @debng @Girlfriendology @Cookerati How great! I'll be the guy in the...pants.    
    
    
    @ostmega (Groggy nod of agreement.) #TypeACon    
    
    
    @Samsungtweets OK, that got a chuckle out of me. Well played.    
    
    
    @djambazov @theamytucker @phollows For the record, I can never thank you three enough for all you've done to support @HeatherSolos.    
    
    
    Really hard to put into words what a great event #TypeACon is. Huge enthusiasm for learning and community, and a super welcoming vibe.    
    
    
    So cool: My longtime friends and clients at @VisitAsheville have created a stunning #html5 exploration of fall color: http://bit.ly/16K9V0v     
    
    
    @gweiswasser @momadvice @Linda_Sellers Looking forward to your session this morning! Hope brand reps attend (and absorb) too.    
    
    
    Just starting: #TypeACon panel on blogger-brand partnerships. Amazing panel - @momadvice, @linda_sellers, @gweiswasser. mod: @chilihead    
    
    
    Brands looking for blog partners now focus on strong content and a wide-reaching network more than raw audience numbers. #typeacon    
    
    
    When bloggers partner with brands that fit their audience, readers often won't notice/care that content is branded. - @momadvice #typeacon    
    
    
    Bloggers should only work for free if there's a chance it could grow into a profitable/rewarding partnership. -@Momadvice #typeacon    
    
    
    I've never asked bloggers to work for free, and no one else should either. It's disrespectful and short-sighted. #TypeACon    
    
    
    "Blogger trips" are getting old, @resourcefulmom says. Becomes less about feedback than about "nice dinners." #typeacon    
    
    
    @notasupermom But there's definitely a huge ripple effect from the way 1%ers are treated/compensated. @ResourcefulMom #typeacon    
    
    
    OH on 'blogger trips': "If you want me to write a blog post, but want me to fly halfway across the country to do it, no." #typeacon    
    
    
    @thesimplerweb If you're doing brand partnerships, especially w/ agencies, helps to mention that you offer that service.    
    
    
    @thesimplerweb Most marketers think of bloggers and freelancers as different crowds, so good to show exp w/ non-opinion, unbylined work.    
    
    
    @notasupermom That factory tour junkets become seen as the pinnacle of blogger compensation.    
    
    
    @cc_chapman @ResourcefulMom I just feel that a multi-day trip is literally the most you can ask from a blogger, and it needs to be rewarding    
    
    
    @ScaryMommy Well I'm glad/sorry to hear it! Slides are here, if you're interested: http://slidesha.re/18w7Iom  Thanks for the note!    
    
    
    Next panel: Amazing women accomplishing amazing things through cause blogging. @chrysula @allthingsfadra @RealLifeSarah @ilinap #TypeACon    
    
    
    How to find your cause: "Start w/ your passion. What do you see happening in the world that breaks your heart?" -@reallifesarah #typeacon    
    
    
    @mochadad @mommyswishlist Whoah, I want one!    
    
    
    @chilihead @ruthburr The tweets are FLYING out of that session. I'm next door but looking forward to seeing the slides. #typeacon    
    
    
    Easy ways to help causes: '10 Empowering Apps for Social Good' via @Mashable - http://mashable.com/2013/09/20/social-good-apps/ … #typeacon    
    
    
    There's a stigma against bloggers being paid for nonprofit work, which stinks. Professional work shouldn't always be pro-bono. #typeacon    
    
    
    Want bloggers to help your nonprofit cause? Share why it's YOUR passion and get them fired up to help. -@allthingsfadra #typeacon    
    
    
    @ResourcefulMom I feel guilty take swag food at booths, so….grab me a cranberry zone bar. :) #seriousrequest    
    
    
    @centsiblelife Before I forget to mention it, you are really crushing it at live-tweeting #TypeACon. Awesome job sharing insight, resources.    
    
    
    Which is here: http://moz.com/beginners-guide-to-seo … RT @chilihead: Check out @Moz's free Beginner's Guide to SEO. #typeacon    
    
    
    Great case study in innovative fundraising: #GivingTuesday, via @chrysula - http://www.92y.org/givingtuesday  #typeacon    
    
    
    Great sponsor, great team - RT @typeamom: "Be sure to stop by and say hello to #typeacon sponsor @FeedBlitz at booth #202!"    
    
    
    How to build your Facebook audience without breaking the rules: http://slidesha.re/18w7Iom  My deck from #typeacon    
    
    
    Bloggers: Approached about a free sample/giveaway you don't really want? Ask if you can donate it to local charity. -@ilinip #typeacon    
    
    
    Think it's not worth sharing a personal cause online? Friend said last night she got an email that her post prevented a suicide. #typeacon    
    
    
    Excited for the next #typeacon session about my niche: bald bloggers. #notreally #actuallydads pic.twitter.com/XG0F9bVRqz    
    
    
    Dad says he was uninvited from blogger event because "the moms would feel uncomfortable, sexually." Ridiculous. #typeacon    
    
    
    Stage tweet! RT @Daddymojo: Speaking with @EPayneTheDad and @mochadad #typeacon pic.twitter.com/jcqkQFnwKr    
    
    
    @momadvice @ResourcefulMom Now just need to get you 2 AND @momspark in same room. Dark Crystal moment: 'When single shines the triple Amys…'    
    
    
    @RealLifeSarah Ditto, forever.    
    
    
    @kittenwithawhip A terrible thing, at best.    
    
    
    @typeamom Officially requesting to moderate the Amy Triforce Panel at #typeacon 2014. @momadvice @MomSpark @ResourcefulMom    
    
    
    Stage tweet WITH VINE! Epic! RT @EPayneTheDad: @daddymojo speaking to branding with dad bloggers. #typeacon https://vine.co/v/h6g651MAl7e     
    
    
    We are 24 minutes into Dad Blogger panel at #TypeACon and BatDad has not yet been mentioned. Waaaaait for it…..    
    
    
    @ColoradoMom I'll be there, Photobomb.    
    
    
    At dad blogger panel, @EPayneTheDad says he has no problem deleting comments from relatives who include real names in anecdotes. #typeacon    
    
    
    Good for blogger fams to have clear house rules, like @daddymojo's wife: "Don't mention me in your blog unless you ask me first." #typeacon    
    
    
    @mommyswishlist AMAZING!    
    
    
    @MelACulbertson If I shouted my wife's name when she least expected it, I would get a foot in the neck. #baddad #capoeirawife    
    
    
    "It was the mom blogs that made it possible for us to do what we do." -@daddymojo on dad blogging panel at #typeacon    
    
    
    How awesome is @mommyswishlist? Sketched this in no time at #typeacon http://instagram.com/p/ez5bs0s5e4/#     
    
    
    @its_jparker @BestDateNight Not sure on official data, but anecdotally, I'd say $20-$50 for a normal-length post (150-300 words)    
    
    
    Getting schooled on photography tricks for amateurs by the wonderful @JennHethcoat  at #typeaparent    
    
    
    For pics outside, shoot in shade, not in sun. "Brides get upset on cloudy days; photographers jump up and down." - @JennHethcoat #typeacon    
    
    
    @ColoradoMom Ha, wondered where you were hiding in this session. Right behind me!    
    
    
    @ResourcefulMom I should have busted out a flash. #punkrocklove    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden I also like to include ingredients that don't actually exist to easily catch people re-using my content. #protip #typeacon    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden *Tip: I like to order my gillyweed from http://BartyCrouchFiveFingerDiscount.com     
    
    
    Putting a thin black frame on photos can help them pop online, says @jennhethcoat (she uses "dark edges" option in PicMonkey) #typeacon    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden I really shouldn't interrupt you. You're my lifeline to the legal session.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Fair trade.    
    
    
    Never heard the word "bokeh" (artsy out-of-focus area of a shot) until @jennhethcoat's photography session at #typeacon.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden I have a Samsung S3, so the bokeh area takes up roughly 100% of every indoor shot.    
    
    
    @ResourcefulMom @coloradomom @techsavvymama That's … just ….                            #nowords    
    
    
    @localMANDI NextGen seems solid - http://wordpress.org/plugins/nextgen-facebook/ … But can't tell for certain it includes article:publisher. Probably does.    
    
    
    Hey @studionashvegas, @tammyhart, @dougal and other wordpress luminaries - best plugin for OG tags and other social metadata?    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Now I've learned about bokeh AND light scoops. Thanks!    
    
    
    @MomSpark I'm willing to take that risk. @momadvice @ResourcefulMom    
    
    
    @dougal @tammyhart Thanks! Led a session on Facebook metadata yesterday and now getting WP questions. Appreciate the tips!    
    
    
    @TheAmyTucker Earnestly, I hate that I couldn't do more. But it makes me feel better to know you did. @djambazov @phollows @HeatherSolos    
    
    
    @TheAmyTucker Yep, until 4:45ish    
    
    
    @localMANDI FYI, check out this thread from a few minutes ago - https://twitter.com/griner/status/384038543053438976 …    
    
    
    @TheAmyTucker 1715? I'm so confused. But no, not going to the att thing.    
    
    
    OK to pick/choose LinkedIn experience. "The story you're trying to tell is not, 'I've been employed my entire life.'" -@dbinkowski #typeacon    
    
    
    This restaurant brings you homemade salsa in a blood vial. http://instagram.com/p/e0kLwGv4sG/     
    
    
    @anniemal You know nothing, Annie Snow.    
    
    
    @techsavvymama @ResourcefulMom @coloradomom All these years, and the first inside joke I'm actually in on is #punkrocklove. I'm…OK with this    
    
    
    @chrysula Thanks! Great meeting you. Really got a lot out of your panel. #typeacon    
    
    
    Fond farewell to the #TypeACon crew. Best crowd / sessions / conversations / dinners / inappropriate hashtags yet. Will miss everyone.    
    
    
    @centsiblelife Definitely! Always end up walking away wishing I'd had even more time with more people. Good sign of a great event.    
    
    
    @LisaJohnson Well, the hashtags became PG shorthand for things best left untweeted. :)    
    
    
    @centsiblelife Yes, tell @roociambriello to be more generous with her time next year.    
    
    
    Three days of #typeacon will straight up thrash your voice. Me and @roociambriello sound like 'Coffee Chat With Bette Davis and Tom Waits'    
    
    
    Missed this crazy kook. http://instagram.com/p/e2ZDgFP4tv/     
    
    
    Great shot of Leticia! RT @typeaparentcon: @techsavvymama talks about short form video in content strategy #typeacon pic.twitter.com/kXTvuPkfFe"    
    
    
    @techsavvymama Great getting to spend so much time with you this time around. And yes, definitely need to know about the PTSD.    
    
    
    Back home and rocking the comfort food - sockeye salmon and lentils. http://instagram.com/p/e3ObZcP4ks/     
    
    
    So #typeacon '13 was officially my favorite conference ever. If we met up, please be sure to find me on LinkedIn: http://linkd.in/1aD9Mfo     
    
    
    @AnissaMayhew Just excited I got to see you as much as I did! Most time we've had together in years - which sucks!    
    
    
    @JulieMPron Heard it here first! :) Glad to hear it's rolling out wider.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Per my far-more-brilliant WP dev friends: @yoast’s SEO plugin, OG plugin by @willnorris, and NextGen- http://bit.ly/12WNiWl     
    
    
    @Finding_Walden That said, I haven't checked any of the three for article:publisher integration. Actually shopping for a new theme now.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Yeah, good question. I've been 100% focused on pub pages, but follower building can be good too.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Article:Author would trigger "Follow" button for public updates on your personal profile, if you opted in.    
    
    
    The Horrorita at #ContentCocktails @ Black Market Bar and Grill http://instagram.com/p/e5tUCSP4li/     
    
    
    Last day at @LuckieAndCo after eight amazing years. Sad to leave, but invigorated by the great response to my upcoming business launch.    
    
    
    @cc_chapman @LPT Official announcement to come, but I have a hunch you two specifically will really dig it.    
    
    
    @TomBLogue To come soon! Wanted to give Luckie 100% of my focus until my last day, but now ready to get moving.    
    
    
    @AdLawGuy You can't shake me that easy, McSunas. :)    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Thanks so much, Tom. That means a lot coming from you.    
    
    
    @boyswithguitars Thanks, BA! Hope to connect again in person sometime soon.    
    
    
    @designtramp Thanks, DT!    
    
    
    @SGibbie Details to come soon, but it involves digital content, amazingness and skyscraper-devouring giant locusts. Well, 2 out of 3.    
    
    
    @mommystory Oh wow, how terrible. So sorry you had to go through that, but great writeup and insights on avoiding it in the future.    
    
    
    @brharrison Hahah, well, details to come. But yes, starting my own content strategy firm and making more time for freelance journalism.    
    
    
    @mareejones I like Hulk Maree! Where's she been all these weeks? :)    
    
    
    @AmandaLeePowell Corn Pops for me, but yes. Glad to see you still know how to live the lifestyle.    
    
    
    @Osborne Thanks, and will do!    
    
    
    @BhamBizBrent Thanks, Brent! Will try to connect with you once the new venture is ready for prime time.    
    
    
    @HeatheroftheEO Here you go! http://www.slideshare.net/Griner/building-your-facebook-audience-dd …    
    
    
    Netflix just added new episodes of The Office, Parks & Rec, How I Met Your Mother and 30 Rock. Plan your night accordingly.    
    
    
    @HeatheroftheEO You two! Wish we'd had more chances to chat. Will never forget meeting over dinner in AVL with @prairiemama    
    
    
    @HeatheroftheEO er, you "too." I swear I'm a professional writer. Just possibly one who shouldn't have woken up at 4.    
    
    
    @aprilwilson_ @roociambriello I'm already sorta regretting this connection. ;)    
    
    
    ATLANTA: Know any openings for an agency account exec? Awesome friend is looking.    
    
    
    @camorose Guess he felt conflicted at that point.    
    
    
    Now that I'm working from home, I've learned something. Namely, my dog barks all. The. Time.    
    
    
    @Finding_Walden Was surprised how fast the day went. Can't say I miss meetings, though.    
    
    
    @RedheadWriting Um....here?    
    
    
    @AddisonDesign Got some email from Slideshare with stats. Otherwise, yeah, not sure where it would be listed.    
    
    
    @jvreeland Thanks, Jeff. Really appreciate your guidance as someone who's been there/here before.    
    
    
    @KellyShibari Hey thanks! I'm a Scotch man...hope we can still be friends. @RayneMillaray    
    
    
    @typeamom @RedheadWriting I was just looking for a reason.    
    
    
    What? I just didn't want the cheddar and salami to go to waste. http://instagram.com/p/fEFkIfv4mf/     
    
    
    @KatieStrasser Ha, the wooooo is mutual.    
    
    
    Hey #WordPress friends, what are some good places to shop around for well-built themes?    
    
    
    @garymoneysmith @robbettis @sarahpressler @AmberCadabra @woothemes @bgardner Thanks, all!    
    
    
    @macgeekppc Oh crap, you found my side job as a male model. #bluesteel #powerofpickles    
    
    
    @Mediawill Fail. You made it better.    
    
    
    @Mediawill Doubles the anxiety of the roof-surfing scene.    
    
    
    Train songs are not listened to. They are merely survived.    
    
    
    @HeatherSolos As always, I'm in awe of your strength. True justice is rare in this world, but I know your love for her will accomplish much.    
    
    
    Just stumbled across this picture w/ @herbadmother at BlissDom 2011 and it cracked me up hard. pic.twitter.com/xqNX8WpCPj    
    
    
    Full ahead, Mr. Sulu. MT @sfiegerman: Either Fox News just bought gigantic iPads or they employ very tiny people. pic.twitter.com/3xbvZLeiVu    
    
    
    @ikepigott All I know is, I want to play Artemis with those guys. @sfiegerman    
    
    
    @seemills You know it.    
    
    
    Yep. RT @dannysullivan: Sometimes, I so hate Fake Forbes that allows anyone to write under the Forbes brand. Forbes used to mean something.    
    
    
    The best furlough stunt yet: Company offering 200 free vibrators per day to idled federal workers. http://adweek.it/15WBP6s     
    
    
    @TomBLogue The phrase "insert pun here" has never been more (in?)appropriate.    
    
    
    @marcvangurp Of course! Great find.    
    
    
    Heading to @Freshfully to arm-wrestle my new Wordpress site, in case anyone wants to come watch me eat a sandwich and swear.    
    
    
    @acnatta I should really just lifestream it for the masses. At least @iheartbham is here to watch the magic happen.    
    
    
    I like this shot of me by @zacksyl. http://instagram.com/p/fOkWSUv4vC/     
    
    
    Finally, a smoke detector you won't ignore and despise: http://adweek.it/17W6d4t  (From @nest, of course)    
    
    
    @Freshfully Btw, nice job on your email marketing. Drove all the way across town for that club. Totally worth it.    
    
    
    @DameWallis Dang, @brycepugh beat me by a few seconds. Thought it was Vertigo at first. Fun game!    
    
    
    If you're not logged in to Twitter and try to follow someone, it pops up a "create account" window instead of a log-in. That's just dumb.    
    
    
    This 2010 headline is almost laughable now: http://on.mash.to/b69kbo  Hard to divide "publishing" from "updating" these days, though.    
    
    
    @tammy Digital Art Director, probably.    
    
    
    Truly a noble, slobbery beast. http://instagram.com/p/fYWuG2P4rB/     
    
    
    Any experienced designers looking for a good magazine gig in the Birmingham area? Hit me up for details. Great opportunity.    
    
    
    @Cecilyk I think I read somewhere that they were based on this: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Slender_Man …    
    
    
    You'll probably enjoy my interview with the man behind the agency world's best Twitter feed, @RGA: http://adweek.it/1hTQfcL     
    
    
    @jr_create I'm not aware of any truly legitimate certification in the way that project managers have PMI    
    
    
    @LZone Resource does a great job - http://www.resource.com/case-studies/     
    
    
    @HumanBeam Hey thanks! @RGA @Chapinc    
    
    
    Schoolteacher asked me to raise her kids and Publix clerk said I had "the most well-thought-out groceries I've seen." #WinningAtBeingAnAdult    
    
    
    Um, what? RT @CBCCommunity: Think your hotel's ice buckets are clean? Sometimes people use them to pee in. http://www.cbc.ca/newsblogs/yourcommunity/2013/10/marketplace-live-chat-have-dirty-hotels-cleaned-up-their-acts.html …    
    
    
    @sarahpressler @apierno And why are there coffee cups next to my urine heater? @CBCCommunity    
    
    
    @BCprairiegirl @CBCCommunity Good point. Let's talk about the remote controls.    
    
    
    @tokissthecook On the opposite note, Lehka Hlava is one of the best vegetarian restaurants I've ever eaten at. Worth a stop if you have time    
    
    
    @tokissthecook Better dinner place, anyway, since the tables are backlit. Hope you're having an amazing trip!    
    
    
    My day is 60%ish. @cozmodiva: Let's all post and tweet in unclear, ambiguous, insignificant terms about how your day is going."    
    
    
    @Kathrin_Bode That's interesting! Glad to see Google addressed something like that way back in 2007.    
    
    
    Glad that my newest post to go viral is about something that actually deserves to go viral: http://adweek.it/19WySsT     
    
    
    How a sour cream coffee cake is born. http://instagram.com/p/fpzFt2P4uN/     
    
    
    I wouldn't even know where to begin. @ McWane Science Center http://instagram.com/p/fqAMsNP4n0/     
    
    
    Step 1: Into the crock pot. Step 2: Into my belly. http://instagram.com/p/fsPDbNv4u8/     
    
    
    @Newilli Ha, my wife hates it, so that's my one concession. Good eye!    
    
    
    @Freshfully Thought you'd like that. ;)    
    
    
    @chrisjohnhunt1 Agreed. Great to see such an important item get so much visibility. Congrats!    
    
    
    @RealLifeSarah @allthingsfadra I'm sure Google+ is blowin' up with new/returning users! Oh wait...no, probably not.    
    
    
    @sarahneedleman Your feed is so delightfully random sometimes. :)    
    
    
    How to blog in 2013: 1. Read Reddit. 2. Embed photos from Reddit in your blog. 3. Sit back and enjoy your lazy-bastard linkbaiting.    
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk Spell a few of those words wrong, and you could have an official Reddit mission statement there.    
    
    
    @Osborne Since tumbloggers are the biggest offenders, I'm not sure how that would go over.    
    
    
    The bank ad for people who don't like bank ads, but love Roy Scheider: http://adweek.it/1eEJf3G     
    
    
    @freshbooks As a first-time visitor, I was pretty annoyed that your "Pricing and Signup" landing page is 90% signup, 10% pricing info.    
    
    
    Just ordered a massive BBQ feast for @mikegruss' first Bham visit. Introduce me to my wife, get yourself free ribs for life.    
    
    
    @FeedBlitz You guys are dreamy. #ThisOnesForTheSupportTeam    
    
    
    @MeghanHoyer (Sad trombone. ) @mikegruss    
    
    
    @adakevms At least their kids gave Him one good sacrifice...and one not-so-good one. @mikegruss    
    
    
    @freshbooks Not really, I just wanted to share a first-time visitor perspective. Just be nice to save the extra click and show the chart.    
    
    
    Weighs 5 lbs and requires you to swipe your own eyeballs. RT @WSJ: Microsoft testing eyewear to rival Google Glass: http://on.wsj.com/1ib3Mgh     
    
    
    According to my dog, the nice man making his monthly visit to pick up poop from our yard is actually here to murder us all.    
    
    
    @jsandford So true.    
    
    
    @NanciScarpulla Dogs are truly the only ones looking out for our safety and well-being.    
    
    
    Clair makes a Brother's Keeper. #octanebham https://vine.co/v/hdYiQeBEluq     
    
    
    Making drinks with fire. https://vine.co/v/hdYp5BhrA7Y     
    
    
    Interested to hear the fallout. RT @AdFreak: The @AJC has deleted and apologized for a racist tweet this morning: http://adweek.it/Hf93Iz     
    
    
    Take a moment and appreciate how odd the word "messenger" is. I mean, you don't send a messenge.    
    
    
    @katykelley I once spent way too long thinking about the phrase "out of order."    
    
    
    @HeatherSolos Judge not.    
    
    
    @d3_designs Sure, hit me up at griner at gmail and I'll send you some info. @evantravers    
    
    
    Pumpkin Appreciation Month continues. http://instagram.com/p/f3VfreP4iN/     
    
    
    @halvorson What's so awkward about singing both parts of the Human League's signature duet "Don't You Want Me"?    
    
    
    Pinterest cracking down on "pin to win" contests: http://adweek.it/1ajdTwR  Lots of new limitations for brands.    
    
    
    @lmerricks My girl @roociambriello beat me to it - http://adweek.it/19Eh0Ac     
    
    
    Bham would-be picklers, don't miss @cturnip's class on canning at @Freshfully tomorrow: http://bit.ly/HiA3H0     
    
    
    @cturnip You bet! Hope you have a great turnout.    
    
    
    As someone who's been making homemade chicken stock for years, this new pressure cooker is straight-up WITCHCRAFT.    
    
    
    @Jayne_Statue Have you ever cooked a whole chicken in it? Was curious to try that.    
    
    
    @Jayne_Statue Any other recommended go-to recipes? I'm drunk on the power now.    
    
    
    @Jayne_Statue Nice! Just learned from a friend last night that pressure cooker risotto is the best ever, btw.    
    
    
    Cute pumpkin idea at Steel City Pops. @ Steel City Pops http://instagram.com/p/gGLkDQv4nX/     
    
    
    Great read by @roociambriello - Why Tesco Mobile's hilarious Twitter feed is actually no joke. http://adweek.it/1aoOB47     
    
    
    Can never have too many YouTube annotations! pic.twitter.com/tsRfULGDRE    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @cebsilver: Technically, today marks three years of no booze. I think I'll have a non-alcoholic coffee to celebrate.    
    
    
    @DameWallis @PeterVerge No wolf on your noggin?    
    
    
    @PeterVerge Hahah, now you look like Mike D circa 1986. :) @DameWallis    
    
    
    My bet? @acarvin will be working for the @guardian in three months' time. http://www.andycarvin.com/?p=1981     
    
    
    @mumby No, removed from the head. Just a bunch of peeled cloves.    
    
    
    @mumby Ah, OK. Then you want to roast the heads first. Try this: http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/robin-miller/roasted-garlic-recipe/index.html …    
    
    
    100% RT @Finding_Walden: Eating Halloween candy for lunch is totally acceptable.    
    
    
    OH: "It's the Arby's version of alcohol." If he's not talking about Horsey Sauce, he's a damn fool.    
    
    
    My post on Star Wars invading Thomas Kinkade paintings is blowing up. Reblogged by @NPR and @wilw. Nice. http://adweek.it/17zEszm     
    
    
    @ColoradoMom Thumbs up, Photobomb.    
    
    
    @jbarbush Glad to hear it, though the artist deserves all the credit. Always happy to pass along good stuff.    
    
    
    Seems legit. pic.twitter.com/2HWucnNcm7    
    
    
    Hope you can join me, @JasonFalls, @ArikHanson, @JennyMunn, @ShellyKramer and more at Solo PR Summit in Feb: http://bit.ly/1a52ZM8     
    
    
    @jsandford I know, right? Felt odd to say. But also oddly empowering.    
    
    
    Who is one person you follow on Twitter whom everyone should follow on Twitter?    
    
    
    @cebsilver You're doing social media right!    
    
    
    @AlanSee I ended up trapped in a Kansas blizzard with Chumbawamba once in the '90s.  As you can guess, they rolled with it.    
    
    
    @AlanSee You should hear abt my run-in the night before w/ the Green Day drummer. #nsfw cc @techsavvymama @ResourcefulMom @ColoradoMom    
    
    
    Been a fan of @lobese for ages, but if you're into food, you REALLY need to be following her on #instagram: http://instagram.com/lobese     
    
    
    @ResourcefulMom I share because I care. #othersurgeries @AlanSee @techsavvymama @ColoradoMom    
    
    
    @lobese Totally deserved.    
    
    
    @natedriver If you're looking at @Kmart's tweet stream, you'll need to click "all" instead of "no replies" @Adweek    
    
    
    @RichFeloni Thanks for the shout-out in your Kmart piece. Glad to know manually counting those tweets was worth it.    
    
    
    @RichFeloni They actually called themselves Sears on accident four times in about an hour. We were just being polite and showing one.    
    
    
    @typeamom Little-known fact: The average height of a Type-A Parent David is 6'2" @Daily_Pinch @dbinkowski    
    
    
    @typeamom Can a list of two have a median? @Daily_Pinch @dbinkowski    
    
    
    @dbinkowski You made the right choice. @Daily_Pinch @typeamom    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sure. I call it 'posting on Twitter.' Heyooo! MT @LisaJohnson: Do you ever talk to yourself to get over a literal or figurative hurdle?    
    
    
    @RealSheree Like all good weapons, I wield it rarely.    
    
    
    @chuckgose Kinda like the price and quality of hotel wi-fi?    
    
    
    @chuckgose Also noticed recently a few nicer places don't have in-room coffee. I'm just surprised it's not $5 per filter pack.    
    
    
    @wanninger Oh I'm sure @CBCCommunity can tell you all about the urine in your ice bucket. http://bit.ly/1hm9wIW  @chuckgose    
    
    
    Take a look at the incredible amount of work that went into SNL's brilliant Wes Anderson parody: http://adweek.it/HCstai     
    
    
    @laurenddick Thanks so much! I appreciate you sharing our posts.    
    
    
    @dbinkowski Hahahah. #ShouldersOfGiants @StudioJewel @typeamom @Daily_Pinch    
    
    
    @jsandford Wait, WHAT? ;) @bhambizjrnl    
    
    
    @DanaVixen Which ad?    
    
    
    @HeatherSolos We have a saying in my house. "No one wins the game of Smell Detective." @phollows @xarker @methodtweet    
    
    
    @wearebig I like the photobomb.    
    
    
    @PRKingGarage @abedecs Pages are all sorts of busted right now. I can only access admin panels.    
    
    
    It's like making money! RT @Polygon: PS4 ships with a $10 PlayStation Store voucher http://sbn.to/HN5SYb     
    
    
    @zacksyl @JasonEng_ I like the mental image of a pissed-off FB taking its toys and going home.    
    
    
    What do you think? Is a PSA like this too disturbing to be effective? Or will it work? http://adweek.it/1c5I2Ac     
    
    
    @txelizabeth @conz 25% paying attention seems quite optimistic. ;)    
    
    
    @KatieStrasser That's AMAZING.    
    
    
    CRASH THEM TOGETHER! RT @JWT_London: JWT's beer trolley and JWT's cake trolley, which is better? #fight pic.twitter.com/izZLzGONBQ    
    
    
    @PRKingGarage Yup, up and running for an hour or two.    
    
    
    @creativeoncall Hahah, that's hilarious. Thanks for the nod.    
    
    
    @markovuorensola Great stuff, thanks! @LBBOnline    
    
    
    Returning to my #NorCal roots and grilling marinated tri-tip. Such an underappreciated cut. http://instagram.com/p/gl4Ujfv4gD/     
    
    
    @scheidel Missed your company yesterday, but I'm sure we'll all cross paths again. @katykelley @bmorrissey @andjelicaaa    
    
    
    Launched my new personal site this week: http://davidgriner.net/  More content to come, but any feedback appreciated.    
    
    
    @zacksyl Those beautiful, uncredited photos! (Realized after I left town I never found a place to pimp you in there….will fix.) And thanks!    
    
    
    @cebsilver Hey, at least it's not parallax.    
    
    
    @cebsilver I almost booked a theme and then realized it was one page only. Like, if you wrote 100 blog posts, it would just keep scrolling.    
    
    
    @sarahpressler That's great to hear. I want to tweak the mobile a bit, but I'm glad it's working well already.    
    
    
    @zacksyl Right now, everyone's just assuming they're selfies.    
    
    
    @foleypod Oh that's great to hear. Hadn't gotten to try it on one yet. Thanks!    
    
    
    @adnostics It's just WP. You mean space between top nav and primary headline?    
    
    
    35 years that changed advertising: http://adweek.it/1gEBQVy  My piece celebrating @Adweek's 35th anniversary.    
    
    
    @mommyniri If you know who they are and you have insurance, their insurance should reimburse your deductible.    
    
    
    @mommyniri Meant to say if THEY have insurance, you should be reimbursed. Sometimes you don't even have to pay b/c insurers work it out.    
    
    
    @Techevarr Thanks!    
    
    
    Any highly active Google+ users out there? I have a question abt how links appear when shared by multiple profiles.    
    
    
    @tessa Thanks, Tessa! Will do.    
    
    
    @estheribrown @MatthewKnell @imtopher On G+, when multiple profiles/pages in your circles share the same link, do they get bundled together?    
    
    
    @estheribrown @MatthewKnell @imtopher Wondering if it's similar to how FB shows the link once and then aggregates the commentary.    
    
    
    Polygon's PS4 review is a masterpiece of modern web design: http://polygon.com/a/ps4-review/     
    
    
    @Techevarr I've written two pieces for @Polygon and thought they did right by both, but this one is just incredible.    
    
    
    Honda's summer hashtag campaigns generated 11K Twitter mentions, and July sales were up 20%: http://bit.ly/1dMAXY0  Nice, @aliciajones!    
    
    
    @jessicahagy Ha, my sister always says she'll know she's rich when she uses "summer" and "winter" as verbs.    
    
    
    @Techevarr My opus on video game voice actors: http://bit.ly/YZdxoC  Spent about a year tracking them all down.    
    
    
    @KeithStoeckeler @Chapinc Already the CEO….of my heart.    
    
    
    Ran into Malcolm Gladwell last night in Times Square. I'm sure he's telling his followers about it, too.    
    
    
    Just found a 2013 survey that says 6% of travelers use MySpace to plan their trips. WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE?    
    
    
    @withoutpause It's like a trick question got thrown in to weed out the people who wanted Starbucks gift cards.    
    
    
    @NoPantsToWork I wouldn't use MySpace to research my summer jam, much less my summer vacation.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @withoutpause Yes! And no.    
    
    
    Lamb shoulders, bacon, parsnips, carrots, potatoes + bottle of wine in pressure cooker. Whatever I'm cooking, it's sure to be awesome.    
    
    
    @RealSheree Hey, it said to use the whole bottle.    
    
    
    @deongordon Lamb Au Vin, not to be confused with a Lame-o Van.    
    
    
    Buzzfeed: Reading Reddit so you don't have to.    
    
    
    Just another day on my family's homestead. RT @Genny_Spencer: Uncle Ott was here. He shot Donald. He wasn't hurt bad. -Nov. 12, 1939    
    
    
    @kenisajerk Surely so. But it's Buzzfeed I always see flooded in my FB feed three days after seeing something on Reddit first.    
    
    
    @kenisajerk Such an odd onion. Buzzfeed gets content from Reddit, where content actually lives on Imgur. Everyone makes money BUT Reddit.    
    
    
    @SarahM Thanks for being a longtime @Genny_Spencer fan!    
    
    
    @MomSpark Safe travels!    
    
    
    @HeatherSolos Thinking of you and your family, friend. Hope it brings some level of comfort.    
    
    
    Where angels fear to tread RT @roociambriello: The 'other' mailbox on Facebook is the stuff of nightmares.    
    
    
    The first Twitter account I ever created, even before mine, was @AdFreak. Awesome to see it hit 100K followers today.    
    
    
    @Jayne_Statue Made lamb shoulder and veggies in the pressure cooker last night. Five-hour recipe in 45 minutes. Love this thing.    
    
    
    @erinshawstreet Thanks, Erin!    
    
    
    @Disco_Chicken That's hilarious.    
    
    
    @zacksyl @AdFreak (Tap Tap feeeeeeedback) "IS THIS THING ON?"    
    
    
    In case you're interested, I have resumed tweeting my great-aunt's diary entries from the Great Depression: @Genny_Spencer    
    
    
    @arrrzzz @nudd This was back when Twitter framed every status update with "What are you doing?" I took it literally.    
    
    
    @slarkpope Yeah, but the hook brings you back.    
    
    
    @TomBLogue You're the extreme couponer of business travelers.    
    
    
    @crollwagen If I don't get a chance to say hi in person at #uabiw13, hope we get to connect soon. Big fan of your shop and writing!    
    
    
    Attending the Innovations in Wellness Conference at @UABWellness. Will be speaking shortly on Getting Strategic with Social. #uabiw13    
    
    
    @KrisCL12 Glad you found it helpful! #uabiw13 @UABWellness    
    
    
    Winter is coming. @ Freshfully http://instagram.com/p/g57-Ksv4ux/     
    
    
    @sawickis We read Wide Sargasso Sea in high school. Book's tame, but teacher warned us "DON'T WATCH THE MOVIE." Lots o' nekkid.    
    
    
    @heathervaclav Sorry you missed it! But glad you got to see @crollwagen and the other great afternoon presenters.    
    
    
    While the plumber's here, I had to tie the dog's leash to the heaviest thing in the house: the wine cabinet.    
    
    
    So that's where I left those. RT @zaibatsu: 1.2 million in gold bars found stashed in Boeing 737's bathroom http://zite.to/1dXTO17     
    
    
    Can we have 6-7 more new gaming consoles just so Polygon will keep knocking out stellar reviews like this? http://bit.ly/1b73XL3     
    
    
    @cpealet Hahah, nice turn of phrase. @adfreak    
    
    
    @cindygallop @VranicaWSJ Thanks for sharing my @goldieblox post on @AdFreak. Great to see it getting so much traction.    
    
    
    @lakarune Pretty sure that goes beyond the level of "questionable" into "actionable."    
    
    
    @onekade @lakarune Or play along like you're into it and see how deep and dark this thing can get.    
    
    
    In Defense of Selfies - http://bit.ly/1bQB449  Good assessment by @crollwagen    
    
    
    @lakarune No, it is certainly not. But, you know, it could be pretty funny. @onekade    
    
    
    Make your own overly emotional, link-baiting headline with the Upworthy Generator: http://adweek.it/18nO6VZ     
    
    
    Kids don't change. RT @Genny_Spencer: We had a Math test. It was terrible. -Nov. 13, 1939    
    
    
    Perfect summary. RT @tessa: “The smartphone is becoming the dashboard of our lives.” #DF13    
    
    
    Does it mean less when ads advocating for women are created by men? http://bit.ly/18ouT6M     
    
    
    Shut up. Not really, right? RT @davedelaney: Two Plurk notifications today.    
    
    
    This year's most popular ads advocating for women were largely made by men. Is that a problem? http://bit.ly/18ouT6M     
    
    
    @bmorrissey I'm sure I could find you the ultimate how-to on that, with 1 strange tip you're not going to believe.    
    
    
    Pop quiz: Can you guess what my dog's been licking loudly for a solid hour? Hint: it rhymes with "It's heinous."    
    
    
    HE BUYS GOLF CLUBS. HE BUYS GOLF CLUBS. HE BUYS GOLF CLUBS. http://adweek.it/1e2Y4wz  #HeBuysGolfClubs    
    
    
    @PabloDAndreu At this point, I'd be willing to make it available.    
    
    
    @katgordon Thanks for the feedback! And for tolerating the awkward umbrella term "feminist ads". :) @creativeoncall    
    
    
    @popcandy Remember that AquaTeen episode with Danzig and the Robot Ghost? I kinda wish that had gotten its own series.    
    
    
    @ShephaliBhatt Hey thanks! That means a lot.    
    
    
    @EstherFreedman @NoMeatballs @hoyboy @seanhaus You're just not viewing it with your 4D glasses on.    
    
    
    Just signed up for @FeedBlitz, in part b/c it's a great service, but also b/c they've hired some of the best people I know.    
    
    
    @phollows Glad to be aboard. @HeatherSolos @FeedBlitz @AshleyTaylorFB @HighImpactMom    
    
    
    I'm only from 4. RT @Tomasco_: Half of all #twitter users are from just 5 countries http://on.mash.to/1c4avqB     
    
    
    Yupyupyupyupyupyup. RT @nudd: Agency guy reminded me this week that not every ad can go viral like "Whatever the Fox Said."    
    
    
    Conecuh Everything. RT @AlabamaFood: Does your family celebrate the holidays with a special Alabama meal or dish?    
    
    
    @osocio Just look for width & height in the embed code and change to whatever fits your site. @Bedsider @AdFreak @CreativeTweets    
    
    
    @marcusgilmer Your North Alabama references make me swoon.    
    
    
    Target's home page redesign is...not going over well. http://adweek.it/I88dgU  pic.twitter.com/9AeYLuYErT    
    
    
    @stuartfoster Strangely, they haven't stepped forward.    
    
    
    @sonnygill Yes, I will sadly admit I didn't know we were supposed to hate drop shadows. @arikhanson    
    
    
    @Danielleri That's actually the bagel pizza oven.    
    
    
    @DUQE My pleasure. You deserved an audience.    
    
    
    @eryno I've literally never heard back from an agency source faster.    
    
    
    @cleverkate @eryno No, but seriously. http://bit.ly/1hRL3WJ     
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo I'm sorry you had to find out this way. @IDWdWkr    
    
    
    @RealSheree Ha, glad you're an avid listener of @nhpr and caught that. ;)    
    
    
    @mallarytenore What you MEANT to say was, "Someone asked @Upworthy's editor how he creates headlines. What he said next is unbelievable."    
    
    
    @mallarytenore Now that Upworthy's style is getting copied all over, I wonder if they'll try to evolve to stay ahead.    
    
    
    My super talented designer friend Piper is selling linocut Xmas cards, with all proceeds going to #typhoon recovery: http://etsy.me/1ek9b4b     
    
    
    @ToddWasserman Seems ok here    
    
    
    @ToddWasserman Maybe it's a stunt to force you over to G+. Everything else seems to be these days.    
    
    
    Chronicling the 35 years that changed advertising: http://bit.ly/182xH5L     
    
    
    @gdouban @see_clair_write @lightdarkroom It was truly an all-star show. #WouldTagNimishIfHeTweeted    
    
    
    Coffee is patient. Coffee is kind. RT @GreenMtnCoffee: Coffee doesn't ask silly questions. Coffee understands. #MondayMantra    
    
    
    @jasongoldberger Jason, would love to chat with you for Adweek about the http://Target.com  redesign. I'm at griner (at) gmail    
    
    
    @zengarden17 Hey, I run the @Genny_Spencer acct. My suggestion would be to have them base it on real writings by those figures.    
    
    
    @zengarden17 Even if they're still making up the tweets. That way they learn how to mimic an older writing style and about primary sources.    
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk My old agency made the "Have you called your mama?" ad w/ Bear. He ad libbed the closer: "I wish I still could"    
    
    
    @jasongoldberger @DusteeJenkins Thanks! Only unanswered Q is whether the redesign was in-house or w/ an agency. Keep getting 'no comment'    
    
    
    No surprise: The guy who publicly fired his lazy PR shop has now hired the amazing @prtini's agency, Geben - http://bit.ly/194hltD     
    
    
        
    
    
    @getwired Unavoidable tonight.    
    
    
    @evantravers @ObjectivityRach  Sadly there's no Tweetbot for PC, which is where I was stuck during the hashtag frenzy.    
    
    
    Who was responsible for the http://Target.com  redesign? I asked (repeatedly), but the brand refuses to answer: http://adweek.it/1eA8wwn     
    
    
    @AmandaLeePowell Achievement unlocked: First Night.    
    
    
    Just watched #Auburn's amazing win with a crowd of Midwesterners...all cheering for Auburn.    
    
    
    Foursquare briefly turned my blood to ice water last night when I landed in Bham and it said "Looks like you're at Charlotte Douglas!"    
    
    
    @GregoryNg Had the whole family with me, 11 p.m. and seated next to engine so I couldn't see out the window. Lordy.    
    
    
    Five easy ways to support women creating amazing content: http://bit.ly/IAvhEL  (My post inspired by @Ehmee)    
    
    
    @HeatherSolos Hey you're the one who inspired me to spend 2 hours writing a blog post. @DresdenPlaid @Lizz_Porter    
    
    
    @Catarino "Lick screen to skip ad"    
    
    
    @AssuranceAgency @adland Here's our item, still w/ original phrasing: http://bit.ly/18ifwif  Wouldn't say we got it wrong.    
    
    
    @adland @AssuranceAgency Yeah, had one on their non-apology: http://bit.ly/1hikzli  No idea on their follow-through on dropping the suit.    
    
    
    New arms race. RT @getwired: Waiting for Google to announce their Autonomic Shipping Service that uses self-driving parcel delivery drones.    
    
    
    Great error message from the #cybermonday flooded http://RedditGifts.com  pic.twitter.com/1L1ObTwIvj    
    
    
    @etbowser You're not supposed to put the whole review in the tweet. #protip    
    
    
    @etbowser Also, have you heard the Riverchase Kia jingle? They've got some Warren G-esque 90s vibe going on.    
    
    
    @etbowser I think it's just radio. I wanted to call you to hear it, but figured it'd be over. Forgot radio is home of the 420-second spot.    
    
    
    5 easy ways to support women creating amazing content: http://bit.ly/IAvhEL     
    
    
    @allthingsfadra @unfoundation Last xmas, when my 4yo daughter began to get snippy abt gifts, we took her to the homeless warming shelter.    
    
    
    @allthingsfadra @unfoundation Shared some candy (huge hit), blankets, coats. The experience really stuck with her.    
    
    
    @allthingsfadra @unfoundation The biggest thing for her was seeing how happy the candy made everyone. So few luxuries. Great perspective.    
    
    
    So the bad guys in Ip Man 1 & 2 play the hero's brother and mentor in the prequel. #KungFuCastingConfusion    
    
    
    @MrWhaite Love your movie neons. Up for doing a quick Q&A on them for @AdFreak?    
    
    
    @abeaujon @jfdulac @mallarytenore At least they didn't go with 'Bae caught me 'leapin"    
    
    
    @GumboShowJoe Thanks!    
    
    
    @JulieAlexandria Put more weight on your back leg so your front leg can kick more easily. ;) @CliveStanden's got it down.    
    
    
    @ourmaninchicago Great cause. Happy to help. Perfect tweet, btw.    
    
    
    Here's why @realjohngreen and other popular content creators grudgingly allow brands to rip them off: http://adweek.it/IRW2p7     
    
    
    @strawberrycough @realjohngreen Let's go ahead and drag @adlawguy into this. Michael, thoughts? http://adweek.it/IRW2p7     
    
    
    @adland The clip is about why their phrase isn't trademarked. @strawberrycough @realjohngreen    
    
    
    @liamgingerino Huh? @realjohngreen    
    
    
    @urbanmommies Who has time for patience? ;)    
    
    
    @Colorado Is the giveaway package just for one person? Couldn't find details in the rules. Thanks!    
    
    
    @Colorado Thank you!    
    
    
    Hips don't lie. RT @AmandaLeePowell: Me: "I can't hula hoop." @griner: "The problem is, you have hips like mine. That's a compliment."    
    
    
    Elderly lady at Sam's said I should be careful about baby-snatchers "this time of year." Had no idea it was seasonal.    
    
    
    Chobani just announced it will make its first-ever appearance as a #SuperBowl advertiser: http://bit.ly/1d4Tpcd     
    
    
    AMAZING ad for Pantene about workplace hypocrisy against women: http://adweek.it/1dhlflY  pic.twitter.com/6cydOicWLj    
    
    
        
    
    
    "You haven't had a burger until you've had the Italiano burger at Olive Garden." Now that's some epic ad hyperbole.    
    
    
    @stephparker I wouldn't know. I've never had a burger. Apparently.    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Be sure to Instagram this moment of clarity.    
    
    
    @mjcontrera What an incredible piece of journalism you've created.    
    
    
    Check out my Super Bowl Ad Tracker for @Adweek, keeping you up to date on every ad in the works: http://bit.ly/19zq6w9     
    
    
    Anyone else plagued by Chrome crashes lately from the shockwave/flash plugin? Hitting me daily on PC and Mac. Plugins keep re-enabling.    
    
    
    @centsiblelife Seems to be an issue with the browser's Flash conflicting with the machine's Flash. Disabling one helps, but it comes back on    
    
    
    Marketing folks, have you seen the #brandsonly hashtag? Without looking up further context, what's your take when you see that?    
    
    
    @KyleWiebalk It's from a real-world event, though yes, the online chatter has been hard to suss out.    
    
    
    @nickjayres Shh, don't get caught talking to us. They'll revoke your waffle privileges. #brandsonly @Szczepanik    
    
    
    @zacksyl People are getting snippy over non-brand folks using the #brandsonly hashtag? That's just ridiculous.    
    
    
    @nickjayres I have a feeling there's a big difference between the #brandsonly event and the way it's coming off on Twitter.    
    
    
    @amybhole This is an either-or thing?    
    
    
    @RyanAmirault So in your opinion, who should be allowed to use the #brandsonly hashtag without it coming across as mooching? Attendees only?    
    
    
    @RyanAmirault The idea of an attendee-only hashtag seems somewhat antisocial, though. Shouldn't others feel comfortable responding?    
    
    
    @RyanAmirault Thanks for the feedback. Interesting topic. Working on a blog post now.    
    
    
    @shaneadams Can you clarify? You don't see a problem with the hashtag being for attendees only? (Just making sure I understand)    
    
    
    @shaneadams Not sure I have a firm opinion to agree/disagree with. My concern is abt trying to limit who can use a hashtag.    
    
    
    @megmroberts Thanks for the feedback! As a consultant, former agency guy and longtime journalist on the side, I have no idea where I'd fit.    
    
    
    @megmroberts This issue has helped me appreciate folks like @ESPN_ProdGirl and @JasonEng_, who didn't dismiss me at conf's b/c I was agency.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ESPN_ProdGirl So my plans on being your office's exclusive provider of artisan pickled okra? Dashed. @megmroberts @JasonEng_    
    
    
    This week's #brandsonly event highlights the tension between vendors and brands, even on Twitter: http://adweek.it/1gZQft3     
    
    
    @JasonEng_ @ESPN_ProdGirl What's funny is that any of us can end up a vendor (sponsorships, etc.). Pays to be respectful on either side.    
    
    
    @JasonEng_ @ESPN_ProdGirl But for the record, it means a lot that I got to know each of you by discussing our passions, not business deals.    
    
    
    @ESPN_ProdGirl Most would probably agree with your initial assessment. But obviously not all. @JasonEng_    
    
    
    @JasonEng_ @ESPN_ProdGirl Ironically, I think I met you within 60 minutes and 30 yards of each other. :)    
    
    
    @CParizman No surprise there. Ninja/guru/awesomeness-catalyst are the stuff of consultants and startups. @YZebraDigital    
    
    
    @cubanalaf @shaneadams Previous relationship. Questions only. No links. Hashtag acceptable-use policy is getting complicated.    
    
    
    @SeanWRyan You pretty well just nailed why this issue first jumped out to me. No hunter likes to become the hunted.    
    
    
    @KellyTirman That starts to get into host/sponsor discussions.  Highlights my point earlier that brand reps often become vendors themselves.    
    
    
    @KellyTirman Most brand-only events I've seen are organized by a vendor, consultant, etc. that wants exclusive access.    
    
    
    @KellyTirman Big client of mine was invited to one once, and he gave me his free ticket since my team ran their social. Event rescinded it.    
    
    
    @KellyTirman Hahah, well said.    
    
    
    @nickjayres It got waffly hot in here. Thanks for staying tuned.    
    
    
    Oh hey, new Galaxy S3 update finally added auto correct. Time to test! Hobgoblin tedtorster amphetamine. Eh, 2/3's not bad. #tedtorster    
    
    
    @bmorrissey It's tricky to stock a mime, to stock a mime that's right in line. It's tricky. Tricky tricky tricky.    
    
    
    Useful for the nonsubscribing freeloader. RT @nytimes: 3 NYT stories you should know about right now http://nyti.ms/19ExhTE     
    
    
    Just announced: Instagram Direct will let you send images to up to 15 people privately. #Instagram    
    
    
    Instagram Direct seems to create an inbox of sorts for private images and conversations (w/ individuals or groups). #instagram    
    
    
    Only people you follow can send you #InstagramDirect photos. Pics from unfollowed go into "Pending Requests" instead of going undelivered.    
    
    
    @Becmwatts Direct message feature. Creates an inbox for private images and video.    
    
    
    @chrisnager Glad it helped! Not much more to report, though working on a blog post now w/ some lingering questions.    
    
    
    @jvreeland Snapchat for people who don't snapchat, mostly. I like the group discussion option, too.    
    
    
    My take on #InstagramDirect: It's about to get naked and spammy up in here - http://adweek.it/JaK8X7     
    
    
        
    
    
    @jvreeland That might explain why he opened the announcement with a long discussion of how feature phones outnumber smartphones 4:1    
    
    
    A subtle and appreciated improvement. RT @mashabletech: Gmail will now display all images within emails automatically http://on.mash.to/19ERuJ9     
    
    
    Do you think Instagram's new direct messaging will make parents less comfortable with kids using the app?    
    
    
    Super true. Streaming selection stinks. RT @GregoryNg: Right now TBS is more relevant than Netflix this holiday    
    
    
    @OhNoSheTwitnt How many hugs and solitary tears were there? Because those ate up 2/3rds of Return of the King.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @camorose That's one more than my last two visits.    
    
    
    The 10 Most Sexist Ads of 2013: http://adweek.it/1bMqwiB  My wrapup for @AdFreak. Cue the men's-rights trolls!    
    
    
    @FoxxiLiberal I joked yesterday that I'd get a "lighten up" and "where are the sexist ads AGAINST GUYS?!" within minutes of posting. Yep x2.    
    
    
    Free idea for OS programmers: If user closes an app right after booting 3 times, it should ask if you want to disable it from startup.    
    
    
    @planit Ha, thanks for the shout-out. Funny stuff.    
    
    
    The best college recruitment video I've seen in a long time: http://adweek.it/1cQVr1B  Congrats, @MonashCollegeAu    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TimMcDougall13 That was actually by the esteemed @GINER, not me (@griner). Great guy, though. Enjoyed dinner with him and family years ago.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats! Who's the homeless man in jeans? RT @Digiday: This is our new company portrait. We're 23 people now! pic.twitter.com/6JB8xZsvbz    
    
    
    @ChrisThilk @Digiday Think that guy accosted me once in Brooklyn. Ripped a mitten off my hand and took a picture of it. @bmorrissey    
    
    
    @mallarytenore That pretty well sums up where the profits are.    
    
    
    @adakevms Love it. Linkbait is my biggest pet peeve these days.    
    
    
    @alivingiano Didn't RT it, just wrote up on @AdFreak pretty soon after I saw Valleywag's item. @armano @voltaire @BuzzFeedBen    
    
    
    @armano And thanks for the credit (and sharing), David. I definitely saw it first on FB via disgusted Silicon Valley friends. @alivingiano    
    
    
    UPDATE: For no clear reason, @Gogo has apologized for its popular #JustineSacco tweet: http://adweek.it/1cHtRk6  pic.twitter.com/SXhSVZAipi    
    
    
    @purplesime Doubt it. @adland    
    
    
    Justine Sacco has officially been fired: http://adweek.it/1bZ0jNE     
    
    
    @majornelson Was this legit? And if so, where was the comment intended to be posted? http://i.imgur.com/VMPQKBm.jpg     
    
    
    @dpoliti Pretty sure that Sacco FB page you wrote about was fake. One of several trolling for more hate. Gone now anyway.    
    
    
    @ap_sims @dartog Yeah, import into Excel should pop up a question about how the data's delimited, then choose comma.    
    
    
    @ap_sims Ah good! @dartog    
    
    
    @atcrawford My kids (2 and 5) are bizarrely enamored with Ice Ice Baby. Cracks me up that it's become a kids' song.    
    
    
    @WriterBren Hahah, no idea why my ad tweet from another account went out via @genny_spencer. Christmas confusion on the twitters.    
    
    
    Meanings have changed since the 1600s, methinks. RT @samuelpepys: Mrs. Pierce is such a slut that I do not love her victualls.    
    
    
    @mareejones But not...(leans in)...the photos, right? RIGHT? OH GOD TELL ME THAT'S RIGHT.    
    
    
    @plante Whoah, @BenKuchera? Nice pickup.    
    
    
    My second monitor's been blinking on and off, and my main monitor just stopped working. I feel like Otto from Sons of Anarchy.    
    
    
    @AmberCadabra The gravitational sucking of rock stardom on the wane? ;)    
    
    
    @logosmith I wish. Time to get a better bag.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs I read #LeanIn and really enjoyed it. I had a few issues w/ the structure, but got a lot out of it.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs One of our execs hated the name-dropping, but can't say it bothered me. Enjoyed reading the VIP acknowledgements    
    
    
    @arikhanson Guess it just didn't bother me. I'm very proud of my mentor, even though he wasn't famous. I'd praise him to the skies.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @marketingprofs 2nd half of #LeanIn is a bit slower to read because it becomes a series of essays, not one consistent narrative.    
    
    
    @arikhanson But she's a chief exec at Facebook and married to the CEO of SurveyMonkey. I didn't really expect direct relatability.    
    
    
    @arikhanson Don't get me wrong, not discounting your take. I did worry that many women would find it too isolated a case to learn from.    
    
    
    @KatFrench Because we're guys or because we're nitpicking? @arikhanson    
    
    
    @KatFrench What, you don't think of me and @arikhanson as Rawhide men? Wait, don't answer that.    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan Probably when I lost my newspaper job back in 2005. A scary, optimistic, limitless time for reflection.    
    
    
    @arikhanson @mrdolson My favorite is still "Steak," the email marketing firm. "Rare medium, well done."    
    
    
    @arikhanson @mrdolson Don't forget this valuable chart of agency naming protocols: http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/infographic-taxonomy-advertising-agency-names-146517 …    
    
    
    Having dinner with this little charmer. http://instagram.com/p/Y0_r7dP4rA/     
    
    
    Feel like I blinked and these appeared. http://instagram.com/p/Y1D3YPP4hG/     
    
    
    Kid at grocery store told his mom, "Buy me something, and I'll stop being annoying!" I double dog dare my kids to try this approach.    
    
    
    @bretttmw Once is right.    
    
    
    Secret political message in my casserole pan. #99percent http://instagram.com/p/Y5xUdqP4vP/     
    
    
    Like bay leaves? Took a few years to mature, but our bay plant is exploding now. http://instagram.com/p/Y5xp4Yv4v1/     
    
    
    Email segmentation done wrong: Forrester sent me a note w/ a subject line that says "Second Blast to Unopens."    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Better than "uninterested party," I suppose.    
    
    
    Big thanks to @Mashable's @ToddWasserman for including me as a consulting expert in the "Social Makeover" series: http://on.mash.to/12PqaUn     
    
    
    @ESPN_ProdGirl Hey thanks, KR. Might jeopardize my precious under-the-radar status. :)    
    
    
    @girllostincity Hey thanks!    
    
    
    My team at @LuckieAndCo has an opening for a Digital Content Writer. Only 1 year exp required. http://bit.ly/11T520h     
    
    
    @cebsilver On-site. We've got a good stable of freelance topic experts all over, but this one's in Bham full-time.    
    
    
    @hushamanda Great to hear! I'll float your idea past HR....    
    
    
    Today's road snack: "rolled to explode with flavor"! http://instagram.com/p/ZEII7zv4rw/     
    
    
    @hushamanda No, that one's "Charlie Tango Crapflush." Totally different.    
    
    
    You keep tools in a gauntlet? RT @SBarnes: #FB is quickly becoming the most expensive, less effective, irrelevant tool in your #smm gauntlet    
    
    
    @SBarnes Well there's your problem right there.    
    
    
    Spain. #CountriesThatStillHaveKingsForNoRealReason    
    
    
    @CaptainAnnoying Love the scene where he punched out Goebbels and blew up the Luftwaffe factory while making love to Maria.    
    
    
    Have you watched "This Is Water" yet? (1.6M have.) Here's my Q&A with the creators: http://adweek.it/12gXjLn     
    
    
    @girllostincity Probably depends how well you curate your sponsors. If they're supporting content you already had planned, it's a win-win    
    
    
    @girllostincity Sponsors always want to be in the content well, not the ad sidebar, but it's definitely rare they bring much of worth.    
    
    
    One of my favorite pics of my daughter (http://i.imgur.com/CbHplu4.jpg ) got a nice upgrade via Reddit: http://i.imgur.com/W98Vkrt.jpg     
    
    
    @ourmaninchicago Just when you start to hate the Internet....    
    
    
    How great is it that the iPhone names every sent photo "Photo.jpg"? Zero great. None great.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 For now, the 30- or 60-second spot is still the core product of advertising.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 In this case, I think the goal is for the Top 10 to have a clear identity & not just feel like a recap of everything we cover.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 Originally, our "Freakiest Ads of the Year" was "Freakiest Advertising Moments" to be more inclusive, but it was just clunky.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 But yeah, good idea on the good ideas. Would probably be a totally different list, too.    
    
    
    @Schwartzie14 "5-10 good things from the past week or so" <- Finally, a pace we can all maintain.    
    
    
    Running a wide range of FB pages is surreal. Stoked about 50 new fans on one, disappointed by 10,000 new fans on another.    
    
    
    @sree Thanks for sharing my Q&A with @seetheglossary. Felt bad my editor, DFW megafan @nudd, was away and didn't get to write it himself.    
    
    
    My niece caught a 5-pound bass off my parents' pier. Biggest fish ever caught at the lakehouse! http://instagram.com/p/ZOM7J7v4o5/     
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk Tiny grub lure. No idea how it held fast.    
    
    
    @jelenawoehr Well, we definitely let this one go. My parents live right next to a nuclear power plant. :)    
    
    
    @megprpr Thanks so much. Really appreciate you coming out to the event.    
    
    
    Chuck E Cheese has a Tro-Lo-Lo parody. Solid. https://vine.co/v/bEa2YrAOK07     
    
    
    @omarg When I read your poor man's Don Draper, all I hear is GOB from Arrested Development.    
    
    
    @megprpr Was not familiar with @FORKology, but it sounds interesting. Could be a good fit for our work on @AlabamaFood.    
    
    
    Email webinar just showed pic of baboons to illustrate acronym APES. Those are monkeys, buddy. I question all your facts now!    
    
    
    @cebsilver I'll retweet that if you retweet this.    
    
    
    Email webinar just corrected baboons as monkeys not apes. Thank you, equally nerdy participant who actually put it in as Q&A feedback.    
    
    
    @mattplanet Everyone in the room seems convinced it was me.    
    
    
    @scottschablow My wife also likes to correct every reference where Curious George is called a "monkey." He has no tail, so must be an ape.    
    
    
    @armano HulkArmano in T minus 3....2...    
    
    
    @armano We don't choose how the gamma radiation affects us.    
    
    
    @SadieAwesome I like my women like I like my alternative-history fiction: Dubious of U.S. exceptionalism & obsessed w/ WWII. #PickupMetaphor    
    
    
    I find the intro of the He-Man remake hilarious. https://vine.co/v/bEUU365WjTA     
    
    
    People who've seen both: Iron Man 3 or Star Trek? Need to make the most of date night.    
    
    
    @bengreenman Good to know someone prospered during the Depression.    
    
    
    @HPippen3 My dad and I were just talking about what a perfect day it is for a movie theater. Muggy as all getout.    
    
    
    Selling my Sega Genesis + Sega CD, both in great working condition. http://bham.craigslist.org/vgm/3813804661.html …    
    
    
    @CamilleTGipson One of the best tweets ever. Could probably become a book deal. @etbowser    
    
    
    So....why are so many people leaving Tumblr? Do we hate Yahoo now?    
    
    
    @Techevarr My mortgage has been sold five times and I've never even cared who bought it. Hard to muster the energy over a tumblog.    
    
    
    @Techevarr It settled down eventually. Re-fi'd 2 years ago, and only one transfer since. Bounced around a lot during the '08 crazies.    
    
    
    @Techevarr I guess a 15-year fixed w/ reliable payment history became a hot commodity after the subprime freakout.    
    
    
    @Boldface My feed is nothing but Oklahoma tornados. Wishing you the best of luck, from one tornado state to another.    
    
    
    Nutella lawyers shut down World Nutella Day, a fan tradition since 2007: http://adweek.it/16M9cx2     
    
    
    @jbarbush Worth checking out this one too, apparently: http://bit.ly/18fAJoD     
    
    
    Apparently video game controller design hit its theoretical limit in 2005. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    Skype / group video chat integration into the Xbox One might finally make sci-fi video calling seem legit. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @katykelley When that day comes, I'll pay you $7 to dress like Princess Leia and repeat the same line over and over.    
    
    
    Xbox One won't have a CD tray, so I guess I'll have to find something else to stab with a paper clip every third night. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    Wait, what? For reals? Re the new Kinect: "When you're exercising it can read your heartbeat." #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @katykelley Shiiiit, I was gonna do that anyway.    
    
    
    @meggerz04 That's some Continuum tech right there. Can it tell if you're pregnant? #xboxreveal    
    
    
    But can the new Kinect make me sweat til I bleed? Because THAT would be dope enough, indeed. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @ElmntsofMadness @meggerz04 I'm sure the Open MRI add-on will be ready for holiday 2014.    
    
    
    First Xbox One sports titles are soccer, football, basketball & ultimate fighting. Baseball joins hockey in the cultural gutter. #xboxreveal    
    
    
    @erniebufflo Crazy, but neat.    
    
    
    How was I not already following my longtime friend, transportation guru and Nat'l Press Club president @agreilingkeane? Fixed.    
    
    
    Good reminder. RT @lmerricks: If you’re sending relief supplies to OK, I learned in AL that manual can openers are always needed. #OKNeeds    
    
    
    Looking gift cookies in the mouth. https://vine.co/v/bVublJwEYK5     
    
    
    @NikiDoyle Not sure how we haven't crossed paths (until @MollyFolse mentioned you to me today). Are you a Huntsville native? (I am.)    
    
    
    @MeghanHoyer Well, you shouldn't crowd the pan. But yeah, not too shabby.    
    
    
    If Nikola Tesla had to ask for money from today's venture capitalists: http://adweek.it/13NyTdB     
    
    
    @thenoodleator Sorry, they want you to be a what? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8668AcOoEpY …    
    
    
    I like the optimism of the vendor who emailed me "Can we connect this week?" on the Friday afternoon before a holiday.    
    
    
    Just learned I've written 427 blog posts for @AdFreak since April 2007. Random Friday stat courtesy of @Nudd.    
    
    
    Never heard of this, but apparently it's quite popular. Last one! http://instagram.com/p/Ztl4ttv4mO/     
    
    
    @NikiDoyle Wow, the phrase "an hour west of Huntsville" is not something you hear often. Let's grab coffee sometime soon.    
    
    
    The Birmingham subreddit is having a Rogue Tavern meetup tonight at 8:30. Details: http://www.reddit.com/r/Birmingham/comments/1f1j4r/meetup_tonight_at_rogue_tavern/ …    
    
    
    Just met a double-jointed guy. It's uh... https://vine.co/v/bVweQqLJ6F1     
    
    
    Capoeira lessons from mommy. https://vine.co/v/bVFljughw7J     
    
    
    Got the peas and hot peppers set up in the #Earthbox. Obviously the cucumbers behind them have a head… http://instagram.com/p/ZyneOQv4my/     
    
    
    He died a noble death. https://vine.co/v/bVU9MEm6Im3     
    
    
    @megprpr Never hurts to ask for case studies or references so you can see what they've actually accomplished vs. just numbers.    
    
    
    Funny how Facebook has turned childbirth into a real-time spectator sport. Watching a friend get peppered w/ update requests by the minute.    
    
    
    @americopywriter Great point. It's a pointless distraction. People need to learn to just wait.    
    
    
    @jsandford I'm sure you can yell for Siri to take care of all that.    
    
    
    @ToddWasserman Tilt your head, and it's Pol Pot drinking from a human skull.    
    
    
    Wisdom from my 5-year-old daughter: "Daddy, let's build a Death Star. But without a hole for good guys to blow it up through."    
    
    
    Copywriter leaves agency after 16 years, and his first solo ad hits the front page of Reddit: http://adweek.it/1aDOSew     
    
    
    @Mister_Wang Only thing Reddit likes better than DIY is DIYWSITTM. Do It Yourself While Sticking It To The Man.    
    
    
    @sssemester Seems like everyone's first or second tweet is "trying to figure out Twitter" or something like "Is this thing on?"    
    
    
    Super excited about finally getting to see Superman's origin story. No idea where that guy came from.    
    
    
    Anyone grow up with Drake's snacks?    
    
    
    @SarahWCaron DMIng you now.... :)    
    
    
    I'm about 6 episodes deep in the new season of Arrested Development. Does it bother to get funny at some point?    
    
    
    @soapnana Good to hear. Watched that one last night.    
    
    
    @adamostrow Hope it's Reddit's turn now.    
    
    
    @Andy_Aspirin Classiness side, I didn't say anything negative about the ad. Said it cut through the clutter by using dubstep. It's fine.    
    
    
    This is amazing: Children's cancer center rebrands chemo treatment as "Superformula" - http://bit.ly/15yjPAJ  By @davegian    
    
    
    @cebsilver Lo, and on the sixth day he pivoted the tables, and it was good.    
    
    
    With SalesForce and ExactTarget merging, my vendor roster will have gone from 4 to 2 to 1 in the course of two years. #MergerMania    
    
    
    @michaeldamboldt And a prestige class.    
    
    
    @patrickklepek Very cool that he's being honored and doubly great that you could accept it in his name.    
    
    
    @mattplanet Your rich uncle, rich father AND rich great-aunt will love it. #MtBrookFamilyFriendly    
    
    
    Asked daughter if she wanted to try someplace "new and exciting for dinner." "Yes!" "Wait, what do you consider exciting?" "A playground!"    
    
    
    @gsalinas I was going to try taking her to that Persian place by Guitar Center. I canceled the plan, then learned later it's closed    
    
    
    @desaraev The random "helpful guy" in the yoga vid was hilarious.    
    
    
    @gsalinas I think it's straight-up closed for good. Haven't driven by, but Urban Spoon says it's gone.    
    
    
    I didn't plant any of these squash. They all grew out if the compost. http://instagram.com/p/aPHgP9P4qO/     
    
    
    @YoungbloodJoe Good idea.    
    
    
    @RealSheree I got one cantaloupe plant last year, but nothing really came out of it. At least this year I'll have something to show for it.    
    
    
    Please take a moment today to vote for my agency, @LuckieAndCo, in the Medium category of #SocialMadness: http://bit.ly/19CIJBR     
    
    
    @JessicaDonlon Researchers plan to first test the invisibility cloak by sneaking past Professor Snape and into Hogsmeade.    
    
    
    @RowdyBowden Edward Burns.    
    
    
    "This video contains adult content. Please enter a completely fake birthday so we can pretend we tried to stop you."    
    
    
    Gamers growing increasingly incensed with Microsoft's #XboxOne: http://bit.ly/14lXyGB     
    
    
    Shrine of the Most Glorious Future, an exhibit by John Lytle Wilson. https://vine.co/v/bLn2dXYHXAd     
    
    
    @natbro Wanted to send you a few questions for an article I'm working on. Can you DM me a good email address to hit you at?    
    
    
    Live blogs are great for some things, but not the Mac Pro reveal. It's like listening to 10 drunk bats describe an elephant. #wwdc    
    
    
    There have been 7.4 trillion iOS push notifications? That's a truly sprawling amount of annoyance. #WWDC    
    
    
    Xbox One will be $499. http://www.engadget.com/2013/06/10/microsoft-xbox-one-price-availability/ …    
    
    
    @LadySnarksalot Oh good, I was just looking for offhanded ways to improve us.    
    
    
    I have no idea why she's reading Lovecraft in the dark, but I'm very proud. http://instagram.com/p/aZmNgiv4gu/     
    
    
    @jenbarnett It is known.    
    
    
    Any guesses on what's growing out of my compost? Butternut? Pumpkin? http://instagram.com/p/acFjSov4i_/     
    
    
    @jasonhmartin That might be more manageable at this point.    
    
    
    @jenbarnett I've never eaten an acorn squash, so doubtful it'd be in my compost. I'm terrified I might have 35 pumpkin plants.    
    
    
    @jenbarnett Zero, but I did throw a whole one into the compost bin after Halloween. Never again.    
    
    
    The 11 grossest fast food abominations from around the world: http://adweek.it/11vU2nU  My collaboration w/ @EpicMealTime    
    
    
    What are you doing in Tennessee, my old Midwestern friend? @ Culver's http://instagram.com/p/aeaA_ev4vw/     
    
    
    Ron Burgundy said it best: http://bit.ly/XrEzDr  RT @jonmbauer: Today's traffic jam gold: a guy eating corn on the cob for breakfast.    
    
    
    Who are some little-known but awesomely talented crafty bloggers?    
    
    
    @TomBLogue Crafty, like in the Beastie Boys way. Gets around, always down.    
    
    
    .@Mashable connected me w/ a photog for free social consulting. He built audience, but struggling to build sales: http://on.mash.to/1bzNN8a     
    
    
    @lmerricks Awesome, thanks!    
    
    
    POP TART TRUCK! https://vine.co/v/blFngL5pOZP     
    
    
    Just visited a site that lets you close its page-covering pop-up ad, but then makes you wait out the 15 seconds of blank screen anyway.    
    
    
    Our midcentury modern house just got a bit more modern. http://instagram.com/p/alJXigP4t0/     
    
    
    And so it begins: Pickle Season! http://instagram.com/p/aoDSmAP4g_/     
    
    
    @hanniespice It's incredibly easy and fun in a zen, crafty way. First few batches can be stressful, but I can send you tips if you go for it    
    
    
    @BitterOldPunk @elizarde Pickling on the stove top kinda wrecks the joy of an air conditioned house, but totally worth it.    
    
    
    @hanniespice Wow, that's super gross. Thanks for the extra motivation to keep up my DIY approach to pickles.    
    
    
    Bham folks, what's up with 31 traffic in Hoover/ Vestavia this morning?  Crawling to work.    
    
    
    Go home, Excel. You're drunk. pic.twitter.com/sk5HfyS7Cn    
    
    
    @digitaldamsel I should just file it and see what happens.    
    
    
    @jvreeland It was all going so well, too, until.... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZWrv3l_2tGQ …    
    
    
    Great Twitter promoted content feature: target non-mobile users. FB needs this, since its apps don't work in mobile. pic.twitter.com/sdjerwbFEM    
    
    
    In case you thought you were having a rough morning... http://instagram.com/p/ax_We9P4kN/     
    
    
    @LaraIsNatasha Overturned semi.    
    
    
    If you have to start a message with "I'm following up on the earlier emails and voicemails I left you," your sales prospects are slim.    
    
    
    Just discovered the "My Imaginary Well-Dressed Toddler Daughter" Pinterest Board. A. Mazing. http://pinterest.com/tiffanywbwg/my-imaginary-well-dressed-toddler-daughter/ …    
    
    
    