@jherskowitz we have a hack day coming up, I might propose it ;-)    
    
    
    #arresteddevelopment #season4 trailer http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?feature=youtu.be&v=vzVhPCMAxWQ&desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DvzVhPCMAxWQ%26feature%3Dyoutu.be …    
    
    
    "Most data isn’t “big,” and businesses are wasting money pretending it is" - a bit confusing, but interesting http://qz.com/81661/most-data-isnt-big-and-businesses-are-wasting-money-pretending-it-is/ …    
    
    
    Daughter: your music is weird and I don't like it. Me: I am glad I don't have the music taste of a 10 y.o. schoolgirl ;-)    
    
    
    @manas_somaiya you're welcome!    
    
    
    St. George Marathon lottery results are out, and we are in! Can't wait! http://www.stgeorgemarathon.com/     
    
    
    Q&A with @adrianco RT @mashable: This man has one of the coolest jobs at @Netflix - http://on.mash.to/10Sz1TL  #GetYourDreamJob    
    
    
    Good read RT @jongertner: My thoughts on Nate Silver—and Nate Silver's thoughts on Big Data—here: http://bit.ly/18FyWdJ .    
    
    
    Whenever I see a twitter profile stating "opinions are my own" I think "what a waste of characters".    
    
    
    @bmabey That's what I have heard. Can't wait!    
    
    
    @pankaj On the other hand, I usually find it is much easier for algo people to learn systems than viceversa.    
    
    
    Probably my favorite #netflix #hackday poster pic.twitter.com/lGTifuydqM    
    
    
    "Measuring User Engagement" - Excellent #www2013 tutorial http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/measuring-userengagement … via @denisparra    
    
    
    "From Amateurs to Connoisseurs..." - in the intersection of beer and algos http://i.stanford.edu/~julian/pdfs/www13.pdf … #www2013 #recsys via @shoha99 @denisparra    
    
    
    The Daily Startup: GraphLab Gathers $6.8M As Machine Learning Gains Steam http://zite.to/10zCfvv     
    
    
    Finished interview for a Wired article. Gotta love my job! /w @jorisevers    
    
    
    @octonion @cdixon they're not??? :-P    
    
    
    Did my half marathon PR today: 1:31 in the Capitola half!    
    
    
    Can you make a company out of buying others? I guess @marissamayer is determined to let us know.    
    
    
    Predicting Black Swans RT @RWW: Blinded By Big Data: It's The Models, Stupid by http://rww.to/18YEaBA     
    
    
    "In media Big Data is booming, but Big Results are lacking" (except for Netflix) http://allthingsd.com/20130520/in-media-big-data-is-booming-but-big-results-are-lacking/ …    
    
    
    "Is it time for a career switch?" - Not a plug for a job in my team, the title of a linkedin #www2013 #recsys [PAPER] http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1377.pdf …    
    
    
    "Online Controlled Experiments at Large Scale" [PAPER] - A/B Testing lessons from Bing by at #sigkdd2013 http://www.exp-platform.com/Pages/ControlledExperimentsAtLargeScale.aspx …    
    
    
    Two more AB test wins, two more algorithmic improvements on their way to improve Netflix member experience. Congrats to the team!    
    
    
    Concurrent Releases Pattern, a Machine Learning DSL for Hadoop http://zite.to/11dEaMn     
    
    
    Google has started a new lab to work on Quantum Machine Learning algorithms http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/05/launching-quantum-artificial.html …    
    
    
    UEFA Champions League tweeter data visualization (great to see Munich did not beat Barcelona so clearly on this) https://uclfinal.twitter.com/     
    
    
    Which proves writing an abstract is too easy MR @yueshi_nl: "We have received 1211 abstract submissions for full papers" #cikm2013    
    
    
    Celebrating #ArrestedDevelopment launch pic.twitter.com/kJU0ZsDuWN    
    
    
    "Timespent Based Models for Predicting User Retention" - Interesting #www2013 paper by @_5K et al. at Stumbleupon http://www2013.org/proceedings/p331.pdf …    
    
    
    "Do Social Explanations Work? Studying and Modeling the Effects of Social Explanations in #recsys" #www2013 http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1133.pdf …    
    
    
    "When Relevance is not Enough: Promoting Diversity & Freshness in Personalized Question #recsys" #www2013 http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1249.pdf …    
    
    
    Really amazed at how many #recsys papers there were at #www2013 this year. All available online: http://www2013.org/papers/proceedings.htm …    
    
    
    "Deep Learning of Representations: Looking Forward"  - Bengio on the promises and challenges of #deeplearning http://arxiv.org/pdf/1305.0445.pdf …    
    
    
    @xamat: List of #recsys related #www2013 papers in the recsys wiki http://recsyswiki.com/wiki/WWW_2013  via @abellogin    
    
    
    @_krisjack agree ;-)    
    
    
    " Your Browsing Behavior for a Big Mac: Economics of Personal Information Online" #www2013 by @elsubliminal et al http://www2013.org/proceedings/p189.pdf …    
    
    
    There is always money... pic.twitter.com/MsVN5fDdjh    
    
    
    Deep Learning Comes of Age http://zite.to/12328vj  at ACM Communications    
    
    
    Attending a talk on @hexadata by @srisatish    
    
    
    @DataJunkie @hexadata @srisatish Private event at Netflix. But, I am sure they can come pay you a visit ;-)    
    
    
    @DataJunkie @hexadata @srisatish Oh no, we got a much more personalized version ;-)    
    
    
    "The dictatorship of data" - good read http://www.technologyreview.com/news/514591/the-dictatorship-of-data/ … via @ravenben    
    
    
    "Machine Learning for Humans: kNN" http://www.jiaaro.com/KNN-for-humans/?utm_source=feedly …    
    
    
    Sumo bot wrestling in #hackPaloAlto pic.twitter.com/IBqZy3TEgT    
    
    
    @pacoid Thanks for the tip. It was great!    
    
    
    @pacoid I think my kids enjoyed the Tech Shop stuff a lot.    
    
    
    New @kaggle challenge: predict Amazon's employee's access rights: https://www.kaggle.com/c/amazon-employee-access-challenge … (at Netflix it would be easy: everyone everything)    
    
    
    What? Twitter no longer uses the whale?    
    
    
    Talk by @aficionado on @bigmlcom in 30 minutes. See you there http://www.sfbayacm.org/event/save-date-topic-tbd-6 …    
    
    
    @aficionado @bigmlcom @jaotwits I tant!    
    
    
    I am attending the "Analytics at Webscale" workshop at Facebook on Thursday http://analyticswebscale.splashthat.com/  - Ping me if you are going    
    
    
    Amazing line-up! Atoms for Peace, Beck, Animal Collective... Wish I could go
  http://www.treasureislandfestival.com/2013/     
    
    
    Women in Cloud meetup at Netflix on Thursday. If you are a woman in technology and are interested in cloud, signup http://womenincloud.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    First talk in the Webscale Analytics workshop: @squarecog on Twitter's infrastructure.    
    
    
    .@squarecog describing Parquet, a columnar format for Hadoop http://parquet.io/     
    
    
    Twitter's Data Access Layer is built on HCatalog @squarecog http://incubator.apache.org/hcatalog  pic.twitter.com/YNtUTRFMvl    
    
    
    Summingbird enables mapreduce-style workflow on Hadoop (batch processing), Storm (realtime processing) or both http://lanyrd.com/2013/lambda-jam/scghxb/ …    
    
    
    Interesting discussion on Mesos vs. YARN by @jaykreps at quora http://www.quora.com/How-does-YARN-compare-to-Mesos …    
    
    
    According to @squarecog Twiter has experimented with Spark, but has not managed to make it work in production http://spark-project.org/     
    
    
    Now @krishnagade talking about Twitter Storm    
    
    
    Btw, all my previous tweets should have been tagged with #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey http://analyticswebscale.splashthat.com/     
    
    
    Twitter's Storm topology for scoring and ranking tweets by @krishnagade pic.twitter.com/L5k8BStwbr    
    
    
    Now @junrao talking about Kafka and Espresso (a timeline consistent no-SQL data base http://data.linkedin.com/projects/espresso …) #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    And @sam_shah now talking about using Azkaban for workflow management #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @bigdatasci Indeed. Are you?    
    
    
    LinkedIn is also using Apache Giraph for iterative graph processing http://giraph.apache.org/  #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @bigdatasci Easy. Look for an Orange #ArrestedDevelopment T-Shirt.    
    
    
    Btw, very related to many of the talks today at #AnalyticsWebscale, my previous post on Netflix #recsys architecture http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/03/system-architectures-for.html …    
    
    
    Ravi Murthy from Facebook: the 600 TB/day we ingest will yield most of our architectures useless soon pic.twitter.com/OSAeHEGZrl    
    
    
    "A good day is when I can run 6 Hive queries" - A Facebook Data Scientist #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Facebook's solution to query inefficiency in Hive is called Presto. Looking forward to it being open sourced in the fall #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    According to Avery Ching, one of the main motivations for Giraph was to improve Facebook Recommendations #recsys #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Talking about Giraph, it will be great to see all graph computation frameworks side by side at the Graphlab workshop http://graphlab.org/graphlab-workshop-2013/ …    
    
    
    Facebook ran Page Rank on user graph with a trillion edges on 200 machines with Giraph in less than 6 minutes/iteration! #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Twitter Summingbird poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/4oRnCylAuZ    
    
    
    Scuba at Facebook poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/zRrZWJIbVo    
    
    
    Twitter's Data Access Layer poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/HWp4vrICLf    
    
    
    And @squarecog and his Parquet poster pic.twitter.com/HGu27sFOAr    
    
    
    "Improving options for unlocking your graph data" #graphlab #giraph #pregel #cassavary #neo4j ... http://strata.oreilly.com/2013/05/improving-options-for-unlocking-your-graph-data.html …    
    
    
    "Facebook unveils Presto engine for querying 250 PB data warehouse" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/06/facebook-unveils-presto-engine-for-querying-250-pb-data-warehouse/ … via @gigaom #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    New blog post: "Tools for Data Processing @ Webscale" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/06/tools-for-data-processing-webscale.html … #AnalyticsWebscale #storm #kafka #scuba #giraph #graphlab ...    
    
    
    Regardless of your opinion, a #mustwatch interview with Edward Snowden #nsafiles http://m.guardiannews.com/world/2013/jun/09/nsa-whistleblower-edward-snowden-why …    
    
    
    "Why you can't dislike something on Facebook?" - @benfrederickson from @zite on rating scales for #recsys    
    
    
    New blog post: "Tools for Data Processing @ Webscale" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/06/tools-for-data-processing-webscale.html … (In case you missed it over the weekend)    
    
    
    Deep Learning for NLP (without Magic) Tutorial by  Socher & Manning http://zite.to/14NaHoM     
    
    
    "Announcing Zuul: Edge Service in the Cloud" http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/announcing-zuul-edge-service-in-cloud.html …    
    
    
    "New from Netflix: Open-sourced gatekeeper to improve the delivery of web services" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/12/new-from-netflix-open-sourced-gatekeeper-to-deliver-web-services-better/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    @danielequercia @rodulforg @bdigital Yes, I even got a picture to prove it ;-) pic.twitter.com/jE3dm48XRu    
    
    
    "How Netflix deploys code" - blogpost about @jedberg's #qconnewyork talk http://www.infoq.com/news/2013/06/netflix …    
    
    
    "A real-time bonanza: Facebook’s Wormhole and Yahoo’s streaming Hadoop" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/14/a-real-time-bonanza-facebooks-wormhole-and-yahoos-streaming-hadoop/ …    
    
    
    When you are in a small meeting and two people are wearing @xkcd T-shirts, you know you are working in the right place ;-)    
    
    
    Mixed feelings about my 3:35 in the #sfmarathon. Great first half, but did not finish that well    
    
    
    @jimjansen Thanks!    
    
    
    @rusmeshenberg True ;-)    
    
    
    @atl Thanks!    
    
    
    Twitter's #recsys RT @dickc: the @magicrecs account is a product of some great work by the team here. Follow it!    
    
    
    The @MagicRecs project would be so much better if Twitter had invested just a little in improving DMs    
    
    
    "Announcing Ice: Cloud Spend and Usage Analytics" be @NetflixOSS http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/announcing-ice-cloud-spend-and-usage.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    "Apple and Netflix dominate online video"  http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/06/19/apple-and-netflix-dominate-online-video/?partner=yahoofinance …    
    
    
    @mdkail I think 41 is not correct.    
    
    
    "Neural networks, Google and cats" http://zite.to/1av1Aze  - Huge Deep Belief Networks running on a handful of GPUs    
    
    
    Improving Photo Search: A Step Across the Semantic Gap | Google Research Blog http://zite.to/12WWMCf     
    
    
    #sfmarathon finisher photo pic.twitter.com/0CngXGxGQR    
    
    
    .@NetflixOSS s01E03 meetup - Learn all about awesome Netflix OS projects first hand: http://www.meetup.com/Netflix-Open-Source-Platform/events/112697702/ …    
    
    
    "Netflix’s decision to renew Hemlock Grove shows its algorithms are working" http://paidcontent.org/2013/06/20/netflixs-decision-to-renew-hemlock-grove-shows-its-algorithms-are-working/ …    
    
    
    @yargnad Which of the two requires proprietary software?    
    
    
    @yargnad Sure, but you don't need an Apple TV to play iTunes content    
    
    
    "Genie is out of the bottle!" - Presenting @NetflixOSS's Hadoop job and resource management tool for the cloud http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/genie-is-out-of-bottle.html …    
    
    
    @badshah79 Thanks! :-)    
    
    
    "Sparse, Deep, and Random" - notes from #icml2013 by @PaulMineiro http://www.machinedlearnings.com/2013/06/icml-2013-sparse-deep-and-random.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&m=1 …    
    
    
    @pedronavf :-)    
    
    
    I will be giving a keynote a the #bigmine2013 workshop at #kdd2013 http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/  - hope to see you there!    
    
    
    @ocelma Si, Chicago. 11 d'Agost.    
    
    
    Very interesting talk at Netflix today on the Future of the Internet and Computers by @docjamesw    
    
    
    @pankaj Congrats! Didn't know you were running too.    
    
    
    Akka vs Storm http://prsm.tc/ykRPj2     
    
    
    @pankaj Next full marathon is St George. But will be running some local halves for sure before that.    
    
    
    @pankaj I did. 3:35. Enjoyed every bit of the first half (did it in 1:41), but really struggled at the end    
    
    
    Still trying to wrap my head around Wendy Davis' story today http://www.npr.org/blogs/thetwo-way/2013/06/26/195723770/texas-lawmakers-11-hour-filibuster-ended-on-a-technicality … - sad for Texas    
    
    
    "Pandora and Royalties" http://blog.pandora.com/2013/06/26/pandora-and-royalties/ … - Important read if, as opposed to RIAA, you care about music and Internet    
    
    
    At Netflix we love movies and TV shows... but also soccer ;-) (watching Spain-Italy over lunch) pic.twitter.com/0XlJ3WvCFc    
    
    
    eHarmony Refines the Science of Love : Hadoop + Machine Learning http://zite.to/154rasm     
    
    
    "The Philosophy of Netflix: Its Chief Content Officer Champions Storytelling" http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/06/the-philosophy-of-netflix-its-chief-content-officer-champions-storytelling/277354/ …    
    
    
    Will be missing #Graphlab2013 today, but will be following your tweets ;-)    
    
    
    A better title would be "A ver basic intro to #recsys" RT @olinhyde: The State of Recommender Technology: http://bit.ly/12bZBrR     
    
    
    ICML 2013 Reading List by @t3kcit http://zite.to/15dONPg     
    
    
    Terrible news: John Riedl, friend and #recsys pioneer died https://plus.google.com/app/basic/stream/z13gglbylz3sxrgiz04cexvgcmyrebgaopg0k … RIP John, your research will live on forever    
    
    
    4th of July, Catalan style pic.twitter.com/ZlUy1UlIAt    
    
    
    Sanfermines in San Francisco on Sunday: http://somastreatfoodpark.com/event/running-of-the-bulls-party/ …    
    
    
    An update on my tweet yesterday on John Riedl. Although he is losing his battle agains cancer, he is still alive http://www.caringbridge.org/visit/windsurferjohn …    
    
    
    A classical (1983) & not-very-technical description of the bootstrap method http://statistics.stanford.edu/~ckirby/techreports/BIO/BIO%2083.pdf … via @DEAGiles - http://davegiles.blogspot.it/     
    
    
    Did @thomyorke's Atoms for Peace album Amok just disappear from @Spotify? I swear it was there on Friday! wtf?    
    
    
    @ogrisel @thomyorke @Spotify That sucks :-(    
    
    
    "Finding Harmony with Big Data" - @techreview's feature article on @echonest's music technology http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2013/echo-nest-harmony-with-big-data-0710.html …    
    
    
    Quora looks to the crowd to solve machine learning problems http://zite.to/15gcGn4  #machinelearning    
    
    
    "You're Doing It Wrong!"-If you're writing data processing code disregarding software engineering practices  http://zite.to/18PIO6C     
    
    
    Graphical Causal Models http://zite.to/12tz9dp     
    
    
    An interesting reading list on Clustering http://zite.to/12tzhJT     
    
    
    Netflix HQ turned into a nice prison to celebrate launch of #OrangeIsTheNewBlack pic.twitter.com/ttpQFNhijM    
    
    
    #OrangeIsTheNewBlack #SoapOnARope pic.twitter.com/TxPmNjUone    
    
    
    @elehack ouch... yes... damn autocomplete :-)    
    
    
    Looking forward to upcoming @coursera course "Intro to Recommender Systems" by @jkonstan and @elehack https://www.coursera.org/course/recsys  #recsys    
    
    
    (Thanks @elehack for pointing out error in my previous tweet on #recsys @coursera course)    
    
    
    @mjcavaretta Thanks :-)    
    
    
    Interesting read RT @krishnagade: Why Microsoft’s reorganization is a bad idea @stratechery http://stratechery.com/2013/why-microsofts-reorganization-is-a-bad-idea/ …    
    
    
    First Workshop on Large-Scale Recommender Systems this year at #recsys2013 http://graphlab.org/lsrs2013/     
    
    
    @mortardata Thanks!    
    
    
    Barça's coach Tito steps down because of his illness http://m.guardian.co.uk/football/2013/jul/19/barcelona-press-conference-tito-vilanova … #AnimsTiTo    
    
    
    Uk government supports Turing's pardon  http://m.guardian.co.uk/uk-news/2013/jul/19/enigma-codebreaker-alan-turing-posthumous-pardon … - Not sure if a pardon feels right at this point really    
    
    
    "TV Foresees Its Future. Netflix Is There." - Great NYT piece http://www.nytimes.com/2013/07/22/business/media/tv-foresees-its-future-netflix-is-there.html?partner=yahoofinance&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Using Less Data http://zite.to/18rukHj  - sub-sampling classifiers at #icml2013    
    
    
    New blogpost: "Recommendations as Personalized Learning to Rank" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com.es/2013/07/recommendations-as-personalized.html … #recsys #machinelearning    
    
    
    Amazon just sent me an email recommending me s book I wrote a chapter for. Maybe they do know I never got a copy ;-) #recsys #fail?    
    
    
    @statpumpkin It was :-)    
    
    
    Yahoo Labs #Barcelona is looking for a Data-oriented Research Engineer http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/web/RRHH/Job_ref_Yahoo_FBM_BM0029.pdf … @danielequercia can give you more details    
    
    
    Excited about the talk I will be giving tomorrow at @IBMResearch Almaden in the "Accelerated Discovery Forum" series at 10 am.    
    
    
    "Unhappy Truckers and Other Algorithmic Problems" - @tomvanderbilt on traveling salesmen & other transportation algos http://nautil.us/issue/3/in-transit/unhappy-truckers-and-other-algorithmic-problems …    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @_rnbrewer: Great talk by Netflix director, @xamat, at @IBMResearch #Almaden today    
    
    
    Netflix rolls out individual user profiles http://blog.netflix.com/2013/08/make-netflix-your-own-with-profiles.html …    
    
    
    One of the biggest unsolved questions for mankind: what to do with the thousands of pictures I have taken during vacation...    
    
    
    @gy4nt Thanks!    
    
    
    In case you missed my last blog post "Recommendations as Personalized Learning to Rank" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/07/recommendations-as-personalized.html …    
    
    
    "Amazon founder says he clicked on Washington Post by mistake" http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/borowitzreport/2013/08/amazon-founder-says-he-clicked-on-washington-post-by-mistake.html … - LOL    
    
    
    Carlos and me talking about @netflix recommendations @WIRED http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/08/qq_netflix-algorithm/ … #recsys via @tomvanderbilt    
    
    
    @JacobMargolis Why don't you send me some details on what you have in mind to xavier at netflix dot com    
    
    
    @davidbs Gracias compi!    
    
    
    "The Algorithm That Tells Netflix Which Movies You Really Want to Watch" http://gizmodo.com/the-algorithm-that-tells-netflix-which-movies-you-reall-1054431105?utm_campaign=socialflow_gizmodo_twitter&utm_source=gizmodo_twitter&utm_medium=socialflow … @Gizmodo's take on the Wired article    
    
    
    Nice compilation :-) MT @TimeOutNewYork 15h  A dead shark on the subway, 200-year-old liquor, and Netflix algorithm http://tmout.us/nJqoh     
    
    
    @squarecog That's the whole point: you can build a successful product on a UI that "only" uses recommendations ;-)    
    
    
    @squarecog You can still do that if you go to the Genre Galleries on the web: you can browse sub-genres, sort.... What do you miss?    
    
    
    "Netflix knows you've been lying about all those foreign films and documentaries you say you like" http://www.avclub.com/articles/netflix-knows-youve-been-lying-about-all-those-for,101336/ …    
    
    
    "How Netflix Helps You Decide What to Watch" http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-netflix-helps-you-decide-601956 …    
    
    
    Hope to see many of you at my invited talk at the @BigDataMining1 workshop at #KDD2013 on Sunday: http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/#amatriain …    
    
    
    @philosophygeek Don't look like Piquillo to me: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Piquillo_pepper … Are you sure they are?    
    
    
    Finished recording my session for the #recsys coursera course with @elehack. Can't wait until it's available! https://www.coursera.org/course/recsys     
    
    
    "Post water-cooler TV" @nytimes via @netflix http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/11/arts/television/how-to-make-a-tv-drama-in-the-twitter-age.html?hp&pagewanted=all&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Heading to Chicago, plane full of #kdd2013 geeks ;-)    
    
    
    @BigDataAnalysis Probably sharing plane ;-)    
    
    
    Any runners in #kdd2013 up for a morning run in Chicago during the conference days?    
    
    
    Good explanation of an important issue MT @DEAGiles: Large and Small Regression Coefficients http://davegiles.blogspot.com/2013/08/large-and-small-regression-coefficients.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    #kdd2013 starting now! Two-sided badge #win. No power outlets in workshop rooms + hearing everything from the neighboring rooms... #fail    
    
    
    @FrancescoBonchi Ricardo told me you would be here... hope we can meet!    
    
    
    In 5 minutes, my talk on Netflix Big Data & Recommendations in the @BigDataMining1 workshop #kdd2013    
    
    
    Actually my talk at @BigDataMining1 is at 10:30 #kdd2013    
    
    
    @kdnuggets Thanks! We should chat. I am sure we will run into each other during the conference.    
    
    
    #kdd2013 RT @smolix: Slides for the KDD tutorial are at https://mega.co.nz/#!ShwEQRKa!SvWgyybALxR7wo5jolelxQQSO1BJyGduK_mnLJgd3_Q … and https://mega.co.nz/#!KoQT3RTQ!eHnOi3HA9nr5u-MHAbeyCkCi_g0yT9-awKe4Yix8PdU …    
    
    
    Context on my previous tweet: slides are Alex Smola & Amr Ahmed's #kdd2013 tutorial "Bayesian Nonparametrics and Mixed Membership Models"    
    
    
    Winners of this years #kddcup (both tracks) are all students from a class in the Taiwan National University #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/LwRLfEclRS    
    
    
    #kddcup winning team used ensemble of GBDT, Random Forests & LambdaMart... and lots of feature engineering http://www.cwi.ugent.be/kddcup2013/track1place1.pdf … #kdd2013    
    
    
    Raghu Ramakrishnan (@raghurwi ) talking about "the digital shoebox" in his "beyond map reduce" #kdd2013 keynote pic.twitter.com/V5wbxZ3QMq    
    
    
    Those of you not in #kdd2013 wondering about @raghurwi's digital shoebox can start in these slides http://research.microsoft.com/en-us/events/fs2013/raghu-ramakrishnan_bigdataplatforms.pdf … #yarn #reef    
    
    
    New Microsoft #REEF framework will be open source and will be presented in @strataconf in October http://strataconf.com/stratany2013/public/schedule/detail/30895 … #kdd2013    
    
    
    Raghu Ramakrishnan: "If you want to implement the next Mahout, contact me to build it on #REEF" #kdd2013    
    
    
    Wow! Rooms at #kdd2013 completely packed. Make my original idea of moving from session to session pretty hard :-(    
    
    
    #kdd2013 influencer graph MT @marc_smith: kdd2013 NodeXL SNA http://bit.ly/19dPMQA     
    
    
    A packed room is even more uncomfortable if the guy sitting next to you is constantly looking at the notes you are taking #kdd2013    
    
    
    Slides for my keynote yesterday at the @BigDataMining1 workshop are now online http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/#amatriain … #kdd2013    
    
    
    .@AndrewYNg's #kdd2013 keynote delivered via videoconferencing a la @coursera pic.twitter.com/JOUjgyPNM3    
    
    
    This is how the Deep Learning talk by @jeremyphoward looks. Either too many people or too little room #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/d4C2kbPuMl    
    
    
    .@gigaom reporting on today's #kdd2013 keynote by Raghu Ramakrishnan's http://gigaom.com/2013/08/12/microsoft-to-open-source-a-big-data-framework-called-reef/ … via @markusweimer    
    
    
    .@jeremyphoward getting to #deeplearning through the idea of avoiding overfitting with tree ensembles. But GBM/GBDT don't #kdd2013    
    
    
    @jeremyphoward I was standing in the last row. But was able to follow. Nice talk!    
    
    
    @juliaxgulia first name at Netflix dot com    
    
    
    Funny that I am getting far more twitter followers from attending #kdd2013 than from being featured at @wired http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/08/qq_netflix-algorithm/ …    
    
    
    #kdd2013 keynote today by Stephen Wright: great tutorial on optimization [SLIDES] http://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~swright/wright-kdd-2013.pdf …    
    
    
    Overbooked industry sessions at #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/veYAZ8JLbz    
    
    
    "Why California Can't Be Home to the Hyperloop"-An article saying that California is bad for business has to be BS http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/227807# !    
    
    
    @usabart I said it was BS!!    
    
    
    @usabart Btw, I also felt tricked by LinkedIn when it appeared in my feed    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @usabart no worries. It's good to read things you don't agree with... occasionally :-)    
    
    
    No visit to Chicago is complete without a proper Jazz/Blues concert #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/2kDq1mG0Xx    
    
    
    +1 (well maybe XXth) MT @frankolken: Chicago Sheraton had neither useable wifi nor electrical power for #kdd2013.  Welcome to 19th century.    
    
    
    Hal Varian (Google's Chief Economist) remembering his UCB Professor times & explaining Kalman Filters, Spike & Slab Regression... #kdd2013    
    
    
    Nice to see Google's Chief Economist using R commands in a keynote (e.g. stl = Seasonal Decomposition of Time Series by Loess) #kdd2013    
    
    
    @cdubhland @twitter Not true... there are twitter people in the audience, not sure they'd want to argue though ;-)    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @rachelmetz 15h  this is like total aural nostalgia. museum of endangered sounds: http://savethesounds.info     
    
    
    Wait... so Google has very smart people working on using their data for economic forecasting. I wonder what they want that for ;-) #kdd2013    
    
    
    I have a proposal for next year's #kddcup: "Predicting audience for KDD sessions". Not hard & could help on deciding room sizes #kdd2013    
    
    
    Since @twitter does not allow for an easy partitioning of my feed into topics, I created @xamat_music for my twitter #music    
    
    
    @_amrahmed Thanks Amr... really appreciate it!    
    
    
    @pathak_s @twitter @Quora I think it's very easy to figure out topics users I follow belong to. You can then split feed according to source    
    
    
    @elversatile @Jetlore There is nothing in that URL except for a server welcome message. Is the system down?    
    
    
    @IgorBrigadir @twitter @xamat_music they could be an option if they also filtered listed people from my main feed.    
    
    
    @elversatile I just signed up. I will let you know. But, from what I read it looks more like @Zite or @Prismatic    
    
    
    @sscdotopen IBM?    
    
    
    @sscdotopen Yes, I know. But, you were there?    
    
    
    @sscdotopen Oh, didn't recognize you :-)    
    
    
    Good idea! RT @manas_somaiya: @xamat , @twitter needs to introduce @netflix style profiles.    
    
    
    Google researcher: "Why are you taking that picture? You could find the exact same one in Google Images" - You gotta love us geeks    
    
    
    .@AmericanAir I understand I have to pay for food in a 4 hour flight. What I don't understand is you run of food to sell!    
    
    
    "Google scientist Jeff Dean on how neural networks are improving everything Google does" http://zite.to/16aEf5R  via @zite    
    
    
    "Frontiers in Massive Data Analysis" - A free downloadable report from the National Academies committee http://www.nap.edu/catalog.php?record_id=18374 … #bigdata    
    
    
    Great to attend #kdd2013 this week. I am sure many of the attendees will be interested in this position in my team: http://jobs.netflix.com/jobsListing.html?id=NFX00370 …    
    
    
    "Demystifying Porn 2.0: A look into a major adult video streaming website" - A pretty interesting [PAPER] http://www.eecs.qmul.ac.uk/~steve/papers/IMC13.pdf … #imc2013    
    
    
    I should have added the previous paper is SFW ;-)    
    
    
    The New Yorker reporting on an #ijcai2013 paper by Levesque on why we are not building "true AI" http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/08/why-cant-my-computer-understand-me.html?mbid=social_retweet … via @mikiobraun    
    
    
    OMG! Shocked :-( RIP MT @HCIR_GeneG: Sad news:  Gene Golovchinsky passed away this Thursday.  It was very sudden. http://tinyurl.com/HCIRGene     
    
    
    "Expecting the unexpected from Jeff Bezos" - interesting portrait in NYT after his purchase of the Washington Post  http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/18/business/expecting-the-unexpected-from-jeff-bezos.html?pagewanted=all&_r=1& …    
    
    
    "We're on the cusp of deep learning for the masses, you can thank Google later" @gigaom - featuring @jeremyphoward http://gigaom.com/2013/08/16/were-on-the-cusp-of-deep-learning-for-the-masses-you-can-thank-google-later/ …    
    
    
    "Big Data Science from R" meetup by @hexadata http://www.meetup.com/H2Omeetup/events/132640822/?gj=wc1f_e&a=wc1f_gnl&rv=wc1f_e …    
    
    
    @emanuel_strauss Definitely! Why don't you connect to me on LinkedIn? Or send email to first_name at netflix dot com.    
    
    
    "The Antifragile Organization" @atseitlin in ACM Communications http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/8/166315-the-antifragile-organization/abstract … (open access version http://delivery.acm.org/10.1145/2500000/2499552/p20-tseitlin.pdf?ip=69.53.237.66&id=2499552&acc=OPEN&key=BF13D071DEA4D3F3B0AA4BA89B4BCA5B&CFID=355023284&CFTOKEN=43477826&__acm__=1377035650_d26c6371466e7ed01e0acd076b3aba13 …)    
    
    
    Featuring our algos MT @TechCrunch: Netflix Introduces 'My List,' A Personalized Instant Queue http://tcrn.ch/172istS     
    
    
    "Introducing My List From Netflix" at the Netflix blog: http://blog.netflix.com/2013/08/introducing-my-list-from-netflix.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    Great summary of the conference with awesome pics MT @dirkvandenpoel: Visual summary #KDD2013 feat.  @xamat and more http://bit.ly/175dtbF     
    
    
    @dirkvandenpoel Thanks for the reference!    
    
    
    "C++ and the culture of complexity" - a #mustread for those of us who consider C++ our mother tongue http://blog.greaterthanzero.com/post/58482859780/c-and-the-culture-of-complexity … via @siah    
    
    
    @elehack why? Do you prefer a piece of paper?    
    
    
    @elehack the only time I did it, the officer did not accept it as a valid ID ;-)    
    
    
    @elehack But, you don't need to hand it, only show it as you do in the airport    
    
    
    @JustinBasilico @freakonomics Seems interesting, but the server has been down all day    
    
    
    So the Simpson paradox is now called a giraffe? MT @kdnuggets: Beware of the "giraffes" in your data http://bit.ly/1dfn8CL  @gigaom    
    
    
    @mikiobraun It depends in what kind of job interviews you have in mind ;-)    
    
    
    "Men should wear a suit and a tie" - Seriously?? RT @mashable: How to Make a Good First Impression at a Job Interview http://on.mash.to/16yVmIV     
    
    
    .@kdnuggets To be clear, I am not against using the term "giraffe", but it would have been nice to cite the more formal name    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey Matt, you are at Google MV, right? I am giving a talk there tomorrow    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey great!    
    
    
    I am giving a tech talk tomorrow at Google HQ. Looking forward to seeing many Googlers there!    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey You did! We should catch up some time so i can give you a personalized version ;-)    
    
    
    Congrats! MT @denisparra  Finally I am a PhD. Thanks to the best mentors I could've had @peterpaws n @xamat , thanks also to whole committee    
    
    
    Great experience today interviewing Netflix members to understand how they use our personalization.    
    
    
    @PENGUINANA_ We are constantly surveying our members on different aspects of the service. We have a team focused on that    
    
    
    When will Twitter realize it needs a tweet ranking algorithm? MT @gigaom: Why Twitter’s new Conversations is a big http://wp.me/p10LZV-2S9P     
    
    
    @_amrahmed Sent you an email. Did you get it?    
    
    
    Watching @baracksdubs #thingsYouDoOnAWeekendWithATeenageKid    
    
    
    I bet they are not thinking on naming a Helsinki street after Elop any time soon    
    
    
    Amazing lineup for #cikm2013 industry track. Psyched to be included http://www.cikm2013.org/industry.php     
    
    
    "Streaming MapReduce with Summingbird" - @twitter announces new OSS http://prsm.tc/iePqSr     
    
    
    @xamat: Does the fact I really like @ifcportlandia make it very easy to profile me? (Glad season 3 is #NowOnNetflix )    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @alexk_z: Jumping in for @xamat and presenting a tutorial on #recsys tomorrow at @essir2013 in Granada http://www.ugr.es/~essir2013/     
    
    
    Cheering for @bholmes who is currently half way of the 100 miles of the #Wasatch100    
    
    
    #recsys RT @mashable: Airlines Are Trying to Get Personal With Your Data http://on.mash.to/15FoHYS     
    
    
    Tempted MT @runnersworld: Try this innovative breathing technique that will maximize your running http://ow.ly/oDN0l     
    
    
    Hosting a nice talk on MLbase, a distributed #machinelearning framework running on #spark and callable from #scala http://mlbase.org/     
    
    
    "Domesticating Pig with Lipstick" - @mortardata integrates @NetflixOSS's Pig visualization tool into Mortar http://blog.mortardata.com/post/60765120319/domesticating-pig-with-lipstick …    
    
    
    @izendejas It was an internal talk I hosted yesterday    
    
    
    "23 things that could only exist in Silicon Valley" http://www.buzzfeed.com/jessicamisener/23-things-that-could-only-exist-in-silicon-valley?s=mobile … via @carlosdomingo    
    
    
    "Q&A The Catalan Way Explained" - to understand a bit better what will happen in Catalonia today http://m.ara.cat/viacatalana/catalan-way-catalonia-independence_0_990501167.html …    
    
    
    .@twitter's trending topic algo failing: #SomEspanya is #TT in Catalonia when #ViaCatalana should http://topsy.com/analytics?q1=%23ViaCatalana%20&q2=%23SomEspanya&via=Topsy … via @sisquere    
    
    
    Will be speaking about #machinelearning and #recsys at #mlconf in SF on 11/15. Great lineup: http://www.mlconf.com/mlconf-2013/     
    
    
    SF ACM Chapter talk on Monday, controversial topic (with which I disagree): designing #recsys as advertising systems http://www.meetup.com/SF-Bay-ACM/events/139785862/?a=ea1_grp&rv=ea1&_af_eid=139785862&_af=event …    
    
    
    @geekycourtney I think you missed the year again ;-)    
    
    
    "Using Chef and Vagrant to Put Lipstick on a Pig"- @mortardata open sources tools to integrate Lipstick to Mortar http://blog.mortardata.com/post/61026715305/using-chef-and-vagrant-to-put-lipstick-on-a-pig …    
    
    
    @mortardata now with link... Thanks!    
    
    
    Twitter files for IPO http://allthingsd.com/20130912/twitter-files-for-ipo/# …! via @allthingsd    
    
    
    My friends at Voctrolabs will be presenting in Barcelona the first virtual concert featuring Bruno, Clara & Ona http://www.voctro-vocaloid.com/en/archives/871     
    
    
    My friend Paul is trying to become JATW's next Chief World Explorer. Please vote for him! http://www.bestjobaroundtheworld.com/submissions/view/15200 …    
    
    
    "A Focus on Efficiency" - a 70 page long white paper by Facebook, Ericsson, and Qualcomm on Data Centers, Apps... https://fbcdn-dragon-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/851560_196423357203561_929747697_n.pdf …    
    
    
    I will be presenting "Machine Learning & Recommender Systems at Netflix Scale" at @qconSF on November 12 http://qconsf.com/presentation/machine-learning-recommender-systems-netflix-scale …    
    
    
    Facebook's LibPhenom: an eventing framework for building high performance and high scalability systems in C http://facebook.github.io/libphenom/     
    
    
    Family bonding time with #GATV ... Sign of the times.    
    
    
    Dear recruiters, if you are trying to impress me by starting your message in Spanish, you should know "Hello" is "Hola", not "Ola" (sigh)    
    
    
    If you are interested in attending @mlconf in SF for  #machineLearning talks from interesting speakers, discount here http://ml1.eventbrite.com/?discount=xaviersdiscount …    
    
    
    Sometimes Google Scholar makes my day when an awesome new paper is citing me. Today: "RUMBATOR: A Flamenco Rumba Cover Generator" :-)    
    
    
    Interesting speakers in the Big Data Spain conference http://www.bigdataspain.org/  #BDSpain    
    
    
    I am looking for an engineering/research manager with strong ML background to help me lead the new AE team at Netflix http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00883 …    
    
    
    Agree, that's why working on it is awesome RT @anjalimullany: Video recommendation is still far from perfect: http://www.fastcompany.com/3017012/tech-forecast/youtube-is-winning-an-emmy-but-video-recommendation-still-has-a-long-way-to-go … #recsys    
    
    
    Lots of research went into this RT @TheOnion: New Netflix Gas Lets Users Inhale Multiple Seasons Of TV Shows http://onion.com/1amuFLK     
    
    
    Dear LinkedIn, your mobile app is a mess. Thank you.    
    
    
    Watching last episode tonight RT @andersoncooper: Has anyone else watched #TheFall on Netflix? I think it was originally on BBC. It's great!    
    
    
    Nothing like adding "deep" to make headlines MT @siah: Facebook 'deep learning’ neural networks to learn about you http://ow.ly/pbLK9     
    
    
    Want to hear Trevor Hastie talking about GBM's, learn about @hexadata, and @netflix? We're hosting an event 10/10 http://www.meetup.com/Silicon-Valley-Big-Data-Science/events/141495222/ …    
    
    
    "Big Data: Does Size Really Matter?" - at Wired http://www.wired.com/insights/2013/09/big-data-does-size-really-matter/ … - Is it me or this post is confusing and misleading?    
    
    
    Functional Programming and the Power of Math at XKCD RT @xkcdrss Functional http://xkcd.com/1270/     
    
    
    .@NetflixOSS #cloudprize nominations announced: http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/09/netflixoss-meetup-s1e4-cloud-prize.html …    
    
    
    Lots of coffee today. Have to connect remotely to give a talk @catosfera at 2 AM local time. Wish me luck ;-)    
    
    
    First time I think I get a paper version of the GPL with a piece of equipment. pic.twitter.com/uPGemBtPFq    
    
    
    @ocelma Si noi, ara surto cap a Netflix per connectar des d'allà ;-)    
    
    
    @Montsinya Gràcies!    
    
    
    @gcapdevila Gràcies!    
    
    
    @pcarriet Un plaer ;-)    
    
    
    2 AM, giving my talk for @catosfera at the Netflix theatre pic.twitter.com/QMtJSiP40M    
    
    
    @_andy_tea yes, but my talk has finished http://2013.catosfera.cat/     
    
    
    @_andy_tea and, it is in Catalan ;-)    
    
    
    Lesson 1 tonight: giving a talk where you don't see your audience is hard    
    
    
    Will try! MT @aquigley: as ridiculous as this sounds. I use photo of an audience on my screen when delivering remote or recording a talk.    
    
    
    Lesson 2: giving a talk it in a language you are not used to (even if that is your mother tongue) is really hard    
    
    
    Magic? MT @JDavidMorris: Topological Data Analysis (TDA), @Ayasdi machine learning w/o algorithms, queries or models. http://ow.ly/pj3R0     
    
    
    Wow! Was surprised by some twitter account with a huge number of followers. Turns most of them have no profile pic or followers.    
    
    
    I guess it would not be hard to put twitter follower buyers to shame with a simple algo. Is anyone doing it already?    
    
    
    @jamneuf Accounts might be completely legitimate, but not the followers. Thousands of russian-sounding names with 0 followers? Weird.    
    
    
    2:03:23... wow!    
    
    
    "How Netflix Uses Analytics To Select Movies, Create Content, and Make Multimillion Dollar Decisions" http://blog.kissmetrics.com/how-netflix-uses-analytics/ … - Nice recap!    
    
    
    St. George Marathon: 3:24. Super happy to beat my goal of 3:30.    
    
    
    Good read. With @spotify no matter what @thomyorke says RT @fulhack: How Spotify Engineered the New Music Economy: http://mashable.com/2013/10/06/spotify-music-economy/ …    
    
    
    "A Month in the Life of a Production News Recommender System" - [PAPER] by @alansaid et al. http://oai.cwi.nl/oai/asset/21477/21477A.pdf … #recsys    
    
    
    @jaume_albaiges oops ;-)    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie and Hexadata will be talking about distributed GBMs at Netflix on Thursday. Hope to see you there! http://www.meetup.com/Silicon-Valley-Big-Data-Science/events/141495222/ …    
    
    
    Will be missing #recsys2013 for the first time ever. But, @JustinBasilico and others will be representing Netflix    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie @netflix talking about trees pic.twitter.com/JsGE52lCYr    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie: "Boosting overfits less quickly, but, given enough noise, it still will"    
    
    
    Today I interviewed someone with PhD and 5+ years working on #machinelearning at Google who could not answer any of my ML questions, wow :-(    
    
    
    Ok, for those of you asking, example question: "What is Logistic Regression?"    
    
    
    @UltimateHurl what? How could anyone get that wrong?!    
    
    
    @notrockstar I think it was    
    
    
    Nice words ;-) RT @greglinden: New post up on Geeking with Greg, "I was wrong on Netflix" http://glinden.blogspot.com/2013/10/i-was-wrong-on-netflix.html …    
    
    
    @leifos @alansaid @jkonstan don't know what the context is, but that's a "stupid generalization" ;-) Recall is great in many scenarios    
    
    
    @philosophygeek they have awesome wines at a very reasonable price, how's the winery?    
    
    
    B.S., look at their job posts! MT @FastCompany: Screw Algorithms! Beats Uses Celebrity Curators To Show You New Music http://f-st.co/nLs4TSh     
    
    
    Everybody, including Beats, knows algorithms beat celebrities @FastCompany - only celebs are easier to get (look at their jobs site)    
    
    
    .@ocelma @FastCompany You mean like doing some sort if expert-based collaborative filtering? I think I know a guy who wrote some papers ;-)    
    
    
    @alansaid @dtunkelang @mitultiwari A few people from Netflix like @JustinBasilico also!    
    
    
    @danielmintz I think most of us have figured out that "plays" are more valuable than ratings. Most music #recsys don't use ratings AFAIK    
    
    
    @danielequercia @FastCompany @johnpaul They sure can be combined! But if you had to choose one, which one would you choose?    
    
    
    @xamat: Are you interested in a phone that lasts and you don't throw away?http://phonebloks.com  - cool idea #phonebloks    
    
    
    Oh no! MT @amt_shrma: The convergence of search, advertising and recommendations http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2011/11/138205-information-seeking-convergence-of-search-recommendations-and-advertising/fulltext … #recsys #recsys2013    
    
    
    @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma I fully disagree. Recommendations & advertising are optimizing different things.    
    
    
    Sorry, I am ok with unifying search & #recsys, but not ads. They have fundamentally different objective functions http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2011/11/138205-information-seeking-convergence-of-search-recommendations-and-advertising/fulltext …    
    
    
    @pankaj @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma Sure, and the web is search + html :-)    
    
    
    Got my ticket to @kendricklamar + @kanyewest next week. Excited to be taking my son to his first concert!    
    
    
    Are you at #recsys2013 & passionate about #recsys & #machinelearning? Look at the position we have at Netflix: http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00882 …    
    
    
    @adityagp I read "All three mechanisms share the same common goal" and I disagree.    
    
    
    @adityagp I read "We predict that in the future the distinction will be blurred" and I hope you are wrong.    
    
    
    @adityagp I did read the article and I disagree, sorry    
    
    
    @adityagp Sharing infrastructure at a low level is fine, but you are blurring the lines    
    
    
    @adityagp @pankaj @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @greglinden @amt_shrma Like "offering a unified interface for user needs"? - I disagree    
    
    
    @adityagp Well, that's wrong, and it's not recommendation ;-)    
    
    
    I think this deserves a blog post (re: #recsys vs. ads). I'll see if I can find the time.    
    
    
    +1 MT @dtunkelang Speaking of interfaces, dear Twitter please figure out a better group chat soon    
    
    
    "Is music the key to success?" - interesting NYT op-ed piece http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/13/opinion/sunday/is-music-the-key-to-success.html?smid=fb-share&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Analyzing sentiment in movie reviews with Deep Learning https://engineering.stanford.edu/news/stanford-algorithm-analyzes-sentence-sentiment-advances-machine-learning …    
    
    
    Tutorial on "People Recommendation" at #recsys2013 by @kamikaze_bhasin [SLIDES] http://www.slideshare.net/anmolbhasin/tutorial-on-people-recommendations-in-social-networks-acm-recsys-2013hong-kong …    
    
    
    One of the great things of living in the Valley is getting to meet all these fascinating people. Tonight dinner with @adamdangelo    
    
    
    Oh Stonebraker! RT @neil_conway: "The Traditional RDBMS Wisdom Is All Wrong" -Stonebraker's slides from his HPTS talk http://hpts.ws/papers/2013/allwrong.pdf …    
    
    
    Microsoft Leans on Machine Learning and Quantum Computing in New Research Strategy http://zite.to/GPNbTx     
    
    
    Oh my RT @mashable: .@Microsoft Pulls @Windows RT 8.1 Update http://on.mash.to/1ezSvGd     
    
    
    "Trouble at the lab" great article @TheEconomist about stats errors & non-reproducible research http://www.economist.com/news/briefing/21588057-scientists-think-science-self-correcting-alarming-degree-it-not-trouble?fsrc=scn/tw_ec/trouble_at_the_lab … via @aficionado    
    
    
    MT @moustaki VistaTV demonstration at #recsys2013 - http://vista-tv.eu/2013/10/18/vista-tv-demonstration-at-recsys-2013/ …    
    
    
    "Netflix's 3Q Earnings Quadruple, Stock Soars" - That's how we roll :-) http://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/netflixs-3q-earnings-quadruple-top-street-views-20638570 …    
    
    
    Sent two tweets yesterday that never seemed to make it to my timeline or drafts. Weird.    
    
    
    .@kanyewest in concert last night (one of the tweets that did not go through... testing) pic.twitter.com/67mOjt2UMD    
    
    
    Looking forward to #cikm2013 next week and my talk in the Industry track  (http://www.cikm2013.org/industry.php ). Ping me if interested in chatting.    
    
    
    "The a Paradox of the Proof" - great read on the mysteries of modern theoretical mathematics http://projectwordsworth.com/the-paradox-of-the-proof/ …    
    
    
    R.I.P. Lou Reed :-( http://m.rollingstone.com/music/news/lou-reed-velvet-underground-leader-and-rock-pioneer-dead-at-71-20131027 …    
    
    
    If you are interested in #mlconf (http://www.mlconf.com/mlconf-2013/speakers-abstracts-and-bios/ …) and haven't registered already, you can use code xaviersdiscount for 25% discount    
    
    
    @n0mad_0 I am there too ;-)    
    
    
    Sad Pedro Domingos tutorial #cikm2013 was cancelled. But enjoying "Large Scale Similarity Learning and Indexing" https://www.dropbox.com/s/tpwcis94utp6equ/CIKM13_tut.pdf …    
    
    
    No wifi at #cikm2013 because "number of allowed devices has been exceeded"?    
    
    
    @DataJunkie We should meet this time. I was also in that tutorial ;-)    
    
    
    Attending a tutorial on "Real-time bidding" at #cikm2013    
    
    
    Some more information about the Real-time Bidding Tutorial at #cikm2013 in this website http://tutorial.computational-advertising.org     
    
    
    Don Draper (Mad Men) quote in the Real-time Bidding tutorial #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/SsmyyxXMzW    
    
    
    Too much stuff in parallel at #cikm2013 Going into 2nd part of "Large Scale Machine Learning for IR" http://www.cs.binghamton.edu/~blong/LSML-tutorial-cikm2013/ …    
    
    
    Nice to see LinkedIn using Thompson Sampling as explore/exploit strategy in their ad optimization system http://books.nips.cc/papers/files/nips24/NIPS2011_1232.pdf … #cikm2013    
    
    
    @dtunkelang What time?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang I decided to go home and work given there is the reception tomorrow and the banquet on Wednesday. Will you be around?    
    
    
    My Macbook Air HD is completely gone. All I did today was copy #cikm2013 proceedings. I'd be careful.    
    
    
    For those in the #cikm2013 large-scale ML tutorial, this year's best papers for #kdd2013 and #recsys2013 were both on large-scale MF ....    
    
    
    (...cont) #kdd2013 best paper on Matrix Sketching: http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/el327/papers/simpleMatrixSketching.pdf# …! & #recsys2013 on parallel SGD http://www.csie.ntu.edu.tw/~cjlin/papers/libmf.pdf# …! #cikm2013    
    
    
    A "classic", but not really MF RT @fulhack: @xamat This paper solved all our issues with large-scale MF: http://www2007.org/paper570.php     
    
    
    At #cikm2013 and interested in a #machinelearning job at Netflix? Ping me during the week http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00882 …    
    
    
    @chr1sa @github that is if you can't figure out yourself in a coding interview I guess?    
    
    
    "Deep Learning for NLP without Magic" - [VIDEO] by Richard Socher and Chris Manning http://techtalks.tv/events/312/573/  (starting with @ML_Hipster quote)    
    
    
    "Spain’s Fiesta del Cine and price elasticity of demand" by @edans https://medium.com/enrique-dans/cd63b2b6753 …    
    
    
    +1 post, -1 to use of "Netflix-style recommender" RT @siah: Music Recommendations and the Logistic Metric Embedding  http://ow.ly/qjfAN     
    
    
    I already proposed in #kdd2013, and we have same issue in #cikm2013: can someone build a demand prediction model for conference sessions?    
    
    
    (...cont) simple predictor: if @edchi and @smolix are authors in a paper, do not use smallest room #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/CuABEjKLaj    
    
    
    Predicting expert Zagat restaurant ratings using grassroot Google Places ratings [PAPER] http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~chenhao/pub/instant-foodie.pdf … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Btw, @edchi and @smolix, did you read our (old) paper analyzing difference between Netflix and RottenTomatoes raters? http://www.nuriaoliver.com/RecSys/wisdomFew_sigir09.pdf …    
    
    
    "Scientiﬁc Articles Recommendation" - Interesting work at #cikm2013 using topic-regression matrix factorization    
    
    
    @yueshi_nl They cite that paper. According to authors main difference is that they also regularize through a Gaussian Prior (besides LDA)    
    
    
    #cikm2013 industry talk by Rich Caruana "Clustering: Probably Approximately Useless". Slides & video of similar talk http://research.microsoft.com/apps/video/dl.aspx?id=204336 …    
    
    
    According to @ted_dunning, most important recsys issues are exploration, diversity, and speed. And #netflixPrize was useless :-/ #cikm2013    
    
    
    One of the most important findings in #recsys in the last 20 years is Result Dithering @ted_dunning #cikm2013 - really?    
    
    
    I do have to say that now @ted_dunning is going into more principled E/E approaches such as Thompson Sampling #cikm2013    
    
    
    (shameless plug) I will be giving my #cikm2013 talk tomorrow 4 pm. And possibly replying to some of @ted_dunning's claims today ;-)    
    
    
    Now Deepak Agarwal on computational advertising at LinkedIn #cikm2013 - reminded me about some famous quote by @hackingdata    
    
    
    Not sure what Deepak meant when saying Explore/Exploit was introduced by Yahoo in Academia in 2008 #cikm2013 - its practical application?    
    
    
    .@LinkedInEng uses ADMM for large-scale logistic regression + Thompson Sampling for explore/exploit - Deepak Agarwal #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@n0mad_0 A similar talk where Deepak explained some of LinkedIn's approaches to advertising http://soihub.org/group/26/hawaii-2-linkedin.pptx … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Creepy. Today I sent a gmail asking about mortgages. Next thing I know, unrelated mortgage agent asks to connect on LinkedIn. Coincidence?    
    
    
    Interesting talk by the yandex guys: "Personalization of Web-search Using Short-term Browsing Context" #cikm2013    
    
    
    Funny to meet random people at #cikm2013 who thank me for tweeting :-)    
    
    
    Interesting paper that unfortunately I missed "Nonparametric Bayesian Multitask Collaborative Filtering" http://www.researchgate.net/publication/256797062_Nonparametric_Bayesian_Multitask_Collaborative_Filtering … #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@AndrewYNg "Education for Everyone" @coursera #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/WwfERFGlNa    
    
    
    Now Jeff Hawkins (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeff_Hawkins …) on Streaming Online Learning. Impressive lineup in the #cikm2013 industry sessions.    
    
    
    Jeff Hawkins on building systems that mimic how our brain works (i.e. the "memory-prediction" framework http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Memory-prediction_framework …)    
    
    
    Hawkins on "Sparse Distributed Representations" http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sparse_distributed_memory … - fascinating #cikm2013    
    
    
    Kevin Murphy on Google building a probabilistic knowledge graph. Funny he's not in when I search for him #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/ArJNy0D4u1    
    
    
    "U.S. Plans Global Network of Free Online Courses" #NYT http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/01/education/us-plans-global-network-of-free-online-courses.html … - I don't think @AndrewYNg mentioned anything in #cikm2013    
    
    
    Carlos Guestrin speaking about distributed #machinelearning with @GraphLabAPI at #cikm2013. Similar slides here http://auai.org/uai2013/prints/tutorial_carlos.pdf …    
    
    
    Kudos to Carlos Guestrin for doing a real demo during his keynote @GraphLabAPI #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@jure Referencing Dan Ariely's quote on Big Data and teenage sex https://m.facebook.com/dan.ariely/posts/904383595868 … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Alon Havely: "I noticed this audience knows how to tweet so I will try to keep my ideas to <140 chars" #cikm2013    
    
    
    My 14 y.o. son would agree MT @Slate: We were wrong about Facebook and teens. That 13-year-old blogger was right: http://slate.me/16Qfiss     
    
    
    My talk at #cikm2013 in 10 minutes    
    
    
    Sick. Apple, MSFT should be ashamed RT @igrigorik: this patent stuff is bullshit: http://bit.ly/17wnfZM  - I'm losing faith in humanity.    
    
    
    @ctrattner You're welcome! Nice meeting you.    
    
    
    Nice piece MT @gigaom CYMI: The Gigaom guide to deep learning: Who’s doing it, and why it matters: http://ow.ly/qpTRr  #machinelearning    
    
    
    @AmericanAir Waited 30 minutes on a phone call just to hear that the ticket I have does not allow changes! Even if I am willing to pay more!    
    
    
    Sad RT @allthingsd: IBM Sues Twitter For Patent Infringement Ahead of IPO -by @MikeIsaac http://dthin.gs/18SEK0e     
    
    
    "Netflix Acquires Streaming Rights to a Highly Praised Documentary" #NYT http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/05/business/media/netflix-acquires-streaming-rights-to-highly-praised-documentary.html?partner=yahoofinance&_r=0 …    
    
    
    "Scryer: Netflix’s Predictive Auto Scaling Engine" http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/11/scryer-netflixs-predictive-auto-scaling.html?m=1 … - More magic from @NetflixOSS    
    
    
    @ocelma De res ;-)    
    
    
    "Disney and Netflix in Deal for Series Based on Marvel Characters" @nytimes http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/08/business/media/disney-and-netflix-in-deal-for-series-based-on-marvel-characters.html?hpw&rref=television&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Very interesting agenda for the first #spark summit in SF December 2 http://spark-summit.org/agenda/     
    
    
    Looking forward to the #QconSF "Applied Machine Learning and Data Science" track on Tuesday http://qconsf.com/track/applied-machine-learning-and-data-science … See you there!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Now @josh_wills on Cloudera's approach to building a machine learning infrastructure #qconsf    
    
    
    .@josh_wills should have attended my earlier #qconsf talk to update his Netflix queue example (more in this post http://techblog.netflix.com/2012/04/netflix-recommendations-beyond-5-stars.html …)    
    
    
    Cloudera's Open Source framework for building and serving machine learning models:  https://github.com/cloudera/oryx  #qconsf    
    
    
    Also from @cloudera : Gertrude, an open-source AB test experimentation framework https://github.com/cloudera/gertrude …    
    
    
    The power of algos! RT @FastCompany: How An Algorithm Is Going To Bring Music To The Deaf http://f-st.co/xVEk3dq     
    
    
    Yay! RT @netflix: Netflix members watch over a billion hours a month. Now it looks a billion times better: http://blog.netflix.com/2013/11/netflix-on-tv-gets-major-makeover.html …    
    
    
    Nice to meet two Spaniards from @plasticscm at #qconsf tonight. Bleeding edge software technology from Valladolid! http://www.plasticscm.com/     
    
    
    @pankaj @hnautiyal @dtunkelang ~75%    
    
    
    Agenda is out for @MLconf on Friday: http://www.mlconf.com/mlconf-2013/mlconf-2013-agenda/ … - Looking forward to seeing you there at 9 AM!    
    
    
    Amazon #Kinesis: A new Amazon Web Service for "real-time processing of streaming data at massive scale": http://aws.amazon.com/kinesis/     
    
    
    Ready for @MLconf pic.twitter.com/XXln2VSjDV    
    
    
    @RobertoGluck Thanks!    
    
    
    #Graphbuilder is an open source package from Intel that allows to construct large-scale graphs using Hadoop Pig https://01.org/graphbuilder     
    
    
    No #machinelearning conference today can call itself such unless there is a Deep Learning talk #mlconf13 pic.twitter.com/qx8j5PCkA0    
    
    
    Quoc Le talking about large-scale ANN using Distbelief model and data parallelism #mlconf13 pic.twitter.com/WxhGASTrha    
    
    
    .@nancast @noowitmags Deep Learning *is* as traditional as machine learning gets ;-)    
    
    
    Btw, talks at #mlconf13 are being live streamed at http://www.ustream.tv/channel/mlconf?rmalang=en_US …    
    
    
    .@GraphLabAPI Notebook offers a way to access the powerful Graphlab engine via a simple Python API: https://beta.graphlab.com/examples/An%20Introduction%20To%20GraphLab%20Notebook.html …    
    
    
    Very interesting talk on randomized regression by Mahoney from Stanford. Slides available here: http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/mmahoney/talks/mahoney-graphlab13.pdf … #mlconf13    
    
    
    LSRN: a parallel iterative least squares solver that is based on random normal projection http://www.stanford.edu/group/SOL/software/lsrn.html … #mlconf13    
    
    
    Josh Patterson now talking about Metronome "a suite of parallel iterative algorithms that run natively on YARN" https://github.com/jpatanooga/Metronome …    
    
    
    "Carnegie Mellon Researchers Break Speed Barrier In Solving Important Class of Linear Systems" http://www.cmu.edu/news/archive/2010/October/oct21_speedyalgorithm.shtml …    
    
    
    .@NetflixOSS Cloud Prize winners announced http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/11/netflix-open-source-software-cloud.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    Fascinating & weird story of academic vs. entrepreneurial interests RT @newsycombinator: Reaching for Silicon Valley http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/17/technology/reaching-for-silicon-valley.html?_r=0&pagewanted=all …    
    
    
    A practical Bayesian alternative to the p-value - interesting article in Nature  http://www.nature.com/news/weak-statistical-standards-implicated-in-scientific-irreproducibility-1.14131?WT.ec_id=NEWS-20131112 … via @ctrattner    
    
    
    My slides on Netflix #machinelearning algorithms from last Friday's #mlconf http://www.slideshare.net/xamat/mlconf     
    
    
    Dilbert on Engineering skills for life http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2013-11-19/ … - LOL    
    
    
    The new iPhone Twitter UI is so overloaded and annoying I really have to wonder how that won an AB test. Oh wait, maybe I *am* in an AB test    
    
    
        
    
    
    Nice! MT @jakevdp Great explanation of histograms & density estimation, using interactive javascript #IPython http://www.mglerner.com/blog/?p=28     
    
    
    According to @FastCompany, @SebastianThrun no longer believes in MOOCs. I think it is a commercial twist http://www.fastcompany.com/3021473/udacity-sebastian-thrun-uphill-climb …    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie's talk on tree ensembles at Netflix #mustwatch #machinelearning [VIDEO] http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-uPiqnjgVeA# …! via @hexadata    
    
    
    Fascinating Math... @WIRED article on recent advances on understanding prime numbers http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/11/prime/all/ …    
    
    
    Wonderful interactive video of Dylan's Like a Rolling Stone http://video.bobdylan.com/mobile.html     
    
    
    The @HuffingtonPost on the US Healthcare chart I shared earlier http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/11/22/american-health-care-terrible_n_4324967.html …    
    
    
    SAMOA, an open source platform for mining big data streams by @abifet http://zite.to/1jx3sJn     
    
    
    Cudatree 0.4: Random Forests for the GPU using PyCUDA http://zite.to/1hac6k6     
    
    
    Putting Spark to Use: Fast In-Memory Computing for Your Big Data Applications - at Cloudera's blog http://zite.to/1bV6iqO     
    
    
    Wait, why do some FB comments now have a reply? Did I miss something?    
    
    
    Project Halo: How Netflix designed its Xbox One app http://gigaom.com/2013/11/22/project-halo-how-netflix-designed-its-xbox-one-app/ …    
    
    
    "Beyond Locality-Sensitive Hashing" - MIT's CSAIL Theory Group theorizing over the practical LSH http://mittheory.wordpress.com/2013/11/22/beyond-lsh/ … via @purbon    
    
    
    From Spain! MT @kaggle: Kaggle has a new #1 ranked data scientist. Congrats José A. Guerrero: https://www.kaggle.com/users/5642/jos-a-guerrero …    
    
    
    "What to Watch on Netflix Based on Your Thanksgiving Turkey" via @mashable http://mashable.com/2013/11/26/netflix-thanksgiving-turkey-guide-watch-infographic/?apcid=52993504 … - Happy #Thanksgiving    
    
    
    The National and Bob's Burgers celebrating Thanksgiving http://insidetv.ew.com/2013/11/27/bobs-burgers-the-national-thanksgiving/ …    
    
    
    "Meet the gastronomic innovators helping Ferran Adrià disrupt the kitchen" http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2013-11/27/ferran-adria-and-disruptive-cooking … - #wired #Barcelona    
    
    
    Crazy... "Amazon Is Experimenting With Autonomous Flying Delivery Drones" http://techcrunch.com/2013/12/01/amazon-is-experimenting-with-autonomous-flying-delivery-drones/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    Ouch RT @slashdot: Telefonica To Shut Down VoIP Provider Jajah On January 31, 2014 http://bit.ly/1j9OifF     
    
    
    "Winamp shutting down after 15 years" http://mobile.theverge.com/2013/11/20/5126666/winamp-media-player-shutting-down-after-over-15-years … - Winamp, what memories...    
    
    
    A "classic" explore/exploit problem MT @freakonometrics: "Why Hacker News should use a Deterministic Algorithm" http://www.bayesianwitch.com/blog/2013/why_hn_shouldnt_use_randomized_algorithms.html …    
    
    
    @ocelma Has mirat que passa si afegeixes algo des de l'altre pais? El problema es gestionar catalegs independents i canviants.    
    
    
    Just heard Amazon will be showcasing the drones in #NIPS2013 this week. PR stunt or war on talent? #MachineLearning    
    
    
    For kids... RT @WIRED: Netflix Kicks the Binge-Watching Habit With New Original Show http://wrd.cm/1awLG3X     
    
    
    .@josh_wills in his Netflix talk yesterday pic.twitter.com/5SYvOB4LIg    
    
    
    How to Burst the "Filter Bubble" that Protects Us from Opposing Views http://www.technologyreview.com/view/522111/how-to-burst-the-filter-bubble-that-protects-us-from-opposing-views/ … #recsys #research #Barcelona via @marctorrens    
    
    
    Would it really be so bad for Wikipedia to include some ads and stop asking people for money every couple of months? Not sure.    
    
    
    Comments more interesting than post MT @freakonometrics: "Ordinary Least Squares is dead to me" http://shape-of-code.coding-guidelines.com/2013/11/28/ordinary-least-squares-is-dead-to-me/ …    
    
    
    Powered by @ocelma? MT @Techmeme: Sony's Gracenote powers music-matching service for Xbox Music http://venturebeat.com/2013/12/05/sonys-gracenote-powers-music-matching-service-for-xbox-music/ …    
    
    
    Running Weka on Hadoop - 3 part blogpost by core Weka developer Mark Hall http://markahall.blogspot.co.nz/2013/10/weka-and-hadoop-part-2.html … #machinelearning    
    
    
    "The Replication Myth: Shedding Light on One of Science's Little Secret" http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/guest-blog/2013/12/04/the-replication-myth-shedding-light-on-one-of-sciences-dirty-little-secrets/ …    
    
    
    Probably interesting RT @newsycombinator: BayesDB - a Bayesian database table http://probcomp.csail.mit.edu/bayesdb/     
    
    
    .@Bandsintown is for now the best app for tracking concerts I found. It connects to most apps and recs are good. Any other to try?    
    
    
    @martinvars I prefer Chromecast over Airplay though    
    
    
    MT @Techmeme: Binge-viewing was just the beginning. Netflix has a plan to rewire our entire culture http://www.newrepublic.com/article/115687/netflixs-war-mass-culture …    
    
    
    +1 RT @jtorras: I hate printers. Really, I do. http://thepattieproject.wordpress.com/2013/01/31/why-printers-are-the-worst-invention-known-to-man/ …    
    
    
    Barabasi in Nature again now on flavor MT @whereisdaz: Food pairing in different cuisines.
http://www.nature.com/srep/2011/111215/srep00196/full/srep00196.html … pic.twitter.com/aktBEJmvZk    
    
    
    My interview at #qconsf RT @InfoQ: Interview: Machine Learning Netflix Style with Xavier Amatriain http://bit.ly/1ks9z22     
    
    
    @namp that is InfoQ's style ;-)    
    
    
    Master in Data Science announced at the Barcelona Graduate School of Economics http://www.barcelonagse.eu/master-data-science.html … via @pauagullo #datascience #Barcelona    
    
    
    Hack? The power of algorithms and data RT @WIRED The Brilliant Hack That Brought Foursquare Back From the Dead http://wrd.cm/18xOyAU     
    
    
    Never thought I'd live to see NIPS described as an "Industry Conference" - @allthingsd on new Facebook AI lab http://allthingsd.com/20131209/facebook-steps-up-artificial-intelligence-efforts-with-new-research-lab/ …    
    
    
    Nice! Reminded me of *my* obscure C++ days ;-) RT @newsycombinator: Obscure C++ Features http://madebyevan.com/obscure-cpp-features/?viksra …    
    
    
    Amazed a CEO can put so much value on Glassdoor MT @dickc: this will be one of my favorite moments: http://cnet.co/18lkgUa     
    
    
    "Netflix knows you better than you know yourself" http://mashable.com/2013/12/11/netflix-data/?utm_cid=mash-com-fb-main-link … #recsys via @mashable    
    
    
    Awesome! Next let's try FC Barcelona or Death Metal RT @Slate: UK Supreme Court Rules Scientology Is a Religion http://slate.me/IQwKGZ     
    
    
    @srisatish Nice! Who's that?    
    
    
    @elsubliminal is that Santa Barbara?    
    
    
    #DataScience and #Recsys positions at Schibsted in #Barcelona http://schibsteddigital.com/data-analytics/     
    
    
    Netflix analyzes binge viewing patterns in the service http://m.us.wsj.com/articles/SB10001424052702303932504579254031017586624 …    
    
    
    Having contributed to @coursera's #recsys https://www.coursera.org/course/recsys  with a lecture, a bit annoyed there is no mention & can't access the video    
    
    
    @andland @coursera that's the point: you need to enroll to the course to know that it even exists cc @elehack    
    
    
    @chl @coursera I agree. Videos at least should be available.    
    
    
    @elehack @andland Thanks! I appreciate it. I would have even enrolled in the course to access the material had I known about it! :-)    
    
    
    @chl @elehack Thanks! Good to know :-)    
    
    
    @totopampin @ocelma @netflix Have you guys contacted Customer Service? I am told it is a tiny use case and we get no complaints.    
    
    
    "The key word in Data Science is not Data, it is Science" http://simplystatistics.org/2013/12/12/the-key-word-in-data-science-is-not-data-it-is-science/ … via @carlosdomingo    
    
    
    Interesting thoughts but they sound as elitist as what it criticizes IMO MT @samkaufman: Zuckerberg crashes NIPS. http://blog.explainmydata.com/2013/12/nips-and-zuckerberg-visit.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    "The Log:What every software engineer should know about real-time data's unifying abstraction" #mustread by @jaykreps http://engineering.linkedin.com/distributed-systems/log-what-every-software-engineer-should-know-about-real-time-datas-unifying …    
    
    
    A humanist approach to understanding software Rt @aquigley: The Algorithms of Our Lives http://zite.to/1dlyDoW     
    
    
    "Machine learning - Bayesian optimization and multi-armed bandits" [VIDEO] - Important stuff by @NandoDF http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vz3D36VXefI …    
    
    
    @mgershoff How does that matter at all when the whole point is to reduce the number of (costly) iterations ?    
    
    
    "Netflix Is the Breakthrough Brand of 2013" http://mashable.com/2013/12/19/netflix-2013/ … - Proud to be part of it!    
    
    
    3K followers... wow! Thanks!    
    
    
    :-( RT @freakonometrics: "How one publisher is stopping academics from sharing their research" http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-switch/wp/2013/12/19/how-one-publisher-is-stopping-academics-from-sharing-their-research/?0 …    
    
    
    @niket_kumar @coursera You're welcome. I still haven't seen it though. Hope it is good ;-)    
    
    
    @AntonioVolpon Thanks!    
    
    
    Of the many #machinelearning books I have on my desk only Barber's mentions LDA (Latent Dirichlet Allocation): hard to keep books up to date    
    
    
    @denisparra That's the point... 2003 is "new" for a book ;-)    
    
    
    @fulhack @rohanag Curious... when you say GBDT gave "best performance", is it measured offline or through AB testing?    
    
    
    @bmabey Yes! Saw that one hour ago and ordered from Amazon. Was missing in my collection ;-)    
    
    
    @fulhack @rohanag I have seen ALL kind of results in AB tests. That's the fun part :-) Besides I don't do WTF recs.    
    
    
    @ocelma @bmabey Yes. Actually in Hastie's is only used with the first meaning, that's what initially surprised me    
    
    
    "Stop treating engagement as science" - oh c'mon! RT @siah: "How Facebook’s Own Algorithms Are Killing Facebook" http://ow.ly/rt2Ty     
    
    
    Bayesian Machine Learning Guide http://metacademy.org/roadmaps/rgrosse/bayesian_machine_learning … via @mxlearn    
    
    
    The Walter Mitty ad and the"secret" Pandora algorithm http://mashable.com/2013/12/19/walter-mitty-movie-ad-pandora/?utm_cid=mash-com-fb-main-link … via @mashable    
    
    
    Btw, Walter Mitty's Pandora campaign might imply their algo is based on Music Genome, but it's a hybrid with lots of collaborative filtering    
    
    
    Can Machine Learning Fix a Broken Patent System? http://zite.to/1cmJD93     
    
    
    NIPSplosion 2013 - NIPS overview by Paul Mineiro http://zite.to/1jvkLjm     
    
    
    Christmas present to self pic.twitter.com/q5gQleKtY4    
    
    
    "We're up all night to get DATA" - Daft Punk parody http://blogs.scientificamerican.com/video-of-the-week/2013/11/13/were-up-all-night-to-get-data-the-next-great-science-parody/ … via @neal_lathia    
    
    
    @olgabot @twiecki @neal_lathia Nice! They do a great job!    
    
    
    Grand Canyon National Park Post Office with a special mailbox for Netflix DVDs! pic.twitter.com/8cDwuLRUT7    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @FastCompany: Messi, Ronaldo And Other Soccer Elites Form Team Earth To Battle Aliens In New Samsung Spot http://f-st.co/DYVHTPs     
    
    
    "How Netflix reverse engineered Hollywood" http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2014/01/how-netflix-reverse-engineered-hollywood/282679/ … - And someone reverse engineered our tagging system!    
    
    
    Interesting RT @jeremyphoward: Do Deep Nets Really Need to be Deep?
Lei Jimmy Ba, Rich Caurana http://arxiv.org/abs/1312.6184     
    
    
    Realized my homepage custom javascript is not working on some browsers (e.g. Chrome). Looking for simple html templates. Any pointer?    
    
    
    @pprasanna looks interesting, thanks!    
    
    
    Vaig néixer a Barcelona de pares no catalans i ara visc a Califòrnia #socunnoucatala    
    
    
    @daniel_julia Bon any!    
    
    
    Managed to completely rebuild my homepage (http://xavier.amatriain.net ) in a few hours with @twbootstrap (thanks for suggesting @pprasanna!)    
    
    
    @pprasanna Some things are a bit hacky, but happy with the result given how much time I invested ;-)    
    
    
    @jherskowitz we have a hack day coming up, I might propose it ;-)    
    
    
    #arresteddevelopment #season4 trailer http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?feature=youtu.be&v=vzVhPCMAxWQ&desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DvzVhPCMAxWQ%26feature%3Dyoutu.be …    
    
    
    "Most data isn’t “big,” and businesses are wasting money pretending it is" - a bit confusing, but interesting http://qz.com/81661/most-data-isnt-big-and-businesses-are-wasting-money-pretending-it-is/ …    
    
    
    Daughter: your music is weird and I don't like it. Me: I am glad I don't have the music taste of a 10 y.o. schoolgirl ;-)    
    
    
    @manas_somaiya you're welcome!    
    
    
    St. George Marathon lottery results are out, and we are in! Can't wait! http://www.stgeorgemarathon.com/     
    
    
    Q&A with @adrianco RT @mashable: This man has one of the coolest jobs at @Netflix - http://on.mash.to/10Sz1TL  #GetYourDreamJob    
    
    
    Good read RT @jongertner: My thoughts on Nate Silver—and Nate Silver's thoughts on Big Data—here: http://bit.ly/18FyWdJ .    
    
    
    Whenever I see a twitter profile stating "opinions are my own" I think "what a waste of characters".    
    
    
    @bmabey That's what I have heard. Can't wait!    
    
    
    @pankaj On the other hand, I usually find it is much easier for algo people to learn systems than viceversa.    
    
    
    Probably my favorite #netflix #hackday poster pic.twitter.com/lGTifuydqM    
    
    
    "Measuring User Engagement" - Excellent #www2013 tutorial http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/measuring-userengagement … via @denisparra    
    
    
    "From Amateurs to Connoisseurs..." - in the intersection of beer and algos http://i.stanford.edu/~julian/pdfs/www13.pdf … #www2013 #recsys via @shoha99 @denisparra    
    
    
    The Daily Startup: GraphLab Gathers $6.8M As Machine Learning Gains Steam http://zite.to/10zCfvv     
    
    
    Finished interview for a Wired article. Gotta love my job! /w @jorisevers    
    
    
    @octonion @cdixon they're not??? :-P    
    
    
    Did my half marathon PR today: 1:31 in the Capitola half!    
    
    
    Can you make a company out of buying others? I guess @marissamayer is determined to let us know.    
    
    
    Predicting Black Swans RT @RWW: Blinded By Big Data: It's The Models, Stupid by http://rww.to/18YEaBA     
    
    
    "In media Big Data is booming, but Big Results are lacking" (except for Netflix) http://allthingsd.com/20130520/in-media-big-data-is-booming-but-big-results-are-lacking/ …    
    
    
    "Is it time for a career switch?" - Not a plug for a job in my team, the title of a linkedin #www2013 #recsys [PAPER] http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1377.pdf …    
    
    
    "Online Controlled Experiments at Large Scale" [PAPER] - A/B Testing lessons from Bing by at #sigkdd2013 http://www.exp-platform.com/Pages/ControlledExperimentsAtLargeScale.aspx …    
    
    
    Two more AB test wins, two more algorithmic improvements on their way to improve Netflix member experience. Congrats to the team!    
    
    
    Concurrent Releases Pattern, a Machine Learning DSL for Hadoop http://zite.to/11dEaMn     
    
    
    Google has started a new lab to work on Quantum Machine Learning algorithms http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/05/launching-quantum-artificial.html …    
    
    
    UEFA Champions League tweeter data visualization (great to see Munich did not beat Barcelona so clearly on this) https://uclfinal.twitter.com/     
    
    
    Which proves writing an abstract is too easy MR @yueshi_nl: "We have received 1211 abstract submissions for full papers" #cikm2013    
    
    
    Celebrating #ArrestedDevelopment launch pic.twitter.com/kJU0ZsDuWN    
    
    
    "Timespent Based Models for Predicting User Retention" - Interesting #www2013 paper by @_5K et al. at Stumbleupon http://www2013.org/proceedings/p331.pdf …    
    
    
    "Do Social Explanations Work? Studying and Modeling the Effects of Social Explanations in #recsys" #www2013 http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1133.pdf …    
    
    
    "When Relevance is not Enough: Promoting Diversity & Freshness in Personalized Question #recsys" #www2013 http://www2013.org/proceedings/p1249.pdf …    
    
    
    Really amazed at how many #recsys papers there were at #www2013 this year. All available online: http://www2013.org/papers/proceedings.htm …    
    
    
    "Deep Learning of Representations: Looking Forward"  - Bengio on the promises and challenges of #deeplearning http://arxiv.org/pdf/1305.0445.pdf …    
    
    
    @xamat: List of #recsys related #www2013 papers in the recsys wiki http://recsyswiki.com/wiki/WWW_2013  via @abellogin    
    
    
    @_krisjack agree ;-)    
    
    
    " Your Browsing Behavior for a Big Mac: Economics of Personal Information Online" #www2013 by @elsubliminal et al http://www2013.org/proceedings/p189.pdf …    
    
    
    There is always money... pic.twitter.com/MsVN5fDdjh    
    
    
    Deep Learning Comes of Age http://zite.to/12328vj  at ACM Communications    
    
    
    Attending a talk on @hexadata by @srisatish    
    
    
    @DataJunkie @hexadata @srisatish Private event at Netflix. But, I am sure they can come pay you a visit ;-)    
    
    
    @DataJunkie @hexadata @srisatish Oh no, we got a much more personalized version ;-)    
    
    
    "The dictatorship of data" - good read http://www.technologyreview.com/news/514591/the-dictatorship-of-data/ … via @ravenben    
    
    
    "Machine Learning for Humans: kNN" http://www.jiaaro.com/KNN-for-humans/?utm_source=feedly …    
    
    
    Sumo bot wrestling in #hackPaloAlto pic.twitter.com/IBqZy3TEgT    
    
    
    @pacoid Thanks for the tip. It was great!    
    
    
    @pacoid I think my kids enjoyed the Tech Shop stuff a lot.    
    
    
    New @kaggle challenge: predict Amazon's employee's access rights: https://www.kaggle.com/c/amazon-employee-access-challenge … (at Netflix it would be easy: everyone everything)    
    
    
    What? Twitter no longer uses the whale?    
    
    
    Talk by @aficionado on @bigmlcom in 30 minutes. See you there http://www.sfbayacm.org/event/save-date-topic-tbd-6 …    
    
    
    @aficionado @bigmlcom @jaotwits I tant!    
    
    
    I am attending the "Analytics at Webscale" workshop at Facebook on Thursday http://analyticswebscale.splashthat.com/  - Ping me if you are going    
    
    
    Amazing line-up! Atoms for Peace, Beck, Animal Collective... Wish I could go
  http://www.treasureislandfestival.com/2013/     
    
    
    Women in Cloud meetup at Netflix on Thursday. If you are a woman in technology and are interested in cloud, signup http://womenincloud.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    First talk in the Webscale Analytics workshop: @squarecog on Twitter's infrastructure.    
    
    
    .@squarecog describing Parquet, a columnar format for Hadoop http://parquet.io/     
    
    
    Twitter's Data Access Layer is built on HCatalog @squarecog http://incubator.apache.org/hcatalog  pic.twitter.com/YNtUTRFMvl    
    
    
    Summingbird enables mapreduce-style workflow on Hadoop (batch processing), Storm (realtime processing) or both http://lanyrd.com/2013/lambda-jam/scghxb/ …    
    
    
    Interesting discussion on Mesos vs. YARN by @jaykreps at quora http://www.quora.com/How-does-YARN-compare-to-Mesos …    
    
    
    According to @squarecog Twiter has experimented with Spark, but has not managed to make it work in production http://spark-project.org/     
    
    
    Now @krishnagade talking about Twitter Storm    
    
    
    Btw, all my previous tweets should have been tagged with #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey http://analyticswebscale.splashthat.com/     
    
    
    Twitter's Storm topology for scoring and ranking tweets by @krishnagade pic.twitter.com/L5k8BStwbr    
    
    
    Now @junrao talking about Kafka and Espresso (a timeline consistent no-SQL data base http://data.linkedin.com/projects/espresso …) #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    And @sam_shah now talking about using Azkaban for workflow management #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @bigdatasci Indeed. Are you?    
    
    
    LinkedIn is also using Apache Giraph for iterative graph processing http://giraph.apache.org/  #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    @bigdatasci Easy. Look for an Orange #ArrestedDevelopment T-Shirt.    
    
    
    Btw, very related to many of the talks today at #AnalyticsWebscale, my previous post on Netflix #recsys architecture http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/03/system-architectures-for.html …    
    
    
    Ravi Murthy from Facebook: the 600 TB/day we ingest will yield most of our architectures useless soon pic.twitter.com/OSAeHEGZrl    
    
    
    "A good day is when I can run 6 Hive queries" - A Facebook Data Scientist #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Facebook's solution to query inefficiency in Hive is called Presto. Looking forward to it being open sourced in the fall #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    According to Avery Ching, one of the main motivations for Giraph was to improve Facebook Recommendations #recsys #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Talking about Giraph, it will be great to see all graph computation frameworks side by side at the Graphlab workshop http://graphlab.org/graphlab-workshop-2013/ …    
    
    
    Facebook ran Page Rank on user graph with a trillion edges on 200 machines with Giraph in less than 6 minutes/iteration! #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    Twitter Summingbird poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/4oRnCylAuZ    
    
    
    Scuba at Facebook poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/zRrZWJIbVo    
    
    
    Twitter's Data Access Layer poster #AnalyticsWebScale pic.twitter.com/HWp4vrICLf    
    
    
    And @squarecog and his Parquet poster pic.twitter.com/HGu27sFOAr    
    
    
    "Improving options for unlocking your graph data" #graphlab #giraph #pregel #cassavary #neo4j ... http://strata.oreilly.com/2013/05/improving-options-for-unlocking-your-graph-data.html …    
    
    
    "Facebook unveils Presto engine for querying 250 PB data warehouse" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/06/facebook-unveils-presto-engine-for-querying-250-pb-data-warehouse/ … via @gigaom #AnalyticsWebScale    
    
    
    New blog post: "Tools for Data Processing @ Webscale" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/06/tools-for-data-processing-webscale.html … #AnalyticsWebscale #storm #kafka #scuba #giraph #graphlab ...    
    
    
    Regardless of your opinion, a #mustwatch interview with Edward Snowden #nsafiles http://m.guardiannews.com/world/2013/jun/09/nsa-whistleblower-edward-snowden-why …    
    
    
    "Why you can't dislike something on Facebook?" - @benfrederickson from @zite on rating scales for #recsys    
    
    
    New blog post: "Tools for Data Processing @ Webscale" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/06/tools-for-data-processing-webscale.html … (In case you missed it over the weekend)    
    
    
    Deep Learning for NLP (without Magic) Tutorial by  Socher & Manning http://zite.to/14NaHoM     
    
    
    "Announcing Zuul: Edge Service in the Cloud" http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/announcing-zuul-edge-service-in-cloud.html …    
    
    
    "New from Netflix: Open-sourced gatekeeper to improve the delivery of web services" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/12/new-from-netflix-open-sourced-gatekeeper-to-deliver-web-services-better/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    @danielequercia @rodulforg @bdigital Yes, I even got a picture to prove it ;-) pic.twitter.com/jE3dm48XRu    
    
    
    "How Netflix deploys code" - blogpost about @jedberg's #qconnewyork talk http://www.infoq.com/news/2013/06/netflix …    
    
    
    "A real-time bonanza: Facebook’s Wormhole and Yahoo’s streaming Hadoop" http://gigaom.com/2013/06/14/a-real-time-bonanza-facebooks-wormhole-and-yahoos-streaming-hadoop/ …    
    
    
    When you are in a small meeting and two people are wearing @xkcd T-shirts, you know you are working in the right place ;-)    
    
    
    Mixed feelings about my 3:35 in the #sfmarathon. Great first half, but did not finish that well    
    
    
    @jimjansen Thanks!    
    
    
    @rusmeshenberg True ;-)    
    
    
    @atl Thanks!    
    
    
    Twitter's #recsys RT @dickc: the @magicrecs account is a product of some great work by the team here. Follow it!    
    
    
    The @MagicRecs project would be so much better if Twitter had invested just a little in improving DMs    
    
    
    "Announcing Ice: Cloud Spend and Usage Analytics" be @NetflixOSS http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/announcing-ice-cloud-spend-and-usage.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    "Apple and Netflix dominate online video"  http://bits.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/06/19/apple-and-netflix-dominate-online-video/?partner=yahoofinance …    
    
    
    @mdkail I think 41 is not correct.    
    
    
    "Neural networks, Google and cats" http://zite.to/1av1Aze  - Huge Deep Belief Networks running on a handful of GPUs    
    
    
    Improving Photo Search: A Step Across the Semantic Gap | Google Research Blog http://zite.to/12WWMCf     
    
    
    #sfmarathon finisher photo pic.twitter.com/0CngXGxGQR    
    
    
    .@NetflixOSS s01E03 meetup - Learn all about awesome Netflix OS projects first hand: http://www.meetup.com/Netflix-Open-Source-Platform/events/112697702/ …    
    
    
    "Netflix’s decision to renew Hemlock Grove shows its algorithms are working" http://paidcontent.org/2013/06/20/netflixs-decision-to-renew-hemlock-grove-shows-its-algorithms-are-working/ …    
    
    
    @yargnad Which of the two requires proprietary software?    
    
    
    @yargnad Sure, but you don't need an Apple TV to play iTunes content    
    
    
    "Genie is out of the bottle!" - Presenting @NetflixOSS's Hadoop job and resource management tool for the cloud http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/genie-is-out-of-bottle.html …    
    
    
    @badshah79 Thanks! :-)    
    
    
    "Sparse, Deep, and Random" - notes from #icml2013 by @PaulMineiro http://www.machinedlearnings.com/2013/06/icml-2013-sparse-deep-and-random.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&m=1 …    
    
    
    @pedronavf :-)    
    
    
    I will be giving a keynote a the #bigmine2013 workshop at #kdd2013 http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/  - hope to see you there!    
    
    
    @ocelma Si, Chicago. 11 d'Agost.    
    
    
    Very interesting talk at Netflix today on the Future of the Internet and Computers by @docjamesw    
    
    
    @pankaj Congrats! Didn't know you were running too.    
    
    
    Akka vs Storm http://prsm.tc/ykRPj2     
    
    
    @pankaj Next full marathon is St George. But will be running some local halves for sure before that.    
    
    
    @pankaj I did. 3:35. Enjoyed every bit of the first half (did it in 1:41), but really struggled at the end    
    
    
    Still trying to wrap my head around Wendy Davis' story today http://www.npr.org/blogs/thetwo-way/2013/06/26/195723770/texas-lawmakers-11-hour-filibuster-ended-on-a-technicality … - sad for Texas    
    
    
    "Pandora and Royalties" http://blog.pandora.com/2013/06/26/pandora-and-royalties/ … - Important read if, as opposed to RIAA, you care about music and Internet    
    
    
    At Netflix we love movies and TV shows... but also soccer ;-) (watching Spain-Italy over lunch) pic.twitter.com/0XlJ3WvCFc    
    
    
    eHarmony Refines the Science of Love : Hadoop + Machine Learning http://zite.to/154rasm     
    
    
    "The Philosophy of Netflix: Its Chief Content Officer Champions Storytelling" http://m.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/06/the-philosophy-of-netflix-its-chief-content-officer-champions-storytelling/277354/ …    
    
    
    Will be missing #Graphlab2013 today, but will be following your tweets ;-)    
    
    
    A better title would be "A ver basic intro to #recsys" RT @olinhyde: The State of Recommender Technology: http://bit.ly/12bZBrR     
    
    
    ICML 2013 Reading List by @t3kcit http://zite.to/15dONPg     
    
    
    Terrible news: John Riedl, friend and #recsys pioneer died https://plus.google.com/app/basic/stream/z13gglbylz3sxrgiz04cexvgcmyrebgaopg0k … RIP John, your research will live on forever    
    
    
    4th of July, Catalan style pic.twitter.com/ZlUy1UlIAt    
    
    
    Sanfermines in San Francisco on Sunday: http://somastreatfoodpark.com/event/running-of-the-bulls-party/ …    
    
    
    An update on my tweet yesterday on John Riedl. Although he is losing his battle agains cancer, he is still alive http://www.caringbridge.org/visit/windsurferjohn …    
    
    
    A classical (1983) & not-very-technical description of the bootstrap method http://statistics.stanford.edu/~ckirby/techreports/BIO/BIO%2083.pdf … via @DEAGiles - http://davegiles.blogspot.it/     
    
    
    Did @thomyorke's Atoms for Peace album Amok just disappear from @Spotify? I swear it was there on Friday! wtf?    
    
    
    @ogrisel @thomyorke @Spotify That sucks :-(    
    
    
    "Finding Harmony with Big Data" - @techreview's feature article on @echonest's music technology http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2013/echo-nest-harmony-with-big-data-0710.html …    
    
    
    Quora looks to the crowd to solve machine learning problems http://zite.to/15gcGn4  #machinelearning    
    
    
    "You're Doing It Wrong!"-If you're writing data processing code disregarding software engineering practices  http://zite.to/18PIO6C     
    
    
    Graphical Causal Models http://zite.to/12tz9dp     
    
    
    An interesting reading list on Clustering http://zite.to/12tzhJT     
    
    
    Netflix HQ turned into a nice prison to celebrate launch of #OrangeIsTheNewBlack pic.twitter.com/ttpQFNhijM    
    
    
    #OrangeIsTheNewBlack #SoapOnARope pic.twitter.com/TxPmNjUone    
    
    
    @elehack ouch... yes... damn autocomplete :-)    
    
    
    Looking forward to upcoming @coursera course "Intro to Recommender Systems" by @jkonstan and @elehack https://www.coursera.org/course/recsys  #recsys    
    
    
    (Thanks @elehack for pointing out error in my previous tweet on #recsys @coursera course)    
    
    
    @mjcavaretta Thanks :-)    
    
    
    Interesting read RT @krishnagade: Why Microsoft’s reorganization is a bad idea @stratechery http://stratechery.com/2013/why-microsofts-reorganization-is-a-bad-idea/ …    
    
    
    First Workshop on Large-Scale Recommender Systems this year at #recsys2013 http://graphlab.org/lsrs2013/     
    
    
    @mortardata Thanks!    
    
    
    Barça's coach Tito steps down because of his illness http://m.guardian.co.uk/football/2013/jul/19/barcelona-press-conference-tito-vilanova … #AnimsTiTo    
    
    
    Uk government supports Turing's pardon  http://m.guardian.co.uk/uk-news/2013/jul/19/enigma-codebreaker-alan-turing-posthumous-pardon … - Not sure if a pardon feels right at this point really    
    
    
    "TV Foresees Its Future. Netflix Is There." - Great NYT piece http://www.nytimes.com/2013/07/22/business/media/tv-foresees-its-future-netflix-is-there.html?partner=yahoofinance&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Using Less Data http://zite.to/18rukHj  - sub-sampling classifiers at #icml2013    
    
    
    New blogpost: "Recommendations as Personalized Learning to Rank" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com.es/2013/07/recommendations-as-personalized.html … #recsys #machinelearning    
    
    
    Amazon just sent me an email recommending me s book I wrote a chapter for. Maybe they do know I never got a copy ;-) #recsys #fail?    
    
    
    @statpumpkin It was :-)    
    
    
    Yahoo Labs #Barcelona is looking for a Data-oriented Research Engineer http://comunicacio.barcelonamedia.org/web/RRHH/Job_ref_Yahoo_FBM_BM0029.pdf … @danielequercia can give you more details    
    
    
    Excited about the talk I will be giving tomorrow at @IBMResearch Almaden in the "Accelerated Discovery Forum" series at 10 am.    
    
    
    "Unhappy Truckers and Other Algorithmic Problems" - @tomvanderbilt on traveling salesmen & other transportation algos http://nautil.us/issue/3/in-transit/unhappy-truckers-and-other-algorithmic-problems …    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @_rnbrewer: Great talk by Netflix director, @xamat, at @IBMResearch #Almaden today    
    
    
    Netflix rolls out individual user profiles http://blog.netflix.com/2013/08/make-netflix-your-own-with-profiles.html …    
    
    
    One of the biggest unsolved questions for mankind: what to do with the thousands of pictures I have taken during vacation...    
    
    
    @gy4nt Thanks!    
    
    
    In case you missed my last blog post "Recommendations as Personalized Learning to Rank" http://technocalifornia.blogspot.com/2013/07/recommendations-as-personalized.html …    
    
    
    "Amazon founder says he clicked on Washington Post by mistake" http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/borowitzreport/2013/08/amazon-founder-says-he-clicked-on-washington-post-by-mistake.html … - LOL    
    
    
    Carlos and me talking about @netflix recommendations @WIRED http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/08/qq_netflix-algorithm/ … #recsys via @tomvanderbilt    
    
    
    @JacobMargolis Why don't you send me some details on what you have in mind to xavier at netflix dot com    
    
    
    @davidbs Gracias compi!    
    
    
    "The Algorithm That Tells Netflix Which Movies You Really Want to Watch" http://gizmodo.com/the-algorithm-that-tells-netflix-which-movies-you-reall-1054431105?utm_campaign=socialflow_gizmodo_twitter&utm_source=gizmodo_twitter&utm_medium=socialflow … @Gizmodo's take on the Wired article    
    
    
    Nice compilation :-) MT @TimeOutNewYork 15h  A dead shark on the subway, 200-year-old liquor, and Netflix algorithm http://tmout.us/nJqoh     
    
    
    @squarecog That's the whole point: you can build a successful product on a UI that "only" uses recommendations ;-)    
    
    
    @squarecog You can still do that if you go to the Genre Galleries on the web: you can browse sub-genres, sort.... What do you miss?    
    
    
    "Netflix knows you've been lying about all those foreign films and documentaries you say you like" http://www.avclub.com/articles/netflix-knows-youve-been-lying-about-all-those-for,101336/ …    
    
    
    "How Netflix Helps You Decide What to Watch" http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/news/how-netflix-helps-you-decide-601956 …    
    
    
    Hope to see many of you at my invited talk at the @BigDataMining1 workshop at #KDD2013 on Sunday: http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/#amatriain …    
    
    
    @philosophygeek Don't look like Piquillo to me: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Piquillo_pepper … Are you sure they are?    
    
    
    Finished recording my session for the #recsys coursera course with @elehack. Can't wait until it's available! https://www.coursera.org/course/recsys     
    
    
    "Post water-cooler TV" @nytimes via @netflix http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/11/arts/television/how-to-make-a-tv-drama-in-the-twitter-age.html?hp&pagewanted=all&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Heading to Chicago, plane full of #kdd2013 geeks ;-)    
    
    
    @BigDataAnalysis Probably sharing plane ;-)    
    
    
    Any runners in #kdd2013 up for a morning run in Chicago during the conference days?    
    
    
    Good explanation of an important issue MT @DEAGiles: Large and Small Regression Coefficients http://davegiles.blogspot.com/2013/08/large-and-small-regression-coefficients.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    #kdd2013 starting now! Two-sided badge #win. No power outlets in workshop rooms + hearing everything from the neighboring rooms... #fail    
    
    
    @FrancescoBonchi Ricardo told me you would be here... hope we can meet!    
    
    
    In 5 minutes, my talk on Netflix Big Data & Recommendations in the @BigDataMining1 workshop #kdd2013    
    
    
    Actually my talk at @BigDataMining1 is at 10:30 #kdd2013    
    
    
    @kdnuggets Thanks! We should chat. I am sure we will run into each other during the conference.    
    
    
    #kdd2013 RT @smolix: Slides for the KDD tutorial are at https://mega.co.nz/#!ShwEQRKa!SvWgyybALxR7wo5jolelxQQSO1BJyGduK_mnLJgd3_Q … and https://mega.co.nz/#!KoQT3RTQ!eHnOi3HA9nr5u-MHAbeyCkCi_g0yT9-awKe4Yix8PdU …    
    
    
    Context on my previous tweet: slides are Alex Smola & Amr Ahmed's #kdd2013 tutorial "Bayesian Nonparametrics and Mixed Membership Models"    
    
    
    Winners of this years #kddcup (both tracks) are all students from a class in the Taiwan National University #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/LwRLfEclRS    
    
    
    #kddcup winning team used ensemble of GBDT, Random Forests & LambdaMart... and lots of feature engineering http://www.cwi.ugent.be/kddcup2013/track1place1.pdf … #kdd2013    
    
    
    Raghu Ramakrishnan (@raghurwi ) talking about "the digital shoebox" in his "beyond map reduce" #kdd2013 keynote pic.twitter.com/V5wbxZ3QMq    
    
    
    Those of you not in #kdd2013 wondering about @raghurwi's digital shoebox can start in these slides http://research.microsoft.com/en-us/events/fs2013/raghu-ramakrishnan_bigdataplatforms.pdf … #yarn #reef    
    
    
    New Microsoft #REEF framework will be open source and will be presented in @strataconf in October http://strataconf.com/stratany2013/public/schedule/detail/30895 … #kdd2013    
    
    
    Raghu Ramakrishnan: "If you want to implement the next Mahout, contact me to build it on #REEF" #kdd2013    
    
    
    Wow! Rooms at #kdd2013 completely packed. Make my original idea of moving from session to session pretty hard :-(    
    
    
    #kdd2013 influencer graph MT @marc_smith: kdd2013 NodeXL SNA http://bit.ly/19dPMQA     
    
    
    A packed room is even more uncomfortable if the guy sitting next to you is constantly looking at the notes you are taking #kdd2013    
    
    
    Slides for my keynote yesterday at the @BigDataMining1 workshop are now online http://bigdata-mining.org/keynotes/#amatriain … #kdd2013    
    
    
    .@AndrewYNg's #kdd2013 keynote delivered via videoconferencing a la @coursera pic.twitter.com/JOUjgyPNM3    
    
    
    This is how the Deep Learning talk by @jeremyphoward looks. Either too many people or too little room #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/d4C2kbPuMl    
    
    
    .@gigaom reporting on today's #kdd2013 keynote by Raghu Ramakrishnan's http://gigaom.com/2013/08/12/microsoft-to-open-source-a-big-data-framework-called-reef/ … via @markusweimer    
    
    
    .@jeremyphoward getting to #deeplearning through the idea of avoiding overfitting with tree ensembles. But GBM/GBDT don't #kdd2013    
    
    
    @jeremyphoward I was standing in the last row. But was able to follow. Nice talk!    
    
    
    @juliaxgulia first name at Netflix dot com    
    
    
    Funny that I am getting far more twitter followers from attending #kdd2013 than from being featured at @wired http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/08/qq_netflix-algorithm/ …    
    
    
    #kdd2013 keynote today by Stephen Wright: great tutorial on optimization [SLIDES] http://pages.cs.wisc.edu/~swright/wright-kdd-2013.pdf …    
    
    
    Overbooked industry sessions at #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/veYAZ8JLbz    
    
    
    "Why California Can't Be Home to the Hyperloop"-An article saying that California is bad for business has to be BS http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/227807# !    
    
    
    @usabart I said it was BS!!    
    
    
    @usabart Btw, I also felt tricked by LinkedIn when it appeared in my feed    
    
    
    @dtunkelang @usabart no worries. It's good to read things you don't agree with... occasionally :-)    
    
    
    No visit to Chicago is complete without a proper Jazz/Blues concert #kdd2013 pic.twitter.com/2kDq1mG0Xx    
    
    
    +1 (well maybe XXth) MT @frankolken: Chicago Sheraton had neither useable wifi nor electrical power for #kdd2013.  Welcome to 19th century.    
    
    
    Hal Varian (Google's Chief Economist) remembering his UCB Professor times & explaining Kalman Filters, Spike & Slab Regression... #kdd2013    
    
    
    Nice to see Google's Chief Economist using R commands in a keynote (e.g. stl = Seasonal Decomposition of Time Series by Loess) #kdd2013    
    
    
    @cdubhland @twitter Not true... there are twitter people in the audience, not sure they'd want to argue though ;-)    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @rachelmetz 15h  this is like total aural nostalgia. museum of endangered sounds: http://savethesounds.info     
    
    
    Wait... so Google has very smart people working on using their data for economic forecasting. I wonder what they want that for ;-) #kdd2013    
    
    
    I have a proposal for next year's #kddcup: "Predicting audience for KDD sessions". Not hard & could help on deciding room sizes #kdd2013    
    
    
    Since @twitter does not allow for an easy partitioning of my feed into topics, I created @xamat_music for my twitter #music    
    
    
    @_amrahmed Thanks Amr... really appreciate it!    
    
    
    @pathak_s @twitter @Quora I think it's very easy to figure out topics users I follow belong to. You can then split feed according to source    
    
    
    @elversatile @Jetlore There is nothing in that URL except for a server welcome message. Is the system down?    
    
    
    @IgorBrigadir @twitter @xamat_music they could be an option if they also filtered listed people from my main feed.    
    
    
    @elversatile I just signed up. I will let you know. But, from what I read it looks more like @Zite or @Prismatic    
    
    
    @sscdotopen IBM?    
    
    
    @sscdotopen Yes, I know. But, you were there?    
    
    
    @sscdotopen Oh, didn't recognize you :-)    
    
    
    Good idea! RT @manas_somaiya: @xamat , @twitter needs to introduce @netflix style profiles.    
    
    
    Google researcher: "Why are you taking that picture? You could find the exact same one in Google Images" - You gotta love us geeks    
    
    
    .@AmericanAir I understand I have to pay for food in a 4 hour flight. What I don't understand is you run of food to sell!    
    
    
    "Google scientist Jeff Dean on how neural networks are improving everything Google does" http://zite.to/16aEf5R  via @zite    
    
    
    "Frontiers in Massive Data Analysis" - A free downloadable report from the National Academies committee http://www.nap.edu/catalog.php?record_id=18374 … #bigdata    
    
    
    Great to attend #kdd2013 this week. I am sure many of the attendees will be interested in this position in my team: http://jobs.netflix.com/jobsListing.html?id=NFX00370 …    
    
    
    "Demystifying Porn 2.0: A look into a major adult video streaming website" - A pretty interesting [PAPER] http://www.eecs.qmul.ac.uk/~steve/papers/IMC13.pdf … #imc2013    
    
    
    I should have added the previous paper is SFW ;-)    
    
    
    The New Yorker reporting on an #ijcai2013 paper by Levesque on why we are not building "true AI" http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/08/why-cant-my-computer-understand-me.html?mbid=social_retweet … via @mikiobraun    
    
    
    OMG! Shocked :-( RIP MT @HCIR_GeneG: Sad news:  Gene Golovchinsky passed away this Thursday.  It was very sudden. http://tinyurl.com/HCIRGene     
    
    
    "Expecting the unexpected from Jeff Bezos" - interesting portrait in NYT after his purchase of the Washington Post  http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/18/business/expecting-the-unexpected-from-jeff-bezos.html?pagewanted=all&_r=1& …    
    
    
    "We're on the cusp of deep learning for the masses, you can thank Google later" @gigaom - featuring @jeremyphoward http://gigaom.com/2013/08/16/were-on-the-cusp-of-deep-learning-for-the-masses-you-can-thank-google-later/ …    
    
    
    "Big Data Science from R" meetup by @hexadata http://www.meetup.com/H2Omeetup/events/132640822/?gj=wc1f_e&a=wc1f_gnl&rv=wc1f_e …    
    
    
    @emanuel_strauss Definitely! Why don't you connect to me on LinkedIn? Or send email to first_name at netflix dot com.    
    
    
    "The Antifragile Organization" @atseitlin in ACM Communications http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/8/166315-the-antifragile-organization/abstract … (open access version http://delivery.acm.org/10.1145/2500000/2499552/p20-tseitlin.pdf?ip=69.53.237.66&id=2499552&acc=OPEN&key=BF13D071DEA4D3F3B0AA4BA89B4BCA5B&CFID=355023284&CFTOKEN=43477826&__acm__=1377035650_d26c6371466e7ed01e0acd076b3aba13 …)    
    
    
    Featuring our algos MT @TechCrunch: Netflix Introduces 'My List,' A Personalized Instant Queue http://tcrn.ch/172istS     
    
    
    "Introducing My List From Netflix" at the Netflix blog: http://blog.netflix.com/2013/08/introducing-my-list-from-netflix.html?m=1 …    
    
    
    Great summary of the conference with awesome pics MT @dirkvandenpoel: Visual summary #KDD2013 feat.  @xamat and more http://bit.ly/175dtbF     
    
    
    @dirkvandenpoel Thanks for the reference!    
    
    
    "C++ and the culture of complexity" - a #mustread for those of us who consider C++ our mother tongue http://blog.greaterthanzero.com/post/58482859780/c-and-the-culture-of-complexity … via @siah    
    
    
    @elehack why? Do you prefer a piece of paper?    
    
    
    @elehack the only time I did it, the officer did not accept it as a valid ID ;-)    
    
    
    @elehack But, you don't need to hand it, only show it as you do in the airport    
    
    
    @JustinBasilico @freakonomics Seems interesting, but the server has been down all day    
    
    
    So the Simpson paradox is now called a giraffe? MT @kdnuggets: Beware of the "giraffes" in your data http://bit.ly/1dfn8CL  @gigaom    
    
    
    @mikiobraun It depends in what kind of job interviews you have in mind ;-)    
    
    
    "Men should wear a suit and a tie" - Seriously?? RT @mashable: How to Make a Good First Impression at a Job Interview http://on.mash.to/16yVmIV     
    
    
    .@kdnuggets To be clear, I am not against using the term "giraffe", but it would have been nice to cite the more formal name    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey Matt, you are at Google MV, right? I am giving a talk there tomorrow    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey great!    
    
    
    I am giving a tech talk tomorrow at Google HQ. Looking forward to seeing many Googlers there!    
    
    
    @mat_kelcey You did! We should catch up some time so i can give you a personalized version ;-)    
    
    
    Congrats! MT @denisparra  Finally I am a PhD. Thanks to the best mentors I could've had @peterpaws n @xamat , thanks also to whole committee    
    
    
    Great experience today interviewing Netflix members to understand how they use our personalization.    
    
    
    @PENGUINANA_ We are constantly surveying our members on different aspects of the service. We have a team focused on that    
    
    
    When will Twitter realize it needs a tweet ranking algorithm? MT @gigaom: Why Twitter’s new Conversations is a big http://wp.me/p10LZV-2S9P     
    
    
    @_amrahmed Sent you an email. Did you get it?    
    
    
    Watching @baracksdubs #thingsYouDoOnAWeekendWithATeenageKid    
    
    
    I bet they are not thinking on naming a Helsinki street after Elop any time soon    
    
    
    Amazing lineup for #cikm2013 industry track. Psyched to be included http://www.cikm2013.org/industry.php     
    
    
    "Streaming MapReduce with Summingbird" - @twitter announces new OSS http://prsm.tc/iePqSr     
    
    
    @xamat: Does the fact I really like @ifcportlandia make it very easy to profile me? (Glad season 3 is #NowOnNetflix )    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @alexk_z: Jumping in for @xamat and presenting a tutorial on #recsys tomorrow at @essir2013 in Granada http://www.ugr.es/~essir2013/     
    
    
    Cheering for @bholmes who is currently half way of the 100 miles of the #Wasatch100    
    
    
    #recsys RT @mashable: Airlines Are Trying to Get Personal With Your Data http://on.mash.to/15FoHYS     
    
    
    Tempted MT @runnersworld: Try this innovative breathing technique that will maximize your running http://ow.ly/oDN0l     
    
    
    Hosting a nice talk on MLbase, a distributed #machinelearning framework running on #spark and callable from #scala http://mlbase.org/     
    
    
    "Domesticating Pig with Lipstick" - @mortardata integrates @NetflixOSS's Pig visualization tool into Mortar http://blog.mortardata.com/post/60765120319/domesticating-pig-with-lipstick …    
    
    
    @izendejas It was an internal talk I hosted yesterday    
    
    
    "23 things that could only exist in Silicon Valley" http://www.buzzfeed.com/jessicamisener/23-things-that-could-only-exist-in-silicon-valley?s=mobile … via @carlosdomingo    
    
    
    "Q&A The Catalan Way Explained" - to understand a bit better what will happen in Catalonia today http://m.ara.cat/viacatalana/catalan-way-catalonia-independence_0_990501167.html …    
    
    
    .@twitter's trending topic algo failing: #SomEspanya is #TT in Catalonia when #ViaCatalana should http://topsy.com/analytics?q1=%23ViaCatalana%20&q2=%23SomEspanya&via=Topsy … via @sisquere    
    
    
    Will be speaking about #machinelearning and #recsys at #mlconf in SF on 11/15. Great lineup: http://www.mlconf.com/mlconf-2013/     
    
    
    SF ACM Chapter talk on Monday, controversial topic (with which I disagree): designing #recsys as advertising systems http://www.meetup.com/SF-Bay-ACM/events/139785862/?a=ea1_grp&rv=ea1&_af_eid=139785862&_af=event …    
    
    
    @geekycourtney I think you missed the year again ;-)    
    
    
    "Using Chef and Vagrant to Put Lipstick on a Pig"- @mortardata open sources tools to integrate Lipstick to Mortar http://blog.mortardata.com/post/61026715305/using-chef-and-vagrant-to-put-lipstick-on-a-pig …    
    
    
    @mortardata now with link... Thanks!    
    
    
    Twitter files for IPO http://allthingsd.com/20130912/twitter-files-for-ipo/# …! via @allthingsd    
    
    
    My friends at Voctrolabs will be presenting in Barcelona the first virtual concert featuring Bruno, Clara & Ona http://www.voctro-vocaloid.com/en/archives/871     
    
    
    My friend Paul is trying to become JATW's next Chief World Explorer. Please vote for him! http://www.bestjobaroundtheworld.com/submissions/view/15200 …    
    
    
    "A Focus on Efficiency" - a 70 page long white paper by Facebook, Ericsson, and Qualcomm on Data Centers, Apps... https://fbcdn-dragon-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash3/851560_196423357203561_929747697_n.pdf …    
    
    
    I will be presenting "Machine Learning & Recommender Systems at Netflix Scale" at @qconSF on November 12 http://qconsf.com/presentation/machine-learning-recommender-systems-netflix-scale …    
    
    
    Facebook's LibPhenom: an eventing framework for building high performance and high scalability systems in C http://facebook.github.io/libphenom/     
    
    
    Family bonding time with #GATV ... Sign of the times.    
    
    
    Dear recruiters, if you are trying to impress me by starting your message in Spanish, you should know "Hello" is "Hola", not "Ola" (sigh)    
    
    
    If you are interested in attending @mlconf in SF for  #machineLearning talks from interesting speakers, discount here http://ml1.eventbrite.com/?discount=xaviersdiscount …    
    
    
    Sometimes Google Scholar makes my day when an awesome new paper is citing me. Today: "RUMBATOR: A Flamenco Rumba Cover Generator" :-)    
    
    
    Interesting speakers in the Big Data Spain conference http://www.bigdataspain.org/  #BDSpain    
    
    
    I am looking for an engineering/research manager with strong ML background to help me lead the new AE team at Netflix http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00883 …    
    
    
    Agree, that's why working on it is awesome RT @anjalimullany: Video recommendation is still far from perfect: http://www.fastcompany.com/3017012/tech-forecast/youtube-is-winning-an-emmy-but-video-recommendation-still-has-a-long-way-to-go … #recsys    
    
    
    Lots of research went into this RT @TheOnion: New Netflix Gas Lets Users Inhale Multiple Seasons Of TV Shows http://onion.com/1amuFLK     
    
    
    Dear LinkedIn, your mobile app is a mess. Thank you.    
    
    
    Watching last episode tonight RT @andersoncooper: Has anyone else watched #TheFall on Netflix? I think it was originally on BBC. It's great!    
    
    
    Nothing like adding "deep" to make headlines MT @siah: Facebook 'deep learning’ neural networks to learn about you http://ow.ly/pbLK9     
    
    
    Want to hear Trevor Hastie talking about GBM's, learn about @hexadata, and @netflix? We're hosting an event 10/10 http://www.meetup.com/Silicon-Valley-Big-Data-Science/events/141495222/ …    
    
    
    "Big Data: Does Size Really Matter?" - at Wired http://www.wired.com/insights/2013/09/big-data-does-size-really-matter/ … - Is it me or this post is confusing and misleading?    
    
    
    Functional Programming and the Power of Math at XKCD RT @xkcdrss Functional http://xkcd.com/1270/     
    
    
    .@NetflixOSS #cloudprize nominations announced: http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/09/netflixoss-meetup-s1e4-cloud-prize.html …    
    
    
    Lots of coffee today. Have to connect remotely to give a talk @catosfera at 2 AM local time. Wish me luck ;-)    
    
    
    First time I think I get a paper version of the GPL with a piece of equipment. pic.twitter.com/uPGemBtPFq    
    
    
    @ocelma Si noi, ara surto cap a Netflix per connectar des d'allà ;-)    
    
    
    @Montsinya Gràcies!    
    
    
    @gcapdevila Gràcies!    
    
    
    @pcarriet Un plaer ;-)    
    
    
    2 AM, giving my talk for @catosfera at the Netflix theatre pic.twitter.com/QMtJSiP40M    
    
    
    @_andy_tea yes, but my talk has finished http://2013.catosfera.cat/     
    
    
    @_andy_tea and, it is in Catalan ;-)    
    
    
    Lesson 1 tonight: giving a talk where you don't see your audience is hard    
    
    
    Will try! MT @aquigley: as ridiculous as this sounds. I use photo of an audience on my screen when delivering remote or recording a talk.    
    
    
    Lesson 2: giving a talk it in a language you are not used to (even if that is your mother tongue) is really hard    
    
    
    Magic? MT @JDavidMorris: Topological Data Analysis (TDA), @Ayasdi machine learning w/o algorithms, queries or models. http://ow.ly/pj3R0     
    
    
    Wow! Was surprised by some twitter account with a huge number of followers. Turns most of them have no profile pic or followers.    
    
    
    I guess it would not be hard to put twitter follower buyers to shame with a simple algo. Is anyone doing it already?    
    
    
    @jamneuf Accounts might be completely legitimate, but not the followers. Thousands of russian-sounding names with 0 followers? Weird.    
    
    
    2:03:23... wow!    
    
    
    "How Netflix Uses Analytics To Select Movies, Create Content, and Make Multimillion Dollar Decisions" http://blog.kissmetrics.com/how-netflix-uses-analytics/ … - Nice recap!    
    
    
    St. George Marathon: 3:24. Super happy to beat my goal of 3:30.    
    
    
    Good read. With @spotify no matter what @thomyorke says RT @fulhack: How Spotify Engineered the New Music Economy: http://mashable.com/2013/10/06/spotify-music-economy/ …    
    
    
    "A Month in the Life of a Production News Recommender System" - [PAPER] by @alansaid et al. http://oai.cwi.nl/oai/asset/21477/21477A.pdf … #recsys    
    
    
    @jaume_albaiges oops ;-)    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie and Hexadata will be talking about distributed GBMs at Netflix on Thursday. Hope to see you there! http://www.meetup.com/Silicon-Valley-Big-Data-Science/events/141495222/ …    
    
    
    Will be missing #recsys2013 for the first time ever. But, @JustinBasilico and others will be representing Netflix    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie @netflix talking about trees pic.twitter.com/JsGE52lCYr    
    
    
    Trevor Hastie: "Boosting overfits less quickly, but, given enough noise, it still will"    
    
    
    Today I interviewed someone with PhD and 5+ years working on #machinelearning at Google who could not answer any of my ML questions, wow :-(    
    
    
    Ok, for those of you asking, example question: "What is Logistic Regression?"    
    
    
    @UltimateHurl what? How could anyone get that wrong?!    
    
    
    @notrockstar I think it was    
    
    
    Nice words ;-) RT @greglinden: New post up on Geeking with Greg, "I was wrong on Netflix" http://glinden.blogspot.com/2013/10/i-was-wrong-on-netflix.html …    
    
    
    @leifos @alansaid @jkonstan don't know what the context is, but that's a "stupid generalization" ;-) Recall is great in many scenarios    
    
    
    @philosophygeek they have awesome wines at a very reasonable price, how's the winery?    
    
    
    B.S., look at their job posts! MT @FastCompany: Screw Algorithms! Beats Uses Celebrity Curators To Show You New Music http://f-st.co/nLs4TSh     
    
    
    Everybody, including Beats, knows algorithms beat celebrities @FastCompany - only celebs are easier to get (look at their jobs site)    
    
    
    .@ocelma @FastCompany You mean like doing some sort if expert-based collaborative filtering? I think I know a guy who wrote some papers ;-)    
    
    
    @alansaid @dtunkelang @mitultiwari A few people from Netflix like @JustinBasilico also!    
    
    
    @danielmintz I think most of us have figured out that "plays" are more valuable than ratings. Most music #recsys don't use ratings AFAIK    
    
    
    @danielequercia @FastCompany @johnpaul They sure can be combined! But if you had to choose one, which one would you choose?    
    
    
    @xamat: Are you interested in a phone that lasts and you don't throw away?http://phonebloks.com  - cool idea #phonebloks    
    
    
    Oh no! MT @amt_shrma: The convergence of search, advertising and recommendations http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2011/11/138205-information-seeking-convergence-of-search-recommendations-and-advertising/fulltext … #recsys #recsys2013    
    
    
    @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma I fully disagree. Recommendations & advertising are optimizing different things.    
    
    
    Sorry, I am ok with unifying search & #recsys, but not ads. They have fundamentally different objective functions http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2011/11/138205-information-seeking-convergence-of-search-recommendations-and-advertising/fulltext …    
    
    
    @pankaj @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma Sure, and the web is search + html :-)    
    
    
    Got my ticket to @kendricklamar + @kanyewest next week. Excited to be taking my son to his first concert!    
    
    
    Are you at #recsys2013 & passionate about #recsys & #machinelearning? Look at the position we have at Netflix: http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00882 …    
    
    
    @adityagp I read "All three mechanisms share the same common goal" and I disagree.    
    
    
    @adityagp I read "We predict that in the future the distinction will be blurred" and I hope you are wrong.    
    
    
    @adityagp I did read the article and I disagree, sorry    
    
    
    @adityagp Sharing infrastructure at a low level is fine, but you are blurring the lines    
    
    
    @adityagp @pankaj @mitultiwari @dtunkelang @greglinden @amt_shrma Like "offering a unified interface for user needs"? - I disagree    
    
    
    @adityagp Well, that's wrong, and it's not recommendation ;-)    
    
    
    I think this deserves a blog post (re: #recsys vs. ads). I'll see if I can find the time.    
    
    
    +1 MT @dtunkelang Speaking of interfaces, dear Twitter please figure out a better group chat soon    
    
    
    "Is music the key to success?" - interesting NYT op-ed piece http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/13/opinion/sunday/is-music-the-key-to-success.html?smid=fb-share&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Analyzing sentiment in movie reviews with Deep Learning https://engineering.stanford.edu/news/stanford-algorithm-analyzes-sentence-sentiment-advances-machine-learning …    
    
    
    Tutorial on "People Recommendation" at #recsys2013 by @kamikaze_bhasin [SLIDES] http://www.slideshare.net/anmolbhasin/tutorial-on-people-recommendations-in-social-networks-acm-recsys-2013hong-kong …    
    
    
    One of the great things of living in the Valley is getting to meet all these fascinating people. Tonight dinner with @adamdangelo    
    
    
    Oh Stonebraker! RT @neil_conway: "The Traditional RDBMS Wisdom Is All Wrong" -Stonebraker's slides from his HPTS talk http://hpts.ws/papers/2013/allwrong.pdf …    
    
    
    Microsoft Leans on Machine Learning and Quantum Computing in New Research Strategy http://zite.to/GPNbTx     
    
    
    Oh my RT @mashable: .@Microsoft Pulls @Windows RT 8.1 Update http://on.mash.to/1ezSvGd     
    
    
    "Trouble at the lab" great article @TheEconomist about stats errors & non-reproducible research http://www.economist.com/news/briefing/21588057-scientists-think-science-self-correcting-alarming-degree-it-not-trouble?fsrc=scn/tw_ec/trouble_at_the_lab … via @aficionado    
    
    
    MT @moustaki VistaTV demonstration at #recsys2013 - http://vista-tv.eu/2013/10/18/vista-tv-demonstration-at-recsys-2013/ …    
    
    
    "Netflix's 3Q Earnings Quadruple, Stock Soars" - That's how we roll :-) http://abcnews.go.com/Technology/wireStory/netflixs-3q-earnings-quadruple-top-street-views-20638570 …    
    
    
    Sent two tweets yesterday that never seemed to make it to my timeline or drafts. Weird.    
    
    
    .@kanyewest in concert last night (one of the tweets that did not go through... testing) pic.twitter.com/67mOjt2UMD    
    
    
    Looking forward to #cikm2013 next week and my talk in the Industry track  (http://www.cikm2013.org/industry.php ). Ping me if interested in chatting.    
    
    
    "The a Paradox of the Proof" - great read on the mysteries of modern theoretical mathematics http://projectwordsworth.com/the-paradox-of-the-proof/ …    
    
    
    R.I.P. Lou Reed :-( http://m.rollingstone.com/music/news/lou-reed-velvet-underground-leader-and-rock-pioneer-dead-at-71-20131027 …    
    
    
    If you are interested in #mlconf (http://www.mlconf.com/mlconf-2013/speakers-abstracts-and-bios/ …) and haven't registered already, you can use code xaviersdiscount for 25% discount    
    
    
    @n0mad_0 I am there too ;-)    
    
    
    Sad Pedro Domingos tutorial #cikm2013 was cancelled. But enjoying "Large Scale Similarity Learning and Indexing" https://www.dropbox.com/s/tpwcis94utp6equ/CIKM13_tut.pdf …    
    
    
    No wifi at #cikm2013 because "number of allowed devices has been exceeded"?    
    
    
    @DataJunkie We should meet this time. I was also in that tutorial ;-)    
    
    
    Attending a tutorial on "Real-time bidding" at #cikm2013    
    
    
    Some more information about the Real-time Bidding Tutorial at #cikm2013 in this website http://tutorial.computational-advertising.org     
    
    
    Don Draper (Mad Men) quote in the Real-time Bidding tutorial #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/SsmyyxXMzW    
    
    
    Too much stuff in parallel at #cikm2013 Going into 2nd part of "Large Scale Machine Learning for IR" http://www.cs.binghamton.edu/~blong/LSML-tutorial-cikm2013/ …    
    
    
    Nice to see LinkedIn using Thompson Sampling as explore/exploit strategy in their ad optimization system http://books.nips.cc/papers/files/nips24/NIPS2011_1232.pdf … #cikm2013    
    
    
    @dtunkelang What time?    
    
    
    @dtunkelang I decided to go home and work given there is the reception tomorrow and the banquet on Wednesday. Will you be around?    
    
    
    My Macbook Air HD is completely gone. All I did today was copy #cikm2013 proceedings. I'd be careful.    
    
    
    For those in the #cikm2013 large-scale ML tutorial, this year's best papers for #kdd2013 and #recsys2013 were both on large-scale MF ....    
    
    
    (...cont) #kdd2013 best paper on Matrix Sketching: http://www.cs.yale.edu/homes/el327/papers/simpleMatrixSketching.pdf# …! & #recsys2013 on parallel SGD http://www.csie.ntu.edu.tw/~cjlin/papers/libmf.pdf# …! #cikm2013    
    
    
    A "classic", but not really MF RT @fulhack: @xamat This paper solved all our issues with large-scale MF: http://www2007.org/paper570.php     
    
    
    At #cikm2013 and interested in a #machinelearning job at Netflix? Ping me during the week http://jobs.netflix.com/jobs.php?id=NFX00882 …    
    
    
    @chr1sa @github that is if you can't figure out yourself in a coding interview I guess?    
    
    
    "Deep Learning for NLP without Magic" - [VIDEO] by Richard Socher and Chris Manning http://techtalks.tv/events/312/573/  (starting with @ML_Hipster quote)    
    
    
    "Spain’s Fiesta del Cine and price elasticity of demand" by @edans https://medium.com/enrique-dans/cd63b2b6753 …    
    
    
    +1 post, -1 to use of "Netflix-style recommender" RT @siah: Music Recommendations and the Logistic Metric Embedding  http://ow.ly/qjfAN     
    
    
    I already proposed in #kdd2013, and we have same issue in #cikm2013: can someone build a demand prediction model for conference sessions?    
    
    
    (...cont) simple predictor: if @edchi and @smolix are authors in a paper, do not use smallest room #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/CuABEjKLaj    
    
    
    Predicting expert Zagat restaurant ratings using grassroot Google Places ratings [PAPER] http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~chenhao/pub/instant-foodie.pdf … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Btw, @edchi and @smolix, did you read our (old) paper analyzing difference between Netflix and RottenTomatoes raters? http://www.nuriaoliver.com/RecSys/wisdomFew_sigir09.pdf …    
    
    
    "Scientiﬁc Articles Recommendation" - Interesting work at #cikm2013 using topic-regression matrix factorization    
    
    
    @yueshi_nl They cite that paper. According to authors main difference is that they also regularize through a Gaussian Prior (besides LDA)    
    
    
    #cikm2013 industry talk by Rich Caruana "Clustering: Probably Approximately Useless". Slides & video of similar talk http://research.microsoft.com/apps/video/dl.aspx?id=204336 …    
    
    
    According to @ted_dunning, most important recsys issues are exploration, diversity, and speed. And #netflixPrize was useless :-/ #cikm2013    
    
    
    One of the most important findings in #recsys in the last 20 years is Result Dithering @ted_dunning #cikm2013 - really?    
    
    
    I do have to say that now @ted_dunning is going into more principled E/E approaches such as Thompson Sampling #cikm2013    
    
    
    (shameless plug) I will be giving my #cikm2013 talk tomorrow 4 pm. And possibly replying to some of @ted_dunning's claims today ;-)    
    
    
    Now Deepak Agarwal on computational advertising at LinkedIn #cikm2013 - reminded me about some famous quote by @hackingdata    
    
    
    Not sure what Deepak meant when saying Explore/Exploit was introduced by Yahoo in Academia in 2008 #cikm2013 - its practical application?    
    
    
    .@LinkedInEng uses ADMM for large-scale logistic regression + Thompson Sampling for explore/exploit - Deepak Agarwal #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@n0mad_0 A similar talk where Deepak explained some of LinkedIn's approaches to advertising http://soihub.org/group/26/hawaii-2-linkedin.pptx … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Creepy. Today I sent a gmail asking about mortgages. Next thing I know, unrelated mortgage agent asks to connect on LinkedIn. Coincidence?    
    
    
    Interesting talk by the yandex guys: "Personalization of Web-search Using Short-term Browsing Context" #cikm2013    
    
    
    Funny to meet random people at #cikm2013 who thank me for tweeting :-)    
    
    
    Interesting paper that unfortunately I missed "Nonparametric Bayesian Multitask Collaborative Filtering" http://www.researchgate.net/publication/256797062_Nonparametric_Bayesian_Multitask_Collaborative_Filtering … #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@AndrewYNg "Education for Everyone" @coursera #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/WwfERFGlNa    
    
    
    Now Jeff Hawkins (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jeff_Hawkins …) on Streaming Online Learning. Impressive lineup in the #cikm2013 industry sessions.    
    
    
    Jeff Hawkins on building systems that mimic how our brain works (i.e. the "memory-prediction" framework http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Memory-prediction_framework …)    
    
    
    Hawkins on "Sparse Distributed Representations" http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sparse_distributed_memory … - fascinating #cikm2013    
    
    
    Kevin Murphy on Google building a probabilistic knowledge graph. Funny he's not in when I search for him #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/ArJNy0D4u1    
    
    
    "U.S. Plans Global Network of Free Online Courses" #NYT http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/01/education/us-plans-global-network-of-free-online-courses.html … - I don't think @AndrewYNg mentioned anything in #cikm2013    
    
    
    Carlos Guestrin speaking about distributed #machinelearning with @GraphLabAPI at #cikm2013. Similar slides here http://auai.org/uai2013/prints/tutorial_carlos.pdf …    
    
    
    Kudos to Carlos Guestrin for doing a real demo during his keynote @GraphLabAPI #cikm2013    
    
    
    .@jure Referencing Dan Ariely's quote on Big Data and teenage sex https://m.facebook.com/dan.ariely/posts/904383595868 … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Alon Havely: "I noticed this audience knows how to tweet so I will try to keep my ideas to <140 chars" #cikm2013    
    
    
    My 14 y.o. son would agree MT @Slate: We were wrong about Facebook and teens. That 13-year-old blogger was right: http://slate.me/16Qfiss     
    
    
    My talk at #cikm2013 in 10 minutes    
    
    
    Sick. Apple, MSFT should be ashamed RT @igrigorik: this patent stuff is bullshit: http://bit.ly/17wnfZM  - I'm losing faith in humanity.    
    
    
    @ctrattner You're welcome! Nice meeting you.    
    
    
    Nice piece MT @gigaom CYMI: The Gigaom guide to deep learning: Who’s doing it, and why it matters: http://ow.ly/qpTRr  #machinelearning    
    
    
    @AmericanAir Waited 30 minutes on a phone call just to hear that the ticket I have does not allow changes! Even if I am willing to pay more!    
    
    
    Sad RT @allthingsd: IBM Sues Twitter For Patent Infringement Ahead of IPO -by @MikeIsaac http://dthin.gs/18SEK0e     
    
    
    "Netflix Acquires Streaming Rights to a Highly Praised Documentary" #NYT http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/05/business/media/netflix-acquires-streaming-rights-to-highly-praised-documentary.html?partner=yahoofinance&_r=0 …    
    
    
    "Scryer: Netflix’s Predictive Auto Scaling Engine" http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/11/scryer-netflixs-predictive-auto-scaling.html?m=1 … - More magic from @NetflixOSS    
    
    
    @ocelma De res ;-)    
    
    
    "Disney and Netflix in Deal for Series Based on Marvel Characters" @nytimes http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/08/business/media/disney-and-netflix-in-deal-for-series-based-on-marvel-characters.html?hpw&rref=television&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Very interesting agenda for the first #spark summit in SF December 2 http://spark-summit.org/agenda/     
    
    
    Looking forward to the #QconSF "Applied Machine Learning and Data Science" track on Tuesday http://qconsf.com/track/applied-machine-learning-and-data-science … See you there!    
    
    
        
    
    
    