The Australian IR conference, ADCS is coming soon http://bit.ly/qL2FuV  Are retro web sites now in fashion? #adcs2011 #in    
    
    
    "The approach is so simple that it may not merit a paper", 264 citations later; BM25F, yes it's simple http://bit.ly/ptM70t  #fb #in    
    
    
    If you count iPads as notebooks/laptops, then Apple now dominates the market http://bit.ly/rrozFq  #fb #in    
    
    
    Why do journal papers take so long to review? I invited 7 reviewers 6 said no. Oh well back to Google Scholar to search for more... #fb #in    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Hey Daniel, what's the timezone for the August 14th deadline, is it the usual one: Samoa?    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @dtunkelang Is there anything west of Samoa? :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @dtunkelang Of course here it's winter and it's late on Monday afternoon, go figure.    
    
    
    Companies have 1 big IT problem: how to store & understand the data deluge from ever more devices & services http://bbc.in/oJqL4L  #fb #in    
    
    
    Ike Antkare: the fake person used to spam Google Scholar: his h was 99 now it's 0. Is Scholar spam checking? http://bit.ly/dULis9  #fb #in    
    
    
    @thesiswhisperer Thanks for the mention :)    
    
    
    Watching Graeme Hirst talk about detecting Alzheimer's in Agatha Christie's novels, promising preliminary results #fb #in    
    
    
    Ever wanted to read four grumpy old men complain (briefly) about evaluation of search engines? Click here http://bit.ly/qhn4f8  #fb #in    
    
    
    A nice summary from Google on how they roll out changes to their search engine http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2011/08/another-look-under-hood-of-search.html?spref=tw … #fb #in    
    
    
    @diazf_y Sorry, I'm being dim, comment on what?    
    
    
    @diazf_y I get you. The commercial focus on high quality evaluation pushes search engines to innovate in ways academia hasn't thought of    
    
    
    Papers in open access journals get higher citation rates compared to journals that charge for access http://bit.ly/pTeI3L  #fb #in    
    
    
    Very comprehensive and impressive set of slides on IR evaluation from Evangelos, Ben and Emine http://bit.ly/pjofTu  #fb #in    
    
    
    Great stat: buy a lottery ticket, you have more chance of dying before the draw than winning the jackpot http://bbc.in/nlmuSG  #fb #in    
    
    
    @jerepick @diazf_y Yes that's a factor, but I don't think that's all, evaluation seems to be valued higher than I see in academia.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff You need something to read during the hurricane don't you?    
    
    
    RMIT 3 year research fellowships. They'll be competitive, but why not apply so you can join the RMIT IR group http://bit.ly/qfzXzA  #fb #in    
    
    
    Stop word removal? That's so last century, stop structure removal is where it's at http://bit.ly/nHPz7U  #fb #in    
    
    
    @noiano No, proceedings will be behind ACM DL's pay wall. But most authors put their papers online & Google Scholar finds those links.    
    
    
    Today I looked at 5 social networks (Twitter FB Yammer LinkedIn & G+) to see what's going on, 10 years ago I just checked my email #fb #in    
    
    
    Show users a bigger query box, they enter longer queries. Seems wrong this paper only 10 citations http://bit.ly/eEWxft #fb #in    
    
    
    Write a message encouraging longer queries from users, they do so & they  find their stuff faster http://bit.ly/f2HTdj #fb #in    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Thanks for the heads up; I'll give that paper a read.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Hey, I enjoyed the paper. I need to follow up with the research experiment papers you cite.    
    
    
    Reading about Indri; I didn't realise that you can control the weight of PageRank as a query command http://bit.ly/pmd4XC  #fb #in    
    
    
    Table 2 of http://bit.ly/nBL1ac  only 1 group beat the baseline system. Not sure if it was a fair comparison though #fb #in    
    
    
    Product rating scores follow a J-shaped distribution, this short paper neatly explains why http://bit.ly/r7jxR3  #fb #in    
    
    
    Quickly estimate 1*2*3*4*5*6*7*8. On average people guess a lower number than if estimating 8*7*6*5*4*3*2*1 http://bit.ly/qqNYeS  #fb #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Stack overflow? Tversky didn't mention that in the paper :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG You're right. I think there are explanations for why people react these ways most times, just good to know they do this    
    
    
    Catching up on an old paper: measuring the minimum distance between query words consistently improves ranking http://bit.ly/qSVLnl  #in    
    
    
    Context sensitive stemming: select stems co-occurring with query, match on stem only if next to other query words http://bit.ly/pkR8rS  #in    
    
    
    #ecir2010 presentation no shows should have been dropped and spaces used for poster people    
    
    
    #ecir2010 current presentation in "semi-live" mode. Five no shows for conference so far, not the organizer's fault, but worrying...    
    
    
    #ecir2010 in my MTurk talk today I said we used direct hit, mistake, we used hit-builder.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman On the stemming? Which paper was that?    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman Hi, yes sounds a bit like the Xu & Croft paper, though with some extra features. The Yahoo one is still my favorite.    
    
    
    Cool analysis of public Facebook data: US can be split into 7 distinct cultures http://bit.ly/ckcXgJ    
    
    
    EVIA 2011: the search evaluation workshop has extended its deadline to Oct 1st - http://bit.ly/odu4Ca  #fb #in    
    
    
    New major review of automatic summarization just out http://bit.ly/o6FI7f  #fb #in    
    
    
    2 versions of a web page, 1 view all; 1 split in chunks, Google will likely send you to the view all version http://bit.ly/oSfQsB  #fb #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG The publisher lets the authors post a PDF on their web site, so there's probably a free version online.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Might be worth emailing the authors and asking for a copy then.    
    
    
    Search engines still have much room for improvement by exploiting personalization http://bit.ly/oiz92v  #fb #in    
    
    
    Another paper showing users move their mouse over search results in the same way their eyes scan the page http://bit.ly/qyULBe  #in #fb    
    
    
    This year's TREC conference had a new record of 119 participating groups. Lots in microblog and an even spread across the others.    
    
    
    @andyy it would be great if Selective Tweets could send tweets only to a pre-defined FB list. Any plans to add that?    
    
    
    Track document history and weight higher terms that survive across the revisions? Seems to work: http://bit.ly/nj137W  #in    
    
    
    Brief old paper on user satisfaction, recall & librarian ideals: http://bit.ly/cB8FIA. I'm with Cooper: recall is often a distraction.    
    
    
    Congratulations to Alan Smeaton for winning the Strix IR research award; another in a long list of worthy winners http://bit.ly/nnnEbL  #in    
    
    
    First look at the accepted #SIGIR2010 papers this year http://bit.ly/ccm3QA.    
    
    
    Chatting to a company last night, they recently dropped their contract for Google Docs as "it hadn't been improved in 2 years". #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG they seemed interested in the Microsoft tools.    
    
    
    Is this Luhn article the 1st IR paper that described document ranking? This one is from 1957 http://bit.ly/nwmOEx  #in    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Thanks. There was a Maron tech report from '58 on probability and IR, which isn't well known, but I know of nothing earlier.    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Sure I can send them to you. Is there a way to send PDFs through Twitter?    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo "Bag of words" No idea, anyone else know?    
    
    
    The FnTIR review paper on summarization can now be downloaded for free from http://bit.ly/qHHV2F  #in    
    
    
    Great page on conference poster design http://bit.ly/ni8aWB  did you know there is a Flickr group called Pimp My Poster? #fb #in    
    
    
    Old evaluation paper full of ideas: cumulative gain; ranked biased Kendall Tau; nasty maths, something for everyone: http://bit.ly/bu0hOf    
    
    
    Teaching & Learning in IR: a new book is out; includes a chapter on teaching evaluation of IR systems http://bit.ly/rd4Ifo  #in    
    
    
    JASIST is now making ultra fast paper decisions, my last two papers were decided on in less than 4 weeks!    
    
    
    ECIR 2013 (European IR conference) will be in Moscow, hosted by Yandex. ECIR has come a long way from its humble UK IR symposium origins.    
    
    
    Tried ACM Author-ize? It's a bit complicated, but it lets you put links to free downloads of your official ACM pubs http://bit.ly/r42tN9     
    
    
    Google paper showing speed of search response affects user behavior: http://bit.ly/CB7jw I wish there was more detail in the note #fb    
    
    
    It's 2 years old, but this paper showing that groupization is better than personalization, was a good read http://bit.ly/qBqYMT  #in    
    
    
    Your social & physical distance from an event, relates to your chances of searching for that event. http://bit.ly/pjMGTr  #in    
    
    
    The tentative program for NTCIR in December is out http://bit.ly/mWzrQh     
    
    
    Final #SIGIR2010 programme up http://bit.ly/bhgxfz Donna Harman one of the keynotes #fb    
    
    
    Does your test collection have the statistical power to measure small differences? Webber et al are here to help http://bit.ly/cp43Ue    
    
    
    ERR measure; relevance is dependent on other documents. ERR validated on test collection with >16K queries, Yikes! http://bit.ly/aE0dvl #fb    
    
    
    ECIR2012, our workshop on session based retrieval has been approved. Now to start working on the call for papers...    
    
    
    Thinking about ACM Author-ize. ACM has created an admittedly involved way to get FREE access to its content, that's quite something  #in    
    
    
    #adcs happens today, looks like a good programme of IR papers http://bit.ly/gUq09K #in #fb    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I very much doubt my Uni pays for ACM Author-izer, there's nothing on the ACM pages about that.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I think they want to restrict the free links to come from only one place.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I think the free download is a carrot to get people to sign up to and own the author pages on the ACM DL.    
    
    
    Our #SIGIR2010 paper is up http://bit.ly/9o6UCq Do user preferences & evaluation measures line up? Answer, yes, & nDCG better than P10 #fb    
    
    
    Search Logs with Relevance Judgments from Yahoo! http://bit.ly/u04Jzq  look for L18 in the list of resources #in    
    
    
    Personal info is used differently depending where u are & who u are with, obvious, but good there's a pub on this http://bit.ly/s3WuPr  #in    
    
    
    Missed the 60th anniversary of the phrase "information retrieval", First used March 29th, 1950, in opening pages http://bit.ly/boUHHn #fb    
    
    
    Great talk from @thesiswhisperer on social media & academic careers: sociology, philosophy, and post modernism, the perfect CS seminar #in    
    
    
    @thesiswhisperer of course they came in their droves, you are The Thesis Whisperer.    
    
    
    I'm all for having conferences in nice places, but these guys seem to really like doing this http://www.waset.org/  #in #fb    
    
    
    Focus groups, eye tracking, log studies; the levels of tests used by #Google before launching its new look http://bit.ly/ddP4aL #fb    
    
    
    Presented our #adcs paper http://bit.ly/gxB7Qk on relevance assessors changing their minds. Great feedback, now to explore more #in #fb    
    
    
    One of my students has been working on singing queries for music retrieval; here are some preliminary results http://bit.ly/rRjLZw  #in    
    
    
    My Google Scholar citations home page is set up http://bit.ly/tl5uQE  I have a feeling I'm going to visiting this very very often #in    
    
    
    Need to join two messy columns of text in Excel, found a fuzzy lookup add-in from MS Research http://bit.ly/tNPQlc  not perfect, but OK #in    
    
    
    Someone is celebrating TREC's 20th birthday in style :) http://twitpic.com/7fswm8     
    
    
    Where do doctors go to seek medical images for work purposes? Journals, personal collections, but mainly Google http://bit.ly/k8EuLy  #in    
    
    
    Short position paper from one of my students on evaluating personal IR systems http://bit.ly/vKiahs  #in    
    
    
    Reading old papers... found that simple acronym handling + BM25 helps you win a track at TREC http://1.usa.gov/vcIjHU  #in    
    
    
    Google maps moves indoors. If they can get the positioning to work well, this is likely to a big thing http://bit.ly/sWbpy4  #in    
    
    
    #irhistory In the old days, documents were indexed by classification codes, then Taube said "let's try words" http://bit.ly/t49cIC  #in    
    
    
    Bruce Croft set up his Google Scholar citations page http://bit.ly/sSVn8x  he's got an h of 73... I give up. #in    
    
    
    #evia2011 different assessors use very different criteria when judging community question answering systems    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I like this paper, getting users to draw a concept map after search is a good idea. Has it been tried before? #evia2011    
    
    
    Watching Ian Soboroff presenting his talk slides from his iPhone. #evia2011    
    
    
    Enjoying Gareth Jones's presentation about MediaEval (http://www.multimediaeval.org ) at #evia2011    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai What would you call a merged CLEF and INEX? CLENEX? #evia2011    
    
    
    The #evia2011 session on CLEF, INEX, TREC, MediaEval, & FIRE, working well: 15 minutes per talk makes nicely condensed presentations    
    
    
    1300 academic papers added to medline each day! Keynote being given at #ntcir9    
    
    
    #ntcir9 in one year there were 25000 papers about one gene type.    
    
    
    #ntcir9 nice grid searching interface to help with exploratory search.    
    
    
    Great fun giving a joint talk with @wewebber at #ntcir9. Private data & reproducability of IR results got lots of feedback and questions.    
    
    
    NRBP, the kitchen sink of IR evaluation measures, every avenue covered... probably: http://bit.ly/am4Ev0    
    
    
    The OED expand its definition of the word information, they think it's quite an important word http://bit.ly/eirk45 #fb #in    
    
    
    CrowdSearch workshop at WWW. Social networks, crowd sourcing, expert finding, community search, all in one place http://bit.ly/t56ycm     
    
    
    An attempt to gather a public query log was canceled as only 200 people in the world were willing volunteers http://bit.ly/eGiwG #fb    
    
    
    Data centres don't need to be as cold as most people think they do http://bit.ly/vdRwad  #in    
    
    
    @giovannaroda I should have put that URL in the talk I was just giving    
    
    
    #IRFC paper on link between standard deviation & bounded effectiveness scores; high SD guarantees middling score http://bit.ly/96Ah14    
    
    
    Dave Hawking doing a live learning to rank demo during his keynote at #IRFC, show off #fb    
    
    
    Cool set of slides on how the design of an MTurk experiment impacts on the quality of data gathered http://bit.ly/9qN3oQ    
    
    
    Web doesn't facilitate scientific innovation - James Boyle co-creator of scientific commons. Great keynote, no notes, no PPT; #irfs2010.    
    
    
    A major IR Prof told me he's given up journal reviewing; conference reviews only now, he thinks that's where the action is #in #fb    
    
    
    @giovannaroda Is that the paper where he proposes the e measure?    
    
    
    @BrotherLogic I don't know that article, have you got a link?    
    
    
    @neelannair I think this is more a comment on the freshness of conference material and not on journal quality.    
    
    
    Pareto and crowdsourcing, many try a task, only a few provide good quality work http://bit.ly/fqIWcm #fb #in    
    
    
    "The amount of information available is becoming unmanageable", turns out this statement's always been true http://bbc.in/zFECYw  #fb #in    
    
    
    I think this is the first paper describing tf*idf weights http://bit.ly/wCjs2p  anyone know an earlier one? #in    
    
    
    Foundations & Trends in IR continues to have more cites per paper than ACM Computer Surveys! http://bit.ly/zwA0i8  #in    
    
    
    How to get your academic article read on the web - some advice I got from a publisher this week #in http://twitpic.com/888gcn     
    
    
    @siandart Hi, they didn't, there is a whole earlier section on that topic.    
    
    
    Associate Professor job in IR at RMIT http://bit.ly/wDAV00  happy to chat to anyone interested #in    
    
    
    Searching for page on how good Google is http://bit.ly/zrSpU8  these results showed there is still room for improvement http://bit.ly/zA3t3P     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff come join us :)    
    
    
    Congratulations to Lida, an RMIT ISAR student, for getting an internship at IBM's new research lab in Melbourne http://bit.ly/w50oLb  #in    
    
    
    Relevance assessors who don't understand a domain make inaccurate judgements simply looking for keyword overlap http://bit.ly/xrRRln  #in    
    
    
    Divide your h by the years since you finished your PhD, bigger number = better apparently. Finally a positive for taking ages to write up.    
    
    
    This service has a long way to go, but it's the start of something important: combining web & private content http://selnd.com/yNeqrc     
    
    
    @noiano I agree, Google say they can't add FB and Twitter because terms of use prevent Google from crawling their content.    
    
    
    1st web query log analysis (1995)? http://bit.ly/azUKeW Mentions Boston Globe article effectively saying ranked retrieval is "faulty"    
    
    
    404 page not found on Google? http://bit.ly/A5fWYQ  #in    
    
    
    45 minutes till the abstract deadline on #sigir2012, but almost no more submissions coming in. Surely not everyone is asleep?    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Not no; at least if I've switched the system correctly, not now.    
    
    
    That's it, no longer Monday anywhere in the world, #sigir2012 abstracts are all in: 650 submitted.    
    
    
    Reviewing for novel evaluation workshops at SIGIR: SimInt2010 & CSE2010, both keen to push beyond the Cranfield approach #in    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 paper deadline? When it stops being Mon the 13th here http://bit.ly/ykIozK  that's the deadline. Good luck with your papers.    
    
    
    Read a paper that drew general conclusions about search engines based on the answers of 15 students. We're just more different than that.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 just under an hour till we switch the submission system off.    
    
    
    #swirl12 #occupymydata is the hot new idea at the Lorne meeting    
    
    
    #swirl12 Doug Oard wants an IR system that is an exoskeleton for the mind.    
    
    
    The first description of IR on a digital computer? This MIT Masters thesis is from 1951 http://bit.ly/c8zUbc  #in    
    
    
    #swirl12 photos from the meeting up online http://bit.ly/y8sb4h     
    
    
    Great talk from @JulioGonzalo1 today at RMIT. Careful analysis of evaluation measures, creating an IR specific significance test. #in    
    
    
    You always suspected, now a study confirms, users are influenced by a search engine's brand http://bit.ly/dh9uiX #in #fb    
    
    
    Stefano has blogged about #swirl12 http://bit.ly/ySULSg     
    
    
    The #sigir2010 next generation test collection workshop is apparently cancelled: lack of interest http://ir.cis.udel.edu/NGTC10/ #in    
    
    
    Some interesting stats on the state of the ICT industry in Australia, more jobs not enough graduates #in    
    
    
    Microsoft 'Illumishare' demonstrates remote physical object interaction... all sort of collaborative search possibilities.    
    
    
    It's a picture, it's a movie, it's a “Cliplet” from MSR who will take the time to do them though? http://bit.ly/zi0WG6  via @MSFTNext    
    
    
    Stack Exchange Q&A site proposal: Information Retrieval and Search Engines http://bit.ly/GLr93i     
    
    
    An economic impact report will show that a healthy chunk of money was generated through research & evaluation fostered by TREC #in #fb    
    
    
    @iFromm Yes, it should be going on the TREC site.    
    
    
    @iFromm the report is at http://trec.nist.gov/pubs/2010.economic.impact.pdf    
    
    
    The daily Google puzzles are fun, but are they experimenting on us: studying how we do complex search? http://bit.ly/Heiwh7  #in    
    
    
    Studying the physics of Angry Birds, pointlessly brilliant research, http://bit.ly/Hm3d4Z  Ig Nobel maybe?    
    
    
    Enjoying query log tutorial at #sigir2010 bit sweaty though #fb    
    
    
    Papers I should've read ages ago. http://bit.ly/Hp0ViZ  excellent early crowd sourcing paper for NLP labelling. #in    
    
    
    OpenStreetMap continues to make gains, Wikipedia using it now instead of Google Maps http://cnet.co/IwMTiS  #in    
    
    
    @asmeaton gave a great talk at RMIT, but did he visit us or come to watch the Iron Man in Melbourne that Sunday :) http://bit.ly/HQMRR7     
    
    
    Manmatha from UMass gave a great talk at RMIT on a cool algorithm he developed on fast duplicate document matching http://bit.ly/HQNBpd  #in    
    
    
    Thrilled for Lida and Jasbir getting their internships at IBM Melbourne http://bit.ly/HQO36U  #in    
    
    
    New paper from RMIT IR group http://bit.ly/HQO9LV  "Using anchor text for homepage and topic distillation search tasks" #in    
    
    
    @elunca Will get a copy sent    
    
    
    Andrei Broder is now at Google after leaving Yahoo a couple of weeks ago. #in    
    
    
    @metzlerd @ian_soboroff Good news Don.    
    
    
    How often were you thanked in the acknowledgements of an academic paper? AckSeer knows http://bit.ly/IIcQvG  #in    
    
    
    Are these the first uses of the term "search engine"? MIS and DB books from '72 & '76? http://bit.ly/JqwfA4  http://bit.ly/HRjPOi  #in    
    
    
    Omar Alonso's crowd sourcing keynote full of great tips at the crowd sourcing workshop #sigir2010    
    
    
    A new batch of historical books and papers now online at SIGIR's museum http://bit.ly/HW8gus  #in    
    
    
    Expert ranking of academics correlate somewhat with citation. Scopus a bit better than Google Scholar http://bit.ly/94QJ7k #in #fb    
    
    
    Splitting a city into social regions derived from FourSquare data http://www.livehoods.org/  #in    
    
    
    This paper says 50 queries are fine for testing, yet search engines use 1000s of queries, we're missing something http://bit.ly/JRW7VP  #in    
    
    
    @julian_urbano They certainly are not sampled, yes, maybe they are a popular style of query, but actually, who knows?    
    
    
    @srchvrs Tell me more    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Yes and the recent web tracks are getting queries from logs also.    
    
    
    That's the SIGIR notifications going out...    
    
    
    Search without those pesky dominating sites like Wikipedia, DBLP, IMDB, etc. Reminds me of the old days http://www.millionshort.com     
    
    
    @seo01 'dunno, sorry    
    
    
    New paper with old PhD student Shahram on image search by doctors is out http://shar.es/27Zaq  free version here http://bit.ly/IJBdb0  #in    
    
    
    Just out, Bruce Croft and I wrote a short history of ranked IR: pay version http://bit.ly/JYpVyd  free version http://bit.ly/ITGMQS  #in    
    
    
    @takis_metaxas One is free and one you have to pay for. Well, also the pay one corrects a few typos that the publisher noticed.    
    
    
    Nice analysis of tweets, seen a lot of this before in query logs, but fun to see elsewhere http://bit.ly/IZBIKW  #in    
    
    
    The report from the SWIRL meeting is out in SIGIR Forum http://bit.ly/JvaU6t  long list of suggested future IR research directions #in    
    
    
    The XBox Kinect tracks bodies by seeing how they deform structured light, here are beautiful photographs of that http://bit.ly/LA2eOp  #in    
    
    
    Matrix of transitions used to arrange the components of exploratory search, nice. @HCIR_GeneG & @jerepick http://bit.ly/JamhzA  #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG No problem, I just liked the way you guys did that.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG It seems to me one big issue is to help the searcher understand when they are going over ground already covered.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Cool, please send me the pointer. I tried something very simple on this 20 years ago :) http://bit.ly/KZUCbB  (p12)    
    
    
    @leifos @HCIR_GeneG my twitter handle that gets truer every day. Just you wait young Leif, it'll happen to you soon enough.    
    
    
    I'm the new co-editor of FnTIR http://bit.ly/K4JSUr  Many thanks for all the years of hard work from Fabrizio who is stepping down #in    
    
    
    Feynman explains the scientific method in a minute, just great http://bit.ly/LYG8oZ  #in    
    
    
    Nice article from Marti Hearst on the future directions for IR http://dl.acm.org/authorize?6592199 … #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aZSmnw another fast way to get IR ground truth like Amitay's TRELs? But should be striving for fast over quality? #in    
    
    
    Google Scholar's top 100 publication venues. This can only be the start of this sort of data from them http://bit.ly/JsALkV  #in    
    
    
    NYT on the debate about academic access to private data for research purposes http://nyti.ms/MbFMvr  #in    
    
    
    Just realised that Google Scholar Metrics is searchable http://bit.ly/JsALkV  SIGIR is not the top IR forum by citation, JASIST is #in    
    
    
    @ssn All measures have problems, h5 can disadvantage low volume forums. It ignores low citation papers, thus arXiv scores high.    
    
    
    This query shows the main IR venues ranked on Scholar http://bit.ly/KoBS1C  JASIST, SIGIR, IP&M, CIKM, WSDM, TOIS, did I miss anything? #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Hmmm searched for that, but I don't see it in there. I couldn't find the WWW conference either.    
    
    
    @amjedbj @msftacademic I like the MSR system, what's cool about Google is it merges conferences with journals.    
    
    
    @guidozuc Welcome to the world of information extraction, there will be missing counts for everything due to inconsistent naming.    
    
    
    @delsweil I know what you mean, but for me it's IR 'enough' :)    
    
    
    @iFromm @phschaer @delsweil So with digital libraries added to the query (thanks) you get this http://bit.ly/KTHXpr     
    
    
    @phschaer @delsweil @ifromm The problem is, people in power use these things.    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer Might be due to ECIR's publishing in LNCS, which I've seen cause referencing confusion.    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer Actually, the strange one that's missing is TREC I search, but I can't find it.    
    
    
    Pairs of words are sometimes ambiguous: search for Belkin ASK on Google Scholar, you get 2 quite distinct threads of research. #fb #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/acclql Belkin's ASK: we search to know, but if we don't know, how do we search? Do we only query the easy stuff? #in    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer If you look at the ECIR citations, it seems to only be pubs from 2010 and 2011 http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?hl=en&view_op=list_hcore&venue=eAz7mQVdMusJ.20120401 … bug    
    
    
    @delsweil @iadh @ifromm @phschaer Does ECIR have its pubs in the ACM DL? If not, maybe it should; that might help Google Scholar.    
    
    
    @phschaer @iadh @delsweil @ifromm It's definitely doable, the Australasian IR Conference (ADCS) I think will soon be on the ACM DL.    
    
    
    @seo01 http://bit.ly/98YStI my 1st IR paper; people always told me about Belkin's ASK, glad I read it, interesting to compare now & then.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/98nlR5 top 1998 web queries? sex, Playboy, Penthouse, chat, Hustler, nude, porn, erotica... the web has changed #fb    
    
    
    How Many Test Users in a Usability Study? Five, mostly (Jakob Nielsen's Alertbox) http://shar.es/q8Pwm  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Published papers aren't a random sample of science: the 97% using a significance test found significance http://bit.ly/fzqCw7 #fb #in    
    
    
    The sharpshooter's fallacy is alive and well in the fields of science http://nyr.kr/hTDy1p #fb #in    
    
    
    Occasionally, you read something that changes your view.; can such teams be used for academic research? I should try http://bit.ly/MrFEJP     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/awwb7m Session DCG, thinking about this (maybe) for the TREC session track... but what's "Scenario D"?    
    
    
    SIGIR is running a panel this year the use of proprietary data in academic research. Should be fun, hopefully productive #in    
    
    
    Neilsen "5 users in a usability test is good" Schmettow "the maths behind that claim is wrong, you need many more" http://bit.ly/KflFd4     
    
    
    Nice early study showing that users want results quickly and care less about the source http://bit.ly/Kfng2L     
    
    
    Search Google Scholar for an email address fragment: e.g. ".ac.uk" you get top UK academics, works for Uni names too. http://bit.ly/KRTnXF     
    
    
    Nice summary of work in probabilistic topic models in April's CACM http://bit.ly/LEc8NP     
    
    
    Call for participation in NTCIR's search evaluations is out. The deadline for joining is looming, miss it, miss out. http://bit.ly/MvhD4k     
    
    
    Crowd sourced vs expert relevance judgements, which is better? Our paper says crowds, but experts aren't redundant yet. http://bit.ly/N5DHm0     
    
    
    @srchvrs Quite possibly, don't under estimate the importance of expert knowledge.    
    
    
    The Google grants recipients for this round are out. A few IR people are in there... including me :) http://bit.ly/MIckA2     
    
    
    @JulioGonzalo1 Very cool Julio, great to see #swirl2012 had such an immediate benefit.    
    
    
    @ieleta Thanks    
    
    
    Someone said this week: "there are 2 types of successful academics: those who know how to write grants; and those who have great ideas" #in    
    
    
    Yet another library digitizing its archives, this time it's the Wellcome trust http://bit.ly/cmTJOD #in    
    
    
    @timgollins Thanks, sorry I couldn't chat for longer today.    
    
    
    Great talk by Pascal Van Hentenryck on optimisation last night; he cited this example showing computing saves lives. http://bit.ly/LDeySt     
    
    
    Berners-Lee's 1999 book on WWW's 1st decade: few search engines, a hint of web 2.0, lots of semantic web http://bit.ly/ieyVDm #fb #in    
    
    
    One of our students presented on news recommender systems yesterday. She's got a nice data set to work with. http://bit.ly/LTghOV     
    
    
    I'm hearing that the main conference hotel for #sigir2012 is filling up, book soon.    
    
    
    #cikm2012 One accept, one reject. I'll take that.    
    
    
    Not everyday someone you know gets his research narrated by Morgan Freeman. http://youtu.be/oeaFYYHShlo  #in    
    
    
    Years ago, I pitched a computers & data in the field idea to archaeologists, their reply? I want a water proof computer http://bit.ly/O8U8wO     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ArjumandYounus Yes I imagine they are, posters tend to be.    
    
    
    I knew cross (translated) language search was on Google, but I didn't realise they had made it easy to use. http://bit.ly/NPvuzg     
    
    
    What is a Browser? If you haven't already, great video for CS people to watch http://youtu.be/o4MwTvtyrUQ     
    
    
    Recent research on eye tracking and search interfaces was presented at the RMIT Tiger talk this week. http://bit.ly/NN5lCL     
    
    
    "Spoken Content Retrieval: A Survey of Techniques and Technologies" is just out in the latest FnTIR edition http://bit.ly/PLOost  #in    
    
    
    Past PhD plagiarism is damaging political and professorial careers in Europe http://bbc.in/SSQWsd     
    
    
    Prof & Assoc. Prof at jobs RMIT: areas include social networks, big data; details here http://bit.ly/NSM5qr  http://bit.ly/NSMs4b  #in    
    
    
    @rainingman1 Thanks for pointer, is this better than Turnitin?    
    
    
    @rainingman1 You can tell Turnitin to ignore individual documents to prevent that from being a problem.    
    
    
    @rainingman1 Yes, Turnitin tells you have 100% match on the earlier document, but you can tell it to ignore that doc and re-calculate    
    
    
    Microsoft adds a Facebook-based collaborative search feature to Bing searches http://cnet.co/Ox8PgJ  via @CNET    
    
    
    @jerepick Sounds reasonable to me. We've got someone here working on mobile collaborative search by the way.    
    
    
    A major review of blog search is just out from the Glasgow and NIST people #in http://bit.ly/M4xXKZ     
    
    
    The IR review journal FnTIR releases another major review, this time in Expertise Retrieval #in http://bit.ly/M4ysEQ     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/wgCg4 Hearst book: one to be left open on your desk covered in scribbles & notes AND on-line version is free! #in    
    
    
    Great talk this evening by Kenneth O. Stanley from Florida on novelty search in AI applications, really cool work.    
    
    
    @jteevan @sigirf if the measure tells you something different, then maybe. That wasn't covered much in the talk #sigir2012    
    
    
    #sigir2012 enjoyed Ryen White's log analysis talk about extracting valuable data from health queries.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 thinking about Tue's proprietary data panel session, note all of this year's log analysis papers are from search engine groups.    
    
    
    @jteevan about proprietary data? To be honest I don't know.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 enjoyed listening about ranking features that are good for mobile local search http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/163550/fp121-lv.pdf …    
    
    
    #sigir2012 when I grow up, I want to be like Steve Robertson. He's virtually retired and he's here enthusiastically presenting his poster.    
    
    
    @eelstretching great donuts, thank you #sigir2012    
    
    
    "@jteevan: @eugeneAgichtein's Given search task that's suspended, predict if searcher will pick it back up later. #SIGIR2012" great talk    
    
    
    #sigir2012 geography to the rescue of search? Apparently yes, according to our current exploratory search speaker.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @BHecht really cool spatial visualisation of search results: maps, periodic tables, where senators sit in congress.    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 Marc Bron tackling the difficult subject of how to evaluate exploratory search. Great session.    
    
    
    @jteevan @sigirf That's a critical point as far as I'm concerned, there are loads of examples of science conducted on unsharable data.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 if I'm a doctor who publishes a patient drug study, it's crazy for others to demand access to my patients, yet this is science.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 it only took Ricardo 3 minutes to mention wine :)    
    
    
    #sigir2012 I see a consensus emerging here.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 for a fresh PhD student @wewebber is holding his own very well with the rest of the panel    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @invertedindex "welcome to the first SIGIR session in the bat cave". This room is terrible.    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 @invertedindex extending his time series analysis work from last year on dealing with time varying queries.    
    
    
    @JeffD we're headed for a question? #sigir2012    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 Etan Aydar talking about zoetrope and other ways of querying and visualising temporal data, cool.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @mdr talking about open geist: a tool that processes Wikipedia trend data.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 really enjoyed the conference this year, good papers, a fun venue, thanks Bill.    
    
    
    I said at #swirl12 that indoor location based information delivery would be important... maybe I was right http://bit.ly/NmBV3B  #in    
    
    
    Our CIKM short paper on inconsistencies in search engine ranking when measured across different collections http://bit.ly/Tblio9  #in    
    
    
    If only I'd had the Manga guides when I was a kid, I wouldn't be having to learn stats in my 40s. http://bit.ly/TbtmoV     
    
    
    @craig_macdonald It doesn't have one yet, we're working on the WoS people about this. It will come and when it does, it should be good.    
    
    
    Rank citation analysis academics by their citation paper h-index, the highly influential inventor of h, Hirsch ranks very low #in #fb    
    
    
    Google Instant shows multiple SERPs to users, is Google getting more training data on user preferences for its results? #in #fb    
    
    
    Password cracking meets big data... and does rather well. http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/08/passwords-under-assault/ … #in    
    
    
    Ricardo Baeza-Yates visiting us at RMIT. Itinerary: meet students, give talk, lunch meet staff, then see penguins: perfect Melbourne visit.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald The average citation count for the 19 papers published by FnTIR http://bit.ly/K4JSUr  is 112. Popular papers indeed #in    
    
    
    @leifos @craig_macdonald power law. So I should use the median. ERA? There were these problems, note the grades aren't being updated.    
    
    
    It's not just relevance, users love simple & familiar designs; websites need to make a great first impression http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2012/08/users-love-simple-and-familiar-designs.html … #in    
    
    
    Excited to announce that Timos Sellis is joining us at RMIT http://scholar.google.gr/citations?user=G1Iux80AAAAJ&hl=en … #in    
    
    
    @KushalDave Sorry about that. Try http://www.optimalworkshop.com/treejack-results … and click on task results follow your nose...    
    
    
    @optimalworkshop @KushalDave It's cool stuff, I was showing it in a usability engineering class at my University this week.    
    
    
    How find without searching; this great talk looked at finding solutions in AI, lessons for search here I think http://youtu.be/tZBViI8ZaU0  #in    
    
    
    How's this for a small conference venue 15 minutes from Melbourne's centre? I like Melbourne http://yfrog.com/oexviegj     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG who needs PowerPoint when you have palm trees?    
    
    
    Visually impaired users find complex searching difficult on Google (no free version of the paper). http://bit.ly/P0xEPY     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG I would go with the 1991 journal paper, that's pretty definitive, we updated the interface later, but didn't write it up :(    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Great name for a journal eh? Yes that one.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Sorry for any confusion, I assumed you were looking at my publications page http://www.seg.rmit.edu.au/mark/publications/ …    
    
    
    4th best student city, 2012? My home town, Melbourne :) http://www.topuniversities.com/student-life/best-student-cities/2012/melbourne#.UE7iikbpz3g.twitter … #fb    
    
    
    Listening to Richard Stallman talk about his 4 freedoms and how they apply to copyright    
    
    
    Hmm Stallman taking A bit too long to get to some interesting points    
    
    
    The BBC picked up on the Melbourne Universities ranking with a lovely photo of the RMIT 'brain' building. http://www.bbc.com/travel/feature/20120907-best-student-cities-melbourne … #in    
    
    
    When selecting a new academic for a post: diverse, great publications may be more important than a high h http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/scientists-what-will-your-career-look-like-in-ten-years/ …    
    
    
    "Designing & testing an improved packaging for large hollow chocolate bunnies" that's *real* research http://www.tappi.org/Downloads/unsorted/UNTITLED---97Aug133pdf.aspx … #in    
    
    
    Attending William Weber's PhD completion talk in Melbourne. So much good IR evaluation work in one thesis. Amazing!    
    
    
    A tough read: essentially pseudo relevance feedback meets sense disambiguation. Good experimental reporting. http://bit.ly/Qxvneo     
    
    
    You can't always trust Google's "My Citation" pages. This person shows that papers you didn't write can be included. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    @IR_oldie The papers added here are so crazy, there's no deception intended here, just an illustration that there is no checking.    
    
    
    A social network aggregator (probably been done elsewhere), but first time I've seen this idea tried out. http://bit.ly/VHH72C     
    
    
    Really nice opinion piece on the multiple roles of computers in cars http://www.wired.com/opinion/2012/10/automakers-become-software-makers-the-next-battle-between-open-and-closed/ …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai It differed quite a bit though, don't you think? I was pleasantly surprised about that part.    
    
    
    Lol, he is on a mission to be the number one IR person on Google Scholar, he's now at number 2. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    The visual version of "is your baseline strong enough?" http://bit.ly/ROpCNq     
    
    
    Yay, he did it: the number 1 IR person in the world. Someone had to show how vulnerable these lists are to spam. http://bit.ly/ROucv8     
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG All the papers have a "J Wang" as an author, just not him. Maybe Google doesn't check that carefully?    
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG Maybe you can overwrite the suggested papers and add extra to the list, keep adding and you move ever up.    
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG The labels are all self-nominated. Google gave up on that idea for the Web years ago, too susceptible to spam.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/b7DoM7 simulated analysis of MTurkers making errors & the benefits of using gold standard data to detect them #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/dtqOBl RMIT-based cost benefit analysis of improving search effectiveness, nice idea.    
    
    
    Academics cite a wider range of more relevant papers than they did before the internet came along. http://bit.ly/SoiG7d     
    
    
    Our Yahoo! Research proposal was funded: "Re-finding information in the Web”, jointly with David Vallet and my student Sargol Sadeghi.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aHgG3Y Google's guide to getting your web page ranked high just updated: detailed solid info #fb #in    
    
    
    Detailed instructions on how to evaluate enterprise search systems. Quite different from TREC style evaluation. http://bit.ly/RqmXr7     
    
    
    His h score rises still, but Google have taken him off the list of IR people. His short reign at the top has ended. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    Lessons on training from the army. Valuable hints for computer scientists, maybe even PhD supervisors http://bit.ly/TOMSXV     
    
    
    @dirkahlers Yeah, though my impression is stop lists aren't Google's style, maybe some clustering to spot paper content outliers?    
    
    
    @dirkahlers Ah :)    
    
    
    Locating & using the tweets of a subset of twitter users to summarise the tweets of a wider population. #cikm2012 http://bit.ly/TnGVk9     
    
    
    @srchvrs @kohlschuetter Both use automatic sense disambiguation and "author intervention", but with different emphasis on the techniques.    
    
    
    @michaeltwofish Sorry, when I put my hand up, I was referring to a private blog for internal notes. This is the only public thing.    
    
    
    @michaeltwofish sorry, you'll need go make do with tweets    
    
    
    Enterprise search person told me the web is a publishing medium, while most enterprises hold a digital archive. Quite different to search.    
    
    
    @srchvrs also no one is (white hat) optimising enterprise archive content. There's no advertising to fund development of the ranker :)    
    
    
    My student got a Yahoo award, with a bit of help from me and David Vallet :) http://shar.es/GFRzh  via    
    
    
    Google Scholar is grouping journals & conferences by sub-topic. IR is in DB&IS: WWW, VLDB, SIGMOD, SIGIR top forums http://bit.ly/SPXO8a     
    
    
    Many people tell about spam on MTurk: sounds like Amazon needs to improve its rating system http://bit.ly/cbv5sP #in    
    
    
    Computer used when walking? Define system quality by user walk speed & how many red crossing lights missed, brilliant. http://bit.ly/UVzcv8     
    
    
    With friends like these, who needs QRELS? Facebook and Bing sharing data http://bit.ly/bANbHk #in #fb    
    
    
    SVD-like mapping of docs to semantic hash codes, then use ML to learn mappings for new docs to new codes http://bit.ly/aofQza #in #fb    
    
    
    A colleague's Google Scholar profile contained papers he didn't write, turns out Scholar added them automatically.    
    
    
    Mood changes measured in Twitter predict US stock market moves 3-4 days later http://bit.ly/aeQzLP #fb #in    
    
    
    Nice side piece from the Leveson (press standards) inquiry in the UK on the inaccuracies of science reporting. http://bit.ly/TvRmDw     
    
    
    @delsweil Is your commute in a helicopter?    
    
    
    The challenge of creating usable security in wireless devices, a great keynote by Gene Tsudik at ACSW in Perth. #fb #in    
    
    
    Social Media Is Eating Our Lives (And Pinterest Is Chewing Fastest) | Wired Business | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/business/2012/12/social-spike/ …    
    
    
    Nice student resource about plagiarism http://plagiarism.org/     
    
    
    New extensive review of contextual search just out. http://bit.ly/TK6IoK     
    
    
    A strong result, computer science at RMIT got two ratings of 4 (out of 5) for its research by the Australian Government yesterday #era    
    
    
    Enjoyed reading this paper on summarizing tweets for events http://bit.ly/UQvDKp     
    
    
    Our RMIT CS students built an app for a Guinness World Record attempt tomorrow evening http://bit.ly/SMOaFs     
    
    
    CLEF is no longer about just cross language search, check out the 2013 call. http://bit.ly/SSdo6P     
    
    
    One part of this paper examines conditional equivalence of documents with respect to a query, nice idea http://bit.ly/9s10sW #fb #in    
    
    
    Tweet sports summarization, showing video of football matches based on tweet volume and some personalization data. http://bit.ly/TVl8SW     
    
    
    Reading about TweetMotif the tweet search engine & browser, the engine is down, anyone know if there's a new link? http://bit.ly/VKBFbY     
    
    
    @sarvk Cool, thanks    
    
    
    @damiano10 Cool, thank you. Has this longer version been published anywhere?    
    
    
    We have an associate professor position at RMIT: big data, semantic search, and/or social data analytics. Interested? contact me.    
    
    
    @brendan642 thanks for contacting me. For now, your paper covers all I need to know, though are you still working on tweet summarization?    
    
    
    #SIGIR2013 call out; reviewers will consider reproducibility of results; 2 page poster replaced with 4 page paper. http://bit.ly/VUlA3q     
    
    
    Tufte's 2006 PPT hate letter blames both Shuttle disasters on good engineers who are bad at visual communication. http://amzn.to/VbJCY8     
    
    
    2013 marks the 20th anniversary that friends and I in Glasgow University set up our first web site. I'm getting old :)    
    
    
    @madereal My first (and only) skydive was about 25 years ago. Seriously you've done 400? Wow!    
    
    
    How doctors search for images used in research/teaching. The publisher's giving the article for free this week; odd. http://www.emeraldinsight.com/fwd.htm?id=aob&ini=aob&doi=10.1108/00012531311297186 …    
    
    
    Nice interview with Amit Singhal (Google search chief) in the Guardian today http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2013/jan/19/google-search-knowledge-graph-singhal-interview …    
    
    
    Use correlations carefully. If you don't, papers like this may come along to destroy you and your work http://bit.ly/azFNE6 #in #fb    
    
    
    "What Davis discovered is that ... big journals are big and small journals are small" http://bit.ly/azFNE6 ouch! #in #fb    
    
    
    Nice little puff piece on an IBM sentiment analysis system for the Australian Tennis Open http://www.theage.com.au/it-pro/business-it/game-set-and-media-20130123-2d5rs.html …    
    
    
    Large UK governemnt research investment focuses on big data infrastructure http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2013-01/24/government-science-spending …    
    
    
    @SIGIR2013 @2run6gap This link has the current time in UTC-12 http://bit.ly/ykIozK     
    
    
    Odd error from a good journal: they published 2 versions of the same paper. If you cite the paper use this version http://shar.es/CKNAL     
    
    
    New ClueWeb12 collection is out: should allow tweet-web linking. 32Tb uncompressed http://bit.ly/WUsg66     
    
    
    Microsoft says I'm IR's 5th best author. These rankings change so often I can likely only celebrate for today http://bit.ly/WzRPde     
    
    
    @delsweil @leifos in my case, at least, the position is a mathematical flaw I think.    
    
    
    Not until today did I realise that my approach to research has parallels with the building of an Alien costume head http://www.wired.com/design/2013/02/under-the-gun/ …    
    
    
    What you always suspected: best conference papers are very rarely most cited conference papers; link from @mjpost http://arnetminer.org/conferencebestpapers#anchor_ACL%20(Natural%20Language%20Processing) …    
    
    
    "dark social": all interaction (e.g., phone, face-to-face) we can't scrape.... yet #cscwsmqa #cscw2013 from @anneohirsch    
    
    
    Patent Retrieval, a major new review just published in FnTIR http://dx.doi.org/10.1561/1500000027 …    
    
    
    @AndreaWiggins That effect turns up often http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1743569 … The great papers are often those that not everyone wants to accept.    
    
    
    Map the cultures in your city by tweets http://www.buzzfeed.com/mbvd/astonishing-map-of-tweets-by-language-in-new-york … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    CIKM 2015 will be in Melbourne. Always nice to have a high ranking international conference you can cycle to.    
    
    
    Want a job? Learn to code http://www.siliconrepublic.com/careers/item/31716-grand-coalition-for-digital … via @siliconrepublic    
    
    
    Users navigate folders to get files instead of searching for them as it is cognitively easier http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007%2Fs00779-012-0544-z?LI=true …    
    
    
    Anyone got this paper "Snippet Search: a Single Phrase Approach to Text Access" with all the figures in? Online versions are text only.    
    
    
    Google: Keep Google Reader Running. I use it all the time, sign the petition to keep it going. https://www.change.org/petitions/google-keep-google-reader-running?share_id=vDqdbmsQYz&utm_campaign=action_box&utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=share_petition&utm_source=share_petition&utm_medium=twitter … via @change    
    
    
    Read the intro to Quantum Models of Cognition & Decision, a theory book for non-theoreticians. Is this a first? :) http://www.amazon.com/dp/110701199X/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_XPArrb0A0R9H4 …    
    
    
    Little noisy in the house, put the head phones on and sink into the ambient bliss that is @birdsongradio    
    
    
    "40 percent of Twitter’s traffic during peak usage is about television", fascinating article in Wired http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/03/nielsen-family-is-dead/ …    
    
    
    Details of the first Asian Summer School in Information Access are out, looks good. https://www.dropbox.com/s/lm47bwfes8h378k/assia2013_cfp_en_20130318.txt …    
    
    
    That's all my main AC reviews done for @SIGIR2013    
    
    
    Always sad to see someone from the IR community go; sorry to hear about 
Kees Koster's death.
 http://www.ru.nl/icis/news/memoriam-kees-koster/ …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @leifos Did Yashar have an answer to Ian's question? It's a good one to ask.    
    
    
    Got an IR evaluation paper? EVIA 2013 has extended its CFP deadline http://research.nii.ac.jp/ntcir/evia2013/     
    
    
    Asian IR conference call for papers is out http://www.colips.org/conference/airs2013/ … deadline late June, conference in Singapore.    
    
    
    The call for the string processing conference, SPIRE is also out http://u.cs.biu.ac.il/~porately/spire2013/ …    
    
    
    I'm giving a talk next week entitled "Twenty years of web search – where to next?" Not too hard a topic then :) http://www.cse.unsw.edu.au/~apweb2013/detailedprogram.html#k3 …    
    
    
    @leifos @ecir2013 There was a SIGIR 2010 paper on this topic from Filip Radlinski... I think.    
    
    
    @pogil @leifos @ecir2013 Cool Paul, is there a paper to go with your industry talk?    
    
    
    Ever played the 1980s Hobbit adventure game with its cool NLP interaction? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Hobbit_%281982_video_game%29 … Its author gave a talk at RMIT today.    
    
    
    No luck with #sigir2013 this year, can't complain about the reviews though, good points, helpful suggestions    
    
    
    #sigir2013 says 366 papers were submitted this year, it was 483 in 2012, 545 in 2011, 520 in 2010. Was this a typo? If not, I'm worried.    
    
    
    Using tweets to detect earthquakes, nice journal version http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/articleDetails.jsp?arnumber=6152108 … of the original WWW paper http://wwwconference.org/proceedings/www2010/www/p851.pdf …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai Congratulations, any chance of a pre-print?    
    
    
    Google's Alon Halevy speaking at RMIT, suggesting that "data philanthropy" is good for organizations to do (subject to privacy of course)    
    
    
    @smfrogers @CraigDButt Alon had your #Guardian maps front and centre in his presentation, said lots of nice things about them.    
    
    
    Alon Halevy opened his RMIT talk stating that Melbourne has the best coffee in the world. The audience took this rather well.    
    
    
    Fan of NTCIR? Leave a message for Noriko to celebrate the 10th running of this event http://bit.ly/14QJ42X     
    
    
    @CraigDButt @ScienceMoJo someone at the #alonhalevy talk was uploading slides to a blog, any idea where they might be?    
    
    
    The #nicta #alonhalevy talk at RMIT is online, starts 10 minutes in http://echo.lcs.rmit.edu.au:8080/ess/echo/presentation/b7b814c2-31de-448f-b593-a45c09a7a3b5 … @CraigDButt @ScienceMoJo    
    
    
    Read "Simple and Usable Web, Mobile, and Interaction Design" http://www.amazon.com/dp/0321703545/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_11Gzrb1KJZ7W2 … some say it's too simplistic, to me that's its strength    
    
    
    #sigir2014 website is up http://sigir.org/sigir2014/     
    
    
    Moredetail on the #alonhalevy #rmit #nicta talk including slides from here http://raws.adc.rmit.edu.au/~X04508/blog2/?p=453 …    
    
    
    Nice illustration of the need to share data in research, but also the importance of encouraging replication studies http://www.nextnewdeal.net/rortybomb/researchers-finally-replicated-reinhart-rogoff-and-there-are-serious-problems#.UW348c6qE6Q.twitter …    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Agreed, another lesson is remember one paper is just one data point, wait for more points before you act.    
    
    
    FnTIR published 21 papers, the highest 
h Google Scholar can give FnTIR is 21, is h ideal for ranking journals? http://www.nowpublishers.com/journals/Foundations%20and%20Trends%C2%AE%20in%20Information%20Retrieval/7 … …    
    
    
    One year job in Sheffield University, Developing a Taxonomy of Search Sessions. Funded by Google. https://jobs.shef.ac.uk/sap/bc/webdynpro/sap/hrrcf_a_posting_apply?PARAM=cG9zdF9pbnN0X2d1aWQ9NTE1MEM2NjM0OTlEMTNDQ0UxMDAwMDAwOEZBN0ZEMTgmY2FuZF90eXBlPUVYVA%3d%3d&sap-client=400&sap-language=EN&sap-accessibility=X&sap-ep-themeroot=%2fSAP%2fPUBLIC%2fBC%2fUR%2fuos …    
    
    
    "User Perception of Search Task Differentiation" accepted at #evia2013, which is part of #ntcir10    
    
    
    @jteevan @ian_soboroff Is Matt Crane's life rich enough for a full day tutorial about him? Half day & I'd sign up. http://www.sigir2013.ie/tutorials.html     
    
    
    Google beat competitors with search snippets http://diegobasch.com/a-relevant-tale-how-google-killed-inktomi … Often wondered if this paper got Google going http://www.seg.rmit.edu.au/mark/publications/my_papers/SIGIR98.pdf …    
    
    
    Interested in sessions for searching? Starting thinking about multi-screen sessions http://www.mobify.com/blog/the-new-multi-screen-world-understanding-consumer-behaviour/ …    
    
    
    @miguelmalvarez @leifos You're sure the students didn't pee in them first?    
    
    
    Re-read Voorhees SIGIR98 paper on test collections: intra-system comparisons almost unaffected by assessor error http://bit.ly/dWXUHj #fb    
    
    
    Table 1 of this paper concisely compares 9 different ways to evaluate IR systems http://bit.ly/ev9jfH #fb    
    
    
    @leifos @iFromm Mixed with a fine Cola I'm sure it will be fine :)    
    
    
    #statsnerd Geometric mean on IR results, for significance this paper say to test on the log of the data. Correct? http://link.springer.com/article/10.3758%2FBF03204171?LI=true …    
    
    
    Find "Artificial Intelligence" confs on Google Scholar Metrics. No IJCAI! Why? 'cause ACM DL spells it artifical http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=1625535 …    
    
    
    For the next few hours, all I have eyes for is the time in San Francisco, #CIKM2013 deadline here I come https://www.google.com.au/search?q=time+san+francisco …    
    
    
    #CIKM2013, well that's the deadline gone fingers crossed for all the papers we submitted.    
    
    
    @wbc11 talking at RMIT today on the need to retrieve answers to queries, not documents.    
    
    
    There have been hints for years what the new Kinect would be able to do, finally it's (almost) here http://video.wired.com/watch/new-xbox-kinect-exclusive-wired-video-398878 …    
    
    
    We are looking for a new Full Professor at RMIT, interested? http://rmit.clients.pageup.com.au/jobDetails.asp?sJobIDs=547773&stp=unijobs&sLanguage=en …    
    
    
    Nice demo of a focussed web crawler, define desired page content and let it go... http://www.arcomem.eu/system-demos/     
    
    
    Based on cites over 2 years, FnTIR http://www.nowpublishers.com/journals/Foundations%20and%20Trends%C2%AE%20in%20Information%20Retrieval/7;jsessionid=E3EC7E8807AED4B600227FB0745A09F2 … is the 2nd best journal in Computer Science! http://www.scimagojr.com/journalrank.php?area=1700&category=0&country=all&year=2011&order=cpd&min=0&min_type=cd …    
    
    
    @lintool Thanks; ignoring all proxy judgments (i.e. impact) & re-assessing work from 1st principles has its own problems though.    
    
    
    @lintool Touche :) If one insisted on only judging by reading papers it might be hard for a faculty to take on people in new areas.    
    
    
    Cut a nine page paper to four with no real loss of clarity. Hmmm omitting needless words works. #cikm2013 poster submitted.    
    
    
    This guy is treating his Google Scholar subject categories with great care: #1 in red wine, cars and travel :) http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?user=uFrX4KMAAAAJ&hl=en …    
    
    
    @mdr Thanks for sharing "Click model-based IR metrics", fantastic analysis of evaluation measures http://bit.ly/10bEd6h  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Great high level review of sentiment analysis research: what's been done where the challenges are http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/4/162501-techniques-and-applications-for-sentiment-analysis/fulltext#.Uaqz7PO9nTs.twitter …    
    
    
    Design chips to make tollerable errors and save huge amounts in energy consumption, what a cool idea http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/4/162511-inexact-design/fulltext#.Uaq1JFoNIo4.twitter …    
    
    
    Using cell phones or accessing the internet hands&eyes free while driving is more dangerous than law makers think http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/4/162505-the-problem-with-hands-free-dashboard-cellphones/abstract …    
    
    
    Got half an hour? This is a good overview of data analytics research with cool examples of what can be done http://youtu.be/xNkUbdt12oE     
    
    
    Beall's List of Predatory Publishers: one man's view of places to avoid publishing in. Very extensive http://scholarlyoa.com/2012/12/06/bealls-list-of-predatory-publishers-2013/ …    
    
    
    58008? No more! A self-censoring calculator, what a great silly idea @jamesthomson had (4 years ago). http://www.dragthing.com/blog/2009/09/pcalc-prevents-iphone-profanity/ …    
    
    
    To reduce false positive & negative rates in significance tests for IR, use more queries, use multi-test adjustments http://boytsov.info/pubs/sigir2013.pdf …    
    
    
    I see the summer weather in northern Europe is rubbish again. Did I mention that RMIT is hiring?    
    
    
    Enjoyed this quick read on effective features for classifying tweets http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.170.3278&rep=rep1&type=pdf … @amoszhou of interest?    
    
    
    Should've read this years ago: exploiting social networks for better collaborative filtering: data set available too http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/download?doi=10.1.1.152.9364&rep=rep1&type=pdf …    
    
    
    I'm a new associate editor of IEEE #TKDE, remember this journal for your IR papers, a strong broad venue http://www.computer.org/portal/web/tkde     
    
    
    @SalhaAlzahrani I don't know the circumstances of such a decision but it can happen.    
    
    
    Goodbye winter, off to sunny Tokyo to attend, #ntcir10, #evia2013 and then #assia2013    
    
    
    Hard core IR evaluation nerditry at #evia2013... Tetsuya Sakai speaking about the lack of reusability of diversity test collections.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai shows condensed retrieval rank measures (ignore unjudged) seem more accurate, than conventional raw list measures #evia2013    
    
    
    Charlie Clarke: approximate graded relevance judgements with aggregated multiple binary nugget judgements #evia2013    
    
    
    Getting qrels cheaply by splitting topic into sub-topics & merging search results. Sounds a bit like trels from an old CIKM paper #evia2013    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries @ian_soboroff can you remember? I think they were merging sets, or was it some sort of ranked list merging?    
    
    
    Hideo Joho giving #ntcir10 overview. Glad to see chronological evaluation run this time: measuring improvements over previous NTCIRs.    
    
    
    Key message from the Google keynote at #ntcir10: eliminate the SERP.    
    
    
    Every available socket used at #ntcir10 pic.twitter.com/LtKMkhhhtY    
    
    
    Cross link poster session at #ntcir10: link first then translate or translate first then link? The former approach seemed better.    
    
    
    Got the last green tea Kit Kat before @claclarke keynote. pic.twitter.com/FhW3FbgMv9    
    
    
    Great #ntcir10, right now the Math Search Engine task overview: formula search, as well as formula and text search.    
    
    
    #ntcir10 medical search task. They sidestepped data privacy issues by hiring doctors to write fabricated records: 30 bucks a record.    
    
    
    "Evaluating the performance of IR systems using test collections" published online in Information Research http://informationr.net/ir/18-2/paper582.html#.UcJMv_lmim5 …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Thanks, much appreciated    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I am IR "The Power" Oldie :)    
    
    
    #ntcir10 #1CLICK2 session: Twente group presenting a system that in a decent experiment showed users prefered their system over Google    
    
    
    #ntcir10 #1CLICK2 Twente group were comparing with pre-knowledge graph Google    
    
    
    #ntcir10 A presentation with "abject failure" in the title: Berkeley shows a bag of words approach for math formula search doesn't work.    
    
    
    #assia2013 I'm learning here too: @iadh saying that Bill Cooper (not Robertson) was the first to propose the probability ranking principle.    
    
    
    #assia2013 Nice overview of retrieval models from @iadh, he really knows his stuff.    
    
    
    #assia2013 Doug Oard, telling us that Chinese is the best language to do IR in: little or no morphology.    
    
    
    #assia2013 @fdiaz_msr web search engines estimate the probability of relevance, given a query, a document, and user feedback.    
    
    
    #assia2013 @fdiaz_msr: when gathering relevant judgements vary the ways retrieved documents are shown to assessors    
    
    
    #assia2013 @fdiaz_msr: showing how web crawling responds to breaking new stories by gathering web content from social media    
    
    
    #assia2013 Doug Oard very entertainingly teaching us about the incredible challenges of search in E-Discovery    
    
    
    Last night's #assia2013 banquet. pic.twitter.com/8sq5GhDfbK    
    
    
    @leifos @tetsuyasakai With that sort of vision, you will go far young man.    
    
    
    Often said that Robertson's PRP paper ignored diversity, but in Sections 5&6 he discusses this very matter http://bit.ly/eMvOoj #fb #in    
    
    
    Diane Kelly's FnTIR interactive evaluation book, Japanese version (translated by Hideo Joho & Noriko Kando) pic.twitter.com/cEiJzVkISc    
    
    
    @alexbowe Thank you, unfortunately I'm leaving Tokyo now, I've met some super smart people & discussed great research ideas, I'll be back.    
    
    
    #assia2013 love the summer school group photo with the proud instigator down on the left; well done Hideo http://www.tsukuba.ac.jp/wp-content/uploads/d8cee0cb8b5f6b8854e57798577b84b11.jpg …    
    
    
    #assia2013 not sure the other lecturers were too interested in what @fdiaz_msr was saying at that time :) http://joho.slis.tsukuba.ac.jp/sites/default/files/IMGP0718.JPG …    
    
    
    Speech recognition and image classification getting much better thanks to deep learning, nice intro here http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/6/164601-deep-learning-comes-of-age/fulltext#.UctiQs6rpK0.twitter …    
    
    
    @fdiaz_msr All joking aside your web search talk at #assia2013 was the best presentation there.    
    
    
    A paper took >18 months to be accepted by my journal (cue complaints), thing is 11 of those months the journal waited for author revisions    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff 2 review rounds + 3 revisions = 18. When people say the journal process is slow, remember it might not be due to reviewers    
    
    
    @gingdottwit sorry no clues.    
    
    
    @VINOD_8055 I very much enjoyed the #yahoosummerschool two years ago, thank you for your kind words.    
    
    
    @gingdottwit I always fall for this sort of joke, my bad ;) but hey MySpace is coming back http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2013/06/myspace-goes-mobile/ …    
    
    
    "everybody expects search to read their minds” Improving search on the beautifully simple new gov.uk web site http://digital.cabinetoffice.gov.uk/2013/06/11/improving-site-search-on-gov-uk/ …    
    
    
    #sigmod in 2015 in Melbourne? I hear a rumour...    
    
    
    @AlanCoffee Thanks, then for certain #sigmod Melbourne 2015 and same place, same year #cikm.    
    
    
    @AlanCoffee There is discussion to see if the ACM MM and ACM CIKM can be set on close dates so you can get 2 great confs in one trip.    
    
    
    RMIT CS in the world's top 100 http://www.topuniversities.com/university-rankings/university-subject-rankings/2013/computer-science-and-information-systems … we're hiring at all levels including possible multi-year teaching relief, interested?    
    
    
    RMIT IR group read this paper today http://sifaka.cs.uiuc.edu/~qmei2/pub/wsdm08-entropy.pdf … an odd read, but nice use of entropy to analyse query logs.    
    
    
    Back then, "got it from the library" sounded reliable. Today we say "got it from a search engine", fast, free, easy, yes, but reliable?    
    
    
    Web search engines are 20 years old, #SIGIR2013 marks this anniversary with a panel on day 1 of the main program http://sigir2013.ie/programme.html     
    
    
    @lmichelbacher They've got the creator of the first web search engine, Jumpstation, plus people from Google, Yahoo and Bing    
    
    
    "Information Retrieval for E-Discovery" review article from FnTIR is out http://dx.doi.org/10.1561/1500000025 … #ediscovery    
    
    
    Google scholar metrics updated: top IR venues WWW, SIGIR, JASIST, WSDM, CIKM. ECIR now listed, any venues missing?http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?hl=en&view_op=search_venues&vq=%22AIRS%22+OR+%22WWW%22+OR+%22information+retrieval%22+OR+%22Information+and+Knowledge+Management%22+OR+%22SIGIR%22+OR+%22information+science+and+technology%22+OR+%22web+search%22+OR+%22TOIS%22+OR+%22information+processing+%26+Management%22 …    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald I'm submitting there next week :)    
    
    
    Ticket, passport, cocktail dress: @jteevan is ready for #SIGIR2013 #FancyAcademics    
    
    
    @gingdottwit @sigirf You're welcome :) missing you all down here in Australia.    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai Good luck with the reason for your disappearance, we'll keep some letters free for your later evaluation papers :)    
    
    
    @iadh Ask him why of all the cities in Australia to could have moved back to, he chose Canberra :)    
    
    
    Great summary of #sigir2013 from @dtunkelang Search: What's Cooking in the Lab | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130805134105-50510-search-what-s-cooking-in-the-lab …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai You need to invent more measures with vowels. I can't make an anagram out of what you have created so far :)    
    
    
    Google research award for my RMIT colleagues Jamie Thom and Timos Sellis. Project is on search of table data in scientific papers.    
    
    
    @tafanor I'll get the guys to contact you    
    
    
    The list of successful Google grants is now up, RMIT the only Australian Uni to get money this time I think http://services.google.com/fh/files/blogs/googlefras-aug2013.pdf …    
    
    
    @IR_oldie For some reason that link from Google broke, awards listed here http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/08/google-research-awards-summer-2013.html …    
    
    
    Looking at CVs for a job, one person forgot to hide track changes before sending the document, does not make a good impression.    
    
    
    Shocked to hear about @HCIR_GeneG passing: met once, tweeted often, always enjoyed reading his papers: XLibris a particular favorite.    
    
    
    @eelstretching Very good question, it crossed my mind also, I'm trusting the earlier tweets I saw are correct, but I think they are.    
    
    
    The web is still bow tie shaped http://www2012.wwwconference.org/proceedings/nocompanion/wwwwebsci2012_metaxas.pdf …    
    
    
    More about @HCIR_GeneG and his life http://genegolovchinsky.blogspot.com/2013/08/funeral-service.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The cloud isn't the solution for everyone http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/08/memsql-and-amazon/ …    
    
    
    Obituary for @HCIR_GeneG from @CACMmag http://cacm.acm.org/news/167019-gene-golovchinsky-1965-2013/fulltext … #CACM    
    
    
    2015 will be Australian data management year: SIGMOD, KDD, & CIKM will all be in Australia that year. Book your Aussie sabbatical now.    
    
    
    It's better than I thought: in Australia, in 2015, the top conferences will be SIGMOD, KDD, ACM Multimedia and CIKM.    
    
    
    The CORE CS conference rating list is up. CORE is looking for feedback on the list and the ratings http://core.edu.au/index.php/categories/conference%20rankings/1 …    
    
    
    @alexk_z They know it's not perfect, some changes are coming soon, for other errors, contact them.    
    
    
    NTCIR, the Japanese information access evaluation exercise has a kick off meeting in Tokyo coming soon http://research.nii.ac.jp/ntcir/ntcir-11/kickoff.html …    
    
    
    Hands free search for QA, adapting speech recognition out to recognize questions http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2013/7/165477-information-distance-between-what-i-said-and-what-it-heard/fulltext …    
    
    
    (from last year) Mobile Use in Developing Nations Skyrockets, it will be smartphones next http://bit.ly/QUBiPF     
    
    
    BBC News - Jonathon Fletcher: forgotten father of the search engine http://bbc.in/1dEn9An     
    
    
    @iFromm Here's thing thing: Fletcher didn't want to do a PhD in IR, he wasn't aware that Glasgow did IR :) He wanted to study graphics.    
    
    
    Few women in CS or science in general? The reasons are complex and not fully understood http://nyti.ms/17Fbuiw     
    
    
    Historians using IR systems for their research, we say "keyword search", they say "distant reading" http://youtu.be/tp4y-_VoXdA  via @youtube    
    
    
    Why are the impact factors of CS journals low? A lack of conference citation coverage might be a reason. http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2240256#.Ui02KYdmFug.twitter …    
    
    
    IBM's Watson move from winning Jeopardy to providing specialized medical search systems http://www.techrepublic.com/article/ibm-watson-the-inside-story-of-how-the-jeopardy-winning-supercomputer-was-born-and-what-it-wants-to-do-next/ …    
    
    
    The A/B Test: evolution of ideas vs. the intelligent design of them? Evolution mostly wins unless you're Steve Jobs http://www.wired.com/business/2012/04/ff_abtesting/ …    
    
    
    Watson won Jeopardy, it's AI but not the logical AI I did at Uni 20 years ago: NLP, QA, IR & lots of ML http://nyti.ms/if24iQ #fb    
    
    
    TREC IR test collections ranked by reliability. Much variation, some collections so noisy they may be unusable http://julian-urbano.info/publications/055-measurement-test-collection-reliability …    
    
    
    Hand and eyes free search: we are looking for a post doc who is interested in working on this topic at RMIT http://iroldie.blogspot.com.au/2013/09/post-doc-job-opportunity-at-rmit.html …    
    
    
    @iadh @ian_soboroff The TREC web site is down http://trec.nist.gov/  thanks US government shutdown    
    
    
    Dave Hawking has left FunnelBack and is joining Microsoft Bing. Going to be based in Canberra.    
    
    
    Never put my publications in BibTeX, but I need to now. Two scripts to scrape from DBLP and I'm done, nice of them to do it for me #fb    
    
    
    More on the CS conference vs journal debate; rejection rates a poor indicator of citation impact http://bit.ly/dB4MEp #fb #in    
    
    
    Australian Computer Scientists showcasing their research in Melbourne on Tuesday. Free event, come along. #nicta http://nicta.com.au/events/event_repository/upcoming_events/victorian_innovation_and_technology_showcase …    
    
    
    Be careful what you infer from averages http://wp.sigmod.org/?p=960     
    
    
    Great day for IR research in Melbourne, 4 ARC grants awarded: 3 to RMIT, 1 to Uni. Melbourne; much celebration on Friday.    
    
    
    Ingenious paper: exploits academic misconduct to learn if journal impact factors influence citation. Answer? They do http://arxiv.org/ftp/arxiv/papers/0908/0908.3177.pdf …    
    
    
    @traintalk Thanks, I'll take a look at that.    
    
    
    A Q&A session detailing background to IBM's Watson; surely Watson itself should answer these questions? http://bit.ly/gflPIa #fb    
    
    
    @traintalk read that paper you suggested, thanks. Search engines and social media over coming the tyranny of the impact factor? :)    
    
    
    @traintalk Wonderful academic anarchy :)    
    
    
    @traintalk Thanks for the pointer, no I hadn't seen that tweet before.    
    
    
    "User Perception of Information Credibility of News on Twitter" accepted as short paper to #ecir2014    
    
    
    Big data defined by 3 Vs: velocity, variety, volume. At Sydney big data conference, everyone wants to add more, veracity, my favourite.    
    
    
    ACM 2013 fellows has a number of IR people on it: Steve Robertson, @Yoellem Jon Kleinberg http://www.acm.org/press-room/news-releases/2013/fellows-2013 …    
    
    
    Very excited to announce that an RMIT CS professor is now an ACM fellow http://www.acm.org/press-room/news-releases/2013/fellows-2013 … Many congratulations Timos Sellis    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Gosh, yes you're right, I missed Marti and Christine, thanks for pointing that out.    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Ingemar Cox for image search too.    
    
    
    #sigir2013 won best organised international conference. Congratulations to its general chairs @ParaicS and Gareth http://www.cngl.ie/cngl-wins-iapco-international-conference-award/ …    
    
    
    @NTCIR tracks are looking for participants. There are some really cool tasks going on there. http://research.nii.ac.jp/ntcir/ntcir-11/tasks.html …    
    
    
    "The 2012 Greek bailout: a €146bn bond renegotiation was completed using iPads", the PC is dying out and quickly http://www.theguardian.com/technology/2013/dec/19/why-tablets-killing-pc-ipad-apple-microsoft …    
    
    
    "A temporal analysis of emoticon use in Swedish, Italian, German
and English", why the heck not? :) http://bit.ly/bxiElY #fb #in    
    
    
    "Debugging relevance" Enterprise search article warning against over use of test collections http://bit.ly/eMOYtr #fb    
    
    
    Submitted a paper to JASIST <3 weeks ago, got the decision today with good quality reviews; that's how to run a journal #fb    
    
    
    Users sometimes click web search results because the summary looks good even if the document is not relevant http://bit.ly/dZEkZt #fb #in    
    
    
    Google Scholar updated its citation data in the last few days, but many errors there now: 2008 paper cited in 1994? Errrm...    
    
    
    Google Scholar spam. Ike Antkare's h is 99: 99 pubs cited 99 times in his 99 papers http://bit.ly/dULis9 http://bit.ly/dG3UT2 #fb    
    
    
    @leitang I agree, what's surprising to me is that they haven't fixed this quickly, people there know about this problem.    
    
    
    7 principles of scamming people & their role in computer security: CACM http://bit.ly/ecwnCs & free version http://bit.ly/gmwPjE #fb #in    
    
    
    How to introduce link, content & duplicate spam into Google Scholar http://bit.ly/fQY1Cz    
    
    
    Craig Mundie demoed a pre-alpha buggy Kinect chat application. Described surface 2 that will detect touch & hover http://bit.ly/iaL0Ox    
    
    
    Google spell correction is outstanding, Google Chrome spell correction is rubbish... how come?    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald would it kill them to import a bit more of the spell correction library into Chrome code?    
    
    
    I missed the announcement back in November, but I see that ACM finally has RSS feeds for all its journals and conferences. #fb    
    
    
    Who needs test collections? Crowd Flower now offering a dedicated search relevance service http://bit.ly/hZXD80 #fb    
    
    
    Do MTurkers lie about where they are based? Some do, most don't http://bit.ly/hS1o0K    
    
    
    I'm not the only one seeing this Google Scholar citation count bug http://bit.ly/h68DVz #fb    
    
    
    Two #sigir2011 papers accepted for the RMIT IR group.    
    
    
    Sounds like the IRF is short of money; they are shutting down their supercomputing infrastructure end of April.    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries Thanks, hope you had some #sigir2011 success too.    
    
    
    Under 50% of our research ideas, to improve systems, work out. Evaluate quickly to spot the good ones http://bit.ly/eyqWVv #fb    
    
    
    What 2009 journal had the most citations/article in all of CS? Foundations & Trends in Information Retrieval http://bit.ly/mgGKwR    
    
    
    Efthimis Efthimiadis died. I read his research my whole career. He was always charming and generous. Sympathies to Jagoda & Nicolas.    
    
    
    The toponym resolution research review of @jochenleidner PhD thesis is outstanding, Jochen, any chance it can go online for others to see?    
    
    
    Volunteers do a good job; workers paid well do a better job; workers paid poorly do a worse job than volunteers http://bit.ly/iCnxw4 #fb    
    
    
    @jochenleidner a paper on your resolution review really would be cool, looking forward to it.    
    
    
    @ipeirotis Thanks for pointing that out.    
    
    
    Thanks to pointer from @SadeghKharazmi, now following Google's new Search blog, http://bit.ly/k9gOEI    
    
    
    For every 100 print books Amazon sells (paper & hard back), it sells 105 eBooks http://bit.ly/mw59rd is the book finally dying?    
    
    
    Analysis of 1/2 a million passwords that confirms many anecdotes: we reuse & forget passwords a lot http://bit.ly/dOi7id #in    
    
    
    (Geeks only) Search result fusion using inter-rank document similarity. Works mostly, tough baselines used http://bit.ly/fZQBU8 #fb #in    
    
    
    Health care professionals searching for images, do they use fancy resources? Yes, but mostly they use Google http://bit.ly/k8EuLy #fb #in    
    
    
    Cognitive skills tests & search experience predict how effective people are at finding relevant documents http://bit.ly/ll8iNC #fb #in    
    
    
    Our SIGIR paper describing our work to devise session-based evaluation measures http://bit.ly/l4dBYO #fb #in    
    
    
    Gold standard data is used to test MTurker quality; seems to be necessary with test collection assessors too http://bit.ly/iCIRuc #fb #in    
    
    
    Is this the first ever notable IR conference in the gulf region? http://www.uowdubai.ac.ae/airs2011/ #fb in    
    
    
    Empirical results trump HIPPOs (Highest Paid Person's Opinion): great read, longer paper better http://bit.ly/ip1ybB #fb #in    
    
    
    Good follow up to HiPPO paper, includes warning against using standard significance tests http://bit.ly/lG1epN #fb #in    
    
    
    "Communicate, persuade, be interesting" I like this guide to giving good academic talks http://bit.ly/mk0XYt #fb #in    
    
    
    A student helping with some lectures suggested we drop 'Web 2.0' from the slides "it's so old fashioned", she said. #fb #in    
    
    
    Great week at Yahoo! IR summer school: great place, great students. Shown this article on it #yheducool #fb #in http://twitpic.com/5h6qg0    
    
    
    I thought the digital divide was a symptom of economic inequality, it's more than that http://www.zdnet.com.au/innovation-to-adoption-the-real-digital-divide-339317394.htm … via @zdnetaustralia #fb #in    
    
    
    Update to Google ranking algorithm. Page relevance & quality seem to measure cross site user interaction http://bit.ly/iF4nov  #fb #in    
    
    
    The Yahoo! IR summer school lecturers happy despite their wardrobe faux pas. http://bit.ly/mhYOZC  #fb #in    
    
    
    Advances in speech recognition summarized clearly (CACM 2004). A graph for IR should exist, but doesn't #in http://twitpic.com/5kfexc    
    
    
    Harry Potter the movie, book or game? Knowing what the user intends in their query matters. Thx Yuda 4 this http://bit.ly/iYqGhc  #fb #in    
    
    
    @michaeltwofish Great! Are you volunteering to run this?    
    
    
    RefSeer recommends citations for a paper. Good idea, so-so suggestions when I tested it.  http://jochenleidner.posterous.com/refseer-automatically-recommending-papers-you … via @jochenleidner #fb #in    
    
    
    Bland & Altman's stats articles are great & concise, this one on multiple significance tests is no exception http://1.usa.gov/kJacYT  #fb #in    
    
    
    New RMIT PhD "Effective retrieval to support learning" now available on-line http://bit.ly/j3xHnO  #in    
    
    
    CrowdLogger: building a collective query log. Last attempt failed; this has more privacy; will you install it? http://bit.ly/m676LX  #fb #in    
    
    
    Call for papers for an up coming evaluation workshop (EVIA 2011) in Tokyo to be run at NTCIR http://bit.ly/oTusiJ  #fb #in    
    
    
    A set of slides and the full PDF of my IR evaluation review paper is now available online http://bit.ly/n336AB  #fb #in    
    
    
    (Long) Fascinating article about Stuxnet and how it was dis-assembled http://bit.ly/n6EIVX  #fb #in    
    
    
    "Sharing Detailed Research Data Is Associated with Increased Citation Rate", paper's title says it all http://bit.ly/9PPfiz #fb #in    
    
    
    New large scale review and tutorial on summarization published in FnTIR http://bit.ly/mRMTlZ  #fb #in    
    
    
    Open data is not enough. Calling for education to teach how to exploit the data sets governments are producing http://www.wired.com/magazine/2011/06/st_essay_datafireworks/ … #fb #in    
    
    
    @falahmari I agree, however, all of this effort won't help unless we work out how to get the public to use & exploit these cool services.    
    
    
    @falahmari Definitely, I'll see you at Tiger on Thursday we can set a time then.    
    
    
    How to rank high on Google? Get people to hate you. http://nyti.ms/e0PuAl Potential for sentiment analysis in web search    
    
    
    Google Scholar Citations, create your own scholar publication home page; this is going to be big http://bit.ly/pTM27v  #fb #in    
    
    
    NTCIR-9 tracks are up: diversity, entailment, geo-temporal search, interactive IR, etc http://bit.ly/ct5Sdh    
    
    
    The Australian IR conference, ADCS is coming soon http://bit.ly/qL2FuV  Are retro web sites now in fashion? #adcs2011 #in    
    
    
    "The approach is so simple that it may not merit a paper", 264 citations later; BM25F, yes it's simple http://bit.ly/ptM70t  #fb #in    
    
    
    If you count iPads as notebooks/laptops, then Apple now dominates the market http://bit.ly/rrozFq  #fb #in    
    
    
    Why do journal papers take so long to review? I invited 7 reviewers 6 said no. Oh well back to Google Scholar to search for more... #fb #in    
    
    
    @dtunkelang Hey Daniel, what's the timezone for the August 14th deadline, is it the usual one: Samoa?    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @dtunkelang Is there anything west of Samoa? :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @dtunkelang Of course here it's winter and it's late on Monday afternoon, go figure.    
    
    
    Companies have 1 big IT problem: how to store & understand the data deluge from ever more devices & services http://bbc.in/oJqL4L  #fb #in    
    
    
    Ike Antkare: the fake person used to spam Google Scholar: his h was 99 now it's 0. Is Scholar spam checking? http://bit.ly/dULis9  #fb #in    
    
    
    @thesiswhisperer Thanks for the mention :)    
    
    
    Watching Graeme Hirst talk about detecting Alzheimer's in Agatha Christie's novels, promising preliminary results #fb #in    
    
    
    Ever wanted to read four grumpy old men complain (briefly) about evaluation of search engines? Click here http://bit.ly/qhn4f8  #fb #in    
    
    
    A nice summary from Google on how they roll out changes to their search engine http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2011/08/another-look-under-hood-of-search.html?spref=tw … #fb #in    
    
    
    @diazf_y Sorry, I'm being dim, comment on what?    
    
    
    @diazf_y I get you. The commercial focus on high quality evaluation pushes search engines to innovate in ways academia hasn't thought of    
    
    
    Papers in open access journals get higher citation rates compared to journals that charge for access http://bit.ly/pTeI3L  #fb #in    
    
    
    Very comprehensive and impressive set of slides on IR evaluation from Evangelos, Ben and Emine http://bit.ly/pjofTu  #fb #in    
    
    
    Great stat: buy a lottery ticket, you have more chance of dying before the draw than winning the jackpot http://bbc.in/nlmuSG  #fb #in    
    
    
    @jerepick @diazf_y Yes that's a factor, but I don't think that's all, evaluation seems to be valued higher than I see in academia.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff You need something to read during the hurricane don't you?    
    
    
    RMIT 3 year research fellowships. They'll be competitive, but why not apply so you can join the RMIT IR group http://bit.ly/qfzXzA  #fb #in    
    
    
    Stop word removal? That's so last century, stop structure removal is where it's at http://bit.ly/nHPz7U  #fb #in    
    
    
    @noiano No, proceedings will be behind ACM DL's pay wall. But most authors put their papers online & Google Scholar finds those links.    
    
    
    Today I looked at 5 social networks (Twitter FB Yammer LinkedIn & G+) to see what's going on, 10 years ago I just checked my email #fb #in    
    
    
    Show users a bigger query box, they enter longer queries. Seems wrong this paper only 10 citations http://bit.ly/eEWxft #fb #in    
    
    
    Write a message encouraging longer queries from users, they do so & they  find their stuff faster http://bit.ly/f2HTdj #fb #in    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Thanks for the heads up; I'll give that paper a read.    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Hey, I enjoyed the paper. I need to follow up with the research experiment papers you cite.    
    
    
    Reading about Indri; I didn't realise that you can control the weight of PageRank as a query command http://bit.ly/pmd4XC  #fb #in    
    
    
    Table 2 of http://bit.ly/nBL1ac  only 1 group beat the baseline system. Not sure if it was a fair comparison though #fb #in    
    
    
    Product rating scores follow a J-shaped distribution, this short paper neatly explains why http://bit.ly/r7jxR3  #fb #in    
    
    
    Quickly estimate 1*2*3*4*5*6*7*8. On average people guess a lower number than if estimating 8*7*6*5*4*3*2*1 http://bit.ly/qqNYeS  #fb #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Stack overflow? Tversky didn't mention that in the paper :)    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG You're right. I think there are explanations for why people react these ways most times, just good to know they do this    
    
    
    Catching up on an old paper: measuring the minimum distance between query words consistently improves ranking http://bit.ly/qSVLnl  #in    
    
    
    Context sensitive stemming: select stems co-occurring with query, match on stem only if next to other query words http://bit.ly/pkR8rS  #in    
    
    
    #ecir2010 presentation no shows should have been dropped and spaces used for poster people    
    
    
    #ecir2010 current presentation in "semi-live" mode. Five no shows for conference so far, not the organizer's fault, but worrying...    
    
    
    #ecir2010 in my MTurk talk today I said we used direct hit, mistake, we used hit-builder.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman On the stemming? Which paper was that?    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman Hi, yes sounds a bit like the Xu & Croft paper, though with some extra features. The Yahoo one is still my favorite.    
    
    
    Cool analysis of public Facebook data: US can be split into 7 distinct cultures http://bit.ly/ckcXgJ    
    
    
    EVIA 2011: the search evaluation workshop has extended its deadline to Oct 1st - http://bit.ly/odu4Ca  #fb #in    
    
    
    New major review of automatic summarization just out http://bit.ly/o6FI7f  #fb #in    
    
    
    2 versions of a web page, 1 view all; 1 split in chunks, Google will likely send you to the view all version http://bit.ly/oSfQsB  #fb #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG The publisher lets the authors post a PDF on their web site, so there's probably a free version online.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Might be worth emailing the authors and asking for a copy then.    
    
    
    Search engines still have much room for improvement by exploiting personalization http://bit.ly/oiz92v  #fb #in    
    
    
    Another paper showing users move their mouse over search results in the same way their eyes scan the page http://bit.ly/qyULBe  #in #fb    
    
    
    This year's TREC conference had a new record of 119 participating groups. Lots in microblog and an even spread across the others.    
    
    
    @andyy it would be great if Selective Tweets could send tweets only to a pre-defined FB list. Any plans to add that?    
    
    
    Track document history and weight higher terms that survive across the revisions? Seems to work: http://bit.ly/nj137W  #in    
    
    
    Brief old paper on user satisfaction, recall & librarian ideals: http://bit.ly/cB8FIA. I'm with Cooper: recall is often a distraction.    
    
    
    Congratulations to Alan Smeaton for winning the Strix IR research award; another in a long list of worthy winners http://bit.ly/nnnEbL  #in    
    
    
    First look at the accepted #SIGIR2010 papers this year http://bit.ly/ccm3QA.    
    
    
    Chatting to a company last night, they recently dropped their contract for Google Docs as "it hadn't been improved in 2 years". #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG they seemed interested in the Microsoft tools.    
    
    
    Is this Luhn article the 1st IR paper that described document ranking? This one is from 1957 http://bit.ly/nwmOEx  #in    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Thanks. There was a Maron tech report from '58 on probability and IR, which isn't well known, but I know of nothing earlier.    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Sure I can send them to you. Is there a way to send PDFs through Twitter?    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo "Bag of words" No idea, anyone else know?    
    
    
    The FnTIR review paper on summarization can now be downloaded for free from http://bit.ly/qHHV2F  #in    
    
    
    Great page on conference poster design http://bit.ly/ni8aWB  did you know there is a Flickr group called Pimp My Poster? #fb #in    
    
    
    Old evaluation paper full of ideas: cumulative gain; ranked biased Kendall Tau; nasty maths, something for everyone: http://bit.ly/bu0hOf    
    
    
    Teaching & Learning in IR: a new book is out; includes a chapter on teaching evaluation of IR systems http://bit.ly/rd4Ifo  #in    
    
    
    JASIST is now making ultra fast paper decisions, my last two papers were decided on in less than 4 weeks!    
    
    
    ECIR 2013 (European IR conference) will be in Moscow, hosted by Yandex. ECIR has come a long way from its humble UK IR symposium origins.    
    
    
    Tried ACM Author-ize? It's a bit complicated, but it lets you put links to free downloads of your official ACM pubs http://bit.ly/r42tN9     
    
    
    Google paper showing speed of search response affects user behavior: http://bit.ly/CB7jw I wish there was more detail in the note #fb    
    
    
    It's 2 years old, but this paper showing that groupization is better than personalization, was a good read http://bit.ly/qBqYMT  #in    
    
    
    Your social & physical distance from an event, relates to your chances of searching for that event. http://bit.ly/pjMGTr  #in    
    
    
    The tentative program for NTCIR in December is out http://bit.ly/mWzrQh     
    
    
    Final #SIGIR2010 programme up http://bit.ly/bhgxfz Donna Harman one of the keynotes #fb    
    
    
    Does your test collection have the statistical power to measure small differences? Webber et al are here to help http://bit.ly/cp43Ue    
    
    
    ERR measure; relevance is dependent on other documents. ERR validated on test collection with >16K queries, Yikes! http://bit.ly/aE0dvl #fb    
    
    
    ECIR2012, our workshop on session based retrieval has been approved. Now to start working on the call for papers...    
    
    
    Thinking about ACM Author-ize. ACM has created an admittedly involved way to get FREE access to its content, that's quite something  #in    
    
    
    #adcs happens today, looks like a good programme of IR papers http://bit.ly/gUq09K #in #fb    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I very much doubt my Uni pays for ACM Author-izer, there's nothing on the ACM pages about that.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I think they want to restrict the free links to come from only one place.    
    
    
    @andrew_trotman I think the free download is a carrot to get people to sign up to and own the author pages on the ACM DL.    
    
    
    Our #SIGIR2010 paper is up http://bit.ly/9o6UCq Do user preferences & evaluation measures line up? Answer, yes, & nDCG better than P10 #fb    
    
    
    Search Logs with Relevance Judgments from Yahoo! http://bit.ly/u04Jzq  look for L18 in the list of resources #in    
    
    
    Personal info is used differently depending where u are & who u are with, obvious, but good there's a pub on this http://bit.ly/s3WuPr  #in    
    
    
    Missed the 60th anniversary of the phrase "information retrieval", First used March 29th, 1950, in opening pages http://bit.ly/boUHHn #fb    
    
    
    Great talk from @thesiswhisperer on social media & academic careers: sociology, philosophy, and post modernism, the perfect CS seminar #in    
    
    
    @thesiswhisperer of course they came in their droves, you are The Thesis Whisperer.    
    
    
    I'm all for having conferences in nice places, but these guys seem to really like doing this http://www.waset.org/  #in #fb    
    
    
    Focus groups, eye tracking, log studies; the levels of tests used by #Google before launching its new look http://bit.ly/ddP4aL #fb    
    
    
    Presented our #adcs paper http://bit.ly/gxB7Qk on relevance assessors changing their minds. Great feedback, now to explore more #in #fb    
    
    
    One of my students has been working on singing queries for music retrieval; here are some preliminary results http://bit.ly/rRjLZw  #in    
    
    
    My Google Scholar citations home page is set up http://bit.ly/tl5uQE  I have a feeling I'm going to visiting this very very often #in    
    
    
    Need to join two messy columns of text in Excel, found a fuzzy lookup add-in from MS Research http://bit.ly/tNPQlc  not perfect, but OK #in    
    
    
    Someone is celebrating TREC's 20th birthday in style :) http://twitpic.com/7fswm8     
    
    
    Where do doctors go to seek medical images for work purposes? Journals, personal collections, but mainly Google http://bit.ly/k8EuLy  #in    
    
    
    Short position paper from one of my students on evaluating personal IR systems http://bit.ly/vKiahs  #in    
    
    
    Reading old papers... found that simple acronym handling + BM25 helps you win a track at TREC http://1.usa.gov/vcIjHU  #in    
    
    
    Google maps moves indoors. If they can get the positioning to work well, this is likely to a big thing http://bit.ly/sWbpy4  #in    
    
    
    #irhistory In the old days, documents were indexed by classification codes, then Taube said "let's try words" http://bit.ly/t49cIC  #in    
    
    
    Bruce Croft set up his Google Scholar citations page http://bit.ly/sSVn8x  he's got an h of 73... I give up. #in    
    
    
    #evia2011 different assessors use very different criteria when judging community question answering systems    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai I like this paper, getting users to draw a concept map after search is a good idea. Has it been tried before? #evia2011    
    
    
    Watching Ian Soboroff presenting his talk slides from his iPhone. #evia2011    
    
    
    Enjoying Gareth Jones's presentation about MediaEval (http://www.multimediaeval.org ) at #evia2011    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai What would you call a merged CLEF and INEX? CLENEX? #evia2011    
    
    
    The #evia2011 session on CLEF, INEX, TREC, MediaEval, & FIRE, working well: 15 minutes per talk makes nicely condensed presentations    
    
    
    1300 academic papers added to medline each day! Keynote being given at #ntcir9    
    
    
    #ntcir9 in one year there were 25000 papers about one gene type.    
    
    
    #ntcir9 nice grid searching interface to help with exploratory search.    
    
    
    Great fun giving a joint talk with @wewebber at #ntcir9. Private data & reproducability of IR results got lots of feedback and questions.    
    
    
    NRBP, the kitchen sink of IR evaluation measures, every avenue covered... probably: http://bit.ly/am4Ev0    
    
    
    The OED expand its definition of the word information, they think it's quite an important word http://bit.ly/eirk45 #fb #in    
    
    
    CrowdSearch workshop at WWW. Social networks, crowd sourcing, expert finding, community search, all in one place http://bit.ly/t56ycm     
    
    
    An attempt to gather a public query log was canceled as only 200 people in the world were willing volunteers http://bit.ly/eGiwG #fb    
    
    
    Data centres don't need to be as cold as most people think they do http://bit.ly/vdRwad  #in    
    
    
    @giovannaroda I should have put that URL in the talk I was just giving    
    
    
    #IRFC paper on link between standard deviation & bounded effectiveness scores; high SD guarantees middling score http://bit.ly/96Ah14    
    
    
    Dave Hawking doing a live learning to rank demo during his keynote at #IRFC, show off #fb    
    
    
    Cool set of slides on how the design of an MTurk experiment impacts on the quality of data gathered http://bit.ly/9qN3oQ    
    
    
    Web doesn't facilitate scientific innovation - James Boyle co-creator of scientific commons. Great keynote, no notes, no PPT; #irfs2010.    
    
    
    A major IR Prof told me he's given up journal reviewing; conference reviews only now, he thinks that's where the action is #in #fb    
    
    
    @giovannaroda Is that the paper where he proposes the e measure?    
    
    
    @BrotherLogic I don't know that article, have you got a link?    
    
    
    @neelannair I think this is more a comment on the freshness of conference material and not on journal quality.    
    
    
    Pareto and crowdsourcing, many try a task, only a few provide good quality work http://bit.ly/fqIWcm #fb #in    
    
    
    "The amount of information available is becoming unmanageable", turns out this statement's always been true http://bbc.in/zFECYw  #fb #in    
    
    
    I think this is the first paper describing tf*idf weights http://bit.ly/wCjs2p  anyone know an earlier one? #in    
    
    
    Foundations & Trends in IR continues to have more cites per paper than ACM Computer Surveys! http://bit.ly/zwA0i8  #in    
    
    
    How to get your academic article read on the web - some advice I got from a publisher this week #in http://twitpic.com/888gcn     
    
    
    @siandart Hi, they didn't, there is a whole earlier section on that topic.    
    
    
    Associate Professor job in IR at RMIT http://bit.ly/wDAV00  happy to chat to anyone interested #in    
    
    
    Searching for page on how good Google is http://bit.ly/zrSpU8  these results showed there is still room for improvement http://bit.ly/zA3t3P     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff come join us :)    
    
    
    Congratulations to Lida, an RMIT ISAR student, for getting an internship at IBM's new research lab in Melbourne http://bit.ly/w50oLb  #in    
    
    
    Relevance assessors who don't understand a domain make inaccurate judgements simply looking for keyword overlap http://bit.ly/xrRRln  #in    
    
    
    Divide your h by the years since you finished your PhD, bigger number = better apparently. Finally a positive for taking ages to write up.    
    
    
    This service has a long way to go, but it's the start of something important: combining web & private content http://selnd.com/yNeqrc     
    
    
    @noiano I agree, Google say they can't add FB and Twitter because terms of use prevent Google from crawling their content.    
    
    
    1st web query log analysis (1995)? http://bit.ly/azUKeW Mentions Boston Globe article effectively saying ranked retrieval is "faulty"    
    
    
    404 page not found on Google? http://bit.ly/A5fWYQ  #in    
    
    
    45 minutes till the abstract deadline on #sigir2012, but almost no more submissions coming in. Surely not everyone is asleep?    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase Not no; at least if I've switched the system correctly, not now.    
    
    
    That's it, no longer Monday anywhere in the world, #sigir2012 abstracts are all in: 650 submitted.    
    
    
    Reviewing for novel evaluation workshops at SIGIR: SimInt2010 & CSE2010, both keen to push beyond the Cranfield approach #in    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 paper deadline? When it stops being Mon the 13th here http://bit.ly/ykIozK  that's the deadline. Good luck with your papers.    
    
    
    Read a paper that drew general conclusions about search engines based on the answers of 15 students. We're just more different than that.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 just under an hour till we switch the submission system off.    
    
    
    #swirl12 #occupymydata is the hot new idea at the Lorne meeting    
    
    
    #swirl12 Doug Oard wants an IR system that is an exoskeleton for the mind.    
    
    
    The first description of IR on a digital computer? This MIT Masters thesis is from 1951 http://bit.ly/c8zUbc  #in    
    
    
    #swirl12 photos from the meeting up online http://bit.ly/y8sb4h     
    
    
    Great talk from @JulioGonzalo1 today at RMIT. Careful analysis of evaluation measures, creating an IR specific significance test. #in    
    
    
    You always suspected, now a study confirms, users are influenced by a search engine's brand http://bit.ly/dh9uiX #in #fb    
    
    
    Stefano has blogged about #swirl12 http://bit.ly/ySULSg     
    
    
    The #sigir2010 next generation test collection workshop is apparently cancelled: lack of interest http://ir.cis.udel.edu/NGTC10/ #in    
    
    
    Some interesting stats on the state of the ICT industry in Australia, more jobs not enough graduates #in    
    
    
    Microsoft 'Illumishare' demonstrates remote physical object interaction... all sort of collaborative search possibilities.    
    
    
    It's a picture, it's a movie, it's a “Cliplet” from MSR who will take the time to do them though? http://bit.ly/zi0WG6  via @MSFTNext    
    
    
    Stack Exchange Q&A site proposal: Information Retrieval and Search Engines http://bit.ly/GLr93i     
    
    
    An economic impact report will show that a healthy chunk of money was generated through research & evaluation fostered by TREC #in #fb    
    
    
    @iFromm Yes, it should be going on the TREC site.    
    
    
    @iFromm the report is at http://trec.nist.gov/pubs/2010.economic.impact.pdf    
    
    
    The daily Google puzzles are fun, but are they experimenting on us: studying how we do complex search? http://bit.ly/Heiwh7  #in    
    
    
    Studying the physics of Angry Birds, pointlessly brilliant research, http://bit.ly/Hm3d4Z  Ig Nobel maybe?    
    
    
    Enjoying query log tutorial at #sigir2010 bit sweaty though #fb    
    
    
    Papers I should've read ages ago. http://bit.ly/Hp0ViZ  excellent early crowd sourcing paper for NLP labelling. #in    
    
    
    OpenStreetMap continues to make gains, Wikipedia using it now instead of Google Maps http://cnet.co/IwMTiS  #in    
    
    
    @asmeaton gave a great talk at RMIT, but did he visit us or come to watch the Iron Man in Melbourne that Sunday :) http://bit.ly/HQMRR7     
    
    
    Manmatha from UMass gave a great talk at RMIT on a cool algorithm he developed on fast duplicate document matching http://bit.ly/HQNBpd  #in    
    
    
    Thrilled for Lida and Jasbir getting their internships at IBM Melbourne http://bit.ly/HQO36U  #in    
    
    
    New paper from RMIT IR group http://bit.ly/HQO9LV  "Using anchor text for homepage and topic distillation search tasks" #in    
    
    
    @elunca Will get a copy sent    
    
    
    Andrei Broder is now at Google after leaving Yahoo a couple of weeks ago. #in    
    
    
    @metzlerd @ian_soboroff Good news Don.    
    
    
    How often were you thanked in the acknowledgements of an academic paper? AckSeer knows http://bit.ly/IIcQvG  #in    
    
    
    Are these the first uses of the term "search engine"? MIS and DB books from '72 & '76? http://bit.ly/JqwfA4  http://bit.ly/HRjPOi  #in    
    
    
    Omar Alonso's crowd sourcing keynote full of great tips at the crowd sourcing workshop #sigir2010    
    
    
    A new batch of historical books and papers now online at SIGIR's museum http://bit.ly/HW8gus  #in    
    
    
    Expert ranking of academics correlate somewhat with citation. Scopus a bit better than Google Scholar http://bit.ly/94QJ7k #in #fb    
    
    
    Splitting a city into social regions derived from FourSquare data http://www.livehoods.org/  #in    
    
    
    This paper says 50 queries are fine for testing, yet search engines use 1000s of queries, we're missing something http://bit.ly/JRW7VP  #in    
    
    
    @julian_urbano They certainly are not sampled, yes, maybe they are a popular style of query, but actually, who knows?    
    
    
    @srchvrs Tell me more    
    
    
    @julian_urbano Yes and the recent web tracks are getting queries from logs also.    
    
    
    That's the SIGIR notifications going out...    
    
    
    Search without those pesky dominating sites like Wikipedia, DBLP, IMDB, etc. Reminds me of the old days http://www.millionshort.com     
    
    
    @seo01 'dunno, sorry    
    
    
    New paper with old PhD student Shahram on image search by doctors is out http://shar.es/27Zaq  free version here http://bit.ly/IJBdb0  #in    
    
    
    Just out, Bruce Croft and I wrote a short history of ranked IR: pay version http://bit.ly/JYpVyd  free version http://bit.ly/ITGMQS  #in    
    
    
    @takis_metaxas One is free and one you have to pay for. Well, also the pay one corrects a few typos that the publisher noticed.    
    
    
    Nice analysis of tweets, seen a lot of this before in query logs, but fun to see elsewhere http://bit.ly/IZBIKW  #in    
    
    
    The report from the SWIRL meeting is out in SIGIR Forum http://bit.ly/JvaU6t  long list of suggested future IR research directions #in    
    
    
    The XBox Kinect tracks bodies by seeing how they deform structured light, here are beautiful photographs of that http://bit.ly/LA2eOp  #in    
    
    
    Matrix of transitions used to arrange the components of exploratory search, nice. @HCIR_GeneG & @jerepick http://bit.ly/JamhzA  #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG No problem, I just liked the way you guys did that.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG It seems to me one big issue is to help the searcher understand when they are going over ground already covered.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Cool, please send me the pointer. I tried something very simple on this 20 years ago :) http://bit.ly/KZUCbB  (p12)    
    
    
    @leifos @HCIR_GeneG my twitter handle that gets truer every day. Just you wait young Leif, it'll happen to you soon enough.    
    
    
    I'm the new co-editor of FnTIR http://bit.ly/K4JSUr  Many thanks for all the years of hard work from Fabrizio who is stepping down #in    
    
    
    Feynman explains the scientific method in a minute, just great http://bit.ly/LYG8oZ  #in    
    
    
    Nice article from Marti Hearst on the future directions for IR http://dl.acm.org/authorize?6592199 … #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aZSmnw another fast way to get IR ground truth like Amitay's TRELs? But should be striving for fast over quality? #in    
    
    
    Google Scholar's top 100 publication venues. This can only be the start of this sort of data from them http://bit.ly/JsALkV  #in    
    
    
    NYT on the debate about academic access to private data for research purposes http://nyti.ms/MbFMvr  #in    
    
    
    Just realised that Google Scholar Metrics is searchable http://bit.ly/JsALkV  SIGIR is not the top IR forum by citation, JASIST is #in    
    
    
    @ssn All measures have problems, h5 can disadvantage low volume forums. It ignores low citation papers, thus arXiv scores high.    
    
    
    This query shows the main IR venues ranked on Scholar http://bit.ly/KoBS1C  JASIST, SIGIR, IP&M, CIKM, WSDM, TOIS, did I miss anything? #in    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Hmmm searched for that, but I don't see it in there. I couldn't find the WWW conference either.    
    
    
    @amjedbj @msftacademic I like the MSR system, what's cool about Google is it merges conferences with journals.    
    
    
    @guidozuc Welcome to the world of information extraction, there will be missing counts for everything due to inconsistent naming.    
    
    
    @delsweil I know what you mean, but for me it's IR 'enough' :)    
    
    
    @iFromm @phschaer @delsweil So with digital libraries added to the query (thanks) you get this http://bit.ly/KTHXpr     
    
    
    @phschaer @delsweil @ifromm The problem is, people in power use these things.    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer Might be due to ECIR's publishing in LNCS, which I've seen cause referencing confusion.    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer Actually, the strange one that's missing is TREC I search, but I can't find it.    
    
    
    Pairs of words are sometimes ambiguous: search for Belkin ASK on Google Scholar, you get 2 quite distinct threads of research. #fb #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/acclql Belkin's ASK: we search to know, but if we don't know, how do we search? Do we only query the easy stuff? #in    
    
    
    @iadh @iFromm @delsweil @phschaer If you look at the ECIR citations, it seems to only be pubs from 2010 and 2011 http://scholar.google.com.au/citations?hl=en&view_op=list_hcore&venue=eAz7mQVdMusJ.20120401 … bug    
    
    
    @delsweil @iadh @ifromm @phschaer Does ECIR have its pubs in the ACM DL? If not, maybe it should; that might help Google Scholar.    
    
    
    @phschaer @iadh @delsweil @ifromm It's definitely doable, the Australasian IR Conference (ADCS) I think will soon be on the ACM DL.    
    
    
    @seo01 http://bit.ly/98YStI my 1st IR paper; people always told me about Belkin's ASK, glad I read it, interesting to compare now & then.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/98nlR5 top 1998 web queries? sex, Playboy, Penthouse, chat, Hustler, nude, porn, erotica... the web has changed #fb    
    
    
    How Many Test Users in a Usability Study? Five, mostly (Jakob Nielsen's Alertbox) http://shar.es/q8Pwm  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Published papers aren't a random sample of science: the 97% using a significance test found significance http://bit.ly/fzqCw7 #fb #in    
    
    
    The sharpshooter's fallacy is alive and well in the fields of science http://nyr.kr/hTDy1p #fb #in    
    
    
    Occasionally, you read something that changes your view.; can such teams be used for academic research? I should try http://bit.ly/MrFEJP     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/awwb7m Session DCG, thinking about this (maybe) for the TREC session track... but what's "Scenario D"?    
    
    
    SIGIR is running a panel this year the use of proprietary data in academic research. Should be fun, hopefully productive #in    
    
    
    Neilsen "5 users in a usability test is good" Schmettow "the maths behind that claim is wrong, you need many more" http://bit.ly/KflFd4     
    
    
    Nice early study showing that users want results quickly and care less about the source http://bit.ly/Kfng2L     
    
    
    Search Google Scholar for an email address fragment: e.g. ".ac.uk" you get top UK academics, works for Uni names too. http://bit.ly/KRTnXF     
    
    
    Nice summary of work in probabilistic topic models in April's CACM http://bit.ly/LEc8NP     
    
    
    Call for participation in NTCIR's search evaluations is out. The deadline for joining is looming, miss it, miss out. http://bit.ly/MvhD4k     
    
    
    Crowd sourced vs expert relevance judgements, which is better? Our paper says crowds, but experts aren't redundant yet. http://bit.ly/N5DHm0     
    
    
    @srchvrs Quite possibly, don't under estimate the importance of expert knowledge.    
    
    
    The Google grants recipients for this round are out. A few IR people are in there... including me :) http://bit.ly/MIckA2     
    
    
    @JulioGonzalo1 Very cool Julio, great to see #swirl2012 had such an immediate benefit.    
    
    
    @ieleta Thanks    
    
    
    Someone said this week: "there are 2 types of successful academics: those who know how to write grants; and those who have great ideas" #in    
    
    
    Yet another library digitizing its archives, this time it's the Wellcome trust http://bit.ly/cmTJOD #in    
    
    
    @timgollins Thanks, sorry I couldn't chat for longer today.    
    
    
    Great talk by Pascal Van Hentenryck on optimisation last night; he cited this example showing computing saves lives. http://bit.ly/LDeySt     
    
    
    Berners-Lee's 1999 book on WWW's 1st decade: few search engines, a hint of web 2.0, lots of semantic web http://bit.ly/ieyVDm #fb #in    
    
    
    One of our students presented on news recommender systems yesterday. She's got a nice data set to work with. http://bit.ly/LTghOV     
    
    
    I'm hearing that the main conference hotel for #sigir2012 is filling up, book soon.    
    
    
    #cikm2012 One accept, one reject. I'll take that.    
    
    
    Not everyday someone you know gets his research narrated by Morgan Freeman. http://youtu.be/oeaFYYHShlo  #in    
    
    
    Years ago, I pitched a computers & data in the field idea to archaeologists, their reply? I want a water proof computer http://bit.ly/O8U8wO     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ArjumandYounus Yes I imagine they are, posters tend to be.    
    
    
    I knew cross (translated) language search was on Google, but I didn't realise they had made it easy to use. http://bit.ly/NPvuzg     
    
    
    What is a Browser? If you haven't already, great video for CS people to watch http://youtu.be/o4MwTvtyrUQ     
    
    
    Recent research on eye tracking and search interfaces was presented at the RMIT Tiger talk this week. http://bit.ly/NN5lCL     
    
    
    "Spoken Content Retrieval: A Survey of Techniques and Technologies" is just out in the latest FnTIR edition http://bit.ly/PLOost  #in    
    
    
    Past PhD plagiarism is damaging political and professorial careers in Europe http://bbc.in/SSQWsd     
    
    
    Prof & Assoc. Prof at jobs RMIT: areas include social networks, big data; details here http://bit.ly/NSM5qr  http://bit.ly/NSMs4b  #in    
    
    
    @rainingman1 Thanks for pointer, is this better than Turnitin?    
    
    
    @rainingman1 You can tell Turnitin to ignore individual documents to prevent that from being a problem.    
    
    
    @rainingman1 Yes, Turnitin tells you have 100% match on the earlier document, but you can tell it to ignore that doc and re-calculate    
    
    
    Microsoft adds a Facebook-based collaborative search feature to Bing searches http://cnet.co/Ox8PgJ  via @CNET    
    
    
    @jerepick Sounds reasonable to me. We've got someone here working on mobile collaborative search by the way.    
    
    
    A major review of blog search is just out from the Glasgow and NIST people #in http://bit.ly/M4xXKZ     
    
    
    The IR review journal FnTIR releases another major review, this time in Expertise Retrieval #in http://bit.ly/M4ysEQ     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/wgCg4 Hearst book: one to be left open on your desk covered in scribbles & notes AND on-line version is free! #in    
    
    
    Great talk this evening by Kenneth O. Stanley from Florida on novelty search in AI applications, really cool work.    
    
    
    @jteevan @sigirf if the measure tells you something different, then maybe. That wasn't covered much in the talk #sigir2012    
    
    
    #sigir2012 enjoyed Ryen White's log analysis talk about extracting valuable data from health queries.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 thinking about Tue's proprietary data panel session, note all of this year's log analysis papers are from search engine groups.    
    
    
    @jteevan about proprietary data? To be honest I don't know.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 enjoyed listening about ranking features that are good for mobile local search http://research.microsoft.com/pubs/163550/fp121-lv.pdf …    
    
    
    #sigir2012 when I grow up, I want to be like Steve Robertson. He's virtually retired and he's here enthusiastically presenting his poster.    
    
    
    @eelstretching great donuts, thank you #sigir2012    
    
    
    "@jteevan: @eugeneAgichtein's Given search task that's suspended, predict if searcher will pick it back up later. #SIGIR2012" great talk    
    
    
    #sigir2012 geography to the rescue of search? Apparently yes, according to our current exploratory search speaker.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @BHecht really cool spatial visualisation of search results: maps, periodic tables, where senators sit in congress.    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 Marc Bron tackling the difficult subject of how to evaluate exploratory search. Great session.    
    
    
    @jteevan @sigirf That's a critical point as far as I'm concerned, there are loads of examples of science conducted on unsharable data.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 if I'm a doctor who publishes a patient drug study, it's crazy for others to demand access to my patients, yet this is science.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 it only took Ricardo 3 minutes to mention wine :)    
    
    
    #sigir2012 I see a consensus emerging here.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 for a fresh PhD student @wewebber is holding his own very well with the rest of the panel    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @invertedindex "welcome to the first SIGIR session in the bat cave". This room is terrible.    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 @invertedindex extending his time series analysis work from last year on dealing with time varying queries.    
    
    
    @JeffD we're headed for a question? #sigir2012    
    
    
    #SIGIR2012 Etan Aydar talking about zoetrope and other ways of querying and visualising temporal data, cool.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 @mdr talking about open geist: a tool that processes Wikipedia trend data.    
    
    
    #sigir2012 really enjoyed the conference this year, good papers, a fun venue, thanks Bill.    
    
    
    I said at #swirl12 that indoor location based information delivery would be important... maybe I was right http://bit.ly/NmBV3B  #in    
    
    
    Our CIKM short paper on inconsistencies in search engine ranking when measured across different collections http://bit.ly/Tblio9  #in    
    
    
    If only I'd had the Manga guides when I was a kid, I wouldn't be having to learn stats in my 40s. http://bit.ly/TbtmoV     
    
    
    @craig_macdonald It doesn't have one yet, we're working on the WoS people about this. It will come and when it does, it should be good.    
    
    
    Rank citation analysis academics by their citation paper h-index, the highly influential inventor of h, Hirsch ranks very low #in #fb    
    
    
    Google Instant shows multiple SERPs to users, is Google getting more training data on user preferences for its results? #in #fb    
    
    
    Password cracking meets big data... and does rather well. http://arstechnica.com/security/2012/08/passwords-under-assault/ … #in    
    
    
    Ricardo Baeza-Yates visiting us at RMIT. Itinerary: meet students, give talk, lunch meet staff, then see penguins: perfect Melbourne visit.    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald The average citation count for the 19 papers published by FnTIR http://bit.ly/K4JSUr  is 112. Popular papers indeed #in    
    
    
    @leifos @craig_macdonald power law. So I should use the median. ERA? There were these problems, note the grades aren't being updated.    
    
    
    It's not just relevance, users love simple & familiar designs; websites need to make a great first impression http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2012/08/users-love-simple-and-familiar-designs.html … #in    
    
    
    Excited to announce that Timos Sellis is joining us at RMIT http://scholar.google.gr/citations?user=G1Iux80AAAAJ&hl=en … #in    
    
    
    @KushalDave Sorry about that. Try http://www.optimalworkshop.com/treejack-results … and click on task results follow your nose...    
    
    
    @optimalworkshop @KushalDave It's cool stuff, I was showing it in a usability engineering class at my University this week.    
    
    
    How find without searching; this great talk looked at finding solutions in AI, lessons for search here I think http://youtu.be/tZBViI8ZaU0  #in    
    
    
    How's this for a small conference venue 15 minutes from Melbourne's centre? I like Melbourne http://yfrog.com/oexviegj     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG who needs PowerPoint when you have palm trees?    
    
    
    Visually impaired users find complex searching difficult on Google (no free version of the paper). http://bit.ly/P0xEPY     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG I would go with the 1991 journal paper, that's pretty definitive, we updated the interface later, but didn't write it up :(    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Great name for a journal eh? Yes that one.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG Sorry for any confusion, I assumed you were looking at my publications page http://www.seg.rmit.edu.au/mark/publications/ …    
    
    
    4th best student city, 2012? My home town, Melbourne :) http://www.topuniversities.com/student-life/best-student-cities/2012/melbourne#.UE7iikbpz3g.twitter … #fb    
    
    
    Listening to Richard Stallman talk about his 4 freedoms and how they apply to copyright    
    
    
    Hmm Stallman taking A bit too long to get to some interesting points    
    
    
    The BBC picked up on the Melbourne Universities ranking with a lovely photo of the RMIT 'brain' building. http://www.bbc.com/travel/feature/20120907-best-student-cities-melbourne … #in    
    
    
    When selecting a new academic for a post: diverse, great publications may be more important than a high h http://arstechnica.com/science/2012/09/scientists-what-will-your-career-look-like-in-ten-years/ …    
    
    
    "Designing & testing an improved packaging for large hollow chocolate bunnies" that's *real* research http://www.tappi.org/Downloads/unsorted/UNTITLED---97Aug133pdf.aspx … #in    
    
    
    Attending William Weber's PhD completion talk in Melbourne. So much good IR evaluation work in one thesis. Amazing!    
    
    
    A tough read: essentially pseudo relevance feedback meets sense disambiguation. Good experimental reporting. http://bit.ly/Qxvneo     
    
    
    You can't always trust Google's "My Citation" pages. This person shows that papers you didn't write can be included. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    @IR_oldie The papers added here are so crazy, there's no deception intended here, just an illustration that there is no checking.    
    
    
    A social network aggregator (probably been done elsewhere), but first time I've seen this idea tried out. http://bit.ly/VHH72C     
    
    
    Really nice opinion piece on the multiple roles of computers in cars http://www.wired.com/opinion/2012/10/automakers-become-software-makers-the-next-battle-between-open-and-closed/ …    
    
    
    @tetsuyasakai It differed quite a bit though, don't you think? I was pleasantly surprised about that part.    
    
    
    Lol, he is on a mission to be the number one IR person on Google Scholar, he's now at number 2. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    The visual version of "is your baseline strong enough?" http://bit.ly/ROpCNq     
    
    
    Yay, he did it: the number 1 IR person in the world. Someone had to show how vulnerable these lists are to spam. http://bit.ly/ROucv8     
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG All the papers have a "J Wang" as an author, just not him. Maybe Google doesn't check that carefully?    
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG Maybe you can overwrite the suggested papers and add extra to the list, keep adding and you move ever up.    
    
    
    @dirkahlers @HCIR_GeneG The labels are all self-nominated. Google gave up on that idea for the Web years ago, too susceptible to spam.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/b7DoM7 simulated analysis of MTurkers making errors & the benefits of using gold standard data to detect them #in    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/dtqOBl RMIT-based cost benefit analysis of improving search effectiveness, nice idea.    
    
    
    Academics cite a wider range of more relevant papers than they did before the internet came along. http://bit.ly/SoiG7d     
    
    
    Our Yahoo! Research proposal was funded: "Re-finding information in the Web”, jointly with David Vallet and my student Sargol Sadeghi.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/aHgG3Y Google's guide to getting your web page ranked high just updated: detailed solid info #fb #in    
    
    
    Detailed instructions on how to evaluate enterprise search systems. Quite different from TREC style evaluation. http://bit.ly/RqmXr7     
    
    
    His h score rises still, but Google have taken him off the list of IR people. His short reign at the top has ended. http://bit.ly/SYLO8W     
    
    
    Lessons on training from the army. Valuable hints for computer scientists, maybe even PhD supervisors http://bit.ly/TOMSXV     
    
    
    @dirkahlers Yeah, though my impression is stop lists aren't Google's style, maybe some clustering to spot paper content outliers?    
    
    
    @dirkahlers Ah :)    
    
    
    Locating & using the tweets of a subset of twitter users to summarise the tweets of a wider population. #cikm2012 http://bit.ly/TnGVk9     
    
    
    @srchvrs @kohlschuetter Both use automatic sense disambiguation and "author intervention", but with different emphasis on the techniques.    
    
    
    @michaeltwofish Sorry, when I put my hand up, I was referring to a private blog for internal notes. This is the only public thing.    
    
    
    @michaeltwofish sorry, you'll need go make do with tweets    
    
    
    Enterprise search person told me the web is a publishing medium, while most enterprises hold a digital archive. Quite different to search.    
    
    
    @srchvrs also no one is (white hat) optimising enterprise archive content. There's no advertising to fund development of the ranker :)    
    
    
    My student got a Yahoo award, with a bit of help from me and David Vallet :) http://shar.es/GFRzh  via    
    
    
    Google Scholar is grouping journals & conferences by sub-topic. IR is in DB&IS: WWW, VLDB, SIGMOD, SIGIR top forums http://bit.ly/SPXO8a     
    
    
    Many people tell about spam on MTurk: sounds like Amazon needs to improve its rating system http://bit.ly/cbv5sP #in    
    
    
    Computer used when walking? Define system quality by user walk speed & how many red crossing lights missed, brilliant. http://bit.ly/UVzcv8     
    
    
    With friends like these, who needs QRELS? Facebook and Bing sharing data http://bit.ly/bANbHk #in #fb    
    
    
    SVD-like mapping of docs to semantic hash codes, then use ML to learn mappings for new docs to new codes http://bit.ly/aofQza #in #fb    
    
    
    A colleague's Google Scholar profile contained papers he didn't write, turns out Scholar added them automatically.    
    
    
    Mood changes measured in Twitter predict US stock market moves 3-4 days later http://bit.ly/aeQzLP #fb #in    
    
    
    Nice side piece from the Leveson (press standards) inquiry in the UK on the inaccuracies of science reporting. http://bit.ly/TvRmDw     
    
    
    @delsweil Is your commute in a helicopter?    
    
    
    The challenge of creating usable security in wireless devices, a great keynote by Gene Tsudik at ACSW in Perth. #fb #in    
    
    
    Social Media Is Eating Our Lives (And Pinterest Is Chewing Fastest) | Wired Business | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/business/2012/12/social-spike/ …    
    
    
    Nice student resource about plagiarism http://plagiarism.org/     
    
    
    New extensive review of contextual search just out. http://bit.ly/TK6IoK     
    
    
    A strong result, computer science at RMIT got two ratings of 4 (out of 5) for its research by the Australian Government yesterday #era    
    
    
    Enjoyed reading this paper on summarizing tweets for events http://bit.ly/UQvDKp     
    
    
    Our RMIT CS students built an app for a Guinness World Record attempt tomorrow evening http://bit.ly/SMOaFs     
    
    
    CLEF is no longer about just cross language search, check out the 2013 call. http://bit.ly/SSdo6P     
    
    
    One part of this paper examines conditional equivalence of documents with respect to a query, nice idea http://bit.ly/9s10sW #fb #in    
    
    
    Tweet sports summarization, showing video of football matches based on tweet volume and some personalization data. http://bit.ly/TVl8SW     
    
    
    Reading about TweetMotif the tweet search engine & browser, the engine is down, anyone know if there's a new link? http://bit.ly/VKBFbY     
    
    
    @sarvk Cool, thanks    
    
    
    @damiano10 Cool, thank you. Has this longer version been published anywhere?    
    
    
    We have an associate professor position at RMIT: big data, semantic search, and/or social data analytics. Interested? contact me.    
    
    
    @brendan642 thanks for contacting me. For now, your paper covers all I need to know, though are you still working on tweet summarization?    
    
    
    #SIGIR2013 call out; reviewers will consider reproducibility of results; 2 page poster replaced with 4 page paper. http://bit.ly/VUlA3q     
    
    
    Tufte's 2006 PPT hate letter blames both Shuttle disasters on good engineers who are bad at visual communication. http://amzn.to/VbJCY8     
    
    
    2013 marks the 20th anniversary that friends and I in Glasgow University set up our first web site. I'm getting old :)    
    
    
    @madereal My first (and only) skydive was about 25 years ago. Seriously you've done 400? Wow!    
    
    
    How doctors search for images used in research/teaching. The publisher's giving the article for free this week; odd. http://www.emeraldinsight.com/fwd.htm?id=aob&ini=aob&doi=10.1108/00012531311297186 …    
    
    
    Nice interview with Amit Singhal (Google search chief) in the Guardian today http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2013/jan/19/google-search-knowledge-graph-singhal-interview …    
    
    
    