The Startup Spouse: On Risks, Trade-Offs And Never Sleeping On The Floor http://onstartups.com/tabid/3339/bid/86543/The-Startup-Spouse-On-Risks-Trade-Offs-And-Never-Sleeping-On-The-Floor.aspx … via @dharmesh    
    
    
    http://fb.me/QFXEbUUP     
    
    
    Infographic: When it comes to Millennials, are you talking to strangers? http://post.ly/54Nu7  via @briansolis    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1N31YE8Tg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/VnEhAO3D     
    
    
    Science: Scientists Create Molecule to Make Teeth Cavityproof - @Gizmodo http://gizmodo.com/5924447/scientists-find-molecule-that-will-make-your-teeth-cavityproof …    
    
    
    I'm at The Sherry Abode (El Cerrito, CA) http://4sq.com/Nmlkrn     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1syw9SNAg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/tGpnSIB0     
    
    
    well… that was disappointing.    
    
    
    Sitting on BART across from a girl with green hair and tattooed eyebrows... Have to post nonsense like this on Facebook to avoid looking up.    
    
    
    Cookie time (@ Specialty's Cafe & Bakery) http://4sq.com/MdiQOx     
    
    
    "If you want a kitten, start out asking for a horse" http://fb.me/WDW8CEeI     
    
    
    http://fb.me/20ey4hyd1     
    
    
    Looks like a great event! http://fb.me/1WBjLNlJ8     
    
    
    I'm at Sausalito Espresso (San Francisco, CA) http://4sq.com/OYuFoX     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1PH2BtEkC     
    
    
    Lalchandani Simon named advisor to WEDWU, Inc. | PR NewsChannel http://fb.me/1elZiM3YO     
    
    
    http://www.dontevenreply.com/view.php?post=100 …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1N1DECALJ     
    
    
    blood makes noise    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1uHsQ0vgx     
    
    
    I wonder what happened to Pat Powers. Pat, Erin Mokarzel and I shared an apartment while I was at Marist. 15... http://fb.me/2c8RskSUn     
    
    
    I think i need this http://fb.me/1czFeEYyH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/26HbCDzIh     
    
    
    This rain is crazy!    
    
    
    StubHub: Anatomy of a game-changing idea http://fb.me/22LZZNzst     
    
    
    Follow Larkr on LinkedIn http://lnkd.in/veEV3z     
    
    
    toast    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1GRQPQdka     
    
    
    my next race? http://adventuretravel.about.com/od/adventureraces/qt/Wife_Carrying.htm … http://fb.me/1VfoaZUUy     
    
    
    Today is National Tequila Day!!!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/22XYDswJz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1AWDJDnAu     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2jnMOnjeI     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/22vUu4sJr     
    
    
    im hungry http://fb.me/1qyEEoyrc     
    
    
    Just did Tallac in 2:43. Tripped on a rock and took a scary fall on the way down, all i could think of while i... http://fb.me/20yiUQjVa     
    
    
    anyone want to do this? http://fb.me/zWhSVJrf     
    
    
    Land Rover Defender Special Edition | Land Rover International http://fb.me/268iMgbac     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/19OWzT5LC     
    
    
    Check out LARKR on @AngelList https://angel.co/larkr     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1Lb2P4A5g     
    
    
    Startup Weekend Boca Raton http://fb.me/2kkrhYpga     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/uyzsy8Hg     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/YXjZI5sM     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1Ui7arBRc     
    
    
    I'm at À Côté w/ @zachsherry http://4sq.com/ObxoO9     
    
    
    iPhone 5 pre-orders reportedly set for September 12, AT&T preps for launch | VentureBeat: http://venturebeat.com/2012/08/13/iphone-5-pre-orders-reportedly-set-for-september-12-att-preps-for-launch/#.UClhfimr8Qw.twitter …    
    
    
    Can't believe tomorrow Finn Kernes will be in 11th grade, and Chloe will start Kindergarden!    
    
    
    Can I Borrow $25 | Big Is The New Small http://fb.me/26T1rHEsQ     
    
    
    "I Like Soli's Cupcakes" - Finn Kernes    
    
    
    http://fb.me/25iuRnsFM     
    
    
    I'm at Pittsburgh International Airport (PIT) (Pittsburgh, PA) w/ 20 others http://4sq.com/Q6WDT6     
    
    
    I'm at Philadelphia International Airport (PHL) (Philadelphia, PA) w/ 84 others http://4sq.com/OFi26e     
    
    
    I'm at JetBlue Airways Terminal (Fort Lauderdale, Fl) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/OdgT7A     
    
    
    9:45am flight from fll to lga, sitting on the plane - still haven't left the gate... Not a fan of JetBlue today    
    
    
    I'm at LaGuardia Airport (LGA) (East Elmhurst, NY) w/ 79 others http://4sq.com/QfJzHJ     
    
    
    Another jet blue delay (@ LaGuardia Airport (LGA) w/ 108 others) http://4sq.com/QpRIgh     
    
    
    Farmhouse burger... (@ Metro Burger Bar) http://4sq.com/NPsAl0     
    
    
    I'm at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport (FLL) (Ft Lauderdale, FL) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/PNHDHz     
    
    
    Nice - David Knight http://fb.me/MlcanXDP     
    
    
    I'm at Private Beach In Boca! (Boca Raton, FL) http://4sq.com/P24obw     
    
    
    Making cider... Could only find pasteurized apple juice in FL, so this batch is being made with beer yeast from Zach http://fb.me/sN6zBbWT     
    
    
    #3 is still my favorite http://fb.me/21jwVg1QY     
    
    
    whats for dinner? http://fb.me/1Upj8vDBQ     
    
    
    Awesome http://fb.me/xxaiLeCD     
    
    
    I would have upgraded right away if it came with Rosario Dawson as an iPhone girlfriend, guess i will be waiting... http://fb.me/11KNS6vpf     
    
    
    Getting ready for Chloe's open house http://fb.me/1aSVNT83P     
    
    
    I'm at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport (FLL) (Ft Lauderdale, FL) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/Pv1ePM     
    
    
    I'm at Hartsfield-Jackson Atlanta International Airport (ATL) (Atlanta, GA) w/ 156 others http://4sq.com/NpXxuH     
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (San Francisco, CA) w/ 162 others http://4sq.com/TYtQSw     
    
    
    I'm at InterContinental San Francisco (San Francisco, CA) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/UQvqoT     
    
    
    Grappa tasting http://fb.me/1KqlHJgHq     
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (San Francisco, CA) w/ 8 others http://4sq.com/SKuNjC     
    
    
    I'm at Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX) (Phoenix, AZ) w/ 69 others http://4sq.com/RRhGpL     
    
    
    I'm at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport (FLL) (Ft Lauderdale, FL) w/ 49 others http://4sq.com/SM2kd1     
    
    
    someone needs to go to the gym http://fb.me/1zfvrqYdi     
    
    
    Its too hot for humans in Florida    
    
    
    I'm at United States Swim Academy (Coral Springs, FL) http://4sq.com/UjTtKU     
    
    
    Date night with Chloe, watching paranorman 3d http://fb.me/2qoVkAvFg     
    
    
    I'm at Regal Magnolia Place 16 for ParaNorman 3D (Coral Springs, FL) http://4sq.com/SJMtFP     
    
    
    I'm at Orange Theory Fitness (Coral Springs, FL) http://4sq.com/QunyX3     
    
    
    Nothing better than a bar dominated by neighborhood and sports talk ;) (@ Parkland Golf & Country Club) http://4sq.com/Sk0Khp     
    
    
    I'm at Regal Magnolia Place 16 for Resident Evil: Retribution (Coral Springs, FL) http://4sq.com/PY6f07     
    
    
    Want to be an entrepreneur? Sign up for FAU event http://fb.me/1R9XOVr9H     
    
    
    ZZ Ward is really really good, kind of reminds me of Res    
    
    
    Getting my espresso at Starbucks today because our machine disappeared (@ Starbucks) http://4sq.com/Ro45tM     
    
    
    Grandma has a broken wrist http://fb.me/1to3kCtxx     
    
    
    Rebel House is the best restaurant I have been to in Florida... Even with the high noise level and disorganized... http://fb.me/2k487oJFT     
    
    
    @teapot360 Join me on Mingle where I'm meeting professionals all around me! http://joinmingle.com  #professionalnetwork    
    
    
    @Wed_Wu Join me on Mingle where I'm meeting professionals all around me! http://joinmingle.com  #professionalnetwork    
    
    
    Launch Pad to open tech accelerator in downtown Miami - Business - http://MiamiHerald.com  http://lnkd.in/Es-cqY     
    
    
    The real winner of tonight's debate was anyone who didn't waste time watching it.    
    
    
    Cloud-free and Secure File Sharing | GetMeMyFiles http://fb.me/1j8b6fORH     
    
    
    It's too hot to sleep    
    
    
    I'm at Regal Magnolia Place 16 for Hotel Transylvania (Coral Springs, FL) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/Q4568Z     
    
    
    The salary boost of working out http://fb.me/1kiXykHrz     
    
    
    Boca Raton Startup Weekend 10/12 http://fb.me/1ABqPncWb     
    
    
    "I hate clubs, they make me feel  judged and rejected by people I would normally judge and reject" -the Mindy project    
    
    
    Warren Miller films on TV... Ski season is coming!    
    
    
    Lets get this party going! (@ startup weekend w/ @marklaymon) http://4sq.com/RUoUgF     
    
    
    #swboca is starting up now    
    
    
    #swboca @SteveRepetti #funny #outofcontext "how do I get him to come?"    
    
    
    Watching final pitches at #swboca    
    
    
    I'm at startup weekend w/ @marklaymon http://4sq.com/WlV4DM     
    
    
    About to run the FAU homecoming 5k (@ Track and Field) http://4sq.com/TK3TD2     
    
    
    5K, then lots and lots of food (@ Topeekeegee Yugnee (TY) Park) http://4sq.com/PWJezP     
    
    
    @Finn_Kernes blocked me from following her on twitter and then gave me a hard time for not following her    
    
    
    Its official: I'm exploring new job opportunities, if you know of anything really exciting (the next big thing) let me know.    
    
    
    What do you think the most interesting companies in FL are? and why? #Florida    
    
    
    Duck. It's What's For Dinner    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/MGw5eW  #in    
    
    
    stumbleupon find of the day http://fb.me/20JQvgXfB     
    
    
    xkcd: Connoisseur http://fb.me/1caZuGcyF     
    
    
    Congratulations Kubs Lalchandani http://fb.me/Rkv3xR54     
    
    
    Watching she-ra    
    
    
    Watching Finn compete in swimming regionals (@ Boca Raton Community High School) http://4sq.com/U7bK3d     
    
    
    "Your body is worn out and you need medical attention, but that would take away from your climbing time, so you... http://fb.me/1lLodZg7u     
    
    
    Waiting in line to vote... Looks like a 3 hour wait. Who is bringing the beer? (@ Park Trails Elementary) http://4sq.com/QkxnMm     
    
    
    Live Election Results http://fb.me/yJMuEKpK     
    
    
    there is clearly something wrong with the "democratic process" when a states electoral college votes are in, but... http://fb.me/1J7UHBQVx     
    
    
    I really want to be skiing right now    
    
    
    Click here to support A New American Diner  by Jonathan M Kosorek http://fb.me/1Q4yzMesp     
    
    
    Where can I give blood near parkland FL?    
    
    
    Gave blood today    
    
    
    Once again, our neighborhood killed it!

Shawn Kernes - 20:00.7 (2nd in group)
Richard Mosquera - 20:37.6 (3rd in... http://fb.me/uS2L6QiV     
    
    
    Replaced Fedora with Ubuntu on 2 old laptops that I use as media servers around the house. So much better.    
    
    
    Download BuzzMob at http://itunes.apple.com/in/app/buzzmob/id455241178?mt=8 …    
    
    
    Quick trip to Denver in the AM    
    
    
    http://fb.me/Pxr5rciG     
    
    
    Heading to Denver (@ Fll/Hollywood International Airport) http://4sq.com/TFNrFG     
    
    
    I'm at Denver International Airport (DEN) (Denver, CO) w/ 109 others http://4sq.com/UpqX9Y     
    
    
    I'm at Omni Interlocken Resort & Spa (Broomfield, CO) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/SoV9SB     
    
    
    At #defrag conference in Broomfield Colorado    
    
    
    Cool http://fb.me/28RmY5e8x     
    
    
    Heading back to Florida (@ Denver International Airport (DEN) w/ 86 others) http://4sq.com/SYzzW2     
    
    
    Didn't know I was going to New Orleans today (@ Louis Armstrong New Orleans International Airport (MSY) w/ 35 others) http://4sq.com/ZTENqy     
    
    
    I'm at Fort Lauderdale-Hollywood International Airport (FLL) (Ft Lauderdale, FL) w/ 19 others http://4sq.com/QKtr7I     
    
    
    Don’t have $1 billion to spend? Buy this Instagram clone with over 1m downloads now for $1.5m http://fb.me/1X0VKJnWJ     
    
    
    5k race with Finn (@ Anchor Park) http://4sq.com/ULNIpg     
    
    
    Finn in 2nd place    
    
    
    I'm at The Fillmore Miami Beach at The Jackie Gleason Theater for Regina Spektor and Only Son (Miami Beach, FL) http://4sq.com/TQJrly     
    
    
    Christianne Bijasa Kernes hugging the security woman in an attempt to get into a restricted aria    
    
    
    with Christianne, Finn (@ Regal Magnolia Place 16 for Skyfall w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/SFT7xx     
    
    
    Add me on Snapchat! http://snapchat.me/skernes     
    
    
    spent the morning researching location based social networks (most of them are basically dating sites, leaving... http://fb.me/1h4QnOjO5     
    
    
    About to start building a POC in ColdFusion, leveraging the Singly API's. This should be fun.    
    
    
    Click here to support A New American Micro Diner  by Jonfood NapaValley http://fb.me/22yCi5UA0     
    
    
    http://www.tripadvisor.com/Attraction_Review-g143010-d108271-Reviews-Precipice_Trail-Acadia_National_Park_Maine.html … http://fb.me/1wkINAfC1     
    
    
    Turkey Trot... Almost time to run. (@ Levis Jewish Community Center w/ 7 others) http://4sq.com/ULCkcH     
    
    
    Post race dance party    
    
    
    happy thanksgiving    
    
    
    Rich Mosquera - 20:40.2
Shawn Kernes - 20:57.9
Finn Kernes - 24:22.6
Ricky Mosquera - 24:37.9
Danielle Lee -... http://fb.me/1LQjwYiUl     
    
    
    I'm never eating again    
    
    
    Makes so much sense http://fb.me/23wonBldX     
    
    
    The right way to spend Black Friday http://fb.me/1iGv1lloQ     
    
    
    Yum :P http://fb.me/AfwXrT6u     
    
    
    Finn Kernes is donating blood for the first time    
    
    
    Giving blood http://fb.me/ACsA91kW     
    
    
    Never going to sleep with all this noise    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1TL81jZwM     
    
    
    Don't Fall For Fake Facebook Privacy Notice http://fb.me/MXxTpKe7     
    
    
    Big news today - "woman in fl arrested for riding on back of a manatee". I saw the pictures, couldn't tell which one was the sea cow.    
    
    
    Grandma has been moved to CCU7. Chris and I are camping out in her room. Grandmas condition seems to be improving,... http://fb.me/ua4ZT1Kw     
    
    
    Are you a #TekFighter? New event at MDC Dec. 7 | The Starting Gate http://fb.me/2hwd7G31P     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1TdgwavuB     
    
    
    Grandma has been in a coma since having a bilateral thalamic infarction (stroke) on Monday. Its time to wake up now.    
    
    
    Grandma has been in a coma since having a bilateral thalamic infarction (stroke) on Monday. She has had family and... http://fb.me/OxTTJNSP     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2yWs958Wi     
    
    
    Nothing is impossible http://fb.me/23b3C4IVG     
    
    
    http://fb.me/25kTzwAp8     
    
    
    "I don't want Bubbe to go, she is my best friend" - Chloe Kernes    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1oLMp7Yjh     
    
    
    Finn Kernes should borrow one of these  awesome sweaters http://fb.me/226Tq9UwD     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1sHyvGWT1     
    
    
    As of 12:30 Grandma has been off life support. She seems much more comfortable without the tubes in her. Her... http://fb.me/2zCZgA5XF     
    
    
    Grandma has been moved to room 457. If you would like to come see her to say goodbye, she can now have visitors at any time.    
    
    
    Thanks Evan Nierman for coming by the hospital tonight.    
    
    
    It has been 12 hours since Grandmas life support was removed, and her body is still going strong. At this rate,... http://fb.me/VF6yziEH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/X4tL3Zwj     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1K1Nwi74A     
    
    
    Grandma is being movie home via ambulance any min    
    
    
    We don't know how much time we have left with Grandma, but we are incredibly grateful to have her home from the... http://fb.me/CWv4NIqq     
    
    
    Thanks Shon Greenblatt Keri Miale Rainone Erika Vianello and Gabriela Pelossi for coming by to see grandma tonight    
    
    
    http://fb.me/MAoN9fVU     
    
    
    Nice http://fb.me/2a5QLwgK0     
    
    
    Thanks to Soli Colon Greenblatt Stacy Ferrante Crystal Lynch Martha González Blum Stuart Blum Danielle... http://fb.me/1Y6lnNaeH     
    
    
    Click here to support A New American Micro Diner  by Jonfood NapaValley http://fb.me/2tGXx7z70     
    
    
    http://fb.me/12nPBYsUi     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1MbAjfX2x     
    
    
    A Grand Opening: Finding Quality Sporting Goods On-Line Just Got Easier http://fb.me/N5Vbgc7n     
    
    
    Bubblegum pop "bands" One direction, Justin Bieber, and the script get passed over for Grammy nominations... Maybe because they lack talent?    
    
    
    This just in: Cuba Gooding Jr. Sought by Miami police... http://fb.me/2gNLV0ScK     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2jxl3FyzD     
    
    
    I wish I could filter out all the posts that start with "like if"    
    
    
    Nice Irene McGee http://fb.me/XIkblrEX     
    
    
    http://fb.me/11oKNaoMn     
    
    
    Undergraduate, Business Development & Sales Intern - Disney Worldwide Services - Job Details http://fb.me/1rgHuLlUy     
    
    
    I think grandma is waiting for Chanukah    
    
    
    “Life is for the living.
Death is for the dead.
Let life be like music. 
And death a note unsaid.” 
― Langston Hughes    
    
    
    Chloe - "Hi daddy, him mommy. Does it look weird that I'm walking around with this pillow?"
Shawn - "No"
Chloe -... http://fb.me/1IdfL6wn7     
    
    
    I don't have the words today, so I borrow and steal from those who do...

"saying goodbye doesn't mean anything.... http://fb.me/BARdhEzb     
    
    
    She was the cool grandma too. http://fb.me/1qP2EybXQ     
    
    
    Someone has had better days http://fb.me/VuCxqiHE     
    
    
    Funeral Services for Grandma (Freda Kernes) will be held tomorrow (Tuesday December 11, 2012) at Robert Schoem's... http://fb.me/z0xn4nm1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/23Bvu5A30     
    
    
    Back in Parkland, but it doesn't feel like home without Bubbe    
    
    
    My first memory of grandma is from December 14th, 1980, I was 3 years old and it is one of my first vivid... http://fb.me/2nYzgPrKW     
    
    
    Somehow I feel like lots of people are going to do this http://fb.me/z7ABJ7in     
    
    
    Just learned that the US census defines middle age as 35 to 54.    
    
    
    Crazy people do crazy things. Cant wait for Chloe to get home today. http://fb.me/23HEqfUs0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/24UHg7hUZ     
    
    
    Im all for gun control, but i really don't understand the relationship between gun control and the tragedy in CT.... http://fb.me/1tbU37yzY     
    
    
    It’s Decembeaver, Grow Your Bush For A Cause http://fb.me/yXsQIpLO     
    
    
    Yum http://fb.me/23mQnclbT     
    
    
    just watched the presidents response to to the CT shootings. It looks like he is pushing for many of the right... http://fb.me/1qlf7rK2B     
    
    
    Community Roundtable - Developing a Tech Industry in South Florida! http://fb.me/PFWl5ID4     
    
    
    Our thoughts are with Christianne Bijasa Kernes grandmother (Inang), who is in intensive care in the Philippines... http://fb.me/20KpsfDit     
    
    
    For some, 12/21/12 really is the end of the world. 

Goodbye Inang. I know you didn't really know what i was... http://fb.me/2pobYZNdZ     
    
    
    Can we just have a redo on December?    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1Q80CjPNc     
    
    
    http://fb.me/QKutOvmn     
    
    
    Apparently Menzies services Virgin.    
    
    
    Finn Kernes is ruining Chloe's life by putting Lego pies on the Lego people's heads.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1feDJXrMe     
    
    
    Happy new year Christianne Bijasa Kernes... We all miss you.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1KX0NSsQM     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/F9yBDCzp     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1Y495zq6d     
    
    
    Drinking Glenmorangie and feeling a bit nostalgic    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/22DZTo7TR     
    
    
    It looks like I'm going to be leaving home again, for at least 6 months. Tried to talk to Christianne Bijasa... http://fb.me/TOmANCgI     
    
    
    you just can't make this stuff up http://fb.me/29P2QY2KN     
    
    
    Introducing Graph Search http://fb.me/wES5GvJa     
    
    
    This place is a ghost town (@ Miami International Airport (MIA) w/ 53 others) http://4sq.com/10ArqQa     
    
    
    Made it to Scotland... Unfortunately the hotel can't find my reservation. (@ Hotel du Vin & Bistro) http://4sq.com/W91ELk     
    
    
    Scotch tasting and Haggis eating all day... I'm ready for bed.    
    
    
    I'm at Parkland Golf & Country Club (Parkland, FL) http://4sq.com/10KsGQI     
    
    
    Start-Up City: Miami http://fb.me/2iTREFEK8     
    
    
    Red Banyan Group Founder Evan Nierman on Lance Armstrong's Crisis PR Efforts http://fb.me/1Oa1aNpWy     
    
    
    Looking for PHP (Web/Webservices) developers, and Mobile (IOS/Android/MADP) developers for a well funded startup in Southern CA.    
    
    
    Brilliant: ‘Birth Control on the Bottom’ Yogurt http://fb.me/29jmlvhON     
    
    
    I have decided to join an exciting early stage startup headquartered in Irvine CA, called BuzzMob. 

It's been a... http://fb.me/1ZjN3Jb6k     
    
    
    Looking forward to catching up with old friends, and explaining why @buzzmob is the next big thing. @NatlSportsForum #NSF2013 @stubhub    
    
    
    We are young? Impressive performance, but Really? #NSF2013    
    
    
    Listening to Disney institute speaker talk about Carny's vs. Disney cast members #NSF2013    
    
    
    I just *didnt* meet 20 people in 40 seconds, although I did shake their hands #NSF2013    
    
    
    Its official http://fb.me/1SQgbN5j7     
    
    
    This panel is making our job easy. Give the fan the ability to emotionally connect, check out @buzzmob #NSF2013    
    
    
    http://fb.me/I6Qdq0ms     
    
    
    A bit of coverage 

http://thenextweb.com/insider/2013/01/28/former-founding-stubhub-cto-shawn-kernes-joins-buzzmob/ … http://fb.me/29qAB0CpR     
    
    
    A bit of coverage 

http://thenextweb.com/insider/2013/01/28/former-founding-stubhub-cto-shawn-kernes-joins-buzzmob/ … http://fb.me/2cLM4hEja     
    
    
    Where is the after party? #NSF2013    
    
    
    Passion, perseverance mark Business Plan Challenge winners’ year - Business Monday - http://MiamiHerald.com  http://fb.me/1vlzdu5xF     
    
    
    I'm at Orange County Convention Center West Concourse (Orlando, FL) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/Wv0M73     
    
    
    Watching Ray (wearing a tie) on the #nsf2013 ticketing panel    
    
    
    I'm at Amway Center (Orlando, FL) w/ 10 others http://4sq.com/WzJIK4     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/D8mRst00     
    
    
    Listening to Pat Williams from the Orlando Magic do a standup routine... Poor Eagles (who are in the room)    
    
    
    Please *Like* BuzzMob to find out more about what i'm up to... http://fb.me/1Da7XB3Fo     
    
    
    I leave for California in about 3.5 hours. I don't know when ill be back in Florida or see Christianne Bijasa... http://fb.me/1TLRR1M7F     
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (San Francisco, CA) w/ 128 others http://4sq.com/11mBefZ     
    
    
    I'm at South Lake Tahoe (South Lake Tahoe, CA) http://4sq.com/WF0fMM     
    
    
    Im in Tahoe enroute to Irvine. Taking a slight detour to Sierra at Tahoe for the next two days to get a little skiing in :)    
    
    
    The wine collection in CA and FL is running a bit low. Just pulled a 2003 BV Merlot, I hope its good.    
    
    
    I'm at Sierra-at-Tahoe® Resort (Twin Bridges, CA) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/UeFXON     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2rdm43o0u     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/DpNV5yuM     
    
    
    Anyone in or around South Lake Tahoe right now?    
    
    
    I now totally understand why there is such a problem with drunk amish buggy drivers. Amish blue cheese pairs with... http://fb.me/23RXInlA0     
    
    
    The best way to spend Super Bowl Sunday (@ Sierra-at-Tahoe® Resort w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/Uj2lqq     
    
    
    I'm at Mirasol Apartment Homes http://4sq.com/XT35gs     
    
    
    I will be a judge at Startup Weekend Orange County, if you would like to attend use Discount code "FRIEND" for... http://fb.me/1vYerSCjT     
    
    
    I will be a judge at Startup Weekend Reno 

http://reno.startupweekend.org/  http://fb.me/1S8fUUI9g     
    
    
    I will be a Judge at Startup Weekend Orange County March 1-3, 2013 http://orangecounty.startupweekend.org/events/startup-weekend-orange-county-32013/ …    
    
    
    Hiring Mobile and PHP Developers, and Techops with LAMP/cloud experience. Contract/Intern/FTE positions available. Remote is an option.    
    
    
    Why hiring B players will kill your startup http://fb.me/2w9URixke     
    
    
    Marrow, From Jon’s Street Eats Guy, Coming to Oakland’s Uptown http://fb.me/HJQm8Nxw     
    
    
    Playing with Sonar  @ Mirasol Apartment Homes @sonar    
    
    
    http://fb.me/206zkt9cI     
    
    
    Definitely not safe for work,  and probably not safe for human consumption either. 

Rum, Whiskey, and Vodka.

"To... http://fb.me/KNGwTaD9     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/zfdO4LWm     
    
    
    Have fun Evan Kanter http://fb.me/DUoDF9Id     
    
    
    Finally managed to get a run in today, my head is in a much better place now.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2sDFI8q6e     
    
    
    Happy valentines day Christianne Bijasa Kernes Finn Kernes and Chloe. I miss you all very much.    
    
    
    Get recommendations from your friends without their knowledge http://fb.me/26ACGd6P3     
    
    
    Meet The Roots of Music, StubHub's Inaugural Rising Star http://fb.me/ySqyebJx     
    
    
    Caterham Superlight R500 | Uncrate http://fb.me/ES2ZNHll     
    
    
    The latest/greatest version of BuzzMob is available for download from iTunes now: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/buzzmob/id455241178?mt=8 …    
    
    
    Valentines dinner for one (@ Mirasol Apartment Homes) [pic]: http://4sq.com/X9BeLH     
    
    
    Running a 5K @ 8AM. Lets see what the SoCal competition looks like. http://www.timberwolf5k.com/     
    
    
    Who do I know in SoCal?    
    
    
    I hate mornings    
    
    
    http://fb.me/WxGM4xBH     
    
    
    The food/wine is great, but eating alone sucks.    
    
    
    Too lazy to run, or shop for furniture... Maybe I'll just look for a motorcycle :)    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1YsMDKsNE     
    
    
    What's the chances I get away with flip-flops an a t-shirt at this event?

http://globalgreen.org/events/189     
    
    
    A little grossed out... The hot tub at my apartment is "foamy".    
    
    
    And that is why I don't even try to make the bed! http://fb.me/2eYyvLLMe     
    
    
    I couldn't help myself 

http://m.youtube.com/#/watch?v=fuMo38g7P4I&desktop_uri=%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DfuMo38g7P4I …    
    
    
    You may find yourself in a beautiful house with a beautiful wife. You may ask yourself, well, how did I get here?... http://fb.me/2icLvGmCp     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2sSI3Qoij     
    
    
    Just ran this race. Not sure what my time was (somewhere around 21), bib number 238.

http://occrun.com/  http://fb.me/CMzOe86e     
    
    
    Love it... http://fb.me/Xo2YEq1E     
    
    
    Things heard around the office "Edmond tried to do it through the front facing backend"    
    
    
    I didn't think it was possible to eat too much spinach... Until now.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/23aPVEcbf     
    
    
    I'm part of Global Green Pre-Oscar Party BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2789 " pic.twitter.com/dEvZTjps    
    
    
    I'm part of Kairos Global Summit BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2778 " pic.twitter.com/5SpYDVmJ    
    
    
    I'm part of Parkland Golf and Country Club BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2631 "    
    
    
    I'm part of BuzzMob Headquarters BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/169 " pic.twitter.com/yYyC9zIf    
    
    
    http://fb.me/28XqiaGq7     
    
    
    Jeff Jackel and I will be Attending the Global Green USA Pre-Oscar Party at the Avalon Hollywood tonight. If you... http://fb.me/2idzliZfP     
    
    
    Join @JeffJackel and I tonight for the @globalgreen pre-oscar party on @buzzmob (iOS or Android).    
    
    
    Rather than being completely clueless here... Who?    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1StiIIUTJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/11Vkmqjkk     
    
    
    @michellebranch @nickmaybury the highlight of the night    
    
    
    10th Annual Pre-Oscar Party http://globalgreen.org/gallery/preoscar0213/ …    
    
    
    Monster goldfish are breeding in Lake Tahoe http://fb.me/2tUjOaH8R     
    
    
    The hashtag for Startup Weekend Reno is #SWReno. Why? Because i said so.    
    
    
    Heading to Tahoe tonight, then Reno for Startup Weekend Reno. Cant wait to meet all the budding entrepreneurs! #SWReno @buzzmob @SWReno    
    
    
    @BuzzMob has create a Mob called "Startup Weeknd Reno" for #SWReno. Time to download the app for your iOS/Android devices.    
    
    
    I'm part of Startup Weekend Reno BuzzMob. Check it out from your mobile device "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2791 " pic.twitter.com/2Qvr5VpGKu    
    
    
    Made it to Tahoe!    
    
    
    AT&T Mobile App Hackathon - Miami http://fb.me/2OdiEpdD8     
    
    
    I look forward to meeting all the #swreno participants this weekend. Internships are waiting @BuzzMob for the most impressive of the bunch.    
    
    
    @Cuskelly - @sonar and @thepool have the same problem as all the rest, sparse community.    
    
    
    Adrienne Tran (adriennetran) on Twitter http://fb.me/FX5lkY60     
    
    
    http://fb.me/FRAandXg     
    
    
    I have to hand it to Mars for having incredibly accurate marketing. Snickers really does satisfy! Though, i... http://fb.me/2uzrczmbB     
    
    
    i like the hub&spoke growth model. where do you have critical mass today? i would be happy to try it there @thepool    
    
    
    @benkepes @atscottybrowns solid time!    
    
    
    @Joshmedia *mistakes* happen ;)    
    
    
    hashtags are so 2010 - http://techcrunch.com/2010/10/15/curate-this-nsyght-makes-curation-as-easy-as-hashtagging-your-tweets/ … @buzzmob @LARKRPRE @singly    
    
    
    This is just a little bit awesome http://fb.me/BwIrUHRr     
    
    
    At lest Poughkeepsie isn't THE most miserable city http://fb.me/2eT1LA1ny     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2nMMeMZ9o     
    
    
    I kind of want to start a startup accelerator/incubator.    
    
    
    First night sleeping on a real bed in weeks. It was incredible!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FaqEgzkl     
    
    
    Good day at Sierra today.    
    
    
    Where can i find Turkey and Qual eggs?    
    
    
    Where can i find Turkey and Quail eggs?    
    
    
    #swreno final pitches about to begin    
    
    
    Great time at #swreno last night. Really impressed by the work you all did this weekend.    
    
    
    Looking forward to @SWOrangeCounty #SWOC. To sweeten the deal, @buzzmob is offering internships to the most impressive of the bunch.    
    
    
    Rode my road bike to work today, such a good way to start the day.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/zmedeaSL     
    
    
    I'm kind of embarrassed to say this... But "one last thing" was a really good movie    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1X2lLcFKD     
    
    
    Awesome http://fb.me/252FYA4CG     
    
    
    40 Amazing Grilled Cheese Sandwich Recipes http://fb.me/DxDpsYgr     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2hIfVRrZ3     
    
    
    Viral marketing is not a marketing strategy | @andrewchen http://fb.me/1yhiOXjfC     
    
    
    Best Advice: Life&rsquo;s Too Short to Work with Dullards http://fb.me/1gnd8TunT     
    
    
    After Recruiting Founding StubHub CTO, Buzzmob Overhauls Its Social Events App To Help Brands Connec http://fb.me/24GDnq8tq     
    
    
    @BuzzMob is looking for PHP developers in Inrvine @OCStartup    
    
    
    Looking forward to meeting all the talented people at #SWOrangeCounty tonight.    
    
    
    @caypenmagazine I look forward to meeting you at #SWOrangeCounty this weekend    
    
    
    @SparksZilla I look forward to meeting you at #SWOrangeCounty this weekend    
    
    
    How to Change the World: The Art of Creating a Community http://fb.me/2mfjhy27C     
    
    
    @SparksZilla @jimengland I may have met Jim once or twice… We also may have the same grandparents :)    
    
    
    #SWOrangeCounty, download and use the BuzzMob app this weekend and gain exclusive access to judges, mentors, product giveaways, and beer.    
    
    
    Finn Kernes, if you kept doing this you could have gone to the olympics http://fb.me/24v6oTcZv     
    
    
    Why Every Office Should Switch To Walking Desks | TechCrunch http://fb.me/FKJig1ve     
    
    
    I hate listening to people talk about me, but it's better than talking about myself #SWOrangeCounty #swoc    
    
    
    Sacked wine guy says build a story around your product #swoc #SWOrangeCounty good advice    
    
    
    Really, pick your exit strategy at day one? Or focus on maintaining exit options? #swoc #sworangecounty    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FLeq92s8     
    
    
    I hear pro-drivers have strong necks... I would love to see danica patrick with a baby elephant hanging from her head    
    
    
    http://www.geeksaresexy.net/2013/02/17/social-media-in-real-life-comic/ …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/C4rB7Ceb     
    
    
    Chicken-wing theft kicked off burglary spree in Parkland, authorities say http://fb.me/26R2eeX2b     
    
    
    Luca G. | A St. Baldrick's Participant http://fb.me/1BSxrkpfl     
    
    
    Ugh... It's 1am and I can't sleep because I have a ton of work related things running through my head. The curse of doing what you love.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/C4IsWeJ8     
    
    
    LSLAWPR | Lalchandani Simon featured in the Daily Business Review http://fb.me/1Bvlj9iPD     
    
    
    Just watched "Beware the Gonzo" while wrapping up some work, surprisingly good movie... Now if i would just stop... http://fb.me/zyl3mjaN     
    
    
    Curation by Location is just a little bit awesome    
    
    
    I'm kind of a momma's boy, not my momma (sorry mom)... My kids momma.    
    
    
    "Walk around looking through a fake lens. Apps this good, whose got time to make friends?"    
    
    
    I'm hiring! Senior PHP Developer at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/3yEjBa     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Mobile Developer at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/2rzT-D     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Marketing Coordinator for Location Based at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/YNZ6Nr     
    
    
    How The Papal Conclave Selects The Pope http://fb.me/2JASq5FeQ     
    
    
    awesome http://fb.me/1oNSm9CKR     
    
    
    Long Exposures Reveal Movements of Sleeping Couples http://fb.me/127kJGM3k     
    
    
    You know its been a long day when I start quoting fight club in press briefings.    
    
    
    I'm craving bone marrow, kale, foie gras, oysters, beef tartar, and sashimi...    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/29VmVExZS     
    
    
    i think i could win a best dressed contest; and no, my facebook account has not been hacked.    
    
    
    didnt get a run in this morning :(    
    
    
    http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/social-media-reach-helps-quality-counts-more-147906 … http://fb.me/2csOxxJtt     
    
    
    Impressive http://fb.me/H2pQ64xD     
    
    
    It’s Time to Kill the Email Signoff http://fb.me/2SiR0LIGB     
    
    
    sorry facebook, #hashtags are not the right solution for content curation.  BuzzMob http://fb.me/DJ1Hwyed     
    
    
    Should i do this? http://fb.me/2jhnFTX2x     
    
    
    Reminder to self: replace office chair with ball    
    
    
    things heard around the office "i love sitting on a ball, we should get some balls"    
    
    
    Teens' Nude Photos From Snapchat Lead to Investigation http://fb.me/1huFRFDbN     
    
    
    now im craving escargot    
    
    
    this is what makes Florida awesome http://fb.me/2qqSEwHk7     
    
    
    had a productive morning today, the afternoon was not so good. hunger got the best of me... lets hope for a productive evening.    
    
    
    "People who fight me always have a plan, then I punch them in the face"    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/wY6rjohr     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/133AFI6TQ     
    
    
    this movie has an unbelievable cast http://fb.me/2Ifc8kCJW     
    
    
    maybe ill check out the SoCal climbing gym's tomorrow    
    
    
    Retired husband syndrome - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia http://fb.me/1jQjgqCh6     
    
    
    didnt set an alarm last night, and ended up sleeping until 4PM today. i really need to get out for a run...    
    
    
    Finn Kernes - this made me think of you http://fb.me/zuujxz3x     
    
    
    http://Amazon.com : Buying Choices: Benchmade 1100 Series Tactical Pen, Damasteel Body, Damasteel Grip, Blac http://fb.me/2uQ1hrw1A     
    
    
    what to do around irvine today?    
    
    
    Nate Weisiger Daniel Fettinger Eric Etu  - Does this sound familiar ;) I also vaguely remember filing a patent... http://fb.me/1XMJ8ihwB     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2gtIlmDab     
    
    
    how has the movie "fierce people" been around since 2005, and this is the first  time i'm seeing it?    
    
    
    White Women's Workout http://fb.me/2PhHcW2YC     
    
    
    How Beer Gave Us Civilization - Slashdot http://fb.me/2iQeocjY4     
    
    
    now the whole world will get to the seven summits before we do -  Finn Kernes http://fb.me/1txBeu3iV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1FABjqLPG     
    
    
    Jeff Jackel is a Buzzword generator    
    
    
    I just got the best gift ever from Christianne Bijasa Kernes, a mattress :)    
    
    
    I'm not to proud to admit that i bought boxed wine, and i like it.    
    
    
    Horrible Grammar in Text Messages Could Be a Sign of a Stroke http://fb.me/1V8TLqvhv     
    
    
    Most frustrating conversation I have ever had with a vendor    
    
    
    I stand by my belief that Jason Mraz is among the best lyricists of all time    
    
    
    A Requiem for Chuck Norris’s Beard http://fb.me/1KKHtjl8w     
    
    
    http://fb.me/Ea2xS1ph     
    
    
    http://www.newuniversity.org/2006/10/features/the_homeless_of_irvine14/ …    
    
    
    I love that this exists http://fb.me/2R0NioJZA     
    
    
    in 1998 i walked into a dealership to buy one of these, after spending months researching cars. The dealer... http://fb.me/11DkxLO58     
    
    
    In 1998 i walked into a dealership to buy one of these, after spending months researching cars. The dealer... http://fb.me/DOKaMlDD     
    
    
    Not sure if you give this to someone you really love, or someone you really want to kill... either way, yes please... http://fb.me/28HqHHqYV     
    
    
    I need some new skills. 

You know, like nunchuku skills, bow hunting skills, computer hacking skills... Girls... http://fb.me/2iBWvdJga     
    
    
    Whats your favorite?

I'm thinking the AC SHELBY COBRA, AUDI SPORT QUATTRO, BMW 2002, ACURA NSX, TOYOTA 2000GT,... http://fb.me/1WshdAhLx     
    
    
    Chloe thinks our apartment in Irvine is a hotel    
    
    
    BMW, Triumph, or Ducati?    
    
    
    I could go for some snoop goat http://fb.me/1dNRQSDq3     
    
    
    Im hungry http://fb.me/N96JrMIj     
    
    
    Maybe some really nice person will make this for me http://fb.me/33wENCoaq     
    
    
    11 Major Passover Food Fails http://fb.me/2CPPxv18z     
    
    
    And Paula Deen http://fb.me/1BaxMzD2x     
    
    
    Disputed Territories: Nice Jewish Girl Claims Foursquare Mayorship of Temple Mount http://fb.me/KOI8matD     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1F6DPlJnw     
    
    
    Mobile design: Avoid these 4 common user experience fails http://fb.me/1C39jJT67     
    
    
    Starbucks CEO Howard Schultz Slaps Down Anti-Gay Marriage Activist At Shareholder Meeting http://fb.me/1HnYt3gTG     
    
    
    Where are all the talented developers around Irvine CA?    
    
    
    I'm hiring! Marketing Coordinator for Location Based at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/YNZ6Nr     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Mobile Developer at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/2rzT-D     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Senior PHP Developer at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/3yEjBa     
    
    
    A little outdated, but awesome... http://fb.me/1XPrLKv6b     
    
    
    Remodel for Marrow - Whole Cookery http://fb.me/2H3Wz767A     
    
    
    Disney World photo captures couple together 15 years before they met | Toronto Star http://fb.me/Bn5SoQyY     
    
    
    I just backed this project, cant wait to taste what Jon cooks up! http://fb.me/TgWU1xWg     
    
    
    Ugh... Flat    
    
    
    7 ways to make your mobile app suck less http://fb.me/2kiJ3jLTg     
    
    
    http://500px.com/photo/16753529  http://fb.me/16plNhfQ7     
    
    
    Guy With 10,000 Tweets, 15 Followers About Ready To Hang It Up http://fb.me/215v8J7l1     
    
    
    http://fb.me/zkesBizd     
    
    
    Todd McKinnon: A Startup Is a Marathon, Not a Sprint http://fb.me/Ex5qBStT     
    
    
    http://fb.me/MODEdmxH     
    
    
    http://fb.me/F2Gawnma     
    
    
    The cell towers kind of ruin it    
    
    
    Anyone know where I can eat some Easter bunny? Rabbit stew sounds really good right now.    
    
    
    Easter brunch http://fb.me/2GgFQTAXa     
    
    
    why are sportiva shoes so ugly? http://fb.me/1jU0s5gNI     
    
    
    It's that time of year again http://fb.me/Br69tL6P     
    
    
    http://fb.me/24YaXYFW2     
    
    
    Ugh... Not feeling well    
    
    
    http://fb.me/IAX1s5fS     
    
    
    http://fb.me/15dfZk2kO     
    
    
    http://fb.me/NSZwghoN     
    
    
    How could i not share this? http://fb.me/16yvvrDi0     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1TojFzC4G     
    
    
    Finn Kernes Christianne Bijasa Kernes - Wow http://fb.me/2fu5WCLsj     
    
    
    StubHub Co-Founder Has New Startup, Spreecast, Rolling - TheStreet http://fb.me/1Sp26Lqvc     
    
    
    Ugh... Havent eaten anything but junk food since Friday, and haven't gotten much exercise in nearly 3 weeks, have... http://fb.me/M530QEHl     
    
    
    Happy April fools day    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1PThmW9VQ     
    
    
    whoever came up with findmyiphone... thank you!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/DYQK1yrf     
    
    
    I did this hike last saturday. no clue how someone gets lost back there. http://fb.me/CATQJ1RH     
    
    
    So close... But i cant throw a football, or make a "drum-tight" bed. http://fb.me/29XK69wtC     
    
    
    last time i climbed with Ethan (at mission cliffs in SF) he was a promising kid, now he's a beast http://fb.me/zVOIRwmF     
    
    
    Impressive office space http://fb.me/1lJy3ysME     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1jczniBzA     
    
    
    cazadores extra anejo limited edition is good, anyone want to help me drink it?    
    
    
    Cow = Yum = Gone    
    
    
    http://fb.me/27tY4r33W     
    
    
    I'm part of NABSHOW 2013 BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2861 "    
    
    
    Saddleback (Santiago Peak) Saturday was a failure. 

16 mile round trip, with 4000 ft of elevation gain. I was... http://fb.me/22a6Yq2p7     
    
    
    This song explains my family so well : Christianne Bijasa Kernes Finn Kernes Barbara Kernes Marc Kernes Kt... http://fb.me/1tPYCfWCs     
    
    
    Bob Dylan and Van Morrison Sing ‘Knockin’ on Heaven’s Door,’ 1998 http://fb.me/2kPW6biaK     
    
    
    ate a $17 burger tonight, and it was worth it... Carne Asada, Fried Egg, Blue Cheese, Fried Onions, Roasted Red... http://fb.me/HoNMjPdT     
    
    
    My Tupperware seems to have gone missing    
    
    
    When did it become cool to be a "computer geek"    
    
    
    Can't sleep    
    
    
    What will science come up with next? http://fb.me/17zrdlVIZ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2NrjZKRuQ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2HuLBcX8q     
    
    
    5 tips for creating great mobile app user interfaces http://fb.me/1sfUcbRvF     
    
    
    13 Reasons Shakira Should Be President Of The World http://fb.me/Gf3diNh7     
    
    
    Get This Salted Caramel Lobster Grilled Cheese, Available For One Week Only http://fb.me/2s3m1QVno     
    
    
    Next offsite? BuzzMob http://fb.me/14ASCymuC     
    
    
    Can't hide plastic surgery forever http://fb.me/2ojU10m8F     
    
    
    Did i not say that the price of bitcoin's were being manipulated? http://fb.me/2zAh2aqB7     
    
    
    I have poison oak :(    
    
    
    After a $41M loan, Foursquare still needs to prove it's an actual business http://fb.me/22XrmfNhY     
    
    
    This is hilarious http://fb.me/29SwWY0ft     
    
    
    Climbing is hard    
    
    
    You have to watch this! http://fb.me/szHh5D6B     
    
    
    Michael Jackson, Thats All    
    
    
    Heard at the Office "It's a big Mac" BuzzMob    
    
    
    Sometimes its overwhelming to be 3000 miles away from the people i love. - Christianne Bijasa Kernes Finn Kernes @Chloe Kernes    
    
    
    unwind or rewind?    
    
    
    http://fb.me/IhGURS4e     
    
    
    This is unbelievable http://fb.me/177Qyl2nl     
    
    
    You Must be Tripping! The Metasearch Platform for the Vacation Rental Industry http://fb.me/Q6CMzToe     
    
    
    Well said. Running a Marathon is suffering enough. http://fb.me/28nafVx3S     
    
    
    I love that google put this up http://fb.me/28RMK8udH     
    
    
    xkcd: Computer Problems http://fb.me/1kOZbkhTB     
    
    
    http://fb.me/22qAZsYuc     
    
    
    How is grounding all american airlines flights for a day not bigger news? http://fb.me/2qOCUfxXF     
    
    
    Great story http://fb.me/23qtQx0a4     
    
    
    Skiers attempt record with simultaneous back flip http://fb.me/GZbiVMPe     
    
    
    Life is hard    
    
    
    WHERE THE FUCK SHOULD I GO TO EAT? http://fb.me/1EEsS7iyE     
    
    
    A clothing store i might actually go into http://fb.me/Ok7R5AT4     
    
    
    How to Make Friends in a New City http://fb.me/C2UAoJV4     
    
    
    Testing BuzzMob #Knicks    
    
    
    http://fb.me/25GIaRisB     
    
    
    I cant wait to spend a very special birthday weekend with Christianne Bijasa Kernes, who looks prettier today... http://fb.me/13EwOF1lu     
    
    
    This seems to be bigger news today than Terrorism in Boston. http://fb.me/2sHockeXj     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1CzHRPEBr     
    
    
    http://fb.me/153tOgedz     
    
    
    BuzzMob    
    
    
    Looking forward to a great launch of the Santiago Hills Elementary BuzzMob tomorrow!    
    
    
    great story : Sriracha hot sauce purveyor turns up the heat http://fb.me/QlhWp1gK     
    
    
    I don't want to sleep tonight. Christianne Bijasa Kernes is leaving in the morning and I don't know when I will see her next.    
    
    
    I'm part of Stan Lee's Comikaze Expo BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2312 "    
    
    
    I'm part of AFI FEST BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/1750 "    
    
    
    I'm part of Yard House Buzz BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2856 "    
    
    
    I'm part of Irvine Spectrum Center BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2815 "    
    
    
    I'm part of BuzzMob Headquarters BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/169 "    
    
    
    http://fb.me/wJdG1qTo     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Mobile Developer at BuzzMob - Orange County, California Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/qdVXsP     
    
    
    What do you think of the new BuzzMob website? http://fb.me/27mZD6gW9     
    
    
    "In spite of all communication technologies, no invention is as effective as the sound of the human voice. When... http://fb.me/1Zw3kzWNU     
    
    
    "Human-beings are hardwired with the impulse to share our ideas, and the desire to know we’ve been heard. It’s... http://fb.me/1SCBjjXG3     
    
    
    The mob is growing http://fb.me/1sT7gjfsi     
    
    
    BuzzMob is Hiring! and whats cooler than getting paid to play with social media all day? http://fb.me/yKFOUZeM     
    
    
    http://fb.me/22yKaWpGA     
    
    
    I'm part of Stoneman Douglas High BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2860 " pic.twitter.com/r6myGhD8fi    
    
    
    I'm part of Park Trails Elementary BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2859 "    
    
    
    I'm part of Parkland Golf and Country Club BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2631 "    
    
    
    I have been rich, an I have been poor... And I'm not sure which I prefer...    
    
    
    Los Angeles' Best Grilled Cheeses http://fb.me/2k8IiMPCQ     
    
    
    I'm part of Canyon View Elementary BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ "    
    
    
    Download BuzzMob at http://itunes.apple.com/in/app/buzzmob/id455241178?mt=8 …    
    
    
    Ginger Ct Crew PGCC - Lemonade for Boston by Ginger Crew pic.twitter.com/dCoSVOyy6k    
    
    
    I can't remember the last time someone made me a meal...    
    
    
    http://fb.me/HPkyEiVQ     
    
    
    Climbing gym was supposed to close at 10, showed up at 8:20... Closing. Looks like I'll manage not to see another person all day.    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FXObey1l     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2UNN0NGja     
    
    
    House of cards was better than I thought. Not great (got way too predictable), but better than I thought it would be.    
    
    
    This is going to change the world http://fb.me/CWigi0Zs     
    
    
    LSD Inventor Albert Hofmann Dead at Age 102 | Wired Science | http://Wired.com  http://fb.me/2f3RqJLb9     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2DPz8rUpi     
    
    
    I cant believe this sort of thing is still happening http://fb.me/29eBUDUxP     
    
    
    http://fb.me/yjtW910i     
    
    
    Tech Profile: BuzzMob http://shar.es/l5808  via @agencypost    
    
    
    Tech Profile: BuzzMob - The Agency Post http://fb.me/RHGaMPd6     
    
    
    You should download this app :) http://fb.me/2AddJ9ncY     
    
    
    shakshuka for dinner :)    
    
    
    Mmmmmm. http://fb.me/15rIn7bOU     
    
    
    I could live out of a day pack...    
    
    
    i manage to set off the some alarm almost every night    
    
    
    Uptown Oakland’s Marrow: An Early Look http://fb.me/2m81PiO4m     
    
    
    Do any of these work if you cant see each other? http://fb.me/1GyScYsuV     
    
    
    This is either the best, or the worst movie I have ever seen.

http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/This_Must_Be_the_Place_(film) …    
    
    
    If there was a playlist describing my life, this song would surely be on it:... http://fb.me/2RhGZDcnY     
    
    
    I just used #Shazam to tag Achille's Heel: II. Second Bounce by Brooklyn Rider. http://shz.am/t56501937     
    
    
    Stupid blue light    
    
    
    i'm so impressed by the little things http://fb.me/15ypF2pqO     
    
    
    My goal is simple. I want a band to follow me around and put music to my life.    
    
    
    Fun new SWAG http://fb.me/1WWnyw59Z     
    
    
    I want to fight for something that matters... Only im not sure i know what matters.    
    
    
    Happy Mother's Day    
    
    
    Dinner for one http://fb.me/w3GSOfD2     
    
    
    So funny http://fb.me/2sTKPh111     
    
    
    I'm part of Aesthetic Climbing Gym BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2243 "    
    
    
    I'm part of Stoneman Douglas High BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2860 " pic.twitter.com/VIVKQr7QKU    
    
    
    Can't sleep    
    
    
    I'm part of Alton Cafe BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/2934 "    
    
    
    I'm part of Marist College BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ "    
    
    
    ZumBolly = Bollywood version of Zumba that is apparently taking over irvine    
    
    
    The Future Of Mobile-Social Could Spell The End For Social Networks http://techcrunch.com/2013/05/18/the-future-of-mobile-social-could-spell-the-end-for-social-networks/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    If it was all about the music his carrear would already be over #justabeaver #tool http://fb.me/25NbM81xd     
    
    
    Just gave blood...    
    
    
    As seen on buzzmob - "If you accidently get your phone wet, leave it in a bowl of rice. At night the rice will... http://fb.me/2ZSKXQb6D     
    
    
    Apple Airport Extreme, you suck. #justsaying    
    
    
    Beer, Words, Words, Words, Beer, Beer...    
    
    
    Incredible: teachers shielding students with their bodies. http://fb.me/1aD14lD5o     
    
    
    @BruxieWaffles Do you have a BuzzMob yet?    
    
    
    @MtgFeeCoach there are some great mobile apps (like buzzmob) designed to help with that    
    
    
    Yum http://fb.me/2vxzW7Ogx     
    
    
    things heard around the BuzzMob office "this guy in high school who was dating me"    
    
    
    Climbing is hard. The end.    
    
    
    Two people told me about this today, and I can only hope that it changes my life... http://fb.me/26uH7KAIa     
    
    
    @michellebranch check out http://upworthly.com , or join me for a beer... either way you win.    
    
    
    @jason_mraz you never seem to have a show when im in town, so how about meeting up for a beer?    
    
    
    @adamlevine its been a long time since french woods and cover bands. im in socal now, how about a drink?    
    
    
    Blue light

http://www.idahostatesman.com/2013/05/15/2576319/to-sleep-better-turn-on-the-light.html …    
    
    
    IBM has turned the Watson super computer into the first CYLON    
    
    
    things heard around the buzzmob office: "is this real" http://fb.me/2iClyny3H     
    
    
    this has been all over the news today http://fb.me/LIiuDPRl     
    
    
    I think I'm the last person still at the airport    
    
    
    Dance recital    
    
    
    I could really use a hand from my South Florida friends and social influencers with the roll-out of BuzzMob.... http://fb.me/2alyz6BeV     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2aL1Tn0LY     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2nxoV1PYZ     
    
    
    I wonder if i can find a nice piece of land in soutern ca to put one of these on? http://fb.me/L0Sojxnl     
    
    
    All the things I'm missing (yea I called you things)    
    
    
    http://fb.me/IFlZAf5F     
    
    
    I'm part of Club Therapy BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ "    
    
    
    I'm part of Red Dog Cantina BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ "    
    
    
    We are having a contest at work to see who can get the most likes for the BuzzMob facebook page. Please help me win!    
    
    
    this is kind of awesome! http://fb.me/1PGeItmyC     
    
    
    Time to get a new bike http://fb.me/1xPYyESnx     
    
    
    http://fb.me/29nwHUkSG     
    
    
    99 of my facebook friends 'like' my company page on facebook. Who will be the 100th to like BuzzMob?    
    
    
    Goodbye Elise, im going to miss you.    
    
    
    One of my favoite climbs at one my favorite places, except i use pro and have never done it in 4.5 minuites. http://fb.me/2pIaHgxgR     
    
    
    Is it better to go to jail for showering naked or for riding a bike without holding the handle bars? http://fb.me/NdYgSyOf     
    
    
    The air on fl is wet. It's not raining, and this can't possibly be described as humid... The air is just wet, and... http://fb.me/xXT0z74p     
    
    
    http://fb.me/VTLvjjDc     
    
    
    Are you a celebrity?    
    
    
    this never gets old http://fb.me/LqcMZxaa     
    
    
    Please help out my newest venture, BuzzMob, by liking the facebook page and downloading the app for ios or android... http://fb.me/DhdhNt9c     
    
    
    http://fb.me/P3iN8V9I     
    
    
    I wish I had an automatic drain on my pool, with all this rain It's about to overflow... Again.    
    
    
    How Teens Are Really Using Facebook http://fb.me/2CCqb9wFP     
    
    
    Crazy Travel Day...

6AM EDT Flight From Fort Lauderdale To Houstan made it onto the runway on time but had to... http://fb.me/2mREF9hsX     
    
    
    i'm really feeling my age today    
    
    
    http://fb.me/29OizK5LN     
    
    
    So much for unlimited data plans:

"ATT Free Msg: Your data usage has reached 3GB this month. Using more than 3GB... http://fb.me/1LmArxfKx     
    
    
    Ugh... Forgot my laptop power supply in the office, lets hope my battery holds out.    
    
    
    This looks... Wow... http://fb.me/1nzeocSkq     
    
    
    Galactus lives in the palm of our hand http://fb.me/2sm5jqAqR     
    
    
    So happy that Finn Kernes is taking classes at Berkeley http://fb.me/w3EC2NTs     
    
    
    Why are back dimples sexy on a woman and gross on a man?    
    
    
    Have you liked/downloaded BuzzMob yet? http://fb.me/1CybSgUZd     
    
    
    Seriously considering dumping my Pandora One account for MOG    
    
    
    As much as a still love the triump speed triple, im thinking this might be a good option http://fb.me/2gwLJkYlk     
    
    
    OK, MOG wins    
    
    
    Yum http://fb.me/2Ggh3YOt7     
    
    
    Some of you are missing out http://fb.me/2rB5boFaa     
    
    
    Life is better in Tahoe    
    
    
    Brad Filip seems to have survived tasting some Laphroaig Quarter Cask Scotch    
    
    
    LP is back at the top of my office music playlist    
    
    
    Stupid food porn http://fb.me/2NCEfpyyr     
    
    
    I think im in love http://fb.me/H01NUw52     
    
    
    Buzz buzz buzz    
    
    
    More buzzing pic.twitter.com/Y1GyRPdZHR    
    
    
    Im only 9 likes short of taking the lead in the office contest to have the most friends like BuzzMob... http://fb.me/2BfrSZm6B     
    
    
        
    
    
    Congratulations Gokul Rajaram #5 http://fb.me/2cPPwYK8x     
    
    
    Plans Change    
    
    
    http://fb.me/EH2AgvCZ     
    
    
    #hashtag    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2G6Ge4o0p     
    
    
    Looking forward to visiting this weekend http://fb.me/RUtKqpsw     
    
    
    Could this be the replacement for Elise? http://fb.me/1KRReTx8d     
    
    
    There arent many people i would want to see wearing this http://fb.me/2x2tsbWk7     
    
    
    High fives are annoying    
    
    
    Why is this not bigger news? http://fb.me/10auWb3nz     
    
    
    But how would you use BuzzMob to meet new people at the bar? http://fb.me/2uupoLjqX     
    
    
    happy first day of summer    
    
    
    that just happened    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2C6Dti9NJ     
    
    
    This is going to be worth watching http://fb.me/2myuop4Oy     
    
    
    Its about time. #IRS #Justice    
    
    
    Study: Women avoid computer science careers because they think 'nerds' are smelly and pale: http://www.geekwire.com/2013/study-women-choose-computer-science-careers-nerd-stereotypes/ …    
    
    
    things heard at BuzzMob "im not poking anyone"    
    
    
    Stupid blue light http://fb.me/2e6D4Dzax     
    
    
    Babblr - chat for tumblr    
    
    
    Next gen democracy - raise issues and present solutions with govt    
    
    
    Vow to be chic - rent bridesmade dresses    
    
    
    Cadreas - not sure what they do    
    
    
    Qgits - words words words    
    
    
    Animal legs - furry crutches    
    
    
    Yes I'm at a pitch comp, and yes these are some of the ideas I'm seeing    
    
    
    Septium - mobile payments    
    
    
    The "I'm feeling" feature on Facebook is awesome... I hope this translates into content ranked by sentiment.    
    
    
    Smart Communities are the Heart of the Smart City Machine http://fb.me/6nxfWZzy3     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2dlMjWqT3     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2tVasCUEw     
    
    
    They are very attached to one another    
    
    
    The biggest Bay Area restaurant openings from the first half of 2013 http://fb.me/1ZNL3Cp4g     
    
    
    heard at BuzzMob - "to get through all this stuff i have to actually have friends"    
    
    
    3 calls before 7:30AM from a blocked number. do these offshoring companies really think that they are going to do... http://fb.me/1Ymw0t9wg     
    
    
    Its getting really hard for a new app to gain traction. A free app needs to be downloaded 72,000 times a day to... http://fb.me/E4kpn4Of     
    
    
    Wow... That was fast! http://fb.me/2OmNbnqDg     
    
    
    Nothing earth shattering here, but Marko does a great job of articulating what i have been saying for the last... http://fb.me/1RBOGVASi     
    
    
    I'm part of Lake Mission Viejo BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ "    
    
    
    New camping gear? http://fb.me/6lchCEeJt     
    
    
    I couldnt help myself http://fb.me/2yFd3Rg0p     
    
    
    Yum http://fb.me/2d8mKvEPK     
    
    
    I just threw up a little http://fb.me/2hJ29yiq2     
    
    
    Chris heard this while waiting in line at Disneyland today:
 
Guy: Hi ladies! What are your names?
Girls: I'm Go and her name is Away.    
    
    
    heard at BuzzMob : "I'm alive, hi"    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Dad, hope its a great one.

It seems like facebook has you all figured out, they recomend... http://fb.me/6igqQk0Ra     
    
    
    Cant wait to get home! http://fb.me/2ij7S2iAz     
    
    
    Download BuzzMob at http://www.buzzmob.com     
    
    
    A clear example of the impact of computers on human development http://fb.me/2qGWoopD0     
    
    
    LOL http://fb.me/6pdzNrB0m     
    
    
    Why do we share stories, news, and information with others? http://fb.me/6mfigpXO1     
    
    
    Murphy's Laws of Camping: Funny Camping Lessons http://fb.me/1rtuE0zmU     
    
    
    Like http://fb.me/2LPLCGqp5     
    
    
    Is anyone surprised by this? http://fb.me/2PhQ3kPcb     
    
    
    Yea... 31.8 percent of americans being obese is still nothing to be proud of http://fb.me/2g6BqU2pO     
    
    
    I kind of love this article. http://fb.me/JINYRdC9     
    
    
    Too hungry to think. Time to drink Beer.    
    
    
    Awesome night... Christianne Bijasa Kernes made dinner, and I got to eat it :)    
    
    
    feeling Hungry    
    
    
    The 7 Types of Hashtag Abusers http://fb.me/YFoOUk3z     
    
    
    SEC Lifts Ban On General Solicitation, Allowing Startups To Advertise That They’re Fundraising |... http://fb.me/1LbBsqBkR     
    
    
    A New Way to Measure Engagement at Your Event? | BizBash http://fb.me/2O1750Wb6     
    
    
    WATCH THIS: Always Finish Things Off http://fb.me/OJz1mfCh     
    
    
    This is what happens when im hungry... http://fb.me/28R70Fq9d     
    
    
    Or this http://fb.me/1lO558mkP     
    
    
    all i have to say is... "Finger Tablet" http://fb.me/1ECexlekM     
    
    
    This would make my life so much better http://fb.me/BnQ0Pz3t     
    
    
    the future of work from home? Christianne Bijasa Kernes http://fb.me/2WeTjRMhY     
    
    
    Did Klout score ever matter? and if it did, does it still matter?    
    
    
    It's really that simple http://fb.me/2l2eR6Imy     
    
    
    I hope I dont die anytime soon http://fb.me/2G1TzPehB     
    
    
    "You don’t get to a position like yours Richard with anything less than a generous sprinkling of observational... http://fb.me/2r9LKYZMr     
    
    
    This is just a little bit awesome http://fb.me/RwNVUSLA     
    
    
    you'll put an eye out with that http://fb.me/B5BxicTg     
    
    
    Missing woman's body found 28 years later, behind false wall http://fb.me/2f2Ok6sHt     
    
    
    Sick Of Paying Rent? Just Build Your Own Tiny Palace, Like These Guys Did. http://fb.me/1hF2E7TLS     
    
    
    In Case You Missed It, Here's What You May Not Realize About The Whole Trayvon Martin Thing http://fb.me/RnHkoP1d     
    
    
    ISIS | iamagamer http://fb.me/Db1GJckj     
    
    
    "The site is run “by a fraternity of Homo-Sensitive Roman Catholic Priests” for those seeking to find “like-minded... http://fb.me/GaYIxPTG     
    
    
    This makes me hungry http://fb.me/1DV0rFL6K     
    
    
    maybe he should have just said she had a bad case of "kim kardashian" http://fb.me/2NGyd6fSB     
    
    
    Is it wrong that i want to eat the blerch? http://fb.me/PelcwM9E     
    
    
    The Typical Day Of A Kid In The Early '90s http://fb.me/Ow07iBl2     
    
    
    Is this real? http://fb.me/XaiVoIsZ     
    
    
    http://assets.lifehack.org/wp-content/files/2012/12/CLIMB-MOUNTAINS.jpg?ecd364 … http://fb.me/2e84ytef5     
    
    
    Sweet. i still have some of these things. http://fb.me/2yJlFiQs9     
    
    
    didnt go to the gym tonight — feeling lazy    
    
    
    great infographic i just stumbledupon http://fb.me/EOlUeQ8G     
    
    
    next time you need a little quiet http://fb.me/2ndCtdeSI     
    
    
    I think i would do ok http://fb.me/KBIhmUll     
    
    
    Just got mistaken for a student at chapman — feeling young    
    
    
    "I Had Sex With My Cat And Everyone Knows," Aggrieved Oklahoma Woman Explained To Arresting Officer http://fb.me/U7l99Td8     
    
    
    Chapman University - The booth at chapman 
Shared from @BuzzMob http://fb.me/y86CxFsd     
    
    
    I'm part of Chapman University BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com/ring/3094 "    
    
    
    I have watched all 76 episodes of the 2003 version of battlestar galactica, and the caprica series... I guess i... http://fb.me/2UcSnH20h     
    
    
    10 Selfies Gone Terribly Wrong http://fb.me/1zbtTb1x8     
    
    
    26 Signs You Work In Social Media http://fb.me/Fnqm0FJD     
    
    
    Why Men Work So Many Hours http://fb.me/2NM8hHyXm     
    
    
    I'm part of Selfies BuzzMob. Check it out! "http://www.buzzmob.com "    
    
    
    Classic http://fb.me/2OuIkjCoV     
    
    
    now that the Vatican is running a website for priests to "hookup", we also have this: http://fb.me/2J2UwAiuw     
    
    
    I hate that this is so true http://fb.me/1oyj5NqJF     
    
    
    Writing PRD's and Drinking Beer    
    
    
    um... http://fb.me/1xGxTudun     
    
    
    Why was there a dog wearing sunglasses? http://fb.me/2FDVdhz1p     
    
    
        
    
    
    It's about time http://fb.me/2xbBo32HU     
    
    
    Not the best execution, but still awesome http://fb.me/1BwEC5Nyu     
    
    
    SV Beer Week – A celebration of craft beer in Silicon Valley (July 28–August 3, 2013) http://fb.me/BTkdACXi     
    
    
    "The only thing surprising about this use case for Google Glass is that actual porn stars beat out exhibitionist... http://fb.me/2cfeRr5Nn     
    
    
    I really hope this finds its way into a museum, and the proceeds go to charity. http://fb.me/2OXlV8oB8     
    
    
    S.F. Has The Skinniest Men In The Nation http://fb.me/1OFgdLvLz     
    
    
    Eating frozen string beans and something that looks like a hockey puck — feeling unhappy    
    
    
    Funny because its true http://fb.me/2vRY3qTad     
    
    
    First-mover disadvantage: The challenges of hitting the market before it’s ready http://fb.me/2wuLhTq90     
    
    
    Irvine, CA http://fb.me/2jtnH3QZ5     
    
    
    Irvine, CA http://fb.me/2N8ltcCkI     
    
    
    Hmmm... http://fb.me/1VlX64UjJ     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1WW4J6TJT     
    
    
    http://fb.me/2xXtYSe8z     
    
    
    Hmm... Does this imply that teens are as likely to sext after a first date as they are to call each other on the... http://fb.me/2i8Dljblu     
    
    
    I'm Sick Of Pretending: I Don't "Get" Art | VICE United Kingdom http://fb.me/2fzxrwujo     
    
    
    Best story today http://fb.me/1RyRqCjtU     
    
    
    Anyone else think this bike is both awesome and ugly http://fb.me/1hWsoLT0e     
    
    
    Hungry

"the mountainous Reuben at Marrow (325 19th St., near Harrison St., Oakland, 510-251-1111) in Oakland,... http://fb.me/2f2SRbuUb     
    
    
    Crowdfunding Reaches Its Terrible, Glorious Climax With ‘Smart Vibrator’ Vibease | TechCrunch http://fb.me/2B5R3KWZM     
    
    
    Paralyzed Man Wakes to Find His Dog Bit Off His Testicle http://fb.me/1RihrnMpD     
    
    
    Play Video: Chloe and Ben get down http://fb.me/1zPbUA3EB     
    
    
    Long Overlooked, the Flourishing Philippines - BoF - The Business of Fashion http://fb.me/GdT6RTZ0     
    
    
    "Children should ride in a belt-positioning booster (that means a high-back!) until they are at least 4 foot, 9... http://fb.me/6phHxctME     
    
    
    Great read http://fb.me/2vimQgago     
    
    
    Tech In Motion: Orange County http://fb.me/WgTdp5Ex     
    
    
    http://fb.me/335bW2eLr     
    
    
    hew house? http://fb.me/6j0O10lcl     
    
    
    Enjoying a Lagunitas Brewing Co IPA for #IPADay http://fb.me/6pSfRf128     
    
    
    32 Reasons California Is The Most Beautiful State In The Country http://fb.me/1h36jsDEN     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1jY335uC0     
    
    
        
    
    
    I kind of want to try this http://fb.me/UamgAFB2     
    
    
    going to have to try making these http://fb.me/241CohwTS     
    
    
    Best thing i read today http://fb.me/377phGG9U     
    
    
    Great cover http://fb.me/1WZrSsTlt     
    
    
    best app ever! http://fb.me/1i5RJnzY9     
    
    
    heard at BuzzMob : "I would rather be dead Steve Jobs than alive Ashton Kutcher"    
    
    
    genius http://fb.me/23q6nhnDp     
    
    
    the future of gaming http://fb.me/VEHYvPHn     
    
    
    Next Summer? http://fb.me/2zLOYHQhc     
    
    
    Yes, its 5:15PM and im hungry http://fb.me/2BW1WZdCw     
    
    
    Ash 'n' Fashn - JEANS GIVEAWAY http://fb.me/2K2epxKup     
    
    
    Whats your favorite?

IS IT BETTER TO BE SINGLE OR MARRIED?
I don’t know which is better, but I’ll tell you one... http://fb.me/2fmh3HhKf     
    
    
    Be carefull who you hand your keys to... http://fb.me/1RlJQI0Xe     
    
    
    Classic http://fb.me/27wgtbZge     
    
    
    I'm 13 and None of My Friends Use Facebook http://fb.me/2gzqXE2L5     
    
    
    Just switched our home internet service in Tahoe to Charter. Lets hope this is better than the last provider!    
    
    
    Ducati Monster 1100EVO vs. BMW R 1200 R vs. Triumph Speed Triple vs. MV Agusta BRUTALE 1090 vs. Ducati... http://fb.me/OYN68aW3     
    
    
    I love it http://fb.me/GLmj6JXJ     
    
    
    Chris [Ashton] Kutcher is my Man Crush

1. I believe opportunity looks a lot like hard work.
2. The sexiest thing... http://fb.me/HRUKwmVX     
    
    
    Did you ever say goodbye to someone knowing it would be forever? http://fb.me/1Rt791iYY     
    
    
    Movies have come a long way since 1987 http://fb.me/34xmz55I1     
    
    
    Dad is dead. You're next. Love Moth http://fb.me/6qVGQHI9A     
    
    
    Ugh... Cant hear past 16000Hz http://fb.me/RT6JnZ56     
    
    
    I'm still hungry, you'd better watch your lunch — in San Francisco, CA http://fb.me/6qcMp0qxq     
    
    
    The listing agent for the house we want to rent in Albany CA might be the least responsive and most dismissive... http://fb.me/11KXkb5pi     
    
    
    worth 11:38 http://fb.me/SEC1kKQl     
    
    
    How about just buying land on the beach in half moon bay and putting a yurt on it?    
    
    
    which version do you prefer? bob or adele? http://fb.me/6qK7duMoc     
    
    
    Chances are that I'm going to get murdered today.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Johnnie Walker Blue Kind of Night    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1I0Dnn4Gp     
    
    
    I cant remember the last time i bought tickets on StubHub    
    
    
    It's nice to be home, even if home is the old (and new) neighbors house    
    
    
    http://fb.me/UWFVy948     
    
    
    New School: Architecture Student Turns A School Bus Into A Nice-Looking Home On Wheels http://fb.me/Xtv8nACe     
    
    
    http://fb.me/6iJteJErz     
    
    
    Study: To The Human Brain, Me Is We http://fb.me/2TqK9YBuB     
    
    
    happy anaversary Marc Kernes and Barbara Kernes    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1nhGTJZGd     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/13NEwj38E     
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2jrW2oTvN     
    
    
    First time over the new bridge    
    
    
        
    
    
    Zach working hard http://fb.me/13EBmE3DD     
    
    
        
    
    
    Mmmm... Bacon http://fb.me/WUrVxaCr     
    
    
    Christianne Bijasa Kernes, hope you are having a great first day! 

are you nervous yet?    
    
    
    I love our new home. When someone takes a shower, the kitchen gets an awesome water feature...    
    
    
    Major storm in the kitchen this morning... It must be coming down 6 inches per hour.    
    
    
    Not a big fan of oracle right now. Open world prep has added 45 min to my commute... And I don't have tickets to the event    
    
    
        
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2T6qmrhcD     
    
    
    Epic day on Tallac. Rain, snow, wind, lightning, and we lost David    
    
    
        
    
    
    Children are suffering a severe deficit of play – Peter Gray – Aeon http://fb.me/3csZSDNCu     
    
    
    this might be the best blog post ever http://fb.me/18BJpmHW6     
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing Jen O'Neal speak... While i drink :) http://fb.me/KRd6XV79     
    
    
        
    
    
    Poor Chloe has my lungs... Which means that once she outgrows the athsma she will be a distance runner. Life only gets harder.    
    
    
    I love comcast. First they didn't show up for a 4pm Sunday appointment. Then I got a 7:30 to 8am appointment for... http://fb.me/2Cd6URj9x     
    
    
    hope to see you there! http://fb.me/GKLeQ4rM     
    
    
    Awesome http://fb.me/2V8pnvhTZ     
    
    
    I thought the federal govt was shut down? http://fb.me/1WzJcU588     
    
    
    Scientists Used Facebook For The Largest Ever Study Of Language And Personality — And The... http://fb.me/11BL6O9G2     
    
    
    This took Sinead O'Connors website down http://fb.me/6nMyrQVKP     
    
    
    Which will be the next keg? http://fb.me/114eluJET     
    
    
    The Psychological Price of Entrepreneurship http://fb.me/6w6X2vBpK     
    
    
    5 Benefits Of Having A Smart And Successful Wife http://fb.me/6w3mOQIZQ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2roSz2jZ0     
    
    
    BoostCTR: Performance-Driven Ad Optimization http://fb.me/11tgrHw6U     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://fb.me/20gdn7EnH     
    
    
    Kill me    
    
    
    Traditional 40's Pinup Photos With Models Wearing High Speed Milk http://fb.me/1qsJYKNR9     
    
    
    What i started my day to http://fb.me/1P1ncx4YB     
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for French and Spanish speaking writers. If you are interested, sign up here... http://fb.me/32dUoTNOv     
    
    
    "I work in social media" http://fb.me/6ipOnWvon     
    
    
    Finn Kernes, you cant try this... http://fb.me/6jDXaotKZ     
    
    
    I still want someone to follow me everywhere I go and put a soundtrack to my life...    
    
    
    I win... Again    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2Jdi8Vqxa     
    
    
    Bye Tahoe... See you next weekend :)    
    
    
    Dads http://fb.me/2u7X5o6uz     
    
    
    http://thumbnails.visually.netdna-cdn.com/myersbriggs-personality-socioeconomic-status_525f2eea9b337 … http://fb.me/13YQB4zUF     
    
    
    Tinder: The Movie (Official Trailer) http://fb.me/17TSwv3JV     
    
    
    This is not who I am and this is not OK… http://fb.me/6wG9sjrhj     
    
    
    Great Album! http://fb.me/2AG3Nhm0D     
    
    
    Time is a thing http://fb.me/32Z0OY7dI     
    
    
    "I didn't realize there were this many lesbians leading this country but they certainly show up in Girl Scout... http://fb.me/31QOF4G1K     
    
    
    What's with 101 this morning? http://fb.me/6wvUZjXBT     
    
    
    Its about time! http://fb.me/2B8DPVBgK     
    
    
    Happy birthday Kai http://fb.me/39cheCf31     
    
    
    The 10 people you'll find in the Apple store http://fb.me/2Whu0DU0U     
    
    
    Hungry http://fb.me/179aCSGOb     
    
    
    Rob Lenderman, McDonald's made a sandwitch just for you! http://fb.me/1YuFHKEZm     
    
    
        
    
    
    Front End Software Engineer http://fb.me/2iyKxLTJJ     
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Front End Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3iEfagw6  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: UI/UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3Wgiagwp  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Account Executive
http://jobvite.com/m?3F4magw0  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Analytics Specialist
http://jobvite.com/m?3x3oagwT  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Customer Success Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3DYragwX  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Analyst
http://jobvite.com/m?3qjtagw7  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Display Client Operational Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3lBvagwm  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Marketing Associate
http://jobvite.com/m?3BJwagwL  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Product Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?34Vyagws  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. NET Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3vfDagwi  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Content and PR Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?30KKagwp  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?39tQagwn  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Front End Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3EITagwa  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: UI/UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3vGVagw1  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Account Executive
http://jobvite.com/m?331ZagwY  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Analytics Specialist
http://jobvite.com/m?3iZ1agwd  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Customer Success Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?30Z3agwX  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Analyst
http://jobvite.com/m?3go4agwD  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Display Client Operational Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3tN5agwg  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Marketing Associate
http://jobvite.com/m?3o77agwx  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Product Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3fnabgwI  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. NET Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3jDgbgw8  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. Platform Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3cEibgw4  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: EBR (Sales Associate)
http://jobvite.com/m?3bcmbgwF  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Content and PR Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3jZpbgwD  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Database Administrator
http://jobvite.com/m?3Gmsbgwq  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3uCvbgwx  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Front End Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3raAbgw7  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: UI/UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3odCbgw9  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Analytics Specialist
http://jobvite.com/m?3YiFbgwR  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Analyst
http://jobvite.com/m?3CMHbgw1  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Display Client Operational Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3gcLbgw9  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Product Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3pAObgwJ  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. NET Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3mZRbgw8  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. Platform Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3N5SbgwG  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: EBR (Sales Associate)
http://jobvite.com/m?39hUbgwg  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Content and PR Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3GcVbgwJ  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Database Administrator
http://jobvite.com/m?3OsXbgw9  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3fSYbgw1  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Front End Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3wA0bgw2  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: UI/UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3Ur1bgwi  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Account Executive
http://jobvite.com/m?31F2bgwE  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Analytics Specialist
http://jobvite.com/m?3tS3bgwk  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Analyst
http://jobvite.com/m?3Pa8bgw3  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Display Client Operational Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3ENacgwy  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Marketing Associate
http://jobvite.com/m?3e7ccgwu  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Product Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3jhdcgwK  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: QA Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3WwecgwD  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. NET Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3eiicgwL  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Sr. Platform Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3IIkcgwH  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: EBR (Sales Associate)
http://jobvite.com/m?335ocgwt  #job    
    
    
        
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Database Administrator
http://jobvite.com/m?3ihrcgwX  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Data Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3RvscgwL  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: Front End Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3rPtcgwG  #job    
    
    
    BoostCTR is looking for: UI/UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3h8vcgwR  #job    
    
    
    The Startup Spouse: On Risks, Trade-Offs And Never Sleeping On The Floor http://onstartups.com/tabid/3339/bid/86543/The-Startup-Spouse-On-Risks-Trade-Offs-And-Never-Sleeping-On-The-Floor.aspx … via @dharmesh    
    
    
    http://fb.me/QFXEbUUP     
    
    
    Infographic: When it comes to Millennials, are you talking to strangers? http://post.ly/54Nu7  via @briansolis    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1N31YE8Tg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/VnEhAO3D     
    
    
    Science: Scientists Create Molecule to Make Teeth Cavityproof - @Gizmodo http://gizmodo.com/5924447/scientists-find-molecule-that-will-make-your-teeth-cavityproof …    
    
    
    I'm at The Sherry Abode (El Cerrito, CA) http://4sq.com/Nmlkrn     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1syw9SNAg     
    
    
    http://fb.me/tGpnSIB0     
    
    
    well… that was disappointing.    
    
    
    Sitting on BART across from a girl with green hair and tattooed eyebrows... Have to post nonsense like this on Facebook to avoid looking up.    
    
    
    Cookie time (@ Specialty's Cafe & Bakery) http://4sq.com/MdiQOx     
    
    
    "If you want a kitten, start out asking for a horse" http://fb.me/WDW8CEeI     
    
    
    http://fb.me/20ey4hyd1     
    
    
    Looks like a great event! http://fb.me/1WBjLNlJ8     
    
    
    I'm at Sausalito Espresso (San Francisco, CA) http://4sq.com/OYuFoX     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1PH2BtEkC     
    
    
    Lalchandani Simon named advisor to WEDWU, Inc. | PR NewsChannel http://fb.me/1elZiM3YO     
    
    
    http://www.dontevenreply.com/view.php?post=100 …    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1N1DECALJ     
    
    
    blood makes noise    
    
    
    http://fb.me/1uHsQ0vgx     
    
    
    I wonder what happened to Pat Powers. Pat, Erin Mokarzel and I shared an apartment while I was at Marist. 15... http://fb.me/2c8RskSUn     
    
    
    I think i need this http://fb.me/1czFeEYyH     
    
    
    