New ISTE Mobile App: http://bit.ly/byaN0M    
    
    
    Verizon Wireless video about St Marys schools mobile phone project: http://bit.ly/aNBbup    
    
    
    SIGML Bookstudy Chp. 8: Design and Devt. of Mobile Learning Objects: http://bit.ly/crWMAX Register and participate!!    
    
    
    Finishing up lots of odds and ends before Christmas break (finally some time off!)    
    
    
    Education Week's Technology Counts 2010: It's all about mobile learning: http://bit.ly/9cACY6    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://bit.ly/rtuyzM  #NEH #RCET #QR    
    
    
    Don't let the #FCC betray us. Demand real #NetNeutrality. Accept no substitutes: http://freepr.es/egkmqk (via @freepress)    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chp. 9: From e-learning to mobile learning part I: http://bit.ly/aVCfM0    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chp. 9: From e-learning to mobile learning part 2: http://bit.ly/9k3oEE    
    
    
    Happy belated New Year everyone!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: two more #QR markers installed for the #GeoHistorian Project: http://bit.ly/q5E1XE     
    
    
    ISTE SIGML book study chp. 10: Mobile tools and svcs for formal and informal learning: http://bit.ly/a3PYk7 Please register and participate!    
    
    
    Enjoying the day off (MLK). Obama inauguration tomorrow!    
    
    
    blogged: Medienpadagogik call for papers on mobile learning: http://bit.ly/9pkJRX    
    
    
    @jont Good report, nothing really new. Blogged at http://tinyurl.com/73gfpm    
    
    
    Good inauguration speech by Obama. Let's hope his actions will match his words. He's got his work cut out for him!!!    
    
    
    @kathtrinder Photo wallpaper. Of course a DUTCH invention ;). And yes electronic is better, and why not? We already have digital photoframes    
    
    
    Still freezing cold over here. And of course we're going camping this weekend, in tents ...    
    
    
    Still defrosting from camp out. It got as low as -19C/-2F. Mummybags rule!    
    
    
    @coolcatteacher Enjoy your break!! Ours was this week but I had to work all week :(    
    
    
    Has anybody used #TagWhat to create content? LMKWYT of it.    
    
    
    @delchoness  ok thanks, didn't know it was that new ...    
    
    
    RCETJ special issue on Handheld Learning 2009 (research papers) released at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX Worth a look!! Please RT    
    
    
    @delchoness  do you guys review tags before they are made public? Trying to do some testing... #TagWhat    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/09/27/celebrating-kent-history-reenacting/ … #geohistorian    
    
    
    @brettbobley Cool! and thanks.....    
    
    
    End of a very busy day. It was 65 degrees here today. Very unusual for Feb. in OH.    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study chp 12: Mobiles in Museums: http://bit.ly/dfqcnZ    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/oLEmV0  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    attending MLC09 (mobilelearning09.org) in DC. Just finished moderating our panel...    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/10/the-perils-of-public-history/ … #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/10/last-two-markers-installed/ … #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    RCETJ manuscript submissions for spring 2012 issue due 12/2/11: http://bit.ly/jnl6l0  please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Project Becomes a Community Effort: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/27/geohistorian-project-becomes-a-community-effort/ …    
    
    
    Three more days until the ISTE SIGML video contest entries are due! http://bit.ly/9sGqnV #sigml Some already in: http://bit.ly/c4oxiL    
    
    
    Just blogged: Local Historians Doing Local Research #GeoHistorian: http://bit.ly/sVcGrB     
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Presentation at #eTech Ohio 2012: http://bit.ly/tpJalv     
    
    
    @TomHarkin #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @DavidObey #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @ThadCochran #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @RepToddTiahrt #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    Our schools need 21st century education, #EETT. Fund #edtech at $500 m please RT    
    
    
    No funding for #edtech? No prep for 21st century. Fund #EETT at $500 please RT    
    
    
    As a parent  and researcher, I know our kids need relevant and meaningful #edtech skills. Fund #EETT at $500m please RT    
    
    
    First #UNESCO Mobile Learning week: http://bit.ly/uK6jQB  #mlearning #mobile    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian in #Kent Tree City Bulletin: http://bit.ly/rEh9Ab     
    
    
    Preparing to present about #GeoHistorian on Friday at #NCSS2011 in Washington DC: http://bit.ly/vYobEw     
    
    
    @sherah1918 Using YouTube to host videos because they work on most mobiles  http://bit.ly/vQNz7k  #GeoHistorian. Have 11, adding 18 soon.    
    
    
    #RCETJ Vol. 7 No. 2 has been published: http://bit.ly/dtoIZX  #edtech Please RT    
    
    
    I just voted in the #eddies11 at edublogawards.com - Check out all of the nominees!, esp. SIGML for best wiki!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: 2nd set of #GeoHistorian Videos Finished: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/12/15/second-set-of-geohistorian-videos-finished/ … #NEH    
    
    
    snowing in Ohio, must be spring X(    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian presentation accepted for #ISTE2012: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/12/16/iste-2012-presentation-accepted/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    @CityMobileAngel Merry Christmas to you too!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/rTeVk0  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/ucAYyL     
    
    
    @yishaym Sorry to hear what happened to you. Hope you get better soon.    
    
    
    Interesting use of twitter for social studies/humanities: Live Tweeting the 2nd WW 70 years later: http://twitter.com/realtimewwii     
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://bit.ly/yGApKa     
    
    
    Just blogged: Using Twitter to Recreate WWII in "Real Time" http://wp.me/p102m-nA     
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/06/second-set-of-qr-code-markers-ready-for-installation/ … #GeoHistorian #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian QR code marker installation continues: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/10/round-two-of-qr-code-marker-installation-begins/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian marker installation: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/11/another-qr-code-marker-installed/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Call for Papers #RCETJ: Special Issue on Technology Use in the Social Studies: http://bit.ly/xppvml  Please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: Next #GeoHistorian #QR code marker installed: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/13/next-qr-code-marker-in-downtown-kent/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    ISTE SIGML January 2012 Webinar http://wp.me/p102m-o9  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    Woh- the internet is rising up to #StopSOPA #PIPA and #InternetCensorship. Write Congress today: http://sopastrike.com/strike  via @fightfortheftr    
    
    
    @GrahamBM Good luck with #LWF12!! I'll have to follow from a distance this year :(    
    
    
    Missing #LWF12 this year, but following from afar (well, sort of)...    
    
    
    @rhodct seems mobile strand is different this year; not being there makes it hard to tell. I'm sure it's good, but not as researchy? #lwf12    
    
    
    Join #ISTE #SIGilt #SIGms: 1 Tool @ a Time FREE Webinar - GIS in Education Wed, Feb 1 at 8pmE/7pmC/6pmM/5pmP http://goo.gl/YJHWt     
    
    
    Join #ISTE #SIGilt for a FREE webinar on Conversations on The Flipped Classroom Th, Feb 9 7pmE/6pmC/5pmM/4pmP http://goo.gl/PmfYb     
    
    
    Hey #tonyvincent, currently attending Tony's pd session on uStream.tv  (Tony Vincent live > http://ustre.am/2cj8)    
    
    
    #PBS Kids study on usefulness of mobile gaming apps: http://bit.ly/dqOJmQ #mlearning #sigml    
    
    
    Just out: Ed Tech & Society special issue on One-to-One Learning in the Mobile and Ubiquitous Computing Age: http://bit.ly/RBKRL    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for papers: Tech in Math and Science: http://bit.ly/buNpvK #RCET    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for papers: Spring 2011 issue: http://bit.ly/9XWzRQ #RCET    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian display table at #oetc12 #neh #odh pic.twitter.com/lJuESrnL    
    
    
    Just blogged #oetc12 #GeoHistorian Table Display: http://bit.ly/x9CMto     
    
    
    at #2010 keynote, discussion of ISTE resources, including mobile ones!    
    
    
    awards and thank yous #iste2010keynote    
    
    
    Stepped down as #SIGML chair, Elliot Soloway taking over. A great ride, and things will get even better, judging from bus mtg #iste10    
    
    
    Please join #SIGilt Board tonight at The Corner Office Martini Barhttp://bit.ly/bMyVLU starting at 8pm. #iste10    
    
    
    Please join #SIGilt in celebrating our members during their poster session from 11-1 pm in Lobby A on Wednesday. #iste10    
    
    
    @hcrompton u have a link for the SIGML QR reader tour pics?    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian curriculum can now be downloaded for free at http://bit.ly/AfNxiS  #ODH #NEH Please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/xLUhwd  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    I just voted for North American Bear Center to win $250k on Chase Community Giving! #chasegiving http://bit.ly/cXdtUx    
    
    
    I'm looking for a job: http://bit.ly/wW92b6  #jobsearch #employment Pleas RT    
    
    
    Apply to become a student app reviewer for #IEAR: http://www.iear.org/student-app-reviews/ #sigml #mobilelearning    
    
    
    #IEAR: app reviewers wanted: http://www.iear.org/iear/2010/3/5/app-reviewers-wanted.html #sigml #mobilelearning    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian: 21 markers installed, 8 to go: http://bit.ly/FQ787H  #ODH #NEH #QR    
    
    
    looking for good examples of qr code use in eduction. Anybody got any?    
    
    
    @jamesclay No but do have Andy R's paper. Thanks!    
    
    
    Join us for a free #ISTE #SIGILT #SIGMS Webinar on Infographics April 4th & 11th at 8pm ET, 7pm CT, 6pm MT, and 5pm PT  http://goo.gl/rDRey     
    
    
    #RCETJ Vol. 8, No. 1 has been published: http://bit.ly/dtoIZX  #edtech    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Brochures: http://bit.ly/IlaqAf  #QR #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Two more #GeoHistorian #QR markers installed: http://bit.ly/JVzPk1  #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    planning SIGHC forum for NECC in DC. It's going to be awesome!    
    
    
    Don't leave the Internet in Jeopardy. Tell the FCC why you need #NetNeutrality http://freepr.es/auh7YC (via @freepress)    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian white paper now published: http://bit.ly/NNcTsK  #NEH #ODH. Please share.    
    
    
    Just blogged installation of two more #QR code markers: http://bit.ly/PrZ5SF  #GeoHistorian #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    HHL 2010 conf is now Learning Without Frontiers 2011. Call 4 research strand abstracts now open:  http://bit.ly/lwfrs11    
    
    
    KSU RCET receives NEH grant for GeoHistorian Project, YES!!: http://bit.ly/9z6As2 and http://bit.ly/al8gCO #mlearning #geohistorian    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt is looking for writers for innovative learning http://bit.ly/a4P200 Paragraphs need to be in by September 8 at 12:00 PM CST    
    
    
    Get a sneak peak of some of the sessions at the Mobile Learning Experience 2011: http://j.mp/msampling #mobile2011    
    
    
    REGISTER NOW! Last week to get early bird price on mobile2011.org. See who will be there: http://j.mp/msampling #mobile2011    
    
    
    attending the ISTE Leadership Symposium. Interesting opening panel    
    
    
    Yes, several panelists mentioned the use of mobile technologies for learning, and how important they can be!!    
    
    
    Tech Plan development working group on Access to High Quality, Rigorous Working Experiences. #NECC09    
    
    
    @julielindsay I'll see you there :)    
    
    
    at the NECC Member Welcome #NECC09    
    
    
    @coolcatteacher Used Etherpad this morning at the Leadership Meeting. Worth a look into #necc09    
    
    
    @julielindsay I completely agree #necc09mg    
    
    
    In Ballroom C for session on cellphones http://bit.ly/4txeGz #necc09    
    
    
    polleverywhere will have pie charts soon    
    
    
    back at the hotel after the SIGML (yes, ML) business meeting. Interesting conversations, attitudes toward mobiles are changing! #necc09    
    
    
    Abstracts for #LWF2011 (formerly #HHL2010) research strands are due tomorrow 9/10: http://bit.ly/coft46 #edtech #GoM4L    
    
    
    just left the vendor area. Where is the mobile stuff?? #necc09    
    
    
    In some ways, teachers are still the missing link: http://bit.ly/18H7CN #necc09    
    
    
    watching the iPod Touch model lesson #necc09    
    
    
    Tony Vincent's App session is packed! I'm outside the door ... #lwf11 #mlearning    
    
    
    Just back from the Library of Congress reception: awesome place!! #necc09    
    
    
    For those who don't know, SIGHC is now SIGML (Mobile Learning) #necc09    
    
    
    Last day of NECC, will finally get to attend some sessions, then drive 6 hours to get home, #necc09    
    
    
    Bernie Dodge's PlacePuzzles: interesting concept. Could be powerful if combined with mobile #necc09    
    
    
    My notes from Bernie Dodge's session:  http://bit.ly/UmSk3 #necc09    
    
    
    waiting for Hal Davidson's mobile phone session #necc09    
    
    
    Hal Davidson: make sure your phones are out and on! #necc09    
    
    
    Hal compares NECC 2008  and 2009, 2 cell phone sessions as compared to 13 this year!! #necc09    
    
    
    just got out of davidson's talk, entertaining as always, wireless didn't work!! #necc09    
    
    
    Back home after 6 hour drive from DC, lots of traffic, one big rainstorm. At least my truck is clean again ;)    
    
    
    Interesting article about cell phone use in schools:  http://bit.ly/14m1eW    
    
    
    #lwf11 First up: Karen Cater US DOE: print-based classroom to digital learning environment, driven by mobile, broadband, apps.    
    
    
    #lwf11 also social media and data...    
    
    
    Karen Cater US DOE: we need better assessment tools, 24/7 student devices, & competency-based models of learning #lwf11    
    
    
    Karen Cater: US educational system needs a new OS, not just a reboot #lwf11    
    
    
    Karen Cater: US education is bi-partisan, really???? So why so little progress? #lwf11    
    
    
    Iris Lapinski: creating a new generation of problem solvers. #lwf11    
    
    
    Iris Lapinski: 70% of developed countries fail to improve their education systems. #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray. Wolfram Research, periodic table table!    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray: for good e-books, you need authors, real programmers, and experience from the tv/movie world.    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray: e-books are not textbooks!! More like enrichment... There is no real market anymore for dig textbooks    
    
    
    @gravesle so why don't you?    
    
    
    @timrylands: Best presentation today, hands down!! Above all, you made the point that tech can't and won't replace great teachers! #lwf11    
    
    
    Congratulations to @jnxyz for winning Primary Practitioner #LWF11 award in London!!    
    
    
    Great day at #lwf11 today (one of the best conference days yet?), start to finish. Mobile research strand tomorrow (10-1530, James Watt Rm)    
    
    
    Dick Winters (Band of Br) has passed away http://bit.ly/fwxeZx One of my heroes for what he did for my family and country in WWII, RIP!    
    
    
    @timbuckteeth Likewise! It was great to see you as well. #lwf11    
    
    
    One week left to submit your proposal for the LWF2011 mobile research strand: http://bit.ly/coft46 (due by 9/24)    
    
    
    Mobile research strand has started in James Watt. Come join us! #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 PrimaryPad link for mobile research strand: http://www.primarypad.com/lwf11    
    
    
    Attewell & Petley now presenting in mob research strand. Royle up next #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle now presenting in mob research strand about netbook project on Telford #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle in mob lrng research strand: netbooks not a good choice from tech pov? #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle in mob research strand: students as co-researchers: awesome! #lwf11    
    
    
    Roundtables starting in mobile research strand. Should be some great discussions! #lwf11    
    
    
    2nd round of mobile research papers about to start in James Watt #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobile research strand: Laura Pearson coming up w mobile for ESL #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobile research papers to be published after #lwf11 Info to follow. #mobile research.    
    
    
    Taylor & Dearnley now presenting at mobile research strand #lwf11    
    
    
    Marcus Specht presenting on AR in mobile research strand #lwf11    
    
    
    Lord David Puttnam: Digitized learning does not equal digital learning #lwf11    
    
    
    Jimmy Wales: dream of free access to knowledge for all = wikipedia #lwf11    
    
    
    Wikipedia contributors are at the intersection of intelligence, obsession & lots of free time - Jimmy Wales #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 was awesome!!! Thanks to G., Kabelo, and crew!!!    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt wants to know: How do you manage your time? Answer 'the question' at http://bit.ly/ilt-f10 Please RT!    
    
    
    Back in Ohio after exhausting/exhilarating #lwf11. Got lots of great ideas this year, met lots of great people!!! Thanks to LWF!!    
    
    
    In DC at #SUG2010: http://bit.ly/bQPxwp. Presenting #GeoHistorian in first lightning round.    
    
    
    Lightning Round sure goes fast!! Lots of great projects. Of course I 4got to mention GeoHistorian co-director Thomas McNeal :( #SUG2010    
    
    
    "In the internet age could we lose the past as we document the present?" This will make you think!! http://bbc.in/ar01RX    
    
    
    Scholastic and AT&T team up for mobile learning: http://shar.es/0JhBc     
    
    
    Frantically trying to finish my AERA proposal. It's due today.    
    
    
    Blogged: Miami U mobile learning presentation: http://bit.ly/cAXBAE #mlearning #GoM4L #SIGML    
    
    
    GeoHistorian project website now online: http://bit.ly/d0SpCU  More content coming soon... #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    @lisasjogren so is that with or without windchill? It's -5 here (with...)    
    
    
    Blogged: #GeoHistorian website now online: http://bit.ly/cxG6pu    
    
    
    blogged: #LWF2011 late breaking papers due 11/29/10: http://bit.ly/d7jE2P    
    
    
    Manuscripts for #RCETJ Spring 2011 issue are due by 11/30/10: http://bit.ly/brMSgs    
    
    
    @GrahamBM: Thanks for the videos!! Now I can watch what I missed (waiting for the Tuesday sessions) :) #lwf11 #lwf    
    
    
    Preparing for HHL. Looking forward to doing two presentations I haven't done before.    
    
    
    @gravesle Congrats on your ABD!!    
    
    
    @gravesle where are you? #oetc11    
    
    
    @gravesle must have missed you! I'll stop by!!    
    
    
    Listening to Sal Khan at #oetc11 (khanacademy.org). Too bad he's not live. Great website though.    
    
    
    Come learn about #QR codes #oetc11 in room D244-245 (3:45-4:30pm). Bring your mobile device!!    
    
    
    listening to futurelab presentation. Lots of interesting projects to check out...    
    
    
    I like the idea of texting questions during the preso; keeps the flow going and audience won't forget questions; of course I don't have my p    
    
    
    ...of course my phone doesn't work here; how about using twitter (like sb else txtd in)    
    
    
    moile learning sig mtg, wow, so many good projects, so much to catch up on...    
    
    
    RT hhl: Check latest Handheld Learning '09 Programme which is now looking v. good http://bit.ly/oGTc1 hope you like! #hhl09    
    
    
    Our #oetc11 QR code presentation now online at http://bit.ly/ghRFNv or http://bit.ly/h772Fy    
    
    
    Reviewing AERA conference proposals. 35 down, 29 more to go X(    
    
    
    And of course working on the research strand for HHL 2009 in London. Should be another great conference this year!!    
    
    
    ISTE's SIGML now has it's own twitter account: sigml    
    
    
    Working on review for HHL 2007, finally...    
    
    
    Getting ready to listen to Obama's speech to students: http://www.whitehouse.gov/live/    
    
    
    Opening act: Arne Duncan, sec. of education.    
    
    
    Next: Pres. of senior class.    
    
    
    Main act: the Prez. Theme seems to be student responsibility for learning.    
    
    
    Lots of mobile phones and cameras in the crowd.    
    
    
    Obama: "You can't drop out and drop into a good job."    
    
    
    Obama: "There is no excuse for not trying."    
    
    
    Obama: "Set your own goals for your education and do what it takes to meet them."    
    
    
    Obama: "Being successful is hard."    
    
    
    Obama: "You have to let your failures teach you."    
    
    
    Obama's connecting education and patriotism throughout...    
    
    
    Obama: "What's your contribution going to be? What problems are you going to solve?    
    
    
    End of speech, Obama's shaking hands with the crowd.    
    
    
    Don’t let Congress sell out your right to free speech online. Take action @freepress: http://freepr.es/g3PVb4 #NetNeutrality    
    
    
    Following "It's Only Rock n Roll" on Engadget: http://bit.ly/e4cCa    
    
    
    Lots of talk about iPod games now.... yawn.    
    
    
    New ad, what about a new iPod!! #apple    
    
    
    iPod nano with camera! http://bit.ly/31F7D #apple    
    
    
    iPod nano now also with FM radio, pedometer (sync to Nike), mic and speaker #apple    
    
    
    No iPod touch with camera? #apple    
    
    
    @GrahamBM  I agree, with the nano your possibilities are more limited...    
    
    
    Mobile app sees science go global:  http://bit.ly/Op6mi (mobile learning at its best!)    
    
    
    My round up of mobile learning stuff for the week:  http://bit.ly/ATAvU    
    
    
    The latest newsletter from #LWF is at: http://bit.ly/lwfnews-250211 with @Abdulchohan @tonyvincent @rankinw #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobility, social interactions, digital content, blended learning #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    #acuconnected #karencator keynote: flashbacks to #lwf11 :)    
    
    
    Assessment: measure what matters #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Teachers need to be highly connected to be highly effective #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Kahn Academy as an example of learning progressions #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    R&D needed: basic research, venture and dev, market (middle section is what we need) #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Seton Hill: iPad use 9-5 (consumption) Mac Book use 5-9 (creation) #acuconnected    
    
    
    Seton Hill: students see largest advantage of iPad as being access to resources #acuconnected    
    
    
    Challenge at ACU is not how to find digital content, but how to assess its value. #scottperkins #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU: though undergrad campus is saturated with iPhones/iPods, budgets are tight. So how to get iPads in hands of fac/students? #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: students positive about mobile learning #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: faculty rate progr as success and student engagement is up. Achievement not nec up #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: attitude, impact and usage vary by device #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: fac report signif class-related use of devices. What is significant? #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: mobility allows faculty to transform ed practices #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU should focus on learning outside of classroom and how to connect it to classroom learning. Learning exp should be 24/7 #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff Right,but what do they do with them 4 learning? #acuconnected    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen I agree.... #acuconnected    
    
    
    Challenge-based learning makes learning relevant #donhenderson #acuconnected www.apple.com/education/challenge-based-learning    
    
    
    @abdulchohan up next at #acuconnected More flashbacks to #lwf11 :)    
    
    
    @abdulchohan iPod Touches at Essa led to increased creativity #acuconnected (challenge: how to assess this ...)    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen very true... But there are some real opportunities here beyond testing on content knowledge. Hence the question... #acuconnected    
    
    
    @GoldsAtWork the device doesn't matter, it's the access to content and tools that does #acuconnected    
    
    
    @busynessgirl Internet as waterfall of info and we're under it! #acuconnected    
    
    
    Great ideas from @busynessgirl about a digital learning system, but who should build it (if not education)? #acuconnected    
    
    
    Students do still use laptops for media (music, movies, etc.) and information mgt, also for some productivity like Excel #acuconnected    
    
    
    Why call an inkling textbook a "textbook"? It's so much more than text or book! #acuconnected #Matt McInnis    
    
    
    Connexions = repository, tools, community #acuconnected #sidneyburrus    
    
    
    Jekyll & Hyde AR book on YouTube http://m.youtube.com/#/results?q=jekyll%20and%20hyde%20ar%20book #acuconnected #AR    
    
    
    Alcatel-Lucent work on shared annotations of e-books. Interesting opportunities, some challenges... #acuconnected #ebooks    
    
    
    Students presenting on textbook purchasing in research strand, nice to see #acuconnected    
    
    
    42% of teachers don't know what textbooks cost, and considering the avg student spends $800-$1,100 per year!!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU Student: iPad didn't make much of a difference because pedagogy didn't change. Teachers should harness its potential #acuconnected.    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen but 10 chapters will still cost you $50-$80 then!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU iPad project: wifi only iPads loaned to students for duration of project  (uses different than if iPad owned and 3g) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff: "Mobile learning *in* the classroom": sounds like an oxymoron to me.... #acuconnected    
    
    
    Scott Hamm: iPad as complement, not replacement, for laptop. Heard same from students yesterday #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff Right, but what do they do with them outside of class with those same devices that could enhance learning in the classroom?    
    
    
    @derekbruff: I got you. I agree that we should focus more on the integration of in and out of the classroom, not focus on one or the other    
    
    
    Scott Hamm: iPad obstacles: no flash, editing docs, poor connectivity, not enough for all students, projection issues #acuconnected    
    
    
    iPad use in Incarnate Word MBA program: typical expectations and concerns. #acuconnected    
    
    
    @HaleyDD #KellerISD  pilot 'BYODevice' next year. N Wireless at school & give Verizon MIFI to students without home access #acuconnected    
    
    
    Incarnate Word: iPad needs more prod tools:keyboard, camera, video conf, flash, printing, no screen switching, Office, VGA out #acuconnected    
    
    
    @krista_scott Yes ;) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @HaleyDD Me too. It could fundamentally change technology integration/funding for that district, probably will #acuconnected    
    
    
    Tatom research paper online at http://bit.ly/dS3bzb #acuconnected    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen Good question. Netbooks don't seem to have gotten a lot of traction #acuconnected    
    
    
    Tatom: some of the FHU profs no longer use a textbook, but online resources. YES!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    FHU: students have MacBook, iPhone/iPod, AND iPad: overkill?? #acuconnected.    
    
    
    FHU research: Students believe iPad encouraged engagement during lecture:. But why still lecture (new tech, old pedagogy) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @krista_scott Agreed. Just providing one could be cost-prohibitive for institutions. BYOD (e.g. Keller ISD) as the answer? #acuconnected    
    
    
    Obama: education is the economic issue of our time #adriansannier #acuconnected    
    
    
    The 4 beyonds: beyond textbooks, bookstores, LMS, school. #adriansannier #acuconnected    
    
    
    Question remains: how can we get education to truly innovate fast enough and in ways that will scale? #acuconnected    
    
    
    AR stuff in the research track, always cool #acuconnected    
    
    
    AR at ACU http://kjar.posterous.com #acuconnected    
    
    
    However beautiful the strategy, you should occasionally look at the result - Churchill (importance of mobile research) #acuconnected    
    
    
    Easy mobility leads to easy collaboration #fraserspeirs #acuconnected    
    
    
    T @hhl Print version of programme for Handheld Learning 2009 now available at: http://bit.ly/hl09guide 3Mb PDF    
    
    
    Checking out WordPress for iPhone. Any tips, tricks, suggestions?    
    
    
    Working url for SIGML survey:  http://bit.ly/12U3Kc    
    
    
    SHARE YOUR VISION OF MOBILE LEARNING and 5 people may win a free registration to www.mobile2011.org  Enter now http://tinyurl.com/66p8ouy    
    
    
    Don't forget Tony Vincent's Podcast Picks today at 3pm PST/6pm EST http://j.mp/1AzB3    
    
    
    #RCETJ special issue on technology in mathematics and science education now online at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX    
    
    
    just posted another mobile learning round-up:  http://bit.ly/17mSBI    
    
    
    ISTE proposals due on Oct. 7, midnight PST!!    
    
    
    At hhl conf hheckl session, catching end of it.    
    
    
    Hheckl top 3, ds, iPod touch, apple tablet #hhl    
    
    
    Hheckl top 3, no mobile phone! #hhl    
    
    
    In learner's y, it's packed! #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y still not started, what gives? #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y BOPOD project w ipods, apps used #hhl    
    
    
    BOPOD: but do the ipods leave the classroom? #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y: BOPOD'a done: half the room cleared out! #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y: next up Oakdale school from London: DS 4 Math #hhl09    
    
    
    in Pecha Kucha now, presentation on how web design for mobile and desktop are influencing each other #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: Stuart Smith talking about mobile web: 30% of websites do not display on iPhone #hhl09    
    
    
    lots of coining of terms at @hhl09: crapps and plearn so far #hhl09    
    
    
    @pressfuturist  yes it is...    
    
    
    @irislapinski  yikes, missed the name, some guy from the US    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha:  M'ubuntu mlearning for South Africa to solve literacy crisis #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: M'ubuntu: pbl, basic skills and teacher pd deliverd on mobile phone #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: M'ubuntu: asking 4 help on getting phones  to sustain the project (Lucy Haagen, lucyhaagen@yahoo.com). Now using Sprint #hhl    
    
    
    Best practices: text your description to the presenter and he'll send you a drawing #hhl09    
    
    
    Best Practices: more people in the session have been to Africa than used Android #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan: students need 24/7 access,. Yes!! #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan listing apps for iPod Touch, Classics, Story Kit, Civ Rev, Leaf Trombone, Wurdle, Geared, Strip Designer, Brushes #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan: is not having a camera on a mobile device a negative? Maybe not... #hhl09    
    
    
    Quick break back at the hotel from #hhl09, then back to Awards Presentation. Busy day so far ...    
    
    
    At hhl awards #hhl09    
    
    
    Hhl awards starting #hhl09    
    
    
    #hhl09 Blog post: Handheld Learning Day 1: http://bit.ly/163xof    
    
    
    mobile learning in current schools: an oxymoron?? #hhl09    
    
    
    Hillwig: 50% of PhD students in USA are not US citizens (and I'm one of them) :D #hhl09    
    
    
    Just posted #hhl09 day 2, part 1 blog post:  http://bit.ly/NPIQP    
    
    
    ... and  #hhl09 day 2, part 2 blog post:  http://bit.ly/LNVjT. Final day of HHL tomorrow. It'll be another long one.    
    
    
    @johntraxler : upping the ante for yourself, aren't you? ;)    
    
    
    Research strand @9:30 in James Watts #hhl09    
    
    
    Tracker kicking of research strand: always entertaining #hhl09    
    
    
    Oops, should be Traxler #hhl09    
    
    
    Traxler: journalism as first draft of history: citiz. Journalism using mobile #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Robin Deegan talks usability #hhl09    
    
    
    Deegan: mobile use us usually in short bursts #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Nicola Bedall-Hill talking about her mobile research: mobile as 'boundary objects' #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill: head cam as tool for data collection #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill showing helmet cam video: interesting pov #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill quizzing the audience! #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill: device not boundary object, but the visual representations #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand: Lucianne Brown presenting on mobile use to teach reading #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: mlearning still exploratory..... #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: using mobile phones for vocabulary frontloading in reading. #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: mobile phones didn't really make a big difference (as compared to non-users) in achievement, but did in motivation #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: maybe better results if students are allowed to use phones outside of class as well? #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Perkins and Saltsman  from ACU presenting their iPhone project #hhl09    
    
    
    @didactylos : it's been full all morning, all good papers so far! #hhl09    
    
    
    ACU study: lots of data! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand papers to be published in RCETJ spring 2010 issue: http://www.rcetj.org    
    
    
    Research strand: student engagement a better metric than achievement? #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Jane Lunsford speaks about student support #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable discussions starting at 12:20  #hhl09    
    
    
    Lunsford: texting more useful than email #hhl09    
    
    
    Lunsford: lots of resources at OU #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand Roundtable 1 now in session: lots of discussion #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable switch, come join us! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research stand presenters: Marco Arrigo, Phil Marston, Rhodri Thomas, Domizio Baldini, Karl Royle #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable 2 starting at 14:30. Presenters: Arrigo, Pemberton, Blair, Pulman, van Ooijen #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand: roundtable 2. They're off! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable 3 at 15:10: presenters Avery, Viswanathan, Arrigo, Mills, Seipold, Bunce #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Steve Bunce's group is playing DS! Who says research is boring ;) #hhl09    
    
    
    @irislapinski presentations should be, papers will be published in special issue of RCETJ: http://www.rcetj.org #hhl09    
    
    
    Research roundtable 3: last chance to attend! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand wrapping up, quite a day!! #hhl09    
    
    
    Thanks to all research strand presenters, great sessions today! #hhl09    
    
    
    Kurzweil: tools of disruptive change are in everyone's hands #hhl09    
    
    
    RT tonyvincent @jont I missed you this year at HHL! 
Same here!!    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for manuscripts (Fall 2011 issue) now open: http://bit.ly/h1C9Bf #edtech Please RT    
    
    
    Please RT: ISTE SIGML members, vote for you favorite book study book: http://bit.ly/90Z4L    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML 2011 Video Contest now accepting submissions!! http://bit.ly/eAKgVo Please RT    
    
    
    @lucretiafraga thx for the compliment!! #mobile2011    
    
    
    @grahamBM keynote at #mobile2011. Always thought-provoking & entertaining. Disruption is good!    
    
    
    @grahamBM m = mainstream #mobile2011    
    
    
    @grahamBM: mobile is transitional, connectivity is key #mobile2011    
    
    
    Learning is not formal v informal. Learning is learning! The artificial dichotomy we've created is part of the problem. #mobile2011    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning    
    
    
    Derek Keenan showing the importance of carefully planned curriculum at #mobile2011 to foster critical thinking.    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning Maybe use one of the sharing sessions on Friday? #mobile2011    
    
    
    Some of the #mobile2011 scavenger hunt videos now aggregated on YouTube: http://bit.ly/fmw4Jp More to come...    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning  I'll be there #mobile2011    
    
    
    @andygstoll I used QR codes, @miami_mlearning plugged the content into wikitude during the event on thursday at Heritage Square #mobile2011    
    
    
    RT:“@tonyvincent: Notes from my #mobile2011 presentation "Mobilize for Productivity" http://tonyv.me/mp ”    
    
    
    More scavenger hunt videos now uploaded at http://bit.ly/gOHPLv #mobile2011    
    
    
    My GeoHistorian and Thursday am keynote slides will be posted later today on mobile2011blog.posterous.com  #mobile211    
    
    
    @JaneneG Yes, 1:30 pm it is. We'll meet in the Regency ballroom and go from there. #mobile2011    
    
    
    Mobile scavenger hunt recap at http://mobile2011blog.posterous.com/mobile-scavenger-hunt … #mobile2011    
    
    
    @ingewassmann ...and very nice to meet you! Tot ziens :) #mobile2011    
    
    
    New animal barcode scanner earns its stripes - Science http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/42500680/ns/technology_and_science-science/ … via @todayshow    
    
    
    Back home from #mobile2011 and packing for #AERA2011. New Orleans, here I come!    
    
    
    @felixjacomino Awesome search story!! :D Should send it to the Arrogant Butcher's manager ;) #mobile2011    
    
    
    @michaelmgrant yep, presenting Monday, 8:15 am #AERA2011    
    
    
    @GrahamBM so what you're really saying is that you need another iPad2 ... :D    
    
    
    SIGML Dec. newsletter contributions due by December 1 to mvanthoo@kent.edu    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study choices survey closes on Dec. 2. Vote now at http://bit.ly/90Z4L    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML video contest blogged by #BrainPOP: http://bit.ly/lWaZrB    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML: One week left to submit your entries for the 2011 Video Contest! See rules and enhanced prize package at http://bit.ly/kktNot    
    
    
    #lwf11 late breaking mobile research papers due in one week!! http://bit.ly/coft46    
    
    
    RCETJ Vol 7 No 1 now published at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX including special section with #LWF2011 mobile research papers #mlearning    
    
    
    Sign up for the SIGML book study at http://bit.ly/6gA411    
    
    
    SIGML December Newsletter available at http://bit.ly/5TcKhg    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML: One day left to submit your entries for the 2011 Video Contest! See rules and enhanced prize package at http://bit.ly/kktNot    
    
    
    #ISTE 2011 #SIGML  volunteers needed for outdoor event (6/28 2-4p) info http://bit.ly/mJiNsO  Interested? Send email to istesigml@gmail.com    
    
    
    Just blogged: First Round of Digital Stories Almost Done!  for the #GeoHistorian Project: http://bit.ly/jE4Ccf #QR #mlearning    
    
    
    @karlroyle The map in the post? Just Google Maps.    
    
    
    @karlroyle ... and #QR codes made with i-nigma.    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML 2011 Video Contest voting now open:  http://svy.mk/jh1oB4 You must be an ISTE member to vote;  voting closes on June 17, 2011.    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian is in the news today: http://www.recordpub.com/news/article/5043971    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt just published innovative learning, read the latest issue at http://bit.ly/sigilt-spring11 'Forward it on' by RT-ing!    
    
    
    Only 10 days left to vote for your favorite #ISTE #SIGML video contest entries! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    First set of #GeoHistorian #QR code markers is ready: http://bit.ly/jawvnl  To be installed on 6/18/11 #mlearning    
    
    
    ISTE SIGML book study starts on 1/25/10. Sign up to participate here: http://bit.ly/6gA411    
    
    
    Only five days left to vote for your favorites in the #ISTE #SIGML 2011 video contest! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    Voting for the  #ISTE #SIGML 2011 video contest closes tomorrow 6/17!! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news again, KHS newsletter article: http://bit.ly/mmEJDF #QR #qrcode    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian: first set of QR code markers to be installed tomorrow (6/18) in Kent, OH #QR #qrcode: http://bit.ly/kHdrZh    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 1 - Developed and Developing Countries http://ning.it/5DqHLp    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 1 - Evaluation http://ning.it/8S26XN    
    
    
    Coontz Center Breakthroughs in Mobile Learning Challenge, $50K top prize for best mobile learning innovation: http://bit.ly/5wJnpc    
    
    
    Following the iPad release online: http://bit.ly/83sf3a    
    
    
    Looks like a big iPhone to me, just thinner ...    
    
    
    I wonder what the cost is going to be ...    
    
    
    iPad Brushes app looks pretty cool...    
    
    
    New app: iBooks. New, really???    
    
    
    @kathtrinder iPad. Not exactly creative, I'd say...    
    
    
    @jamesclay: yep, but for 64 GB with 3G it'll run you $829, not so cheap...    
    
    
    checking out new hhl site, preparing presentations for NECC.    
    
    
    @graham: sure, netbooks are good tools for learning while mobile    
    
    
    Listening to Julie Lindsay and Vicki Davis talking about digiteen and flat classroom project. Interesting stuff.    
    
    
    At eTech Ohio conference: http://www.etech.ohio.gov/conference/    
    
    
    eTech Ohio: St. Marys mobile phone presentation: 630 + smart phones in grades 3-6 :)    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 2: Learning Content: http://ning.it/cc8851    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study: Chapter 2 - Vygotskys zone http://ning.it/b7suOE    
    
    
    eTech Ohio keynote: not bad for a 12-yr-old:  http://bit.ly/55raSR    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://kent.patch.com/articles/qr-codes-provide-link-to-kents-past … #QR #ISTE11    
    
    
    PBS Digital Nation:  http://bit.ly/akObM4    
    
    
    #SIGML walking tour at 2p (Indep Square). Join us or find handout at http://sigml.iste.wikispaces.net/ISTE_2011  #QR #ISTE11    
    
    
    #BrainPOP feature movie of the day about Ben Franklin to coincide with #SIGML walking tour: http://bit.ly/lJD7NG #ISTE11 #QR    
    
    
    #setsig #sigml #iste11 so much to learn at setsig playground-mobile apps, techs, pedagogy, and lots of really smart people-please visit soon    
    
    
    #SIGML video contest winners at http://sigml.iste.wikispaces.net/2011_Video_Contest  #ISTE11    
    
    
    I just told Washington to stand with me and Obama for #NetNeutrality. Your turn: http://bit.ly/4sJgrp (via @freepress)    
    
    
    GeoHistorian Project in Chronicle of Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/91honP    
    
    
    blogged: eTech Ohio mobile tech sessions: http://bit.ly/c2401h    
    
    
    Blogged: eTech Ohio Tuesday morning panel: http://bit.ly/aYZeJE    
    
    
    Blogged: eTech Ohio: St Marys Cell Phone project, deja vu? http://bit.ly/9peTRc    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/jTiDU6 #GeoHistorian #QR    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for manuscripts Spring 2012 issue: http://bit.ly/jnl6l0 #edtech    
    
    
    #ISTE2011 #SIGML tour videos now posted: http://bit.ly/j9IDep #QR #mobile. Great job by students from Omaha North High Magnet School!!    
    
    
    #SIGilt asks: What Stood Out for You at #ISTE2011? Fill out the form and share here: http://tinyurl.com/5wqll7y    
    
    
    Blogged: http://bit.ly/qgt0D9. 5 #QR codes installed, 6 more to go #NEH #GeoHistorian #RCET    
    
    
    "Chapter 4 - Mobile in Nursing Education" on SIGML Book Study 2010: http://ning.it/bCapGH    
    
    
    2010 ISTE SIGML video contest is on!! http://bit.ly/9sGqnV    
    
    
    SIGML bookstudy Chp. 5, Informal Learning in Online Communities: http://bit.ly/cxYdnF    
    
    
    Preparing for the HHL 2008 research strand. Go out and shoot some video for cell-phone presentation later today. It's raining now.    
    
    
    @hhl. I'm bringing a laptop, digital camera, two mobile phones and a palm TX. I wonder if the phones will actually work....    
    
    
    Got to London for HHL2008 this morning. Beautiful weather!!    
    
    
    @ kathtrinder Cool! Hope to see you guys soon.    
    
    
    @mamk Video shoot went great, in between the rain drops. You'll see it on Tuesday.    
    
    
    @hhl Andy Black's session was good, variety of presentations. Now at Pecha Kucha (yes I got there late).    
    
    
    @kathtrinder: hope to see you there.    
    
    
    hhl d watching Derek Robertson    
    
    
    #tonyvincent where are you?    
    
    
    @tonyvincent: where are you? Ech, can't type today.    
    
    
    @kathtrinder go look at Spore when you get home ;)    
    
    
    @jamesclay don't worry, MAMK is streaming the keynote live to qik and will have a detailed report for you in triplicate :D    
    
    
    @jont oh I don't know, Wall Street maybe, or the White House?    
    
    
    @jamesclay quick, put in your feedback form and win a fabulous prize!    
    
    
    made it to Taiwan, long trip, reception great!    
    
    
    Pictures of the 6th #GeoHistorian #qr marker, installed at #Kent Hotel: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/07/29/marker-6-is-in-place/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    SIGML book study chp 6: Applying M-Learning: http://bit.ly/codN2D    
    
    
    #SIGilt  (ISTE) collecting policies about digital citizenship and innovation http://bit.ly/aS49bG Please RT and get the word out!    
    
    
    Google blog about QR codes: http://bit.ly/bFV23P, via @audreywatters    
    
    
    New ISTE Mobile App: http://bit.ly/byaN0M    
    
    
    Verizon Wireless video about St Marys schools mobile phone project: http://bit.ly/aNBbup    
    
    
    SIGML Bookstudy Chp. 8: Design and Devt. of Mobile Learning Objects: http://bit.ly/crWMAX Register and participate!!    
    
    
    Finishing up lots of odds and ends before Christmas break (finally some time off!)    
    
    
    Education Week's Technology Counts 2010: It's all about mobile learning: http://bit.ly/9cACY6    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://bit.ly/rtuyzM  #NEH #RCET #QR    
    
    
    Don't let the #FCC betray us. Demand real #NetNeutrality. Accept no substitutes: http://freepr.es/egkmqk (via @freepress)    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chp. 9: From e-learning to mobile learning part I: http://bit.ly/aVCfM0    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chp. 9: From e-learning to mobile learning part 2: http://bit.ly/9k3oEE    
    
    
    Happy belated New Year everyone!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: two more #QR markers installed for the #GeoHistorian Project: http://bit.ly/q5E1XE     
    
    
    ISTE SIGML book study chp. 10: Mobile tools and svcs for formal and informal learning: http://bit.ly/a3PYk7 Please register and participate!    
    
    
    Enjoying the day off (MLK). Obama inauguration tomorrow!    
    
    
    blogged: Medienpadagogik call for papers on mobile learning: http://bit.ly/9pkJRX    
    
    
    @jont Good report, nothing really new. Blogged at http://tinyurl.com/73gfpm    
    
    
    Good inauguration speech by Obama. Let's hope his actions will match his words. He's got his work cut out for him!!!    
    
    
    @kathtrinder Photo wallpaper. Of course a DUTCH invention ;). And yes electronic is better, and why not? We already have digital photoframes    
    
    
    Still freezing cold over here. And of course we're going camping this weekend, in tents ...    
    
    
    Still defrosting from camp out. It got as low as -19C/-2F. Mummybags rule!    
    
    
    @coolcatteacher Enjoy your break!! Ours was this week but I had to work all week :(    
    
    
    Has anybody used #TagWhat to create content? LMKWYT of it.    
    
    
    @delchoness  ok thanks, didn't know it was that new ...    
    
    
    RCETJ special issue on Handheld Learning 2009 (research papers) released at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX Worth a look!! Please RT    
    
    
    @delchoness  do you guys review tags before they are made public? Trying to do some testing... #TagWhat    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/09/27/celebrating-kent-history-reenacting/ … #geohistorian    
    
    
    @brettbobley Cool! and thanks.....    
    
    
    End of a very busy day. It was 65 degrees here today. Very unusual for Feb. in OH.    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study chp 12: Mobiles in Museums: http://bit.ly/dfqcnZ    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/oLEmV0  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    attending MLC09 (mobilelearning09.org) in DC. Just finished moderating our panel...    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/10/the-perils-of-public-history/ … #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/10/last-two-markers-installed/ … #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    RCETJ manuscript submissions for spring 2012 issue due 12/2/11: http://bit.ly/jnl6l0  please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Project Becomes a Community Effort: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/10/27/geohistorian-project-becomes-a-community-effort/ …    
    
    
    Three more days until the ISTE SIGML video contest entries are due! http://bit.ly/9sGqnV #sigml Some already in: http://bit.ly/c4oxiL    
    
    
    Just blogged: Local Historians Doing Local Research #GeoHistorian: http://bit.ly/sVcGrB     
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Presentation at #eTech Ohio 2012: http://bit.ly/tpJalv     
    
    
    @TomHarkin #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @DavidObey #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @ThadCochran #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    @RepToddTiahrt #EETT Support innovation in learning & teaching. Fund #edtech at $500m please RT    
    
    
    Our schools need 21st century education, #EETT. Fund #edtech at $500 m please RT    
    
    
    No funding for #edtech? No prep for 21st century. Fund #EETT at $500 please RT    
    
    
    As a parent  and researcher, I know our kids need relevant and meaningful #edtech skills. Fund #EETT at $500m please RT    
    
    
    First #UNESCO Mobile Learning week: http://bit.ly/uK6jQB  #mlearning #mobile    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian in #Kent Tree City Bulletin: http://bit.ly/rEh9Ab     
    
    
    Preparing to present about #GeoHistorian on Friday at #NCSS2011 in Washington DC: http://bit.ly/vYobEw     
    
    
    @sherah1918 Using YouTube to host videos because they work on most mobiles  http://bit.ly/vQNz7k  #GeoHistorian. Have 11, adding 18 soon.    
    
    
    #RCETJ Vol. 7 No. 2 has been published: http://bit.ly/dtoIZX  #edtech Please RT    
    
    
    I just voted in the #eddies11 at edublogawards.com - Check out all of the nominees!, esp. SIGML for best wiki!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: 2nd set of #GeoHistorian Videos Finished: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/12/15/second-set-of-geohistorian-videos-finished/ … #NEH    
    
    
    snowing in Ohio, must be spring X(    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian presentation accepted for #ISTE2012: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/12/16/iste-2012-presentation-accepted/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    @CityMobileAngel Merry Christmas to you too!!    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/rTeVk0  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/ucAYyL     
    
    
    @yishaym Sorry to hear what happened to you. Hope you get better soon.    
    
    
    Interesting use of twitter for social studies/humanities: Live Tweeting the 2nd WW 70 years later: http://twitter.com/realtimewwii     
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://bit.ly/yGApKa     
    
    
    Just blogged: Using Twitter to Recreate WWII in "Real Time" http://wp.me/p102m-nA     
    
    
    Just blogged: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/06/second-set-of-qr-code-markers-ready-for-installation/ … #GeoHistorian #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian QR code marker installation continues: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/10/round-two-of-qr-code-marker-installation-begins/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian marker installation: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/11/another-qr-code-marker-installed/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Call for Papers #RCETJ: Special Issue on Technology Use in the Social Studies: http://bit.ly/xppvml  Please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: Next #GeoHistorian #QR code marker installed: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2012/01/13/next-qr-code-marker-in-downtown-kent/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    ISTE SIGML January 2012 Webinar http://wp.me/p102m-o9  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    Woh- the internet is rising up to #StopSOPA #PIPA and #InternetCensorship. Write Congress today: http://sopastrike.com/strike  via @fightfortheftr    
    
    
    @GrahamBM Good luck with #LWF12!! I'll have to follow from a distance this year :(    
    
    
    Missing #LWF12 this year, but following from afar (well, sort of)...    
    
    
    @rhodct seems mobile strand is different this year; not being there makes it hard to tell. I'm sure it's good, but not as researchy? #lwf12    
    
    
    Join #ISTE #SIGilt #SIGms: 1 Tool @ a Time FREE Webinar - GIS in Education Wed, Feb 1 at 8pmE/7pmC/6pmM/5pmP http://goo.gl/YJHWt     
    
    
    Join #ISTE #SIGilt for a FREE webinar on Conversations on The Flipped Classroom Th, Feb 9 7pmE/6pmC/5pmM/4pmP http://goo.gl/PmfYb     
    
    
    Hey #tonyvincent, currently attending Tony's pd session on uStream.tv  (Tony Vincent live > http://ustre.am/2cj8)    
    
    
    #PBS Kids study on usefulness of mobile gaming apps: http://bit.ly/dqOJmQ #mlearning #sigml    
    
    
    Just out: Ed Tech & Society special issue on One-to-One Learning in the Mobile and Ubiquitous Computing Age: http://bit.ly/RBKRL    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for papers: Tech in Math and Science: http://bit.ly/buNpvK #RCET    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for papers: Spring 2011 issue: http://bit.ly/9XWzRQ #RCET    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian display table at #oetc12 #neh #odh pic.twitter.com/lJuESrnL    
    
    
    Just blogged #oetc12 #GeoHistorian Table Display: http://bit.ly/x9CMto     
    
    
    at #2010 keynote, discussion of ISTE resources, including mobile ones!    
    
    
    awards and thank yous #iste2010keynote    
    
    
    Stepped down as #SIGML chair, Elliot Soloway taking over. A great ride, and things will get even better, judging from bus mtg #iste10    
    
    
    Please join #SIGilt Board tonight at The Corner Office Martini Barhttp://bit.ly/bMyVLU starting at 8pm. #iste10    
    
    
    Please join #SIGilt in celebrating our members during their poster session from 11-1 pm in Lobby A on Wednesday. #iste10    
    
    
    @hcrompton u have a link for the SIGML QR reader tour pics?    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian curriculum can now be downloaded for free at http://bit.ly/AfNxiS  #ODH #NEH Please RT    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/xLUhwd  #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    I just voted for North American Bear Center to win $250k on Chase Community Giving! #chasegiving http://bit.ly/cXdtUx    
    
    
    I'm looking for a job: http://bit.ly/wW92b6  #jobsearch #employment Pleas RT    
    
    
    Apply to become a student app reviewer for #IEAR: http://www.iear.org/student-app-reviews/ #sigml #mobilelearning    
    
    
    #IEAR: app reviewers wanted: http://www.iear.org/iear/2010/3/5/app-reviewers-wanted.html #sigml #mobilelearning    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian: 21 markers installed, 8 to go: http://bit.ly/FQ787H  #ODH #NEH #QR    
    
    
    looking for good examples of qr code use in eduction. Anybody got any?    
    
    
    @jamesclay No but do have Andy R's paper. Thanks!    
    
    
    Join us for a free #ISTE #SIGILT #SIGMS Webinar on Infographics April 4th & 11th at 8pm ET, 7pm CT, 6pm MT, and 5pm PT  http://goo.gl/rDRey     
    
    
    #RCETJ Vol. 8, No. 1 has been published: http://bit.ly/dtoIZX  #edtech    
    
    
    Just blogged: #GeoHistorian Brochures: http://bit.ly/IlaqAf  #QR #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    Two more #GeoHistorian #QR markers installed: http://bit.ly/JVzPk1  #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    planning SIGHC forum for NECC in DC. It's going to be awesome!    
    
    
    Don't leave the Internet in Jeopardy. Tell the FCC why you need #NetNeutrality http://freepr.es/auh7YC (via @freepress)    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian white paper now published: http://bit.ly/NNcTsK  #NEH #ODH. Please share.    
    
    
    Just blogged installation of two more #QR code markers: http://bit.ly/PrZ5SF  #GeoHistorian #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    HHL 2010 conf is now Learning Without Frontiers 2011. Call 4 research strand abstracts now open:  http://bit.ly/lwfrs11    
    
    
    KSU RCET receives NEH grant for GeoHistorian Project, YES!!: http://bit.ly/9z6As2 and http://bit.ly/al8gCO #mlearning #geohistorian    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt is looking for writers for innovative learning http://bit.ly/a4P200 Paragraphs need to be in by September 8 at 12:00 PM CST    
    
    
    Get a sneak peak of some of the sessions at the Mobile Learning Experience 2011: http://j.mp/msampling #mobile2011    
    
    
    REGISTER NOW! Last week to get early bird price on mobile2011.org. See who will be there: http://j.mp/msampling #mobile2011    
    
    
    attending the ISTE Leadership Symposium. Interesting opening panel    
    
    
    Yes, several panelists mentioned the use of mobile technologies for learning, and how important they can be!!    
    
    
    Tech Plan development working group on Access to High Quality, Rigorous Working Experiences. #NECC09    
    
    
    @julielindsay I'll see you there :)    
    
    
    at the NECC Member Welcome #NECC09    
    
    
    @coolcatteacher Used Etherpad this morning at the Leadership Meeting. Worth a look into #necc09    
    
    
    @julielindsay I completely agree #necc09mg    
    
    
    In Ballroom C for session on cellphones http://bit.ly/4txeGz #necc09    
    
    
    polleverywhere will have pie charts soon    
    
    
    back at the hotel after the SIGML (yes, ML) business meeting. Interesting conversations, attitudes toward mobiles are changing! #necc09    
    
    
    Abstracts for #LWF2011 (formerly #HHL2010) research strands are due tomorrow 9/10: http://bit.ly/coft46 #edtech #GoM4L    
    
    
    just left the vendor area. Where is the mobile stuff?? #necc09    
    
    
    In some ways, teachers are still the missing link: http://bit.ly/18H7CN #necc09    
    
    
    watching the iPod Touch model lesson #necc09    
    
    
    Tony Vincent's App session is packed! I'm outside the door ... #lwf11 #mlearning    
    
    
    Just back from the Library of Congress reception: awesome place!! #necc09    
    
    
    For those who don't know, SIGHC is now SIGML (Mobile Learning) #necc09    
    
    
    Last day of NECC, will finally get to attend some sessions, then drive 6 hours to get home, #necc09    
    
    
    Bernie Dodge's PlacePuzzles: interesting concept. Could be powerful if combined with mobile #necc09    
    
    
    My notes from Bernie Dodge's session:  http://bit.ly/UmSk3 #necc09    
    
    
    waiting for Hal Davidson's mobile phone session #necc09    
    
    
    Hal Davidson: make sure your phones are out and on! #necc09    
    
    
    Hal compares NECC 2008  and 2009, 2 cell phone sessions as compared to 13 this year!! #necc09    
    
    
    just got out of davidson's talk, entertaining as always, wireless didn't work!! #necc09    
    
    
    Back home after 6 hour drive from DC, lots of traffic, one big rainstorm. At least my truck is clean again ;)    
    
    
    Interesting article about cell phone use in schools:  http://bit.ly/14m1eW    
    
    
    #lwf11 First up: Karen Cater US DOE: print-based classroom to digital learning environment, driven by mobile, broadband, apps.    
    
    
    #lwf11 also social media and data...    
    
    
    Karen Cater US DOE: we need better assessment tools, 24/7 student devices, & competency-based models of learning #lwf11    
    
    
    Karen Cater: US educational system needs a new OS, not just a reboot #lwf11    
    
    
    Karen Cater: US education is bi-partisan, really???? So why so little progress? #lwf11    
    
    
    Iris Lapinski: creating a new generation of problem solvers. #lwf11    
    
    
    Iris Lapinski: 70% of developed countries fail to improve their education systems. #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray. Wolfram Research, periodic table table!    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray: for good e-books, you need authors, real programmers, and experience from the tv/movie world.    
    
    
    #lwf11 Theo Gray: e-books are not textbooks!! More like enrichment... There is no real market anymore for dig textbooks    
    
    
    @gravesle so why don't you?    
    
    
    @timrylands: Best presentation today, hands down!! Above all, you made the point that tech can't and won't replace great teachers! #lwf11    
    
    
    Congratulations to @jnxyz for winning Primary Practitioner #LWF11 award in London!!    
    
    
    Great day at #lwf11 today (one of the best conference days yet?), start to finish. Mobile research strand tomorrow (10-1530, James Watt Rm)    
    
    
    Dick Winters (Band of Br) has passed away http://bit.ly/fwxeZx One of my heroes for what he did for my family and country in WWII, RIP!    
    
    
    @timbuckteeth Likewise! It was great to see you as well. #lwf11    
    
    
    One week left to submit your proposal for the LWF2011 mobile research strand: http://bit.ly/coft46 (due by 9/24)    
    
    
    Mobile research strand has started in James Watt. Come join us! #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 PrimaryPad link for mobile research strand: http://www.primarypad.com/lwf11    
    
    
    Attewell & Petley now presenting in mob research strand. Royle up next #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle now presenting in mob research strand about netbook project on Telford #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle in mob lrng research strand: netbooks not a good choice from tech pov? #lwf11    
    
    
    Royle in mob research strand: students as co-researchers: awesome! #lwf11    
    
    
    Roundtables starting in mobile research strand. Should be some great discussions! #lwf11    
    
    
    2nd round of mobile research papers about to start in James Watt #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobile research strand: Laura Pearson coming up w mobile for ESL #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobile research papers to be published after #lwf11 Info to follow. #mobile research.    
    
    
    Taylor & Dearnley now presenting at mobile research strand #lwf11    
    
    
    Marcus Specht presenting on AR in mobile research strand #lwf11    
    
    
    Lord David Puttnam: Digitized learning does not equal digital learning #lwf11    
    
    
    Jimmy Wales: dream of free access to knowledge for all = wikipedia #lwf11    
    
    
    Wikipedia contributors are at the intersection of intelligence, obsession & lots of free time - Jimmy Wales #lwf11    
    
    
    #lwf11 was awesome!!! Thanks to G., Kabelo, and crew!!!    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt wants to know: How do you manage your time? Answer 'the question' at http://bit.ly/ilt-f10 Please RT!    
    
    
    Back in Ohio after exhausting/exhilarating #lwf11. Got lots of great ideas this year, met lots of great people!!! Thanks to LWF!!    
    
    
    In DC at #SUG2010: http://bit.ly/bQPxwp. Presenting #GeoHistorian in first lightning round.    
    
    
    Lightning Round sure goes fast!! Lots of great projects. Of course I 4got to mention GeoHistorian co-director Thomas McNeal :( #SUG2010    
    
    
    "In the internet age could we lose the past as we document the present?" This will make you think!! http://bbc.in/ar01RX    
    
    
    Scholastic and AT&T team up for mobile learning: http://shar.es/0JhBc     
    
    
    Frantically trying to finish my AERA proposal. It's due today.    
    
    
    Blogged: Miami U mobile learning presentation: http://bit.ly/cAXBAE #mlearning #GoM4L #SIGML    
    
    
    GeoHistorian project website now online: http://bit.ly/d0SpCU  More content coming soon... #GeoHistorian    
    
    
    @lisasjogren so is that with or without windchill? It's -5 here (with...)    
    
    
    Blogged: #GeoHistorian website now online: http://bit.ly/cxG6pu    
    
    
    blogged: #LWF2011 late breaking papers due 11/29/10: http://bit.ly/d7jE2P    
    
    
    Manuscripts for #RCETJ Spring 2011 issue are due by 11/30/10: http://bit.ly/brMSgs    
    
    
    @GrahamBM: Thanks for the videos!! Now I can watch what I missed (waiting for the Tuesday sessions) :) #lwf11 #lwf    
    
    
    Preparing for HHL. Looking forward to doing two presentations I haven't done before.    
    
    
    @gravesle Congrats on your ABD!!    
    
    
    @gravesle where are you? #oetc11    
    
    
    @gravesle must have missed you! I'll stop by!!    
    
    
    Listening to Sal Khan at #oetc11 (khanacademy.org). Too bad he's not live. Great website though.    
    
    
    Come learn about #QR codes #oetc11 in room D244-245 (3:45-4:30pm). Bring your mobile device!!    
    
    
    listening to futurelab presentation. Lots of interesting projects to check out...    
    
    
    I like the idea of texting questions during the preso; keeps the flow going and audience won't forget questions; of course I don't have my p    
    
    
    ...of course my phone doesn't work here; how about using twitter (like sb else txtd in)    
    
    
    moile learning sig mtg, wow, so many good projects, so much to catch up on...    
    
    
    RT hhl: Check latest Handheld Learning '09 Programme which is now looking v. good http://bit.ly/oGTc1 hope you like! #hhl09    
    
    
    Our #oetc11 QR code presentation now online at http://bit.ly/ghRFNv or http://bit.ly/h772Fy    
    
    
    Reviewing AERA conference proposals. 35 down, 29 more to go X(    
    
    
    And of course working on the research strand for HHL 2009 in London. Should be another great conference this year!!    
    
    
    ISTE's SIGML now has it's own twitter account: sigml    
    
    
    Working on review for HHL 2007, finally...    
    
    
    Getting ready to listen to Obama's speech to students: http://www.whitehouse.gov/live/    
    
    
    Opening act: Arne Duncan, sec. of education.    
    
    
    Next: Pres. of senior class.    
    
    
    Main act: the Prez. Theme seems to be student responsibility for learning.    
    
    
    Lots of mobile phones and cameras in the crowd.    
    
    
    Obama: "You can't drop out and drop into a good job."    
    
    
    Obama: "There is no excuse for not trying."    
    
    
    Obama: "Set your own goals for your education and do what it takes to meet them."    
    
    
    Obama: "Being successful is hard."    
    
    
    Obama: "You have to let your failures teach you."    
    
    
    Obama's connecting education and patriotism throughout...    
    
    
    Obama: "What's your contribution going to be? What problems are you going to solve?    
    
    
    End of speech, Obama's shaking hands with the crowd.    
    
    
    Don’t let Congress sell out your right to free speech online. Take action @freepress: http://freepr.es/g3PVb4 #NetNeutrality    
    
    
    Following "It's Only Rock n Roll" on Engadget: http://bit.ly/e4cCa    
    
    
    Lots of talk about iPod games now.... yawn.    
    
    
    New ad, what about a new iPod!! #apple    
    
    
    iPod nano with camera! http://bit.ly/31F7D #apple    
    
    
    iPod nano now also with FM radio, pedometer (sync to Nike), mic and speaker #apple    
    
    
    No iPod touch with camera? #apple    
    
    
    @GrahamBM  I agree, with the nano your possibilities are more limited...    
    
    
    Mobile app sees science go global:  http://bit.ly/Op6mi (mobile learning at its best!)    
    
    
    My round up of mobile learning stuff for the week:  http://bit.ly/ATAvU    
    
    
    The latest newsletter from #LWF is at: http://bit.ly/lwfnews-250211 with @Abdulchohan @tonyvincent @rankinw #lwf11    
    
    
    Mobility, social interactions, digital content, blended learning #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    #acuconnected #karencator keynote: flashbacks to #lwf11 :)    
    
    
    Assessment: measure what matters #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Teachers need to be highly connected to be highly effective #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Kahn Academy as an example of learning progressions #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    R&D needed: basic research, venture and dev, market (middle section is what we need) #karencator #acuconnected    
    
    
    Seton Hill: iPad use 9-5 (consumption) Mac Book use 5-9 (creation) #acuconnected    
    
    
    Seton Hill: students see largest advantage of iPad as being access to resources #acuconnected    
    
    
    Challenge at ACU is not how to find digital content, but how to assess its value. #scottperkins #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU: though undergrad campus is saturated with iPhones/iPods, budgets are tight. So how to get iPads in hands of fac/students? #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: students positive about mobile learning #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: faculty rate progr as success and student engagement is up. Achievement not nec up #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: attitude, impact and usage vary by device #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: fac report signif class-related use of devices. What is significant? #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU research: mobility allows faculty to transform ed practices #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU should focus on learning outside of classroom and how to connect it to classroom learning. Learning exp should be 24/7 #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff Right,but what do they do with them 4 learning? #acuconnected    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen I agree.... #acuconnected    
    
    
    Challenge-based learning makes learning relevant #donhenderson #acuconnected www.apple.com/education/challenge-based-learning    
    
    
    @abdulchohan up next at #acuconnected More flashbacks to #lwf11 :)    
    
    
    @abdulchohan iPod Touches at Essa led to increased creativity #acuconnected (challenge: how to assess this ...)    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen very true... But there are some real opportunities here beyond testing on content knowledge. Hence the question... #acuconnected    
    
    
    @GoldsAtWork the device doesn't matter, it's the access to content and tools that does #acuconnected    
    
    
    @busynessgirl Internet as waterfall of info and we're under it! #acuconnected    
    
    
    Great ideas from @busynessgirl about a digital learning system, but who should build it (if not education)? #acuconnected    
    
    
    Students do still use laptops for media (music, movies, etc.) and information mgt, also for some productivity like Excel #acuconnected    
    
    
    Why call an inkling textbook a "textbook"? It's so much more than text or book! #acuconnected #Matt McInnis    
    
    
    Connexions = repository, tools, community #acuconnected #sidneyburrus    
    
    
    Jekyll & Hyde AR book on YouTube http://m.youtube.com/#/results?q=jekyll%20and%20hyde%20ar%20book #acuconnected #AR    
    
    
    Alcatel-Lucent work on shared annotations of e-books. Interesting opportunities, some challenges... #acuconnected #ebooks    
    
    
    Students presenting on textbook purchasing in research strand, nice to see #acuconnected    
    
    
    42% of teachers don't know what textbooks cost, and considering the avg student spends $800-$1,100 per year!!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU Student: iPad didn't make much of a difference because pedagogy didn't change. Teachers should harness its potential #acuconnected.    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen but 10 chapters will still cost you $50-$80 then!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    ACU iPad project: wifi only iPads loaned to students for duration of project  (uses different than if iPad owned and 3g) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff: "Mobile learning *in* the classroom": sounds like an oxymoron to me.... #acuconnected    
    
    
    Scott Hamm: iPad as complement, not replacement, for laptop. Heard same from students yesterday #acuconnected    
    
    
    @derekbruff Right, but what do they do with them outside of class with those same devices that could enhance learning in the classroom?    
    
    
    @derekbruff: I got you. I agree that we should focus more on the integration of in and out of the classroom, not focus on one or the other    
    
    
    Scott Hamm: iPad obstacles: no flash, editing docs, poor connectivity, not enough for all students, projection issues #acuconnected    
    
    
    iPad use in Incarnate Word MBA program: typical expectations and concerns. #acuconnected    
    
    
    @HaleyDD #KellerISD  pilot 'BYODevice' next year. N Wireless at school & give Verizon MIFI to students without home access #acuconnected    
    
    
    Incarnate Word: iPad needs more prod tools:keyboard, camera, video conf, flash, printing, no screen switching, Office, VGA out #acuconnected    
    
    
    @krista_scott Yes ;) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @HaleyDD Me too. It could fundamentally change technology integration/funding for that district, probably will #acuconnected    
    
    
    Tatom research paper online at http://bit.ly/dS3bzb #acuconnected    
    
    
    @ccoppolsen Good question. Netbooks don't seem to have gotten a lot of traction #acuconnected    
    
    
    Tatom: some of the FHU profs no longer use a textbook, but online resources. YES!! #acuconnected    
    
    
    FHU: students have MacBook, iPhone/iPod, AND iPad: overkill?? #acuconnected.    
    
    
    FHU research: Students believe iPad encouraged engagement during lecture:. But why still lecture (new tech, old pedagogy) #acuconnected    
    
    
    @krista_scott Agreed. Just providing one could be cost-prohibitive for institutions. BYOD (e.g. Keller ISD) as the answer? #acuconnected    
    
    
    Obama: education is the economic issue of our time #adriansannier #acuconnected    
    
    
    The 4 beyonds: beyond textbooks, bookstores, LMS, school. #adriansannier #acuconnected    
    
    
    Question remains: how can we get education to truly innovate fast enough and in ways that will scale? #acuconnected    
    
    
    AR stuff in the research track, always cool #acuconnected    
    
    
    AR at ACU http://kjar.posterous.com #acuconnected    
    
    
    However beautiful the strategy, you should occasionally look at the result - Churchill (importance of mobile research) #acuconnected    
    
    
    Easy mobility leads to easy collaboration #fraserspeirs #acuconnected    
    
    
    T @hhl Print version of programme for Handheld Learning 2009 now available at: http://bit.ly/hl09guide 3Mb PDF    
    
    
    Checking out WordPress for iPhone. Any tips, tricks, suggestions?    
    
    
    Working url for SIGML survey:  http://bit.ly/12U3Kc    
    
    
    SHARE YOUR VISION OF MOBILE LEARNING and 5 people may win a free registration to www.mobile2011.org  Enter now http://tinyurl.com/66p8ouy    
    
    
    Don't forget Tony Vincent's Podcast Picks today at 3pm PST/6pm EST http://j.mp/1AzB3    
    
    
    #RCETJ special issue on technology in mathematics and science education now online at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX    
    
    
    just posted another mobile learning round-up:  http://bit.ly/17mSBI    
    
    
    ISTE proposals due on Oct. 7, midnight PST!!    
    
    
    At hhl conf hheckl session, catching end of it.    
    
    
    Hheckl top 3, ds, iPod touch, apple tablet #hhl    
    
    
    Hheckl top 3, no mobile phone! #hhl    
    
    
    In learner's y, it's packed! #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y still not started, what gives? #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y BOPOD project w ipods, apps used #hhl    
    
    
    BOPOD: but do the ipods leave the classroom? #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y: BOPOD'a done: half the room cleared out! #hhl09    
    
    
    Learner's y: next up Oakdale school from London: DS 4 Math #hhl09    
    
    
    in Pecha Kucha now, presentation on how web design for mobile and desktop are influencing each other #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: Stuart Smith talking about mobile web: 30% of websites do not display on iPhone #hhl09    
    
    
    lots of coining of terms at @hhl09: crapps and plearn so far #hhl09    
    
    
    @pressfuturist  yes it is...    
    
    
    @irislapinski  yikes, missed the name, some guy from the US    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha:  M'ubuntu mlearning for South Africa to solve literacy crisis #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: M'ubuntu: pbl, basic skills and teacher pd deliverd on mobile phone #hhl09    
    
    
    Pecha Kucha: M'ubuntu: asking 4 help on getting phones  to sustain the project (Lucy Haagen, lucyhaagen@yahoo.com). Now using Sprint #hhl    
    
    
    Best practices: text your description to the presenter and he'll send you a drawing #hhl09    
    
    
    Best Practices: more people in the session have been to Africa than used Android #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan: students need 24/7 access,. Yes!! #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan listing apps for iPod Touch, Classics, Story Kit, Civ Rev, Leaf Trombone, Wurdle, Geared, Strip Designer, Brushes #hhl09    
    
    
    Louise Duncan: is not having a camera on a mobile device a negative? Maybe not... #hhl09    
    
    
    Quick break back at the hotel from #hhl09, then back to Awards Presentation. Busy day so far ...    
    
    
    At hhl awards #hhl09    
    
    
    Hhl awards starting #hhl09    
    
    
    #hhl09 Blog post: Handheld Learning Day 1: http://bit.ly/163xof    
    
    
    mobile learning in current schools: an oxymoron?? #hhl09    
    
    
    Hillwig: 50% of PhD students in USA are not US citizens (and I'm one of them) :D #hhl09    
    
    
    Just posted #hhl09 day 2, part 1 blog post:  http://bit.ly/NPIQP    
    
    
    ... and  #hhl09 day 2, part 2 blog post:  http://bit.ly/LNVjT. Final day of HHL tomorrow. It'll be another long one.    
    
    
    @johntraxler : upping the ante for yourself, aren't you? ;)    
    
    
    Research strand @9:30 in James Watts #hhl09    
    
    
    Tracker kicking of research strand: always entertaining #hhl09    
    
    
    Oops, should be Traxler #hhl09    
    
    
    Traxler: journalism as first draft of history: citiz. Journalism using mobile #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Robin Deegan talks usability #hhl09    
    
    
    Deegan: mobile use us usually in short bursts #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Nicola Bedall-Hill talking about her mobile research: mobile as 'boundary objects' #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill: head cam as tool for data collection #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill showing helmet cam video: interesting pov #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill quizzing the audience! #hhl09    
    
    
    Bedall-Hill: device not boundary object, but the visual representations #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand: Lucianne Brown presenting on mobile use to teach reading #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: mlearning still exploratory..... #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: using mobile phones for vocabulary frontloading in reading. #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: mobile phones didn't really make a big difference (as compared to non-users) in achievement, but did in motivation #hhl09    
    
    
    Brown: maybe better results if students are allowed to use phones outside of class as well? #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Perkins and Saltsman  from ACU presenting their iPhone project #hhl09    
    
    
    @didactylos : it's been full all morning, all good papers so far! #hhl09    
    
    
    ACU study: lots of data! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand papers to be published in RCETJ spring 2010 issue: http://www.rcetj.org    
    
    
    Research strand: student engagement a better metric than achievement? #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Jane Lunsford speaks about student support #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable discussions starting at 12:20  #hhl09    
    
    
    Lunsford: texting more useful than email #hhl09    
    
    
    Lunsford: lots of resources at OU #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand Roundtable 1 now in session: lots of discussion #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable switch, come join us! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research stand presenters: Marco Arrigo, Phil Marston, Rhodri Thomas, Domizio Baldini, Karl Royle #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable 2 starting at 14:30. Presenters: Arrigo, Pemberton, Blair, Pulman, van Ooijen #hhl09    
    
    
    Research Strand: roundtable 2. They're off! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: roundtable 3 at 15:10: presenters Avery, Viswanathan, Arrigo, Mills, Seipold, Bunce #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand: Steve Bunce's group is playing DS! Who says research is boring ;) #hhl09    
    
    
    @irislapinski presentations should be, papers will be published in special issue of RCETJ: http://www.rcetj.org #hhl09    
    
    
    Research roundtable 3: last chance to attend! #hhl09    
    
    
    Research strand wrapping up, quite a day!! #hhl09    
    
    
    Thanks to all research strand presenters, great sessions today! #hhl09    
    
    
    Kurzweil: tools of disruptive change are in everyone's hands #hhl09    
    
    
    RT tonyvincent @jont I missed you this year at HHL! 
Same here!!    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for manuscripts (Fall 2011 issue) now open: http://bit.ly/h1C9Bf #edtech Please RT    
    
    
    Please RT: ISTE SIGML members, vote for you favorite book study book: http://bit.ly/90Z4L    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML 2011 Video Contest now accepting submissions!! http://bit.ly/eAKgVo Please RT    
    
    
    @lucretiafraga thx for the compliment!! #mobile2011    
    
    
    @grahamBM keynote at #mobile2011. Always thought-provoking & entertaining. Disruption is good!    
    
    
    @grahamBM m = mainstream #mobile2011    
    
    
    @grahamBM: mobile is transitional, connectivity is key #mobile2011    
    
    
    Learning is not formal v informal. Learning is learning! The artificial dichotomy we've created is part of the problem. #mobile2011    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning    
    
    
    Derek Keenan showing the importance of carefully planned curriculum at #mobile2011 to foster critical thinking.    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning Maybe use one of the sharing sessions on Friday? #mobile2011    
    
    
    Some of the #mobile2011 scavenger hunt videos now aggregated on YouTube: http://bit.ly/fmw4Jp More to come...    
    
    
    @miami_mlearning  I'll be there #mobile2011    
    
    
    @andygstoll I used QR codes, @miami_mlearning plugged the content into wikitude during the event on thursday at Heritage Square #mobile2011    
    
    
    RT:“@tonyvincent: Notes from my #mobile2011 presentation "Mobilize for Productivity" http://tonyv.me/mp ”    
    
    
    More scavenger hunt videos now uploaded at http://bit.ly/gOHPLv #mobile2011    
    
    
    My GeoHistorian and Thursday am keynote slides will be posted later today on mobile2011blog.posterous.com  #mobile211    
    
    
    @JaneneG Yes, 1:30 pm it is. We'll meet in the Regency ballroom and go from there. #mobile2011    
    
    
    Mobile scavenger hunt recap at http://mobile2011blog.posterous.com/mobile-scavenger-hunt … #mobile2011    
    
    
    @ingewassmann ...and very nice to meet you! Tot ziens :) #mobile2011    
    
    
    New animal barcode scanner earns its stripes - Science http://www.msnbc.msn.com/id/42500680/ns/technology_and_science-science/ … via @todayshow    
    
    
    Back home from #mobile2011 and packing for #AERA2011. New Orleans, here I come!    
    
    
    @felixjacomino Awesome search story!! :D Should send it to the Arrogant Butcher's manager ;) #mobile2011    
    
    
    @michaelmgrant yep, presenting Monday, 8:15 am #AERA2011    
    
    
    @GrahamBM so what you're really saying is that you need another iPad2 ... :D    
    
    
    SIGML Dec. newsletter contributions due by December 1 to mvanthoo@kent.edu    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study choices survey closes on Dec. 2. Vote now at http://bit.ly/90Z4L    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML video contest blogged by #BrainPOP: http://bit.ly/lWaZrB    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML: One week left to submit your entries for the 2011 Video Contest! See rules and enhanced prize package at http://bit.ly/kktNot    
    
    
    #lwf11 late breaking mobile research papers due in one week!! http://bit.ly/coft46    
    
    
    RCETJ Vol 7 No 1 now published at http://bit.ly/dtoIZX including special section with #LWF2011 mobile research papers #mlearning    
    
    
    Sign up for the SIGML book study at http://bit.ly/6gA411    
    
    
    SIGML December Newsletter available at http://bit.ly/5TcKhg    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML: One day left to submit your entries for the 2011 Video Contest! See rules and enhanced prize package at http://bit.ly/kktNot    
    
    
    #ISTE 2011 #SIGML  volunteers needed for outdoor event (6/28 2-4p) info http://bit.ly/mJiNsO  Interested? Send email to istesigml@gmail.com    
    
    
    Just blogged: First Round of Digital Stories Almost Done!  for the #GeoHistorian Project: http://bit.ly/jE4Ccf #QR #mlearning    
    
    
    @karlroyle The map in the post? Just Google Maps.    
    
    
    @karlroyle ... and #QR codes made with i-nigma.    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGML 2011 Video Contest voting now open:  http://svy.mk/jh1oB4 You must be an ISTE member to vote;  voting closes on June 17, 2011.    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian is in the news today: http://www.recordpub.com/news/article/5043971    
    
    
    #ISTE #SIGilt just published innovative learning, read the latest issue at http://bit.ly/sigilt-spring11 'Forward it on' by RT-ing!    
    
    
    Only 10 days left to vote for your favorite #ISTE #SIGML video contest entries! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    First set of #GeoHistorian #QR code markers is ready: http://bit.ly/jawvnl  To be installed on 6/18/11 #mlearning    
    
    
    ISTE SIGML book study starts on 1/25/10. Sign up to participate here: http://bit.ly/6gA411    
    
    
    Only five days left to vote for your favorites in the #ISTE #SIGML 2011 video contest! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    Voting for the  #ISTE #SIGML 2011 video contest closes tomorrow 6/17!! http://svy.mk/jh1oB4    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news again, KHS newsletter article: http://bit.ly/mmEJDF #QR #qrcode    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian: first set of QR code markers to be installed tomorrow (6/18) in Kent, OH #QR #qrcode: http://bit.ly/kHdrZh    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 1 - Developed and Developing Countries http://ning.it/5DqHLp    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 1 - Evaluation http://ning.it/8S26XN    
    
    
    Coontz Center Breakthroughs in Mobile Learning Challenge, $50K top prize for best mobile learning innovation: http://bit.ly/5wJnpc    
    
    
    Following the iPad release online: http://bit.ly/83sf3a    
    
    
    Looks like a big iPhone to me, just thinner ...    
    
    
    I wonder what the cost is going to be ...    
    
    
    iPad Brushes app looks pretty cool...    
    
    
    New app: iBooks. New, really???    
    
    
    @kathtrinder iPad. Not exactly creative, I'd say...    
    
    
    @jamesclay: yep, but for 64 GB with 3G it'll run you $829, not so cheap...    
    
    
    checking out new hhl site, preparing presentations for NECC.    
    
    
    @graham: sure, netbooks are good tools for learning while mobile    
    
    
    Listening to Julie Lindsay and Vicki Davis talking about digiteen and flat classroom project. Interesting stuff.    
    
    
    At eTech Ohio conference: http://www.etech.ohio.gov/conference/    
    
    
    eTech Ohio: St. Marys mobile phone presentation: 630 + smart phones in grades 3-6 :)    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study Chapter 2: Learning Content: http://ning.it/cc8851    
    
    
    SIGML Book Study: Chapter 2 - Vygotskys zone http://ning.it/b7suOE    
    
    
    eTech Ohio keynote: not bad for a 12-yr-old:  http://bit.ly/55raSR    
    
    
    #GeoHistorian in the news: http://kent.patch.com/articles/qr-codes-provide-link-to-kents-past … #QR #ISTE11    
    
    
    PBS Digital Nation:  http://bit.ly/akObM4    
    
    
    #SIGML walking tour at 2p (Indep Square). Join us or find handout at http://sigml.iste.wikispaces.net/ISTE_2011  #QR #ISTE11    
    
    
    #BrainPOP feature movie of the day about Ben Franklin to coincide with #SIGML walking tour: http://bit.ly/lJD7NG #ISTE11 #QR    
    
    
    #setsig #sigml #iste11 so much to learn at setsig playground-mobile apps, techs, pedagogy, and lots of really smart people-please visit soon    
    
    
    #SIGML video contest winners at http://sigml.iste.wikispaces.net/2011_Video_Contest  #ISTE11    
    
    
    I just told Washington to stand with me and Obama for #NetNeutrality. Your turn: http://bit.ly/4sJgrp (via @freepress)    
    
    
    GeoHistorian Project in Chronicle of Higher Ed: http://bit.ly/91honP    
    
    
    blogged: eTech Ohio mobile tech sessions: http://bit.ly/c2401h    
    
    
    Blogged: eTech Ohio Tuesday morning panel: http://bit.ly/aYZeJE    
    
    
    Blogged: eTech Ohio: St Marys Cell Phone project, deja vu? http://bit.ly/9peTRc    
    
    
    Just blogged: http://bit.ly/jTiDU6 #GeoHistorian #QR    
    
    
    #RCETJ call for manuscripts Spring 2012 issue: http://bit.ly/jnl6l0 #edtech    
    
    
    #ISTE2011 #SIGML tour videos now posted: http://bit.ly/j9IDep #QR #mobile. Great job by students from Omaha North High Magnet School!!    
    
    
    #SIGilt asks: What Stood Out for You at #ISTE2011? Fill out the form and share here: http://tinyurl.com/5wqll7y    
    
    
    Blogged: http://bit.ly/qgt0D9. 5 #QR codes installed, 6 more to go #NEH #GeoHistorian #RCET    
    
    
    "Chapter 4 - Mobile in Nursing Education" on SIGML Book Study 2010: http://ning.it/bCapGH    
    
    
    2010 ISTE SIGML video contest is on!! http://bit.ly/9sGqnV    
    
    
    SIGML bookstudy Chp. 5, Informal Learning in Online Communities: http://bit.ly/cxYdnF    
    
    
    Preparing for the HHL 2008 research strand. Go out and shoot some video for cell-phone presentation later today. It's raining now.    
    
    
    @hhl. I'm bringing a laptop, digital camera, two mobile phones and a palm TX. I wonder if the phones will actually work....    
    
    
    Got to London for HHL2008 this morning. Beautiful weather!!    
    
    
    @ kathtrinder Cool! Hope to see you guys soon.    
    
    
    @mamk Video shoot went great, in between the rain drops. You'll see it on Tuesday.    
    
    
    @hhl Andy Black's session was good, variety of presentations. Now at Pecha Kucha (yes I got there late).    
    
    
    @kathtrinder: hope to see you there.    
    
    
    hhl d watching Derek Robertson    
    
    
    #tonyvincent where are you?    
    
    
    @tonyvincent: where are you? Ech, can't type today.    
    
    
    @kathtrinder go look at Spore when you get home ;)    
    
    
    @jamesclay don't worry, MAMK is streaming the keynote live to qik and will have a detailed report for you in triplicate :D    
    
    
    @jont oh I don't know, Wall Street maybe, or the White House?    
    
    
    @jamesclay quick, put in your feedback form and win a fabulous prize!    
    
    
    made it to Taiwan, long trip, reception great!    
    
    
    Pictures of the 6th #GeoHistorian #qr marker, installed at #Kent Hotel: http://www.rcet.org/geohistorian/2011/07/29/marker-6-is-in-place/ … #NEH #ODH    
    
    
    SIGML book study chp 6: Applying M-Learning: http://bit.ly/codN2D    
    
    
    #SIGilt  (ISTE) collecting policies about digital citizenship and innovation http://bit.ly/aS49bG Please RT and get the word out!    
    
    
    Google blog about QR codes: http://bit.ly/bFV23P, via @audreywatters    
    
    
    