#7: http://languagelog.ldc.upenn.edu/nll/  (85% of posts read)    
    
    
    #6: http://marginalrevolution.com  (86% of posts read)    
    
    
    #5: http://radar.oreilly.com/  (90% of posts read)    
    
    
    #4: http://leonardo.blogspot.be/  (94% of posts read)    
    
    
    #3: http://www.umsu.de/opp/  Online Papers in Philosophy (96% of posts read)    
    
    
    #2:http://www.shorpy.com  (98% of posts read)    
    
    
    #1: drumroll... http://www.smbc-comics.com  a perfect score of 100% of posts read. that's all...    
    
    
    Mount Emei, where males use their moustaches for aggressive interaction, http://bit.ly/14HHpcA     
    
    
    Thai movie Ploy http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0993778/ … shows how jet lag induces previous unattainable moral distinctions, much like the kernel of an SVM    
    
    
    just found balloon launched by the young Mathys Broeders from Geertruidenberg https://maps.google.com/maps?q=Van+Beverenlaan+5,+Geertruidenberg,+The+Netherlands&hl=en&ll=51.703204,4.851837&spn=0.72256,2.113495&sll=37.0625,-95.677068&sspn=58.206849,135.263672&oq=5+van+beverenl&hnear=Van+Beverenlaan+5,+Geertruidenberg,+Noord-Brabant,+The+Netherlands&t=m&z=10 … please form a chain and let him know    
    
    
    it's July 1 and I still can log on Google Reader. Now I know how http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Harold_Camping … 's followers must have felt...    
    
    
    Memory Limited, Streaming PCA. (arXiv:1307.0032v1 [stat.ML]) http://bit.ly/19R0M9V     
    
    
    Movers and Shakers: Kinetic Energy Harvesting for the Internet of Things. (arXiv:1307.0044v1 [cs.ET]) http://bit.ly/1b3Rk1c     
    
    
    real time self service bicycles open data API from @JCDecauxDev https://developer.jcdecaux.com/#/home     
    
    
    Git and GitHub for data http://blog.okfn.org/2013/07/02/git-and-github-for-data/ … by @rufuspollock    
    
    
    @drstevenwooding indeed. Thanks    
    
    
    Orienteering in Knowledge Spaces: The Hyperbolic Geometry of Wikipedia Mathematics http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/plosone/PLoSONE/~3/p6C0dujP_K0/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0067508 …    
    
    
    Observing parent(s)/offspring clusters at Cambridge Open Days http://www.study.cam.ac.uk/undergraduate/events/opendays/cambridge/ … is an exercise in applied sociology/psychology    
    
    
    Parents drive schedule, logistics with brutal efficiency. Offsprings hide their passions very well behind fear of parents and unknown    
    
    
    @Nigel_Shadbolt is there a URL for #midata ?    
    
    
    @carlmalamud @kncukier evidently, Skinner did not have to deal with intervening interruptions. Good for him.    
    
    
    @danbri in general, think of the sonic boom that happens when technology evolves faster than moral/political intuitions/institutions    
    
    
    @Nigel_Shadbolt great, thanks. Will be following    
    
    
    Super interesting conversation on data privacy preserving methods with @ThoreG at @MSFTResearchCam    
    
    
    At @MSFTResearchCam learned about somewhat homomorphic encryption http://research.microsoft.com/apps/mobile/publication.aspx?id=148825 … as pragmatic method for privacy protection    
    
    
    At @MSFTResearchCam also learned about MyPersonality project http://www.psychometrics.cam.ac.uk/page/255/mypersonality.htm … by http://www.michalkosinski.com/     
    
    
    Heard conjecture that Izbicki's algebraic classifiers http://izbicki.me/public/papers/icml2013-algebraic-classifiers.pdf … could allow removal of individual person's info from classifier    
    
    
    Recruiters from http://www.kaust.edu.sa/  looking at my LinkedIn profile    
    
    
    Using linked data as training data, gold corpus, for information extraction http://oak.dcs.shef.ac.uk/ld4ie2013/index.html …    
    
    
    @shevski battle hardened, strategic, schedule conscious elders dragging along anxious, confused, greenhouse raised very bright young shoots    
    
    
    Just as you can't catch yourself falling asleep you can't detect the moment at which youth starts looking attractive to you in and of itself    
    
    
    @mocost could I have @vaughanbell 's copy? :) :)    
    
    
    The rooms of The Castle http://www.booking.com/hotel/gb/the-castle-cambridge.en.html … are made of special materials that collect and amplify noises for miles around    
    
    
    Haven't been able to access Feedly for past 24h (always over capacity). Have others experienced same?    
    
    
    @PaulZH thanks!    
    
    
    @Noahpinion @seanmcarroll in Italian there's a dedicated expression, "toscanaccio" to refer to the cantankerous wit of people from Tuscany    
    
    
    “Recently there have been people getting on in the world as strategists, but they are usually just sword-fencers” Miyamoto Musashi    
    
    
    @feedly very courteous of you to get in touch. Will update asap, thanks    
    
    
    La femme {Niki|metada}ta    
    
    
    Remarkable how many reviews/ads on New York Review of Books don't convey ideas but just aspiration of (intellectual) status    
    
    
    Observing 100s of students facing decisions realized that, although not always right/successful, was blessed w/ always knowing what I wanted    
    
    
    @janl quis custodiet custodes?    
    
    
    Improving data utility in differential privacy and k-anonymity. (arXiv:1307.0966v1 [cs.CR]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.0966     
    
    
    Quantum support vector machine for big feature and big data classification. (arXiv:1307.0471v1 [quant-ph]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.0471     
    
    
    Up-goer five semantics http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/semanticsetc/~3/28D4HjyG1y8/ … see also Growing a Language http://cs.au.dk/~hosc/local/HOSC-12-3-pp221-236.pdf … http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_ahvzDzKdB0 …    
    
    
    calling 13y old son vacationing at home to see if he's up at 11:48am is considered 'a bit fascist'    
    
    
    neural dust: a roadmap to build a network of permanent sensors inside the brain http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.2196  via @eboyden3    
    
    
    @mocost @vaughanbell my daughter is reading http://www.amazon.com/Human-Brain-Ideas-Really-ebook/dp/B00CUE0BPI/ … to prepare for Oxbridge interview and she loves it    
    
    
    @gagnier well done for exposing this ageist hypocrisy. the right to control what information is released about oneself begins at home.    
    
    
    @random_walker did you notice that they identify *you* and use your presumed location in the background sign?    
    
    
    I bet within ten years similar big data preference analyses will be run over individually identified food items http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2013/echo-nest-harmony-with-big-data-0710.html …    
    
    
    @thulme @nytimes @brucenussbaum Big Doodoo?    
    
    
    @scheeinfo I will be in Taipei on 11 and 12 August. Lunch?    
    
    
    @scheeinfo great. bring interesting friends if you can and if they are interested.    
    
    
    entertainment Big Data meets the http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lucas_critique … : http://motherboard.vice.com/blog/why-there-are-so-many-terrible-movies-on-netflix …    
    
    
    A Reliable Effective Terascale Linear Learning System. (arXiv:1110.4198v3 [cs.LG] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/1110.4198  via @feedly    
    
    
    @johnlsheridan aubade? http://www.poemhunter.com/best-poems/philip-larkin/aubade/ …    
    
    
    A Data Management Approach for Dataset Selection Using Human Computation. (arXiv:1307.3673v1 [cs.LG]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.3673     
    
    
    Data Structures and Algorithms for Counting Problems on Graphs using GPU http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/hgpuorg/~3/RprhF5UFGro/ …    
    
    
    wonder if one could use the same approach http://research.microsoft.com/apps/video/dl.aspx?id=172991 … to re-engineer formal processes in organizations    
    
    
    @FroehlichMarcel is there also an easy explanation to go with the easy answer?    
    
    
    @FroehlichMarcel not if you replace a human calculation cost=X, value=Y with another human calculation at cost=X/N, value=Y/M with N>>>M    
    
    
    @FroehlichMarcel important point of the paper is method to *verifiably* train the new routine to match results of old modulo margin of error    
    
    
    @mijopo well: can we?    
    
    
    @mijopo the quality of *whose* life if the same dollar could go either to better child care *or* to longer terminal care (but not both)?    
    
    
    @FroehlichMarcel you may, if you can harness things like http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Honest_signal … http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Prediction_market … http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mechanism_design …    
    
    
    @hadleybeeman @danbri @sandhawke for most comprehensive, I am willing to bet http://www.cyc.com/platform/opencyc … biggest take-up I don't know    
    
    
    @jesolem @timoreilly do they also work for corporate meetings?    
    
    
    @FroehlichMarcel organize people in contexts in which what they would *naturally* do creates a *reliable* signal which you can exploit    
    
    
    @NeinQuarterly do you mean "you might *love* Hegel"?    
    
    
    Remarkable how the Controle Technique in Luxembourg can bring even a grown man into a state of panic. Wish me luck.    
    
    
    built dry-stack stone wall as flower bed for our lavenders. started Trotsky's autobiography. noticed the difference in scope.    
    
    
    Ground Control http://flic.kr/p/fduqXD     
    
    
    paper submission deadline for http://privon.semanticweb.org  on web scale data integration and privacy extended to 31 July /cc @ThoreG @FBorgesius    
    
    
    @FBorgesius ok, then, please, pass it on...    
    
    
    Deterministic Coreference Resolution Based on Entity-Centric, Precision-Ranked Rules http://www.mitpressjournals.org/doi/abs/10.1162/COLI_a_00152?ai=t0&mi=3dqbka&af=R …    
    
    
    Hegel's Philosophy of Food http://privatewww.essex.ac.uk/~wmartin/HegelPhilosophyofFood.pdf … to protect the children, in my library I keep Hegel hidden behind de Sade    
    
    
    To reduce astronomical waste: take your time, then go very fast http://lesswrong.com/lw/hll/to_reduce_astronomical_waste_take_your_time_then/ …    
    
    
    following @andraz 's lead http://andraz.wpengine.com/2013/03/microcredit-kiva-zidisha/ … switching from http://www.kiva.org  to http://www.zidisha.org     
    
    
    also started monthly donation to http://www.givedirectly.org/howitworks.php  because http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/03/want_to_help_people_just_give.html … and because they use M-Pesa http://www.dailydealmedia.com/bitcoins-payable-through-kenyas666-m-pesa-service-via-kipochi-mobile-wallet/ …    
    
    
    Legal Entity Identifiers: global system to identify parties to financial transact http://www.treasury.gov/connect/blog/Pages/System-Taking-Shape-to-Assign-IDs-for-Financial-Market-Participants.aspx … via @soramaki /cc @opencorporates    
    
    
    who would have thought... https://www.geiportal.org/index.php  http://www.leiroc.org  http://www.ciciutility.org     
    
    
    @opencorporates well done! btw, do you know @soramaki ? it looks as you if guys have very complementary interests    
    
    
    https://www.goodjudgmentproject.com  season 3 started. quick poll: who thinks that Turkey will ratify new constitution by 1 February 2014?    
    
    
    @AmyDrummond I doubt it. @gavagai_corp are very large scale, hard core computational semantic holists (hence the name)    
    
    
    Microsoft Research working on embedding ID tags in 3D printed objects http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130723-microsoft-research-working-on-embedding-id-tags-in-3d-printed-objects.html …    
    
    
    The Ringtone Dialectic http://mitpress.mit.edu/books/ringtone-dialectic … sounds like a really interesting book    
    
    
    I wonder if http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130723-microsoft-research-working-on-embedding-id-tags-in-3d-printed-objects.html … will speed up embedding of identifiers in individual food items http://qz.com/86685/the-audacious-plan-to-end-hunger-with-3-d-printed-food/ … /cc @cbrewster    
    
    
    European Commission call for tender to measure progress with respect to size and trends of the European data economy https://ec.europa.eu/digital-agenda/en/news/smart-20130063-study-european-data-market-and-related-services …    
    
    
    notice that https://ec.europa.eu/digital-agenda/en/news/smart-20130063-study-european-data-market-and-related-services … requires delivery of data (#linkeddata preferred) to be later published on http://open-data.europa.eu/     
    
    
    @cbrewster not even spaghetti, linguini, rigatoni, fusilli... ?    
    
    
    the European Commission employs more economists and scientists than lawyers http://blogs.lse.ac.uk/europpblog/2013/06/27/european-commision-strenghts/ …    
    
    
    If We Share Data, Will Anyone Use Them? Data Sharing and Reuse in the Long Tail of Science and Technology http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/plosone/PLoSONE/~3/QlGXxwUZbjc/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0067332 … via @feedly    
    
    
    Sensor architecture for single-photon sampling http://www.pnas.org/content/110/30/E2752.short?rss=1 … more sensors, more photons, more data    
    
    
    World's First 3D Printed Ink Cartridges http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130724-worlds-first-3d-printed-ink-cartridges.html …    
    
    
    business strategy courses https://www.coursera.org/course/compstrategy … https://www.coursera.org/course/strategy101 … , like Benjamin's Angel of History, always look at the past    
    
    
    Too Good To Be True:  The Scientific Mass Production of Spurious Statistical Significance http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/StatisticalModelingCausalInferenceAndSocialScience/~3/0IaSQp0NO3U/ …    
    
    
    @jesolem best of luck. come back to Europe, start another company :)    
    
    
    hope to get pleasurable memories implants with my pension plan http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/inception-mit-scientists-implant-a-false-memory-into-a-mouses-brain/2013/07/25/47bdee7a-f49a-11e2-a2f1-a7acf9bd5d3a_story.html …    
    
    
    would utilitarian repugnantly conclude http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/repugnant-conclusion … it worth creating billions with false positive memories http://www.sciencemag.org/content/341/6144/387 …    
    
    
    @DNADigest what are technical plans for preserving data privacy in the face of results as http://research.microsoft.com/apps/pubs/default.aspx?id=187496 … ? see also @random_walker    
    
    
    when cost fake pleasurable memories < cost of *real* pleas mems http://www.sciencemag.org/content/341/6144/387 … liberal civilizations implode http://seedmagazine.com/content/article/why_we_havent_met_any_aliens/ …    
    
    
    have you installed filter against corrosive influence of fake pleasurable memories? http://www.sciencemag.org/content/341/6144/387 … pardon my Spengler    
    
    
    having kissed off wife+kids on their early vacation start, now walking into living room with shoes on just to feel what it's like #overrated    
    
    
    don't make the mistake of confusing for silent types those who are {infra|ultra}sonic or telepathic    
    
    
    judging from your favourites, you guys like my living room antics more than my Spengler    
    
    
    @vrandezo awesome movie indeed. what do you think we learned from it?    
    
    
    @opencorporates notice lament on absence of EU-wide system of identifiers for companies http://lod2.eu/BlogPost/1704-lod2-presentation-at-the-publications-office-of-the-european-union.html … by @lod2project    
    
    
    you know what I don't see? http://www.predictioneersgame.com  practitioners taking top spot(s) at https://www.goodjudgmentproject.com     
    
    
    50 shades of gray:  A research story http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/StatisticalModelingCausalInferenceAndSocialScience/~3/-v3rgS9J3k0/ …    
    
    
    3D printed luxury homes for hermit crabs http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130728-3d-printed-luxury-homes-for-hermit-crabs.html …    
    
    
    done with my paper reviews for http://privon.semanticweb.org  workshop    
    
    
    is anyone making plans for possible convergence of http://deeplearning.net  and memcapacitive neural networks http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.6921  ?    
    
    
    I've contributed to The LinkedIn Inspiration Index http://lnkd.in/ii_tw  #InspirationIndex would be really curious to see the results    
    
    
    looking forward to day when there'll be as many interesting food recipes as there are songs on iTunes http://www.cmarcelo.com/cornucopia     
    
    
    Security Economics in the HTTPS Value Chain http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2277806 …    
    
    
    Fennel, an online/streaming algorithm for very big graph partitioning http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3q0IGg9enns … at @MSFTResearchCam    
    
    
    apparently they are no utilitarian consequentialists in robotically operated mobile foxholes http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/07/the-surprising-ethics-of-robot-cars/ …    
    
    
    @WiredOpinion it's a riff on "there are no atheists is a foxhole" = people prefer to be/feel safe than to stick to proclaimed beliefs    
    
    
    @WiredOpinion you show how even a consequentialist would not want to be in a consequentialist robotic car if on losing side of dilemma    
    
    
    traffic jams as a proxy measure for economic activity http://qz.com/109859/why-traffic-jams-are-the-sign-of-a-healthy-economy/ …    
    
    
    Flavor Pairing in Medieval European Cuisine: A Study in Cooking with Dirty Data (arXiv:1307.7982v1 [physics.soc-ph]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1307.7982     
    
    
    pondering how much of our social, legal order depends on our believing we know what being dead means http://www.spiegel.de/international/world/doctor-sam-parnia-believes-resurrection-is-a-medical-possibility-a-913075.html …    
    
    
    Ranking wines using the Shapley Value http://www.VoxEU.org/index.php?q=node/9595 …    
    
    
    Glad to be sad, and other examples of benign masochism http://journal.sjdm.org/12/12502a/jdm12502a.pdf …    
    
    
    @jluismarin did they give him an aluminum ingot?    
    
    
    just saw on my LinkedIn stream a recommendation from someone who died a few years ago    
    
    
    .@RedLinkGmBH going live with its semantic enrichment platform http://redlink.co     
    
    
    is there a single German word to describe the pain of visiting a place that means a lot to you with a person who couldn't care less?    
    
    
    @brettbobley ausgezeichnet! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lIRd4lC04l8 …    
    
    
    I have reached the http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Troxler%27s_fading … point of grant proposal reading    
    
    
    I just bought: 'Against Intellectual Monopoly' by Michele Boldrin http://www.amazon.com/dp/B001E9731A/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_ask_iDdyF.1AHWBSS …    
    
    
    Depressed Cakes http://www.ediblegeography.com/depressed-cakes/ … reminds me of Des Esseintes' dinner where dishes were all jet black http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_rebours     
    
    
    the purist will of course realise that cryptopocalypse is an oxymoron http://feeds.arstechnica.com/~r/arstechnica/index/~3/mvKfGVkuwRs/story01.htm …    
    
    
    NOVA: A Functional Language for Data Parallelism http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/hgpuorg/~3/grLrzA2Or2g/ …    
    
    
    Why Movement Is Captured by Music, but Less by Speech: Role of Temporal Regularity http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/plosone/PLoSONE/~3/bGfvACLYH2Q/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0071945 … /cc @MarkChangizi    
    
    
    In Taichung, doing the 7Eleven thing    
    
    
    @serracchiani OK, dicci come    
    
    
    All my solipsist friends are reading Fifty Shades of Eigengrau    
    
    
    @scheeinfo please check e-mail for lunch hookup info on 12 August in Taipei    
    
    
    Feeling close to having a Helen Keller moment wrt Chinese script in Taiwan. Subtitles of bad movies are very helpful.    
    
    
    @fbancilhon a penny for your EU data space consolidation thoughts    
    
    
    Some thoughts on EU data space consolidation by @fbancilhon http://www.data-publica.com/content/2013/08/early-consolidation-in-the-data-eco-system/ …    
    
    
    @fbancilhon well done and thanks for pointing out EU tender to produce study. Note that study is itself required to produce open data    
    
    
    @theno23 so you are done serving your time? :)    
    
    
    Been reading a couple of books on strategy. They feel very much like  http://knowyourmeme.com/memes/how-to-draw-an-owl …    
    
    
    Who is genius @ Google who decided that, based on location, logged in users must receive instructions in a language/script they never use?    
    
    
    Who is genius @ Google who thinks that they must serve you a language/script you don't want even after you have *selected* the one you want?    
    
    
    @FBorgesius hey thanks, I'll try that    
    
    
    Failed to meet @scheeinfo for lunch. Found him on cover of Big Data book pic.twitter.com/SsBdSgJU9p    
    
    
    @theophani @janl tradeoff between amount of nestedness and richness of your language ontology. e.g. u can drop subordinates reifying events    
    
    
    Innovation networks http://arxiv.org/abs/1308.2234     
    
    
    @eurohumph consider a simple hypothesis http://www.blomasa.com     
    
    
    Reading "An Introduction to Zen Buddhism": remarkable how ready monks are to slap enlightenment into pupils http://amzn.com/0802130550     
    
    
    Taipei subway display: real time availability of bathroom stalls pic.twitter.com/1UfaxpMf4E    
    
    
    Iron Man at Taipei 101 pic.twitter.com/ipQtKMrCzz    
    
    
    Things people do when they are bored of being dragged around shopping pic.twitter.com/4q4FOtAjmQ    
    
    
    Inspiratuonal Psychology pic.twitter.com/xPPkLFn8GB    
    
    
    Hidden Structure and Function in the Lexicon. (arXiv:1308.2428v1 [cs.CL]) » good read http://arxiv.org/abs/1308.2428     
    
    
    Parallel Triangle Counting in Massive Streaming Graphs. (arXiv:1308.2166v1 [cs.DB]) » good read http://arxiv.org/abs/1308.2166     
    
    
    Bodleyan balloon pic.twitter.com/28HfweLW3F    
    
    
    Referred to http://www.paulgraham.com/lies.html  to discuss Donnie Darko's teen anxiety with daughter    
    
    
    Efficient Learning Strategy of Chinese Characters Based on Network Approach http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0069745?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+plosone%2FPLoSONE+%28PLOS+ONE+Alerts%3A+New+Articles%29 …    
    
    
    Nap-time dream: vast meadows with 100s of people yelling to attract the others' attention wobbling at the top of very high Maslow stilts    
    
    
    Optimizing the MapReduce Framework on Intel Xeon Phi Coprocessor http://hgpu.org/?p=10449     
    
    
    Shortest Paths in Microseconds. (arXiv:1309.0874v1 [cs.DC]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.0874     
    
    
    Mapping the Bitcoin Economy Could Reveal Users’ Identities  http://www.technologyreview.com/news/518816/mapping-the-bitcoin-economy-could-reveal-users-identities/ …    
    
    
    The ritual of the Street Corner — a “tonic” exercise in humility http://davidbrin.wordpress.com/2013/08/24/the-ritual-of-the-street-corner-a-tonic-exercise-in-humility/ …    
    
    
    @mclduk do you have a reference for that? thx    
    
    
    visual analytics job in Luxembourg http://www.linkedin.com/jobs2/view/6884912?trk=rj_em … /cc @moritz_stefaner    
    
    
    On the Strategic Allocation of Social Gratification. (arXiv:1309.2052v1 [cs.SI])  http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.2052     
    
    
    '3-Sweep' software can create 3D models from a single photo (video)  http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130910-3-sweep-extracting-editable-objects-out-of-a-single-photo.html … this is beyond impressive    
    
    
    more on the (in my opinion inevitable) convergence of food and 3D printing (pace @cbrewster ) http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130910-3d-systems-buys-the-sugar-lab-maker-of-3d-printed-sugar-confections.html …    
    
    
    Wild Orangutan Males Plan and Communicate Their Travel Direction One Day in Advance http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0074896 … better than many people I know    
    
    
    Zebedee: 3D point clouds on a stick http://diydrones.ning.com/xn/detail/705844:BlogPost:1403231 …    
    
    
    does anyone have a copy of Thomson Reuters report on patents and supply chains? http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/09/what-can-patents-and-scientific-papers-tell-you-about-global-supply-chains/ …    
    
    
    Hardware-Oblivious Parallelism for In-Memory Column-Stores http://hgpu.org/?p=10509  via @feedly    
    
    
    trying again on Monday: can anyone share Thomson Reuters' report on patents and supply chains http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/09/what-can-patents-and-scientific-papers-tell-you-about-global-supply-chains/ … ? thanks in advance    
    
    
    Haze: Privacy-Preserving Real-Time Traffic Statistics. (arXiv:1309.3515v1 [cs.CR]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.3515     
    
    
    I usually enjoy John Kay's columns on the FT but his Obliquity http://www.amazon.com/Obliquity-Goals-Best-Achieved-Indirectly/dp/0143120557/ … wasn't worth the paper it's printed on. Avoid    
    
    
    .@ScraperWiki comes out with a scraper to extract tabular data from PDF docs   http://goo.gl/trSpdQ     
    
    
    Prosocial Bonuses Increase Employee Satisfaction and Team Performance http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0075509 …    
    
    
    immortality http://techland.time.com/2013/09/18/google-vs-death/ … and the Maes-Garreau point http://www.kk.org/thetechnium/archives/2007/03/the_maesgarreau.php … looking forward to the existential anxiety dividends    
    
    
    3D scan of the Tower of Pisa http://www.3ders.org/articles/20130919-aussie-scientists-create-first-detailed-3d-scan-of-the-tower-of-pisa.html … very much looking forward to the drone version of this    
    
    
    had quite possibly the most productive conversation of the year with @delftscott who gave me scads of pointers on serious strategy research    
    
    
    My wife explained to me that nobody puts the picture of her husband as desktop background: that's reserved for children #goodtoknow    
    
    
    Ever feel you are expected to hit one out of the ballpark using only the *shadow* of a baseball bat?    
    
    
    free lectures on quantitative economic modeling, programmed in Python http://quant-econ.net/index.html     
    
    
    On the Philosophical Interest and Surprising Significance of the Asshole
   https://webfiles.uci.edu/ajjames/On%20the%20Philosophical%20Interest%20and%20Surprising%20Significance%20of%20the%20AssholeTEXT.doc … academic paper from UC Irvine    
    
    
    In a gold rush, money is made by those who sell picks and shovels http://zipfianacademy.com     
    
    
    Fast $k$-NNG construction with GPU-based quick multi-select. (arXiv:1309.5478v1 [cs.DC]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.5478     
    
    
    Undefined By Data: A Survey of Big Data Definitions. (arXiv:1309.5821v1 [cs.DB]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.5821  the lexicography of hype    
    
    
    On the `Semantics' of Differential Privacy: A Bayesian Formulation. (arXiv:0803.3946v2 [cs.CR] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/0803.3946     
    
    
    Coding 35GB of Data in 35 Pages of Numbers. (arXiv:1211.2853v6 [cs.IT] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/1211.2853     
    
    
    human development opportunities lost due to not all family members being ready for certain dinner table conversations http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kremer%27s_O-Ring_Theory_of_Economic_Development …    
    
    
    Location, Location, Location: Data-Intensive Distributed Computing in the Cloud http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.6452  cfr @DataGravity    
    
    
    Chemical concrete machine. (arXiv:1309.6914v1 [cs.FL]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.6914  Turing complete    
    
    
    Large Graphs on multi-GPUs http://hgpu.org/?p=10588     
    
    
    Research endogamy as an indicator of conference quality http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?id=2503795 …    
    
    
    lighter, cheaper lenses are also easier to put on a drone... http://petapixel.com/2013/09/29/newly-developed-software-helps-get-high-quality-photos-crappy-lenses/ …    
    
    
    Choice blindness in financial decision making http://journal.sjdm.org/13/13804/jdm13804.pdf … one wonders in what other choice domains one would find the same    
    
    
    Tal Zarsky http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2324240 … on transparency: what predictions about people can governments and corporations make using data they have?    
    
    
    Hopping over Big Data: Accelerating Ad-hoc OLAP Queries with Grasshopper Algorithms. (arXiv:1310.0141v1 [cs.DB]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.0141     
    
    
    Evolutionary Algorithm for Graph Anonymization. (arXiv:1310.0229v1 [cs.DB]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.0229     
    
    
    CloudMine: Multi-Party Privacy-Preserving Data Analytics Service. (arXiv:1206.2038v2 [cs.CR] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/1206.2038     
    
    
    Answering n^{2+o(1)} Counting Queries with Differential Privacy is Hard. (arXiv:1207.6945v3 [cs.CR] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/1207.6945     
    
    
    based on my ArXiv feed, I sense a disturbance in the Data Privacy Force today    
    
    
    Optimizing RDF stores by coupling General-purpose Graphics Processing Units and Central Processing Units http://hgpu.org/?p=10620     
    
    
    Data Fusion: Resolving Conflicts from Multiple Sources http://research.google.com/pubs/pub41657.html …    
    
    
    Rolling Up Random Variables in Data Cubes http://research.google.com/pubs/pub41652.html …    
    
    
    at the construction site next to my house very big machines are digging a very big hole, of which I feel as proud as if I had dug it myself    
    
    
    @datamarket well played, Sir, well played...    
    
    
    Ribbon Crystals http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0074932 …    
    
    
    On End Of Period Spending http://www.overcomingbias.com/2013/10/spending.html … the really important part is the broader lesson drawn here by @robinhanson    
    
    
        
    
    
    Jacques Santer at Taiwanese national day celebration in Luxembourg pic.twitter.com/bWGpRDuYA1    
    
    
    US gov shutdown effect http://news.xinhuanet.com/english/business/2013-10/05/c_132772944.htm … on @EU_TTIP_team makes me jump from 171th to 39th place on https://www.goodjudgmentproject.com     
    
    
    don't pontificate about science and technology: publicly predict (and let others do the same) @scicasters just opened http://signup.scicast.org/question_form.html …    
    
    
    c'mon guys, I can't believe you are not excited by the opening of science & technology prediction market @scicasters http://signup.scicast.org/question_form.html …    
    
    
    enormous amounts of data streams will soon be produced by autonomous cars http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=CKqJccK_EkM … what are possible downstream data services?    
    
    
    .@RinkeHoekstra awesome. do you know about http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/European_Legislation_Identifier … and the work done by @johnlsheridan ? would love to see links with EU law    
    
    
    Learned of death at 48 of former high school classmate. His best idea was using tiny paintings as titles for much larger paintings.    
    
    
    A DNA-Based Semantic Fusion Model for Remote Sensing Data http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0077090 … shake and bake semantics for Big Data /cc @witbrock    
    
    
    Obfuscatory obscanturism: making workload traces of commercially-sensitive systems safe to release http://research.google.com/pubs/pub41686.html …    
    
    
    Analyzing Big Data with Dynamic Quantum Clustering. (arXiv:1310.2700v1 [physics.data-an]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.2700     
    
    
    Privacy Aware Learning http://arxiv.org/abs/1210.2085     
    
    
    Measuring the Evolution of Ontology Complexity: The Gene Ontology Case Study http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0075993 …    
    
    
    Nearest Neighbor Search in Google Correlate http://research.google.com/pubs/pub41694.html …    
    
    
    this http://www.spiegel.de/international/zeitgeist/scientist-uses-brainwaves-to-test-ideal-prices-for-products-a-926807.html … becomes important when preferences freely revealed by people similar to you are used to infer *your* preferences    
    
    
    In Watership Down -like situation all moles escaped from construction site next door moved under our lawn    
    
    
    .@valeriadepaiva moles or voles, this is the current situation pic.twitter.com/gpGgvlaRvH    
    
    
    Scaling Graph-based Semi Supervised Learning to Large Number of Labels Using Count-Min Sketch. http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.2959     
    
    
    A Turing test for free will. (arXiv:1310.3225v1 [quant-ph]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.3225     
    
    
    Predictive Policing: Forecasting Crime for Law Enforcement | RAND: http://www.rand.org/pubs/research_briefs/RB9735.html#.UlwTNl6QGvs.twitter … via @RANDCorporation    
    
    
    how many of you regularly receive quality assurance plans full of "Reference undefined!" typesetting errors?    
    
    
    .@mfhepp have you seen this http://blog.sfgate.com/techchron/2013/10/14/google-andreessen-startup-economics-bigdata/ … ? real-time price tracking seems very much your cup of tea    
    
    
    the Neanderthal and the Toothpick http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0076852 … mon semblable, — mon frère!    
    
    
    Empirical performance modeling of GPU kernels using active learning http://hgpu.org/?p=10732     
    
    
    cudaMap: a GPU accelerated program for gene expression connectivity mapping http://hgpu.org/?p=10729     
    
    
    Daughter just got admitted to http://www.reading.ac.uk  now waiting to hear from other schools    
    
    
    Collective Cognition in Humans: Groups Outperform Their Best Members in a Sentence Reconstruction Task http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0077943 …    
    
    
    @eileentso thanks. she is still at sea, trying to harpoon the white whale some 40km NNW of Reading    
    
    
    timeo Danaos et data ferentes http://www.data-elite.com  @eileentso how do you see this space shaping up in Europe?    
    
    
    On Demand Memory Specialization for Distributed Graph Databases. (arXiv:1310.4802v1 [cs.DB]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.4802     
    
    
    @eileentso the latter. I'll join you in the hmmmmm...    
    
    
    completely smooth install of http://www.cyc.com/platform/opencyc … on my new MacBook Pro. well done @cyc_ai @witbrock    
    
    
    FlexGrip: A Soft GPGPU for FPGAs http://hgpu.org/?p=10756     
    
    
    Bostrom's simulation argument http://www.simulation-argument.com  meets cultural dynamics http://www.smbc-comics.com/index.php?db=comics&id=3150 …    
    
    
    Qongratulations to all Turkish friends http://www.lrb.co.uk/blog/2013/10/16/yasmine-seale/q-v-k/ …    
    
    
    .@bigdata for GPUs for #bigdata see also @ParStream https://www.parstream.com/product/gpu-ready/ …    
    
    
    Interesting piece on Sjon on NYRB http://www.nybooks.com/articles/archives/2013/oct/10/sjon-magus-north/ … @gthb @hjalli what say you: worth the time investment?    
    
    
    @gthb @hjalli OK, what should I start with?    
    
    
    Work Efficient Parallel Algorithms for Large Graph Exploration http://hgpu.org/?p=10759     
    
    
    I would guess that the real bottleneck of this operation http://www.lemonde.fr/technologies/article/2013/10/21/comment-la-nsa-espionne-la-france_3499758_651865.html … would be the availability of people who understand French    
    
    
    Massive Query Expansion by Exploiting Graph Knowledge Bases. (arXiv:1310.5698v1 [cs.IR]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.5698     
    
    
    can't keep up with @marin_dim 's feed this couple of days: amazing amount of excellent links on all things #rdf #semanticweb    
    
    
    the software engineering vs procurement operating procedure impedance mismatch http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2013/10/21/the-way-government-does-tech-is-outdated-and-risky/ … as always GOTO http://www.amazon.com/Bureaucracy-Government-Agencies-Classics-ebook/dp/B002K0IEBK …    
    
    
    A Core Calculus for Provenance. (arXiv:1310.6299v1 [cs.PL]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.6299  /cc @pgroth    
    
    
    A multi-Teraflop Constituency Parser using GPUs http://hgpu.org/?p=10781     
    
    
    daughter just received admission letter from Glasgow Psychology http://www.gla.ac.uk/undergraduate/degrees/psychology/ … now only waiting to hear from the big O    
    
    
    @gromgull feed it to the remaining ones    
    
    
    2004 worked on networks/software vulnerabilities modelling, inference-based what-if attack/repair planning. in 2013 http://www.darpa.mil/NewsEvents/Releases/2013/10/22.aspx …    
    
    
    GPU-accelerated natural language parser (half-trillion rule evaluations per second) https://github.com/jcanny/BIDParse     
    
    
    Thinking Things: sensors + API for the internet of things from Telefonica http://www.thinkingthings.telefonica.com/     
    
    
    good piece on chinese medicine http://www.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/medical_examiner/2013/10/traditional_chinese_medicine_origins_mao_invented_it_but_didn_t_believe.html … by @top_philosopher I note that it prospers even in very non-Maoist Republic of China    
    
    
    also @top_philosopher have you ever read Herbert Giles' comments on the "Instructions to the Chinese Coroner" http://www.amazon.com/Historic-China-other-sketches-Herbert-ebook/dp/B0082YW5FO … ?    
    
    
    Distance frictions and firm border effects in knowledge creation: Evidence from Japanese patent data http://www.VoxEU.org/index.php?q=node/9881 …    
    
    
    Big Data singled out as a political priority at 24-25 Oct European Council http://www.consilium.europa.eu/uedocs/cms_data/docs/pressdata/en/ec/139189.pdf … (point 3, page 2)    
    
    
    can we treat location, and thus citizenship, as rent? http://blogs.ft.com/off-message/2013/10/25/the-one-chart-that-explains-the-world/ … see http://openborders.info     
    
    
    A Datalog Engine for GPUs http://hgpu.org/?p=10798     
    
    
    there ain't no rest for the wicked (nor the married man with children)    
    
    
    Scaling SVM and Least Absolute Deviations via Exact Data Reduction. (arXiv:1310.7048v1 [cs.LG]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.7048     
    
    
    @fbancilhon just hope it's not acronyms all the way down...    
    
    
    the economics of data markets (pricing of data and queries in cloud environments) http://cloud-data-pricing.cs.washington.edu/     
    
    
    The Thermodynamic Cost of Fast Thought http://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s11023-013-9302-x … #springerlink    
    
    
    Graham Cormode on Streaming, Sketching and Sufficient Statistics for #bigdata http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-QSkMcPmXN8 … sea also http://strata.oreilly.com/2013/10/stream-mining-essentials.html …    
    
    
    The Optimal Mechanism in Differential Privacy. (arXiv:1212.1186v3 [cs.CR] UPDATED) http://arxiv.org/abs/1212.1186     
    
    
    http://research.google.com/tables?hl=en&ei=TQhyUobQOq7E0AG2i4DQBQ&q=%22big+data%22+europe … you are welcome    
    
    
    15-16 Jan 2014, Luxembourg, Info Day for the next EU call for proposals on data and language technologies http://ec.europa.eu/information_society/newsroom/cf/dae/itemdetail.cfm?item_id=12579 …    
    
    
    done watching Breaking Bad. high point for me was when Walt talks about using the http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kelly_criterion … for gambling    
    
    
    A Philosophy of Tickling -  Aaron  Schuster http://www.cabinetmagazine.org/issues/50/schuster.php … deliciously weird    
    
    
    G2: in-memory graph processing engine with GPU-specific optimizations http://hgpu.org/?p=10839     
    
    
    .@FrankVanHarmele so, is this Marvin http://www.larkc.eu/marvin/  on broadband?    
    
    
    http://www.npr.org/blogs/13.7/2013/11/01/242138044/the-smarter-you-are-the-stupider-you-are … my modest theory: polarised positions are like emotional local maxima: emotionally mature people learn to hyper jump    
    
    
    http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/German_tank_problem … makes me wonder which branches of which peace time governments do their planning by comparably sophisticated methods    
    
    
    people's intuitions about other people's true self are determined in large part by their own value judgments http://philosophycommons.typepad.com/xphi/2013/11/value-judgments-and-the-true-self-1.html …    
    
    
    @evgenymorozov I would expect Chomsky to argue against the unreasonable effectiveness of data http://norvig.com/chomsky.html  , no?    
    
    
    Do Greek people really interrupt each other more than other linguistic communities? http://languagelog.ldc.upenn.edu/nll/?p=8219     
    
    
    http://app.easyopendata.com/#  oh...!    
    
    
    The Composition Theorem for Differential Privacy. (arXiv:1311.0776v1 [cs.DS]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.0776     
    
    
    Making Research Data Repositories Visible: The http://re3data.org  Registry http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0078080 …    
    
    
    Revolutionary narcissism of small differences, in Pantone http://www.dosisdiarias.com/2013/11/58.html  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Narcissism_of_small_differences …    
    
    
    Chelyabinsk meteor trajectory from satellites http://www.pnas.org/content/110/45/18092.short …    
    
    
    this feels a lot like many meetings I remember attending http://xkcd.com/1287/     
    
    
    shouting #opendata from the rooftops http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage&v=ZyvnqCzPViI#t=70 … #ICT2013eu    
    
    
    IBM using Big Data to create new recipes http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.1213  the proof omits the pudding as an exercise for the reader    
    
    
    I am looking for EU-based experts in real time Java http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Real_time_Java … please send pointers and retweet    
    
    
    @BIG_FP7 what about incentive? are there any http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Complementary_good … that require Big Data tech to be produced thus spurring cooperation?    
    
    
    algorithm to discover simultaneous discoveries (e.g. Bell and Gray with telephone) http://afinetheorem.wordpress.com/2013/11/07/is-knowledge-trapped-inside-the-ivory-tower-m-bikard-2013/ … consequences for innovation    
    
    
    GooFit: A library for massively parallelising maximum-likelihood fits. (arXiv:1311.1753v1 [cs.DC]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.1753     
    
    
    The concept of a person is arguably the most important interface ever developed. And other UX musings by @KevinSimler http://www.ribbonfarm.com/2013/11/07/ux-and-the-civilizing-process/ …    
    
    
    .@MissAJBurton @yoditstanton program or be programmed http://www.rushkoff.com/program-or-be-programmed/ …    
    
    
    .@moritz_stefaner I'd also like to see how Bechdel test results correlate with measures of social/economic well being    
    
    
    is "Huh?" a Universal Word? http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0078273 …    
    
    
    .@yoditstanton experience has trained me to strongly associate the word 'synergy' to the lack of an underlying substantive thought    
    
    
    http://amzn.com/k/quyUZGozRLqIUPJZZybwLg … If you think, “I breathe,” the “I” is extra.    
    
    
    I want to say one word to you. Just one word. Plumbing. http://www.overcomingbias.com/2013/11/the-bright-future-of-pipes.html …    
    
    
    Europeans interested in presenting at http://solidcon.com/solid2014  {soft¦hard}ware convergence, #iot please get in touch with @yoditstanton    
    
    
    Political colour is half genetic http://sciencenordic.com/political-colour-half-genetic … which implies that fertility rates matter /cc @aleksj    
    
    
    Achieving food waste efficiencies through innovation and global cooperation http://ec.europa.eu/research/infocentre/article_en.cfm?id=/research/headlines/news/article_13_11_11_en.html&amp;item=Infocentre&amp;artid=31336 …    
    
    
    @aleksj amen to that    
    
    
    Cupio dissolvere    
    
    
    Oh great! Now philosophical intuitions too have a genetic component...  http://philosophycommons.typepad.com/xphi/2013/11/predicting-disagreement-strange-fictions-in-x-phi.html …    
    
    
    Querying Knowledge Graphs by Example Entity Tuples. (arXiv:1311.2100v1 [cs.DB]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.2100     
    
    
    Redlink Brings The Semantic Web To Integrators http://semanticweb.com/redlink-brings-semantic-web-integrators/ … a spinoff of @iks_project    
    
    
    $100M investment fund for data and analytics companies http://techcitynews.com/2013/11/11/kpmg-launches-investment-fund/ … via @eileentso    
    
    
    "The chinese room problem asks if computers can think; I ask here if most humans can."
 (arXiv:1311.2912v1 [cs.AI]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.2912     
    
    
    http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/nov/12/occupy-wall-street-activists-15m-personal-debt … good idea but utilitarian minds might wonder what $400K could have accomplished elsewhere e.g. http://www.givedirectly.org     
    
    
    who is, in Europe, the person to talk to about the medium/long term economics of data centers? http://www.datacenterknowledge.com/archives/2013/11/12/microsoft-will-use-fuel-cells-create-self-powered-racks/ …    
    
    
    just done negotiating my last FP7 project. moving on to H2020. Then the next programme and the one after that. Then I retire    
    
    
    http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/11/weird-nanophotonic-materials/?viewall=true … the non-pharmacological road to the Doors of Perception http://www.amazon.com/Aldous-Huxley-Doors-Perception-Heaven/dp/B004R5VG5W/ …    
    
    
    study on business models for linked open government data https://joinup.ec.europa.eu/community/semic/document/study-business-models-linked-open-government-data-bm4logd …    
    
    
    Daughter just got admission letter from http://psyc.info.yorku.ca     
    
    
    Sorry, wrong York. Daughter got accepted at http://www.york.ac.uk/psychology/  not Canadian one    
    
    
    @AnneJHunt she's also been admitted to Glasgow and Reading psychology. We are waiting to hear from Oxford. Fingers crossed...    
    
    
    Recent Advances in Graph Partitioning. (arXiv:1311.3144v1 [cs.DS]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.3144     
    
    
    Fingerprinting Codes and the Price of Approximate Differential Privacy. (arXiv:1311.3158v1 [cs.CR]) http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.3158     
    
    
    sympathy for the unlucky dissolves under cognitive load http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0079091 … political implications left as an exercise for the reader    
    
    
    .@simon fantastic stunt. I admire the person who knows how to do their job (communicate an important idea in unforgettable terms)    
    
    
    Copernicus: free access to EU satellite data http://europa.eu/rapid/press-release_IP-13-1067_en.htm …    
    
    
    Happiness and voting: newly widowed women are 10% less likely to be pro-incumbent http://www.VoxEU.org/index.php?q=node/9972 …    
    
    
    privacy in statistical databases http://unescoprivacychair.urv.cat/psd2014/     
    
    
    my children's lack of interest in getting driving licence adds to the demand side that would lead to more efficient/shared self-driving cars    
    
    
        
    
    
    watching Casanova http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0074291/ … again after 30y his difficulties in connecting to European courts resonate more than his escapades    
    
    
    is anyone in Europe looking at http://openxcplatform.com  API or similar to work with telemetry data from cars? see http://blog.programmableweb.com/2013/11/15/splunk-uses-openxc-api-to-analyze-ford-telemetry-data/ …    
    
    
    I see the recent Splunk/Ford announcement http://blog.programmableweb.com/2013/11/15/splunk-uses-openxc-api-to-analyze-ford-telemetry-data/ … as the best example I know of http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Product_Space … idea in the data space    
    
    
    .@Kiva is it realistic to budget $1775 to buy three piglets in Bali http://www.kiva.org/lend/631377  ?    
    
    
    I find http://goodjudgmentproject.com  prediction market highly illiquid of lately    
    
    
    Interesting how my 17y old daughter immediately filled the power vacuum left by my wife, away for the week. 13y old son & me cower in fear    
    
    
    Big Data Benchmarks, Performance Optimization, and Emerging Hardware in Las Vegas, March 2014 http://prof.ict.ac.cn/bpoe_4_asplos/     
    
    
    oh! a Big Data benchmark suite http://prof.ict.ac.cn/BigDataBench/  comments anyone?    
    
    
    ... aaand another Big Data benchmarking workshop http://clds.sdsc.edu/wbdb2013.us/program … does anyone know of any European work in this domain?    
    
    
    .@peterabcz @RobVesse thanks for pointer http://ldbc.eu  which I know well. do you know any *other* EU work on Big Data benchmarks?    
    
    
    .@eurohumph it reacts thus http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dunbar%27s_number …    
    
    
    I often fantasize about this in my line of work http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/11/jpal-randomized-trials/ …    
    
    
    .@andraz @lemire I like international R&D networking because it offers a route of escape for talented people stuck in low quality equilibria    
    
    
    more info http://2014.data-forum.eu/about/press-area … on @EUDataForum 19-20 March 2014 in Athens    
    
    
    100 acres and a drone https://www.mapbox.com/blog/drone-imagery-openstreetmap/ … more, better geospatial data from @openstreetmap    
    
    
    23% population growth in Luxembourg in 2012 http://epp.eurostat.ec.europa.eu/cache/ITY_PUBLIC/3-20112013-AP/EN/3-20112013-AP-EN.PDF … source @EU_Eurostat    
    
    
    Belgian Big Data community http://bigdata.be     
    
    
    @gthb indeed. What was I thinking? In my defense, buses around here really feel 23% more crowded...    
    
    
    sad to hear Refinder is shutting down https://www.getrefinder.com/about/blog/2013/11/09/we-are-shutting-refinder-down … wish all involved the very best for their next gig. hire them if you can    
    
    
    ah, to be young again! @Europarl_EN votes to expand Erasmus program beyond students http://www.euractiv.com/education/erasmus-wants-reach-university-s-news-531841 …    
    
    
    using Bitcoin as the basis for new protocols http://www.newscientist.com/article/dn24620-bitcoin-moves-beyond-mere-money.html#.Uo3FbndXt8E … see http://coloredcoins.org  from Cyprus    
    
    
    funny. just looked up on LinkedIn someone who lists as languages German, English, French and Java    
    
    
        
    
    
    Stone Throwing as a Sexual Display in Wild Female Bearded Capuchin Monkeys, Sapajus libidinosus http://feedly.com/e/fa-CZaq7     
    
    
    Bohrium: Unmodified NumPy Code on CPU, GPU, and Cluster http://feedly.com/e/2PZdx7un     
    
    
    automobile data systems will yield approximately $14.5 billion in revenue from automotive data assets by 2020 http://www.datanami.com/datanami/2013-11-21/report:_big_data_will_represent_billions_in_automotive.html …    
    
    
    too tired to exercise this morning. making crepes for my children instead.    
    
    
    hard to swallow thoughts: somebody who is today my son's age (13) will one day entertain the ambition to become Pope    
    
    
    why do we work so hard to teach children to write in cursive, which is difficult for them to learn and for computers to interpret?    
    
    
    .@Comunardo how do you write "Path Dependence" http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Path_dependence … in cursive? ;)    
    
    
    interface to CUDA in Wolfram language http://reference.wolfram.com/language/CUDALink/ref/CUDAFunctionLoad.html …    
    
    
    just looked up someone on LinkedIn: been working in California for 5y and only listing German as language. This is @NeinQuarterly material    
    
    
    Microsoft Azure sneakernet http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sneakernet  http://www.toolsjournal.com/cloud-articles/item/2450-microsoft-azure-will-allow-developers-to-ship-hard-drives-to-export/import-data … via @BigDataDiary    
    
    
    topics about Stalin visualized in R, d3 http://quantifyingmemory.blogspot.co.uk/2013/11/d3-without-javascript.html … by @RolfFredheim . I am surprised @evgenymorozov is not all over this already    
    
    
    I see that things are already gearing up for @bigdataweek 5-11 May 2014 http://bigdataweek.com/     
    
    
    does utilitarianism *require* 'repugnant' http://plato.stanford.edu/entries/repugnant-conclusion/ … simulations http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Simulation_hypothesis … with centillions of (just) happy people?    
    
    
    in other words, is the chance that we live in a simulation dependent on moral principles?    
    
    
    my wife's being away for business for the past week gave me quite a bit of emotional Ma http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ma_(negative_space) … to enjoy with my children    
    
    
    as, I discovered, there is such a things as Horror Vacui http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Horror_vacui … in maternal love    
    
    
    just signed up for the Liquid Feedback platform of @Fare2013 http://www.fermareildeclino.it/liquidfeedback     
    
    
    Seeing a Hat http://feedly.com/e/gJHMoShV  I understand Zen as the deliberate focus on sensory experience over pre-conceived knowledge of objects    
    
    
    ...and in goes the third load of laundry. like a boss.    
    
    
    Circuit Scribe, a rollerball pen that writes with conductive silver ink http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/electroninks/circuit-scribe-draw-circuits-instantly …    
    
    
    Fast approximate k-nearest neighbours search using GPGPU http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/hgpuorg/~3/9ReyVQTF30c/ …    
    
    
    .@qanderson7 @LRouesnel what trend would that be?    
    
    
    Scalable Data Cube Analysis over Big Data. (arXiv:1311.5663v1 [cs.DB]) http://feedly.com/e/m2P3gnND     
    
    
    .@qanderson7 @LRouesnel in which domain(s), if I may ask?    
    
    
    @qanderson7 @LRouesnel oh. thanks and good luck to you.    
    
    
    there's a lot of fish in the sea. http://groups.inf.ed.ac.uk/f4k/  has automatically extracted from video and categorized 1B+ fish observations    
    
    
    The Distributed Complexity of Large-scale Graph Processing. (arXiv:1311.6209v1 [cs.DC]) http://feedly.com/e/k7VZ1Iw9     
    
    
    the last still missing arch of the new Pont Adolphe under construction is like the leading-tone http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leading-tone … of my morning commute    
    
    
    French website to collect all scientific data on CO2 emissions http://feedly.com/e/PnHBIlL8     
    
    
    Gov Open Data in the EU: Still Lacking Commercial Opportunity? http://feedly.com/e/S-qxsijV  featuring @EC_opendata 's @BeyerMalte    
    
    
    plumbing http://www.overcomingbias.com/2013/11/the-bright-future-of-pipes.html … https://bitcointalk.org/index.php?topic=346134.msg3709913#msg3709913 …    
    
    
    The card game UNO is NP-complete. (arXiv:1003.2851v2 [cs.DM]) http://feedly.com/e/LpEfuj7y     
    
    
    to break tension at my cremation, I'd like a funeral march exclusively made of annoying ringtones and structured like Ravel's Bolero    
    
    
        
    
    
    real time sensor based tide peak http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Acqua_alta  alerts in Venice #opendata http://www.acqualta.org     
    
    
    Pricing Private Data http://www.cs.nyu.edu/~gkatz/PricingPrivateData.pdf … via @BeyerMalte    
    
    
    those who like previous tweet on Pricing Private Data should also look at http://cloud-data-pricing.cs.washington.edu/     
    
    
    My daughter just showed me the entry in the dictionary where a parent is defined as a convenient means of transportation    
    
    
    On @tech_eu: Action speaks louder than words: time for more European countries to facilitate entrepreneur visas  http://on.tech.eu/1brWXIQ     
    
    
    Productivity in Italy: The great unlearning | vox http://www.voxeu.org/article/productivity-italy-great-unlearning#.UpsjpTdpDlY.twitter …    
    
    
    @ashishsingru back in the USA?    
    
    
    "Anyone But Richard M Stallman" open source licence https://github.com/landondyer/kasm/blob/master/LICENSE …    
    
    
    http://www.amazon.com/b?ie=UTF8&node=8037720011 … if Amazon does this, what type of data can its drones collect in the process and what is to worth to whom?    
    
    
    Daughter just passed http://www.abrsm.org  piano 8 with distinction    
    
    
    Cache policies for cloud-based systems: To keep or not to keep. (arXiv:1312.0499v1 [cs.NI]) http://feedly.com/e/-5S9Ho55     
    
    
    @tanyalewis314 could you please post details of original published study (journal, issue, page, url) for your piece http://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=how-mens-brains-are-wired-differently-than-women … ?    
    
    
    just learned about travelling salesman algorithm app http://www.portatour.com  it seems both simple and useful    
    
    
    .@fbancilhon enormously envious of the range of non-Hollywood movies you get to see & appreciative of the love you show for this form of art    
    
    
    @trifacta @pgroth @RIAnalytics so: what's the best way to get people to keep a clean data shop? standards without tears + good converters?    
    
    
    .@PrivacyMemes this seems a special case of the more general issue https://twitter.com/sclopit/status/407535003304599552 …    
    
    
    @ScienceNordic could you please provide a link to the actual paper http://sciencenordic.com/secure-computation-confidential-data … or at least full title + journal ? thanks    
    
    
    data privacy and multi-party computation http://sciencenordic.com/secure-computation-confidential-data … Danish spinoffs http://www.partisia.dk  and @SepiorCorp    
    
    
    @aleksj a completely rational move, if you follow this logic http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2013/12/amazon-drones-and-pre-lobbying.html …    
    
    
    August 2014, workshop on controlled natural languages in Galway, Ireland http://attempto.ifi.uzh.ch/site/cnl2014/     
    
    
    @tanyalewis314 thanks. I suggest you do anyway because journal articles are easier to file, say, on Mendeley, even if just as abstracts    
    
    
    @davidbgk I actually find parenting as one of the few things that are simultaneously very very hard and such that most people succeed at it    
    
    
    @ScienceNordic great, thanks    
    
    
    nightmares surfacing anxieties related to a previous profession are a welcome break from those based on the current profession    
    
    
    just made a donation to randomized-control-trial charity http://www.givedirectly.org  for next few weeks http://www.goodventures.org/research-and-ideas/blog/our-giving-season-plans … will match yours    
    
    
    Big Privacy: Bridging Big Data and the Personal Data Ecosystem Through Privacy by Design http://www.privacybydesign.ca/index.php/paper/big-privacy/ … by @embedprivacy    
    
    
    @tommyh I'll pass it on...    
    
    
    Protestant Work Ethic http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Protestant_work_ethic … localised in brain? https://www.simonsfoundation.org/quanta/20131205-inside-a-brain-circuit-the-will-to-press-on/ … where can I pre-order the implant?    
    
    
    @piellemme for the anecdotal record, both of my children show zero interest in the idea of learning how to drive    
    
    
    will be in London on Mon-Tue 16-17 December. Anyone/thing I should see/do?    
    
    
        
    
    
    ok then. with apologies to @tommyh , would 10:30-11:00 on Tues 17 at @UKODI work for @Nigel_Shadbolt @fhr @JeniT  ?    
    
    
    .@telecomitalia makes available anonymized datasets for #bigdata challenge. Applications by 14 January http://www.telecomitalia.com/tit/en/bigdatachallenge/contest/dataset.html …    
    
    
    @kristianak are you by any chance on https://www.goodjudgmentproject.com  ? would be interested in sharing thoughts    
    
    
    http://probcomp.csail.mit.edu/bayesdb/   technically brilliant. Privacy implications left as an exercise for the reader.    
    
    
    @kristianak exactly the thought I wanted to share. I am quite annoyed/disappointed by how illiquid the market is    
    
    
    reducing waste first piece in food resource puzzle http://www.euractiv.com/specialreport-sustainable-health/eu-tackle-waste-sustainable-food-news-532184?utm_source=RSS_Feed&utm_medium=RSS&utm_campaign=EurActivRSS …    
    
    
    A Distributed Data Mining Framework Accelerated with Graphics Processing Units http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/hgpuorg/~3/DhsOjWtEFeE/ …    
    
    
    Parallel tree-ensemble algorithms for GPUs using CUDA http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/hgpuorg/~3/J3IT0kF9iyw/ …    
    
    
    A Fully Automated High-Throughput Training System for Rodents. Like it when science is automated. http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/plosone/PLoSONE/~3/UWpiU-qgi2s/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0083171 …    
    
    
    doing http://hello.processing.org  with 13y son. when we got to mouseX/mouseY he had sudden flash of understanding, his first visible aha! moment    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mhausenblas who knows what comparably amazing goodness you know about that I don't (yet)... much to learn there in terms of dissemination    
    
    
    economists failing to eat own dogfood http://www.voxeu.org/article/our-uneconomic-methods-measuring-economic-research …    
    
    
    .@shiffman will do. current level of ambition is to build together a one-sided version of Pong next week-end    
    
    
    @ahzf amen to that.    
    
    
    Big Data, new tricks for econometrics  http://people.ischool.berkeley.edu/~hal/Papers/2013/ml.pdf#%21 …    
    
    
    .@vmansinghka indeed. here's another paper from your next door neighbours at MIT http://www.nature.com/srep/2013/130325/srep01376/full/srep01376.html …    
    
    
    @ahzf hopefully in publications, open source software repositories, commercial products.    
    
    
    .@scicasters prediction market now online, scores of very interesting questions in science/technology. see you there.    
    
    
    example @scicasters prediction question relevant for @LDBCproject : by June 2014 will same machine rank #1 in both Top500 and Graph500?    
    
    
    .@scicasters yes. but I have no expert knowledge on the subject, so I'll refrain from making predictions.    
    
    
    Who else phenomenologically experiences missing a bus as a moral failure?    
    
    
    RAM-Efficient External Memory Sorting. (arXiv:1312.2018v1 [cs.DS]) http://feedly.com/e/38zMfuw-     
    
    
    I just learned the German word "Spielverderber" which I think could be translated as "Nein". /cc @NeinQuarterly    
    
    
    Data Protection Principles for the 21st Century http://www.oii.ox.ac.uk/publications/Data_Protection_Principles_for_the_21st_Century.pdf …    
    
    
    Learning Random Forests on the GPU http://feedly.com/e/v3oDEGEe     
    
    
    http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-25198154 … me, I haven't found a French author I like past Camus. Suggestions? (with short explanation why I'll like them)    
    
    
    thanks to the Romans, French towns were stuck in the wrong places for many centuries http://www.voxeu.org/article/are-towns-stuck-wrong-places …    
    
    
    your data, sold in less than 100ms for less than $0.0005 http://www.inrialpes.fr/planete/people/lukasz/rtbdesc.html …    
    
    
    outstanding essay by Zadie Smith http://www.nybooks.com/articles/archives/2013/dec/05/zadie-smith-man-vs-corpse … on visual/literate aesthetic of you-are-going-to-die-but-me-I-am-not-so-sure    
    
    
    I'll be in London on Monday 16, afternoon wide open. Would love to meet/visit data startups. Any takers? Anyone who can make intros for me?    
    
    
    The Oxford Comma is your friend http://feedly.com/e/gu2MTwLW     
    
    
    @alisonmarigold yes, on Tuesday :)    
    
    
    phylogeny recapitulates ontology http://semanticweb.com/w3cs-semantic-web-activity-folds-new-data-activity/ …    
    
    
    .@NeelieKroesEU data technologies designed to respect privacy, without the law becoming a strait-jacket to innovation http://europa.eu/rapid/press-release_SPEECH-13-1059_en.htm …    
    
    
    so @jesolem has been busy... http://arcticstartup.com/2013/12/11/jan-erik-solem-launches-mapilary-putting-images-on-the-map … congrats!    
    
    
    .@PaulMiller thanks. can you make personal intros to @importio @Acunu or anyone on https://delicious.com/stefano.bertolo/london,startup,data … ?    
    
    
    just learned about LexisNexis' Apache-licenced Big Data platform http://hpccsystems.com     
    
    
    Swiss Set Sights on Becoming World's Data Vault http://www.securityweek.com/swiss-set-sights-becoming-worlds-data-vault …    
    
    
    New Baltic Data Cable Plan Unfolding http://feedly.com/k/1fmiwtq     
    
    
    as size of org grows, chances of encountering two people A and B who say they are "responsible for X" but don't know each other approach 1    
    
    
    @ABI_Cloud interested in data assets produced by IoT. Please share what you can. Thanks    
    
    
    Forgiver Triumphs in Alternating Prisoner's Dilemma http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/plosone/PLoSONE/~3/QLzPMP-RKLY/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0080814 …    
    
    
    Munich Open Source Switch 'Completed Successfully' http://rss.slashdot.org/~r/Slashdot/slashdot/~3/i5UcBwrQlec/story01.htm …    
    
    
    .@allisonschrager shows how 2 rights (reasonable incentive systems: TA's and student's) make a wrong: grade inflation http://qz.com/157579/confession-of-an-ivy-league-teaching-assistant-heres-why-i-inflated-grades/ …    
    
    
    idea for a novel: write a long story from which it is impossible to infer any of the characters' levels of income or social ranks    
    
    
    @umbrquil thanks!    
    
    
    Pre-Peano space filling curve on 18th Century snuff box at Wallace Collection London pic.twitter.com/f1BMPBq87B    
    
    
    @mikko "big brother big" is Chinese for mobile phone. Big brother only means oldest male sibling    
    
    
    I am the Parthenon Galleries, British Museum. A guard walks up to me and says "frieze!"    
    
    
    Extremely useful conversation with @ds_ldn learned lots about which type of companies are ready to data mine and London community of miners    
    
    
    @umbrquil great. I'll keep an eye on that    
    
    
    @janl Urklang?    
    
    
    Just received my @NeoLucida will experiment over Christmas pic.twitter.com/kJHV2Skcg2    
    
    
    very confused by @NeoLucida when prism is right-handed mounted as per diagram, subject is upside down & can't see paper/pencil    
    
    
    When I reverse orientation of @NeoLucida prism, subject is upright, I can see pencil but to draw line top to bottom must draw *away* from me    
    
    
    photo set by @quasimondo reusing artwork from the British Library Collection http://www.flickr.com/photos/quasimondo/sets/72157638820730895 …    
    
    
    interesting example of how regulation could co-evolve with (Big) Data technologies http://www.forbes.com/sites/leoking/2013/12/20/volcker-compliance-the-ultimate-big-data-challenge-has-begun … via @kdnuggets /cc @eurohumph    
    
    
    also via @kdnuggets another example (Massachusetts Open Cloud to spur Big Data R&D) worth studying http://gcn.com/articles/2013/12/16/massachusetts-open-cloud.aspx … /cc @eurohumph    
    
    
    unexpected paper of the day: the effects of using Prezi to teach about polygamy in Islam http://feedly.com/e/C-vwQTwj     
    
    
    Oblivious Query Processing http://feedly.com/e/KEOg_Tcr  building block of privacy by designed proved hard    
    
    
    @NeoLucida finally got it, thanks. giveaway was "ghost image of the subject". I recommend you stress this in your instructions. Thanks again    
    
    
        
    
    
    breakfast: would it be so wrong to tuck into the overnight leftovers of a delicious cheese fondue?    
    
    
    Efficient implementation of fully homomorphic encryption, US Patent #8,565,435, to IBM http://patft.uspto.gov/netacgi/nph-Parser?Sect1=PTO1&Sect2=HITOFF&d=PALL&p=1&u=%2Fnetahtml%2FPTO%2Fsrchnum.htm&r=1&f=G&l=50&s1=8,565,435.PN.&OS=PN/8,565,435&RS=PN/8,565,435 …    
    
    
    one for @egabbert on the effability of odours http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/24355816  via @vaughanbell    
    
    
    “That’s easy — meat eating.” http://www.rationaloptimist.com/blog/the-civilising-process.aspx … next bad habit to drop in Civilising Process. why not make it a New Year's resolution?    
    
    
    The Cardboard Box Just Got Way Better (Seriously) http://on.digg.com/1jBJ8fl     
    
    
    Are Graduate Students Rational? Evidence from the Market for Biomedical Scientists http://feedly.com/e/owF9siKI  via @feedly    
    
    
    last week @andrewfogg gave me demo of @importio APIfication http://semanticweb.com/import-io-turns-website-api-free_b41013 … capabilities targeting http://open-data.europa.eu  cool stuff    
    
    
    .@EUTenders could a more targeted #food supply related URL have been more effective?    
    
    
    .@EUTenders an example query URL  a la "/?q=food" would be more more direct for the audience your are trying to reach. is that not possible?    
    
    
    .@EUTenders taking someone to the room and shelf of the books they want is more effective than dropping them at the doors of a huge library    
    
    
    .@EUTenders great. love your work. you deserve to be known and succeed with the broadest possible EU public. just a nudge in that direction    
    
    
        
    
    
    when my wife writes a groceries list for me she also marks a few items that she definitely *doesn't* want me to buy    
    
    
    I would imagine this http://www.stanford.edu/class/msande239/ … would be a good place to start to learn about the economics (e.g. pricing) of personal data    
    
    
    this http://www.nytimes.com/2013/12/26/science/in-the-human-brain-size-really-isnt-everything.html … would also seem an interesting model to make organisations smarter    
    
    
    Aristotelian physics is correct approximation of Newtonian physics in appropriate domain as Newton's is of Einstein's http://philsci-archive.pitt.edu/10144/     
    
    
    wife and I going to Maastricht to celebrate 20th anniversary of our Union. negotiations had started in 1991. State of the Union is strong    
    
    
        
    
    
    promised @michaelerard next time he's in Europe I'll take him to http://www.polare.nl/onze-winkels/maastricht/ … Maastricht pic.twitter.com/pCPGZmNvpN    
    
    
    At http://www.bonnefanten.nl/en/  pic.twitter.com/DG7wp3VSPv    
    
    
    Next to Adrian Ghenie at http://www.bonnefanten.nl/en/  I feel like Bergotte in front of Vermeer pic.twitter.com/YCZlrwwrYR    
    
    
    Were it so simple... David Noor at http://www.bonnefanten.nl/en/  pic.twitter.com/qMrM7iOZLT    
    
    
    Sol LeWitt at http://www.bonnefanten.nl/en/  pic.twitter.com/jGnSBitwli    
    
    
    Augur: a Modeling Language for Data-Parallel Probabilistic Inference http://feedly.com/e/-kPuT3AQ     
    
    
    Efficient Large-Scale Graph Processing on Hybrid CPU and GPU Systems http://feedly.com/e/c9QBvNMO     
    
    
        
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #9 http://www.amazon.com/Neurogastronomy-Brain-Creates-Flavor-Matters-ebook/dp/B006BAJBUS … because there is a lot of non-trivial structure in perception    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #8 http://www.amazon.com/Good-Strategy-Bad-difference-matters-ebook/dp/B005331U7Q … because I know too many people who refuse to think about this    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #7 http://www.amazon.com/Ego-Tunnel-Science-Mind-Myth-ebook/dp/B0097DHVGW … because it explains why we are not zombies    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #6 http://www.amazon.com/Debt-First-5-000-Years-ebook/dp/B00513DGIO/ … because it made me see the depth of my ignorance    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #5 http://www.amazon.com/Hierarchy-Forest-Evolution-Egalitarian-Behavior-ebook/dp/B002OEBNQU … because political phylogeny illuminates political ontogeny    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #4 http://www.amazon.com/Seeing-Like-State-Condition-Institution-ebook/dp/B00D8JJYWA …  because ruling carries the responsibility to be informed    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #3 http://www.amazon.com/Myth-Rational-Voter-Democracies-Policies-ebook/dp/B007AIXLDI/ … because choosing carries the responsibility to be informed    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #2 http://www.amazon.com/Denationalisation-Money-Argument-Refined-LvMI-ebook/dp/B005DTKORM/ … because competition creates choice    
    
    
    best 10 books I have read this year: #1 http://www.amazon.com/Why-Law-Perverse-Leo-Katz-ebook/dp/B005J3TQEO/ … because reconciling preferences is much harder than you think    
    
    
    .@janl I don't have a personally managed web presence. would you accept this (can it be bookmarked) ? https://plus.google.com/u/0/109041783112047240352/posts/f7LsxXErV5a …    
    
    
        
    
    
    hyperdecanting http://feedly.com/e/2i6Rxgas  the process that removes pretentiousness from chemistry and physiology of taste    
    
    
    We want to know meat's origin – but not if it costs http://feedly.com/e/P8h8GqNy  file under http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Revealed_preference …    
    
    
    5 years ago EC was already funding work for personal data to be kept under user control using best privacy practices http://flic.kr/p/6bWH2J     
    
    
    .@gthb if u have time for only 1, read http://www.amazon.com/Why-Law-Perverse-Leo-Katz-ebook/dp/B005J3TQEO/ … a deep idea that explains a surprising range of everyday frustrating phenomena    
    
    
    .@janl this http://www.dime-project.eu  happened    
    
    
    Bounded Rationality and Voting Decisions over 160 Years: Voter Behavior and Increasing Complexity in Decision-Making http://feedly.com/e/0U9XDzcz     
    
    
    dogs prefer to excrete with body aligned on a North-South axis http://www.frontiersinzoology.com/content/10/1/80/abstract …    
    
    
    Big Data visualisation I made for my 15 Jan presentation http://ec.europa.eu/digital-agenda/en/news/information-and-networking-days-h2020-work-programme-2014-2015-connecting-europe-facility … feel free to reuse http://flic.kr/p/iQVE1q     
    
    
    point of http://flic.kr/p/iQVE1q  is that increases in data volumes force non-linear changes in data management/analytics processes    
    
    
    Elastic Pathing: Your Speed is Enough to Track You. (arXiv:1401.0052v1 [cs.CR]) http://feedly.com/e/RA-JaFbP     
    
    
    Europe's Societal Challenges: An analysis of global societal trends to 2030 and their impact on the EU | RAND: http://www.rand.org/pubs/research_reports/RR479.html#.UsabSqZH5zc.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    MysmartFarm looks a bit like @farmeron bringing data analytics to farming http://www.bigdata-startups.com/BigData-startup/mysmartfarm/ …    
    
    
    very important article (in Italian) on the difference between innovation and self promotion http://www.chefuturo.it/2014/01/fuggetta-ce-un-abisso-fra-fare-vera-innovazione-e-parlarne/ …    
    
    
    it would be so nice if more of the conversations I have on big data took account of all levels of the stack as in http://highscalability.com/blog/2014/1/3/stuff-the-internet-says-on-scalability-for-january-3rd-2014.html …    
    
    
    .@piellemme one wonders if investment companies have similarly specific investment products built from specialised ontologies...    
    
    
    .@mla_lma I was just teasing @piellemme based on our common professional past and his current job. happy to have learned something from you    
    
    
    I often meet people who would benefit from reading http://blog.nullspace.io/building-search-engines.html … reality is that thing that doesn't go away if you don't believe it    
    
    
    .@mla_lma https://www.motifinvesting.com/motifs  sounds like an excellent way to cure oneself from delusional obsessions. a sort of empiricist's hair shirt    
    
    
    oh, look! the #bigdata investment motif! https://www.motifinvesting.com/motifs/big-data#/overview …    
    
    
    Olfaction and Quality Space Theory http://feedly.com/e/yDKSB_gL  /cc @egabbert    
    
    
    @piellemme just curious about the underlying ontology and its combinatorial structure    
    
    
    a thoughtful critique of effective altruism http://lesswrong.com/lw/j8n/a_critique_of_effective_altruism/ …    
    
    
    lots of interesting ideas in http://ntoll.org/article/ppdd  for decentralized sharing of data assets. interesting @fluidinfo conceptual ancestry    
    
    
    