« >_< It's not even 9:00 am and I'm already wasting my time outwitting morons» #Dammit #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «Works with Last.FM profiles,too» RT @hypem: Get artist recommendations for SXSW based on your Hype Machine profile: http://bit.ly/cmBSsb    
    
    
    «So while waiting for lunch I was doodling on a napkin and the waitress then told me I should start an art career» #Boink!    
    
    
    «Fatalysia #3 review at Indy Comic Review! Go lookie!» http://moourl.com/us0hh    
    
    
    «Task for today:write a piece about history of rocket science.Fun fact:I'll write most of it from memory (I'm such a nerd,I know,I know)»    
    
    
    «Only 44 more songs until I reach the 50,000 tracks played on Last.FM —wondering which will be the lucky tune...»    
    
    
    «11:11 pm,4,9987 tracks...»    
    
    
    «11:23pm,Happy Birthday You by Jay Jay Pistolet is track #4,9990...»    
    
    
    «Track #4,9995 ~ Phonobaloon song by Takako Minekawa»    
    
    
    «...and track #50,000 is...Fell In Love With a Girl by The White Stripes! —Okay now,that's all,goodnite everyone»    
    
    
    «Ain't it funny how artists more concerned about their copyrights are usually the least likely to be plagiarized by anyone?»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Katy Perry (2), Phil Collins (1) & Britney Spears (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    Frank Miller Ink: The official homepage of Frank Miller http://twurl.nl/px7r4r    
    
    
    « O_o So this client says he loves my lineart —and then asks me to emulate Dreamwork's CGI style» #WTF? #CreoQueMePaseUnReten    
    
    
    just loved The Rentals - Friends Of P. (Album Version) http://awe.sm/52Qdf on @hypem    
    
    
    «Ask me anything,whatever (beware:I have answers for everything)» http://www.formspring.me/everyueveryme  #formspringme    
    
    
    Harmony - Procedural drawing tool: Sketch online tool http://twurl.nl/uxkjja    
    
    
    Tiny Vices: Mary Karaplis (Mei K) is a freelance artist based in the cozy, cloudy city of Vancouver, B.C. http://tiny-vices.com/    
    
    
    Q:What is the wallpaper on your cellphone? A:I don't have a cellphone —we true action me... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/301123262    
    
    
    Watch Zombie Hunt! on Vimeo! http://vimeo.com/10155622    
    
    
    @Man_Tsun Yes,indeed! The zombie is Zabel —or Lord Raptor as he's known in America    
    
    
    «"Superman is Clark Kent". Signed: #Wikileaks  (←predictable bad joke but still ironic,uh?)»    
    
    
    «Whoah! No spam this morning on any of my e-mail inboxes! Wonder if I should buy a lottery ticket or something...»    
    
    
    «Can you keep a secret? I've been accepted in a models network (!) —boldly going where no starving artist has gone before!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «WIP —Horses!» http://brizzly.com/pic/1QIC    
    
    
    «Fell asleep reading old magazines,woke up in the living room with nasty foot cramps» #sleepwalking    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ We'll take our hearts outside...Leave our lives behind...I'll watch the stars go out ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    just loved Imperial Teen - Yoo Hoo http://awe.sm/52dEN on @hypem    
    
    
    «Seems like I urgently need an agent...and maybe a secretary...and a horse»    
    
    
    «Jésus Marie Joseph,libérez moi!!!»    
    
    
    just loved Dire Straits - Sultans of Swing http://awe.sm/52fYj on @hypem    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/19m4de - «The kid that drew this has a great future as an artist,you know...»    
    
    
    @thenoise_fm Why,thank you!    
    
    
    «1st day of Spring.And instead of doing something productive I ended up as translator & babysitter for some German gay tourists» #DontAsk    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Katy Perry (2), Phil Collins (1) & Britney Spears (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Ain't it cute when potential clients disappear right after you tell them your rates?» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «Between Follow Fridays,Tumblr Tuesdays & Fazebooq's suggestions,Can anybody please suggest me people to follow on Formspring & Flickr?»    
    
    
    just loved Zombina and the Skeletones - Nobody Likes You (When You're Dead) http://awe.sm/52nU9 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Arrive early,be the last to leave and kick ass all fucking day.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Pitbull (4), Lady Gaga (3) & TLC (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    http://brizzly.com/pic/1UJS  «Stuff I've been doing lately —actual panels but not actual sequence»    
    
    
    "What price do we put on a soul?" "$7.25 an hour" «No wonder I haven't been able to sell mine...»    
    
    
    Dear Coke Talk: Shady advice from a raging bitch who has no business answering any of these questions. http://twurl.nl/y467kv    
    
    
    Coke Talk: Staggering through Hollywood with an eager nose and a sharp tongue. http://twurl.nl/szb088    
    
    
    «Seems like I'm too old for listening Lady Gaga and too young for understanding Peter Gabriel...Or was it viceversa?»    
    
    
    just loved Asobi Seksu - Bossa http://awe.sm/5362n on @hypem    
    
    
    «Got an Easter egg as a gift.It's the first time I actually get one of these and now I don't know what I'm supposed to do with it.»    
    
    
    «I need a lot of things,but right now,I'd settle for a chocobar.» #AprilWish    
    
    
    «On Sundays even fresh coffee tastes like dirty sock tea» #ScrewSundays #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1cmmdl - «Something different in case you're bored of watching Jesuschrist Superstar as every year»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I hear a noise inside my brain it is controlling me...It is controlling me...It is controlling me ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Woke up on the kitchen floor.Fortunately without cramps» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «WIP —Dragonslaying!» http://brizzly.com/pic/1YP0    
    
    
    Wkly #lastfm artists: Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (131), Buffalo Daughter (104) & Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (27) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    « X_X Guess I caught something in my throat —I've been coughing more than a little kid working in a Victorian era factory...»    
    
    
    «Called the doctor about my throat & he said I should rest and take some medicine.As if my deadlines and my finances would allow all that»    
    
    
    «Seems like I'm high on cough syrup and my throat is still not very cooperative (been trying to learn to cough opera arias though)»    
    
    
    "I didn't jump to kill myself —I did it to fly" ←«Please take note,I demand this as my epitaph»    
    
    
    «The cogh seems to be under control now,but now my voice sounds like Marlon Brandon's on you-know-which-movie»    
    
    
    «Oh,and in the meantime,I've been featured on the Kirby-Vision blog —Go look!» http://tinyurl.com/yhq6pnl    
    
    
    just loved Suzanne Vega - Tom's Diner http://awe.sm/53PV8 on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Patrick Hernandez - Born To Be Alive http://awe.sm/53SGM on @hypem    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where & this time it's a classic:Dream A Little Dream» ~ http://moourl.com/9t4h1    
    
    
    «Watching Animaniacs reruns while checking your e-mails —Monday mornings are the best!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Doug Savage just explained my whole life in one single Post-It™ cartoon» ~ http://bit.ly/bqLmq5    
    
    
    ben newman art: naughty art, filthy fairytales and other perverted nonsense. http://twurl.nl/32cx6z    
    
    
    just loved SALEM - Frost http://awe.sm/5EB4o on @hypem    
    
    
    «Right now I should be researching about Mexico's bicentennial —and instead,I'm inking an elephant stampede» #FreedomOfChoiceIsBeautiful!    
    
    
    «The elephant stampede I mentioned? Okay,here it is (yup,it's just a panel from a new comic page)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/22OP    
    
    
    just loved The Mary Onettes - The night before the funeral http://awe.sm/53cVb on @hypem    
    
    
    «Happy Birth...er,Deathday Pedro Infante!» http://tweetphoto.com/18531096    
    
    
    «There's no pleasure in having nothing to do...the fun is in having lots to do and not doing it»    
    
    
    «WIP —Yup,that's a gunslinging lion...Do I need to mention how fun is to draw this kind of things?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3YMS    
    
    
    @nuisance Petunia Pig dyed her hair?    
    
    
    « ^_^ Upcoming —and yup,I'm included in this book» http://tweetphoto.com/18816194    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ If I had words to make a day for you...I'd sing you a morning,golden and new ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #1.-If you want your opponent to take you seriously,look into their eyes and make 'em feel pain...»    
    
    
    «...yet once again I ask to anyone who can answer:How are you supposed to fight an opponent that has no face to punch at?» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    RT myself in case you missed it « ^_^ Upcoming —and yup,I'm included in this book» http://bit.ly/ccomuk    
    
    
    just loved Tears for Fears - Everybody Wants to Rule the World http://awe.sm/54Kb6 on @hypem    
    
    
    @f_francavilla Dick Tracy! Or The Spirit! Or even better:Dick Tracy vs The Spirit! #PulpFestWeek    
    
    
    «Just turned the radio on & found out they are playing a Xmas carol!» #CoolRandomness #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #2.-Pain is your friend.Pain means you're not fucked up.»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I ain't dying to offend you,I got a dyslexic heart... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «This made my morning:someone just asked me in which side of Europe was Mexico located» #Hopes&Omens    
    
    
    «Trust me,no free lunch is worth having to listen an annoying "artist" trying to be weird just for the sake of weirdness» #KillAllPoseurs    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #3.-To make your opponents afraid of you,become a reflex of them and show them that you're not afraid of killing yourself»    
    
    
    «I really shouldn't be saying this because of the circumstances,but...boy,it's really damn exciting to ride in an ambulance!»    
    
    
    «WIP —Xiaolin gator!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3YSM    
    
    
    «Of all the funerals I've seen,the one that I attended today sure was the most beautiful of them all...»    
    
    
    «WIP —Friday cheesecake!»  http://brizzly.com/pic/2708    
    
    
    JIRAT JAMES PATRADOON: Jirat James Patradoon Fine Arts and Illistration http://twurl.nl/2oxq4l    
    
    
    «Good Monday morning! Made a guest strip for Dumm Comics with blood,bondage and elephants —Go lookie!» ~ http://moourl.com/up34n    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #4.-Don't go quietly unto your grave»    
    
    
    «Seems like I pulled a muscle or something while practicing the Singing In The Rain coreography» #Ouchie    
    
    
    just loved Eagle Seagull - You're the Reason Why I'm Afraid to Die http://awe.sm/55QKy on @hypem    
    
    
    «I really should be working but...somebody is playing a violin version of Ode To Joy at the music school around the corner»    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #5.-Never play an ace if a two will do»    
    
    
    «One of these days I'll be a celebrity famous enough to have human shields instead of fans»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ But all the promises we make...From the cradle to the grave...When all I want is you ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Adele (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Someone really should use this Craiglist post as the plot for a movie or something...» http://moourl.com/9ssqt    
    
    
    «The measure of success is getting paid for writing a piece about Ed Wood,Andy Warhol and John Waters»    
    
    
    Super Mario Crossover - Free Arcade Game Played Online: You can choose any other classic Nintendo character to p... http://twurl.nl/8kketa    
    
    
    I connected my #iCheckMovies account to Twitter! http://bit.ly/9i5ssF    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I'm looking over a four leaf clover...That I overlooked before... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «WIP —Based upon a book,Can you guess which?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2AHV    
    
    
    «A girlfriend of mine had a fetish for kicking guys in the groin.Needless to say she is NOT my girlfriend anymore»    
    
    
    «So creepy it's funny,and so funny it's disturbing» #NSFW http://twitpic.com/1knwok    
    
    
    THE JOHNNY CASH PROJECT: A unique crowd-sourced music video project honoring the legacy of Johnny Cash —user-sub... http://twurl.nl/xboaao    
    
    
    Check out this drawing for THE JOHNNY CASH PROJECT, a community-created video for Johnny Cash’s"Ain't No Grave." http://is.gd/bUv2Z    
    
    
    «yeah,yeah...Happy Mexican St. Patrick's Day and all that stuff (and happy no-birthday to me)»    
    
    
    just loved School Of Seven Bells - Babelonia http://awe.sm/55po9 on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Delays - Find A Home http://awe.sm/55poX on @hypem    
    
    
    «Some days not even your imaginary friends want to talk with you»    
    
    
    «Battle of the zombies & strippers trailers —choose your fav!» ~ http://moourl.com/fq7o6    
    
    
    «Wondering how to fight against the system —Should I cancel my Fazebooq account or keep it and sabotage the network from inside?»    
    
    
    «WIP —Just because drawing pervertions is always a fun challenge» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2CUU    
    
    
    «Woke up in the kitchen floor.Fortunately,no cramps this time» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «I've just unclogged a toilet with no plunger —with my bare hands only.Try to top that»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Wonder if he'll ever know...He's in the best selling show...Is there life on Mars? ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Because in the name of honesty someone has to say it today (in Mexico at least)» → #ChingadaMadre    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ In your eyes I see the eyes of somebody who could be strong...Tell me if I'm wrong ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    just loved Sky Ferreira - Animal (Miike Snow cover) http://awe.sm/5624V on @hypem    
    
    
    «...and just when you think you've licked all your wounds,an ex-girlfriend reappears —somebody push me onto the subway tracks,please!!!»    
    
    
    «One of these days I'll be a celebrity famous enough to have fun making my fans fight against my haters —in a gladiator arena,of course»    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where.If you download only 1 song this week,it must be this one» ~ http://moourl.com/cxi9o    
    
    
    «Went to a job interview and all that I achieved was beating my record playing Space Invaders»    
    
    
    «WIP —Apocalyptic epidemy! (based upon a Jack London novel,Can you guess the title?)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2FKW    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Cool! (Uh...For what? And when do I start?)    
    
    
    «Now,this irony totally made my morning» http://tweetphoto.com/22372656    
    
    
    «And so today begins the Guadalupe-Reyes celebration marathon...» http://plixi.com/p/62556793    
    
    
    «\m/ It's raining!!!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Sometimes I wish it were 1964,just for one day.That way I could go watch an @El_Santo movie and no cell phones would be ringing»    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Britney Spears (4) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Dinner sketch!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3ZD4    
    
    
    «WIP —I think I'll call this kaiju Elmer Ceronterrino...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2H0R    
    
    
    just loved Jack Mercer - I'm Popeye the Sailor Man http://awe.sm/56HSF on @hypem    
    
    
    Fun Latin: Some phrases from Latin for all Occasions, by Henry Beard. http://twurl.nl/hmw6gq    
    
    
    «Sometimes when I stop & think how many Mexicans genuinely enjoy stuff like Chespirito & Michael Moore,it scares the living shit out of me»    
    
    
    «Good News:I found a needle that I lost the other day - Bad News:I found it with my pinky toe.» #ThePain    
    
    
    «Sometimes I hate to know things and not being able to share them because I must let people learn by themselves» #GuardianAngelSyndrome    
    
    
    «Useless fact for today» http://tweetphoto.com/23149295    
    
    
    «This time I didn't wake in another room.But in my sleep I managed to wrap myself in the sheets as in a straitjacket»    
    
    
    «WIP —Characters for a poster that will have the title of 'Join The Red Corps'» http://brizzly.com/pic/2IQ5    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Oingo Boingo (58), Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (32) & A Brokeheart Pro (32) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «New print for sale at my Zazzle shop:Join The Red Corps —go get yours!» ~ http://bit.ly/9vksGg    
    
    
    «If you really love me,you'd buy/steal/make me a piano like this one.But you don't.Goodnight» http://tweetphoto.com/23857644    
    
    
    «Is it your computer? Or Facebook's?»    
    
    
    «MySpace.-A fun place now that Phazebooq made it less crowded» #Definitions    
    
    
    «Facebook.-A place where everyone forwards their tweets to» #Definitions    
    
    
    «Dorothy Gambrell is a genius» ~ http://catandgirl.com/?p=2759    
    
    
    «In periods of drought even wild storms are preferable to yet another sunny day»    
    
    
    «Now I don't know if what I need is a muse,a housewife,vacations,an EuroMastercard,or a log cabin in the woods...»    
    
    
    just loved The Kingston Trio - Scotch and Soda http://awe.sm/56ZxC on @hypem    
    
    
    «If cereal is breakfast of champions,then Valentina® sauce is what maniacs use to fuel theselves in the morning (& I just did that!)»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I do it all because I'm evil...And I do it all for free —Your tears are all the pay I'll ever need! ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «There should be some zen paradox in the fact that I've been answering emails all this morning,but no one has answered my requests yet»    
    
    
    100 People I Hate on Facebook http://gizmodo.com/5713173/  via @gizmodo    
    
    
    «WIP —Vinyl records rule!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2KZZ    
    
    
    @coketweet That drink is unknown around here.On the other hand,brand names usually don't get translated because English is more commercial.    
    
    
    just loved David Bowie - Life On Mars http://awe.sm/56ear on @hypem    
    
    
    «Feeling a bit sick today —not sure if it's because of the flu I got or all those Gary Coleman videos everywhere on the web»    
    
    
    «If there's something I hate more than a Sunday morning,it's a Sunday morning with nose diarrhea» #SendAspirins    
    
    
    «WIP —A typical MySpace shot» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3ZQ8    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Maron (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «No matter how proud you are,always remember:with the right storytelling you'll always be the villain in someone else's movie» #HellYeah!    
    
    
    «Ask me anything,whatever (beware:I have answers for everything)» http://bit.ly/ahkHoz    
    
    
    Marcio Takara: Marcio Takara is a Brazilian artist, living in Toronto, Canada. He has been working with illust... http://twurl.nl/mltzuk    
    
    
    «Woke up with this tune stuck in my head...» http://chir.ps/5qH    
    
    
    «Hunt Rule #1.-There're a million ways to stalk your prey and there're a million ways to chase your prey.Pick one.»    
    
    
    «Happiness is expensive and you can't buy it anyway —that's why you have to steal it»    
    
    
    «Mark today as the day when I officially blocked over 100 persons on Phazebooq»    
    
    
    «Hunt Rule #2.-If your prey fights back in fair conditions it's not a hunt anymore —it's a life or death combat.»    
    
    
    @olganunes Usually,via random links at HypeMachine & Last.FM.Also spying on other peoples' profiles at social networks #whereifindnewmusic    
    
    
    «Some guy wrote offering me to translate my bilingual website into "proper Spanish" —seems he thought I was British!» #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    «Hunt Rule #3.-When hunger is unbearable,even lions eat carrion.»    
    
    
    «Just realized that MySpace became the same as Fazebooq:a glorified Twitter list» #Deja-Vu    
    
    
    «Related to previous tweet:it's weird that people use Tumblr to continue conversations started on Twitter» #Crossover    
    
    
    i will destroy you: Tom Neely's website http://twurl.nl/u16z40    
    
    
    «Hunt Rule #4.-Never hunt more than what you need.And never forget to leave some leftovers for scavengers and plants.»    
    
    
    «WIP —Paperless illo!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2O1O    
    
    
    Q:Can you explain the story behind your everyueveryme ni... A:Well,I needed something unique and with enough charact... http://4ms.me/bXS73V    
    
    
    «Hunt Rule #5.-Curiosities become quests;outings become overnighters;pastimes become passions —this is how a true hunt begins.»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Adele (11), Britney Spears (7) & Yuridia (5) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «The Matrix Exists!» ~ Largest supercomputers to simulate life on Earth, including economies and whole societies: http://bit.ly/bXl1cc    
    
    
    «Whoever said that the perfect crime was impossible? I've just committed a couple of them» #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    Just played CEO2. My company just decreased its CO2 emissions by 55%, while my stock increased by $34. Beat that! http://bit.ly/cSj7j4    
    
    
    «I've just found out that a robin made its nest on the tree right in front of my house» #Hopes&Omens    
    
    
    «WIP —if you ask me,this is how I currently feel with everybody around here talking about soccer only» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2PH7    
    
    
    Behold! Super Mario Bros. Cumbia! http://chir.ps/5yt    
    
    
    «Mojiwar!» ~ http://moourl.com/lbviv    
    
    
    «WIP —So far I have mixed feelings with this piece» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2QAG    
    
    
    « ✌ Peace ♥ Love & ☠ Oblivion »    
    
    
    «J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur! J'ai peur!»    
    
    
    just loved The Prodigy - Breathe http://awe.sm/57MC0 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Some Sunday mornings I really,really,really wish I were Irish:drunk and violent»    
    
    
    Ơ̴̴͡.̮Ơ̴͡    
    
    
    «WIP —Behold! El Naco Asesino splash page!» http://brizzly.com/pic/408Y    
    
    
    «And just after some relaxed weeks,this morning I woke up drooling over the rug on the living room» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «Worse than elevator music:elevator forced conversations with creepy people»    
    
    
    «Friendly Reminder:the 100% Carne art show is tomorrow nite!» ~ http://moourl.com/tcltg    
    
    
    (via  @trixietreats Tumblr) Depeche Mode | Route 66  [Beatmasters Mix] ~ http://moourl.com/d8bnt    
    
    
    «Dear Spammer Guys:Please,don't mess with my feelings like that.I may grow up traumatized or something» http://tweetphoto.com/27825019    
    
    
    @pulphope The real Alejandro Jodorowsky is this one: @alejodorowsky    
    
    
    «Death by hypothermia in a remote forest» #ThingsWorthTrying    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Ramomex (80), Oingo Boingo (58) & Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (44) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «It's official folks:among all my weirdness,I have prosopagnosia» How to tell if you have it: http://bit.ly/arALkk (via @olganunes )    
    
    
    « ◕‿◕ If you're reading this,congrats —you're alive.If that's not something to smile about,then I don't know what is.»    
    
    
    «Friendly Reminder»  http://bit.ly/dg0P7t    
    
    
    «GERONIMOOOOOO...!!! (personal note:I do need a battle cry of my own)»    
    
    
    «If I'm helping a company sell their products,I expect to be paid.Did you hear me,Mark Elliot Zuckerberg...?»    
    
    
    «Now that everyone is watching the soccer game,it's a darn good time for phoning them» #CuzI'mEvil    
    
    
    «WIP —things like this make me glad that I choose a career in graphic arts instead of sciences» http://brizzly.com/pic/2UH6    
    
    
    just loved Killing Joke - Eighties http://awe.sm/57mkW on @hypem    
    
    
    «Wondering if I should offer my services as a ghost writer of social networks status messages.It's possible,y'know»    
    
    
    «Did I mention that now that MySpace is less crowded it's fun again...?» http://tweetphoto.com/28806647    
    
    
    «Prosopagnosia + Scott Pilgrim avatars = I don't know who's who anymore» #DrivingMeInsane    
    
    
    «Had another of those wacky dreams where I wake up and suddenly wake up for real» #Déjà-Vu #Déjà-Rêvé    
    
    
    «WIP —They came from outer space!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/40M8    
    
    
    «Teaser...» http://brizzly.com/pic/2W3J    
    
    
    *  ❄     * ❄      *       *      ❄ .     *  ❄    * .  ❄    ❄        *        ❄ _______________________☃_____    
    
    
    "Dream as if you'll live forever, live as if you'll die today." ~James Dean    
    
    
    «Woke up behind the front door,with cramps in the lower back and the jaw» #Sleepwalking #Dammit    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ With my flesh they'll make a feast/I'm gonna be there in that number/That's 666 the number of the beast ♬♫♬» ~ http://audioboo.fm/boos/242247-hell-in-a-handbasket?utm_campaign=detailpage&utm_content=retweet&utm_medium=social&utm_source=twitter …    
    
    
    «Go buy a copy of this book right now! (it's for a good cause)» ~ http://moourl.com/0o66r    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where:because it's Just Another Day» ~ http://moourl.com/a0bkb    
    
    
    Ben Balistreri: Storyboard artist and character designer at Dreamworks, Emmy Award winner for character designs ... http://twurl.nl/em16uz    
    
    
    «New guest comic by you-know-who at Dumm Comics —Go lookie!» ~ http://moourl.com/if0gc    
    
    
    just loved Avicii & Sebastien Drums - My Feelings for You (Original Mix) http://awe.sm/57zp6 on @hypem    
    
    
    «If you gave Archimedes a place to stand,he'd move the Earth.If you give me a Sharpie,I'll draw all over it» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2X82    
    
    
    «Happy blogiversary to me! —8 years ago I started blogging.Wonder if I should do something special...suggestions?»    
    
    
    «WIP —Something simple,but sometimes simplicity does say a lot,ah?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2XLT    
    
    
    just loved Waylon Jennings - Ain't No God In Mexico http://awe.sm/583Qw on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —Morning quickie.When adding color,I think I'll use only pink» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/40UG    
    
    
    «WIP —I don't draw owls very frequently,but this illo was very amusing to draw» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2YG4    
    
    
    ❒Taken ❒Single ✔ «But you can say that art is my wife,music is my girlfriend and life is my bitch»    
    
    
    «Not a WIP at all —the piece is already finished but I forgot to show the lineart here first» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2Z17    
    
    
    «Revenge should never have collateral damage.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    «O_o #WTF? Somebody used my voter card (finger scars & all) to illustrate a blog post about people in Chihuahua» ~ http://moourl.com/983ht    
    
    
    PDFmyURL.com: PDFmyURL.com is a free online tool to easily convert and save any web page to PDF http://pdfmyurl.com/    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Here: http://bit.ly/bvrMih (some are simply Big Bad Wolves,but all content is credited)    
    
    
    Yuki 7 and the Gadget Girls: Fashionista and spy girl Yuki 7, along with her team of beautiful secret agents, th... http://www.yuki-7.com/    
    
    
    @IPTower I wish...to have the weapons I need,and a fair opportunity,since I'm ready to fight and help others while at it.Just that.Thanks.    
    
    
    @queentantrum Found you via Jaymes Reed.Regarding your request for an artist,I've got a video sampler ~ http://vimeo.com/6783480    
    
    
    «I've just spent 1 whole hour at the phone only reporting a lost debit card.And they won't give me a new one until 10 days» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «\m/» RT @fragmentscomic: Fragments is available now! Proceeds go to Save the Children: http://bit.ly/9ib62E    
    
    
    CSS3 Please! The Cross-Browser CSS3 Rule Generator: You can edit the underlined values in this css file, but don... http://css3please.com/    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Angels love bad men...that's how it's always been... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «More Sharpie™ sketches on a CD!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/30V1    
    
    
    « X_X Sleeping pills are not for me...»    
    
    
    «Task for today:write a piece about buddhism.Fun but challenging.»    
    
    
    « \m/ Happy International Rock Day!» http://chir.ps/66V    
    
    
    «Stop announcing everyone that they shouldn't fuck with you.At best,it's a sign of weakness.At worst,it's a sign that you're batshit insane»    
    
    
    «Ask no questions & just go read this.Now.» ~ On saying i love you. http://bit.ly/a2Tj7z    
    
    
    «I would rather be ashes than dust!»    
    
    
    «The bank hasn't sent my new card,yet somehow they've already sent me a new NIP» #LivingInAnAlternateTimeline    
    
    
    @werewolfnews O_o That's funny:yesterday I made a sketch of a new concept piece with them.Hopefully next week I'll be able to draw it.    
    
    
    «Teaser of some mischief I've just made» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/31YS    
    
    
    just loved Band of Skulls - Death By Diamonds & Pearls http://awe.sm/58Sjd on @hypem    
    
    
    «Grown-ups all get drunk on beer.Me? I get drunk on ink and chocolate.And dancing with myself as Billy Idol taught me»    
    
    
    «Heard some voices in the kitchen at 2:30 am.I though there were ghosts but it was just the cellphone a friend forgot here» #FuckRingtones    
    
    
    «I'm included in a new collective art show! YEEE-HAW!!!» #I♥mystupidlife #HellYeah! #Hopes&Omens    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Oingo Boingo (58), Ramomex (39) & Les & Larry Elgart (30) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    just loved The Divine Comedy - Life On Mars http://awe.sm/58b7H on @hypem    
    
    
    «For a corporation in its way of world domination Google sure uses some awful design work —yes,I talk about the new Google Images interface»    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Actually I think the new interface is overdesigned.Trying too hard to match the design of both Bing Images and Tumblr Mosaic.    
    
    
    «Know that I did what Peter Parker never could:stopped a thief that was being chased by a cop (okay,he tripped with me,but still counts)»    
    
    
    «Now if you'll excuse me,I'll go rest my achy bones...»    
    
    
    «I urgently neeed a victory yell of my own.In the meantime,guess this will do» http://chir.ps/6kz    
    
    
    «Good news:after 2 whole weeks,finally I've got a new bank card.Bad news:I can't activate it until next Monday» #WinOneLoseAnother    
    
    
    «WIP  —Supposed to be just a warm up sketch but just had to ink it» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/34CX    
    
    
    «This time didn't woke up in another room yet my feet hurt as if I ran a marathon» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    @comicsreporter Hey,congrats for that Eisner award!    
    
    
    «One of these days I'll be famous enough to be the latest victim of a Twitter death hoax»    
    
    
    «WIP —Chewed to bits by giant turtles!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/41NI    
    
    
    «Boy,Gloria Trevi sure used to write some really fun songs before going to jail.A punk band totally should cover 1 or 2 of them» #Hint    
    
    
    «I know it's just someone's nickname,but the irony totally made my morning» http://tweetphoto.com/35204031    
    
    
    «Friendly reminder:tonite is the openning of The Toe Fluff Show» ~ http://moourl.com/twqyj    
    
    
    «If you really love me,you'd buy/steal/make me a bike like this one for X-mas.But you don't.Goodnite» ~ http://flic.kr/p/8n3v5X    
    
    
    «...And this is the way my websites and online profiles are connected among them» ~ http://tweetphoto.com/35377395    
    
    
    «WIP —I know at least 5 of you out there were expecting to see these 2 again» #WerewolfWednesday http://brizzly.com/pic/35RR    
    
    
    «Today's Early Morning Lesson:Never EVER trust in someone that uses the words 'hippie','goth','religious' & 'naco' as insults»    
    
    
    «My solution for dealing with annoying Beatles fans:telling them the truth that my favorite Beatle is @yokoono »    
    
    
    «New music —a whole playlist actually— posted at my sketchlog.You'll regret if you don't download it.» ~ http://moourl.com/21tv4    
    
    
    «After some weeks of relative tranquility,this morning I woke up in the living room» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «There were enough mud to create a swamp,but I must admit that the outdoors wedding I attended yesterday was really cute»    
    
    
    «...don't tell anyone but it seems something I wrote will be used on the History Channel (Latin America signal)»    
    
    
    Giclée print ~ Ginny & Clutch (Greetings From Route 66) ~ http://society6.com/r/p-11244208    
    
    
    «WIP —A piggy playing the banjo!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/36X9    
    
    
    taxidermy - Ravishing Beasts: Taxidermy: Ravishing Beasts: dedicated to all things taxidermy. Sometimes the most... http://twurl.nl/n5cg2v    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Personally,I've loved taxidermy since I was a kid (easy when you grow up watching Addams Family reruns)    
    
    
    «Never regret anything.Because at one time it was exactly what you wanted.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    «I still need a girlfriend,a wife,a husband and an iPod™...but somehow it seems that I officially have a muse now»    
    
    
    just loved Bombay Bicycle Club - Ivy & Gold http://awe.sm/591Qu on @hypem    
    
    
    «I don't want perfection.Perfection is pretty boring.I want more of a beautiful disaster —if that's okay with you.»    
    
    
    « O_o A telemarketer just called & said that with my voice I should work in a sex hotline» #WTF #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    #aWiseManOnceSaid «Never trust someone that on Phazebooq clicks the 'Like This' button but never types anything telling you why»    
    
    
    #aWiseManOnceSaid «Every pretty girl or gorgeous man is someone’s ex,who was too much hassle for someone»    
    
    
    #aWiseManOnceSaid «Beat on the brat with a baseball bat» http://chir.ps/6Gz    
    
    
    «If you only had one day to live,What would you do? Now,go be bad and be good at it —I'll be lurking in the shadows...»    
    
    
    «WIP —Homage piece.Fun but challenging (I don't know how I'm supposed to color & design it now)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/37UU    
    
    
    «You have never seen me.I'm just a bot programmed to please your random needs of weirdness.Cause,yes,you do need weirdness»    
    
    
    «You have never seen me.I'm just a split personality created by you.So,yeah,I'm just a projection of yourself»    
    
    
    @sopelana Actually you're Norman Bates.And I'm your mommy.    
    
    
    «You have never seen me.I'm just an alias used by 15 different persons to make you believe that there's still hope for humanity»    
    
    
    «You have never seen me.I'm just a ghost from the future haunting you so you don't feel lonely at all»    
    
    
    «You have never seen me.I'm just a series of pre-inserted messages in your hard drive designed to make you believe someone agrees with you»    
    
    
    «Just realized that both the ones that love me & the ones that fear me the most usually don't mention my name.Wonder if it means something»    
    
    
    «Sitting in front of the computer,typing a tweet» #CrypticTweets    
    
    
    An Awesome Book!: An Awesome Book http://twurl.nl/zrdv4p    
    
    
    «Hi! Good morning! How do you do?» #CrypticTweets    
    
    
    «Took a taxi and listened to the driver's problems.Maybe I should've asked him to pay me for the therapy session»    
    
    
    «WIP —♬♫♬ Only dead girls don't walk away from me...Sad as it seems ♬♫♬» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/38ZX    
    
    
    «For those who fought for it,freedom has a special flavor the protected will never know»    
    
    
    «Woke up twice last nite.First,at 2:20 am in the kitchen,then at 4:37am in the living room» #Sleepwalking #Dammit    
    
    
    «I should be working but my head & soul are an awful mess —I'll take the day off.If you need me,I'll be at the zoo talking with the zebras»    
    
    
    «WIP —A rat,a girl & a cat in a hi-tech armor...stuff like this makes me glad I didn't became an agronomist» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/39JR    
    
    
    just loved The Bastard Fairies - Ode To The Prostitute http://awe.sm/59KRN on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved The Bastard Fairies - Memento Mori http://awe.sm/59KX7 on @hypem    
    
    
    @akagoyal Suppose so;but no,thank you.I've got already way too many online services connected to Twitteer ^_^    
    
    
    «The Red Project just reached its post #2,000!» ~ http://moourl.com/co93k    
    
    
    «Don't tell anyone but now it seems like someone put my name in Heavy Metal magazine...»    
    
    
    «...oh,and in another order of ideas —movie of the year:The Expendables.Period.» #\m/    
    
    
    «Story of my life...» ~ http://catandgirl.com/?p=2571    
    
    
    «Never tell your problems to anyone.20% can't help or don't care,and the remaining 80% are glad you have them»    
    
    
    «You.Yes,you.Uncross your feet/legs and take off your hand from your face.Now.» #YouKnowIcanSeeYou    
    
    
    «Don't make desicions when you're angry and don't make promises when you're happy» #RulesOfFreelancing    
    
    
    «Simply amazing hair creativity» ~ A CROWN OF CREATIVITY  IN ETHIOPIA ~  http://flic.kr/p/8sJ2hA    
    
    
    «You.Yes,you.You're making a mistake and you know it.Stop,breathe,double check things and this time do them right» #YouKnowIcanSeeYou    
    
    
    «Work for free or for full price —NEVER for cheap» #RulesOfFreelancing    
    
    
    «Shame? Me? Sorry,I have none» #EasyWhenYouAreEvil    
    
    
    «WIP —Yup,that's a T-Rex driving the Batmobile.Told you I had no shame» #EasyWhenYouAreEvil ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3B5D    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Garfunkel and Oates (37), Björk (36) & Ramomex (34) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Did I ever mention that I love living near a hospital with a heliport? Well,I do» #I?MyStupidLife http://chir.ps/6W8    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ One little,two little,three little Indians... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «WIP —A quick sketch of a winged girl» ~  http://brizzly.com/pic/3BDW    
    
    
    «"I didn't know you liked opera!" "Actually,I'm singing that simply cuz I'm a fan of Tom & Jerry"» (←real conversation I had this morning)    
    
    
    «WIP —One is an alien,the other is a ghost...They fight crime!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/42FM    
    
    
    "Quit giving a fuck what others think, especially assholes like me, okay?" «If I could,I'd tattoo that on my chest —Salvatrucha style»    
    
    
    «My sins of excess prove to me that I exist.»    
    
    
    «So,What kind of trouble can I get into today?»    
    
    
    «After wasting all morning in an useless job interview,it's time for typing a piece about the Pachuco movement» #NoRestForTheWicked    
    
    
    . — . ..--.. / .. ... / .. - / .- / - .-. .. -.-. -.- / --.- ..- . ... - .. --- -. ..--.. http://4ms.me/gYeqgu    
    
    
    you happy? — ^_^ Why,yes,quite.Thank you for asking. http://4ms.me/g8vdQK    
    
    
    "You know, a long time ago being crazy meant something. Nowadays everybody’s crazy." —Charles Manson    
    
    
    just loved Velvet Underground - Heroin http://awe.sm/59h7x on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Slayer - In-A-Gadda-Da-Vida http://awe.sm/59h90 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Don't hate your scars —they are reminders that you have survived something»    
    
    
    just loved Dandy Warhols - Not If You Were The Last Junkie On Earth http://awe.sm/59jND on @hypem    
    
    
    «Go lookie!» ~ http://www.remindblog.com/2010/08/26/u2/    
    
    
    «WIP —So Gillman,the Invisible Man,the Wolfman and Dracula's Daughter started a band...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3CW0    
    
    
    «While buying morning coffee I've just realized that Axe deodorant really is useful —it helps to spot douchebags just by their smell»    
    
    
    just loved Lo-Fidelity Allstars Feat. Pigeonhead - Battle Flag http://awe.sm/59loz on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —Breakfast doodle.You'll never guess what superhero is redesigned here» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/42M4    
    
    
    «Wondering why (Mexican) clients keep asking me for vector art when it's clear I only draw images by hand» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Jack! - http://kirbymuseum.net/blogs/kirby-vision/2010/08/28/happy-birthday-jack-2/    
    
    
    just loved B-52's - Strobe Light http://awe.sm/5F43V on @hypem    
    
    
    «Someone please motivate me to run»    
    
    
    «—"Remind me why we are friends" —"Because you listen to geriatric rock yet don't make a big deal about it like poseurs do"» #TrueStory    
    
    
    «Holden Caulfield wondered where the ducks go in Winter.Personally,I'm wondering where have the mosquitoes gone this Summer.»    
    
    
    «A character of mine has reached the Super Match on Mojiwar (guess I have to draw girls in underwear more often)» ~ http://moourl.com/my2ie    
    
    
    TO MY HUSBAND: NOTES FOR MY FUTURE HUSBAND.
THINGS YOU'LL DO, THINGS YOU WON'T.
EITHER WAY, YOU WON'T BE THIS GUY. http://twurl.nl/yh7aa6    
    
    
    vNes: VirtualNES.com is the largest website on the Internet that allows you to play classic Nintendo Entertain... http://twurl.nl/xj40me    
    
    
    «Now I didn't woke up in another room,yet I have a couple of bruises I have no idea where they came from» #Sleepwalking #AlienAbduction?    
    
    
    "I know there's Tlaxcalteca blood in you but sometimes I wonder if there's some Apache in there,too" «←I fucking love my friends»    
    
    
    «These days apparently everybody has to do story about zombies.This week seems like it's my turn and I don't know where to start»    
    
    
    «Found an idea for that zombie story.Not the most original but with a tight deadline it'll have to do» #WishMeLuck    
    
    
    «After some peaceful weeks,this morning I woke up in the bathroom with a sore arm...» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    just loved Scissor Sisters - I Don't Feel Like Dancin' http://awe.sm/59weP on @hypem    
    
    
    "When I descend upon the Earth, darkness will unveil its banner across yet another region of the cosmos!" ←«One day I'll say this aloud»    
    
    
    «Something for #WerewolfWednesday » ~ http://moourl.com/yfviz    
    
    
    «Not sure why but I joined iTunes' Ping»    
    
    
    just loved The Cure - Purple Haze http://awe.sm/59zFN on @hypem    
    
    
    Classically Trained Musician Weighs in on Metal Vocalists ~ http://moourl.com/c1vos    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Amadeus Amadeus...Amadeus Amadeus Amadeus...Amadeus Amadeus Amadeus...Oh-Oh-Amadeus... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Arrive early,be the last to leave and kick ass all fucking day.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    «Somebody just described my style as 'estética de comic book clásico' (classic comic book aesthetic).Pity no one is hiring me for that»    
    
    
    «Someone I admire just described me as "a hardcore motherfucker on fire".Expect so see me with an idiot smile for the rest of the month»    
    
    
    I Shot The Serif / Vote for your favourite Sans-Serif typeface http://designyoutrust.com/2011/01/06/i-shot-the-serif-vote-for-your-favourite-sans-serif-typeface/ …    
    
    
    Almost Fameless: I work in the film and tv industry. I make fun of the weird stuff I find in the mail.
Welcome... http://twurl.nl/j5fkuw    
    
    
    «WIP —A cute tender scene with a zombie (at least it's not a glittering vampire,y'know)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3FS5    
    
    
    «Sometimes,deep inside,I'm just a fucking boy scout.Please,don't divulge it.»    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Why,thank you!    
    
    
    Pizza-delivering boy,office boy,translator,Summer school teacher,journalist,storyboarder,radio maker,writer,starving artist #JobsIveHad    
    
    
    «I'm feeling very tempted to leave the Winter decorations up so I can have later a Nightmare Before Xmas-themed birthday party»    
    
    
    hello babe you a member of any other social internet s… — Let's see...I've got profiles on MySpace,Tumblr,iCheck… http://4ms.me/gLLhPD    
    
    
    «WIP —This videogame tribute is easy to guess...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4329    
    
    
    «WIP —Sometimes coulrophobia is well-justified...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3G1S    
    
    
    «The song's title says it all —What a Way to Die!»  http://chir.ps/7km    
    
    
    «If you're happy you will remember the person whom you love.If you're sad,you will remember the person whom loves you»    
    
    
    «I'm not questioning you,simply because I don't expect any answers from you»    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Jean-Michel Jarre (48), David Bowie (28) & Dawn Xiana Moon (24) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «If you really love me,you'd buy/steal/make me a bike like this one.But you don't.Good nite.» ~ http://moourl.com/ouols    
    
    
    @TenNapel In many Aztec stories number 5 is used a lot.But sure,their calendar didn't use weeks of 7 days and they didn't knew Pythagoras.    
    
    
    «May the bridges I burn light the way —Je me lance vers la glorie!»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Though you may shudder the memory remains...Come drink a toast as you dance on my grave ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «That distant sound you heard? Yup,that was me.Singing a victory chant after another battle won»    
    
    
    «Never define yourself by what you do or with whom you do stuff for» #RulesOfFreelancing    
    
    
    «Can anyone out there recommend me a good metal band? The kind with singers with voices like Cookie Monster's»    
    
    
    just loved Noisettes - Ever Fallen In Love With Someone You Shouldn't've (Buzzcoc... http://awe.sm/5ATFM on @hypem    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Thank you! I'll check 'em out    
    
    
    «I do know that all those pork heads in the supermarket are meant for cooking pozole today...but they remind me of Lord Of The Flies»    
    
    
    @missmandymurder That's said as 'No quiero probar tu pito de condimento' (noh kee-ehro pro-bar too pee-toh the kondee-mento).    
    
    
    2nd Anniversary of The Red Project! ~ http://tumblr.com/xarpel11i    
    
    
    «Moji War Champ! (Now I wonder if I should do something more with these characters...)» ~ http://moourl.com/gmgw6    
    
    
    «I don't have an ego problem,it's you the one that needs to fight against low self-steem»    
    
    
    just loved The Love Supreme - Bela Lugosi's Dead http://awe.sm/5Ac8N on @hypem    
    
    
    «Either somebody is talking about me a lot or I just caught a cold...» #Dammit    
    
    
    «One of these days I should investigate how come flu virus always increase my productivity»    
    
    
    «I'd give my prehensile tail for some ice cream.NOW.»    
    
    
    @WitlessMinion I agree.Unfortunately not everyone does,as you never can find around here an ice cream shop open after 7:00 pm    
    
    
    «Highlight of this day:a fortune teller read the lines in my hand and told me that I'll commit suicide.Nothing I didn't know,though»    
    
    
    «This day 25 years ago an earthquake destroyed this city,but I survived.Now you know why apocalyptic movies always make me laugh»    
    
    
    «Ouch!» RT @KARENSTEVER: "The ones who are hardest to love are usually the ones who need it most."~D. Millman    
    
    
    «Can anybody explain me this photo,please?» http://plixi.com/p/46184380    
    
    
    @missmandymurder Try here ~ http://twitpic.com/2qbfba    
    
    
    «"Facebook is boring". Signed:Tumblr. (Proof: ~ http://fuckyeahbloodfest.tumblr.com )» #NSFW #HellYeah!    
    
    
    «WIP —I've been drawing Aztec human sacrifices and getting paid for that,ain't it cool?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3JCU    
    
    
    «After some weeks of relative calm (hard to make good things last,ah?),once again I woke up behind the front door» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «Seems like it's going to be one of those days when not even your imaginary friends want to talk with you...»    
    
    
    «If hope dies last...who's going to bury it?»    
    
    
    «The more I see Jack Black,the more convinced I am that he's the unfunny American version of Capulina»    
    
    
    just loved Duane Eddy - Peter Gunn http://awe.sm/5AsZk on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved The Animals - The House of the Rising Sun http://awe.sm/5Asb4 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Sometimes seems like I really need both a wife and a husband.And maybe a horse.And a chocobar,of course»    
    
    
    «Do I love you? Why,yes.Now,in love with you? That,darling,it's another story that is all up to you»    
    
    
    «Only 2 more followers on Tumblr and I'll reach a hundred.Wonder if I should do something special for celebrating that»    
    
    
    I tweet since 11 Feb 2009. My #first5 followers were @EpitaphRecs @liamkemp @ClubMixture @sandcateye and @bibi_org. http://bit.ly/first5    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ The Devil made me do it,and I'll do it again...The Devil made me do it,and I'll do it again... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    “It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change.” ~Chuck Darwin    
    
    
    «It's 11:11 —make a wish!»    
    
    
    «There's a Finnish metal band called Hevisaurus.They are for kids.They dress as dinosaurs.» ~ http://bit.ly/aR1bn9 #UltimateCoolness    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where —a @katemicucci track! Enjoy!» ~ http://moourl.com/ocdfl    
    
    
    «The Scott Pilgrim movie is better than the books —at least with the movie I finally could understand what the story was about exactly»    
    
    
    @missmandymurder Pain is your friend.Pain means you're not fucked up.    
    
    
    «Wish it were 2025,just for one day.That way,everyone using aftershave lotion would be in jail for crimes against the enviroment»    
    
    
    My Twitter Rank is "Cool Person". What's your Rank? http://twit-rank.com #TwitRank    
    
    
    "I am an agent of chaos. And you know the thing about chaos? It’s fair." «←If I could,I'd tattoo that on my chest»    
    
    
    «WIP —Big Foot!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/43WO    
    
    
    just loved Weezer - Kids & Poker Face (MGMT & Lady Gaga Cover) http://awe.sm/5B8tZ on @hypem    
    
    
    «New Zombie Girl Tee Shirt —go buy yours and help feed the starving artist» ~ http://moourl.com/2jlif    
    
    
    Zombie Girl http://society6.com/r/tobrkkns    
    
    
    «WIP —Drew this during breakfast.Orange juice + Oreos™ + Doom = Best way to start a day,ah?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3LFH    
    
    
    «(...don't tell anyone,but now it seems this Spring I'll be part of an art show in Germany...)» #HellYeah! #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    «Sometimes I'm not sure if what I've got is guardian angel syndrome or simply a frustrated vocation as human shield...»    
    
    
    «It was a while since I used my Jack Nicholson Manoeuvre ©...but that grumpy cashier totally asked for it» #EasyWhenYouAreEvil    
    
    
    «If you use Firefox,you may be interested in giving a try to the Persona I designed» ~ http://www.getpersonas.com/en-US/gallery/Designer/everyueveryme …    
    
    
    «Too old for listening jazz in an ironic way and too young for honestly enjoying dance pop...Or was it viceversa?» #EverythingIsTheSame    
    
    
    «Sundays still suck.Today not much though,since my breakfast was cold cocoa and the first pan de muerto of the season» #Yummy!    
    
    
    «One day I'll be famous enough to use the word 'Official' in all my internet profiles as if it were a real surname»    
    
    
    «WIP —Not the most original designs but hopefully things will improve with color» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3MF2    
    
    
    just loved Deep Purple - Smoke on the Water http://awe.sm/5BNVg on @hypem    
    
    
    « X_X One of these days I really,really,REALLY should try to learn to keep my big mouth silenced...» #SomebodyShootMe    
    
    
    «I'll be starting a series of illos based upon real serial killers —feel free to suggest me your favorite»    
    
    
    «Truth is,in the end everyone is gonna hurt you.So the trick is you just gotta find the ones worth suffering for.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    Revenge Is My Name http://society6.com/r/jfhmlioa    
    
    
    just loved Big Audio Dynamite - Rush http://awe.sm/5BWGE on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Aloha Sex Juice - Cover, More Than Words (Hawaiian version) (Extreme cover) http://awe.sm/5BWHx on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Simple Minds - Dont Forget About me http://awe.sm/5BWMv on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —Well,I don't need to say who's this serial killer,do I?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3NAK    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: David Bowie (127), Nelson Riddle (68) & Jean-Michel Jarre (47) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    « ^_^ I won't be available today —I'm trying to learn how to fly!»    
    
    
    パックマン! (Pac-man!) http://society6.com/r/dclybxku    
    
    
    «10:10 10/10/10 —make a wish!»    
    
    
    @Simonjfletcher More relative if we notice that said moment actually happened twice in the same day —in the morning and at night.    
    
    
    «YooToob didn't kill the music video star —it killed the music video director,it seems»    
    
    
    «^_^ This day needs to start with a little energy —looks like a job for the Murderdolls» http://chir.ps/7ZB    
    
    
    repaneled: Copied Comics Panels: Artists redrawing comic book panels http://twurl.nl/wue22y    
    
    
    «WIP —Never hire me to draw your wedding portrait...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/44E3    
    
    
    «It's not that I use only my own rules —to be more exactly,I'm breaking yours»    
    
    
    Mapping Stereotypes by alphadesigner: Personal art project by visual artist, graphic designer and illustrator Ya... http://twurl.nl/xdose6    
    
    
    «Weather reflects the people.And currently here the city is waaay too dry,cold and bitter» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «WIP —Jeff Dahmer.Oddly,sketching this image made me hungry» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3OK8    
    
    
    «Google is the new Microsoft,Phazebooq is the new MySpace,Tumblr is the new Twitter...Can we spread the rumor that I'm the new Elvis?»    
    
    
    «"Why did you do that? I thought you were a pacifist" "Yes...but not a humanist"»    
    
    
    «I'm not leading a double life.I'm simply schizoparanoid,Didn't you know?» #FunCuzIsTrue    
    
    
    @missmandymurder I agree.Don't buy a machete,you can borrow mine: http://goo.gl/g7YR3 PS.-Happy & Orgasmic Birthday! ^_^    
    
    
    «"No,you don't like classics.You simply listen old music and brag about it" ←one of these days someone's going to punch me in the face.Hard»    
    
    
    «WIP —so far this one has been lots of fun to draw...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/44HL    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Take me down to the paradise city...Where the grass is green and the girls are pretty...Take me home ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Wounded in the line of duty...but not dead yet» #PersonalNow    
    
    
    «If they don't chase when you walk away...well,just keep walking and don't look back»    
    
    
    just loved School Of Seven Bells - I L U http://awe.sm/5C7p1 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Panic is waking up thinking it's Sunday.Relief is realizing it's Wednesday» #NeedMoreSleep    
    
    
    « X_X In one single day I melted a water brush,ripped the sleeve of a shirt and lost a contact lens» #Dammit    
    
    
    «Beetlejuice! Beetlejuice! Beatlejuice?» http://plixi.com/p/51975552    
    
    
    «WIP —After a long day typing,nothing like sketching goth girls with sabretooth tigers» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3Q8D    
    
    
    «Blocked users score: Tumblr=0 || MySpace=4 || Twitter=2 || Facebook=128»    
    
    
    «Her:"Please,don't laugh" Me:"Why?" Her:"Because you sound creepier than usual"» #WithFriendsLikeThese #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    «Wondering what's the use of watching the International trending topics when the most idiot local ones still show up there» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «I'd gladly start using 'Cowabunga!' as a personal battle cry but everyone here would start thinking I'm just a fan of the Ninja Turtles»    
    
    
    @missmandymurder If it hurts it's good —it means you still have it there.Still,just know it won't last forever and you're loved ❀-}--    
    
    
    «Last nite sleeping pills helped a little.But their price was I woke up puking all what I ate last 2 weeks» #SayNoToDrugs    
    
    
    «WIP —Ed Gein,as you've never seen him before» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3QSJ    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ You don't have to call me darlin', darlin'...You never even call me by my name ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    just loved Blur - To The End (With Francoise Hardy) http://awe.sm/5CPSh on @hypem    
    
    
    «It's hard to be told you're looking for someone just like you when you can't stand yourself.»    
    
    
    «One day I'll be famous enough to start using 'Official' as my internet second name.And have a Twitter death hoax each week,of course»    
    
    
    «Was there a celebration and no one told me? Last nite I heard fireworks in the distance»    
    
    
    just loved Gustavo Cerati - Cozumel http://awe.sm/5CUrw on @hypem    
    
    
    @missmandymurder Pick me and you can take me for free ¡Llévame contigo,güerita!    
    
    
    just loved Wax Audio - Thunder Busters (AC/DC VS the Ghostbusters theme) http://awe.sm/5CY3f on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Elvira - Here Comes the Bride (The Bride of Frankenstein) http://awe.sm/5CYAM on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Joan Jett & The Blackhearts - Science Fiction (Punk Version) http://awe.sm/5CYBE on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —Another one for the series of serial killers.Can you guess who's this one?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3UEI    
    
    
    "A person who truly loves you will encourage your independence." (via @KARENSTEVER ~ http://moourl.com/9blbn )    
    
    
    «WIP —Part of a short comic about relationships» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3S7D    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: David Bowie (96), Jean-Michel Jarre (65) & Nelson Riddle (38) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Featured at The Beat's 31 Days of Halloween —Go Lookie!» ~ http://moourl.com/qbitk    
    
    
    « \m/ ??? It was the Day of the Dead!...I try not to lose my head...Oh-oh-ohh...Way down in Mexico ???» http://chir.ps/8lp    
    
    
    «In case you missed it,here's a zombie tale I made» ~ http://moourl.com/igjlf    
    
    
    «Just because it's not Sunday anymore,I proclaim this day as Cumbia Monday —Enjoy the sound of it» ~ http://boo.fm/b261598    
    
    
    «Good news:Someone cited 1 of my websites as a source | Bad news:They got my name wrong —called me both Daniel and Ariel» #TaoWorksWeirdly    
    
    
    just loved Zola Jesus - Sea Talk http://awe.sm/5Cjsf on @hypem    
    
    
    Pin-up Girl http://society6.com/r/qnfbsovi    
    
    
    «Don't know what extra ingredient had the Froot-Loops™ of my breakfast but today I pencilled and inked a page in 2.75 hours» #OnFire!    
    
    
    @WitlessMinion As my za-zen sensei used to say:never worry,as everything always happens in its exact moment.    
    
    
    «✪ Warrior by nature ✪ Dreamer by trade ✪ Bastard by choice ✪»    
    
    
    hola :)donde donde? — WTF? Ты говоришь по-русски? ¿Titlatoa náhuatl? http://4ms.me/hOKaM2    
    
    
    «What do you mean when you say that I can't be a celebrity without personality? Last time I saw,they all are like that!»    
    
    
        
    
    
    «Mark today as the day when I angered someone just by saying that I don't own a cellphone»  #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    just loved Pet Shop Boys - Rent http://awe.sm/5Fob6 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Any volunteers care to scatter my path with rose petals? Pretty please with sugar?»    
    
    
    «I said it before but it's worth repeating:it's funny how artists using the biggest watermarks are the least likely to be plagiarized»    
    
    
    «I'm sure there's something behind the fact that today is both National Kazoo Day (US) & International Data Privacy Day» #ConspiracyTheory    
    
    
    «Hipsters and their bikes —a fetichism I'll simply never understand»    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Misfits (45), Jean-Michel Jarre (41) & Kim Lenz And Her Jaguars (30) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    just loved Marina And The Diamonds - Living Dead http://awe.sm/5FyMi on @hypem    
    
    
    «Those who criticize our generation forget who raised it»    
    
    
    «The Social Network movie in 4 single panels by Tatsuya Ishida» ~ http://moourl.com/6w257    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where:You're The Reason Why I'm Afraid To Die» ~ http://moourl.com/kvypz    
    
    
    «Somebody described an illo I made as 'costumed clip-art'.Not sure if it was supposed to be an insult,a compliment or a riddle»    
    
    
    «What are you supposed to do when one of your best friends is about to do something really stupid yet they won't listen to you?»    
    
    
    «Woke up in the living room,with a sore leg» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    just loved The Clash - Train In Vain http://awe.sm/5G4iq on @hypem    
    
    
    «\m/ Guess who's now the new owner of a genuine japanese brushpen» #ThereIsAGod #MyOnlineFriendsRock #HappyGroundhogDay    
    
    
    «恭喜發財!» #HappyNewYear!    
    
    
    ACTION ALERT: Help stop oil exploration inside one of Africa’s most iconic national parks! Pls RT! http://ow.ly/3FN4z  via @wwf    
    
    
    «I'm not so good at this "life" thing.But I'm quite hard to kill so I guess there's a balance or something»    
    
    
    just loved Little Richard - Zip-A-Dee-Doo-Dah http://awe.sm/5G9N8 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Just realized that half of the music on my HD is by dead people.My music taste outgoths anyone else's»    
    
    
    «If you are what you eat,I'd rather be a colorful and tasty bowl of Froot-Loops™ than an insipid and dry granola bar» #NuffSaid    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Marina & the Diamonds (97), Oingo Boingo (75) & Eagle Seagull (61) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Batman fights villains with serious birth defects and/or mental sickness —Why does he hate the handicapped?»    
    
    
    «Music posted you-know-where & obituary:¡Viva Satana!» ~ http://moourl.com/6rft2    
    
    
    how do overcome a lack of inspiration? — Getting some distraction so you don't waste time chasing your own tail is… http://4ms.me/i9gfVI    
    
    
    «After creating a custom font and struggling with metrics and kerning,I'll admit it:sometimes I can be a dirty perfectionist»    
    
    
    «I have feelings,just like you.I have red blood,just like you.I'd love to have a prehensile tail (just like you...?)»    
    
    
    «Sometimes I like to fantasize about how my life would be like if I had any idea of what I'm doing...»    
    
    
    «WIP —If you're a graphic designer or a typographer,sure you'll know what this cartoon is supposed to be» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/47C3    
    
    
    «WIP —expect some character designs like this (© @incogvito) in the next days» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/47E6    
    
    
    «Made a digital font and giving it away for free —Go download it and tell your friends!» ~ http://moourl.com/sxdwi    
    
    
    «WIP —A girl and her tiguar (well,a big cat with spots and stripes)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/47GH    
    
    
    «I "love" how my family check Twitter to see if they should bother calling me»    
    
    
    «In case you missed it yesterday:I'm giving away my handwriting as a digital font for free» ~ http://moourl.com/sxdwi    
    
    
    «WIP —say what you want about nurse uniforms,but syringes still are creepy» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/47LG    
    
    
    «Money doesn't bring happiness.Fine.But I'd rather cry while listening music on an iPod™ than on the radio» #StarvingArtist    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Marina & the Diamonds (83), Oingo Boingo (72) & Eagle Seagull (50) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Spanglish karaoke air guitar» #LastNite    
    
    
    «If you need something for today,you can go read the comic I made about relationships» ~ http://moourl.com/u5sbi    
    
    
    «Same as last year but what the hey:Happy St. Valentine's Day Massacre Day!» ~ http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iwpoKZY0IJc …    
    
    
    «WIP —Another one of @incogvito's characters» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/480U    
    
    
    «I hope to one day be a strange smell in someone's basement.» #Epicness    
    
    
    just loved Adele - Rolling in the deep (Guy Gadbois REmix) http://su.pr/1ch7xt on @hypem    
    
    
    «If you really love me,you'd buy/steal/make me some shoes like these ones for my birthday.But you don't.G'nite» ~ http://moourl.com/5a4es    
    
    
    «It scares me that I'm having such a great day...hope I don't snap and start stabbing people.Or something.»    
    
    
    «Who knew? Seems I can be in 2 places at the same time.Unfortunately the electrical bill goes through the roof if I do it.»    
    
    
    «WIP —Lucha heroes are always fun to depict» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/48GW    
    
    
    «Just noticed I'm about to reach 3,000 posts on the Red Project.Now,how should I celebrate that?»    
    
    
    @incogvito ^_^ Aw,thank you!    
    
    
    «WIP —More serial killer fun! (Can you guess who's this one?)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3T3S    
    
    
    «Just discovered a way to hack the pressure setting of a pen tablet.Really needed to change that» #HellYeah! #EverythingIsPossible    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Garfunkel and Oates (98), Elvis Presley (93) & Oingo Boingo (72) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «^_^ Posts like this one make my Tumblr dashboard a terrific place to visit every morning» ~ http://moourl.com/tsfrn #Awww    
    
    
    «WIP —Spider-man riding his pet ostrich!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4910    
    
    
    «I'm being very nice and polite this morning.I'm afraid I'm officially mentally ill.» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    Just loved Fleet Foxes - Helplessness Blues http://su.pr/2gemnf on @hypem    
    
    
    «I won't just settle for a woman who can cook me dinner.I have ambition.I want dinner and dessert» #NotSexistJustStarving    
    
    
    «Woke up at 4:20 AM on the kitchen floor» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «If you've ever tried to talk with a Mexican Beatles fan you'll understand why Chuck Manson became a killer after listening Helter Skelter»    
    
    
    «So I tried to draw a cartoon in a '50s style and the client then liked it because for him it looked like '80s stuff» #TimeIsRelative    
    
    
    «In my version of sex (and pleasure in general),one person cries from pain while the other cries from laughter» #EasyWhenYouAreEvil    
    
    
    «WIP —Sometimes I'm such a fanboy but at least I know who my role models are...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3V0A #MondayInspiration    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Elvis Presley (143), Voltaire (97) & Garfunkel and Oates (71) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    What's the best place near you to get a drink? — The kitchen sink (that's where I have installed the water filter)… http://4ms.me/emeAzD    
    
    
    «Task for today:write a piece about obesity.Irony for today:I only had animal crackers and tap water for breakfast»    
    
    
    «Still typing about obesity.It's hard making the text informative without sounding too technical and boring»    
    
    
    «I need a secretary,a sponsor,a pet,a girlfriend,a wife and a husband.Oh,and a chocobar.Not neccesarily in that order.»    
    
    
    «There are some voids even cheap chocolate won't fill»    
    
    
    http://huff.to/gUjjOT #ChingueSuMadreMarkZuckerberg    
    
    
    «If I ever start a musical career,I don't know what I'd like for backup vocals.A gospel chorus or a barbershop quartet perhaps?»    
    
    
    «WIP —Stuff I've been drawing this week (Princesses can't fly)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4A4C    
    
    
    «Seems like true internet popularity is not the number of fake friends on social networks but the number of loyal trolls and spammers»    
    
    
    «Must...resist..urge of...creating...a second...Tumblr...account...»    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Elvis Presley (106), 少年ナイフ (80) & Voltaire (68) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    CUBOCC: Creepy girl http://twurl.nl/lrrla4    
    
    
    What's one thing that most people don't know about you? — The fact that I can see them. http://4ms.me/eojft8    
    
    
    hello how are you doing me any questions:) — Hi there.I have no idea...asking,perhaps? http://4ms.me/dIv8WT    
    
    
    «WIP —bringing the Little Red Riding Hood tale back to its roots as a horror story» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4AJP    
    
    
    Just loved Dick Dale - Deltone Rock http://su.pr/2VmCww on @hypem    
    
    
    "I've already told you, the only way to a woman's heart is along the path of torment. I know none other as sure." ~ Marquis de Sade    
    
    
    Just loved Traveling Wilburys - Handle With Care http://su.pr/2faPU7 on @hypem    
    
    
    Just loved The Dollyrots - Om Nom Nom http://su.pr/1KksNW on @hypem    
    
    
    «Just reached 3,000 posts at The Red Project!» ~ http://moourl.com/enqul    
    
    
    Little Red Riding Hood - Untold Ending http://society6.com/r/osufmrtm    
    
    
    «While uploading some files,I've finally collected the 17 golden eggs in Angry Birds.Anyone care to suggest me a new game?»    
    
    
    @SomerEsat Looks cute and fun but unfortunately not available for desktops    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Sinéad O'Connor (121), The Dollyrots (76) & Soda Stereo (64) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «After spending all morning paying this month's bills,it's time to dedicate the rest of the day to type about espionage» #NoRestForTheWicked    
    
    
    "I'm sick of just liking people. I wish to God I could meet somebody I could respect."
~ J.D. Salinger    
    
    
    «WIP —I'm not very sure how to explain this...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3VBE    
    
    
    «Nothing says 'fuck you' quite like having a huge smile on your face.I may look mentally ill...but I'm still smiling»    
    
    
    Just loved Los Lobos - Rango Theme Song http://su.pr/93RnXj on @hypem    
    
    
    National Days: This purports to be a real list of "national" "days" http://twurl.nl/lhyrsk    
    
    
    «What's keeping us on Earth,indeed?» ~ http://catandgirl.com/?p=2875    
    
    
    «WIP —Cute gals in underwear.There.Now go ahead and click the link,you know you wanna» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4BNV    
    
    
    Revealed: US spy operation that manipulates social media http://gu.com/p/2nzaq/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    @olganunes I'm in Mexico City and curious —count me in?    
    
    
    @olganunes Looks like fun.I'll be sending you something between today or tomorrow.    
    
    
    just loved Joan Jett - Hanky Panky http://awe.sm/5DMCa on @hypem    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: The Dollyrots (87), Elvis Presley (66) & Sinéad O'Connor (55) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    What's the easiest way to hide something from you? — Post it on Phazebooq.If you've not blocked me yet very probab… http://4ms.me/gF4pYG    
    
    
    «While writing about giant monsters,I managed to mention my fav 007 trivia fact:that Sean Connery wore a toupee in all his Bond films»    
    
    
    «Woke up in the kitchen this time» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    Just loved David Bowie - Love Missile F1-11 http://su.pr/5tDJ7O on @hypem    
    
    
    «Choco-Torro™ and tap water for breakfast!» #Yummy! #DontTellMyParentsImPoor    
    
    
    «WIP —Testing this Autodesk Sketchbook app.Quite fun and user-friendly!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4CIT    
    
    
    «What do I have to do to prove my love to you people? Burn your houses down and eat your cats?»    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: 芸能山城組 (55), Smash-Up Derby (54) & The Dollyrots (44) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ And they're handing down my sentence now...And I know what I must do...Another mile of silence while I'm coming...Back to you ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    "Trying to move forward by hitting refresh/All I see is nostalgia" ←«If I could,I'd tattoo that on my chest.In Helvetica»    
    
    
    «If my cyber-karma doesn't try anything funny,I'll try to install Photoshop CS5.If in 24 hrs. you don't hear from me,please avenge my death»    
    
    
    «Seems like Photoshop was successfully installed along with my custom brushes.So here's a Wolverine doodle» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4D1J    
    
    
    «Music posted you-know-where:something fun by Marina & The Diamonds» ~ http://moourl.com/6bwxu    
    
    
    Just loved The La's - There She Goes http://su.pr/2dHm6w on @hypem    
    
    
    Just loved The Cramps - Surfin' Bird http://su.pr/5jfs4K on @hypem    
    
    
    «An elephant doodle! Lookie!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4D5F    
    
    
    @kawaiinot Knight Rider!    
    
    
    «Nice to know I'm not the only one with this lifestyle» ~ http://moourl.com/4hyfo    
    
    
    «\m/ YES!!!» || RT @asobi_seksu: More info on our show in Mexico City on May 13! http://j.mp/fCvjYH     
    
    
    «WIP —Inked this while waiting for lunch at a restaurant.The waitress was really slow» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4D9M    
    
    
    "Bugs Bunny, American Trickster god" ←«As a polytheist and as a fanboy,yeah,that was the best and truest thing I've read this week»    
    
    
    @Michael_Cho That was made by Kerry Callen,and originally posted on his blog ~ http://moourl.com/25jye     
    
    
    «It's official:unless you wanna feel like in the scene of a typical funny movie,never take me to a fancy restaurant»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Elvis Presley (35), Jean-Michel Jarre (28) & Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (26) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    Just loved Dead or Alive - You Spin Me Round (Like A Record) http://su.pr/1alcYn on @hypem    
    
    
    «I was just asked if I could worship the Devil at a lower volume —like I'm really sitting here worshipping myself»    
    
    
    «Those who think that my work as a writer is easy should try to explain the whole history of Tibet in only 12 lines» #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    «Earthquake!!!» #Wheeee!    
    
    
    Just loved ZZ Top - Sharp Dressed Man http://su.pr/1JAnU5 on @hypem    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Perdí mi ojo de venado...nadie me va a proteger...♬♫♬»    
    
    
    Girls Face Left http://dlvr.it/N31Nf    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: The B-52's (50), Jean-Michel Jarre (28) & Murderdolls (27) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Nothing like a whole week of birthday festivities to make you feel that in the end you're actually doing something right» #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    «So yes,now I've got a 2nd Tumblr —Go lookie!» ~ http://moourl.com/9bg23    
    
    
    «It's odd that people think I'm a psycho or something (more than usual,that's it) when I tell 'em that I don't own a cellphone»    
    
    
    «WIP —Is there life on Mars?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4ECX    
    
    
    Just loved Iron Maiden - Run to the Hills (live) http://su.pr/2j1uNd on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —Daredevil!» http://brizzly.com/pic/4EEX    
    
    
    Video: Black Sunrise - Trailer (by Nick Cross) http://tumblr.com/xb923qjtdd    
    
    
    «Sheena is a punk rocker parasite in a goth gang» #CrypticTweet    
    
    
    Happle Tea - Comics! http://dlvr.it/NVpWq    
    
    
    «What I lack in tact I make up with fast reflexes,indeed»    
    
    
    «Woke up in the living room with a swimmer's ear  —I totally need vacations» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Caifanes (118), Murderdolls (110) & Jean-Michel Jarre (31) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Who needs good manners when you already have fast reflexes...?»  #I♥MyStupidLife    
    
    
    Audio: The (Vitamin) String Quartet - Buddy Holly http://tumblr.com/xb926c7jhv    
    
    
    «I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I HATE hospitals.» #ForTheRecord    
    
    
    Video: Dead alien found in UFO hotspot in Russia ; With translation (by Allnewsweb) http://tumblr.com/xb926zblw4    
    
    
    Audio: Amandititita - La Mataviejitas http://tumblr.com/xb9273ref0    
    
    
    «What do atheists scream during sex instead of "Oh God"?» #HonestQuestion    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Murderdolls (79), Caifanes (71) & The Cure (29) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    Farel Dalrymple | illustrations and comics http://dlvr.it/PcJLC    
    
    
    'Don’t kid yourself into thinking you’ve gotten your act together. You’ve only learned how to play house.' (wisdom provided via @coketweet )    
    
    
    «Spent the morning re-reading Lord Of The Flies...the things I do so I can pay my rent»    
    
    
    Audio: This Is Not America - David Bowie http://tumblr.com/xb929z1st0    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tumblr.com/xb92afkvu3    
    
    
    @rikilindhome Haiti is still in the American continent so it's correct.However the proper term to begin with is Afro-Antillean.    
    
    
    @DaniDraws Okay: http://www.garabatorama.com     
    
    
    «WIP —Needed to distract myself and the best I could do was this pic of Popeye fighting Bluto» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/4FOS    
    
    
    «Music posted you-know-where:Autosufiencia by Zü» ~ http://moourl.com/lewjl    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Murderdolls (103), Danger Beach (45) & Jean-Michel Jarre (28) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    okbjgm: http://tumblr.com/xb92cvk4j0    
    
    
    @TenNapel Alligator meat actually does taste like chicken.If you ask me,I'd say the McRib is more like horse meat (yup,I've eaten that,too).    
    
    
    Audio: hockeyteeth: http://tumblr.com/xb92d68xae    
    
    
    Just loved The Temptations - My Girl  (Acapella) http://su.pr/1iQmTF on @hypem    
    
    
    Music: http://tumblr.com/xb92dtw9mi #CumbiaWednesday    
    
    
    «If you can read this & are not ignoring me yet just know this:I've been diagnosed with skin cancer»    
    
    
    Video: Hugo And Holger Pilot (by Teddy Kristiansen) http://tumblr.com/xb92eponnk    
    
    
    Mike's Amazing World of DC Comics-The Newsstand http://dlvr.it/Qrc8s    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Mecano (108), Ramones (65) & Murderdolls (47) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «Him:"What are you? Her husband?" Me:"No,I'm her executive producer" Yup,1 of these days I'll wake up in a hospital» #GuardianAngelSyndrome    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ We'll take our hearts outside...Leave our lives behind...I'll watch the stars go out... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «I'm not arrogant.Arrogant people are condescending.I just passionately believe in myself»    
    
    
    «If sickness doesn't kill me,bureaucracy sure will» #Dammit #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    Just loved Oingo Boingo - Spider http://su.pr/28LoMb on @hypem    
    
    
    @kawaiinot How about Skeletor?    
    
    
    «A quick girl sketch» ~ http://cl.ly/2i071n1X3V3Y1N2J0E2c …    
    
    
    «There's no such thing as bragging —you're either lying or telling the truth»    
    
    
    Music: http://tumblr.com/xb92ixn6gg    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Oingo Boingo (49), Ramones (28) & Jean-Michel Jarre (28) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «One day I'll be famous enough that people will listen to me only when I tweet something that will make me look like an idiot»    
    
    
    @sketchee Thanks!    
    
    
    «Big fight tomorrow.Stay tuned and bring your popcorn» #CrypticTweet    
    
    
    «Today almost at noon,part of me shall begin dyeing.Hopefully it'll be only the cancer.Cue some Ennio Morricone BG music now»    
    
    
    «If sickness doesn't kill me,bureaucracy sure will —again» #Dammit #GetMeOuttaHere #Deja-Vu    
    
    
    «Also:I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I hate hospitals.I DO HATE hospitals.Period»    
    
    
    «Alright folks,I'll be offline a few days.Don't break anything while I'm away.I love you»    
    
    
    «^_^ Hey,I forgot to tell you earlier that I'm not at 100% but I'm back at home,alive and safe.Thanks for caring!»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Oingo Boingo (26), U2 (20) & The Bastard Fairies (13) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    just loved Asobi Seksu - New Years (acoustic) http://awe.sm/32GLP on @hypem    
    
    
    «Random sketch:a Western skeleton» ~ http://cl.ly/123V0C0K0u2q0F2f1F0c …    
    
    
    «$550 US dollars for my rent and a chocobar would be nice (better yet:make it 2 chocobars)» #2010wish    
    
    
    «Oh,and ice cream everyday for breakfast,of course!» #2010wish    
    
    
    «A cake ended half burned...but the 2nd one is fine! Not bad for my first atempt at baking,uh?» #VeniVidiVici    
    
    
    «Expect the best,be prepared for the worst,fuck what others think & do your own thing...oh,and have an awesome 2010 while at it ^_^ »    
    
    
    «WIP —Cowabunga!!!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3TC4    
    
    
    «Now I've got a Google Profile and it looks silly with over than 20 personal links» http://moourl.com/oz0b2    
    
    
    «It's official:as cheesy and geeky I may look with it,I totally need to add a cowboy hat to my wardrobe»    
    
    
    «First Sunday of the year...and it's raining! (softly,yet enough to make my day and make me 100% sure that this year will be great)»    
    
    
    Music: http://tumblr.com/xb92olwqvw #CumbiaWednesday    
    
    
    «If you can read this,stop what you're doing and bring me a bowl of cereal with capuccino right now.Please.And thanks in advance.»    
    
    
    @ggpony At home (in Mex. City),resting from my first chemotherapy    
    
    
    «I know some of you were expecting this:the Ginny & Clutch illo is now available for sale as a print ~ http://moourl.com/zw6qs »    
    
    
    Audio: Thank You For Hearing Me - Sinéad O’Connor http://tumblr.com/xb92pcob68    
    
    
    «So I was singing to myself at the subway,and then a little girl gave me a coin —not sure if she liked the song or wanted me to shut up»    
    
    
    «Another year,another lump of coal for me...»    
    
    
    «WIP —expecting to color it before the nightfall» http://tweetphoto.com/8153839    
    
    
    «WIP —Breakfast zombie girl doodle» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3W9M    
    
    
    just loved Groove Armada - I Won't Kneel http://awe.sm/34GPH on @hypem    
    
    
    «So,the sketch I twitted earlier today? Here's the finished illo» http://moourl.com/3rpj1    
    
    
    «Taking down Xmas ornaments» #SaddestSoundInTheWorld    
    
    
    «I've been featured at ILikeCharacters.com! Go lookie!» http://moourl.com/gp47h    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Mecano (34), David Bowie (18) & Pink Floyd (13) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «9ºC and people around here are already dressed up as if we were in Antarctica —bunch'a whinny wimps» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    The -U! / Uriel A. Duran Daily is out! http://bit.ly/fD90jJ ▸ Top stories today by @elwarpig @rikilindhome @cameronMstewart @DavidALapham    
    
    
    «Why must be that when my old zen sensei shows up in my dreams is for scolding me?»    
    
    
    «Trying to translate Cuban reggaeton lyrics into English should be appreciated as a heroic task (don't ask me how I ended up doing that)»    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/xsssw - «So,Those urban legends about tacos made of dog meat? They're true»    
    
    
    «In case you're interested,I've just enabled Tumblr's question feature at The Red Project» http://redproject.tumblr.com/ask    
    
    
    «FYI,after my death I'll come back for more either as Woody Harrelson or as Jim Morrison»    
    
    
    just loved The Doors - People Are Strange http://awe.sm/37GQJ on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved The Doors - Light My Fire http://awe.sm/37GQR on @hypem    
    
    
    «Bandwagon! Go ask me whatever || Pregúntame lo que sea» http://formspring.me/everyueveryme #formspringme    
    
    
    Q:What do you think is your most attractive... A:Apparently,the capacity of seeing and hea... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/46147886    
    
    
    «On top but not in control...yet» #BeAfraid    
    
    
    Q:Who put the ram in the rama lama ding dong? A:I'd guess Lovecraft writing one of those si... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/50750510    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ If you're fond of sand dunes and salty air...Quaint little villages here and there ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «This time I didn't woke up in another room,only on the floor —but my feet hurt as if I ran a marathon» #sleepwalking    
    
    
    «Writing a piece about pollution on Mexican beaches —now I don't want to go to one ever» #ScaryStories #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    Q:girlfriend? A:Currently no,and I think at least for a while there won't.... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/54999403    
    
    
    Q:the color you wear the most? A:After taking a quick peek at my closet,it seems it's blue.... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/58839899    
    
    
    just loved Gorillaz - Stylo - Feat. Bobby Womack & Mos Def http://awe.sm/39XSD on @hypem    
    
    
    «Now kids,this is what here in Mexico is known as a '¡Qué poca...!' situation» http://brizzly.com/pic/16UM    
    
    
    «Ouch!» http://catandgirl.com/?p=2348    
    
    
    «The December Mail Me Art 2 gallery is up —and my envelope is there! Go look!» http://moourl.com/yanp9    
    
    
    Q:What did you hope to accomplish in 2009 b... A:A promise I made.I'm looking to make it t... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/66692705    
    
    
    Q:What is your funniest memory of love gone... A:There's a story about a roasted chicken f... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/68739854    
    
    
    @Bergting ¡Chidérrimo cumpleaños! || Most happiest birthday!    
    
    
    «According to my horoscope I should be planning a trip to Tokyo.But right now I'm typing a piece about illegal immigrants...» #DoNotDareMe    
    
    
    «After a long week typing stuff,finally I have time for drawing —and then my Wacom thinks it's a good moment for dying.I HATE Sundays!!!»    
    
    
    «I couln't do any digital painting so did some inking instead.I'll let you guess what this doodle is for» http://brizzly.com/pic/18BB    
    
    
    Q:what song can you listen to over nd over ... A:The Lion Sleeps Tonight.But there are man... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/75034856    
    
    
    «Bought myself a new Wacom™ tablet,and I'm still amazed that it's smaller and lighter than the old one» #ThingsThatMakeMeFeelMyAge    
    
    
        
    
    
    Q:What tv shows did you used to watch that ... A:Fraggle Rock,Invader Zim,Batman Beyond,Th... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/79038505    
    
    
    «The Red Project just reached its post #1,000 —check it out!» http://moourl.com/y99v8    
    
    
        
    
    
    just loved The La's - There She Goes http://awe.sm/44QBX on @hypem    
    
    
    «WIP —A reinterpretation of a panel from Ambassador Atom» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3WPA    
    
    
    «"Don’t forget to check your kid’s homework",via SuicideGeeks» - http://bit.ly/dyWlwd  #Priceless    
    
    
    «Good News:E-mail inbox with an interesting job offer that seems legit || Bad News:Currently I don't live in Munich» #Dammit!    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Rose tints my world...Keeps me safe from my trouble and pain... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Music posted you-know-where.Flavor for this time:Power Ballad Sunday!» http://moourl.com/jx0h5    
    
    
    Q:What do you want from life?  A:I think nothing.I've got no problem with life as it is.No... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/105763767    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/10wze4 - «O_o Whatever happened to Axl Rose? He looks just like my dear,dead grampa!»    
    
    
    «I survived Y2K,bird flu,mad cow disease,9/11,Vicente Fox's administration and swine flu —no surprise sometimes I feel reaaally tired...»    
    
    
    «...then again,I'm also way too stubborn to know when it's time to give up»    
    
    
    «3 new audio files uploaded to my Behance portfolio (in Spanish)» http://moourl.com/x5jez    
    
    
    «Should've been working yet went out & spent almost all day at the zoo (now I feel a bit depressed but also very inspired)» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    just loved Creedence Clearwater Revival - Have You Ever Seen The Rain? http://awe.sm/50hWA on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Icehouse - Great Southern Land (live) http://awe.sm/50hZk on @hypem    
    
    
    «Characters I've been working at today» http://brizzly.com/pic/1CSK    
    
    
    @Man_Tsun Thanks! Glad you liked it    
    
    
    @Man_Tsun That's correct.It's just a quick sketch.There'll be more of those characters though,as they're meant for a comic book.    
    
    
    «Ouch!» http://catandgirl.com/?p=2364    
    
    
    @Man_Tsun Thanks! That project is still in early stages.However here's another one more developed http://bit.ly/adcNiO    
    
    
    Calling London Creatives - http://bit.ly/b1hE3M    
    
    
    «If someone tells me once more that I should have been born a samurai,I'll get a sword and start chopping heads...»    
    
    
    «Now,this was interesting:my Popeye sketch video on ASCII» http://www.asciimeo.com/7380243    
    
    
    «Work in progress —panel from a short comic» http://brizzly.com/pic/1DW8    
    
    
    «This time I fell asleep watching a movie on TV and woke up in the kitchen with a nasty foot cramp» #sleepwalking    
    
    
    @marinaneira Looks cool! How are you going to color it?    
    
    
    Frank Stockton Illustration: Website of Frank Stockton http://twurl.nl/64pz8s    
    
    
    just loved Tom Waits - Downtown Train http://awe.sm/51190 on @hypem    
    
    
    «I won't attend this,but I'm posting it in case any of you out there is here in the city & interested» http://tweetphoto.com/10868813    
    
    
    «And with Google Buzz™ that's 5 websites that I can update from Twitter.Not sure if that's practical or creepy.»    
    
    
    Q:if you could go anywhere right now, where... A:I've been hearing that the Iberian Penins... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/151316453    
    
    
    «So I went to the movies and the mall police started following me —but it was okay,I imagined I was important enough to have bodyguards»    
    
    
    «There should be a law against clients whom think that a Phazebooq photo album is enough material for hi-res works (dammit!)»    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where:Todo Mío El Otoño» ~ http://moourl.com/7vp9m    
    
    
    just loved Technotronic - Move this (Shake your body) http://awe.sm/51Dja on @hypem    
    
    
    «恭喜發財! - Happy New Year!» http://bit.ly/a3BKpN    
    
    
    «Celebration for today? Okay —have a Saint Valentine's Day massacre music video» http://youtu.be/iwpoKZY0IJc    
    
    
    «A dog howled in the distace all nite long.This morning,I've been transformed into a Zombie de Zahuayo»    
    
    
    «I'd like to find some use for Google Buzz & watch interesting people but currently there only are reposts from Twitter & Google Reader»    
    
    
    «If you liked my Year of the Tiger illo,it's now available as a print at my Zazzle Shop —go get yours!» http://bit.ly/bydqEo    
    
    
    «Funny thing about blocking persons on Fazebooq:it makes some people look like they're talking alone (perhaps cuz they are?)»    
    
    
    Q:What kind of pens do you use for inking? A:Well,I have 3 Staedtler Marsmatic pens (0.2,0... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/188984742    
    
    
    «Work in progress —pencils...won't say what is 'cause I think is quite obvious for some of you» http://brizzly.com/pic/1HW2    
    
    
    just loved The Temper Trap - Sweet Disposition http://awe.sm/51b65 on @hypem    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/14qfsy - «Guess I found an use for Google Buzz™ —be afraid» #DidItCuzICan    
    
    
    «Reminder:my Year of the Tiger illo is available as a print —go get yours! (PS.-I need the money,y'know)» http://moourl.com/pw7nk    
    
    
    just loved Foals - Everybody Wants To Rule The World (Tears For Fears Cover) http://awe.sm/5Ds6Q on @hypem    
    
    
    Coolness! RT @TenNapel: Don't look at me. Blame post-modernism: http://bit.ly/nG4vY    
    
    
    @ectomo Video ~ Little Ponies doing Musicals http://youtu.be/wouG4GpL1-I    
    
    
    «Fell down a set of subway stairs.It actually was kinda fun,like bobsleighing without snow —and without a sled,of course»    
    
    
    «For the record,just because (sometimes) I can follow orders doesn't mean that I will take them.That's different things,y'know» #Untamed    
    
    
    « ^_^ You know,I could get used to sketching on manila envelopes more regularly» http://brizzly.com/pic/1K74    
    
    
    just loved Norah Jones - Jesus, Etc. (Wilco cover) http://awe.sm/5DtBX on @hypem    
    
    
    Q:What's keeping you warm tonight? A:Winters are a bad joke around here —not cold at all... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/230885056    
    
    
    just loved Pictureplane - Goth Star http://awe.sm/51wU1 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Just noticed that I'm close to reach 50,000 played tracks at Last.FM —Anyone wants to bet which will be the lucky song?»    
    
    
    «Typing about natural disasters as long as blackouts let me...»    
    
    
    CO2 emissions, birth & death rates by country, simulated real-time: A visual real-time simulation that displays ... http://twurl.nl/646wrk    
    
    
    «Went for lunch and a real bagpiper was playing Scotland The Brave.Gave him $200 pesos» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where —special for all those looking for their way back to home» http://moourl.com/ccvgl    
    
    
    «For the record,I don't have plans of creating a fan page on Fazebooq —if the guys from the CIA want my data they can google it»    
    
    
    just loved Glasvegas - Daddy's Gone http://awe.sm/529S0 on @hypem    
    
    
    «I haven't even had breakfast and I already made Osamu Tezuka roll in his grave.Beat that» ~ http://moourl.com/jo2oh    
    
    
    « >_< It's not even 9:00 am and I'm already wasting my time outwitting morons» #Dammit #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «Works with Last.FM profiles,too» RT @hypem: Get artist recommendations for SXSW based on your Hype Machine profile: http://bit.ly/cmBSsb    
    
    
    «So while waiting for lunch I was doodling on a napkin and the waitress then told me I should start an art career» #Boink!    
    
    
    «Fatalysia #3 review at Indy Comic Review! Go lookie!» http://moourl.com/us0hh    
    
    
    «Task for today:write a piece about history of rocket science.Fun fact:I'll write most of it from memory (I'm such a nerd,I know,I know)»    
    
    
    «Only 44 more songs until I reach the 50,000 tracks played on Last.FM —wondering which will be the lucky tune...»    
    
    
    «11:11 pm,4,9987 tracks...»    
    
    
    «11:23pm,Happy Birthday You by Jay Jay Pistolet is track #4,9990...»    
    
    
    «Track #4,9995 ~ Phonobaloon song by Takako Minekawa»    
    
    
    «...and track #50,000 is...Fell In Love With a Girl by The White Stripes! —Okay now,that's all,goodnite everyone»    
    
    
    «Ain't it funny how artists more concerned about their copyrights are usually the least likely to be plagiarized by anyone?»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Katy Perry (2), Phil Collins (1) & Britney Spears (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    Frank Miller Ink: The official homepage of Frank Miller http://twurl.nl/px7r4r    
    
    
    « O_o So this client says he loves my lineart —and then asks me to emulate Dreamwork's CGI style» #WTF? #CreoQueMePaseUnReten    
    
    
    just loved The Rentals - Friends Of P. (Album Version) http://awe.sm/52Qdf on @hypem    
    
    
    «Ask me anything,whatever (beware:I have answers for everything)» http://www.formspring.me/everyueveryme  #formspringme    
    
    
    Harmony - Procedural drawing tool: Sketch online tool http://twurl.nl/uxkjja    
    
    
    Tiny Vices: Mary Karaplis (Mei K) is a freelance artist based in the cozy, cloudy city of Vancouver, B.C. http://tiny-vices.com/    
    
    
    Q:What is the wallpaper on your cellphone? A:I don't have a cellphone —we true action me... http://formspring.me/everyueveryme/q/301123262    
    
    
    Watch Zombie Hunt! on Vimeo! http://vimeo.com/10155622    
    
    
    @Man_Tsun Yes,indeed! The zombie is Zabel —or Lord Raptor as he's known in America    
    
    
    «"Superman is Clark Kent". Signed: #Wikileaks  (←predictable bad joke but still ironic,uh?)»    
    
    
    «Whoah! No spam this morning on any of my e-mail inboxes! Wonder if I should buy a lottery ticket or something...»    
    
    
    «Can you keep a secret? I've been accepted in a models network (!) —boldly going where no starving artist has gone before!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «WIP —Horses!» http://brizzly.com/pic/1QIC    
    
    
    «Fell asleep reading old magazines,woke up in the living room with nasty foot cramps» #sleepwalking    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ We'll take our hearts outside...Leave our lives behind...I'll watch the stars go out ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    just loved Imperial Teen - Yoo Hoo http://awe.sm/52dEN on @hypem    
    
    
    «Seems like I urgently need an agent...and maybe a secretary...and a horse»    
    
    
    «Jésus Marie Joseph,libérez moi!!!»    
    
    
    just loved Dire Straits - Sultans of Swing http://awe.sm/52fYj on @hypem    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/19m4de - «The kid that drew this has a great future as an artist,you know...»    
    
    
    @thenoise_fm Why,thank you!    
    
    
    «1st day of Spring.And instead of doing something productive I ended up as translator & babysitter for some German gay tourists» #DontAsk    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Katy Perry (2), Phil Collins (1) & Britney Spears (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Ain't it cute when potential clients disappear right after you tell them your rates?» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    «Between Follow Fridays,Tumblr Tuesdays & Fazebooq's suggestions,Can anybody please suggest me people to follow on Formspring & Flickr?»    
    
    
    just loved Zombina and the Skeletones - Nobody Likes You (When You're Dead) http://awe.sm/52nU9 on @hypem    
    
    
    «Arrive early,be the last to leave and kick ass all fucking day.Pass it on.»    
    
    
    My Top 3 #lastfm Artists: Pitbull (4), Lady Gaga (3) & TLC (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    http://brizzly.com/pic/1UJS  «Stuff I've been doing lately —actual panels but not actual sequence»    
    
    
    "What price do we put on a soul?" "$7.25 an hour" «No wonder I haven't been able to sell mine...»    
    
    
    Dear Coke Talk: Shady advice from a raging bitch who has no business answering any of these questions. http://twurl.nl/y467kv    
    
    
    Coke Talk: Staggering through Hollywood with an eager nose and a sharp tongue. http://twurl.nl/szb088    
    
    
    «Seems like I'm too old for listening Lady Gaga and too young for understanding Peter Gabriel...Or was it viceversa?»    
    
    
    just loved Asobi Seksu - Bossa http://awe.sm/5362n on @hypem    
    
    
    «Got an Easter egg as a gift.It's the first time I actually get one of these and now I don't know what I'm supposed to do with it.»    
    
    
    «I need a lot of things,but right now,I'd settle for a chocobar.» #AprilWish    
    
    
    «On Sundays even fresh coffee tastes like dirty sock tea» #ScrewSundays #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1cmmdl - «Something different in case you're bored of watching Jesuschrist Superstar as every year»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I hear a noise inside my brain it is controlling me...It is controlling me...It is controlling me ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Woke up on the kitchen floor.Fortunately without cramps» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «WIP —Dragonslaying!» http://brizzly.com/pic/1YP0    
    
    
    Wkly #lastfm artists: Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (131), Buffalo Daughter (104) & Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart (27) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    « X_X Guess I caught something in my throat —I've been coughing more than a little kid working in a Victorian era factory...»    
    
    
    «Called the doctor about my throat & he said I should rest and take some medicine.As if my deadlines and my finances would allow all that»    
    
    
    «Seems like I'm high on cough syrup and my throat is still not very cooperative (been trying to learn to cough opera arias though)»    
    
    
    "I didn't jump to kill myself —I did it to fly" ←«Please take note,I demand this as my epitaph»    
    
    
    «The cogh seems to be under control now,but now my voice sounds like Marlon Brandon's on you-know-which-movie»    
    
    
    «Oh,and in the meantime,I've been featured on the Kirby-Vision blog —Go look!» http://tinyurl.com/yhq6pnl    
    
    
    just loved Suzanne Vega - Tom's Diner http://awe.sm/53PV8 on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Patrick Hernandez - Born To Be Alive http://awe.sm/53SGM on @hypem    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where & this time it's a classic:Dream A Little Dream» ~ http://moourl.com/9t4h1    
    
    
    «Watching Animaniacs reruns while checking your e-mails —Monday mornings are the best!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Doug Savage just explained my whole life in one single Post-It™ cartoon» ~ http://bit.ly/bqLmq5    
    
    
    ben newman art: naughty art, filthy fairytales and other perverted nonsense. http://twurl.nl/32cx6z    
    
    
    just loved SALEM - Frost http://awe.sm/5EB4o on @hypem    
    
    
    «Right now I should be researching about Mexico's bicentennial —and instead,I'm inking an elephant stampede» #FreedomOfChoiceIsBeautiful!    
    
    
    «The elephant stampede I mentioned? Okay,here it is (yup,it's just a panel from a new comic page)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/22OP    
    
    
    just loved The Mary Onettes - The night before the funeral http://awe.sm/53cVb on @hypem    
    
    
    «Happy Birth...er,Deathday Pedro Infante!» http://tweetphoto.com/18531096    
    
    
    «There's no pleasure in having nothing to do...the fun is in having lots to do and not doing it»    
    
    
    «WIP —Yup,that's a gunslinging lion...Do I need to mention how fun is to draw this kind of things?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3YMS    
    
    
    @nuisance Petunia Pig dyed her hair?    
    
    
    « ^_^ Upcoming —and yup,I'm included in this book» http://tweetphoto.com/18816194    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ If I had words to make a day for you...I'd sing you a morning,golden and new ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #1.-If you want your opponent to take you seriously,look into their eyes and make 'em feel pain...»    
    
    
    «...yet once again I ask to anyone who can answer:How are you supposed to fight an opponent that has no face to punch at?» #GetMeOuttaHere    
    
    
    RT myself in case you missed it « ^_^ Upcoming —and yup,I'm included in this book» http://bit.ly/ccomuk    
    
    
    just loved Tears for Fears - Everybody Wants to Rule the World http://awe.sm/54Kb6 on @hypem    
    
    
    @f_francavilla Dick Tracy! Or The Spirit! Or even better:Dick Tracy vs The Spirit! #PulpFestWeek    
    
    
    «Just turned the radio on & found out they are playing a Xmas carol!» #CoolRandomness #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #2.-Pain is your friend.Pain means you're not fucked up.»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I ain't dying to offend you,I got a dyslexic heart... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «This made my morning:someone just asked me in which side of Europe was Mexico located» #Hopes&Omens    
    
    
    «Trust me,no free lunch is worth having to listen an annoying "artist" trying to be weird just for the sake of weirdness» #KillAllPoseurs    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #3.-To make your opponents afraid of you,become a reflex of them and show them that you're not afraid of killing yourself»    
    
    
    «I really shouldn't be saying this because of the circumstances,but...boy,it's really damn exciting to ride in an ambulance!»    
    
    
    «WIP —Xiaolin gator!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3YSM    
    
    
    «Of all the funerals I've seen,the one that I attended today sure was the most beautiful of them all...»    
    
    
    «WIP —Friday cheesecake!»  http://brizzly.com/pic/2708    
    
    
    JIRAT JAMES PATRADOON: Jirat James Patradoon Fine Arts and Illistration http://twurl.nl/2oxq4l    
    
    
    «Good Monday morning! Made a guest strip for Dumm Comics with blood,bondage and elephants —Go lookie!» ~ http://moourl.com/up34n    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #4.-Don't go quietly unto your grave»    
    
    
    «Seems like I pulled a muscle or something while practicing the Singing In The Rain coreography» #Ouchie    
    
    
    just loved Eagle Seagull - You're the Reason Why I'm Afraid to Die http://awe.sm/55QKy on @hypem    
    
    
    «I really should be working but...somebody is playing a violin version of Ode To Joy at the music school around the corner»    
    
    
    «Combat Rule #5.-Never play an ace if a two will do»    
    
    
    «One of these days I'll be a celebrity famous enough to have human shields instead of fans»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ But all the promises we make...From the cradle to the grave...When all I want is you ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Adele (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Someone really should use this Craiglist post as the plot for a movie or something...» http://moourl.com/9ssqt    
    
    
    «The measure of success is getting paid for writing a piece about Ed Wood,Andy Warhol and John Waters»    
    
    
    Super Mario Crossover - Free Arcade Game Played Online: You can choose any other classic Nintendo character to p... http://twurl.nl/8kketa    
    
    
    I connected my #iCheckMovies account to Twitter! http://bit.ly/9i5ssF    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I'm looking over a four leaf clover...That I overlooked before... ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «WIP —Based upon a book,Can you guess which?» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2AHV    
    
    
    «A girlfriend of mine had a fetish for kicking guys in the groin.Needless to say she is NOT my girlfriend anymore»    
    
    
    «So creepy it's funny,and so funny it's disturbing» #NSFW http://twitpic.com/1knwok    
    
    
    THE JOHNNY CASH PROJECT: A unique crowd-sourced music video project honoring the legacy of Johnny Cash —user-sub... http://twurl.nl/xboaao    
    
    
    Check out this drawing for THE JOHNNY CASH PROJECT, a community-created video for Johnny Cash’s"Ain't No Grave." http://is.gd/bUv2Z    
    
    
    «yeah,yeah...Happy Mexican St. Patrick's Day and all that stuff (and happy no-birthday to me)»    
    
    
    just loved School Of Seven Bells - Babelonia http://awe.sm/55po9 on @hypem    
    
    
    just loved Delays - Find A Home http://awe.sm/55poX on @hypem    
    
    
    «Some days not even your imaginary friends want to talk with you»    
    
    
    «Battle of the zombies & strippers trailers —choose your fav!» ~ http://moourl.com/fq7o6    
    
    
    «Wondering how to fight against the system —Should I cancel my Fazebooq account or keep it and sabotage the network from inside?»    
    
    
    «WIP —Just because drawing pervertions is always a fun challenge» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2CUU    
    
    
    «Woke up in the kitchen floor.Fortunately,no cramps this time» #Sleepwalking    
    
    
    «I've just unclogged a toilet with no plunger —with my bare hands only.Try to top that»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ Wonder if he'll ever know...He's in the best selling show...Is there life on Mars? ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «Because in the name of honesty someone has to say it today (in Mexico at least)» → #ChingadaMadre    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ In your eyes I see the eyes of somebody who could be strong...Tell me if I'm wrong ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    just loved Sky Ferreira - Animal (Miike Snow cover) http://awe.sm/5624V on @hypem    
    
    
    «...and just when you think you've licked all your wounds,an ex-girlfriend reappears —somebody push me onto the subway tracks,please!!!»    
    
    
    «One of these days I'll be a celebrity famous enough to have fun making my fans fight against my haters —in a gladiator arena,of course»    
    
    
    «New music posted you-know-where.If you download only 1 song this week,it must be this one» ~ http://moourl.com/cxi9o    
    
    
    «Went to a job interview and all that I achieved was beating my record playing Space Invaders»    
    
    
    «WIP —Apocalyptic epidemy! (based upon a Jack London novel,Can you guess the title?)» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2FKW    
    
    
    @werewolfnews Cool! (Uh...For what? And when do I start?)    
    
    
    «Now,this irony totally made my morning» http://tweetphoto.com/22372656    
    
    
    «And so today begins the Guadalupe-Reyes celebration marathon...» http://plixi.com/p/62556793    
    
    
    «\m/ It's raining!!!» #I♥mystupidlife    
    
    
    «Sometimes I wish it were 1964,just for one day.That way I could go watch an @El_Santo movie and no cell phones would be ringing»    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Britney Spears (4) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «Dinner sketch!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3ZD4    
    
    
    «WIP —I think I'll call this kaiju Elmer Ceronterrino...» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2H0R    
    
    
    just loved Jack Mercer - I'm Popeye the Sailor Man http://awe.sm/56HSF on @hypem    
    
    
    Fun Latin: Some phrases from Latin for all Occasions, by Henry Beard. http://twurl.nl/hmw6gq    
    
    
    «Sometimes when I stop & think how many Mexicans genuinely enjoy stuff like Chespirito & Michael Moore,it scares the living shit out of me»    
    
    
    «Good News:I found a needle that I lost the other day - Bad News:I found it with my pinky toe.» #ThePain    
    
    
    «Sometimes I hate to know things and not being able to share them because I must let people learn by themselves» #GuardianAngelSyndrome    
    
    
    «Useless fact for today» http://tweetphoto.com/23149295    
    
    
    «This time I didn't wake in another room.But in my sleep I managed to wrap myself in the sheets as in a straitjacket»    
    
    
    «WIP —Characters for a poster that will have the title of 'Join The Red Corps'» http://brizzly.com/pic/2IQ5    
    
    
    My Top 3 Weekly #lastfm artists: Oingo Boingo (58), Joan Jett and the Blackhearts (32) & A Brokeheart Pro (32) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0    
    
    
    «New print for sale at my Zazzle shop:Join The Red Corps —go get yours!» ~ http://bit.ly/9vksGg    
    
    
    «If you really love me,you'd buy/steal/make me a piano like this one.But you don't.Goodnight» http://tweetphoto.com/23857644    
    
    
    «Is it your computer? Or Facebook's?»    
    
    
    «MySpace.-A fun place now that Phazebooq made it less crowded» #Definitions    
    
    
    «Facebook.-A place where everyone forwards their tweets to» #Definitions    
    
    
    «Dorothy Gambrell is a genius» ~ http://catandgirl.com/?p=2759    
    
    
    «In periods of drought even wild storms are preferable to yet another sunny day»    
    
    
    «Now I don't know if what I need is a muse,a housewife,vacations,an EuroMastercard,or a log cabin in the woods...»    
    
    
    just loved The Kingston Trio - Scotch and Soda http://awe.sm/56ZxC on @hypem    
    
    
    «If cereal is breakfast of champions,then Valentina® sauce is what maniacs use to fuel theselves in the morning (& I just did that!)»    
    
    
    «♬♫♬ I do it all because I'm evil...And I do it all for free —Your tears are all the pay I'll ever need! ♬♫♬»    
    
    
    «There should be some zen paradox in the fact that I've been answering emails all this morning,but no one has answered my requests yet»    
    
    
    100 People I Hate on Facebook http://gizmodo.com/5713173/  via @gizmodo    
    
    
    «WIP —Vinyl records rule!» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/2KZZ    
    
    
    @coketweet That drink is unknown around here.On the other hand,brand names usually don't get translated because English is more commercial.    
    
    
    just loved David Bowie - Life On Mars http://awe.sm/56ear on @hypem    
    
    
    «Feeling a bit sick today —not sure if it's because of the flu I got or all those Gary Coleman videos everywhere on the web»    
    
    
    «If there's something I hate more than a Sunday morning,it's a Sunday morning with nose diarrhea» #SendAspirins    
    
    
    «WIP —A typical MySpace shot» ~ http://brizzly.com/pic/3ZQ8    
    
    
    My Top 1 #lastfm Artists: Maron (1) http://bit.ly/i3Xva0     
    
    
    «No matter how proud you are,always remember:with the right storytelling you'll always be the villain in someone else's movie» #HellYeah!    
    
    
    