Is graphics finally mature for the web. WebGL is so far the best way
http://lnkd.in/YBu4JH    
    
    
    I like terminology. Well-behaved function. What does it really mean...    
    
    
    Yesterday it snowed in Tokyo. It was pretty cold and slippery! (and I was sleepy too!) Snowflakes are nice for dreaming!    
    
    
    Levy processes and brownian processes. Statistical modeling and stock ticks... fascinating topics.    
    
    
    I would like airbag for the jet fly pack. Amazing!!
http://bit.ly/dtWN0B    
    
    
    I began using Java Processing language. That is great!    
    
    
    There are some people who look more androids than android.  That is good. There is hope for androids looking more human than human...    
    
    
    Enum does not work in processing. Why not?    
    
    
    I like programming because not only it gives intuition but also it shows our mathematical proof flaws when writing papers...    
    
    
    embedding, immersion, isometric embedding...    
    
    
    Poetic reality...    
    
    
    Playstation Move. I remember siggraph emerging technologies, ten years or more ago. that is the time span between R&D&B    
    
    
    Bertrand Russell is confusing me. Are we all doing tautology in research?    
    
    
    I need to fight entropy in my desktop!    
    
    
    The Normal Inverse Gaussian Levy Process
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K6VDzJ2Vijs
We live in a stochastic reality?    
    
    
    Brownian motions, Ito integrals, the late Kiyosi ITO:
http://www.academie-sciences.fr/membres/I/Ito_Kiyosi.htm    
    
    
    One day, I need to be fluent in chinese. They are exciting stuff going...
http://www.nsfc.gov.cn/Portal0/default124.htm    
    
    
    Ellison started selling Oracle II. There was never Oracle I. It was a trick to show product maturity.... that is smart    
    
    
    The personal life of Nash who the nobel prize is incredible... Check wikipedia
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Forbes_Nash,_Jr.    
    
    
    Jensen inequality... only 100 years old... Consciousness of math....    
    
    
    I saw the Ootoya dalton at lunch... Always great    
    
    
    clear blue skies in Tokyo!    
    
    
    Gomboc geometry is fascinating...
http://www.gomboc.eu/     
    
    
    Theil income inequality....    
    
    
    Adicity is not acidity. dyadicity is binaricity,... like a poem.    
    
    
    Taxonomy of principal distances
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/index.php    
    
    
    They are people who bear really amazing names... Shannon Fisher...
http://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/geneticmedicine/People/Faculty/fisher.html    
    
    
    bisymmetry of means. very nice!    
    
    
    Additive and non-additive entropy with java source code:
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/    
    
    
    Inifnite set can be in 1to1 correspondence with proper subsets. And without contradiction Yes,but when we think twice we are always puzzled    
    
    
    A set S is  infinite iff.there exists a proper subset
of S which has the same cardinality as S.
(e.g., the integers and the even integers)    
    
    
    Crazy transparent fish head: http://lnkd.in/in65_U     
    
    
    space of rotations and the miracle of geometric conformal embedding...    
    
    
    360 degrees jigsaw (puzzles)
http://www.mindagame.com/jpp/jeudepuzzle.php
Technology brings us there!    
    
    
    Procrustes refers to a bandit from Greek mythology who made his victims fit his bed either by stretching their limbs or cutting them off.    
    
    
    PlanetMath is great!    
    
    
    Take the quizz !!!!
http://www.informationgeometry.org/informationtheoreticdistances.html    
    
    
    Think about things. That is mathematics!    
    
    
    Do animal do mathematics?    
    
    
    Another ranking
http://lnkd.in/2yWqPW     
    
    
    Constantin Carathéodory (or Constantine Karatheodori)  was greek but with an accent in his name... That is not so intuitive...    
    
    
    New mailing list: infogeo for information geometry
http://www.informationgeometry.org/mailman/listinfo/infogeo    
    
    
    I have released the second quizz on information geometry:
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/index.php    
    
    
    Towars a better understanding of reality? Breaking the celerity limit, or the strange speed of neutrinos...  http://lnkd.in/UiV5pd     
    
    
    Computable reals are of measure zero in the set of reals. Fortunately, we got PI, sqrt(2) ! How lucky!    
    
    
    Humanoid wife...
http://www.is.sys.es.osaka-u.ac.jp/development/0006/mpeg/ReplieeQ2DemoFace.mpg    
    
    
    Four-Dimensional Electron Microscopy...    
    
    
    New mailing list on information geometry:
http://www.informationgeometry.org/mailman/listinfo/infogeo    
    
    
    The Burbea-Rao and Bhattacharyya centroids    
    
    
    Subscribe to the international mailing list on information geometry at informationgeometry.org    
    
    
    Happy new year to all of you. I recommend reading the book
The Tibetan Book of Living and Dying. It is inspiring. Science and spirituality.    
    
    
    Faster than the FFT, with sparsity! 
http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2012/faster-fourier-transforms-0118.html …    
    
    
    Pacman is NP-hard. http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/arxiv/27528/?p1=blogs …    
    
    
    Winter time... time to watch videos. Here is a recommendation: FOCS video:http://techtalks.tv/focs/2010/    
    
    
    What is neat with research is when you find how simple seemingly complex things are!    
    
    
    8 million degrees bursts from the sun... into the cold 0.K space. What a fantastic universe!    
    
    
    What is the "best" OO language nowadays beating Ruby with Mixins... ?!? http://lnkd.in/iMagJs  http://lnkd.in/Gw68vr     
    
    
    Science is idealizing the ungraspable world. Modeling is loosing information... The gap will always be.    
    
    
    I read that more than 200 000 planes/day go over USA. It is crazy world. I like figures that strike you. Is it common sense...?    
    
    
    Matrix Information Geometry almost there! http://www.springer.com/engineering/signals/book/978-3-642-30231-2 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Geometry and Experience, 
http://lnkd.in/hSkkdY     
    
    
    Incommensurate structures in nature are fascinating...    
    
    
    Ipe version 7 is out. It supports many SVG-like functionalities. 
http://bit.ly/by8vnF    
    
    
    I have uploaded a video on an old work
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xde8wAJquU4
using the same system, we could get 360 stereo videos.    
    
    
    3D movies and previsualization;
http://lnkd.in/4mhGf5     
    
    
    In Java, you can force garbage collector with System.gc();
It was effective for my problem today -:)    
    
    
    Used tag 5793b870  to disambiguate myself from the Nielsen Frank in future.
http://lnkd.in/KRbPhH 
ORCID http://about.o…http://lnkd.in/ft537m     
    
    
    Lego danish company is  pushing market. I recently tried their digital box, and my kids liked it. http://bit.ly/9habic    
    
    
    I think it is good kids play with VR and cybercode-inspired technology.    
    
    
    Did you know fewnomial theory, algebraic results for polynomials with few monomials? Quite interesting line of work.    
    
    
    Processing language is fun, but processing name is not discriminatory enough for searching. Hence, type tricky proce55ing !    
    
    
    I updated http://www.informationgeometry.org/    
    
    
    Nice to see that my blog is listed in 
http://www.mastersincomputerscience.net/top-50-computer-science-blogs.html    
    
    
    Amazing reading: Science Without Numbers: A Defence of Nominalism by
Hartry H. Field    
    
    
    Yet another inspiring book by one of the greatest geometrician!
Geometry Revealed: A Jacob's Ladder to Modern Higher Geometry    
    
    
    The value of philosophy for scientists...
http://www.ditext.com/russell/rus15.html    
    
    
    @sowd Shigeru, your son develops biz. skills -:) as my son does-:) A Difference with girls when they are young. Curious to read stats about!    
    
    
    Equivocation: ambiguity arising from the misleading use of a word    
    
    
    Three-body problem has an exact analytic solution since 1909 (Sundman)... why is there such a common myth -:) http://www.scholarpedia.org/article/Three_body_problem …    
    
    
    Enormous problem: classification. In search of structures. 1200+ page proof...
http://lnkd.in/y7WBDP     
    
    
    Computer etymology stems from com (together) + putare (trim), French origin. but in French  ordinator (“one who orders”) is computer !-:)    
    
    
    A nice principle for abstraction is the abduction! Check wikipedia. I reason this way someties...    
    
    
    Shannon paper has been retyped with Tex source -:)
http://cm.bell-labs.com/cm/ms/what/shannonday/paper.html    
    
    
    Algorithmic trading is over 50% in the biz i recently learnt. Within 25 years, I wonder how much information geometry in it!!!    
    
    
    Volume graphics = future of CG, same as color was the future of grey. http://www-ui.is.s.u-tokyo.ac.jp/~kenshi/DiffusionSurfaces/index.html    
    
    
    Matrix information geometry book:
http://lnkd.in/hn6A-P     
    
    
    Matrix Information Geometry http://www.springer.com/engineering/signals/book/978-3-642-30231-2 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Recently in the US, I was asked my ID to buy beer, but today I try some software with face recognition that indicated age probability: 50!!!    
    
    
    Typhoon came today close to Tokyo. It was quite rainy... and humid...    
    
    
    Adobe labs have synthesized some of their conference technologies at 
http://www.adobe.com/technology/ 
Harmonizing presentation is nice    
    
    
    The 18th century was a world without Jehttp://www.springerlink.com/content/r55q1411g840j446/nsen inequality. I wonder how!!!    
    
    
    A Concise and Practical Introduction to Programming Algorithms in Java http://www.springer.com/computer/swe/book/978-1-84882-338-9 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Stephen Wolfram: Computing a theory of everything at TED:
http://www.ted.com/talks/stephen_wolfram_computing_a_theory_of_everything.html    
    
    
    Judo@Tokyo 2010. The gold medals are amazingly won by Japanese showing a strong art in the country. France has its chance today...    
    
    
    Read that Google research, after Zurich,  is setting some structure in France.    
    
    
    Digging articles in library make u feel a bit historian. Always good to go to physical library!    
    
    
    Poincare was a fine philosopher as well. Every nice writings:
http://www.ac-nancy-metz.fr/enseign/philo/textesph/Dernierespensees.pdf    
    
    
    An amazing video of computer science/vision in action for extreme piloting of helicopter:    
    
    
    Try saving a presentation pdf as con.pdf in windows... -:) !    
    
    
    Science = Reversing Reality...    
    
    
    Dual view and 3D by means of parallax barrier. Great!
http://lnkd.in/iiMzzJ    
    
    
    GSI2013 - Geometric Science of Information in Paris! http://www.gsi2013.org/     
    
    
    Prof Vaclav Skala gave a nice overview why projective geometry is useful in CG.
dot and cross are GPU instructions.
http://www.vaclavskala.eu/     
    
    
    In action
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RujA9V4CGqs&feature=colike …
at the poster session of SIG ASIA    
    
    
    A Concise and Practical Introduction to Programming Algorithms in Java http://lnkd.in/Y7MTd5     
    
    
    Precursor usage of Computational geometry: Perceptrons: An Introduction to Computational Geometry by Minsky and Papert, back to 1969!    
    
    
    Shannon was a student of Vannevar Bush, father of the memex vision  ! http://lnkd.in/-ApRbE     
    
    
    An Information-Geometric Characterization of Chernoff Information http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/articleDetails.jsp?arnumber=6423793 … via @ieeexplore    
    
    
    Poincare wisely said: "One geometry cannot be more true than another; it can only be more convenient. " Ultimate knowledge = illusion quest    
    
    
    Did you know sedonion numbers?
http://lnkd.in/NEihpt 
Can build googlenion numbers too -:)!    
    
    
    In IT, KL means Kullback-Leibler . Today I went to kiddy land and took their catalogue KL... Acronyms and context! -:)    
    
    
    Human language uses the duality operator: anti-derivative and anti-fragility are two such examples!    
    
    
    Amazing computing device from 2000 years ago:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RLPVCJjTNgk    
    
    
    Many typings for Occam's principle. Like Ockham. Maybe Okam should be best -:)    
    
    
    If you like Bayes error analysis, you need these latex notations: $
\mathop{\gtreqless}^{C_1}_{C_2}
\quad
\mathop{\lesseqgtr}^{C_1}_{C_2}
$    
    
    
    Infinity is the melting pot: Infinitely many coverings of a same infinite space by inf. subspaces Structures = chosen for convenience?    
    
    
    Using computer algebra systems to crunch formula. I discovered a bug in Wolfram Mathematica(R). We need to have certifications of formula!!!    
    
    
    Nearing HAL 9000 in 2001: A Space Odyssey with brainwave authentification!
http://lnkd.in/cTUS-R     
    
    
    Guess who received the Nobel Laureate, the Turing Award and was inducted ACM Fellow...
http://lnkd.in/6Q_Uuv     
    
    
    List of siggraph accepted papers is available on-line: many sections of CG!    
    
    
    Clustering histograms a la k-means. Yes, but what distance? Which centroid?
Jeffreys divergence! http://lnkd.in/csdyvF     
    
    
    Logging safely in public spaces using color PINs 
http://lnkd.in/wA6g4m 
http://lnkd.in/PUT65V     
    
    
    Experiments with power diagrams... http://lnkd.in/csdyvF     
    
    
    Computing with high radiation doses in space.... http://lnkd.in/zmgWNN     
    
    
    Perspective click and drag selection in photos received the best practical paper award at MVA http://lnkd.in/5npwRA     
    
    
    Deep learning http://lnkd.in/34DJp3     
    
    
    Another deep learning: http://lnkd.in/FNhx_2 
...improvements in mathematical formulas...    
    
    
    How simple!  "matter tells Spacetime how to curve, and Spacetime tells matter how to move". Thanks Mr. John Wheeler. then egg and chicken...    
    
    
    C.R. Rao and information geometry http://lnkd.in/cDKV5Q     
    
    
    Time for Science to challenge as large as possible time problems, beyond climate prediction/sustainable issues? Beyond big data is big time!    
    
    
    Abel impossibility theorem of degree 5 polynomial original proof in a mere 7 pages.
http://lnkd.in/DYEA6r     
    
    
    Did you know that it is Arthur Cayley that in 1855 introduced matrices and its algebra? http://lnkd.in/ftwSTp     
    
    
    Cn y rd txts wtht vwls?    
    
    
    Geometric Science of Information - First International Conference, GSI 2013, Paris, France, August http://www.springer.com/computer/image+processing/book/978-3-642-40019-3 … #springer    
    
    
    Scanning internet in 45 min on a single machine:
https://zmap.io/  need to check!    
    
    
    Strangely enough, the area of an ellipse is pi a b but the perimeter requires an infinite series to sum... Mysteries of nice formula...    
    
    
    Always good (!!!) to look at roots of core concepts like Taylor series in 1715: Visualize the original formula: …http://lnkd.in/bV9VNrm     
    
    
    Calculating chi square amd approximating f-divergences using Taylor expansions  #infogeo
http://lnkd.in/b7vTHmx     
    
    
    List of computer vision papers accepted at ICCV: http://lnkd.in/b-c2x4J     
    
    
    We are heading for the Indo-French workshop on Matrix Information Geometries:
http://lnkd.in/E4ucg6    
    
    
    Siggraph Asia tech brief program is out!
 http://lnkd.in/bKkFqBu  http://lnkd.in/bPE5-C3     
    
    
    BNF for Java: write your own language:
http://lnkd.in/zNEj5R    
    
    
    Total Jensen divergences: Definition, Properties
and k-Means   Clustering http://lnkd.in/bhDRx8Y     
    
    
    Revisiting space zooming techniques for enriched context focus  interfaces:
http://lnkd.in/b4sb5KH     
    
    
    Posted a blog note on image segmentation that keeps improving with time:
http://lnkd.in/bC4umYE 
SRM->Consensus Region Merging    
    
    
    Matrix information geometries
http://lnkd.in/E4ucg6    
    
    
    Geat! Information geometry and Fisher information matrix in Science magazine... 
http://lnkd.in/byDK2n2     
    
    
    A family of statistical symmetric divergences based on Jensen's inequality http://lnkd.in/bbxGRTv     
    
    
    Great work: Information Theoretical Estimators (ITE) Toolbox 
http://lnkd.in/bhYEehP 
Need more software/tutorials on those topics!    
    
    
    Another affine exponential family are multinomials of course... http://lnkd.in/bRfHgTY  
The letter appears brushed …http://lnkd.in/bzm5SNa     
    
    
    On the Chi Square and Higher-Order Chi Distances for Approximating $f$ -Divergences http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/articleDetails.jsp?arnumber=6654274 … via @ieeexplore    
    
    
    Slides: On the Chi Square and Higher-Order Chi Distances for Approximating f-Divergences http://lnkd.in/b3gcKJZ     
    
    
    Slides: Hypothesis testing, information divergence and computational geometry http://lnkd.in/b2VY66U     
    
    
    Slides: Perspective click-and-drag area selections in pictures http://lnkd.in/bNz4VWB     
    
    
    360-video: Real-Time Spherical Videos from a Fast Rotating Camera http://lnkd.in/bH7FNUR     
    
    
    The dual Voronoi diagrams with respect to representational Bregman divergences (ISVD 2009) http://lnkd.in/bgJXZwA     
    
    
    2 laptops are better than 1 when travelling.    
    
    
    Simplifying Gaussian Mixture Models Via Entropic Quantization (EUSIPCO 2009) http://lnkd.in/bZiG_Bs     
    
    
    Information-Geometric Lenses for Multiple Foci   Contexts Interfaces http://lnkd.in/bmc-kNY     
    
    
    New draft: On conformal divergences and their population minimizers
http://lnkd.in/bB5ePcY 
robust clustering/non-extensive entropy    
    
    
    A glance at information-geometric signal processing http://lnkd.in/bVXMTfN     
    
    
    Pattern learning and recognition on statistical manifolds: An information-geometric review http://lnkd.in/bYDPyAZ     
    
    
    Japan has many old companies created before 800 still existing nowadays
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_oldest_companies …
amazing !    
    
    
    On Approximating the Smallest Enclosing Bregman Balls http://lnkd.in/btvKUsx     
    
    
    On the smallest enclosing information disk http://lnkd.in/bYKjkPs     
    
    
    Slides: On the Precision of Textures (MVA 2000, IEICE 2001) http://lnkd.in/bD3P69D     
    
    
    All geometries are imaginaries, including the 'familiar' Euclidean geometry!    
    
    
    Projecting Computer Graphics on Moving Surfaces: A Simple Calibration and Tracking Method , Sketch & Applications, N…http://lnkd.in/bc2VvTc     
    
    
    Slides: The Centroids of Symmetrized Bregman Divergences http://lnkd.in/bpidHzk     
    
    
    Matrix information geometry, computational geometry on matrix manifolds
http://lnkd.in/b4c2XeW     
    
    
    Cluster histograms using symmetrical Kullback-Leibler divergence (SKL)? Get the tutorial in language R: http://lnkd.in/dJsNNz9     
    
    
    Slides: Logging safely in public spaces using color PINs http://lnkd.in/b7dMa88     
    
    
    Searching high-dimensional neighbors: CPU-based tailored data-structures versus GPU-based brute-force method (MIRAGE…http://lnkd.in/b-HDAVn     
    
    
    Dreams... The digital chameleon principle: Computing invisibility by rendering transparency:
http://lnkd.in/bqHJVbH     
    
    
    Simplifying Gaussian Mixture Models Via Entropic Quantization (EUSIPCO 2009) http://lnkd.in/byMDaYs     
    
    
    Intuitive perspective selection in images. Interactive techniques and computational photography! http://lnkd.in/bhHj4Ww     
    
    
    K-nearest neighbor search:Fast GPU-based implementations and application to high-dimensional feature matching http://lnkd.in/bBt3H5V     
    
    
    ClickRemoval: interactive pinpoint image object removal 
http://lnkd.in/bX8seS3     
    
    
    Good bye POP3, Hello IMAP !!    
    
    
    Some cherry trees in Japan have over 2000 years...
http://www.yamanashi-kankou.jp/foreign/english/spot/022.html    
    
    
    Hagfishes have 4 hearts and 2 brains. Nature is amazing. Redundancy and fault-tolerant... Next human evolution?    
    
    
    It is getting hot in tokyo without air conditioning...    
    
    
    Sharp 3D technology:
http://www.c3technologies.com/    
    
    
    Temperatures in Tokyo are varying a lot! What a dynamic atmospheric system!    
    
    
    Finished reading Paul Allen memoir, idea man.  Nicely written, sensitive, human, and inspiring. He mentioned even "computational geometry"    
    
    
    Amazing Linux in browser. http://bellard.org/jslinux/
We have made incredible progress since Altair BASIC!!!    
    
    
    Everybody agrees that the true circle does not exist in the physical world.
So why should a formula perfectly describes reality.    
    
    
    TEDxTokyo was spontaneously refreshing. Miraikan is a nice place to visit too    
    
    
    One of the big news is to know that the electron may be a perfect sphere... Platon world finally? 
http://lnkd.in/CwcxDE    
    
    
    Yesterday, I played with Rubik cube. Long time I did not complete it. Always fun to do, even with the formula..    
    
    
    A bit blazy in Tokyo. But summer time is nearing! Cloud computing is a  necessity, not a hype...    
    
    
    Nature of randomness is one of the most puzzling question.  No wonder information theory focus on it.    
    
    
    Video stems from the latin verb "videre". Video="I see". Same for audio coming from Latin "audire"... Etymology explains it all!    
    
    
    Flying   ball: era of spherical bots coming soon...
http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/mv/wbs/trend_tamago/post_2124/    
    
    
    So many people work in statistics, but does randomness truly exists. Does God plays with dice?
Chaos is deterministic.    
    
    
    Complexity from simplicity : Chaos
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vHHfFnVGyFc …    
    
    
    ICCV 2011 papers on the web - Changelog http://lnkd.in/yk2xnA    
    
    
    It doesn't matter how beautiful your theory is, it doesn't matter how smart you are. If it doesn't agree with experiment, it's wrong/Feynman    
    
    
    I have always problems spelling statistical distances. Bhattacharyya is with 2 t and 2 y
http://bit.ly/iZfLZ    
    
    
    A library for string metrics http://www.dcs.shef.ac.uk/~sam/stringmetrics.html  face all the same problem which one for which applications!    
    
    
    Kameo Matusita also studied Hellinger metric...    
    
    
    They are really famous people in the world. Some of them did not even know it. -:) look at
http://www.linkedin.com/pub/dir/Shannon/Jensen/    
    
    
    One geometry cannot be more true than another: it can only be more convenient
Poincaré    
    
    
    Legendre transformation preserves homogeneous functions. Scaling property http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Legendre_transformation    
    
    
    Kinetic Data Structures: Animating Proofs Through Time. Symposium on Computational Geometry 1999: 427-428    
    
    
    Seems we go for some rain in Tokyo today...    
    
    
    I confirm it is raining now... !    
    
    
    Ok, I download Haskell. Have a try on functional programming. Remember the good old days at school. There was the exam then...    
    
    
    Long time I did not use a currency converter. They are web 2.0 now. Great.
http://finance.yahoo.com/currency-converter/    
    
    
    Japanese figure skater Mao Asada Mao-chan got a medal at the Olympic games. Unfortunate it was not the gold.    
    
    
    Neat and elegant. 
The Bhattacharyya Metric as an Absolute Similarity Measure for Frequency Coded Data    
    
    
    Went to the the expo at Shibuya. It is great! 
 http://imposs.ible.jp/events/20100226/    
    
    
    Impossible objects such as 2d drawn Penrose triangle are just possible shadows of 3D objects.. I like this concept very much. Post Magritte    
    
    
    There are african female mouses which are XY. Nature is fascinating. Human is trying to categorize things...    
    
    
    Haskell Curry is one of the greatest logician.* Both* his first and last names were used for functional progamming languages. what a legacy!    
    
    
    John McCarthy coined the term "Artificial intelligence " in 1963. We have been a long way since then.    
    
    
    Prokhorov metric, Levy metric two good probabiliy metrics...    
    
    
    I posted on my blog.informationgeometry.org, 
Bhattacharyya matrices and Cramer-Rao lower bounds    
    
    
    Sankhya: one of the six leading systems of Hindu philosophy, stressing the reality and duality of spirit and matter    
    
    
    I am reading proof of the Weiszefeld iterations for approximating the Fermat-Weber point. Many papers were wrong and add corrigendum!!!    
    
    
    Tonight, I play futsal outdoor. Is that futnotsal?    
    
    
    PNAS has amazing article quality, but very different writing style from usual CS conferences.    
    
    
    I am using more and more Mendely to get Bibtex entries. Good!    
    
    
    What is mathematics?: an elementary approach to ideas and methods    
    
    
    Is graphics finally mature for the web. WebGL is so far the best way
http://lnkd.in/YBu4JH    
    
    
    I like terminology. Well-behaved function. What does it really mean...    
    
    
    Yesterday it snowed in Tokyo. It was pretty cold and slippery! (and I was sleepy too!) Snowflakes are nice for dreaming!    
    
    
    Levy processes and brownian processes. Statistical modeling and stock ticks... fascinating topics.    
    
    
    I would like airbag for the jet fly pack. Amazing!!
http://bit.ly/dtWN0B    
    
    
    I began using Java Processing language. That is great!    
    
    
    There are some people who look more androids than android.  That is good. There is hope for androids looking more human than human...    
    
    
    Enum does not work in processing. Why not?    
    
    
    I like programming because not only it gives intuition but also it shows our mathematical proof flaws when writing papers...    
    
    
    embedding, immersion, isometric embedding...    
    
    
    Poetic reality...    
    
    
    Playstation Move. I remember siggraph emerging technologies, ten years or more ago. that is the time span between R&D&B    
    
    
    Bertrand Russell is confusing me. Are we all doing tautology in research?    
    
    
    I need to fight entropy in my desktop!    
    
    
    The Normal Inverse Gaussian Levy Process
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K6VDzJ2Vijs
We live in a stochastic reality?    
    
    
    Brownian motions, Ito integrals, the late Kiyosi ITO:
http://www.academie-sciences.fr/membres/I/Ito_Kiyosi.htm    
    
    
    One day, I need to be fluent in chinese. They are exciting stuff going...
http://www.nsfc.gov.cn/Portal0/default124.htm    
    
    
    Ellison started selling Oracle II. There was never Oracle I. It was a trick to show product maturity.... that is smart    
    
    
    The personal life of Nash who the nobel prize is incredible... Check wikipedia
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/John_Forbes_Nash,_Jr.    
    
    
    Jensen inequality... only 100 years old... Consciousness of math....    
    
    
    I saw the Ootoya dalton at lunch... Always great    
    
    
    clear blue skies in Tokyo!    
    
    
    Gomboc geometry is fascinating...
http://www.gomboc.eu/     
    
    
    Theil income inequality....    
    
    
    Adicity is not acidity. dyadicity is binaricity,... like a poem.    
    
    
    Taxonomy of principal distances
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/index.php    
    
    
    They are people who bear really amazing names... Shannon Fisher...
http://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/geneticmedicine/People/Faculty/fisher.html    
    
    
    bisymmetry of means. very nice!    
    
    
    Additive and non-additive entropy with java source code:
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/    
    
    
    Inifnite set can be in 1to1 correspondence with proper subsets. And without contradiction Yes,but when we think twice we are always puzzled    
    
    
    A set S is  infinite iff.there exists a proper subset
of S which has the same cardinality as S.
(e.g., the integers and the even integers)    
    
    
    Crazy transparent fish head: http://lnkd.in/in65_U     
    
    
    space of rotations and the miracle of geometric conformal embedding...    
    
    
    360 degrees jigsaw (puzzles)
http://www.mindagame.com/jpp/jeudepuzzle.php
Technology brings us there!    
    
    
    Procrustes refers to a bandit from Greek mythology who made his victims fit his bed either by stretching their limbs or cutting them off.    
    
    
    PlanetMath is great!    
    
    
    Take the quizz !!!!
http://www.informationgeometry.org/informationtheoreticdistances.html    
    
    
    Think about things. That is mathematics!    
    
    
    Do animal do mathematics?    
    
    
    Another ranking
http://lnkd.in/2yWqPW     
    
    
    Constantin Carathéodory (or Constantine Karatheodori)  was greek but with an accent in his name... That is not so intuitive...    
    
    
    New mailing list: infogeo for information geometry
http://www.informationgeometry.org/mailman/listinfo/infogeo    
    
    
    I have released the second quizz on information geometry:
http://blog.informationgeometry.org/index.php    
    
    
    Towars a better understanding of reality? Breaking the celerity limit, or the strange speed of neutrinos...  http://lnkd.in/UiV5pd     
    
    
    Computable reals are of measure zero in the set of reals. Fortunately, we got PI, sqrt(2) ! How lucky!    
    
    
    Humanoid wife...
http://www.is.sys.es.osaka-u.ac.jp/development/0006/mpeg/ReplieeQ2DemoFace.mpg    
    
    
    Four-Dimensional Electron Microscopy...    
    
    
    New mailing list on information geometry:
http://www.informationgeometry.org/mailman/listinfo/infogeo    
    
    
    The Burbea-Rao and Bhattacharyya centroids    
    
    
    Subscribe to the international mailing list on information geometry at informationgeometry.org    
    
    
    Happy new year to all of you. I recommend reading the book
The Tibetan Book of Living and Dying. It is inspiring. Science and spirituality.    
    
    
    Faster than the FFT, with sparsity! 
http://web.mit.edu/newsoffice/2012/faster-fourier-transforms-0118.html …    
    
    
    Pacman is NP-hard. http://www.technologyreview.com/blog/arxiv/27528/?p1=blogs …    
    
    
    Winter time... time to watch videos. Here is a recommendation: FOCS video:http://techtalks.tv/focs/2010/    
    
    
    What is neat with research is when you find how simple seemingly complex things are!    
    
    
    8 million degrees bursts from the sun... into the cold 0.K space. What a fantastic universe!    
    
    
    What is the "best" OO language nowadays beating Ruby with Mixins... ?!? http://lnkd.in/iMagJs  http://lnkd.in/Gw68vr     
    
    
    Science is idealizing the ungraspable world. Modeling is loosing information... The gap will always be.    
    
    
    I read that more than 200 000 planes/day go over USA. It is crazy world. I like figures that strike you. Is it common sense...?    
    
    
    Matrix Information Geometry almost there! http://www.springer.com/engineering/signals/book/978-3-642-30231-2 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Geometry and Experience, 
http://lnkd.in/hSkkdY     
    
    
    Incommensurate structures in nature are fascinating...    
    
    
    Ipe version 7 is out. It supports many SVG-like functionalities. 
http://bit.ly/by8vnF    
    
    
    I have uploaded a video on an old work
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xde8wAJquU4
using the same system, we could get 360 stereo videos.    
    
    
    3D movies and previsualization;
http://lnkd.in/4mhGf5     
    
    
    In Java, you can force garbage collector with System.gc();
It was effective for my problem today -:)    
    
    
    Used tag 5793b870  to disambiguate myself from the Nielsen Frank in future.
http://lnkd.in/KRbPhH 
ORCID http://about.o…http://lnkd.in/ft537m     
    
    
    Lego danish company is  pushing market. I recently tried their digital box, and my kids liked it. http://bit.ly/9habic    
    
    
    I think it is good kids play with VR and cybercode-inspired technology.    
    
    
    Did you know fewnomial theory, algebraic results for polynomials with few monomials? Quite interesting line of work.    
    
    
    Processing language is fun, but processing name is not discriminatory enough for searching. Hence, type tricky proce55ing !    
    
    
    I updated http://www.informationgeometry.org/    
    
    
    Nice to see that my blog is listed in 
http://www.mastersincomputerscience.net/top-50-computer-science-blogs.html    
    
    
    Amazing reading: Science Without Numbers: A Defence of Nominalism by
Hartry H. Field    
    
    
    Yet another inspiring book by one of the greatest geometrician!
Geometry Revealed: A Jacob's Ladder to Modern Higher Geometry    
    
    
    The value of philosophy for scientists...
http://www.ditext.com/russell/rus15.html    
    
    
    @sowd Shigeru, your son develops biz. skills -:) as my son does-:) A Difference with girls when they are young. Curious to read stats about!    
    
    
    Equivocation: ambiguity arising from the misleading use of a word    
    
    
    Three-body problem has an exact analytic solution since 1909 (Sundman)... why is there such a common myth -:) http://www.scholarpedia.org/article/Three_body_problem …    
    
    
    Enormous problem: classification. In search of structures. 1200+ page proof...
http://lnkd.in/y7WBDP     
    
    
    Computer etymology stems from com (together) + putare (trim), French origin. but in French  ordinator (“one who orders”) is computer !-:)    
    
    
    A nice principle for abstraction is the abduction! Check wikipedia. I reason this way someties...    
    
    
    Shannon paper has been retyped with Tex source -:)
http://cm.bell-labs.com/cm/ms/what/shannonday/paper.html    
    
    
    Algorithmic trading is over 50% in the biz i recently learnt. Within 25 years, I wonder how much information geometry in it!!!    
    
    
    Volume graphics = future of CG, same as color was the future of grey. http://www-ui.is.s.u-tokyo.ac.jp/~kenshi/DiffusionSurfaces/index.html    
    
    
    Matrix information geometry book:
http://lnkd.in/hn6A-P     
    
    
    Matrix Information Geometry http://www.springer.com/engineering/signals/book/978-3-642-30231-2 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Recently in the US, I was asked my ID to buy beer, but today I try some software with face recognition that indicated age probability: 50!!!    
    
    
    Typhoon came today close to Tokyo. It was quite rainy... and humid...    
    
    
    Adobe labs have synthesized some of their conference technologies at 
http://www.adobe.com/technology/ 
Harmonizing presentation is nice    
    
    
    The 18th century was a world without Jehttp://www.springerlink.com/content/r55q1411g840j446/nsen inequality. I wonder how!!!    
    
    
    A Concise and Practical Introduction to Programming Algorithms in Java http://www.springer.com/computer/swe/book/978-1-84882-338-9 … via @twitterapi    
    
    
    Stephen Wolfram: Computing a theory of everything at TED:
http://www.ted.com/talks/stephen_wolfram_computing_a_theory_of_everything.html    
    
    
    Judo@Tokyo 2010. The gold medals are amazingly won by Japanese showing a strong art in the country. France has its chance today...    
    
    
    Read that Google research, after Zurich,  is setting some structure in France.    
    
    
    Digging articles in library make u feel a bit historian. Always good to go to physical library!    
    
    
    Poincare was a fine philosopher as well. Every nice writings:
http://www.ac-nancy-metz.fr/enseign/philo/textesph/Dernierespensees.pdf    
    
    
    An amazing video of computer science/vision in action for extreme piloting of helicopter:    
    
    
    Try saving a presentation pdf as con.pdf in windows... -:) !    
    
    
    Science = Reversing Reality...    
    
    
    Dual view and 3D by means of parallax barrier. Great!
http://lnkd.in/iiMzzJ    
    
    
    GSI2013 - Geometric Science of Information in Paris! http://www.gsi2013.org/     
    
    
    Prof Vaclav Skala gave a nice overview why projective geometry is useful in CG.
dot and cross are GPU instructions.
http://www.vaclavskala.eu/     
    
    
    In action
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RujA9V4CGqs&feature=colike …
at the poster session of SIG ASIA    
    
    
    A Concise and Practical Introduction to Programming Algorithms in Java http://lnkd.in/Y7MTd5     
    
    
    Precursor usage of Computational geometry: Perceptrons: An Introduction to Computational Geometry by Minsky and Papert, back to 1969!    
    
    
    Shannon was a student of Vannevar Bush, father of the memex vision  ! http://lnkd.in/-ApRbE     
    
    
    An Information-Geometric Characterization of Chernoff Information http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/articleDetails.jsp?arnumber=6423793 … via @ieeexplore    
    
    
    Poincare wisely said: "One geometry cannot be more true than another; it can only be more convenient. " Ultimate knowledge = illusion quest    
    
    
    Did you know sedonion numbers?
http://lnkd.in/NEihpt 
Can build googlenion numbers too -:)!    
    
    
    In IT, KL means Kullback-Leibler . Today I went to kiddy land and took their catalogue KL... Acronyms and context! -:)    
    
    
    Human language uses the duality operator: anti-derivative and anti-fragility are two such examples!    
    
    
    Amazing computing device from 2000 years ago:
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RLPVCJjTNgk    
    
    
    Many typings for Occam's principle. Like Ockham. Maybe Okam should be best -:)    
    
    
    If you like Bayes error analysis, you need these latex notations: $
\mathop{\gtreqless}^{C_1}_{C_2}
\quad
\mathop{\lesseqgtr}^{C_1}_{C_2}
$    
    
    
    Infinity is the melting pot: Infinitely many coverings of a same infinite space by inf. subspaces Structures = chosen for convenience?    
    
    
    Using computer algebra systems to crunch formula. I discovered a bug in Wolfram Mathematica(R). We need to have certifications of formula!!!    
    
    
    Nearing HAL 9000 in 2001: A Space Odyssey with brainwave authentification!
http://lnkd.in/cTUS-R     
    
    
    Guess who received the Nobel Laureate, the Turing Award and was inducted ACM Fellow...
http://lnkd.in/6Q_Uuv     
    
    
    List of siggraph accepted papers is available on-line: many sections of CG!    
    
    
    Clustering histograms a la k-means. Yes, but what distance? Which centroid?
Jeffreys divergence! http://lnkd.in/csdyvF     
    
    
    Logging safely in public spaces using color PINs 
http://lnkd.in/wA6g4m 
http://lnkd.in/PUT65V     
    
    
    Experiments with power diagrams... http://lnkd.in/csdyvF     
    
    
    Computing with high radiation doses in space.... http://lnkd.in/zmgWNN     
    
    
    Perspective click and drag selection in photos received the best practical paper award at MVA http://lnkd.in/5npwRA     
    
    
    Deep learning http://lnkd.in/34DJp3     
    
    
    Another deep learning: http://lnkd.in/FNhx_2 
...improvements in mathematical formulas...    
    
    
    How simple!  "matter tells Spacetime how to curve, and Spacetime tells matter how to move". Thanks Mr. John Wheeler. then egg and chicken...    
    
    
    C.R. Rao and information geometry http://lnkd.in/cDKV5Q     
    
    
    Time for Science to challenge as large as possible time problems, beyond climate prediction/sustainable issues? Beyond big data is big time!    
    
    
    Abel impossibility theorem of degree 5 polynomial original proof in a mere 7 pages.
http://lnkd.in/DYEA6r     
    
    
    Did you know that it is Arthur Cayley that in 1855 introduced matrices and its algebra? http://lnkd.in/ftwSTp     
    
    
    Cn y rd txts wtht vwls?    
    
    
    Geometric Science of Information - First International Conference, GSI 2013, Paris, France, August http://www.springer.com/computer/image+processing/book/978-3-642-40019-3 … #springer    
    
    
    Scanning internet in 45 min on a single machine:
https://zmap.io/  need to check!    
    
    
    Strangely enough, the area of an ellipse is pi a b but the perimeter requires an infinite series to sum... Mysteries of nice formula...    
    
    
    Always good (!!!) to look at roots of core concepts like Taylor series in 1715: Visualize the original formula: …http://lnkd.in/bV9VNrm     
    
    
    Calculating chi square amd approximating f-divergences using Taylor expansions  #infogeo
http://lnkd.in/b7vTHmx     
    
    
    List of computer vision papers accepted at ICCV: http://lnkd.in/b-c2x4J     
    
    
    We are heading for the Indo-French workshop on Matrix Information Geometries:
http://lnkd.in/E4ucg6    
    
    
    Siggraph Asia tech brief program is out!
 http://lnkd.in/bKkFqBu  http://lnkd.in/bPE5-C3     
    
    
    BNF for Java: write your own language:
http://lnkd.in/zNEj5R    
    
    
    Total Jensen divergences: Definition, Properties
and k-Means   Clustering http://lnkd.in/bhDRx8Y     
    
    
    Revisiting space zooming techniques for enriched context focus  interfaces:
http://lnkd.in/b4sb5KH     
    
    
    Posted a blog note on image segmentation that keeps improving with time:
http://lnkd.in/bC4umYE 
SRM->Consensus Region Merging    
    
    
    Matrix information geometries
http://lnkd.in/E4ucg6    
    
    
    Geat! Information geometry and Fisher information matrix in Science magazine... 
http://lnkd.in/byDK2n2     
    
    
    A family of statistical symmetric divergences based on Jensen's inequality http://lnkd.in/bbxGRTv     
    
    
    Great work: Information Theoretical Estimators (ITE) Toolbox 
http://lnkd.in/bhYEehP 
Need more software/tutorials on those topics!    
    
    
    Another affine exponential family are multinomials of course... http://lnkd.in/bRfHgTY  
The letter appears brushed …http://lnkd.in/bzm5SNa     
    
    
    On the Chi Square and Higher-Order Chi Distances for Approximating $f$ -Divergences http://ieeexplore.ieee.org/xpl/articleDetails.jsp?arnumber=6654274 … via @ieeexplore    
    
    
    Slides: On the Chi Square and Higher-Order Chi Distances for Approximating f-Divergences http://lnkd.in/b3gcKJZ     
    
    
    Slides: Hypothesis testing, information divergence and computational geometry http://lnkd.in/b2VY66U     
    
    
    Slides: Perspective click-and-drag area selections in pictures http://lnkd.in/bNz4VWB     
    
    
    360-video: Real-Time Spherical Videos from a Fast Rotating Camera http://lnkd.in/bH7FNUR     
    
    
    The dual Voronoi diagrams with respect to representational Bregman divergences (ISVD 2009) http://lnkd.in/bgJXZwA     
    
    
    2 laptops are better than 1 when travelling.    
    
    
    Simplifying Gaussian Mixture Models Via Entropic Quantization (EUSIPCO 2009) http://lnkd.in/bZiG_Bs     
    
    
    Information-Geometric Lenses for Multiple Foci   Contexts Interfaces http://lnkd.in/bmc-kNY     
    
    
    New draft: On conformal divergences and their population minimizers
http://lnkd.in/bB5ePcY 
robust clustering/non-extensive entropy    
    
    
    A glance at information-geometric signal processing http://lnkd.in/bVXMTfN     
    
    
    Pattern learning and recognition on statistical manifolds: An information-geometric review http://lnkd.in/bYDPyAZ     
    
    
    Japan has many old companies created before 800 still existing nowadays
http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_oldest_companies …
amazing !    
    
    
    On Approximating the Smallest Enclosing Bregman Balls http://lnkd.in/btvKUsx     
    
    
    On the smallest enclosing information disk http://lnkd.in/bYKjkPs     
    
    
    Slides: On the Precision of Textures (MVA 2000, IEICE 2001) http://lnkd.in/bD3P69D     
    
    
    All geometries are imaginaries, including the 'familiar' Euclidean geometry!    
    
    
    Projecting Computer Graphics on Moving Surfaces: A Simple Calibration and Tracking Method , Sketch & Applications, N…http://lnkd.in/bc2VvTc     
    
    
    Slides: The Centroids of Symmetrized Bregman Divergences http://lnkd.in/bpidHzk     
    
    
    Matrix information geometry, computational geometry on matrix manifolds
http://lnkd.in/b4c2XeW     
    
    
    Cluster histograms using symmetrical Kullback-Leibler divergence (SKL)? Get the tutorial in language R: http://lnkd.in/dJsNNz9     
    
    
    Slides: Logging safely in public spaces using color PINs http://lnkd.in/b7dMa88     
    
    
    Searching high-dimensional neighbors: CPU-based tailored data-structures versus GPU-based brute-force method (MIRAGE…http://lnkd.in/b-HDAVn     
    
    
    Dreams... The digital chameleon principle: Computing invisibility by rendering transparency:
http://lnkd.in/bqHJVbH     
    
    
    Simplifying Gaussian Mixture Models Via Entropic Quantization (EUSIPCO 2009) http://lnkd.in/byMDaYs     
    
    
    Intuitive perspective selection in images. Interactive techniques and computational photography! http://lnkd.in/bhHj4Ww     
    
    
    K-nearest neighbor search:Fast GPU-based implementations and application to high-dimensional feature matching http://lnkd.in/bBt3H5V     
    
    
    ClickRemoval: interactive pinpoint image object removal 
http://lnkd.in/bX8seS3     
    
    
    Good bye POP3, Hello IMAP !!    
    
    
    Some cherry trees in Japan have over 2000 years...
http://www.yamanashi-kankou.jp/foreign/english/spot/022.html    
    
    
    Hagfishes have 4 hearts and 2 brains. Nature is amazing. Redundancy and fault-tolerant... Next human evolution?    
    
    
    It is getting hot in tokyo without air conditioning...    
    
    
    Sharp 3D technology:
http://www.c3technologies.com/    
    
    
    Temperatures in Tokyo are varying a lot! What a dynamic atmospheric system!    
    
    
    Finished reading Paul Allen memoir, idea man.  Nicely written, sensitive, human, and inspiring. He mentioned even "computational geometry"    
    
    
    Amazing Linux in browser. http://bellard.org/jslinux/
We have made incredible progress since Altair BASIC!!!    
    
    
    Everybody agrees that the true circle does not exist in the physical world.
So why should a formula perfectly describes reality.    
    
    
    TEDxTokyo was spontaneously refreshing. Miraikan is a nice place to visit too    
    
    
    One of the big news is to know that the electron may be a perfect sphere... Platon world finally? 
http://lnkd.in/CwcxDE    
    
    
    Yesterday, I played with Rubik cube. Long time I did not complete it. Always fun to do, even with the formula..    
    
    
    A bit blazy in Tokyo. But summer time is nearing! Cloud computing is a  necessity, not a hype...    
    
    
    Nature of randomness is one of the most puzzling question.  No wonder information theory focus on it.    
    
    
    Video stems from the latin verb "videre". Video="I see". Same for audio coming from Latin "audire"... Etymology explains it all!    
    
    
    Flying   ball: era of spherical bots coming soon...
http://www.tv-tokyo.co.jp/mv/wbs/trend_tamago/post_2124/    
    
    
    So many people work in statistics, but does randomness truly exists. Does God plays with dice?
Chaos is deterministic.    
    
    
    Complexity from simplicity : Chaos
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vHHfFnVGyFc …    
    
    
    ICCV 2011 papers on the web - Changelog http://lnkd.in/yk2xnA    
    
    
    It doesn't matter how beautiful your theory is, it doesn't matter how smart you are. If it doesn't agree with experiment, it's wrong/Feynman    
    
    
    I have always problems spelling statistical distances. Bhattacharyya is with 2 t and 2 y
http://bit.ly/iZfLZ    
    
    
    A library for string metrics http://www.dcs.shef.ac.uk/~sam/stringmetrics.html  face all the same problem which one for which applications!    
    
    
    Kameo Matusita also studied Hellinger metric...    
    
    
    They are really famous people in the world. Some of them did not even know it. -:) look at
http://www.linkedin.com/pub/dir/Shannon/Jensen/    
    
    
    One geometry cannot be more true than another: it can only be more convenient
Poincaré    
    
    
    Legendre transformation preserves homogeneous functions. Scaling property http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Legendre_transformation    
    
    
    Kinetic Data Structures: Animating Proofs Through Time. Symposium on Computational Geometry 1999: 427-428    
    
    
    Seems we go for some rain in Tokyo today...    
    
    
    I confirm it is raining now... !    
    
    
    Ok, I download Haskell. Have a try on functional programming. Remember the good old days at school. There was the exam then...    
    
    
    Long time I did not use a currency converter. They are web 2.0 now. Great.
http://finance.yahoo.com/currency-converter/    
    
    
    Japanese figure skater Mao Asada Mao-chan got a medal at the Olympic games. Unfortunate it was not the gold.    
    
    
    Neat and elegant. 
The Bhattacharyya Metric as an Absolute Similarity Measure for Frequency Coded Data    
    
    
    Went to the the expo at Shibuya. It is great! 
 http://imposs.ible.jp/events/20100226/    
    
    
    Impossible objects such as 2d drawn Penrose triangle are just possible shadows of 3D objects.. I like this concept very much. Post Magritte    
    
    
    There are african female mouses which are XY. Nature is fascinating. Human is trying to categorize things...    
    
    
    Haskell Curry is one of the greatest logician.* Both* his first and last names were used for functional progamming languages. what a legacy!    
    
    
    John McCarthy coined the term "Artificial intelligence " in 1963. We have been a long way since then.    
    
    
    Prokhorov metric, Levy metric two good probabiliy metrics...    
    
    
    I posted on my blog.informationgeometry.org, 
Bhattacharyya matrices and Cramer-Rao lower bounds    
    
    
    Sankhya: one of the six leading systems of Hindu philosophy, stressing the reality and duality of spirit and matter    
    
    
    I am reading proof of the Weiszefeld iterations for approximating the Fermat-Weber point. Many papers were wrong and add corrigendum!!!    
    
    
    Tonight, I play futsal outdoor. Is that futnotsal?    
    
    
    PNAS has amazing article quality, but very different writing style from usual CS conferences.    
    
    
    I am using more and more Mendely to get Bibtex entries. Good!    
    
    
    What is mathematics?: an elementary approach to ideas and methods    
    
    
    