The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @specialreports @DianaUrban    
    
    
    Just stumbled on this. Thanks for the shout @jdlasica!! Hope you're well. http://is.gd/fVVbHJ  #BetterLateThanNever http://lnkd.in/EbbB9q     
    
    
    Ex-Packer says #NFL hoping retirees die off http://espn.go.com/nfl/story/_/id/9442146/ex-green-bay-packers-te-gary-knafelc-says-nfl-hoping-retirees-die-off …    
    
    
    HAHAHA RT @NeinQuarterly The #NSA walks into a bar, orders a beer. Bartender: "Domestic or imported?" NSA: "What's the difference?"    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @HarvardAlumni    
    
    
    This place is a great. Met a surgeon / community doctor who blew my mind. And the, of course there's Marat, an ins... http://4sq.com/15eUGvG     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @getunreal    
    
    
    Hahah. I mean Jajajaja ... Costa Rica Accidentally Approves Same-Sex Unions: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cSqGpW     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @karabaic    
    
    
    USA! USA! USA! (@ Jaleo) http://4sq.com/13vwvtJ     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @robpegoraro @eclisham    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @NationalsReport @acomak @Jason    
    
    
    Who Should Stop Writing About Egypt Today?: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cZFGTd     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @patriotledger    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @shawnmullin    
    
    
    "Evil will always win because good is dumb." Bin Laden Report Details How Al Qaeda Leader Evaded Capture In Pakistan http://huff.to/1aVob9I     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LaurieP    
    
    
    Now playing: Cuts You Up by Peter Murphy. I love coming here ... (at @Floyds99 Barbershop) http://4sq.com/14Hb2Ms     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    House Republicans Have A New Problem With Immigration Reform: Obama: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1b12BAG     
    
    
    Random meeting on bus w/ a former hospital client this am who said she was "proud" to work w/ Genuine Interactive. Good start to the day.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @acomak    
    
    
    US Government Records $116.5 Billion Surplus In June: via HuffPost http://huff.to/155RRuP     
    
    
    "Thank You! Your 1-Click order has been placed." is one of my favorite phrases ever.    
    
    
    .RT @aayers324 "On Second thought I can see how NC got confused on this one" #vaginamotorcycle pic.twitter.com/fnPo2g8NnH    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    .@karenxcheng is my new hero  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=daC2EPUh22w&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    I have never had a glass of milk. This makes me feel better ... Got Proof? Lack of Evidence for Milk's Benefits http://huff.to/1dmkpmC     
    
    
    I feel like Summer's Eve missed its "Oreo moment" with the #Texas legislature Friday. "How many DBs does it take to ..." and solicit tweets.    
    
    
    .RT @perryhewitt: Is LinkedIn “silently drawing what might be the first global economic graph”? http://buff.ly/1dqzS5k     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @kailanikm    
    
    
    I turn 40 soon. Amazed at how forward & backward we've come as a country in that time. If this was a car, the transmission would be toast.    
    
    
    Florida, go to your room.    
    
    
    The only solace I am taking in the #TrayvonMartin #ZimmermanTrial outcome is that I have Dave Chappelle tickets.    
    
    
    Never a bad time here ... (@ Toad w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/12x2mZL     
    
    
    Tonight is a good reminder of the difference between innocent and not guilty.    
    
    
    "Stoned cavemen" I needed to hear those words today. Now Barney Rubble's laugh takes on a whole new meaning. http://www.salon.com/2013/07/14/were_cave_men_high_on_psychedelic_drugs_partner/ …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    I'm at Shakespeare on the Common - @commshakes (Boston, MA) w/ 20 others http://4sq.com/1dym5JV     
    
    
    It's fixin' to be really "hot" in #Boston today. So cute. Where's my not-iced coffee?    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @GloPan    
    
    
    Blame States For Not Expanding Medicaid, Obama Administration Will Tell Poor Residents: via HuffPost http://huff.to/13KKsWc     
    
    
    Stem Cell Tracking Made Possible With Common Anemia Drug At Stanford: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bhBGAV     
    
    
    The best thing I think I'll see on the Series of Tubes today ... http://lnkd.in/b-mKnM     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @Innovationepoch @dansinker @HarvardAlumni    
    
    
    http://www.bethesdamagazine.com/Bethesda-Magazine/March-April-2013/Television-Wheaton/ … Yea, my hometown of Wheaton, Md. is also home of the first licensed TV station. Good read.    
    
    
    Love watching @elizabethforma on CNBC. Teacher teach, teach them well ... http://www.upworthy.com/cnbc-hosts-decided-to-teach-senator-warren-how-regulation-works-probably-shouldnt-have-done-that …    
    
    
    Thanks @DavidGewirtz 4 days into my S4, & now with my dual battery charger, I feel unstoppable. Enjoy yours http://www.zdnet.com/ios-7-why-im-finally-dumping-my-iphone-for-an-android-7000017123/?part=taboola&ttag=taboola_zdnet_ros … #Android    
    
    
    High socks on baseball players is one of my favorite things in sports #mlb    
    
    
    @mallarytenore but, but it's scary to talk to girls.  Or something.    
    
    
    For perspective, Mariano Rivera has been saving games since before almost everyone had an email account.  #asg #mlb #bowdown    
    
    
    Bob Filner Responds To Sexual Harassment Allegations: 'I'm A Hugger': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bmjINI     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Elizabeth Warren: Student Loan Profits 'Morally Wrong': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dFpxCz     
    
    
    Rolling Stone Did Nothing Wrong: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dFvSxM     
    
    
    +1 rt @cshirky A prescient post from last yr: "Big Data is our generation’s civil rights issue, and we don’t know it" http://goo.gl/z5KcY     
    
    
    Oakland Cafe Has Amazing Response To Broken Window After Zimmerman Protests: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dG7CLX     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LEBassett    
    
    
    So sad ... That Awkward Moment When The Tea Party Rally Gets Overtly Racist http://huff.to/1dHGBrB     
    
    
    I *might* be that guy up here RT @TheOnion: Heat Wave Doesn't Bother Local Contrarian http://onion.com/13nFWd3     
    
    
    http://mobile.nytimes.com/2013/07/21/magazine/jack-handey-is-the-envy-of-every-comedy-writer-in-america.html?pagewanted=all& … Jack Handey Is the Envy of Every Comedy Writer in America    
    
    
    Wimps. @elizabethforma's Takedown Of CNBC Removed From YouTube: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dIePes     
    
    
    Saw a dude parallel park next to a hydrant, maneuver to get out around it then look dumbfounded when I said "Don't think you can park there"    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Ever wish you could tag a few of your #LinkedIn contacts as "meh" because, well, you know ...    
    
    
    "I'd take their bb shots to the face if it meant I could look these ppl in the eye while I beat the shit out of 'em" http://imgur.com/a/VxOqG     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @perryhewitt    
    
    
    Just beautiful... Open Letter to My Daughter, the Camper: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bvl88t     
    
    
    Wow has it really been a week since a Florida jury decided I could really use a drink right about now?    
    
    
    To my #boston friends, what 1 or 2 must see / must eat tips to you have for first-time visitors?    
    
    
    Inspired by this piece by @scottkirsner Bose’s greatest innovation may be his company http://www.bostonglobe.com/business/2013/07/20/bose-greatest-innovation-may-his-company/ARdTMG37pvKAWHqhr7yu2O/story.html …    
    
    
    To not play tennis today after this heatwave would be a crime against the sport    
    
    
    Of all the things I love about living in #cambridge #ma the Saturday and Sunday #tennis meetups are among my favorites, even when I lose  ;)    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    John McCain: Arizona's Stand Your Ground Law Should Be Reviewed: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dNCoCG     
    
    
    @laurenfaith thanks Lauren. I'll note that with a shahhpey maahkah    
    
    
    @David_Boaz possibly the lamest false equivalency I have read this year. Methinks you should meet more Americans. Like non-wealthy ones.    
    
    
    In #boston when you're thinking to yourself 'WTF is going on" follow @universalhub ... like today for example.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @mallarytenore    
    
    
    RIP Dennis Farina. I've been a fan since NBC's Crime Story but I didn't take your advice, and I DID go to London a couple times.    
    
    
    @chrislhayes But wouldn't our country be so much better off if we held people who REALLY know math in a higher standing?    
    
    
    CBS vs. Time Warner Cable vs. You by @martykaplan http://www.huffingtonpost.com/marty-kaplan/cbs-vs-time-warner-cable-_b_3632160.html …    
    
    
    Feds Sue Florida Over Warehousing Kids With Disabilities In Nursing Homes: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dQggYs     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @mikeloukides    
    
    
    Oy. NSA Can't Search Its Own Emails http://huff.to/1dT6QLW  via @HuffPostPol    
    
    
    As a part-time CNN alum who started the day the Cold War ended, this really struck a nerve ... Is Dead, Long Live HBO http://huff.to/1dSat4y     
    
    
    #carlosdanger made my friend's flight 2 hours late ... (at @BostonLogan International Airport (BOS) w/ 65 others) http://4sq.com/14F0LTG     
    
    
    Fighting the urge to page #carlosdanger at Logan ...    
    
    
    @kldd210 my Spidey sense told me to not say "danger" -- even by proxy -- at an airport ...    
    
    
    As a Peruvian friend of mine says "Are you serious?!" House Republicans Fight Obama's 'War On Ceiling Fans' http://huff.to/1dUCxUV     
    
    
    Just got an Outlook reminder about a meeting that's 36(!) weeks overdue.  Way to help me start the day on a positive note. So confused ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @epharma @jdlasica @BarackObama    
    
    
    Amy Lord, former colleague @wearegenuine wrongfully taken from us, radiated positivity & soaked up knowledge. I'm so privileged to know her.    
    
    
    http://m.washingtonpost.com/blogs/the-fix/wp/2013/07/24/the-best-carlos-danger-tweets/ … #carlosdanger best of is teh awsum    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @alexwoodcreates    
    
    
    Blimps Over Washington: JLENS Brings Football-Field Sized Anti-Missile Aerostats To Spy On, Protect D.C: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dXG3Ov     
    
    
    Well done. The new Puritanism - When did liberals become so uptight? http://www.newrepublic.com/article/113632/oregon-fluoridation-proof-liberals-are-new-puritans … by @markopp1    
    
    
    Thinking of Amy Lord & a better world I'd like to see her passing make.  #idea: unique distress pin that alerts cops immediately. Thoughts?    
    
    
    @brittanylake agreed. Needs to be super sleuth. Something bad people  can't subvert. Like a silent alarm for customers. Banks can afford it.    
    
    
    @brittanylake thanks Brittany. Your endorsement counts for a whole lot in my book.    
    
    
    Sequestration Will Prevent Creation Of Up To 1.6 Million Jobs In Next Year, CBO Concludes: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bRUDKP     
    
    
    Jeremy Scahill Condemns White House Opposition To Freeing Of Abdulelah Haider Shaye (VIDEO): via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bRo2F0     
    
    
    A #Terp scientist might have discovered the cause of #beemageddon http://bit.ly/18DqDSB  http://lnkd.in/c5iyeS     
    
    
    @jdbasketball I thought I was gonna miss my train, but then I realized it's actually 10 minutes later than I thought. Inspired?    
    
    
    Just got invited to explain / describe my career in 300-400 words. Hmm, maybe I should try a few haikus?    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @ClevelandClinic @perryhewitt @greglinch    
    
    
    . @propstm "When the going gets weird, the weird turn pro." - HST    
    
    
    After a longer week than any of them deserved, it was really good to give some hugs to some of my @WeAreGenuine friends tonight.    
    
    
    #Maryland is teh awsum ...State Touts Lowest Obamacare Health Insurance Premiums Yet http://huff.to/1bWMvZj     
    
    
    Tension Between Journalists, Army Continues At Bradley Manning Trial: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bW40Jr     
    
    
    So messed up... Bananas Thrown At Black Italian Minister, Cecile Kyenge, During Speech: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1e20KJg     
    
    
    Holy crap! Anyone remember the Commodore CBM? I had one, wrote my first articles on it and just spotted one in @computer_chess last night!    
    
    
    Yes! RT @JohnLuginbill: So true: "Cynicism is fear posing as confidence; joy is hope springing into action." - @bobgoff    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @sgiunta6 @gregsantos    
    
    
    @libbycrews I smell a Foursquare tie-in. At least, I think that's what I smell.    
    
    
    @RunBritRun next time, answer "Pi."    
    
    
    KTVU Producer Fired Over Fake Pilot Names Says 'My Hard-Earned Reputation Is Intack': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dZQeC8  #doh    
    
    
    Pretty sure I just walked by the State Farm "can I get a hot tub" guy.    
    
    
    FPSRussia, One Of The Most Popular YouTube Channels Ever, Will Start Blowing Up Stuff Again: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bVjrSe     
    
    
    D'oh. Advil. #knewiforgotsomething    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @misschatter @GordonEdes @acomak    
    
    
    Love the youth telling the elders to grow up ... Young Republicans: GOP Must Make Substantive Changes: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1c2JA1k     
    
    
    Goal for the week: better understand this ... RT @daveying99: Twitter Bootstrap Now Powering 1% of The Web http://bit.ly/1e4d4Zs     
    
    
    Fincher kinda day: Started w/ giving a Harvard Sq. tour & giving a tip about Social Network filming then moved on to House of Cards. #hooked    
    
    
    Not to overstate it but #HouseofCards might end up being life changing for me.    
    
    
    In addition to my 4 PhDs I'm also, apparently, a preschool teacher ... https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X9S1XKooFMM&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Pro tip: Ensure your fancy pretty mobile app for your content-based site actually enables people to share content. #ifatreefallsintheforest    
    
    
    I really am digging the love affair between Congressman Soze and Princess Buttercup #HouseofCards    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Checking out a performance by my voice teacher, Jennifer Matthews ... come on by! (at @ZuZuBar) http://4sq.com/13qDRdh     
    
    
    Doubling McDonald's Salaries Would Cause Your Big Mac To Cost Just 68¢ More: Study: via HuffPost http://huff.to/153NnZk     
    
    
    Help me out: Where's the best slice of pizza in #DC? And if you say Pizza Mart, you're dead to me.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    My favorite message of the day: <br><h4>Reset Password Link sent.</h4>    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @wemedia @AdrienneLB @clickbrain    
    
    
    There was a shooting near Mass General Hospital today. http://bo.st/13ZI9M9  Suspect in custody. One officer shot. Sheesh. I'm fine.    
    
    
    Having a great birthday dinner! (at @Tangierino w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/168NJdY     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @patriotledger @baratunde @LaurenYoung    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @dabeard @PowerFlite    
    
    
    Taking the 4 bus through #Boston. Alone. In daylight. This is weird.    
    
    
    T-minus BECK!!! (@ Jerry Remy’s Sports Bar & Grill - @jerry_remys_sea w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/138U3QG     
    
    
    Google Glass should be a hat.    
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb thanks for the Beck ticket!!!    
    
    
    EXCLUSIVE: #boston #bruins mascot dude caught dancing at #beck concert??!?!?!?! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nD5OspWcw54&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Blaming the dryer for lost socks really lets the washer off the hook ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @SullivanTire    
    
    
    Chillin' with the TomTom club ... #whattheygonnadowhentheygetouttajail (@ Tavern in the Square - @tavernporter) http://4sq.com/11FgK1i     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @patriotledger    
    
    
    BREAKING: #Dolphins to change logo back at halftime #NFL    
    
    
    Woman Pays For Two iPhones, Reportedly Tricked Into Buying Two $600 Apples Instead: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cnxTCF     
    
    
    Why Republicans Want Jobs to Stay Anemic: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1coOtC4     
    
    
    Wow, did that weekend happen? Amazing time with some great people.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @NanB @BeWellBoston    
    
    
    Wow, the two newspapers I worked in the newsrooms of on a regular basis are going to be owned by the owner of the Red Sox and Amazon. Wow.    
    
    
    Methinks some of my Washington Post tech friends are about to get a lot more familiar with the wonder that is http://aws.amazon.com/     
    
    
    I wonder if @HuffingtonPost knows that Hoffman and Redford didn't ACTUALLY work at the Washington Post ...    
    
    
    Good night. #EndOfBirthdayWeek    
    
    
    Asperger's And Autism: Researchers Find Brain Differences: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1entnR8     
    
    
    BREAKING: M. Burns to buy Springfield Shopper. "Like taking candy from a bay-, a bay-, a ..." (BANG!)    
    
    
    Woah. A ‘Magnet-Powered’ Flying Carpet Capable Of Lifting Small Pets In The Air http://designtaxi.com/news/359691/A-Magnet-Powered-Flying-Carpet-Capable-Of-Lifting-Small-Pets-In-The-Air/ …    
    
    
    By @jonweiler: On Arod and what should be Commissioner Selig's tarnished legacy: http://www.huffingtonpost.com/jonathan-weiler/after-arod-ban-time-to-ta_b_3707598.html … #mlb    
    
    
    @propstm that is a question that needs at least a cup of coffee to answer.    
    
    
    @propstm the point is about revisionist history, not new discoveries.    
    
    
    Dear John Henry, make friends w/ the Globe newsstand guy outside N. Station. Dear Jeff Bezos, drop a "Cool Disco Dan" reference.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @postmetrogirl @patriotledger @HarvardAlumni    
    
    
    'Hotshot' Firefighter's Widow Denied Lifetime Benefits By City (VIDEO): via HuffPost http://huff.to/188hEV0     
    
    
    Why Does the NCAA Exist?: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1ctzZB2     
    
    
    With these "I was there in its last days of glory" posts, I'm sure the poster's predecessors thought the glory days were long gone by then.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    As a simultaneous union-& non-union PT employee at the Post/.com in college @KaraSwisher's letter to Bezos nailed it http://dthin.gs/15brwJI     
    
    
    A-Rod should TOTALLY buy the New York Times right now.    
    
    
    Nearly 80 percent of smartphones shipped last quarter ran Android, says IDC

http://lnkd.in/yH9tP2     
    
    
    Yo @WeAreGenuine check out! Bitly Lets You Tell People How You Really Feel About Links You Post

http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/13/08/luvitme-bitly-lets-you-tell-people-how-you-really-feel-about-links-you-post/278471/ …    
    
    
    "such links between Islamic holy days and militancy allow al Qaeda to continue to define what Islam is"  http://religion.blogs.cnn.com/2013/08/06/islams-night-of-power-and-the-terror-alert/ … #ramadan    
    
    
    State-Funded Crisis Pregnancy Centers Talk Women Out Of Birth Control, Condoms: Report: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1etiWeS     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @gregsantos    
    
    
    .@SteveButtry @jayrosen_nyu @chrislhayes can we give @ErinEdwards7 her just props for this Great takedown? http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/08/08/stephanie-banister-australia_n_3726171.html …    
    
    
    I guess my main question is, who gains from such ignorant statements? Huckabee Calls Muslims 'Uncorked Animals' http://huff.to/1cxGL8P     
    
    
    Would calamari sell better if it was called "Squid McNuggets"?    
    
    
    +1 rt @ericuman: Every NSA scoop story should have a little text box: "1) what we already knew... 2) this is different because..."    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Ex-JPMorgan Employees To Be Arrested Over 'London Whale' Scandal: Report: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cANcYJ     
    
    
    @ErinEdwards7 my pleasure.  Please provide more reports and do visit the country of Islam. It's beautiful this time of year ;)    
    
    
    Must have buffalo chicken pizza ... (@ Hancock Tavern) http://4sq.com/19hDD0k     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Good read. Thanks @bobholt! Literacy is reading AND writing. Same with computer literacy: http://www.coding2learn.org/blog/2013/07/29/kids-cant-use-computers/ …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @patriotledger    
    
    
    Reince Priebus: Debate Boycott Is Aimed At Companies Putting Hillary Clinton Content 'On The Air' (VIDE: via HuffPost http://huff.to/16JuwBP     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @margaretweigel @jmascott @specialreports    
    
    
    No signing ceremony. Shocker ... North Carolina Voter ID Bill Signed Into Law By Gov. Pat McCrory, Sparking Lawsuits http://huff.to/1cIw17N     
    
    
    How do you lose a remote control in a 3 br apartment?!    
    
    
    The Saggy Pants Don't Make the Man, The Prisons Do http://huff.to/1eEPVx4     
    
    
    Mitch McConnell Seeks Delay For Obamacare Insurance Exchanges http://huff.to/17k0ra6  #cms #emr #ehr    
    
    
    A Closer Look At Elon Musk's Much-Hyped Hyperloop

http://lnkd.in/s-4JPy     
    
    
    "It wasn’t the Facebook it was when I was seven. It got complicated ..." http://lnkd.in/VvEVRa     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @MikeWiseguy @sunjeffbarker    
    
    
    Bleepin' lovely ... Sequestration Ushers In A Dark Age For Science In America: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cMhdF8     
    
    
    Anyone ever use http://www.vcasmo.com ? Looking into possible Slideshare alternatives. Not that I really want to ... http://www.vcasmo.com/     
    
    
    That moment when you thought you found 5 answers to your Google question, only to realize that 5 others are asking the exact same question.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @froomkin @dweinberger @yelvington    
    
    
    So amazing! Best teamwork I've seen in a while ... Royals - Walk off the Earth https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QgD5p1XiVT0&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    +1 RT @bigdaddykane I love seeing Hip Hop as a competitive sport, I just hate seeing it as a contact sport.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @dianerayfield    
    
    
    +1 http://ow.ly/nXAp8     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Sequestration Forces Scientist To Euthanize His Genetically Modified Rabbits http://huff.to/1ePJaIF  via @HuffPostPol    
    
    
    For Whites (Like Me): On White Kids: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eHSUEY     
    
    
    Peter Shih '10 Things I Hate About You' Post Draws San Francisco's Ire, Confirms Startup Stereotypes: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1ePI6ol     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    But, but the ammendment has electrolytes! Judge Bars Oklahoma From Implementing Anti-Sharia Law: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cUV1sw     
    
    
    Don't wanna overstate it, but this might be the greatest love song ever. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=baUkocatZa4&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    This story by @embeedub is almost as fascinating as it is depressing ... Can a spoon end forced marriage? http://www.salon.com/2013/08/16/can_a_spoon_end_forced_marriage/ …    
    
    
    One benefit to not understanding many #REM lyrics the way Stipe sings them is that their music is the perfect thing to play while working.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @danfell @GordonEdes @robpegoraro    
    
    
    For my #boston friends: Does getting to a show at Comcast, say, two hours early help expedite your departure from the parking lot later?    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @jeromestarkey @kgfashion @greglinch    
    
    
    I guess those claiming Social Media "Guru-ness" need to be ready to drop a Patton Oswalt reference http://lnkd.in/DjgDaT     
    
    
    "... the truth is never told during the nine-to-five hours." - H.S. Thompson ... The reason PowerPoint decks are easier to do at night?    
    
    
    MJ's Human Nature, w/  the lyric "electric eyes are everywhere", was on 1982's Thriller. Clearly, Michael, we were just getting started.    
    
    
    UGH ... Baseball player killed because kids 'were bored' http://espn.go.com/college-sports/story/_/id/9583091/baseball-player-killed-kids-were-bored …    
    
    
    So I have *one* hypothesis ;) Federal Drug Agency Denies Marijuana Is Less Toxic Than Alcohol: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eYklun     
    
    
    I always thought my 9 minute #mbta commute was best in the morning, until I left my office at 10:30 tonight ...    
    
    
    Awesome. RT @andrewchen: OH: "Jobs" would be better if they had split it into 3 parts: "Jobs Begins" "Dark Jobs" and finally "Jobs Rises"    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @EricNewton1 @sunjeffbarker @whatcounts    
    
    
    Woah. Rt @Salon: How the Tesla Model S got a "better-than-perfect" safety rating http://slnm.us/nze11YC     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @jmfbrooks @corinaroy    
    
    
    Smart phones might not make us smarter, but they sure show us how dumb we are more easily than ever. See also: http://lnkd.in/baKvJa     
    
    
    My boss is great. At a going away party today he said: "Carnak. Johnny Carson? Google it." Here you go ... https://www.google.com/search?q=carnak&rlz=1Y3YOJM_enUS544US545&oq=carnak&aqs=chrome.0.69i57j0l3&client=ms-android-verizon&sourceid=chrome-mobile&espv=1&ie=UTF-8 …    
    
    
    @ErinOfBoston thanks! And now so am I. Remember Rappin' Duke? Da ha, da ha ... HAHAHAHA    
    
    
    Obama should totally pardon Peyton, Eli ... and of course, Bradley http://huff.to/1f3lZL9     
    
    
    Fascinating ... News Outlets Continue To Refer To Chelsea Manning As 'He': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1d7G7it     
    
    
    Pretty stellar advice: Jon Wertheim: Tips for tennis fans attending the 2013 U.S. Open http://m.si.com/3290051/tips-for-tennis-fans-attending-the-2013-u-s-open/ …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @jdlasica    
    
    
    FYI @thetaskforce "almost a fifth (24%)" should either read "more than a fifth (24%)" or "almost a quarter (24%)"    
    
    
    New balls, please.    
    
    
    An Open Letter to My Former NSA Colleagues http://mobile.slate.com/articles/health_and_science/science/2013/08/nsa_domestic_spying_mathematicians_should_speak_out.html?original_referrer=http%3A%2F%2Fm.facebook.com%2Fl.php%3Fu%3Dhttp%253A%252F%252Fwww.slate.com%252Farticles%252Fhealth_and_science%252Fscience%252F2013%252F08%252Fnsa_domestic_spying_mathematicians_should_speak_out.html%26h%3DpAQEI9DQu%26s%3D1 …    
    
    
    NIH Director On Sequestration: Lives Are On The Line http://huff.to/1f77OEN  via @HuffPostPol    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @alexwoodcreates    
    
    
    Happy Friday! ♫ Walking On A Dream – Empire Of The Sun http://spoti.fi/IIJJKj  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    What a load of crap from @Milbank Blaming Gen X for the world's problems is like blaming Obama for Katrina. http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/dana-milbank-generation-x--the-weakest-generation/2013/08/23/d5b8a5a0-0c08-11e3-8974-f97ab3b3c677_story.html …    
    
    
    Hahahahahahahah ... #Maryland Secessionist Sees State Split As 'Amicable Divorce': via HuffPost http://huff.to/14qff8J     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Eighty years ago today – the Chesapeake and Potomac hurricane  http://m.washingtonpost.com/blogs/capital-weather-gang/wp/2013/08/23/eighty-years-ago-today-the-chesapeake-and-potomac-hurricane/?wpisrc=nl_buzz …    
    
    
    Mike Tyson sounds sincere as he looks to mend fences http://espn.go.com/videohub/video/clip?id=9596455&categoryid=2378529 …    
    
    
    Loving this song by Chris Velan. Check him out with me at Toad Oct 6! http://spoti.fi/17cXSqF  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    New York Sues Donald Trump For $40 Million http://huff.to/1faxjFp  via @HuffPostNY    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Colin Powell: Voter ID Laws Will 'Backfire' For Republicans: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1deYJx5     
    
    
    Great read. Interesting though that no women are mentioned in the lead. Vin Scully, the best broadcaster of all time http://lnkd.in/nWz86w     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LaurieP    
    
    
    Pretty stellar. 12 Comedian Quotes for When Your Job Makes You Want to Cry  http://lnkd.in/QSAXX3     
    
    
    Among the many SMH moments in here are the grammar choices by people involved in a SCHOOL BOARD election ... http://huff.to/1diK6ZS     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @DubJ    
    
    
    Well I just saved some time: Don’t Wash Your Chicken! It Only Makes Things Worse.http://lnkd.in/wzSPWF     
    
    
    Hoping Tobias Kamke is playing on Saturday when I go to the #USOpen some exciting shots tonight!    
    
    
    New Element 115, Ununpentium, May Join Periodic Table: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dkCbuU     
    
    
    Taxpayer Dollars Paid A Third Of Richest Corporate CEOs: Report: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1fhWEwY     
    
    
    WOAH. Or, duh. ... NYPD Secretly Designated Entire Mosques As Terrorism Organizations (VIDEO): via HuffPost http://huff.to/1fikJE9     
    
    
    HAHA "is this the 50s, or 1999" ... and oh how long ago 1999 seems now ;-). Looking forward to the show tonight! http://spoti.fi/J6W1LC     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @Fliptop @RLubb    
    
    
    I love everything about this: Lycurgus Cup, Ancient Roman Artifact, Inspires Modern-Day Nanotechnology http://huff.to/1fgQqxv     
    
    
    This is one of the best things I've read in a while. Your results may vary. http://lnkd.in/r3apZC ! http://lnkd.in/zKGyh3     
    
    
    #Boston #Noir pic.twitter.com/KkaBTJrQam    
    
    
    Chris Berman introduced Huey Lewis in #Boston. I am the guy who screamed out "Why did you screw Frontline?!?!?!"    
    
    
    I have friends who go here. And they love America. Not acceptable ... Sign Vandalized at Burlington Mosque http://www.boston.com/metrodesk/2013/08/28/sign-vandalized-burlington-mosque/rOOzCnIvDv55iKnIfUX6kO/story.html … #boston    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Johnny Manziel, trailblazer: The #NCAA is a total joke, again http://www.salon.com/2013/08/29/johnny_manziel_trailblazer_the_ncaa_is_a_total_joke_again/ … via @Salon    
    
    
    Bill O'Reilly Falsely Claims Republicans Not Invited To March On Washington Event (VIDEO): via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dqlf6k     
    
    
    Not sure if @AlTrautwig knows we can hear him on the changeovers through the #USOpen livestream. I'm hoping he knows and doesn't care ;-)    
    
    
    British Parliament Votes Against Military Intervention In Syria: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1drllKZ     
    
    
    Did my parking space just try to curse me out? pic.twitter.com/X0CZdmiuCF    
    
    
    Aetna Pulls Out Of Another Obamacare Health Exchange: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1drApZ9     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LaurieP @acomak    
    
    
    T-minus 13 hours until #usopen !! (@ Joe's Pizzeria) http://4sq.com/18cCUbw     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @BostInno @moniguzman @katieirwin    
    
    
    I think I am part of Hangover IV and Alan is sitting behind me at the #USOpen. I stole his skittles.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    #protip when running a red light at night,  at least turn on your headlights    
    
    
    Hahahah Rt @ochocinco: Well my credit score says otherwise RT @nikkayy24: Chad is such a white name tho . @ochocinco"    
    
    
    The fact that this is news kinda saddens me ... Lenovo chief shares $3.25 million of bonus with staff http://lnkd.in/myVeTC     
    
    
    Pulling for Alison Riske. Pittsburgh native, born on my bro & dad's b-day, and a base in College Park, MD, I'm sold. Go Alison! #USOpen    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @daldridgetnt @typepad    
    
    
    Aww yea. Alison Riske is on FIRE. Taking it to Hantuchova and on to a 3rd set. Good stuff at the #USOpen. Oh yea, the rain delay is over ;-)    
    
    
    Well this just depressed the crap outta me ...   http://m.si.com/3334658/federer-remains-tormented-by-self-doubt-after-u-s-open-loss/ … Roger Federer remains tormented by self-doubt after #USOpen loss    
    
    
    London's Walkie Talkie Tower Blamed For Melting Car: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cBK8t0     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @cristymaldonado @jtuohey21 @joansalgeblake    
    
    
    G-20 Should Break UN Deadlock and Call for Removal of All Chemical Weapons From Syria: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dDx8pH     
    
    
    Rate Shock: The Scare That Wouldn't Stick http://huff.to/1fwqBcO  By @wendellpotter    
    
    
    The only thing I can compare @serenawilliams to right now is classic Mike Tyson. Hey #Ashe play some Redman on a changeover! #USOpen    
    
    
    @AlTrautwig sounds annoyed he even has to call this beatdown at the #USOpen on #Ashe    
    
    
    Hahah RT @ezraklein: A searing final paragraph from @ErikWemple on @HowardKurtz -- and Fox News: http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/erik-wemple/wp/2013/08/27/pari-bradlee-and-the-brilliance-of-fox-newss-howard-kurtz/ …"    
    
    
    HAHAHAHA Istomin. You are my new favorite player, for trying that dumb-ass shot and still winning the set. Oh and that outfit. #USOpen #Ashe    
    
    
    AP's Matt Apuzzo And Adam Goldman Crack Open Secretive Institutions, From NYPD To CIA: via HuffPost http://huff.to/176hMon     
    
    
    I'm gonna nickname Istomin Honey Badger, because clearly he don't ... #USOpen #Ashe    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @runofplay @reidhoffman    
    
    
    Bummed #Ferrer lost in the quarters. I love watching him play. I'm amazed how nostalgic seeing shadows creep over the #USOpen makes me.    
    
    
    Columbia, South Carolina Rescinds Decision To Criminalize Homelessness: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dHgIfX     
    
    
    When your day is long, and the night ... Woman Steals $5,000 From Boyfriend  Hides It In Her Butt http://huff.to/1fzeFHv  #EverybodyHurts    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @washingnats @journtoolbox    
    
    
    +1 ... @Maddow's Mission: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dHNKfP     
    
    
    @scottzolak ... so close! Nu Shooz. Go Terps!    
    
    
    Female Peyton Manning fans are an entertaining group #nfl #broncos #colts    
    
    
    Never forget ... Ruby Bridges Thanks Marshal Who Escorted Her To Previously All-White School (PHOTO): via HuffPost http://huff.to/163FLVM     
    
    
    @RunBritRun  I now know 3 ;)    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Help this adorable pup find a home! It's currently sitting with my apartment's trash. So sad ... pic.twitter.com/ihXwcGhLoO    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @patriotledger    
    
    
    Bridezillas invade #Boston. pic.twitter.com/5sArLJq6M0    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @mullenunbound @carriemelago    
    
    
    Ouch ... DRUNK WASPS: Just When You Thought They Couldn't Get Worse http://huff.to/1dQ1uVT     
    
    
    Prison Phone Call Industry Will Fight New FCC Rules Lowering Rates For Inmates: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1fRoali     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Yes. This. ♫ How Will I Know – The Lemonheads http://spoti.fi/MzyH7v  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I hope when people declare "remember 9/11" that that includes all of the aftermath and what we SHOULD benefit from w/ the gift of hindsight.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @jtuohey21    
    
    
    Shawarma plane!!!! #meat #mmmmmm pic.twitter.com/njGCjZAXoa    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @ljndawson @chrisseper    
    
    
    I’m attending a Meetup with Hacks/Hackers Boston http://meetu.ps/1Zj0VP     
    
    
    Pennsylvania's GOP Governor Flips To Support Obamacare Medicaid Expansion: Reports: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1g6FrY2     
    
    
    Taxpayers Shoulder Bulk Of Gun Violence Costs, Study Finds: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1g83Xbf     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @webbmedia @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    For F(lu)ck's sake ... Sequestration Forces Air Force To Limit Free Flu Shots: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1e9BGo7     
    
    
    Hahahahah ... Here's The Passive-Aggressive Payback Legislation Dinging David Vitter For His Prostitution Scandal http://huff.to/1e9QdQs     
    
    
    Gun Violence Study Links State Levels Of Gun Ownership And Homicide http://huff.to/1gcwUTb     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Rt @philshapiro: "The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams" -Eleanor Roosevelt #makermovement    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    @craignickels I DVR'd the game.    
    
    
    @craignickels haha I actually didn't I just had no other retort ;)    
    
    
    Massachusetts General Hospital's @MGHpsychiatry testing hot yoga for treatment of depression http://www.massgeneral.org/psychiatry/about/newsarticle.aspx?id=4359#.UjZMjJZ6YV8.twitter …    
    
    
    Daniel Snyder changing his team's name might be the most fitting punctuation mark on what is looking to be a POS season ... #nfl    
    
    
    Great insights by @ezraklein: Five reasons Obama should name Janet Yellen to chair the Federal Reserve http://wapo.st/19VwK0X     
    
    
    And the public gets what the public wants ... http://open.spotify.com/track/0hhikHUpfUlMBRD2gSf0mu …    
    
    
    Rt @acarvin:  1000: "I beg journalists to make media literacy a part of their mission." - @dangillmor at #MediaConfDCU    
    
    
    Thinking of DC peeps as the Navy Yard shooting unfolds. I noticed http://WTOP.com  is redirecting to http://liveblog.wtop.com/Event/Navy_Yard_Shooting … FYI    
    
    
    WTOP seems to have redirected itself out of streaming live from its own site. I found this link, however: http://www.surfmusic.de/radio-station/wtop-1500-am,5482.html …    
    
    
    HAHAHA TV Station Issue Apology For Broadcasting Terrible NFL Team http://huff.to/1egL2yj  #nfl    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @dansinker @daldridgetnt    
    
    
    Heads up #boston ... Ceremony at the State House tomorrow, and the National Guard will fire cannons on the West Lawn from 10:15 to 10:45 am.    
    
    
    Perhaps, instead of just the debate on gun control, we could examine our definition of terrorism.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    You are anti-health-care reform? Then @realjohngreen is gonna get real with you. (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/his-first-4-sentences-are-interesting-the-5th-blew-my-mind-and-made-me-a-little-sick-2?g=2&c=upw1 …    
    
    
    Bluegrass? Bluegrass. (@ Cantab Lounge w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/16jrH7A     
    
    
    When It Comes To Illegal Drug Use, White America Does The Crime, Black America Gets The Time http://huff.to/1gulQ3Z     
    
    
    http://www.theonion.com/articles/indianamerican-miss-america-attacked-on-twitter,33879/ … this.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    Blood pressure rising while attending  Lawrence Lessig's Interview with Robert Kaiser @harvard http://conta.cc/15ZhjAH     
    
    
    This @Lessing - Kaiser conversation could be a script for a back story for #HouseofCards    
    
    
    As someone who works for a hospital website this made me feel better. pic.twitter.com/M36TWYy8gq    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/b4pRt6w  Court: Clicking 'Like' on Facebook is free speech    
    
    
    Tim Kaine Wins National Press Club Centennial Spelling Bee, Journalists Take Home Team Victory: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1gCUHMo     
    
    
    PSYCHED ... I'm going to volunteer in the artist area at the @LifeisGood Festival! #aww #yea Anyone I know going? http://content.lifeisgood.com/festival/     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Loving these guys! And not just because my school mascot is a #Terp ... ♫ Where Is My Mind – Trampled By Turtles http://spoti.fi/KJoMcE     
    
    
    Realizing at #Bnt32 that you're not just a number. You're a boatload of 1s and 0s ...    
    
    
    Digging @Ubidots at #Bnt32    
    
    
    So you're saying there's a chance ... #nats    
    
    
    @tybbnet and #pirates please please please please please please please please please sweep the #reds ... #nats    
    
    
    Wendy Chandler, Alabama Mom, Furious Over 'Corporal Punishment Consent Form': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1etmPEW     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @TonyMassarotti @acomak @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/baeiphh  "Captricity" wants to help healthcare providers convert to electronic health record system required by #ACA    
    
    
    Shudder... Atom Bomb Almost Exploded Over North Carolina In 1961, The Guardian Reports: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1gJGwoT     
    
    
    http://open.spotify.com/track/0BZmAQV9oA9j9TRYZ1jQj4 … I get to see these guys, in person, this weekend? #LifeIsGood    
    
    
    @AgustinPelaezG yes but next week is bad. DM me ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @R_Oben    
    
    
    Pretty sweet access to the stage. That's Quinn Sullivan, who played a good set at #ligfest pic.twitter.com/l9KlQpky2e    
    
    
    Trampled by Turtles at #ligfest. #AWESOME pic.twitter.com/S2MOGHrobc    
    
    
    Ryan Montbleau at #ligfest pic.twitter.com/hRAvJl7tbf    
    
    
    Yea, golf carts are too slow. Great show! MT @questlove: We made it! Nexttime @theRoots will take the train to Boston pic.twitter.com/SLG8tPnpc9    
    
    
    Obamacare Exchanges Could Weather Government Shutdown: State Officials: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eyhlJi     
    
    
    Thank you thank you #terps for pasting WVa the weekend before I crash in Harper's Ferry for the weekend ... http://scores.espn.go.com/ncf/gamecast?gameId=332640120&version=mobile&date=20130921&groupId=1 …    
    
    
    Psyched to be seeing (and maybe driving around @GoodOldWar atb #ligfest https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7jlNjSdDhfQ&feature=youtube_gdata_player … Making My Life is a brilliant song.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @NationalsReport    
    
    
    No better spot to take in @DeltaRae ... #ligfest pic.twitter.com/TCWABNvraw    
    
    
    Surprise! Jack Johnson cameo appearance at the Coffee House at #ligfest ... @lifeisgood with Zach Gill pic.twitter.com/Jg8FcscSyG    
    
    
    https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7jlNjSdDhfQ&feature=youtube_gdata_player … Jack Johnson covers Sweet Caroline at #ligfest and the #Boston crowd approves ...    
    
    
    Chris Van Hollen Reminds Republicans Their Budget Includes Savings From Obamacare: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1ezTd9a     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @HaydenWright @LaurieP @howardowens    
    
    
    I'm really glad I postponed things on my to-do list to read the comments of that article, said no one, ever.    
    
    
    @chrislhayes Should I read something ironic into that typo?    
    
    
    Lindsey Graham: I Associate 'Allahu Akbar' With A War Chant, And 'I Duck': via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eCkQhO     
    
    
    I regret reading this while standing up. WOW on like a dozen levels. http://www.wgy.com/pages/chuckandkelly.html?article=11670767&desktop=true&desktopviewduration=72000 …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @acarvin @specialreports    
    
    
    I just rented a car through @Priceline's mobile app. Or I just rented three cars. We shall see!    
    
    
    State House Staffer Leaves Loaded Gun In Missouri Capitol Men's Room http://huff.to/1eEQUl4     
    
    
    As one the owner of a Jesse Jackson autographed copy of Green Eggs & Ham, thanks Ted Cruz for highlighting this book! http://maddowblog.msnbc.com/_news/2013/09/25/20692124-getting-all-the-way-to-the-end-of-green-eggs-and-ham …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @EricBoehlert @graphicsgirl    
    
    
    So sad ... The Only Child Survivor Of The 1985 MOVE Bombing Has Died: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eHOQZC     
    
    
    Most Gun Dealers Support Expanded Background Checks, Survey Says http://huff.to/1h3nBFE  via @HuffPostPol    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @tiffanycampbell    
    
    
    Big Consumer Win: Gmail Judge Rules For Privacy In Email: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eKk2aD     
    
    
    Cool! (Literally) ... FireIce Is The Only Thing Between This Guy's Hand And A Blowtorch: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1eJuAH1     
    
    
    Anyone out there attend this? Any thoughts on Sy's comments? http://lnkd.in/btmzMTQ     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @AmPress @RunBritRun    
    
    
    I SO hope they discuss the movie Argo http://www.washingtonpost.com/politics/2013/09/27/228f6ece-27af-11e3-b75d-5b7f66349852_story.html?hpid=z1 …    
    
    
    Yuup. (at @Walmart Supercenter) http://4sq.com/161lvET     
    
    
    In Government Shutdown, Congress Members Still Get Paid While Federal Workers Wait In Limbo: via HuffPost http://huff.to/194AGzv     
    
    
    So awesome ... http://flip.it/AL7Cw     
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing @chrisvelan and @riaisawake at Toad in Cambridge next Sunday 10/6 starting at 8 pm!!    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Rep. Jared Polis Is Really, Really Struggling To Explain Twitter To His Mom: via HuffPost http://huff.to/18A3qfG     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @AdamKilgoreWP    
    
    
    Power robs the brain of empathy http://a.nicco.org/16tNn77     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @mikeloukides    
    
    
    On CNN: "For decades, the component stereo system was the way to listen to audio. Now it's all about computers & MP3 devices." um, phones?    
    
    
    So the plan is to shut down the gov't so people have more time to sign up for Obamacare tomorrow? Brilliant! Wait, what's that? Oh. Carry on    
    
    
    Tues, Oct. 1, overnight into Wed., Oct. 2, complete lane closures of I-93 South through #Boston. http://mass.gov/massdot  #goodtimes    
    
    
    What a mess ... Peter King: 25 Republicans May Vote Against Taking Up Spending Bill With Obamacare Provision http://huff.to/1dSN58W     
    
    
    In honor of Throwback Tuesday 90s style, I am welcoming this government shutdown in with "Runaway Train" ...    
    
    
    "We stayed away from chicken and beer. That helped." -- Terry Francona on Indians' success http://espn.go.com/mlb/story/_/id/9750094/terry-francona-jokes-cleveland-indians-stayed-away-chicken-beer …    
    
    
    Can I buy a “catastrophic” plan? https://www.healthcare.gov/can-i-buy-a-catastrophic-plan … via @HealthCareGov    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    @humanallianceco thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    Any recommendations on a Pirates fan sports bar in #Boston?    
    
    
    Heh. RT @markos: Lots of people don't know that FREEDOM! RT @thinkprogress: Obamacare enrollment beating expectations http://thkpr.gs/18LSZWo     
    
    
    Ad for the Somali pirate movie during the #Pirates playoff game.  Hahahah    
    
    
    Hahah rt @TheOnion: Last Thing Government Worker Needed Was Agency Labeling Him ‘Non Essential’ http://onion.com/1fH3fqk     
    
    
    So so so happy for my friend amd #terp @tybbnet and the #Pirates! Great turnaround guys!!!    
    
    
    KKK Rally At Gettysburg Canceled Because Of Government Shutdown: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bqUwDn     
    
    
    After playing in Firebug, I figured out that @HuffingtonPost current 107px headline can go to 227px before it doesn't fit in my screen ;-)    
    
    
    Really sad to hear this. One of my mom's favorite authors ... Bestselling Author Tom Clancy Dies At 66 http://huff.to/1c4ASAb     
    
    
    "Some 60,000 requested live chats." Wow. I have no idea what to compare this number to. http://lnkd.in/b5cPf87     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LaurieP @OBEYGIANT    
    
    
    Congrats to @WeAreGenuine & http://NEBH.org  for winning the WMA healthcare award. Proud to play a small role. http://lnkd.in/bF7N5ry     
    
    
    $83.65 per hour ... Tea Party Senator: 'I'll Continue To Get Paid' http://huff.to/1701OsQ     
    
    
    @chrispape You're too kind. Ditched TV & car / walk more, playing more tennis, skip dessert, KINDA reduced carbs, cut out MUCH stress.    
    
    
    Sounds about right ... The social media manager is dead. Long live social media.  http://lnkd.in/bCHeYEW     
    
    
    Eek!! In my lifetime the world could see 3.4°C of global warming. How about yours? http://bitly.com/howhotwillitget  #howhotwillitget via @guardianeco    
    
    
    @skalka hey hey! So glad to see one of my favorite people on the web here!    
    
    
    @skalka it's all what you make of it ...    
    
    
    @generalgentry hahah that's what I said about Jayson Blair ...    
    
    
    Endgame. RT @CharlesMBlow: Read tomorrow's column, "Minority Rules," tonight and let me know what you think. http://www.nytimes.com/2013/10/03/opinion/blow-minority-rules.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    Wow. RT @davewiner: Stunning Banksy art in Birmingham, Alabama. http://bit.ly/1hmj7Kn     
    
    
    Truth. MT @WendyGoliff: Meet Butch Matthews (R) Who Came To Love Obamacare After Realizing It Will Save Him $13K http://thkpr.gs/1g4F8j7     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @anachison @RachelBaribeau    
    
    
    Methinks @runofplay wins the day: The Dad-Rock Prometheus - A portrait of Peyton Manning at 37 http://www.grantland.com/story/_/id/9761407/quarterback-peyton-manning-37 …    
    
    
    http://www.theonion.com/articles/emergency-team-of-8thgrade-civics-teachers-dispatc,21023/ … Emergency Team Of 8th-Grade Civics Teachers Dispatched To Washington    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @ajvsell @jennifertribe    
    
    
    Friend at the end of the rainbow in #boston pic.twitter.com/TKIsRJtIuL    
    
    
    Catching the last few Sox innings ... (@ The Greatest Bar) http://4sq.com/177s05I     
    
    
    Just caught the #Fugazi reference in Tape Deck by @jackjohnson ... 13 days after standing next to him for 5 minutes at #LIGFest ... d'oh    
    
    
    http://boston.cbslocal.com/2013/10/03/toucher-rich-hang-up-on-rick-pitino-in-shortest-interview-ever/ … cried laughing at this on a crowded rush hour train. #celtics #boston #RestaurantTable    
    
    
    http://www.theonion.com/articles/tea-party-leaders-announce-support-for-deal-in-exc,34101/?utm_source=Twitter&utm_medium=SocialMarketing&utm_campaign=Default:3:Default … Tea Party Leaders Announce Support For Deal In Exchange For Malia Obama    
    
    
    Hotels and Highways w/ Gregory Douglas. Should be good. Plenty of seats available http://m.bpt.me/event/470582  http://4sq.com/17Dn9Ng     
    
    
    Hey @tybbnet ... One way to conjugate yinz. #pirates pic.twitter.com/HwLRbhIsyJ    
    
    
    http://open.spotify.com/artist/5wYuY1OWcLirqbnAa3LuhL … Hotels and Highways ... so so so good!    
    
    
    @berkun methinks you should get a Flintstones-like stone TOC for each book too ;)    
    
    
    Fight Club Med #AddaWordRuinaMovie    
    
    
    Still pondering the transcendent, dynamic talents that form to make @hotelshighways. Incredible show last night. Was a privilege to attend.    
    
    
    Hahaha great headline!! MT @digiphile: "Ctrl-Alt-Meat" MT @FastCompany: @BillGates Invests In Vegan Meat Startup http://f-st.co/RbLUfhU     
    
    
    Obama Would 'Think About Changing' Washington #Redskins Name If He Owned Team: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bIox1K     
    
    
    Great moment in Porter Sq. Violinist w/ a #playmeimyours piano player. Music stops. "You skipped a page" of music. 6 people laugh. #bliss    
    
    
    http://open.spotify.com/track/33jr3FbRLDmxo9vh8L95sE … do you ever wake up as the person that you thought that you could be? By @hotelshighways    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    @hotelshighways my pleasure. Go Lightning!    
    
    
    This wedding is a BFD ... that's the #boston fire depart leading 5he Provincetown II pic.twitter.com/liLzupDQGR    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @GordonEdes    
    
    
    Fox News' Anna Kooiman Falls For Parody About Obama Funding Muslim Museum: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bMzK1r     
    
    
    Hahaha. Yes. This. RT @darrenrovell: Headline Of The Day: enver efeats allas #NoDHere (via @BigLiciousT)    
    
    
    Counting down to a show I've been looking forward to for more than a year, depending on how you look at it. (@ Toad) http://4sq.com/19sVdy2     
    
    
    Gonna just be mad at Kerry '04 today... Supreme Court Begins New Term With Campaign Finance, Affirmative Action Cases http://huff.to/1bLZGu1     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LaurieP    
    
    
    Sam Wyche: Badass http://espn.go.com/nfl/story/_/id/9785450/sam-wyche-nfl-tried-stop-no-huddle-1980s … #bengals #nfl #NoFunLeague    
    
    
    How much exercise is raking leaves? What should people do ahead of time to prevent injury #MGHDSME    
    
    
    @MGHDiabetesEd @sjmokeefe if there's one thing I have an abundance of it's tennis balls. ;)    
    
    
    Be afraid. Be very afr... oh what's that? NM ... Health Care Reform Works in Massachusetts & It Will Work in America http://huff.to/1bQqfhL     
    
    
    @blamberr noted.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @dickc    
    
    
    Role Models II is out?!?! ... 9-Year-Old Boy Who Snuck On Plane Also Stole A Car http://huff.to/19f3DqQ     
    
    
    The Surreal Logic Of The Debt Ceiling Deniers: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bVTOym     
    
    
    Truth. RT @darrenrovell: It's no accident that the NFL settled its concussion case before #LeagueOfDenial aired.    
    
    
    @louisck thought this was a http://healthcare.gov  post for a second. Congrats. Thankk you for your last #Boston show. So so good.    
    
    
    Managers matter. #redsox    
    
    
    Nobel Prize Winner Furloughed Due To Government Shutdown: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19ekqu8     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @randylewiskemp    
    
    
    Meanwhile ... Climate Change Will Bring Conditions Outside Historical Variability In Coming Decades: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1c0Jd5n     
    
    
    President Obama Might Ask Who Benefits From U.S. Debt Default: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1bZq3g9     
    
    
    Janet Yellen's Nomination Just Changed The Game For Economists: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19l9HOz     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @perryhewitt @Digidave @postpartumprog    
    
    
    If you were taking a Moroccan visitor to their first-ever hockey game, what would you make sure they know / saw? @nhlbruins #nhl #boston    
    
    
    Kind of a big deal. What Google's Hummingbird Update Means for Small Business http://lnkd.in/bXeVqm5     
    
    
    Jim Carrey can solve the debt crisis! Let's just blare the most annoying sound in the world until the Tea Party admits defeat.    
    
    
    NOW Are We Allowed Talk About Firing Jamie Dimon?: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19FbuA5     
    
    
    @MGHDiabetesEd eating a burrito while reading this.  Hope that's okay ;)    
    
    
    Lesus! Vatican Jesus Medal Recalled After Embarrassing Misspelling http://huff.to/GNXyY5     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @ibarguen @kenyatta    
    
    
    What, was the Hon. Murray McCully organizing this thing? http://www.washingtonpost.com/local/trafficandcommuting/va-state-police-trucker-protest-launched-on-i-95-north-vehicles-head-toward-beltway/2013/10/11/c8049b7e-3266-11e3-89ae-16e186e117d8_story.html … Trucker protest hits Beltway but causes no major delays    
    
    
    @ICherryBlsm they make those?    
    
    
    What values? Sandy Rios At Values Voter Summit: Matthew Shepard's Murder Was 'A Total Fraud' http://huff.to/19w5NCl     
    
    
    That is rich ... Steve Pearce Tells Furloughed Workers To Take Out Loans To Pay Bills: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19vRSMM     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @LiveMLBchat @edsbs    
    
    
    Syria Pundits Had Rampant, Undisclosed Conflicts Of Interest: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19uQSbK     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @generalgentry @JonEasley @cpriceNFL    
    
    
    Larry Klayman Tells Obama 'To Put The Quran Down' At Veterans Rally: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1chPwSd     
    
    
    @cpriceNFL my pleasure!    
    
    
    Pity the Values Voter Summit: via HuffPost http://huff.to/18VdJfH     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @copyrightclear @blamberr @GordonEdes    
    
    
    Couch and coffee table for sale. Currently in storage in Medford http://boston.craigslist.org/gbs/fuo/4128838446.html … $300 obo. Please share!    
    
    
    Patriots Radio Batshit Winning TD Call Matched Up With Tecmo Bowl Sim http://deadspin.com/patriots-radio-batshit-winning-td-call-matched-up-with-1444831527 … #unicorns #showponies #beef @scottzolak #terps    
    
    
    @wilw @LeftHandBrewing it's what Guinness wishes it could be. #realtalk    
    
    
    @blamberr my fave Rivers stat ever: 0-for-Maryland #terps    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @gregsantos @kailanikm @NanB    
    
    
    How would you solve the debt crisis, and would it involve two tickets to the gun show? @Newseum #ASKRON http://newseum.org/anchorman     
    
    
    @chrislhayes shhhhh don't jinx it! ;)    
    
    
    This #redsox game was so tense my twitter feed was virtually void of dirty water until the last pitch. Also, Gomes metaphors are wonderful.    
    
    
    Want to deter muggers? Tell them you intern for the NSA. http://bit.ly/18iMV9P     
    
    
    Small Tax On Pacemakers Threatens To Blow Up World Economy: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19LXt1B     
    
    
    How Do You Not Condemn the Waving of: via HuffPost http://www.huffingtonpost.com/rev-al-sharpton/confederate-flag-white-house_b_4100189.html …    
    
    
    http://www.washingtonmonthly.com/ten-miles-square/2013/10/regional_differences_have_doom047323.php … Regional Differences Have Doomed the Tea Party    
    
    
    GREAT READ http://mobile.businessweek.com/articles/2013-10-16/open-source-everything-the-moral-of-the-healthcare-dot-gov-debacle … Why the Obamacare Website Was Destined to Fail — and How to Do Better Next Time    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @dabeard @TheChannelCo @AdrienneLB    
    
    
    http://www.msnbc.com/rachel-maddow-show/chart-the-house-gops-demand-list … day-um. GOP demands list via @maddow    
    
    
    There are few tortures like being a self-aware bore.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @janeroper @ajvsell @nancyshute    
    
    
    Making a bad 3rd base coach call, at home, in the first inning, during the playoffs has got to suck. #nowheretohide #tigers #redsox #mlb    
    
    
    What got smacked harder, the GOP or the baseball Napoli just hit? Trick question! America did. #24billiondollars #lesigh #inners #redsox    
    
    
    I correctly spelled tangentially on the first try, then thought my spellcheck must surely be broken.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @cpriceNFL @GronkNation    
    
    
    All I have to do to beat a http://washingtonpost.com  or http://bostonglobe.com  paywall is rt-click in Chrome & view in incognito window? Wow.    
    
    
    New business model for the NSA: Disaster recovery of data that's gone from cloud-based storage in a lapsed account.    
    
    
    @jimbradysp @stevejfox If they think your white shirt is yellow ...    
    
    
    SO want my "goblin destroyer" merit badge ... WATCH: Scout Leaders Destroy Ancient Rock Formation http://huff.to/19XZgka  via @HuffPostGreen    
    
    
    Thanks to my #terps friends for sharing midnight madness pix from Cole. Was so fortunate to cover some of the resurgence. So many memories!    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Fish in a barrell ... Sean Hannity Gets Fact-Checked Hard On Obamacare Claims: via HuffPost http://huff.to/19YOv14     
    
    
    Bussing between Broadway and JFK y'all #boston #mbta    
    
    
    Pissah: Mammals Pee For Same Duration Of 21 Seconds, Urination Study Finds http://huff.to/19ZQQZu     
    
    
    Been a lomg time ... (@ Starbucks) http://4sq.com/19Tfo2n     
    
    
    Go Spellman! (@ Arlington High School) http://4sq.com/19iDjvc     
    
    
    Woah. Kodi Whitfield Touchdown Catch Gave Stanford Lead Over UCLA, May Have Been Wizardry (VIDEO/GIF): via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cHzzEZ     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    So I finally root for Peyton Manning in a game and ... so far, not so good. #colts #broncos #rootfortheolderguy    
    
    
    @dabeard I got some ideas ;)  Let's catch up sometime. Hope you're well.    
    
    
    @davewiner Trex are for kids. Sorry, couldn't resist. I blame the brownie sundae.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @FredToucher    
    
    
    Gravity: Let's Not Make the Movie a Reality: via HuffPost http://www.huffingtonpost.com/bharath-gopalaswamy/space-debris_b_4136154.html …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Hello #istanbul / @istanbul ... I have an 8 hour layover (5 pm-1 am local time on a Thurs. night / Fri. morning).  Suggestions very welcome    
    
    
    @MaryTreseler @berkun where u at?    
    
    
    @KeithOlbermann @dweisscomedy heh. This was not a problem 10 days ago ;)    
    
    
    As Immigration Reform Comes Up Again, Watch This Private Prison Company: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cTzvCd     
    
    
    http://www.salon.com/2013/10/22/why_the_oscar_race_still_matters/ … ANDREW O'HEHIR'S 1st world problems aside, I still intend to see every Oscar best picture nominee again this year.    
    
    
    OS X Mavericks Fixes Apple Contacts Vulnerability NSA May Have Exploited: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1dgqDJp     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  ▸ Top stories today via @TedLeonsis    
    
    
    I'd be more sympathetic for the #Cardinals if their city did not perpetrate such bad beer on the world. #redsox #boston #stlouis #mlb    
    
    
    In addition to everything else that's causing some to have http://healthcare.gov  heartburn, is the dual meaning of "CMS" Good times ...    
    
    
    @cbc_belmont Thanks for the tips!    
    
    
    Ted Cruz Gets His Health Insurance Through Goldman Sachs, His Wife Confirms: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1cZ2k09     
    
    
    #cardinals fans: "We wuz robbed from dem being robbed. Time for another Bud Light Lime." #redsox #worldseries    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @WBUR @usopen @AdamKilgoreWP    
    
    
    Had a blast in my John Grayson costume @wearegenuine's party last night. Even fooled at least 4 people ;)    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @eclisham @ChildrensTheOne @greglinch    
    
    
    Anyone can now sign up for Medium with their Twitter account http://lnkd.in/b7RKaZV     
    
    
    My first college newspaper beat! @umterps: FH: #1 Terps Clinch ACC Regular Season Title http://bit.ly/1d8RiFw     
    
    
    @piink726 and a drunk person at that, apparently ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @EricNewton1 @davbunnell @HarvardAlumni    
    
    
    Discovered http://youtube.com/pair  and can now sync my smartphone to the youtube app on my smart tv. So so awesome. Binging on NY Times ret…    
    
    
    Thinking this #WorldSeries game is gonna go to extra innings. Getting ready now.    
    
    
    I don't believe, what I just saw. #WorldSeries #RedSox #Cardinals    
    
    
    Guess the #Cardinals can stop complaining about that overturned call in Game 1 now. #WorldSeries    
    
    
    Twitter people, I'm proud of you. So many people are spelling Saltalamacchia correctly. Though I'm pretty sure most are copying and pasting.    
    
    
    Will Middlebrooks must feel like the whole game happened at third base. I don't know how you get any sleep after that.    
    
    
    A rule is a rule. Also, I love the umpires available for a press conference. And Fox 25 is doing a Saltalamacchian job in this postgame.    
    
    
    What will get lost on that last play is that Pedroia is the man and so did not deserve this. #RedSox #WorldSeries    
    
    
    I can't believe Tuck Rule town can actually get upset at the umps on this game.    
    
    
    How was that last play scored, by the way? Wish it could be 8675309. Sigh. #worldseries    
    
    
    What could be better? Seriously. ... Alternate Version Of 'Anchorman 2' In the Works Using '250 New Jokes' http://huff.to/1auwGr3     
    
    
    Mrs. Krabappel Will Be Retired From 'The Simpsons' Following Marcia Wallace's Death: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1axj6mB     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Am I the only one, who upon hearing about Lou Reed's passing, started thinking about Renton and Sick Boy in the park?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @coolmcjazz you know you'll miss him ...    
    
    
    If #WorldSeries goes 7 I'll dress like H.S. Thompson 4 Halloween, be around Fenway & mutter "When the going gets weird, the weird turn pro."    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @postmetrogirl @probert06 @LaurieP    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @specialreports @dansinker    
    
    
    I really love this. 10 Habits of Exceptionally Happy People http://lnkd.in/bMBWErn     
    
    
    Talked to StL tv reporter (4). Told him Popeye's is where chicken came from in chicken & beer days while holding a box of fries. Stay tuned.    
    
    
    Wonder what Ike would say 
... James Clapper: Spying On Leaders Not Significant Enough To Tell Congress http://huff.to/17vvvXA     
    
    
    Making Australian Open watch party plans with my boys James and Derek. (at @TempleBar02138) http://4sq.com/18AuLwr     
    
    
    Sooo I'm gonna hang in the Fenway area tomorrow. If you wanna meet up, let me know and I'll let you know where we're at.    
    
    
    @ProfessorShayla my bad.    
    
    
    @BonnieBernstein "I'm a professional cynic but my heart's not in it." - Blur    
    
    
    @ProfessorShayla I vicariously introduced a friend to Iota last week and immediately thought of you.    
    
    
    Fargin Bastages is my favorite non-curse curse ever.    
    
    
    @courtneyrau I honestly don't understand    
    
    
    Just dropped a "Hey, let's be careful out there" at the end of an analytics meeting. Wonder what Renko is up to these days ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @perryhewitt    
    
    
    Went to a wearable technology meetup yesterday. Read this today: 
Woman got ticket for wearing Google Glass behind t…http://lnkd.in/b3unjvp     
    
    
    My prediction: If the #RedSox win tonight, it'll be thanks in part to a 2-run double by Stephen Drew. #worldseries    
    
    
    Just encountered, literally, the blind leading the blind. It was inspiring and has me pondering a lot.    
    
    
    This game's going to take 4 hours. Good thing Fox Sports squeezed in those commercials over the @DropkickMurphys. #WorldSeries #RedSox    
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb baseball gods willing.    
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb too soon. Too soon.    
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb what is the fascination with ... oh wait, wrong Drew.    
    
    
    This catch jeremy ad missed a great opportunity: running talley of his data charges each time the ad runs. Oh well, next time T-mobile    
    
    
    @PeteAbe as long as it's right in the story ;) #wehaveallbeenthere    
    
    
    David Freese: 17(?!l) stranded runners in the #worldseries #redsox #cardinals    
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb it had to happen. Low man rises all the time in this postseason for the #redsox    
    
    
    Do not swallow Spiriva capsule.    
    
    
    Dear #boston ... don't burn shit. Thx!    
    
    
    Who wants Popeyes? #redsox #boston #worldseries    
    
    
    This is where Support Our Troops matters ... When Veterans Get Food Stamps Cut, It's Time to Prioritize Our Budget http://huff.to/1dpxLkq     
    
    
    Dear @FoxSports, Dennis Eckersly to replace Tim McCarver?  He's got rings, personality, opinions, and oh yea, his own vocabulary. #mlb    
    
    
    I'm proud to live in a country that gives options. I am more rising tide lifts all boats than trickle-down. Thank you for your service!    
    
    
    @eclisham USA! USA!    
    
    
    @wcsmith40 Happy can help your chances on the other two ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @jimbradysp @acomak @cristymaldonado    
    
    
    HEH http://lnkd.in/bAwkfDC     
    
    
    Democrats, Republicans Launch New Effort To Fight The Drug War Together http://huff.to/1duYM5Z     
    
    
    Dear Snickers: "Fun size" should not be the one given to the one I call "Snick-nugget."    
    
    
    Still trying to process the botched rundown and the balk from last night's #worldseries game 6. Way to treat your fans like W.E. Coyote    
    
    
    PBR2D2 gets a thumbs up. #halloween #boston pic.twitter.com/MT752iaUsy    
    
    
    Happy November #boston ... stay hydrated, it's gonna be a scorcher today ;)    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @dcsportsbog @runofplay    
    
    
    For upcoming Hong Kong flights and layovers, trying to decide if I devour the Wire, Boardwalk Empire or Breaking Bad    
    
    
    Great day to take the boat to Hingham for dinner. Is it really November? (at @Alma_Nove) http://4sq.com/1e0vVsW     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    #redsox owners celebrating during the #rollingrally #boston pic.twitter.com/xIHLaL4RGj    
    
    
    Japan representing at #redsox #rollingrally ... glad I spotted that flag! pic.twitter.com/SdrkfrQR3u    
    
    
    I'm at @Wahlburgers (Hingham, MA) http://4sq.com/1b38KI6     
    
    
    Dear fall daylight savings time, even though we don't save daylight w/ you, I really appreciate the extra hour of sleep.    
    
    
    Killed LAX TSA Officer Gerardo I. Hernandez Remembered As Family Man: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1aSTzV7     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @karabaic    
    
    
    Found and packed my passport < 2 weeks before leaving the country, AND it's not expired. More than kinda awesome.    
    
    
    HAHAHA Red Sox Pitcher Jake Peavy Bought A 'Duck Boat' After Parade http://huff.to/1dFIA1Z     
    
    
    First time here but I will be back so often. 5 min walk from my place. Aww yea. (@ R. F. O'Sullivan & Son Pub) http://4sq.com/16ZP0DW     
    
    
    So to respond to accusations of mental laziness, Rand Paul responds w/ mentally lazy approach of advocating violence http://huff.to/1dFajQ9     
    
    
    Think I'd rather be a #Steelers fan than a #Texans fan tonight. That was awful.    
    
    
    Texas' Restrictive Voter ID Law Stops A Former U.S. House Speaker From Getting A Voter ID Card: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1hcfL1T     
    
    
    College Presidents Escape Leadership Pressures By Moving To Smaller Schools: via HuffPost http://huff.to/1aVJTJw     
    
    
    Haha @Steven_Strauss says apply electronic 'Stop and Frisk' to Potentially Corrupt Bank CEOs ... then drops mic http://huff.to/1aW5mCj     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @ron_miller    
    
    
    Can't believe it's 8 p.m. and I'm still working. What's that? Oh, ok. It's apparently just after 5.    
    
    
    @littleidea ha! I still have a talking http://pets.com  sock puppet in the original package. Best clearance find ever.    
    
    
    @KristineLeahy sometimes, the stench can't be contained by the garbage can ...    
    
    
    @washingtonpost curious about the word "just" for example methinks <16% are fans of "America's team" + many encounter it through other tools    
    
    
    @edsbs sadly, so would Incognito.    
    
    
    Sometimes, I just come here for the music. Tonight's "Don't take your guns to town" feels tragically ironic. http://4sq.com/1dJqGv9     
    
    
    Hahah rt @owillis: here's a hedgehog punching http://i.imgur.com/SP6TrQO.gif     
    
    
    Hmmm rt @steverubel: Study: Does Content Marketing Produce Results? http://flip.it/V3XbA     
    
    
    So so awesome. RT @angryburrito: Hilarious animation! 'Why you shouldn't kill the Chinese' | http://ow.ly/qviv7 "    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @electra    
    
    
    Heheh RT @iamdevloper: 10 lines of code = 10 issues. 500 lines of code = "looks fine." Code reviews.    
    
    
    Northern #Virginia ... helping save the commonwealth from itself. Also if it's called a commonwealth, shouldn't that be a guiding principle?    
    
    
    Ouch. Rand Paul's Washington Times Column Put To An End Amid Plagiarism Charges http://huff.to/1b3MIZ4     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @ChipotleTweets @JonEasley    
    
    
    Soooo useful!! http://lnkd.in/b_Rghrp     
    
    
    Crap! I called the wrong Lisa Baldelli-Hunt to congratulate her on becoming the next mayor of Woonsocket.    
    
    
    http://forums.androidcentral.com/samsung-galaxy-s4/303476-google-play-music-sd-card-root-required.html … saving this for later to save files to an sd card ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sweet! Just bought MGMT tix for Dec. 5 in Boston. Psyched!! http://www.songkick.com/concerts/18089224-mgmt-at-orpheum-theatre?utm_source=8123&utm_medium=partner …    
    
    
    .@scottzolak You'll always be one of my favorite #Terps    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm at @TheHarpBoston (Boston, MA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/18bENot     
    
    
    @owillis I assume you mean the fetal position.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @TheJimmyFund    
    
    
    Paging @angryburrito RT @GenePark BREAKING NEWS FROM CNN: Hong Kong is now in Brazil pic.twitter.com/misYRDWi8H    
    
    
    Oh man how I want the Toronto mayor and Richie Incognito to be related.    
    
    
    @TheHarpBoston it was better than I deserved ;-)    
    
    
    My job gives me a great chance to show valuable work can be done to bring along vital web sites that can't just blow things up & start over.    
    
    
    Post #terps loss consolation pic.twitter.com/fu4d89LAKF    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Soo  hungry. Been a while since I was last here ... (@ The Paramount - @paramount44) http://4sq.com/1hYqMBG     
    
    
        
    
    
    3 downloads for my world-wind tour: The Stench of Honolulu by Jack Handy, Hatching Twitter by @nickbilton and the Year w/o Pants by @berkun.    
    
    
    Been a long time since this too! (@ The Dogwood) http://4sq.com/18keool     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    “We can stop this madness”: Philippines delegate urges action at U.N. climate talks http://www.salon.com/2013/11/11/we_can_stop_this_madness_philippines_delegate_urges_action_at_u_n_climate_talks/ … via @Salon    
    
    
    This will come in handy in a social media chat I'm having tomorrow ... http://hub.am/1eF18SM     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @theRab    
    
    
    No day can be all bad when it starts by wearing pants that used to be too tight that you now need a belt for.    
    
    
    @TedStarkey I know! Tried it at work with similar results ...    
    
    
    @TedStarkey they responded "PROCESS"    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Abilene Christian better go on to win their conference.  #terps    
    
    
    If the #terps play like crap but no one is there to see it, did it really happen?    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @DrPeggyDrexler @HarvardAlumni @mikeloukides    
    
    
    Greetings from Istanbul! pic.twitter.com/E0yEcYD5cd    
    
    
    I fell in love with Istanbul last night. Or today. I've happily lost track. Greetings from over Kabul.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    @liamfitzmlb you're welcome but I still don't see the point of it all.    
    
    
    Great time last night @TakeOutComedy. Learned and laughed a lot during a great set by Butch Bradley. Poor Faye ...    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @sunjeffbarker @TennisHalloFame    
    
    
    https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pdp-CeyEivw&feature=youtube_gdata_player … nothing extraordinary in this short video of a cab ride in Hong Kong,  other than how much stuff is in the city.    
    
    
    Beautiful view from Yung Shue Wan pic.twitter.com/1KuVMWKEEa    
    
    
    http://distractify.com/fun/illustrator-draws-faces-lets-4-year-old-draw-bodies-ends-up-with-adorably-weird-art/ … I love everything about this story    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @chrispape    
    
    
    http://www.thenation.com/blog/177240/death-len-bias-my-generations-one-person-shock-doctrine … @EdgeofSports reflects on the would-be 50th bday of Len Bias and his legacy. I feel 12 years old and numb again.    
    
    
    Lunch! (at @ThePawnHk) http://4sq.com/1faC86b     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Good read: The scourge of Veil Porn http://www.patheos.com/blogs/akramsrazor/2013/11/veil-por/ …    
    
    
    This Slide Shows Why http://HealthCare.gov  Wouldn't Work At Launch http://n.pr/1fRYJSI     
    
    
    What Mong Kok just happened? pic.twitter.com/msnnp0qIUo    
    
    
    Ancient Humans Had Sex With Mystery Species, New DNA Study Shows http://huff.to/1bMUPJU     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @chrislhayes    
    
    
    Got an old-school shave. Face hasn't been this smooth since I slept in a crib. (at @mo_hotels) http://4sq.com/17spLxH     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    @tim_hume great meeting you last night.    
    
    
    The tour continues ... (@ The Dawin) http://4sq.com/1e7sMod     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lunch is only late relative to when you eat breakfast ... (@ No Idea) http://4sq.com/17CAXrs     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @BostonTweet    
    
    
    This place was so hot a fire alarm literally went off. On the sixth floor. Solo glad it was a false alarm! http://4sq.com/1fwOlSS     
    
    
    Because when you're on holiday and someone slaps a wristband on you and says free cover at the afterparty, you go... http://4sq.com/1i4vPDn     
    
    
    Gave homeless woman equivalent of $100 US. She cried & we hugged. I did much selfish stuff here in Bangkok but that will stick w/ me forever    
    
    
    Just saw a dude carrying a hula hoop. No idea how you fit that into the overhead bin or under the seat ... http://4sq.com/1efyTa3     
    
    
    Leaving just in time ...
http://www.abc.net.au/news/2013-11-24/anti-government-protesters-gather-in-bangkok-ahead-of-rally/5113578?section=australianetworknews … Thai capital tense as tens of thousands of rival Yellow Shirt and Red Shirt protesters rally    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Rt @Harvard: 3-D imaging has entered the laboratory as an important research tool http://ow.ly/r6beW     
    
    
    Who is more bad-ass than Poon Lim? No one. 133 days on a raft. Damn. (@ Hong Kong Maritime Museum 香港海事博物館) [pic]: http://4sq.com/IbxZAH     
    
    
    I've had worse afternoons ... (@ View 62 by Paco Roncero) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1iJcc1y     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/d4arHWf  How much does it cost to develop an app? The true price of starting from scratch    
    
    
    The South’s New Lost Cause http://nyti.ms/18Ui8gA     
    
    
    Last night in Hong Kong. Getting in touch with my German heritage or something ... (@ Schnurrbart) http://4sq.com/1fCLoQH     
    
    
    Just received "French" toast that had peanut butter in it. Still not sure how I feel about this ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    There's a Popeye's here?!?!?! Awesome. (@ Hong Kong International Airport | HKG | 香港國際機場 - @hkairport) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Ikofoq     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @eclisham    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Seven Nation Army is one of the best things to happen to sports fan culture in the past couple decades    
    
    
        
    
    
    Brain Cells 'Geotag' Memories To Cache What Happened — And Where http://n.pr/187D1Vr     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @DrPeggyDrexler @NERevolution    
    
    
    One working ear is better than none ... happy to be back. (at @BostonLogan International Airport (BOS) w/ 70 others) http://4sq.com/1fSNhsH     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @DrPeggyDrexler    
    
    
    This Los Angeles Billionaire Is Reinventing Your Health Care - http://huff.to/1eNT0Nz     
    
    
    @MBTA red line car number 01632 has a metal ad frame that's loose on top and could eventually injure someone sitting. Saw it at MGH this am    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @LaurieP @mikeloukides @EASPORTSMauiInv    
    
    
    HAHAHA well done @QuantumPirate http://lnkd.in/dQj8FQg     
    
    
    Landmark Princeton Study Sends Bots Across The Web To Track Discrimination http://lnkd.in/daEUKfQ     
    
    
    Just finished Hatching Twitter: A True Story of Money, Power, Friendship, and Betrayal by @nickBilton & read the whole thing on my phone ;)    
    
    
    @chrisabraham and tweeting it is weirder, but it would probably make @jack proud ;)    
    
    
    Alleged Perils Of Left-Handedness Don't Always Hold Up http://n.pr/19gNhu1     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @greglinch @jtuohey21    
    
    
    OMG, BuzzFeed's Investing In Serious News Coverage! Is It FTW? http://n.pr/IESQwA     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Disclosure: David is a friend of mine. That said, this made me laugh out loud. A U.S.-Japan Territorial Dispute…Betw…http://lnkd.in/dxqAt9S     
    
    
    WHY are there Zubaz directly behind the Maryland #terps bench? Thought those were banned as part of NAFTA ...    
    
    
    Dear @ESPN Jimmy V would like to request Maryland #terps v. Duke in next year's Big Ten(welveteen) Challenge #ncaa    
    
    
    A crowd gathers to see a church near Porter Sq. move to new foundation to make room for Lesley U's new art center. pic.twitter.com/uvLv6Vzfku    
    
    
    Started my day watching a church be moved (!) on hydraulic rollers and will end it at an MGMT concert.  #TrippyThursday    
    
    
        
    
    
    Did a triple-take at #NBA's Atlantic Division in the Eastern Conference. Every team with a losing record. So, #Celtics (.400) in 1st. #SMH    
    
    
    Take only what you need ... (@ Orpheum Theatre for MGMT and Kuroma w/ 43 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1cp7Jyd     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @davidsirota @Digidave    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Great time soaking up some of the inventive projects at CS50 at Harvard University this afternoon.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    @godhearsu your bio has a typo. How is this possible? Did I just commit heresy?    
    
    
    @jtuohey21 @JeffreyGoldberg does he know the beeper guy, a.k.a Liz Lemon's BF a.k.a. Mayhem?    
    
    
    Considering renaming auto-correct "auto-fwyou" ...    
    
    
    Pretty cool: New, minimally invasive mitral valve repair system treats patients with severe mitral regurgitation http://www.massgeneral.org/heartcenter/about/newsarticle.aspx?id=4492 …    
    
    
    I needed this today: In a “rainbow” universe, time may have no beginning http://lnkd.in/dNcnMuR     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Man Charged With 142 Felonies After Cop Sees Instagram Page - http://huff.to/1cBJjBx     
    
    
    This place is even better in the winter. (at @TempleBar02138) http://4sq.com/1bXE4xH     
    
    
    Facebook Wants to Be a Newspaper. Facebook Users Have Their Own Ideas. http://lnkd.in/dtvDbyM     
    
    
    http://www.miamiherald.com/2013/12/11/3812944/american-univ-campus-on-lockdown.html … AU on lockdown? Be safe Eagles.    
    
    
    @neil_fahey @zHeather well there's this: http://www.npr.org/blogs/codeswitch/2013/12/03/248515217/why-chaucer-said-ax-instead-of-ask-and-why-some-still-do …    
    
    
    Yikes. Tea Party Rep: Fast-Food Workers Shouldn't Ask For Higher Wages - http://huff.to/1fkT0Vi     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @Buster_ESPN @DrPeggyDrexler @karabaic    
    
    
    REVEALED: American Missing In Iran Was Working For CIA - http://huff.to/1fodNYc     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @seanbonner @reidhoffman    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Watched a movie on Netflix.  From my phone, connected to a big screen TV. For monthly fee that's about the cost of one cable ppv movie.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/d9REpQc  Montgomery superintendent makes call for cyber civility    
    
    
    The Lingering Mystery Of The Max Headroom Television Hack - http://huff.to/1exYLyN     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @RBReich    
    
    
    Hahahahhahahahahah thanks December Romo! #Cowboys #Packers    
    
    
    I rode an elevator once with a dead-man-walking Barry Switzer in Dallas. Wonder why I thought of that right now? #Cowboys #NFL    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @blamberr @mikeloukides    
    
    
    Pro tip of the day, @harvard edition: explosion http://lnkd.in/d4RkqmD  and explosive http://lnkd.in/dkiAs3H  are different words #CheckYoS…    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @lisawilliams    
    
    
    When the going gets weird, the weird turn pro. #GenuineiDeers    
    
    
    Good night to register for and book my first Uber ride. Let it snow let it snow let it snow!    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Watched the #wizards win and the #Cowboys meltdown replayed. I've had worse nights ... (@ The Four's w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/1jjVU1T     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/d8-v_Br  My first Shazaam to Spotify-captured song. A new era for me personally.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    Enjoying how my Samsung Galaxy S4 can beam music to the car via bluetooth while serving as a WiFi hotspot at the same time. Pretty cool!    
    
    
    It's been a long time ... (@ Cactus Cantina - @70cindy w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/1ciR3u4     
    
    
    Sam & Dave playing.  I like this place. (at @BreadsodaDc) http://4sq.com/18Z5I7x     
    
    
    Chemicals Found At Fracking Sites Linked To Cancer, Says New Study - http://huff.to/1fMnKip     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @JonEasley    
    
    
    OOF. @OatesTom: BU vs. UM turned into BU vs. BM #Terps    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @chezpazienza    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @AmyKNelson    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    http://scottberkun.com/2012/eight-ways-to-avoid-killing-your-family-over-the-holidays/ … Good tips from @berkun 
... Cheers!    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    I'm at Stained Glass Pub - @sgp_silvrspring (Silver Spring, MD) http://4sq.com/1dLFnMV     
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks everyone! (@ Washington Dulles International Airport (IAD) - @dulles_airport w/ 74 others) http://4sq.com/JDdgpV     
    
    
    Interesting read about Elon Musk ... Triumph of His Will http://flip.it/ywm7c     
    
    
    Turbulence expected on my flight.  I love turbulence!  Not even joking ...    
    
    
    @ScottAxelrod579 thanks!    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem  Stories via @tiffanycampbell @DrPeggyDrexler @owillis    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    I think a hung over Vince Vaughn would be pretty entertaining to listen to comment on the Tournament of Roses parade.    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    I think what makes this #boston storm so tough is that the inch totals will be higher than degrees Fahrenheit. #SoupIsGoodFood    
    
    
    Chicago Fails to Live Up to the Hype: Murders Plummet in 2013 - The Wire http://flip.it/vDUuo     
    
    
        
    
    
    It's hard to get around the wind ... thanks psychic Spotify! http://open.spotify.com/track/2AFoi1vBRcUFjSvfIDxOOM …    
    
    
    The Chad Capellman Daily is out! http://paper.li/chadrem     
    
    
    