2012 #CSR & #Sustainability Salary Survey Results Released http://bit.ly/LS1ggo     
    
    
    Good approach! > #Sustainability is nothing more than good business in a changing environment http://bit.ly/Mnj5Cj     
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights. Do you see the connection? http://wp.me/p2awtX-S     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @ISDuurzaam @DaveStangis    
    
    
    Small Businesses and Human Rights, do you see the connection? http://wp.me/p12b0J-gu  #SME #SMEs #CSR #Sustainability    
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights, is there a connection? Or is it only for multinationals http://wp.me/p12b0J-gu  #SME #csr4sme #CSR #Sustainability    
    
    
    Some good tips about making a Business Case out of #CSR http://goo.gl/xeLS6     
    
    
    Do SMEs have a responsibility on Human Rights? http://juanvillamayor.wordpress.com/2012/07/12/pymes-y-derechos-humanos-ves-la-conexion/ … #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    @excelenciacl  @schwild @jgomlop @borjavega @Coethica @trinipa Gracias por RTs /Thanks for RTs! SMEs and Human Rights http://bit.ly/OH6FXh     
    
    
    Here is a list of interesting business ethics movies you might want to watch this summer #csr #ethics http://fb.me/1cXHzLPNg     
    
    
    It’s Not Rocket Science to Change a Lightbulb http://bit.ly/SuSV5S  by @earthprints #green #sustainability    
    
    
    "Human Rights are for governments, not for small and medium enterprises" Do you agree? http://bit.ly/OH6FXh  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    “Better CSR Advice To SMEs” Event Report Now Available http://goo.gl/Af84g  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    What's the social purpose of your company? Great question! http://goo.gl/t1fQP  va @ELdaily #CSR    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @FabianGPastor    
    
    
    Do SMEs have a responsibility on Human Rights? http://juanvillamayor.wordpress.com/2012/07/12/pymes-y-derechos-humanos-ves-la-conexion/ … #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @FRSIberoamerica    
    
    
    Olympic #CSR tip: a #sustainability report is like a medal, you have to work and train hard in order to get it.... http://fb.me/12f6PAPhJ     
    
    
    #Sustainability message failing to get thru to middle managers  http://goo.gl/xXFSQ  >Very interesting information to take into account #csr    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Terra Infirma! http://bit.ly/OB1KIC  @GarethKane #csr    
    
    
    At BSD Consulting Spain we are happy to have finished a business plan for sustainable, inclusive acuiculture. I... http://fb.me/2iUmO8qpY     
    
    
    Last days to take the poll: SMEs and Human Rights. Do you see the connection? http://goo.gl/2LNIk  #SME #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    For the sake of credibility > "Why I Love the #Sustainability Report Assurance Process" via @TriplePundit http://goo.gl/CBBG2  #csr    
    
    
    Playing for a better world – and a different consumption via @SwedenSustBlog http://goo.gl/HPA5q  #sustainability    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @JuanVillamayor @davidcoethica    
    
    
    Not very sure if this is the kind of twist we need > "Why the #Green Economy Needs a Marlboro Man" http://goo.gl/gQBtp  #sustainability    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @Juliengoy @diarioresponsab @debmberman    
    
    
    Great article by @mike_earthshine "Mind the gap between corporate behaviour and #sustainability" http://bit.ly/Rfu6hs  #csr    
    
    
    In the UK, small firms urged to be more socially responsible http://goo.gl/g9dIk  #csr #csr4sme > would love to know more about this    
    
    
    Has anyone read #diageo's #csr report? I think I like it!    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @Unilever_Press @JeffHollender @debmberman    
    
    
    #Gay #pride banned for 100yrs, #PussyRiot jailed, #MDNA fined $10m for speaking out? Join the Russian riot NOW http://www.allout.org/en/actions/russianriot …    
    
    
    "Should companies create #CSR departments?" Among other super interesting questions posed by @AmanSinghCSR - http://goo.gl/SwJpS     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @debmberman @UxioMalvido    
    
    
    THX, Honored! @CRISTERENZIO 50 Top #CSR & #Sustainability Accounts @scoopit http://sco.lt/71CN1d  @ElaineCohen @Davidcoethica @JuanVillamayor    
    
    
    Thanks for including me, I'm honored!! 50 Top #CSR and #Sustainability Twitter Accounts to Follow by @braveoneagency - http://goo.gl/Jvm8k     
    
    
    Getting organized for #sustainability: 8 questions to ask http://goo.gl/3z757     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @CatedraTEF_UNED @elainecohen    
    
    
    #CSR Preparing the roundtable on Human Rights and Small and Medium Entreprises that will take place on 12... http://fb.me/uuEKolej     
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights: Both inside and outside count http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights, there is a connection http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Upcoming discussion roundtable on SMEs and Human Rights in Brussels http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Would you like to know more abut who I am and what I do? Check my updated "about me" page on my website.    
    
    
    If not familiar with reading #CSR reports, this is interesting: #Sustainability Reporting? 8 Tips for the Casual Reader http://bit.ly/Qeqc3x     
    
    
    Wishing the PLATO AG team, where I had my first real job back in 1995, a successful User Conference in Lübeck and... http://fb.me/21zkSj6RV     
    
    
    Untrue myths about CSR and SMEs http://goo.gl/YDsGs  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME > Really worth reading    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @aksvi    
    
    
    Why Apple Needs to Bring Back the Philanthropy http://bit.ly/OBWSCa  > money cant buy you love    
    
    
    #GRI G4: Goodbye application levels, good riddance! CC: @GRI_Secretariat #sustainability #csr    
    
    
    The day has come: On Monday 1 October I'm presenting my master thesis on the "Quality of #Sustainability... http://fb.me/142t5IHCt     
    
    
    @TurnMeGreen I like the EU definition: it's taking responsibility for their impacts on society what makes companies sustainable #csr    
    
    
    #CSR: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Sustainable and socially responsible tobacco companies, is it science fiction or could it be reality? With... http://fb.me/1TGnjLtZA     
    
    
    #CSR in the Tobacco Industry: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Hope it was worth reading! @gintzy: Reading: RT @JuanVillamayor: #CSR: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Trasparency, impact management, balance. That's what tobacco companies are missing in their #CSR strategies and... http://fb.me/28jE6th4m     
    
    
    Volunteer work for Economistas Sin Fronteras this morning: Mini conference "CSR for SMEs" at the Ayuntamiento of... http://fb.me/zIG8eNVn     
    
    
    News from Berlin: The future of #CSR? 5th International Conference in Berlin http://bit.ly/Rp79E8  via @csrnews    
    
    
    #Sustainability: slow, but steady progress http://bit.ly/Rd68yv  via @GuardianSustBiz 78% leaders believe sustainability vital for business    
    
    
    Very interesting article on the Business Case for #Sustainability http://bit.ly/VTmqT7  via @CSRWire    
    
    
    Darn! MIssed again :( @susanmcp1: @CiscoNetAcad thanks so much for supporting our #CSRChat!    
    
    
    Any recommendations about #CSR or #sustainability books I should read?    
    
    
    Gracias! @jmagreen Hola Juan, Entre otros, te puedo recomendar Strategy for Sustainability:​ A Business Manifesto, escrito por Adam Werbach    
    
    
    Thanks Jay! @jdthakkar: Sustainable Excellence by @aroncramer and @zacharykarabell Any recommendations about #CSR or #sustainability books?    
    
    
    Thanks for the recommendation! @drewtremblay: @lisahorvat @zoecaron @idutkay @juanvillamayor "Green to Gold"    
    
    
    #Sustainability: The Key to Small Business Survival? http://bit.ly/X8yePA  via @TaigaCompany #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Top tips for communicating #sustainability « http://bit.ly/Xd1VPw  by @guybigwood    
    
    
    CSR and Diversity http://wp.me/p2awtX-1z  #CSR #diversity #CSRfood    
    
    
    #Diversity pays off in terms of performance, employee productivity, innovative ideas, out-of-the-box thinking #CSR http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x     
    
    
    @AoifeCptPlanet Thanks  for the comment, really appreciate it, Aoife!    
    
    
    Like! RT @company2keepinc: 4 ways to help small farmers to be more shock resilient http://c2k.co/53k  #worldfoodday #foodsecurity #PPP    
    
    
    Companies that take #diversity seriously have more chances 2 survive , they face challenges in an innovative way #csr http://businesswithcommonsense.com/2012/10/15/csr-and-diversity/ …    
    
    
    #Diversity pays off in terms of performance, employee productivity, innovative ideas, out-of-the-box thinking  http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x  #CSR    
    
    
    Diverse co's not only better prepared for the future, they're also not boring #Diversity #sustainability http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x  #CSR #diageo    
    
    
    I will be attending the event "Driving Innovation & Value through Responsible & Sustainable Business" on October... http://fb.me/2jPsdMj4E     
    
    
    #csr-reporting: #GRI Application Levels: For and Against - http://bit.ly/WD13pv  by @ElaineCohen    
    
    
    Why are ALL companies going to be #sustainable in the future? Because resources are limited and need to be used... http://fb.me/1mGICOTer     
    
    
    Please lets dont confuse #CSR with a massive branding campaign > "Six marketing lessons from Red Bull Stratos" http://bit.ly/QKpDzZ     
    
    
    "Is there a payoff from top-team #diversity?" http://bit.ly/Q4gfKF  > the question is, what is diversity, only the cultural background?    
    
    
    Nestlé UK Ireland Commitment To FAIRTRADE As KitKat 2-fingers Is Certified http://bit.ly/X0N9O2   via @CSREuropeOrg ¿y en España @Nestle_es?    
    
    
    @NicoFekete You are welcome, Nico! Yep, that's nothing but greenwashing    
    
    
    Great post! RT @MarcGunther Corporate America embraces gays, but what about gay marriage? | new blogpost http://bit.ly/Yq23wA  #csr #lgbt    
    
    
    Thanks from Hamburg! @aksvi: Happy b'day @JuanVillamayor !! - its the 17th already in #India. Have a smashing day & a fabulous year ahead!!    
    
    
    Thx! @TheGreenDen BIG b'day hugs @JuanVillamayor frm the team! Hve a smashing day! @jdthakkar @kcboyce @envirotarian @Sustain_Transpo @aksvi    
    
    
    @aksvi thanks Aks. They certainly have to be careful with their value chain. I had heard this as a rumour before    
    
    
    Do you need a guide for conscious holiday shopping? Here's a useful one developed by Taiga Company. Shop #green... http://fb.me/1pc57zgaV     
    
    
    IIRC Releases Prototype of the International Integrated Reporting Framework http://bit.ly/YjXyoC  > worth a look! #CSR #CSRreporting    
    
    
    My thoughts go to the victims, families and workers of the #Caritas workshop for the handicapped that burnt today in Germany    
    
    
    @barilla I have a question concerning your sustainability report. Could you please tell me whom I should address this question? Thanks    
    
    
    Culture Change Tips from the #Sustainability Masterminds http://bit.ly/Y49RGO  > very useful tips, @GarethKane    
    
    
    Dole Sued for #Greenwashing Guatemalan Banana Operations - http://bit.ly/QvJANe  via @triplepundit > the dangers of fake #CSR?    
    
    
    Like! Very useful: Inexperienced But Passionate: 4 Essential Tips for #CSR & #Sustainability Job Seekers - http://bit.ly/SH2O0J  via @CSRwire    
    
    
    European Commission Publishes Guide To Human Rights For SMEs  http://bit.ly/QGywgd  via @CSREurope > glad I participated! #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Stakeholdercracy: the growing power of stakeholders http://wp.me/p2awtX-1O     
    
    
    Stakeholdercracy: the growing power of stakeholders http://fb.me/2ye5kttDa     
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR    
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Zara, Telecinco, Dole are good examples of the growing power of stakeholders. How companies deal with... http://fb.me/25vGE472K     
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #sustainability #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Do you think  #stakeholders have more and more power? http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR #sustainability    
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #sustainability #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Gracias /Thnks RT's! @diarioresponsab @dandhicks @greendoula @VerantRSE @CapacitaRSE @MikeBeardshall Stakeholdercracy : http://bit.ly/VvISm3     
    
    
    Gracias /Thnks RT's! @RSEonline @joraguer @vinuales81 @SoledadTeixido @andytuit Stakeholdercracy : http://bit.ly/VvISm3     
    
    
    Have you liked me yet? ;) http://on.fb.me/YUdQVy  Everyone a great Friday and a nice weekend!  #CSR #sustainability    
    
    
    Interesting findings, surprised about the 38% > What CEOs Really Think about #Sustainability #CSR http://bit.ly/WQt7kN  via @CSRInternational    
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching the 1st #GRI training ever in Spain 4 companies in the food processing sector 22/23 Jan in Madrid #CSR #CSRfood    
    
    
    "What corporations DO TO society is far more important than what corporations CAN DO FOR society" http://bit.ly/X6OK0q  via @SSIReview #CSR    
    
    
    Blessed r the poor for theirs is the kingdom of God @Pontifex,respectfully,is the Church doing enuff 2 support the poor? #lesspraymoreaction    
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - Happy Holidays http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas    
    
    
    Happy Holidays / Felices Fiestas / Bones Festes http://fb.me/wAbf1za3     
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - Happy Holidays http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013    
    
    
    How to pay lip service to #sustainability http://bit.ly/Rzq0kV  by @GarethKane #CSR    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Happy Holidays to you too! And a great new year :)    
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - My very special Christmas card http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013    
    
    
    Thanks, Felices Fiestas! @company2keepinc: V Nice greeting! #OccupyXmas - My very special Christmas card http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #2013    
    
    
    Having a look at the Business and Human Rights Resource Center #csr http://fb.me/1QoySCQ6m     
    
    
    There is no limit to where innovation and #sustainability can take us. Happy holidays from @TheGreenDen team http://fb.me/xnIZF3Yt     
    
    
    Feliz Navidad/Merry Christmas/Bon Nadal/Frohes Fest/Joyeux Noël/God Jul http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013 #OccupyXmas    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! Boas Festas! Frohe Festtage! ¡Feliz Navidad! from the BSD Consulting Team http://fb.me/1Oh2NKaw5     
    
    
    @Radisson Is this true? If so, how does it fit in2 ur "responsible business" strategy? http://www.mopo.de/nachrichten/-radisson-blu--am-dammtor-reinigungskraefte-klagen-an--ausgebeutet-im-luxus-hotel,5067140,21001270.html … #csr As a fan, I need an explan.    
    
    
    The Top 10 #CSR and #Sustainability Reports of 2012 by @LeonKaye This deserves a closer look! http://fb.me/2rLlPvNSf     
    
    
    @Radisson Thanks for the reply. Looking forward to hearing the results of your investigations    
    
    
    I love beautiful illustrations wishing a happy new year - http://s.shr.lc/W6aZSH  #offtopic #2013 #illustration    
    
    
    Sustainability - No Place for Wimps! http://bit.ly/VT6e09  by @GarethKane > Are you ready to fight for #CSR?    
    
    
    Finding the Right #Sustainability Initiatives for Your Business http://smallbiztrends.com/2013/01/sustainability-initiatives-for-business.html … via @smallbiztrends #CSR    
    
    
    "World's Largest Gaming Company Recognized for #Sustainability" http://bit.ly/WIQD2y  > yeah, but what about its social impact? #CSR    
    
    
    I'd add employment and fair distribution of wealth > Top 10 Stakeholder Issues in 2013 http://s.shr.lc/WIQM68  via @triplepundit #csr    
    
    
    #CSR #HR Human Rights for Small Businesses "Companies should be managed by values to get results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28     
    
    
    Human Rights for Small Businesses "Companies should be managed by values to get results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR    
    
    
    Do Human Rights Apply for Small Businesses? http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR    
    
    
    Human Rights for Small Businesses -  http://xing.com/r/UQqSD  Some learnings from the "guide to human rights for SMEs" published by the Eu...    
    
    
    "Human Rights protected, respected and their violations remedied regardless of economic results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Next week I shall be giving a #GRI certified course about "#Sustainability Reporting in the Food Processing... http://fb.me/1tfDkWn1D     
    
    
    Just a thought before the weekend: #Transparency is the best ally of #sustainability.    
    
    
    @2GEM_CSR Thanks! You too have a nice weekend! Greetings from Barcelona    
    
    
    Everything ready for tomorrow's GRI-certified course on #sustainability reporting in the food industry I'm giving... http://fb.me/2j7LblLuH     
    
    
    Ready 4 the GRI course on #sustainability reporting in the food industry @ Madrid Chamber of Commerce on behalf of @BSDConsulting Spain    
    
    
    Surprised so many companies still think #CSR reporting is a question of quantity, not quality. The value of... http://fb.me/Hb1uyoVn     
    
    
    #Transparency is a two-ways virtue. Companies not only open themselves to public scrutiny, they also make... http://fb.me/2s3gI2S1M     
    
    
    Linear economy is the past> Circular Economy: Own Performance, Not the Product via @ecopreneurist http://ecopreneurist.com/2013/01/28/circular-economy-own-performance-not-the-product/ … vía @envirotarian    
    
    
    #Sustainability in plain language > Cut the Bull**** - Straight Talking & Sustainability http://bit.ly/14rLiTC  by @GarethKane    
    
    
    European Parliament publishes report on #CSR. Will take a look at it. Have you read it? http://www.europarl.europa.eu/sides/getDoc.do?pubRef=-//EP//TEXT+REPORT+A7-2013-0017+0+DOC+XML+V0//EN …    
    
    
    Check out this interview with Priti Ambani, my colleague at GreenDen Consultancy and editor of Ecopreneurist:... http://fb.me/zkkYQIFk     
    
    
    Just finished reading Strategy For #Sustainability, by Adam Werbach. One of the best books I've read on sustainability. Very inspiring.    
    
    
    Communication, key 2 successful CSR http://s.shr.lc/Xklt3E  via @SB_GreenBiz > Not only communication itself, also the process till reporting    
    
    
    Are you aware of business model canvas adapted to sustainable business? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QoAOzMTLP5s … #sustainability    
    
    
    Please give a warm welcome to @BSDConsulting in Berlin, Germany! The new team joins as the 11th office in our... http://fb.me/2fU8xuIy5     
    
    
    Unsustainable practices at Amazon: This is what happens when you don't manage your supply chain in a proper way:... http://fb.me/1T3f93RWu     
    
    
    I'm no longer buying at Amazon until this is clear. @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing... http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    I'm no longer buying at @Amazon until this is clear. @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing... http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    Why #Unilever is not BP http://bit.ly/XoDXks  #sustainability    
    
    
    #6AC up to now, speakers are full of common places. Tell us something really new, please. Long talk about himself by Jim bendell so far    
    
    
    Creating value for companies, society and the environment while applying ethical principles is http://businesswithcommonsense.com  #csr #sustainability    
    
    
    http://businesswithcommonsense.com  today at #6AC #csr #sustainability #sustainable business models #socialInnovation    
    
    
    New jobs with sustainable business models "Rebelling With Your Feet to help Ethiopia: Sole Rebels" http://s.shr.lc/XCt0vL  via @Ecopreneurist    
    
    
    No longer buying at Amazon until this is clear @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing with this? http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    Great article RT @Paulatimpakt 6 Criteria for Selecting a CSR Consultant - Forbes http://onforb.es/11SLpdu  #csr    
    
    
    Communicating #CSR to a Cynical Public - http://s.shr.lc/URaJwo  > tell the truth about your mistakes, you cant fool your stakeholders    
    
    
    Thank you so much, I feel so honored! @CageFreeMedia: #FF @JuanVillamayor, who provides helpful words & news on #CSR and #Sustainability.    
    
    
    Preparing my conference at the EAE Business School this Wednesday: #CSR in Spain. Cultural Differences.    
    
    
    Off to Valencia tomorrow for the #GRI certified training at the Universitat Politécnica. Valencia is always worth a trip!    
    
    
    Cuaderno @foretica: 30 reglas d oro d #RSE para pymes http://www.foretica.org/biblioteca/cuadernos-foretica/doc_details/694-18-las-30-reglas-de-oro-de-la-rse-para-la-pyme?lang=es … by @plemonche @jgomlop @Marta_adaptaRSE @beatrizlorenzol et al.    
    
    
    How many #csr consultants do probono work? Lets take an example from English and Welsh barristers  http://www.barcouncil.org.uk/media-centre/news-and-press-releases/2013/february/bar-survey-barristers-set-leading-csr-example/#.US_d1Us3PYE.twitter …    
    
    
    "We were searching for employees but people turned up instead / Buscábamos empleados y lo que vinieron fueron... http://fb.me/Y0QoQ9to     
    
    
    Reading "The future of corporate reporting" by #KPMG #csr #reporting http://www.kpmg.com/Global/en/IssuesAndInsights/ArticlesPublications/Documents/future-of-corporate-reporting.pdf …    
    
    
    I have very much enjoyed the document "30 golden rules of #CSR for SMEs" published by Forética. It's only too bad... http://fb.me/1sbseaVIN     
    
    
    Please raise your hands those tired of useless #CSR reports that are nothing but a handful of money wasted in... http://fb.me/SonqjBJK     
    
    
    @NeiraSchliemann @DesignThinkers @James_Rock @TimSchuurman_DT Sounds really interesting! Enjoy both the workshop and Amsterdam :)    
    
    
    Happy International Women's Day! Read @Aksvi's post on the business case for women's empowerment. #csr http://fb.me/2h2RvWLfR     
    
    
    Ever heard of the so called "political #CSR"?    
    
    
    "Hershey and Barry Callebaut Lag Industry in Addressing Child Labor" #CSRfood http://feedly.com/k/Yz0rNr     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR vs Co- and self-regulation. Interesting discussion  http://feedly.com/k/XLBTr3     
    
    
    H&M unveils supplier factory list. #Transparency is crucial to #CSR and #sustainability http://about.hm.com/AboutSection/en/About/Sustainability/Commitments/Responsible-Partners/Supply-Chain/SupplierList.html# …    
    
    
    Looking 4 connection points between the #GRI indicators & Christian Felber's Common Good Balance Sheet. GRI cud use some good new indicators    
    
    
    Remarkable! @elainecohen: New on the #CSR Reporting Blog: A fabulous first #SME report http://shrd.by/m98Bgd     
    
    
    Salt, sugar & horsemeat RT @ethicsblogger #food industry: When ethics just isn’t enough http://www.canadianbusiness.com/blogs-and-comment/the-food-industry-when-ethics-just-isnt-enough/ … >Transparency wanted #CSRfood    
    
    
    #Bacardi releases 2012 #CSR report http://www.bacardilimited.com/Content/uploads/corporate/responsible/pdf/corp_resp_report_2012.pdf#page=1&zoom=auto,0,794 … Have a weakness 4 reports made by alcoholic beverage companies, let's have a look!    
    
    
    Companies that Practice "Conscious Capitalism" Perform 10x Better than those who dont > What we need is companies... http://fb.me/1YROhj1tR     
    
    
    @tonyvives Deseando leerlo!    
    
    
    Oxfam released some weeks ago a study about the state of #CSR in food and beverage multinationals. You can... http://fb.me/Ix0B2GuD     
    
    
    Most, if not all, #CSR strategies, #sustainability reports fail to demonstrate their overall contribution to... http://fb.me/2t6loFt1U     
    
    
    Some so called ethical banks, like the @GLSbank, still have a long way to learn how to deal with stakeholders,... http://fb.me/21iu0AdsE     
    
    
    In Madrid attending @foretica's event "CSR Spain 2013" #csr #rsc #rse    
    
    
    I have my doubts that Integrated Reporting will satisfy the needs of mainstream stakeholders. It will be good for... http://fb.me/PyMRMrXW     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRfood Romantic image vs Factory aseptical: Food companies who want to be transparent after the horsemeat... http://fb.me/2Jt2laudO     
    
    
    M.Porter unveils HIS health & happiness index http://ht.ly/k6HIQ  Thought we already had the human development index    
    
    
    "Ben & Jerry's Social Mission"  • good read #csr #sustainablebusiness http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/04/ben-jerrys-social-mission/ …    
    
    
    RSC.-Burger King regalará patatas gratis x alcanzar 250.000 fans en Facebook. Esto es #RSC??? #AntiRSE #ActivismoRSC http://www.europapress.es/nacional/noticia-rsc-burger-king-regalara-patatas-gratis-proximo-viernes-haber-alcanzado-250000-fans-facebook-20130419154517.html …    
    
    
    @JuanVillamayor: "EU Corporate Reporting proposal not strong enough to improve company behaviour". Too discretional http://www.business-humanrights.org/Links/Repository/1018468 …    
    
    
    It's #greenwashing when you try to distract public attention from your negative impacts by stressing positive... http://fb.me/BkwszZ4t     
    
    
    #CSR Communication: Quality, not quantity http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    The more indicators, the better. Wrong! #CSR #CSRreporting http://fb.me/2pRkvwrDb     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRreporting The more indicators, the better. Wrong!  http://fb.me/2pRkvwrDb     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRreporting "The more indicators are reported, the more sustainable the company is". This is how a... http://fb.me/2L7ee4ri1     
    
    
    For a company, the value of #csr reporting lies mainly on the process, not on the quantity of indicators http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    For a company, the value of #csr reporting lies mainly on the process, not on the quantity of indicators http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    "Hundreds Die in Bangladesh, You Save Money"  http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/04/hundreds-die-bangladesh-save-money/ …    
    
    
    Stakeholders need relevant information, a true picture of the company, not an overwhelming battery of indicators #CSR http://businesswithcommonsense.wordpress.com/2013/04/27/csr-communication-quality-not-quantity/ …    
    
    
    #CSR communication has many faces. Effective CSR communication sometimes requires different channels, depending... http://fb.me/2e9EQFN1N     
    
    
    Done! @theecosaurus Help protect #consumers from the #SFI's false #eco-label Tell the FTC 2 improve #green guidelines http://ow.ly/kr5Ne     
    
    
    The more indicators, the more sustainable the company is? #csr #CSRreporting http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l " CSR communication with Quality    
    
    
    "Shud co's source from Bangladesh?" http://s.shr.lc/18i8wOX  Real question: shud co's take responsibiity, no matter where they source from?    
    
    
    As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    As a #CSR consultant, who am I accountable to? my client? its stakeholders? Society? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Thanks! @nmartellbundock: Good question... As a CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u  via @JuanVillamayor    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    This post is over a year old. We are still waiting for a Spanish National CSR Plan http://businesswithcommonsense.wordpress.com/2012/01/27/hello-world/ …    
    
    
    @FairPhone too good to be true! Can't wait to see this turned into reality    
    
    
    @Abercrombie If what's said on the article is true, you cant get any more "uncool" than this. This is derogatory,... http://fb.me/IxECIkWI     
    
    
    @AndreaLearned lucky you! enjoy    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    @JuanVillamayor: @FabianPattberg @aksvi greetings to you both! And all the best to @sustforum!!    
    
    
    Did you take the poll? As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    THIS is #sustainability: self-healing fabrics... http://fb.me/2yxJMsloT     
    
    
    In Amsterdam, learning about the new G4 #sustainability reporting guidelines. #GRI. Very interesting topic though... http://fb.me/1bzcQYzLJ     
    
    
    The new #GRI G4 guidelines will make it more difficult to publish a #CSR report without having a proper... http://fb.me/1Hz4GaIUV     
    
    
    New #GRI reporting guidelines: https://www.globalreporting.org/reporting/g4/Pages/default.aspx … A, B, C levels? Good riddance! Core or comprehensive, that's the question    
    
    
    If true, an example of Corporate Social Irresponsibility. And I bet this happens not only in Germany... http://fb.me/CpMGvaa9     
    
    
    @GreenbizStartup welcome back, Simone!    
    
    
    Flying back to Barcelona. It was great meeting my new colleagues @EHSustainableM and @CVHH2011 in Hamburg #csr    
    
    
    G4: It's NOT about #materiality http://feedly.com/k/ZAxoAc  by @elainecohen >As in G3.1 it's the process towards materiality what counts    
    
    
    Two weeks after publishing the new G4 reporting guidelines, I think some disclosures and new indicators are missing. You miss anything?    
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity: Let's report! http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    For more trust and transparency. Ethics and Integrity: Let's report! http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    New standard disclosures on Ethics and Integrity. A good chance for companies to report on their values and codes... http://fb.me/IDrY1Pvl     
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity make their GRI debut, hopefully for more trust and transparency. http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    Speakers are making way too many sexist jokes, it's not funny anymore. @TEDxhamburg #tedxhamburg    
    
    
    Will social media save or kill #CSR reporting? http://feedly.com/k/13070wy  > it will help channel specific information to specific audiences    
    
    
    Developing a sustainable business model canvas, inspired in the one created by Osterwalder. It's a very useful graphic and ideation tool!    
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity make their GRI debut, hopefully for more trust and transparency. http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    Very interesting article > McDonald's Customers Don't Buy Salads - But Whose Fault is That? - http://s.shr.lc/15RJ40P  via @triplepundit    
    
    
    What does a $14 shirt really cost? http://fb.me/2NMcyLvrF     
    
    
    Ralph Lauren finally decides to publish a #sustainability report after pressure from an investor http://feedly.com/k/17016C5     
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    GRI G4: A Gateway to Meaningful #Sustainability Reporting? http://s.shr.lc/13AdTpX  via @CSRwire >Me too, it's a step in the good direction    
    
    
    +1 @DavidKlingen: Interesting @Unilever CEO: 4 sustainable business, against 'mindless consumption' http://shrd.by/rjQ6kd  via @AmanSinghCSR    
    
    
    Project for an alternative beyond economic growth http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/how-on-earth-a-book-for-a-new-economy … via @donmacca > We need to re-think our current economic model    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Of Consultants And Their #Stakeholders #CSR #stakeholder http://wp.me/p2awtX-2J     
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a tool/app that allows working with Facebook,Twitter, Goggle+ &LinkedIn at the same time? Tired of switching back&forth    
    
    
    Of Consultants And Their #Stakeholders #CSR #stakeholder http://wp.me/p2awtX-2J  "There goes your reputation as a consultant down the drain"    
    
    
    Y se quedan tan panchos: Perlas en #RSE by @tonyvives http://www.diarioresponsable.com/portada/destacados/16594.html …    
    
    
    10 tips stakeholder engagement with activists http://s.shr.lc/15LB5zO  via @GreenBiz > Dont remove negative comments, dont call the cops etc    
    
    
    "Reputation is overrated" @helenaancos: The frame of corporate #reputation http://helenaancos.com/2012/06/27/the-frame-of-corporate-reputation/ …    
    
    
    Great news but, where are the cars??? > IKEA Doubles Down on EV Charging Stations at Retail Stores http://feedly.com/k/12qxdqa     
    
    
    Does it??? > Does Nestlé's Bottled Water Pass the 'Creating Shared Value' Test? - http://s.shr.lc/10peZ7N  via @triplepundit    
    
    
    Another reason to be sustainable: Three reasons job seekers prefer sustainable companies http://feedly.com/k/11NjAlh     
    
    
    ‘Sustainable’ German Auto Companies Lobby to Stop EU Climate Regulation http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/07/german-auto-companies-sustainable-lobby-stop-eu-climate-regulation/ … #AntiCSR #AntiRSC    
    
    
    @bewastewise & @TheGreenDen: 1st panel on July 10 "Recycling in North-American Cities" http://wastewise.be/ai1ec_event/recycling-in-north-american-cities/?instance_id=237 … #wastewise #sustainability    
    
    
    @BeWasteWise Offers a Series of Online Talks to Promote Dialogue on Waste Management #wastewise http://fb.me/6mh7laZeK     
    
    
    4 Inaccurate Assumptions About Social Media for #Sustainability and #CSR Communications via @taigacompany http://fb.me/1ePnWce2H     
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Hi Julie, yes, I have been a little quiet on twitter but I am back! I hope you are doing great too, enjoy the summer!    
    
    
    Thanks for the great pieces of advise! @tobiaswebb76: Some lessons learned from #sustainability and #CSR training: http://shrd.by/FXkD2j     
    
    
    @viet_ha_ Thank you! I'm glad you like it, tho I've been a little lazy lately. Greetings to Toronto, I love that city!    
    
    
    Agree! @BenjaFagerland A good @HuffPostBiz post of @alicekorngold on unconscious biases, #diverseboards and #corpgov http://huff.to/1dwpWXZ     
    
    
    Sounds like Economy 4 the Common Good http://www.gemeinwohl-oekonomie.org/en  Common Wealth Cntributins By Business via @Ecopreneurist http://ecopreneurist.com/2013/07/22/expecting-more-from-business-common-wealth-contributions-by-business-part-2/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+IM-ecopreneurist+%28Ecopreneurist%29 …    
    
    
    Great ideas. Israeli invents a 9$ bicycle made of cardboard http://www.social-startups.de/fahrrad-aus-pappe/ …    
    
    
    "George Clooney and Nespresso" u can't create an unsustainable product & then pretend u found the solution http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/07/george-clooney-coffee-pod-problem/ …    
    
    
    ROI of #CSR: Cargill's new tool quantifies return on investment for #sustainability initiatives http://www.foodnavigator-usa.com/Suppliers2/Cargill-s-new-tool-quantifies-return-on-investment-for-sustainability-initiatives?utm_source=copyright&utm_medium=OnSite&utm_campaign=copyright …    
    
    
    I find that the concept of "overall impact on society, economy and environment" is often being neglected when we... http://fb.me/2UXhPAKHf     
    
    
    I find that the concept of "overall impact on society, economy and environment" is often neglected when we talk about a company's #CSR    
    
    
    Sustainable Summer: The Common Good Approach #CSR #Sustainability http://wp.me/p2awtX-2Y     
    
    
    Gracias! @RSCDigital: ' We need clear rankings' Sustainable Summer: The Common Good Approach #CSR #Sustainability http://wp.me/p2awtX-2Y     
    
    
    Thanks so much! @terrafiniti: #FF @greeneconpost @greenbiztweets @practicallygrn @JuanVillamayor for green and #sustainability news!    
    
    
    One month... until THE FUTURE OF SUSTAINABILITY REPORTING event on 6 September in Berlin, Germany organised by... http://fb.me/GV9ifvZ6     
    
    
    Good read! RT @CarbonImpact: Swamped by #sustainability indicators failing to drive transformation http://zite.to/1cwNKyF  via @guardian #GRI    
    
    
    Abgeschminkt! Bilder in Nachhaltigkeitsberichten http://csr-news.net/main/2013/08/09/abgeschminkt-die-bilderwelten-der-nachhaltigkeitsberichte/?lp_lang_pref=de … > Why do many #GRI reports show only beautiful people? (GERMAN)    
    
    
    Abgeschminkt! http://csr-news.net/main/2013/08/09/abgeschminkt-die-bilderwelten-der-nachhaltigkeitsberichte/?lp_lang_pref=de … > Why do many #GRI reports show only beautiful people? by @EikeHellmann und Annika Martens    
    
    
    Funny video about gender-specific advertising http://youtu.be/Vmnt31UgGT4  #responsibleads #csr    
    
    
    @CarbonImpact You too, Fred, enjoy the summer!    
    
    
    @LeonKaye Hey Leon, belated thanks for #FF, hope you are enjoying the summer!    
    
    
    LOL @GarethKane: And the environmental jargon of the day award goes to 'enhanced basal lubrication' sounds like some spam I got recently...    
    
    
    Sounds great! @susanmcp1 Come work with me! hiring a marketing & new biz mngr in @FentonProgress's NY office http://www.fenton.com/careers/  #CSR #PR    
    
    
    Like! > The Backbone of a Small Business #Sustainability Strategy http://blog.taigacompany.com/blog/sustainability-business-life-environment/the-backbone-of-a-small-business-sustainability-strategy … by @taigacompany #CSR #CSRforSME    
    
    
    This one is dedicated to Julie @taigacompany. Always with my bike! Many greetings from Barcelona! pic.twitter.com/EEd9JZUq1M    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Glad you like it! What would we do without bicycles??? <3    
    
    
    @aksvi @AmanSinghCSR @namratarana @jdthakkar @WayneVisser Mandatory sounds scary but sometimes it's the only way. That said,prefer voluntary    
    
    
    AccountAbility releases report on Materiality: Non-financial materiality matters! http://s.shr.lc/16KWDic  via @CSRWire #CSR    
    
    
    Coming soon: The shortcomings of #CSR. Meanwhile, enjoying a well deserved summer break.    
    
    
    "Creating shared value: Revolution or clever con? By @WayneVisser > IMHO CSV is just a part of real #CSR 2.0 http://www.csrinternational.org/2013/08/20/creating-shared-value-revolution-or-clever-con/ …    
    
    
    @elainecohen tells us about "The first G4 Sustainability Report in the World" > need to check it http://csr-reporting.blogspot.com/2013/08/the-first-g4-sustainability-report-in.html …    
    
    
    "Transparent Disclosure to Stakeholders Critical for Corporations Today" Will stakeholders rule? #csr http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/08/21/transparent-disclosure-to-stakeholders-critical-for-corporations-today/ …    
    
    
    GRI G4-PR7: Non-compliance with regulations & voluntary codes concerning marketing comms: sexist, non-inclusive ads still a big issue    
    
    
    Thanks for #FF, Leon! @LeonKaye @mary_mazzoni @NateLipka @joconfino @BeyondMeat @paolafiore @CarbonImpact @KoreaCSR @FashionGreen    
    
    
    @elanecohen: G4 Tip of the Day(17): In #G4 Reports, material issues should smack you in the face. If they don't, it's not G4....    
    
    
    In Spain #CSR is shifting to philanthropy/corporate giving, leaving its strategic approach aside and missing all kind of opportunities    
    
    
    #CSR is the way, good reputation is the consequence (if CSR is real #sustainability and not just charity or #greenwashing)    
    
    
    Good one! RT @jfonru: “@JuanVillamayor: #CSR is the way, good reputation is the consequence (...)"  and #ethics is the foundation    
    
    
    Exactly 20 years ago I took my 1st course on Business Ethics (Wirtschaftsethik) at the University of Augsburg. So long ago... Good choice!    
    
    
    "How to Win Customers and Save Money with Sustainable Products" now this is #sustainability http://feedly.com/k/148uwNk     
    
    
    Counting down to Friday... a full day on #Reporting 3.0 in Berlin. Organised by @BSDConsulting Germany #CSR http://fb.me/2EoeCfFRb     
    
    
    G4 Tip ofthe day(25): Transition from G3 to G4 with consistency. The objective is G4, not G3 plus new bits.#UG4 http://fb.me/2tG0cIExc     
    
    
    "In G4, Material Aspects should be boundary specific: the place where they occur must be identified" http://s.shr.lc/1dTWNeN  by @elainecohen    
    
    
    I wonder how many companies will secretly decide to report CORE so that they won't have to disclose G5-54 & G4-55 #GRI #G4 #CSR #governance    
    
    
    NL leading the way on sustainable business http://s.shr.lc/1el9q2N  via @GuardianSustbiz "a strong consensus-driven approach"    
    
    
    Could anyone recommend me any energy efficiency gurus? Thanks and have a good Sunday/week!    
    
    
    "31 Tips for writing a G4 Report" great tips by @elainecohen #csr #reporting #gri http://csr-reporting.blogspot.com/2013/09/31-tips-for-writing-g4-report.html …    
    
    
    #Sustainability strategy not equal sustainable business. Just saying.    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. Part I http://wp.me/p2awtX-32     
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. "CSR fails to reflect a company's overall contribution to the common good" http://wp.me/p2awtX-32     
    
    
    Interesting view on McDo's #CSR strategy: "#Sustainability at McDonald’s. Really." http://www.marcgunther.com/sustainability-at-mcdonalds-really/ … by @marcgunther    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. "CSR fails to reflect a company's contribution to the common good" http://wp.me/p2awtX-32  >but we can solve it!    
    
    
    Do you think the new GRI G4 guidelines give more value to #sustainability reports? I do! Both company & its stakeholders will benefit    
    
    
    5 ways companies are making packaging more sustainable "Clearer labeling, lifecycle approach etc" http://s.shr.lc/1cK8YJS  via @GreenBiz    
    
    
    "Hershey Converts Two More Plants to Zero Waste to Landfill" this is #sustainability http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/10/23/hershey-converts-two-more-plants-to-zero-waste-to-landfill/ …    
    
    
    "Sainsbury’s ‘Water Neutral’ Store Saves About 1bn Liters of Water Annually" this is #sustainability http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/10/23/sainsburys-water-neutral-store-saves-about-1bn-liters-of-water-annually/ …    
    
    
    My two previous tweets are examples of how #csr means #sustainability and not #philanthropy or corporate giving    
    
    
    Agree @PuigGarciaSmith When a company's CSR is only philantropy, it is charity washing. CSR means sustainability &, if possibly, philantropy    
    
    
    "GRI G4 Materiality Assessment – Validation of Material Aspects" very interesting read http://icarbonnews.com/gri-g4-materiality-tool-validation-of-material-aspects/ …    
    
    
    Interesting @helenaancos: role & geography of the Big 4 auditors in the offshore tax haven business @RichardJMurphy http://www.taxresearch.org.uk/Documents/Where4Art.pdf …    
    
    
    Credit Suisse: #LGBT invstmnt index http://www.corporateregister.com//news/item/?n=560 … >Do they outpetform due 2 employee retention,bettr reflection of customers needs?    
    
    
    Interesting initiative to push Electric Vehicles - http://s.shr.lc/18qKe1V  ia @sustainablebizz #sustainablebusiness    
    
    
    Mercy me! @susanmcp1: Fascinating look at a big player in corporate #philanthropy: '@GoldmanSachs, Buying Redemption' http://nyti.ms/1dwSJAv     
    
    
    CSR Reports: Let's include issues that really matter to stakeholders, shall we? Luckily more and more companies are applying this already    
    
    
    While the rest of the world concentrates on sustainable business strategies, we Spaniards are still blinded by corporate giving…    
    
    
    Heja Sverige! @Mgutierrezalv: Swedish Government Leads the Way on Sustainability with not ‘traditional’ regulation. http://ow.ly/27z1fG     
    
    
    Is your supply chain a ticking time bomb? http://www.terrainfirma.co.uk/blog/2013/11/is-your-supply-chain-a-ticking-time-bomb.html … by @GarethKane #sustainability #supplychain #CSR    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. Part II http://wp.me/p2awtX-3g     
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR: failing to reflect overall contribution to common good http://wp.me/p2awtX-3g     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://lnkd.in/dVN2JrH     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Why reporting and sustainability strategies are not enough http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Companies who cause important negative externalities are often encouraged NOT to change their way of doing business http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a #CSR that makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr  #sustainability    
    
    
    BSD's final G4 Trainings this year in: Lisboa, México D.F., Geneva, Porto Alegre. For details:... http://fb.me/18YM5tl1m     
    
    
    Five Reasons You Will Be Using GRI’s New G4 Guidelines Sometime Soon by @elainecohen http://s.shr.lc/182VL8y  > G4 is reporting that matters    
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a #CSR that makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr  #sustainability    
    
    
    H&M Makes Commitment to Pay a Fair Living Wage By 2018 - http://s.shr.lc/1iVYdFB     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Startup helps restaurants and groceries turn food waste into fertilizar > innovation & #sustainability http://feeds.importantmedia.org/~r/IM-ecopreneurist/~3/ybYrjgeroiU/ …    
    
    
    5 lessons from the Japanese “kaizen” approach to #sustainability http://www.greenbiz.com/blog/2013/12/03/5-lessons-japanese-kaizen-approach-sustainability?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+greenbuzz+%28GreenBiz%29 …    
    
    
    The #GRI offers a new "Materiality Matters" check for G4 #CSR reports: http://www.stream-eu.com/index.php/news/113-materiality-matters-check … #reporting    
    
    
    #Sustainability is simplicity is happiness #2014 http://wp.me/p2awtX-3q     
    
    
    Happy holidays and a great 2014 ***#Sustainability is simplicity is happiness*** pic.twitter.com/jxX6Pijmdv    
    
    
    Dear #CSR Gang: Happy holidays and a great 2014!!! #Sustainability is simplicity is happiness pic.twitter.com/jxX6Pijmdv    
    
    
    Thanks @josephineECO Holiday cheer from Barcelona to lovely Toronto! #HappyHolidays    
    
    
    Just updated my twitter profile: Consultant in #CSR/#Sustainability. Sustainable business models. Sustainability... http://fb.me/17ZCk5VLX     
    
    
    Very interesting question > ‘Why Do Good People Do Bad Things?’ The Role of Spiritual Intelligence http://feedly.com/e/2WrBYIHd  #Business #Ethics    
    
    
    CSR managers will deal with stakeholder dialogue, business modeling & reporting >The evolution of the #CSR manager: http://s.shr.lc/1kPDIZh     
    
    
    Have yourself a merry little Christmas (and a sustainable 2014) #xmas #2014 pic.twitter.com/b4Wh64X0zJ    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Thanks Julie, you too! All the best for the new year XXX    
    
    
    "Getting the most out of #Sustainability Report Interviews" Great, useful post, Elaine @elainecohen http://feedly.com/k/1btVlbY     
    
    
    Coming soon: my new year's resolutions (for both business and personal life). The most important one is on my... http://fb.me/1Rqyog4pJ     
    
    
    The Top Ten #CSR Reports of 2013 http://feedly.com/e/EOF08RCU  by @elainecohen #RSE > Love your AIM method, Elaine. HNY!!!    
    
    
    Feliz 2014! @FRSIberoamerica @dresponsable @tonyvives @aandreup @iroser_RSE @germangranda @plemonche @anavaz73 @CarmenMarti_ @jalmagro    
    
    
    How to use Twitter effectively for #CSR/#sustainability communications http://s.shr.lc/1cqinnK  via @CSRExaminer    
    
    
    Cities of the future: Challenges for the developing world http://feedly.com/e/wDrxNLgr  by @aksvi #sustainability    
    
    
    #Sustainability Execs Should Look to ‘Mavericks and Outsiders’ > good approach http://www.environmentalleader.com/2014/01/07/sustainability-execs-should-look-to-mavericks-and-outsiders/ …    
    
    
    ISO 26000:2010 Comprender la norma by @syeconsulting #iso26000 #rse http://www.diarioresponsable.com/portada/opinion/17005-iso-260002010-comprender-la-norma.html …    
    
    
    Microsoft's #sustainability predictions for 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/greenbuzz/~3/c2OZAUU2aYQ/microsoft-sustainability-predictions-2014 …    
    
    
    I miss #CSR reports that include critical views from stakeholders. @elainecohen do you think that reports shud incl. constructive criticism?    
    
    
    #CSR makes u win: Affordable, good food; Trustworthy behavior; Trash in2 cash; Clean technologies; Women leaders http://s.shr.lc/1hQjfUy     
    
    
    @elainecohen @estrujillo I dont find it very often in reports though; it would offer a very balanced view of the business    
    
    
    @BSDConsulting Thank you! :)    
    
    
    Ten tips for SMEs to get the most out of their #sustainability strategies http://s.shr.lc/1alrVRi  #CSR #csr4sme via @GuardianSustBiz    
    
    
    Next dates for #GRI trainings with @BSDConsulting all over the world. Check it up! http://fb.me/3FVYvxDbY     
    
    
    This is too good: RT @bizethicartoons: Good Christmas feelings about corporate social responsibility #CSR pic.twitter.com/lsKz6zCKcg    
    
    
    Three sustainability resolutions for all businesses in 2014 http://feedly.com/e/Qs2lL33J  vía @GuardianSustBiz #sustainability #csr    
    
    
    Good one! @GarethKane: We need 2 accept the inherent ambiguities of #sustainability and leap into the dark –otherwise we’ll achieve nothing.    
    
    
    Mandatory CSR? Yes but no. http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR? Yes but no. In some cases, for some aspects. http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR? Yes but no. No but yes http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Great post, Elaine. Why the battle??? New on @elainecohen's blog: #GRI vs. #IIRC. vs #SASB: Round Nine. All Lose. http://shrd.by/fWcV10     
    
    
    Microvinyas: ethical vineyards producing wine for the common good http://s.shr.lc/1jkG85M  #sustainability #CommonGood    
    
    
    #CSR is empathy applied to business, what impacts u have on others / #RSE es empatía aplicada a la empresa, qué impactos hay sobre los demás    
    
    
    A business with empathy is a successful business. #Sustainability and empathy are closely linked.    
    
    
    Dont miss the dates for the next GRI certified training courses provided by @BSDConsulting http://fb.me/6uts0yExH     
    
    
    2012 #CSR & #Sustainability Salary Survey Results Released http://bit.ly/LS1ggo     
    
    
    Good approach! > #Sustainability is nothing more than good business in a changing environment http://bit.ly/Mnj5Cj     
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights. Do you see the connection? http://wp.me/p2awtX-S     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @ISDuurzaam @DaveStangis    
    
    
    Small Businesses and Human Rights, do you see the connection? http://wp.me/p12b0J-gu  #SME #SMEs #CSR #Sustainability    
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights, is there a connection? Or is it only for multinationals http://wp.me/p12b0J-gu  #SME #csr4sme #CSR #Sustainability    
    
    
    Some good tips about making a Business Case out of #CSR http://goo.gl/xeLS6     
    
    
    Do SMEs have a responsibility on Human Rights? http://juanvillamayor.wordpress.com/2012/07/12/pymes-y-derechos-humanos-ves-la-conexion/ … #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    @excelenciacl  @schwild @jgomlop @borjavega @Coethica @trinipa Gracias por RTs /Thanks for RTs! SMEs and Human Rights http://bit.ly/OH6FXh     
    
    
    Here is a list of interesting business ethics movies you might want to watch this summer #csr #ethics http://fb.me/1cXHzLPNg     
    
    
    It’s Not Rocket Science to Change a Lightbulb http://bit.ly/SuSV5S  by @earthprints #green #sustainability    
    
    
    "Human Rights are for governments, not for small and medium enterprises" Do you agree? http://bit.ly/OH6FXh  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    “Better CSR Advice To SMEs” Event Report Now Available http://goo.gl/Af84g  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    What's the social purpose of your company? Great question! http://goo.gl/t1fQP  va @ELdaily #CSR    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @FabianGPastor    
    
    
    Do SMEs have a responsibility on Human Rights? http://juanvillamayor.wordpress.com/2012/07/12/pymes-y-derechos-humanos-ves-la-conexion/ … #CSR #SME #CSR4SME    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @FRSIberoamerica    
    
    
    Olympic #CSR tip: a #sustainability report is like a medal, you have to work and train hard in order to get it.... http://fb.me/12f6PAPhJ     
    
    
    #Sustainability message failing to get thru to middle managers  http://goo.gl/xXFSQ  >Very interesting information to take into account #csr    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Terra Infirma! http://bit.ly/OB1KIC  @GarethKane #csr    
    
    
    At BSD Consulting Spain we are happy to have finished a business plan for sustainable, inclusive acuiculture. I... http://fb.me/2iUmO8qpY     
    
    
    Last days to take the poll: SMEs and Human Rights. Do you see the connection? http://goo.gl/2LNIk  #SME #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    For the sake of credibility > "Why I Love the #Sustainability Report Assurance Process" via @TriplePundit http://goo.gl/CBBG2  #csr    
    
    
    Playing for a better world – and a different consumption via @SwedenSustBlog http://goo.gl/HPA5q  #sustainability    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @JuanVillamayor @davidcoethica    
    
    
    Not very sure if this is the kind of twist we need > "Why the #Green Economy Needs a Marlboro Man" http://goo.gl/gQBtp  #sustainability    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @Juliengoy @diarioresponsab @debmberman    
    
    
    Great article by @mike_earthshine "Mind the gap between corporate behaviour and #sustainability" http://bit.ly/Rfu6hs  #csr    
    
    
    In the UK, small firms urged to be more socially responsible http://goo.gl/g9dIk  #csr #csr4sme > would love to know more about this    
    
    
    Has anyone read #diageo's #csr report? I think I like it!    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @Unilever_Press @JeffHollender @debmberman    
    
    
    #Gay #pride banned for 100yrs, #PussyRiot jailed, #MDNA fined $10m for speaking out? Join the Russian riot NOW http://www.allout.org/en/actions/russianriot …    
    
    
    "Should companies create #CSR departments?" Among other super interesting questions posed by @AmanSinghCSR - http://goo.gl/SwJpS     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @debmberman @UxioMalvido    
    
    
    THX, Honored! @CRISTERENZIO 50 Top #CSR & #Sustainability Accounts @scoopit http://sco.lt/71CN1d  @ElaineCohen @Davidcoethica @JuanVillamayor    
    
    
    Thanks for including me, I'm honored!! 50 Top #CSR and #Sustainability Twitter Accounts to Follow by @braveoneagency - http://goo.gl/Jvm8k     
    
    
    Getting organized for #sustainability: 8 questions to ask http://goo.gl/3z757     
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @CatedraTEF_UNED @elainecohen    
    
    
    #CSR Preparing the roundtable on Human Rights and Small and Medium Entreprises that will take place on 12... http://fb.me/uuEKolej     
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights: Both inside and outside count http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    SMEs and Human Rights, there is a connection http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Upcoming discussion roundtable on SMEs and Human Rights in Brussels http://wp.me/p2awtX-15  #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Would you like to know more abut who I am and what I do? Check my updated "about me" page on my website.    
    
    
    If not familiar with reading #CSR reports, this is interesting: #Sustainability Reporting? 8 Tips for the Casual Reader http://bit.ly/Qeqc3x     
    
    
    Wishing the PLATO AG team, where I had my first real job back in 1995, a successful User Conference in Lübeck and... http://fb.me/21zkSj6RV     
    
    
    Untrue myths about CSR and SMEs http://goo.gl/YDsGs  #CSR #SME #CSR4SME > Really worth reading    
    
    
    The #CSR Gang Weekly is out! http://bit.ly/hVftzn  ▸ Top stories today via @aksvi    
    
    
    Why Apple Needs to Bring Back the Philanthropy http://bit.ly/OBWSCa  > money cant buy you love    
    
    
    #GRI G4: Goodbye application levels, good riddance! CC: @GRI_Secretariat #sustainability #csr    
    
    
    The day has come: On Monday 1 October I'm presenting my master thesis on the "Quality of #Sustainability... http://fb.me/142t5IHCt     
    
    
    @TurnMeGreen I like the EU definition: it's taking responsibility for their impacts on society what makes companies sustainable #csr    
    
    
    #CSR: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Sustainable and socially responsible tobacco companies, is it science fiction or could it be reality? With... http://fb.me/1TGnjLtZA     
    
    
    #CSR in the Tobacco Industry: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Hope it was worth reading! @gintzy: Reading: RT @JuanVillamayor: #CSR: Impacts and smoke curtains http://wp.me/p2awtX-1g     
    
    
    Trasparency, impact management, balance. That's what tobacco companies are missing in their #CSR strategies and... http://fb.me/28jE6th4m     
    
    
    Volunteer work for Economistas Sin Fronteras this morning: Mini conference "CSR for SMEs" at the Ayuntamiento of... http://fb.me/zIG8eNVn     
    
    
    News from Berlin: The future of #CSR? 5th International Conference in Berlin http://bit.ly/Rp79E8  via @csrnews    
    
    
    #Sustainability: slow, but steady progress http://bit.ly/Rd68yv  via @GuardianSustBiz 78% leaders believe sustainability vital for business    
    
    
    Very interesting article on the Business Case for #Sustainability http://bit.ly/VTmqT7  via @CSRWire    
    
    
    Darn! MIssed again :( @susanmcp1: @CiscoNetAcad thanks so much for supporting our #CSRChat!    
    
    
    Any recommendations about #CSR or #sustainability books I should read?    
    
    
    Gracias! @jmagreen Hola Juan, Entre otros, te puedo recomendar Strategy for Sustainability:​ A Business Manifesto, escrito por Adam Werbach    
    
    
    Thanks Jay! @jdthakkar: Sustainable Excellence by @aroncramer and @zacharykarabell Any recommendations about #CSR or #sustainability books?    
    
    
    Thanks for the recommendation! @drewtremblay: @lisahorvat @zoecaron @idutkay @juanvillamayor "Green to Gold"    
    
    
    #Sustainability: The Key to Small Business Survival? http://bit.ly/X8yePA  via @TaigaCompany #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Top tips for communicating #sustainability « http://bit.ly/Xd1VPw  by @guybigwood    
    
    
    CSR and Diversity http://wp.me/p2awtX-1z  #CSR #diversity #CSRfood    
    
    
    #Diversity pays off in terms of performance, employee productivity, innovative ideas, out-of-the-box thinking #CSR http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x     
    
    
    @AoifeCptPlanet Thanks  for the comment, really appreciate it, Aoife!    
    
    
    Like! RT @company2keepinc: 4 ways to help small farmers to be more shock resilient http://c2k.co/53k  #worldfoodday #foodsecurity #PPP    
    
    
    Companies that take #diversity seriously have more chances 2 survive , they face challenges in an innovative way #csr http://businesswithcommonsense.com/2012/10/15/csr-and-diversity/ …    
    
    
    #Diversity pays off in terms of performance, employee productivity, innovative ideas, out-of-the-box thinking  http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x  #CSR    
    
    
    Diverse co's not only better prepared for the future, they're also not boring #Diversity #sustainability http://bit.ly/V1jJ2x  #CSR #diageo    
    
    
    I will be attending the event "Driving Innovation & Value through Responsible & Sustainable Business" on October... http://fb.me/2jPsdMj4E     
    
    
    #csr-reporting: #GRI Application Levels: For and Against - http://bit.ly/WD13pv  by @ElaineCohen    
    
    
    Why are ALL companies going to be #sustainable in the future? Because resources are limited and need to be used... http://fb.me/1mGICOTer     
    
    
    Please lets dont confuse #CSR with a massive branding campaign > "Six marketing lessons from Red Bull Stratos" http://bit.ly/QKpDzZ     
    
    
    "Is there a payoff from top-team #diversity?" http://bit.ly/Q4gfKF  > the question is, what is diversity, only the cultural background?    
    
    
    Nestlé UK Ireland Commitment To FAIRTRADE As KitKat 2-fingers Is Certified http://bit.ly/X0N9O2   via @CSREuropeOrg ¿y en España @Nestle_es?    
    
    
    @NicoFekete You are welcome, Nico! Yep, that's nothing but greenwashing    
    
    
    Great post! RT @MarcGunther Corporate America embraces gays, but what about gay marriage? | new blogpost http://bit.ly/Yq23wA  #csr #lgbt    
    
    
    Thanks from Hamburg! @aksvi: Happy b'day @JuanVillamayor !! - its the 17th already in #India. Have a smashing day & a fabulous year ahead!!    
    
    
    Thx! @TheGreenDen BIG b'day hugs @JuanVillamayor frm the team! Hve a smashing day! @jdthakkar @kcboyce @envirotarian @Sustain_Transpo @aksvi    
    
    
    @aksvi thanks Aks. They certainly have to be careful with their value chain. I had heard this as a rumour before    
    
    
    Do you need a guide for conscious holiday shopping? Here's a useful one developed by Taiga Company. Shop #green... http://fb.me/1pc57zgaV     
    
    
    IIRC Releases Prototype of the International Integrated Reporting Framework http://bit.ly/YjXyoC  > worth a look! #CSR #CSRreporting    
    
    
    My thoughts go to the victims, families and workers of the #Caritas workshop for the handicapped that burnt today in Germany    
    
    
    @barilla I have a question concerning your sustainability report. Could you please tell me whom I should address this question? Thanks    
    
    
    Culture Change Tips from the #Sustainability Masterminds http://bit.ly/Y49RGO  > very useful tips, @GarethKane    
    
    
    Dole Sued for #Greenwashing Guatemalan Banana Operations - http://bit.ly/QvJANe  via @triplepundit > the dangers of fake #CSR?    
    
    
    Like! Very useful: Inexperienced But Passionate: 4 Essential Tips for #CSR & #Sustainability Job Seekers - http://bit.ly/SH2O0J  via @CSRwire    
    
    
    European Commission Publishes Guide To Human Rights For SMEs  http://bit.ly/QGywgd  via @CSREurope > glad I participated! #CSR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Stakeholdercracy: the growing power of stakeholders http://wp.me/p2awtX-1O     
    
    
    Stakeholdercracy: the growing power of stakeholders http://fb.me/2ye5kttDa     
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR    
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Zara, Telecinco, Dole are good examples of the growing power of stakeholders. How companies deal with... http://fb.me/25vGE472K     
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #sustainability #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Do you think  #stakeholders have more and more power? http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #CSR #sustainability    
    
    
    Companies beware, people have the power! http://bit.ly/VvISm3  #sustainability #CSR #stakeholders    
    
    
    Gracias /Thnks RT's! @diarioresponsab @dandhicks @greendoula @VerantRSE @CapacitaRSE @MikeBeardshall Stakeholdercracy : http://bit.ly/VvISm3     
    
    
    Gracias /Thnks RT's! @RSEonline @joraguer @vinuales81 @SoledadTeixido @andytuit Stakeholdercracy : http://bit.ly/VvISm3     
    
    
    Have you liked me yet? ;) http://on.fb.me/YUdQVy  Everyone a great Friday and a nice weekend!  #CSR #sustainability    
    
    
    Interesting findings, surprised about the 38% > What CEOs Really Think about #Sustainability #CSR http://bit.ly/WQt7kN  via @CSRInternational    
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching the 1st #GRI training ever in Spain 4 companies in the food processing sector 22/23 Jan in Madrid #CSR #CSRfood    
    
    
    "What corporations DO TO society is far more important than what corporations CAN DO FOR society" http://bit.ly/X6OK0q  via @SSIReview #CSR    
    
    
    Blessed r the poor for theirs is the kingdom of God @Pontifex,respectfully,is the Church doing enuff 2 support the poor? #lesspraymoreaction    
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - Happy Holidays http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas    
    
    
    Happy Holidays / Felices Fiestas / Bones Festes http://fb.me/wAbf1za3     
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - Happy Holidays http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013    
    
    
    How to pay lip service to #sustainability http://bit.ly/Rzq0kV  by @GarethKane #CSR    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Happy Holidays to you too! And a great new year :)    
    
    
    #OccupyXmas - My very special Christmas card http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013    
    
    
    Thanks, Felices Fiestas! @company2keepinc: V Nice greeting! #OccupyXmas - My very special Christmas card http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #2013    
    
    
    Having a look at the Business and Human Rights Resource Center #csr http://fb.me/1QoySCQ6m     
    
    
    There is no limit to where innovation and #sustainability can take us. Happy holidays from @TheGreenDen team http://fb.me/xnIZF3Yt     
    
    
    Feliz Navidad/Merry Christmas/Bon Nadal/Frohes Fest/Joyeux Noël/God Jul http://wp.me/p2awtX-20  #csr #xmas #2013 #OccupyXmas    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! Boas Festas! Frohe Festtage! ¡Feliz Navidad! from the BSD Consulting Team http://fb.me/1Oh2NKaw5     
    
    
    @Radisson Is this true? If so, how does it fit in2 ur "responsible business" strategy? http://www.mopo.de/nachrichten/-radisson-blu--am-dammtor-reinigungskraefte-klagen-an--ausgebeutet-im-luxus-hotel,5067140,21001270.html … #csr As a fan, I need an explan.    
    
    
    The Top 10 #CSR and #Sustainability Reports of 2012 by @LeonKaye This deserves a closer look! http://fb.me/2rLlPvNSf     
    
    
    @Radisson Thanks for the reply. Looking forward to hearing the results of your investigations    
    
    
    I love beautiful illustrations wishing a happy new year - http://s.shr.lc/W6aZSH  #offtopic #2013 #illustration    
    
    
    Sustainability - No Place for Wimps! http://bit.ly/VT6e09  by @GarethKane > Are you ready to fight for #CSR?    
    
    
    Finding the Right #Sustainability Initiatives for Your Business http://smallbiztrends.com/2013/01/sustainability-initiatives-for-business.html … via @smallbiztrends #CSR    
    
    
    "World's Largest Gaming Company Recognized for #Sustainability" http://bit.ly/WIQD2y  > yeah, but what about its social impact? #CSR    
    
    
    I'd add employment and fair distribution of wealth > Top 10 Stakeholder Issues in 2013 http://s.shr.lc/WIQM68  via @triplepundit #csr    
    
    
    #CSR #HR Human Rights for Small Businesses "Companies should be managed by values to get results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28     
    
    
    Human Rights for Small Businesses "Companies should be managed by values to get results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR    
    
    
    Do Human Rights Apply for Small Businesses? http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR    
    
    
    Human Rights for Small Businesses -  http://xing.com/r/UQqSD  Some learnings from the "guide to human rights for SMEs" published by the Eu...    
    
    
    "Human Rights protected, respected and their violations remedied regardless of economic results" http://wp.me/p2awtX-28  #CSR #HR #CSR4SME    
    
    
    Next week I shall be giving a #GRI certified course about "#Sustainability Reporting in the Food Processing... http://fb.me/1tfDkWn1D     
    
    
    Just a thought before the weekend: #Transparency is the best ally of #sustainability.    
    
    
    @2GEM_CSR Thanks! You too have a nice weekend! Greetings from Barcelona    
    
    
    Everything ready for tomorrow's GRI-certified course on #sustainability reporting in the food industry I'm giving... http://fb.me/2j7LblLuH     
    
    
    Ready 4 the GRI course on #sustainability reporting in the food industry @ Madrid Chamber of Commerce on behalf of @BSDConsulting Spain    
    
    
    Surprised so many companies still think #CSR reporting is a question of quantity, not quality. The value of... http://fb.me/Hb1uyoVn     
    
    
    #Transparency is a two-ways virtue. Companies not only open themselves to public scrutiny, they also make... http://fb.me/2s3gI2S1M     
    
    
    Linear economy is the past> Circular Economy: Own Performance, Not the Product via @ecopreneurist http://ecopreneurist.com/2013/01/28/circular-economy-own-performance-not-the-product/ … vía @envirotarian    
    
    
    #Sustainability in plain language > Cut the Bull**** - Straight Talking & Sustainability http://bit.ly/14rLiTC  by @GarethKane    
    
    
    European Parliament publishes report on #CSR. Will take a look at it. Have you read it? http://www.europarl.europa.eu/sides/getDoc.do?pubRef=-//EP//TEXT+REPORT+A7-2013-0017+0+DOC+XML+V0//EN …    
    
    
    Check out this interview with Priti Ambani, my colleague at GreenDen Consultancy and editor of Ecopreneurist:... http://fb.me/zkkYQIFk     
    
    
    Just finished reading Strategy For #Sustainability, by Adam Werbach. One of the best books I've read on sustainability. Very inspiring.    
    
    
    Communication, key 2 successful CSR http://s.shr.lc/Xklt3E  via @SB_GreenBiz > Not only communication itself, also the process till reporting    
    
    
    Are you aware of business model canvas adapted to sustainable business? https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QoAOzMTLP5s … #sustainability    
    
    
    Please give a warm welcome to @BSDConsulting in Berlin, Germany! The new team joins as the 11th office in our... http://fb.me/2fU8xuIy5     
    
    
    Unsustainable practices at Amazon: This is what happens when you don't manage your supply chain in a proper way:... http://fb.me/1T3f93RWu     
    
    
    I'm no longer buying at Amazon until this is clear. @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing... http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    I'm no longer buying at @Amazon until this is clear. @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing... http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    Why #Unilever is not BP http://bit.ly/XoDXks  #sustainability    
    
    
    #6AC up to now, speakers are full of common places. Tell us something really new, please. Long talk about himself by Jim bendell so far    
    
    
    Creating value for companies, society and the environment while applying ethical principles is http://businesswithcommonsense.com  #csr #sustainability    
    
    
    http://businesswithcommonsense.com  today at #6AC #csr #sustainability #sustainable business models #socialInnovation    
    
    
    New jobs with sustainable business models "Rebelling With Your Feet to help Ethiopia: Sole Rebels" http://s.shr.lc/XCt0vL  via @Ecopreneurist    
    
    
    No longer buying at Amazon until this is clear @AmazonEspa, what are you doing about it? How are you dealing with this? http://fb.me/1V5Qt5Vo3     
    
    
    Great article RT @Paulatimpakt 6 Criteria for Selecting a CSR Consultant - Forbes http://onforb.es/11SLpdu  #csr    
    
    
    Communicating #CSR to a Cynical Public - http://s.shr.lc/URaJwo  > tell the truth about your mistakes, you cant fool your stakeholders    
    
    
    Thank you so much, I feel so honored! @CageFreeMedia: #FF @JuanVillamayor, who provides helpful words & news on #CSR and #Sustainability.    
    
    
    Preparing my conference at the EAE Business School this Wednesday: #CSR in Spain. Cultural Differences.    
    
    
    Off to Valencia tomorrow for the #GRI certified training at the Universitat Politécnica. Valencia is always worth a trip!    
    
    
    Cuaderno @foretica: 30 reglas d oro d #RSE para pymes http://www.foretica.org/biblioteca/cuadernos-foretica/doc_details/694-18-las-30-reglas-de-oro-de-la-rse-para-la-pyme?lang=es … by @plemonche @jgomlop @Marta_adaptaRSE @beatrizlorenzol et al.    
    
    
    How many #csr consultants do probono work? Lets take an example from English and Welsh barristers  http://www.barcouncil.org.uk/media-centre/news-and-press-releases/2013/february/bar-survey-barristers-set-leading-csr-example/#.US_d1Us3PYE.twitter …    
    
    
    "We were searching for employees but people turned up instead / Buscábamos empleados y lo que vinieron fueron... http://fb.me/Y0QoQ9to     
    
    
    Reading "The future of corporate reporting" by #KPMG #csr #reporting http://www.kpmg.com/Global/en/IssuesAndInsights/ArticlesPublications/Documents/future-of-corporate-reporting.pdf …    
    
    
    I have very much enjoyed the document "30 golden rules of #CSR for SMEs" published by Forética. It's only too bad... http://fb.me/1sbseaVIN     
    
    
    Please raise your hands those tired of useless #CSR reports that are nothing but a handful of money wasted in... http://fb.me/SonqjBJK     
    
    
    @NeiraSchliemann @DesignThinkers @James_Rock @TimSchuurman_DT Sounds really interesting! Enjoy both the workshop and Amsterdam :)    
    
    
    Happy International Women's Day! Read @Aksvi's post on the business case for women's empowerment. #csr http://fb.me/2h2RvWLfR     
    
    
    Ever heard of the so called "political #CSR"?    
    
    
    "Hershey and Barry Callebaut Lag Industry in Addressing Child Labor" #CSRfood http://feedly.com/k/Yz0rNr     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR vs Co- and self-regulation. Interesting discussion  http://feedly.com/k/XLBTr3     
    
    
    H&M unveils supplier factory list. #Transparency is crucial to #CSR and #sustainability http://about.hm.com/AboutSection/en/About/Sustainability/Commitments/Responsible-Partners/Supply-Chain/SupplierList.html# …    
    
    
    Looking 4 connection points between the #GRI indicators & Christian Felber's Common Good Balance Sheet. GRI cud use some good new indicators    
    
    
    Remarkable! @elainecohen: New on the #CSR Reporting Blog: A fabulous first #SME report http://shrd.by/m98Bgd     
    
    
    Salt, sugar & horsemeat RT @ethicsblogger #food industry: When ethics just isn’t enough http://www.canadianbusiness.com/blogs-and-comment/the-food-industry-when-ethics-just-isnt-enough/ … >Transparency wanted #CSRfood    
    
    
    #Bacardi releases 2012 #CSR report http://www.bacardilimited.com/Content/uploads/corporate/responsible/pdf/corp_resp_report_2012.pdf#page=1&zoom=auto,0,794 … Have a weakness 4 reports made by alcoholic beverage companies, let's have a look!    
    
    
    Companies that Practice "Conscious Capitalism" Perform 10x Better than those who dont > What we need is companies... http://fb.me/1YROhj1tR     
    
    
    @tonyvives Deseando leerlo!    
    
    
    Oxfam released some weeks ago a study about the state of #CSR in food and beverage multinationals. You can... http://fb.me/Ix0B2GuD     
    
    
    Most, if not all, #CSR strategies, #sustainability reports fail to demonstrate their overall contribution to... http://fb.me/2t6loFt1U     
    
    
    Some so called ethical banks, like the @GLSbank, still have a long way to learn how to deal with stakeholders,... http://fb.me/21iu0AdsE     
    
    
    In Madrid attending @foretica's event "CSR Spain 2013" #csr #rsc #rse    
    
    
    I have my doubts that Integrated Reporting will satisfy the needs of mainstream stakeholders. It will be good for... http://fb.me/PyMRMrXW     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRfood Romantic image vs Factory aseptical: Food companies who want to be transparent after the horsemeat... http://fb.me/2Jt2laudO     
    
    
    M.Porter unveils HIS health & happiness index http://ht.ly/k6HIQ  Thought we already had the human development index    
    
    
    "Ben & Jerry's Social Mission"  • good read #csr #sustainablebusiness http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/04/ben-jerrys-social-mission/ …    
    
    
    RSC.-Burger King regalará patatas gratis x alcanzar 250.000 fans en Facebook. Esto es #RSC??? #AntiRSE #ActivismoRSC http://www.europapress.es/nacional/noticia-rsc-burger-king-regalara-patatas-gratis-proximo-viernes-haber-alcanzado-250000-fans-facebook-20130419154517.html …    
    
    
    @JuanVillamayor: "EU Corporate Reporting proposal not strong enough to improve company behaviour". Too discretional http://www.business-humanrights.org/Links/Repository/1018468 …    
    
    
    It's #greenwashing when you try to distract public attention from your negative impacts by stressing positive... http://fb.me/BkwszZ4t     
    
    
    #CSR Communication: Quality, not quantity http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    The more indicators, the better. Wrong! #CSR #CSRreporting http://fb.me/2pRkvwrDb     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRreporting The more indicators, the better. Wrong!  http://fb.me/2pRkvwrDb     
    
    
    #CSR #CSRreporting "The more indicators are reported, the more sustainable the company is". This is how a... http://fb.me/2L7ee4ri1     
    
    
    For a company, the value of #csr reporting lies mainly on the process, not on the quantity of indicators http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    For a company, the value of #csr reporting lies mainly on the process, not on the quantity of indicators http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l     
    
    
    "Hundreds Die in Bangladesh, You Save Money"  http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/04/hundreds-die-bangladesh-save-money/ …    
    
    
    Stakeholders need relevant information, a true picture of the company, not an overwhelming battery of indicators #CSR http://businesswithcommonsense.wordpress.com/2013/04/27/csr-communication-quality-not-quantity/ …    
    
    
    #CSR communication has many faces. Effective CSR communication sometimes requires different channels, depending... http://fb.me/2e9EQFN1N     
    
    
    Done! @theecosaurus Help protect #consumers from the #SFI's false #eco-label Tell the FTC 2 improve #green guidelines http://ow.ly/kr5Ne     
    
    
    The more indicators, the more sustainable the company is? #csr #CSRreporting http://wp.me/p2awtX-2l " CSR communication with Quality    
    
    
    "Shud co's source from Bangladesh?" http://s.shr.lc/18i8wOX  Real question: shud co's take responsibiity, no matter where they source from?    
    
    
    As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    As a #CSR consultant, who am I accountable to? my client? its stakeholders? Society? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Thanks! @nmartellbundock: Good question... As a CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u  via @JuanVillamayor    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    This post is over a year old. We are still waiting for a Spanish National CSR Plan http://businesswithcommonsense.wordpress.com/2012/01/27/hello-world/ …    
    
    
    @FairPhone too good to be true! Can't wait to see this turned into reality    
    
    
    @Abercrombie If what's said on the article is true, you cant get any more "uncool" than this. This is derogatory,... http://fb.me/IxECIkWI     
    
    
    @AndreaLearned lucky you! enjoy    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    @JuanVillamayor: @FabianPattberg @aksvi greetings to you both! And all the best to @sustforum!!    
    
    
    Did you take the poll? As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    THIS is #sustainability: self-healing fabrics... http://fb.me/2yxJMsloT     
    
    
    In Amsterdam, learning about the new G4 #sustainability reporting guidelines. #GRI. Very interesting topic though... http://fb.me/1bzcQYzLJ     
    
    
    The new #GRI G4 guidelines will make it more difficult to publish a #CSR report without having a proper... http://fb.me/1Hz4GaIUV     
    
    
    New #GRI reporting guidelines: https://www.globalreporting.org/reporting/g4/Pages/default.aspx … A, B, C levels? Good riddance! Core or comprehensive, that's the question    
    
    
    If true, an example of Corporate Social Irresponsibility. And I bet this happens not only in Germany... http://fb.me/CpMGvaa9     
    
    
    @GreenbizStartup welcome back, Simone!    
    
    
    Flying back to Barcelona. It was great meeting my new colleagues @EHSustainableM and @CVHH2011 in Hamburg #csr    
    
    
    G4: It's NOT about #materiality http://feedly.com/k/ZAxoAc  by @elainecohen >As in G3.1 it's the process towards materiality what counts    
    
    
    Two weeks after publishing the new G4 reporting guidelines, I think some disclosures and new indicators are missing. You miss anything?    
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity: Let's report! http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    For more trust and transparency. Ethics and Integrity: Let's report! http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    New standard disclosures on Ethics and Integrity. A good chance for companies to report on their values and codes... http://fb.me/IDrY1Pvl     
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity make their GRI debut, hopefully for more trust and transparency. http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    Speakers are making way too many sexist jokes, it's not funny anymore. @TEDxhamburg #tedxhamburg    
    
    
    Will social media save or kill #CSR reporting? http://feedly.com/k/13070wy  > it will help channel specific information to specific audiences    
    
    
    Developing a sustainable business model canvas, inspired in the one created by Osterwalder. It's a very useful graphic and ideation tool!    
    
    
    Ethics and Integrity make their GRI debut, hopefully for more trust and transparency. http://wp.me/p2awtX-2B  #CSR #GRI #G4 #reporting    
    
    
    Very interesting article > McDonald's Customers Don't Buy Salads - But Whose Fault is That? - http://s.shr.lc/15RJ40P  via @triplepundit    
    
    
    What does a $14 shirt really cost? http://fb.me/2NMcyLvrF     
    
    
    Ralph Lauren finally decides to publish a #sustainability report after pressure from an investor http://feedly.com/k/17016C5     
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    GRI G4: A Gateway to Meaningful #Sustainability Reporting? http://s.shr.lc/13AdTpX  via @CSRwire >Me too, it's a step in the good direction    
    
    
    +1 @DavidKlingen: Interesting @Unilever CEO: 4 sustainable business, against 'mindless consumption' http://shrd.by/rjQ6kd  via @AmanSinghCSR    
    
    
    Project for an alternative beyond economic growth http://www.indiegogo.com/projects/how-on-earth-a-book-for-a-new-economy … via @donmacca > We need to re-think our current economic model    
    
    
    Take the poll! As a #CSR consultant, who are my stakeholders? http://wp.me/p2awtX-2u     
    
    
    Of Consultants And Their #Stakeholders #CSR #stakeholder http://wp.me/p2awtX-2J     
    
    
    Can anyone recommend a tool/app that allows working with Facebook,Twitter, Goggle+ &LinkedIn at the same time? Tired of switching back&forth    
    
    
    Of Consultants And Their #Stakeholders #CSR #stakeholder http://wp.me/p2awtX-2J  "There goes your reputation as a consultant down the drain"    
    
    
    Y se quedan tan panchos: Perlas en #RSE by @tonyvives http://www.diarioresponsable.com/portada/destacados/16594.html …    
    
    
    10 tips stakeholder engagement with activists http://s.shr.lc/15LB5zO  via @GreenBiz > Dont remove negative comments, dont call the cops etc    
    
    
    "Reputation is overrated" @helenaancos: The frame of corporate #reputation http://helenaancos.com/2012/06/27/the-frame-of-corporate-reputation/ …    
    
    
    Great news but, where are the cars??? > IKEA Doubles Down on EV Charging Stations at Retail Stores http://feedly.com/k/12qxdqa     
    
    
    Does it??? > Does Nestlé's Bottled Water Pass the 'Creating Shared Value' Test? - http://s.shr.lc/10peZ7N  via @triplepundit    
    
    
    Another reason to be sustainable: Three reasons job seekers prefer sustainable companies http://feedly.com/k/11NjAlh     
    
    
    ‘Sustainable’ German Auto Companies Lobby to Stop EU Climate Regulation http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/07/german-auto-companies-sustainable-lobby-stop-eu-climate-regulation/ … #AntiCSR #AntiRSC    
    
    
    @bewastewise & @TheGreenDen: 1st panel on July 10 "Recycling in North-American Cities" http://wastewise.be/ai1ec_event/recycling-in-north-american-cities/?instance_id=237 … #wastewise #sustainability    
    
    
    @BeWasteWise Offers a Series of Online Talks to Promote Dialogue on Waste Management #wastewise http://fb.me/6mh7laZeK     
    
    
    4 Inaccurate Assumptions About Social Media for #Sustainability and #CSR Communications via @taigacompany http://fb.me/1ePnWce2H     
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Hi Julie, yes, I have been a little quiet on twitter but I am back! I hope you are doing great too, enjoy the summer!    
    
    
    Thanks for the great pieces of advise! @tobiaswebb76: Some lessons learned from #sustainability and #CSR training: http://shrd.by/FXkD2j     
    
    
    @viet_ha_ Thank you! I'm glad you like it, tho I've been a little lazy lately. Greetings to Toronto, I love that city!    
    
    
    Agree! @BenjaFagerland A good @HuffPostBiz post of @alicekorngold on unconscious biases, #diverseboards and #corpgov http://huff.to/1dwpWXZ     
    
    
    Sounds like Economy 4 the Common Good http://www.gemeinwohl-oekonomie.org/en  Common Wealth Cntributins By Business via @Ecopreneurist http://ecopreneurist.com/2013/07/22/expecting-more-from-business-common-wealth-contributions-by-business-part-2/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+IM-ecopreneurist+%28Ecopreneurist%29 …    
    
    
    Great ideas. Israeli invents a 9$ bicycle made of cardboard http://www.social-startups.de/fahrrad-aus-pappe/ …    
    
    
    "George Clooney and Nespresso" u can't create an unsustainable product & then pretend u found the solution http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/07/george-clooney-coffee-pod-problem/ …    
    
    
    ROI of #CSR: Cargill's new tool quantifies return on investment for #sustainability initiatives http://www.foodnavigator-usa.com/Suppliers2/Cargill-s-new-tool-quantifies-return-on-investment-for-sustainability-initiatives?utm_source=copyright&utm_medium=OnSite&utm_campaign=copyright …    
    
    
    I find that the concept of "overall impact on society, economy and environment" is often being neglected when we... http://fb.me/2UXhPAKHf     
    
    
    I find that the concept of "overall impact on society, economy and environment" is often neglected when we talk about a company's #CSR    
    
    
    Sustainable Summer: The Common Good Approach #CSR #Sustainability http://wp.me/p2awtX-2Y     
    
    
    Gracias! @RSCDigital: ' We need clear rankings' Sustainable Summer: The Common Good Approach #CSR #Sustainability http://wp.me/p2awtX-2Y     
    
    
    Thanks so much! @terrafiniti: #FF @greeneconpost @greenbiztweets @practicallygrn @JuanVillamayor for green and #sustainability news!    
    
    
    One month... until THE FUTURE OF SUSTAINABILITY REPORTING event on 6 September in Berlin, Germany organised by... http://fb.me/GV9ifvZ6     
    
    
    Good read! RT @CarbonImpact: Swamped by #sustainability indicators failing to drive transformation http://zite.to/1cwNKyF  via @guardian #GRI    
    
    
    Abgeschminkt! Bilder in Nachhaltigkeitsberichten http://csr-news.net/main/2013/08/09/abgeschminkt-die-bilderwelten-der-nachhaltigkeitsberichte/?lp_lang_pref=de … > Why do many #GRI reports show only beautiful people? (GERMAN)    
    
    
    Abgeschminkt! http://csr-news.net/main/2013/08/09/abgeschminkt-die-bilderwelten-der-nachhaltigkeitsberichte/?lp_lang_pref=de … > Why do many #GRI reports show only beautiful people? by @EikeHellmann und Annika Martens    
    
    
    Funny video about gender-specific advertising http://youtu.be/Vmnt31UgGT4  #responsibleads #csr    
    
    
    @CarbonImpact You too, Fred, enjoy the summer!    
    
    
    @LeonKaye Hey Leon, belated thanks for #FF, hope you are enjoying the summer!    
    
    
    LOL @GarethKane: And the environmental jargon of the day award goes to 'enhanced basal lubrication' sounds like some spam I got recently...    
    
    
    Sounds great! @susanmcp1 Come work with me! hiring a marketing & new biz mngr in @FentonProgress's NY office http://www.fenton.com/careers/  #CSR #PR    
    
    
    Like! > The Backbone of a Small Business #Sustainability Strategy http://blog.taigacompany.com/blog/sustainability-business-life-environment/the-backbone-of-a-small-business-sustainability-strategy … by @taigacompany #CSR #CSRforSME    
    
    
    This one is dedicated to Julie @taigacompany. Always with my bike! Many greetings from Barcelona! pic.twitter.com/EEd9JZUq1M    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Glad you like it! What would we do without bicycles??? <3    
    
    
    @aksvi @AmanSinghCSR @namratarana @jdthakkar @WayneVisser Mandatory sounds scary but sometimes it's the only way. That said,prefer voluntary    
    
    
    AccountAbility releases report on Materiality: Non-financial materiality matters! http://s.shr.lc/16KWDic  via @CSRWire #CSR    
    
    
    Coming soon: The shortcomings of #CSR. Meanwhile, enjoying a well deserved summer break.    
    
    
    "Creating shared value: Revolution or clever con? By @WayneVisser > IMHO CSV is just a part of real #CSR 2.0 http://www.csrinternational.org/2013/08/20/creating-shared-value-revolution-or-clever-con/ …    
    
    
    @elainecohen tells us about "The first G4 Sustainability Report in the World" > need to check it http://csr-reporting.blogspot.com/2013/08/the-first-g4-sustainability-report-in.html …    
    
    
    "Transparent Disclosure to Stakeholders Critical for Corporations Today" Will stakeholders rule? #csr http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/08/21/transparent-disclosure-to-stakeholders-critical-for-corporations-today/ …    
    
    
    GRI G4-PR7: Non-compliance with regulations & voluntary codes concerning marketing comms: sexist, non-inclusive ads still a big issue    
    
    
    Thanks for #FF, Leon! @LeonKaye @mary_mazzoni @NateLipka @joconfino @BeyondMeat @paolafiore @CarbonImpact @KoreaCSR @FashionGreen    
    
    
    @elanecohen: G4 Tip of the Day(17): In #G4 Reports, material issues should smack you in the face. If they don't, it's not G4....    
    
    
    In Spain #CSR is shifting to philanthropy/corporate giving, leaving its strategic approach aside and missing all kind of opportunities    
    
    
    #CSR is the way, good reputation is the consequence (if CSR is real #sustainability and not just charity or #greenwashing)    
    
    
    Good one! RT @jfonru: “@JuanVillamayor: #CSR is the way, good reputation is the consequence (...)"  and #ethics is the foundation    
    
    
    Exactly 20 years ago I took my 1st course on Business Ethics (Wirtschaftsethik) at the University of Augsburg. So long ago... Good choice!    
    
    
    "How to Win Customers and Save Money with Sustainable Products" now this is #sustainability http://feedly.com/k/148uwNk     
    
    
    Counting down to Friday... a full day on #Reporting 3.0 in Berlin. Organised by @BSDConsulting Germany #CSR http://fb.me/2EoeCfFRb     
    
    
    G4 Tip ofthe day(25): Transition from G3 to G4 with consistency. The objective is G4, not G3 plus new bits.#UG4 http://fb.me/2tG0cIExc     
    
    
    "In G4, Material Aspects should be boundary specific: the place where they occur must be identified" http://s.shr.lc/1dTWNeN  by @elainecohen    
    
    
    I wonder how many companies will secretly decide to report CORE so that they won't have to disclose G5-54 & G4-55 #GRI #G4 #CSR #governance    
    
    
    NL leading the way on sustainable business http://s.shr.lc/1el9q2N  via @GuardianSustbiz "a strong consensus-driven approach"    
    
    
    Could anyone recommend me any energy efficiency gurus? Thanks and have a good Sunday/week!    
    
    
    "31 Tips for writing a G4 Report" great tips by @elainecohen #csr #reporting #gri http://csr-reporting.blogspot.com/2013/09/31-tips-for-writing-g4-report.html …    
    
    
    #Sustainability strategy not equal sustainable business. Just saying.    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. Part I http://wp.me/p2awtX-32     
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. "CSR fails to reflect a company's overall contribution to the common good" http://wp.me/p2awtX-32     
    
    
    Interesting view on McDo's #CSR strategy: "#Sustainability at McDonald’s. Really." http://www.marcgunther.com/sustainability-at-mcdonalds-really/ … by @marcgunther    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. "CSR fails to reflect a company's contribution to the common good" http://wp.me/p2awtX-32  >but we can solve it!    
    
    
    Do you think the new GRI G4 guidelines give more value to #sustainability reports? I do! Both company & its stakeholders will benefit    
    
    
    5 ways companies are making packaging more sustainable "Clearer labeling, lifecycle approach etc" http://s.shr.lc/1cK8YJS  via @GreenBiz    
    
    
    "Hershey Converts Two More Plants to Zero Waste to Landfill" this is #sustainability http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/10/23/hershey-converts-two-more-plants-to-zero-waste-to-landfill/ …    
    
    
    "Sainsbury’s ‘Water Neutral’ Store Saves About 1bn Liters of Water Annually" this is #sustainability http://www.environmentalleader.com/2013/10/23/sainsburys-water-neutral-store-saves-about-1bn-liters-of-water-annually/ …    
    
    
    My two previous tweets are examples of how #csr means #sustainability and not #philanthropy or corporate giving    
    
    
    Agree @PuigGarciaSmith When a company's CSR is only philantropy, it is charity washing. CSR means sustainability &, if possibly, philantropy    
    
    
    "GRI G4 Materiality Assessment – Validation of Material Aspects" very interesting read http://icarbonnews.com/gri-g4-materiality-tool-validation-of-material-aspects/ …    
    
    
    Interesting @helenaancos: role & geography of the Big 4 auditors in the offshore tax haven business @RichardJMurphy http://www.taxresearch.org.uk/Documents/Where4Art.pdf …    
    
    
    Credit Suisse: #LGBT invstmnt index http://www.corporateregister.com//news/item/?n=560 … >Do they outpetform due 2 employee retention,bettr reflection of customers needs?    
    
    
    Interesting initiative to push Electric Vehicles - http://s.shr.lc/18qKe1V  ia @sustainablebizz #sustainablebusiness    
    
    
    Mercy me! @susanmcp1: Fascinating look at a big player in corporate #philanthropy: '@GoldmanSachs, Buying Redemption' http://nyti.ms/1dwSJAv     
    
    
    CSR Reports: Let's include issues that really matter to stakeholders, shall we? Luckily more and more companies are applying this already    
    
    
    While the rest of the world concentrates on sustainable business strategies, we Spaniards are still blinded by corporate giving…    
    
    
    Heja Sverige! @Mgutierrezalv: Swedish Government Leads the Way on Sustainability with not ‘traditional’ regulation. http://ow.ly/27z1fG     
    
    
    Is your supply chain a ticking time bomb? http://www.terrainfirma.co.uk/blog/2013/11/is-your-supply-chain-a-ticking-time-bomb.html … by @GarethKane #sustainability #supplychain #CSR    
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR. Part II http://wp.me/p2awtX-3g     
    
    
    The Shortcomings of #CSR: failing to reflect overall contribution to common good http://wp.me/p2awtX-3g     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://lnkd.in/dVN2JrH     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Why reporting and sustainability strategies are not enough http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Companies who cause important negative externalities are often encouraged NOT to change their way of doing business http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a #CSR that makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr  #sustainability    
    
    
    BSD's final G4 Trainings this year in: Lisboa, México D.F., Geneva, Porto Alegre. For details:... http://fb.me/18YM5tl1m     
    
    
    Five Reasons You Will Be Using GRI’s New G4 Guidelines Sometime Soon by @elainecohen http://s.shr.lc/182VL8y  > G4 is reporting that matters    
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a #CSR that makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr  #sustainability    
    
    
    H&M Makes Commitment to Pay a Fair Living Wage By 2018 - http://s.shr.lc/1iVYdFB     
    
    
    Sustainable business models that contribute to common good. That's key for a CSR that really makes a change http://fb.me/NKjyIiTr     
    
    
    Startup helps restaurants and groceries turn food waste into fertilizar > innovation & #sustainability http://feeds.importantmedia.org/~r/IM-ecopreneurist/~3/ybYrjgeroiU/ …    
    
    
    5 lessons from the Japanese “kaizen” approach to #sustainability http://www.greenbiz.com/blog/2013/12/03/5-lessons-japanese-kaizen-approach-sustainability?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+greenbuzz+%28GreenBiz%29 …    
    
    
    The #GRI offers a new "Materiality Matters" check for G4 #CSR reports: http://www.stream-eu.com/index.php/news/113-materiality-matters-check … #reporting    
    
    
    #Sustainability is simplicity is happiness #2014 http://wp.me/p2awtX-3q     
    
    
    Happy holidays and a great 2014 ***#Sustainability is simplicity is happiness*** pic.twitter.com/jxX6Pijmdv    
    
    
    Dear #CSR Gang: Happy holidays and a great 2014!!! #Sustainability is simplicity is happiness pic.twitter.com/jxX6Pijmdv    
    
    
    Thanks @josephineECO Holiday cheer from Barcelona to lovely Toronto! #HappyHolidays    
    
    
    Just updated my twitter profile: Consultant in #CSR/#Sustainability. Sustainable business models. Sustainability... http://fb.me/17ZCk5VLX     
    
    
    Very interesting question > ‘Why Do Good People Do Bad Things?’ The Role of Spiritual Intelligence http://feedly.com/e/2WrBYIHd  #Business #Ethics    
    
    
    CSR managers will deal with stakeholder dialogue, business modeling & reporting >The evolution of the #CSR manager: http://s.shr.lc/1kPDIZh     
    
    
    Have yourself a merry little Christmas (and a sustainable 2014) #xmas #2014 pic.twitter.com/b4Wh64X0zJ    
    
    
    @TaigaCompany Thanks Julie, you too! All the best for the new year XXX    
    
    
    "Getting the most out of #Sustainability Report Interviews" Great, useful post, Elaine @elainecohen http://feedly.com/k/1btVlbY     
    
    
    Coming soon: my new year's resolutions (for both business and personal life). The most important one is on my... http://fb.me/1Rqyog4pJ     
    
    
    The Top Ten #CSR Reports of 2013 http://feedly.com/e/EOF08RCU  by @elainecohen #RSE > Love your AIM method, Elaine. HNY!!!    
    
    
    Feliz 2014! @FRSIberoamerica @dresponsable @tonyvives @aandreup @iroser_RSE @germangranda @plemonche @anavaz73 @CarmenMarti_ @jalmagro    
    
    
    How to use Twitter effectively for #CSR/#sustainability communications http://s.shr.lc/1cqinnK  via @CSRExaminer    
    
    
    Cities of the future: Challenges for the developing world http://feedly.com/e/wDrxNLgr  by @aksvi #sustainability    
    
    
    #Sustainability Execs Should Look to ‘Mavericks and Outsiders’ > good approach http://www.environmentalleader.com/2014/01/07/sustainability-execs-should-look-to-mavericks-and-outsiders/ …    
    
    
    ISO 26000:2010 Comprender la norma by @syeconsulting #iso26000 #rse http://www.diarioresponsable.com/portada/opinion/17005-iso-260002010-comprender-la-norma.html …    
    
    
    Microsoft's #sustainability predictions for 2014 http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/greenbuzz/~3/c2OZAUU2aYQ/microsoft-sustainability-predictions-2014 …    
    
    
    I miss #CSR reports that include critical views from stakeholders. @elainecohen do you think that reports shud incl. constructive criticism?    
    
    
    #CSR makes u win: Affordable, good food; Trustworthy behavior; Trash in2 cash; Clean technologies; Women leaders http://s.shr.lc/1hQjfUy     
    
    
    @elainecohen @estrujillo I dont find it very often in reports though; it would offer a very balanced view of the business    
    
    
    @BSDConsulting Thank you! :)    
    
    
    Ten tips for SMEs to get the most out of their #sustainability strategies http://s.shr.lc/1alrVRi  #CSR #csr4sme via @GuardianSustBiz    
    
    
    Next dates for #GRI trainings with @BSDConsulting all over the world. Check it up! http://fb.me/3FVYvxDbY     
    
    
    This is too good: RT @bizethicartoons: Good Christmas feelings about corporate social responsibility #CSR pic.twitter.com/lsKz6zCKcg    
    
    
    Three sustainability resolutions for all businesses in 2014 http://feedly.com/e/Qs2lL33J  vía @GuardianSustBiz #sustainability #csr    
    
    
    Good one! @GarethKane: We need 2 accept the inherent ambiguities of #sustainability and leap into the dark –otherwise we’ll achieve nothing.    
    
    
    Mandatory CSR? Yes but no. http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR? Yes but no. In some cases, for some aspects. http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Mandatory #CSR? Yes but no. No but yes http://wp.me/p2awtX-3y     
    
    
    Great post, Elaine. Why the battle??? New on @elainecohen's blog: #GRI vs. #IIRC. vs #SASB: Round Nine. All Lose. http://shrd.by/fWcV10     
    
    
    Microvinyas: ethical vineyards producing wine for the common good http://s.shr.lc/1jkG85M  #sustainability #CommonGood    
    
    
    #CSR is empathy applied to business, what impacts u have on others / #RSE es empatía aplicada a la empresa, qué impactos hay sobre los demás    
    
    
    A business with empathy is a successful business. #Sustainability and empathy are closely linked.    
    
    
    Dont miss the dates for the next GRI certified training courses provided by @BSDConsulting http://fb.me/6uts0yExH     
    
    
    