@Infinityindies @noticiashacker1 @roman_soft ya lo veo complicado :)    
    
    
    whatsapp://send?text=Hello%2C%20World!    
    
    
    WhatsApp hooks in iOS http://bit.ly/14y8mTO     
    
    
    @0xroot es lo primero que pensé!    
    
    
    OVH compromised. http://bit.ly/16Ve65X     
    
    
    I haven’t log on in the Apple Developer section for some months, and today I needed to. Kudos to Murphy :)    
    
    
    The Secret Service Agent Who Collared Cybercrooks by Selling Them Fake IDs http://bit.ly/18wXcOB  <- kingpin reloaded :)    
    
    
    The thin line of entrapment    
    
    
    The Challenge Posed by Chinese Psychological Warfare http://herit.ag/163Wi9F     
    
    
    How Would the U.S. Respond to a Nightmare Cyber Attack? http://bit.ly/11bv810     
    
    
    @mobiplayer :)    
    
    
    Cisco to buy cybersecurity firm Sourcefire for $2.7 billion http://cnb.cx/17AJGZ9  /via @areino    
    
    
    Now you can't tell that Cisco has a crappy IDS :)    
    
    
    But at the end of the day, an IDS is like an AV, it helps you to detect some bad stuff, but just some.    
    
    
    At least IDS allow you to set up and tailor the rules    
    
    
    @DennisF @cBekrar xDD    
    
    
    Is Cisco going to keep the Sourcefire brand (I hope so) or it will be renamed as Cisco IPS2 or some obscure acronym?    
    
    
    Sorry for being so pessimist,but is there any success story of a security product acquisition by Cisco? #pun    
    
    
    Phone and texting app ‘Viber’ hacked by Syrian Electronic Army [update: Viber comments] http://bit.ly/15e0XXS     
    
    
    ‘Today the Viber Support site was defaced after a Viber employee unfortunately fell victim to an email phishing attack'    
    
    
    @ateixei hmm somehow yes    
    
    
    @briankrebs add Viber    
    
    
    Good morning twitverse!    
    
    
    @Packetknife @krypt3ia are there people beyond US borders? :)    
    
    
    @peepdf @EternalTodo I want one! :)    
    
    
    @Packetknife @0xabad1dea the problem is that there are really good alternatives on Europe    
    
    
    Hmm there aren't big headlines from #Defcon, just a mention that Will Smith was there. #strange    
    
    
    Germans’ fear of American spying surges - http://on.ft.com/154W2Vq     
    
    
    German Minister on EU Company Ban For Privacy Violation http://bit.ly/1ctjUez     
    
    
    10 PRINT "Hello World!"
20 GOTO 10    
    
    
    @cBekrar @csoghoian can we have the two of you in the same panel? It would definitely a success :)    
    
    
    @jeremiahg @Beaker @hpsecurity @CiscoSecurity hehe they removed the post.    
    
    
    Hmm I'm getting many promoted tweets by @Sourcefire. For me it is like receiving a spam email, but on Twitter.    
    
    
    MS: Windows Phone 8 Wi-Fi Vulnerable, Cannot Be Patched http://bit.ly/13ISCfw     
    
    
    @ecasbas congratulations! Let's see if we can meet there soon! :)    
    
    
    @kylemaxwell @briankrebs good contacts in the industry and clients.    
    
    
    @jlhortelano xD cierto    
    
    
    @hacktimes @Groove es flipante.    
    
    
    Silent Mail also shuts down its service, fearing the 'Lavabit experience' http://bit.ly/17bp60t     
    
    
    But Silent Circle should also take care about the rest of their products, they are on the same page.    
    
    
    At the end of the day, there is a huge opportunity for a non-US secure email service provider.    
    
    
    @Packetknife I'd say that with their products they could “be complicit in crimes against the American people.”    
    
    
    @Packetknife Caiman Islands is a great place to live in :)    
    
    
    @Packetknife time will tell. I hope rationality survives    
    
    
    A concept that I really hate: Next Generation SOC #derp    
    
    
    @mikk0j it just has a NG before the word SOC :P    
    
    
    The SOC/CSIRT/CERT concept/hype has caused a lot of damage in the security industry.    
    
    
    @VS_ @Packetknife the hole thing. Very few companies take advantage of the investment and make them really useful    
    
    
    Counting down to the launch of ardusat – world’s first open source satellite (based on arduino) http://bit.ly/15WW99H     
    
    
    Slight shift seen in official Chinese attitude on cybersecurity http://bit.ly/19d4fMz     
    
    
    @areino mola :P    
    
    
    Veo mucha histeria con el tema de Lavabit o SilentMail pero no veo a (casi) nadie que use PGP/GPG o sMIME    
    
    
    Police nab alleged DDoS extortion gang at Heathrow Airport http://bit.ly/17iRfTy     
    
    
    Estonian Intelligence Official Confesses to Spying for Russia http://bit.ly/18pScL1     
    
    
    London Turns Off Snooping Trash Cans That Tracked Pedestrians' Phones  http://bit.ly/1d242hG     
    
    
    If You Use Gmail, You Should Have 'No Legitimate Expectation Of Privacy' http://read.bi/14akbuz     
    
    
    @martibk @TheCookie_es the other day I tried the honey cookey with almonds and was great!    
    
    
    Congrats to the @Trusteer guys for the acquisition. They were really doing a great job. Another success for a security startup in Israel    
    
    
    @Packetknife @Wh1t3Rabbit read it again and put yourself in a non-US citizen's shoes. I haven't got any words to describe the article :(    
    
    
    @Wh1t3Rabbit I have the same feeling after watching the movie ‘Independence day’ :)    
    
    
    Bletchley - A collection of practical application cryptanalysis tools http://bit.ly/17Xqe7c     
    
    
    United Internet (1&1) acquires Spanish webhosting and cloud specialist Arsys http://bit.ly/150uDZp     
    
    
    Why Some Startups Say the Cloud Is a Waste of Money http://Wired.com  http://bit.ly/1cT982d  <- not some big enterprises too    
    
    
    @rafaorga safe trip!    
    
    
    LastPass Vulnerability Left IE Passwords Exposed, Update Now http://bit.ly/1cTsowH     
    
    
    Come on, it's 2013 and the adduser command still asks for Room Number, Work and Home phone.How come is not asking for a twitter account? :)    
    
    
    So after @Trusteer acquisition by IBM, my bet is that the next israeli security startup to be acquired is @seculert    
    
    
    Changing IP address to access public website ruled violation of US law  http://ars.to/17ZLYzk     
    
    
    @Packetknife @georgiaweidman @jadedsecurity I’ve also seen @rik_ferguson    
    
    
    From hackers to entrepreneurs: The Sino-US cyberwar veterans going straight http://bit.ly/13RNsdR     
    
    
    @DennisF nice pic at the header :P    
    
    
    German IT officials reportedly deem Windows 8 too ‘dangerous’ to use http://bit.ly/19z6qdq     
    
    
    Introducing a brand new way to share everything: PRSM - The Sharing Network http://bit.ly/12rLZxc  :)    
    
    
    After some years, the 0.7.3 version of Yersinia is out!! Thanks to Alfredo :) https://github.com/tomac/yersinia     
    
    
    @CipherLaw there isn’t AFAIK.    
    
    
    Si vis pacem, para bellum    
    
    
    It's great to see that Yersinia runs perfectly on OSX 10.8 (the ncurses GUI)    
    
    
    @osxreverser where have you read that?    
    
    
    @5ean5ullivan actually, that specific registrar offers antiphishing solutions :P    
    
    
    “@officialmcafee: JOHN MCAFEE TELLS ALL / RAW: http://bit.ly/1dPPORD ” <- finally the truth :)    
    
    
    The Password is dead. Long live The Password!    
    
    
    @trufae I’ve used for several months and it works great    
    
    
    @NecronoiD @francisco_oca skate or die! :p    
    
    
    Is This the Leader of the Syrian Electronic Army? (Update) http://bit.ly/15jFbFS     
    
    
    Glyph should be the most hated word in the world today for iOS and OSX users (including me!!)    
    
    
    CTGlyphRun::CloneRange(CTRun const*, CFRange, TRun::SubrangingStyle) + 142    
    
    
    I see glyphs everywhere    
    
    
    Dark Patterns: inside the interfaces designed to trick you http://bit.ly/15pefO6  <- nice article    
    
    
    Former White House 'copyright czar' appointed CEO of powerful tech lobby group http://bit.ly/18pxSaz  <- oops    
    
    
    @mgesteiro @pof but kicking a connected guy out of the network is a crime :P    
    
    
    @carlosdomingo @tomiahonen yes, I was also waiting for his comments about Elop :)    
    
    
    AlienVault Announces $26.5 Million in Series D Funding Led by GGV Capital to Accelerate Rapid Growth 
http://on.mktw.net/13iEF7E     
    
    
    Why Silicon Valley Funds Instagrams, Not Hyperloops http://bit.ly/1fE5Rjz  <- nice article    
    
    
    @suffert we are all doomed :)    
    
    
    The NSA should go to Pamplona next July to participate in the running of the bulls    
    
    
    @avilarenata it depends of your definition of safe enough, but I’d stay away from software from the US if I were paranoid    
    
    
    My last RT shows the an smart configuration for privacy, but it has a huge problem:it entirely relies on TrueCrypt    
    
    
    The Cowboy of the NSA Keith Alexander http://bit.ly/18Inmgb     
    
    
    ExecScent: Mining for New C&C Domains in Live Networks with Adaptive Control Protocol Templates http://bit.ly/15dyjYf     
    
    
    CrowdStrike Closes $30 Million In Series B Financing, Led By Accel Partners http://prn.to/1awIOu5  <- wow offensive bubble? :)    
    
    
    “@matthew_d_green:I received a request from my Dean this morning asking me to remove all copies of my NSA blog post from University servers.    
    
    
    @DennisF I’m running with some similar sandals and once you get used, they are really great. Also for normal activities    
    
    
    @DennisF not at all, but I spent some days until I managed to find the best configuration    
    
    
    NSA and Israeli intelligence: memorandum of understanding – full document http://bit.ly/1b6puDj     
    
    
    "Kleptography: persuading the party to be intercepted to use a  form of crypto that the attacker knows they can break."    
    
    
    @victor_mb :P    
    
    
    Cybersécurité: les ministres interdits de smartphones http://bit.ly/17sIBmX     
    
    
    "From now on any highly classified information must only be transmitted over specially encrypted telephones "    
    
    
    "and all electronic documents can only be transferred using the government’s secure ISIS system"    
    
    
    "not to insert a USB key unless they know exactly where it came from and that it is safe"    
    
    
    "and not to click on any attachments in messages without checking them first."    
    
    
    @cedricpernet I can read it but not speak it though :P    
    
    
    The iPhone 5s fingerprint reader: what you need to know http://bit.ly/15Wi8eu     
    
    
    New Details in How the Feds Take Laptops at Border http://nyti.ms/15WSg8n     
    
    
    @ronaldotcom no :P    
    
    
    @hacktimes :)    
    
    
    Microsoft Warns of New IE Zero Day http://bit.ly/19bqMbt     
    
    
    This seems to be one of those days when you can't distinguish who are the good and the bad guys    
    
    
    @acadenas then I do not know if I will like the result :)    
    
    
    Updated SSL/TLS Deployment Best Practices deprecates RC4 http://bit.ly/1aIByIj     
    
    
    @hacktimes @CamaradaBakunin @javierM :)    
    
    
    Apple #hNR6    
    
    
    "Torvalds was also asked if he had ever been approached by the U.S. government to insert a backdoor into Linux. " http://www.eweek.com/developer/linus-torvalds-talks-linux-development-at-linuxcon.html#sthash.9IDrJYmf.dpuf …"    
    
    
    "Torvalds responded "no" while shaking his head "yes," as the audience broke into spontaneous laughter."    
    
    
    Counter-Forensics: Pair-Lock Your iOS 7 Device with Apple’s Configurator  http://bit.ly/1eYlJlP  <- nice advice    
    
    
    The FireEye bubble    
    
    
    Talking about proactive security in Copenhagen pic.twitter.com/DF4DZfYKlX    
    
    
    So this week @ElevenPaths is presenting in such remote countries like Argentina and Denmark    
    
    
    My warmest welcome to the @ElevenPaths team to @holesec and @Kachakil #hackers    
    
    
    How a Crypto 'Backdoor' Pitted the Tech World Against the NSA http://Wired.com  http://bit.ly/1dGcy5x     
    
    
    Great sessions in Copenhagen.I did emphasized the importance of being proactive vs being reactive by monitoring and profiling your attackers    
    
    
    It is important to detect and analyze the tools and methods your attackers are using against other targets. At least the known unknowns :)    
    
    
    But it is important to comply with the privacy laws, so you’d better check them before gathering intelligence about your attackers    
    
    
    So today was an strange day. First I bumped into a friend at Schipol airport    
    
    
    Then I bough a train ticket with discount but I wasn't eligible for it. At the train, they were about to give me a fine, but a nice guy    
    
    
    said that I was going with him and that I could use his discount card. Karma++ for that gentleman    
    
    
    And finally, in the same wagon, there was a small fight between 2 guys, that forced me to jump onto the next wagon    
    
    
    Holland, I like you so much :)    
    
    
    BlackBerry's future -- or what's left of it -- is in messenger services, not devices http://bit.ly/15S5OzP  <- I totally disagree    
    
    
    @TheJumpshot @avast_antivirus congrats! Let’s see when you come to San Sebastián to celebrate it!    
    
    
    Big security vendors are so lost when talking about security. Small boutique vendors are always a gem    
    
    
    @areino yes, that is also true, but they can get rid of it by talking to customers and other companies    
    
    
    A European security company proposing to hack back as a good approach. Please don’t do that    
    
    
    I hate the term ‘public-private partnership’ when talking about security.    
    
    
    And it won’t work unless the public and the private companies share the same rules of the game    
    
    
    @infosecadvocate :p    
    
    
    @Antoniojojojo solo odio su forma de presentar :)    
    
    
    @arkaist Public sector is constrained by jurisdiction and legal issues. Private companies are not always constrained by them.    
    
    
    @arkaist opinions are always welcome :)    
    
    
    @frovirosa :p    
    
    
    @acrtn true    
    
    
    @antonio_ramosga @ISACAMadrid @MarlonMolina no prezi nooooo :P    
    
    
    Me he vuelto un master del git.    
    
    
    @antonio_ramosga @ffranz claro!    
    
    
    Shadowy data-mining startup Palantir closed over $196 million in funding http://bit.ly/14QVB5Y  <- wow!!!!!    
    
    
    @acrtn is overrated :)    
    
    
    I have some fears about how some companies are using Palantir, but its stealthiness is really worrying    
    
    
    CTV footage of a hi-tech bank robbery in Sweden http://bit.ly/18j8sOA     
    
    
    "In the year 2012, over 160 baby girls in the U.S. were legally named "Khaleesi""    
    
    
    Long week still ahead but a very positive attitude :)    
    
    
    LogEntries Secures $10M Led By Polaris Ventures To Scale Log Management For SMEs
 http://bit.ly/16cnN49     
    
    
    You won’t believe what email provider Lavabit did to avoid giving the US government its data http://tnw.co/1a1VzYJ     
    
    
    iOS 7 adds multipath TCP http://bit.ly/1c9unfb     
    
    
    Yahoo quick response to the big bounty critics http://bit.ly/1bAx0Eb  <- great! Nice job Ramses!    
    
    
    Experian Buys 41st Parameter For Web Fraud Detection http://bit.ly/18yEDdd  <- $324M for $20M revenue OMG    
    
    
    Acquisitions of companies like SilverTail or 41stParameter are interesting, but I prefer the distributed model of @siftscience    
    
    
    Contrary to what you’ve heard, Android is almost impenetrable to malware http://bit.ly/175HSF2  <- sure?    
    
    
    Threats to Mobile Devices Using the Android Operating System (leaked FBI document) http://bit.ly/17AmxrI     
    
    
    @EddyWillems @gcluley buuuhhhhh!! :P    
    
    
    @georgiaweidman you should definitely check it.    
    
    
    Ola ke ase, ase IPO o ke ase    
    
    
    @J0Milan Initial Public Offering    
    
    
    Russia to monitor 'all communications' at Winter Olympics in Sochi http://bit.ly/17boCHb     
    
    
    I’m thinking about creating a section in the Yersina website about screenshots of yersinia running with info. Any volunteers?    
    
    
    It seems that @alienvault is triying to convince me of something :) pic.twitter.com/CBLjxyl7co    
    
    
    Doubt: many students in China knows SELinux very well, but I'm not sure of the same in Europe/America    
    
    
    How the NSA might use Hotmail or Yahoo cookies to identify Tor users http://bit.ly/15RQSn3     
    
    
    "Can we exploit nodes? Probably not. Legal and technical challenges"    
    
    
    @krypt3ia do you mean Iñigo? :p    
    
    
    @krypt3ia who knows :O    
    
    
    @dkarg @alienvault hmm sort of :)    
    
    
    On my way. I hate waking up at 4:30am.  Not a good time for thinking about code.    
    
    
    Loooong day today, from 4:30am and now leaving the office #exhausted    
    
    
    Hmm reviewing the number of spanish advisors of Europol EC3.... zero #fail    
    
    
    21 advisors from almost any country in Europe (but Spain) http://bit.ly/1amXKWR     
    
    
    @_alt3kx_ ya :P    
    
    
    "run-of-the-mill tech pwnage + intel / insight/evidence gleaned from informants cultivated from within the target site's probable user base"    
    
    
    @InfosecManBlog who knows :)    
    
    
    @InfosecManBlog that's the reason to say it is a fail. I'm not blaming EC3 :)    
    
    
    Here we go back this is the moment tonight is the night we'll fight t'll it's over    
    
    
    @hacktimes @InfosecManBlog yeah, it could be    
    
    
    @lorenzoplanas @InfosecManBlog I'd say that there are many.    
    
    
    How the NSA Thinks About Secrecy and Risk http://bit.ly/1ab57PO  <- 'old' but nice article by Mr Schneier    
    
    
    ¿Qué opináis? O quizás ya me esté volviendo demasiado paranoico :)    
    
    
    @areino indeed :)    
    
    
    @hacktimes @areino pero por otros motivos no? :)    
    
    
    @areino @hacktimes xDDDDDD    
    
    
    @lsaiz @areino beer++ :)    
    
    
    PGP inventor doesn't use PGP "because it doesn't run well on a Mac" http://aol.it/GIklnP  :)    
    
    
    @Carlos_Perez @GPGTools I guess he has, but I think he really means his software, PGP and not GPG    
    
    
    @jordi_prats screen o tmux son obligatorias :)    
    
    
    TSA Loudspeakers Threaten Travelers With Arrest For Joking About Security http://bit.ly/1hKaxW9  <- ¿?¿?    
    
    
    Reverse Engineering a D-Link Backdoor http://bit.ly/1hNwraV  <- great!    
    
    
    xmlset_roodkcableoj28840ybtide    
    
    
    #FreeJoel    
    
    
    @Packetknife @thegrugq @TheDailyShow any link?    
    
    
    Why Android SSL was downgraded from AES256-SHA to RC4-MD5 in late 2010 http://bit.ly/16Jr0Zb     
    
    
    If you care about your company, stop treating yourself like shit. http://bit.ly/19K283Z  <- true    
    
    
    Lessons from Silk Road: don't host your virtual illegal drug bazaar in Iceland http://bit.ly/17H8MmW     
    
    
    Is it recommended a detached signature of a self signed CA?    
    
    
    @JoseSelvi congratulations! Well done!    
    
    
    @jchernandcastro @veorq and ROT13 can also be mentally calculated in real time :)    
    
    
    @matalaz :p    
    
    
    @roman_soft @bquintero @fjserna Google is evil    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife can you please talk properly for us, the foreign citizens of the world? :)    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife much appreciated :)    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife I’ve written down everything so that I can say it in my next speech :)    
    
    
    Do we have the % of Spanish GSEs compared to the rest of the world? /cc @JoseSelvi @taddong    
    
    
    @JoseSelvi @taddong @Angelill0 @jdortiz well done guys!!    
    
    
    .@qustodio is looking for a Customer Service Manager in Barcelona http://bit.ly/1fHGx0s     
    
    
    The presentation about iMessage privacy by @quarkslab is really great http://bit.ly/1gpK8Br  [PDF]    
    
    
    @osxreverser :P    
    
    
    Sueñozzzzzz    
    
    
    @acrtn a mi me mola, pero nunca consigo meter la palabra :)    
    
    
    Can we please set up as a good practice to offer Spanish ham and boletus in any security event cocktail?    
    
    
    @SantityKi indeed!    
    
    
    The Cybersecurity Industry Is Hiring, But Young People Aren’t Interested http://bit.ly/H4cktF     
    
    
    @SantityKi prueba a ver :)    
    
    
    @pof @cryptax +1 :)    
    
    
    @GSICoruna @Tarlogic pics or it didn’t happen :)    
    
    
    @BraianBressan si :)    
    
    
    National Cyber Security Strategies in the World http://bit.ly/1g4FvvM     
    
    
    A (relatively easy to understand) primer on elliptic curve cryptography http://bit.ly/Hkf2vw     
    
    
    @Groove xDDD    
    
    
    Edward Snowden: public indifference is the real enemy in the NSA affair http://bit.ly/18ryHPN     
    
    
    @sergiohernando @spiralstairs they need gel with their LDAP trees :)    
    
    
    Bypassing security scanners by changing the system language http://bit.ly/17njXb0     
    
    
    Barcenas file wiper by @rampa http://bit.ly/Hr5uhK  :)    
    
    
    @fjserna @ExodusIntel @aaronportnoy great picture at @rootedcon!    
    
    
    I've just received my first LINE message in the last 12 months and it's a fake woman trying to scam me!    
    
    
    @enelpc ;)    
    
    
    Australia Says Broadband Ban on Huawei Stays http://bit.ly/16iIg70     
    
    
    MongoHQ Security Breach http://bit.ly/1aKLGB7     
    
    
    @mattgemmell wow, enjoy one of the most beautiful islands!    
    
    
    Lockheed Martin Brings FireEye, Red Hat And Splunk To Its Cyber Security Alliance http://on.wsj.com/1gfiiqO     
    
    
    @trufae and use some kind of IRM too    
    
    
    @txipi espero que no sea nada!    
    
    
    Pinczakko's Guide to AMI BIOS Reverse Engineering - Pinczakko Official Website http://bit.ly/HjLU7t  #BadBIOS    
    
    
    DON'T BREW THAT CUPPA! Your kettle could be a SPAMBOT http://bit.ly/19XF69m     
    
    
    Liberty Reserve co-founder pleads guilty to money laundering http://cnet.co/1f8Qkdg     
    
    
    Bad BIOS, whatcha want
Watcha want, whatcha gonna do?
When sheriff John Brown come for you
Tell me whatcha wanna do, whatcha gonna do?    
    
    
    Probabilistic Programming and Bayesian Methods for Hackers http://bit.ly/19t6eha     
    
    
    iPads banned from Cabinet meetings over fears Chinese spies could use them as covert bugs to listen in on ministers http://dailym.ai/1aXUnYX     
    
    
    @jpmens ejabberd?    
    
    
    Former DHS/NSA Official Attacks Bruce Schneier With Bizarre, Factually Incorrect, Non-sensical Rant http://bit.ly/1874o1F     
    
    
    @JuanMLSanta @jatorre any interesting big data visualization companies apart from Pallantir?    
    
    
    GCHQ data snooping has "destroyed trust in British tech" http://bit.ly/1iRGbS4     
    
    
    Operation Ephemeral Hydra: IE Zero-Day Linked to DeputyDog Uses Diskless Method http://bit.ly/1bt0fI4     
    
    
    Malicious PDF Analysis Evasion Techniques http://bit.ly/18lfEHW     
    
    
    Trustwave acquires data security provider Application Security, Inc. http://bit.ly/17ZFWmA     
    
    
    Quantum Spying: GCHQ Used Fake LinkedIn Pages to Target Engineers http://bit.ly/16W9zEw     
    
    
    Tech companies respond to reports of NSA tracking switched-off mobile phones http://bit.ly/1aAKaNK     
    
    
    @cesarcer @e_kaspersky using XP maybe? :)    
    
    
    It seems that @psaneme and @segofensiva are doing great with their WhatsApp research. Well done!    
    
    
    Renault introduces DRM for car batteries http://bit.ly/1bmozJT     
    
    
    Arbor cloud to offer third-layer of defence against DDoS attacks http://bit.ly/1bBoq7d     
    
    
    Amazon's new virtual desktop is a good product, but it is only Windows based :(    
    
    
    @andrewsmhay BeOS maybe :p    
    
    
    Brazil and Germany issue joint UN resolution on Digital Privacy http://bit.ly/HStyuO     
    
    
    New OSX/Crisis or Business Cards Gone Wild http://bit.ly/1aVm5HF     
    
    
    I've just discovered Norvig's spelling collector in 21 lines of Python http://bit.ly/HP6xsh  <- awesome read. /via @aitorciki    
    
    
    @MoebiuZ my fault! :p    
    
    
    I meant spelling correctors, not collectors in my last tweet :p    
    
    
    Being awake since 4am is not the best way to start a busy as a bee Friday    
    
    
    @acrtn Ex nihilo nihil fit. :)    
    
    
    @J0SM1 seguro que te gusta :)    
    
    
    Why Companies Are Thinking Twice About Buying American http://ti.me/1al2ZZx     
    
    
    EMET 4.1 Uncovered by @0xdabbad00 [PDF] http://bit.ly/1aBaKde     
    
    
    So it seems that vBulletin was compromised http://bit.ly/1bJa6eV     
    
    
    CDNs are better managed by fraudsters than by legit applications    
    
    
    Dynamic generation of malicious APK-as-a-service #concept    
    
    
    @daniel_rome @corelanc0d3r @rootedcon @pwntester @patowc +1    
    
    
    There were some attempts to compromise my GitHub account, coming from a Jakarta ip address.    
    
    
    If you connect to that ip address, there is a router web configuration panel with admin/admin :(    
    
    
    Langner’s final Stuxnet analysis comes with surprises http://bit.ly/17LLLG2  <- recommended    
    
    
    @Beaker where is its official web page? :)    
    
    
    @andrewsmhay @Beaker resilience will be valuable too :)    
    
    
    Family of alleged Silk Road operator Ross Ulbricht launches legal defense fund http://bit.ly/1b8GUj3     
    
    
    The kidnapping in Milan CIA OPSEC fiasco is a fascinating story about phone metadata :)    
    
    
    1.Combine the man-in-the-middle BGP hijacking attacks described by @renesys with a CA compromise
2.???
3.PROFIT    
    
    
    @fjjariego I disagree. Even when in tribes your privacy scope was the tribe, and no other tribe knew anything private about you    
    
    
    Google Account Recovery Vulnerability http://bit.ly/I7hMge     
    
    
    Tools for fingerprinting and exploiting Amazon cloud infrastructures http://bit.ly/1elLlWr  <- impressive by @w3af    
    
    
    @segofensiva @w3af how was your presentation? Are the slides available? :) Have fun both of you there!    
    
    
    @w3af @segofensiva Yes, I got them. I was also asking for Jaime's slides :)    
    
    
    Yesterday in the plane I read the RFC 2660 about 'Secure HTTP' (not HTTPS) that had some advantages over https http://bit.ly/I4dR3h     
    
    
    After a quick look, it seems that there aren't any sHTTP implementation in any browser or server.    
    
    
    OMG Safari push notifications http://bit.ly/I7Ic1m     
    
    
    @lsaiz more flexibility, non repudiation, better proxy or virtual hosts support etc.    
    
    
    @lsaiz old crypto yes, but some interesting features as well :p    
    
    
    “@ForbesTech: Hackers broke into the computers of Syria's secret police. And found porn. http://bit.ly/Iast1Q ” :-O    
    
    
    I've just watched 'Startup..com' and I'm shocked after finding out that it's a documental and not a movie :-O    
    
    
    @leonardonve and kids? :)    
    
    
    @msuiche @thegrugq @snare Irún is a legit Spanish city :)    
    
    
    @_Angelucho_ congrats :)    
    
    
    PE-Parse: A PE parser resistant to malformed or maliciously crafted PE files http://bit.ly/1gcrREe     
    
    
    @diervo indeed! :P    
    
    
    @nicowaisman big lebowski lo aprobaría :)    
    
    
    @cynicalsecurity I'm a heavy user of all those apps (including Threema), but what does Nagios to do with them? :)    
    
    
    @cynicalsecurity ahh got it.    
    
    
    Brazil, Argentina push for joint cyber shield for South America http://bit.ly/IdGlaT  <- it will work if they don't talk about football :)    
    
    
    There Is A 'Very Surprising' Connection Between Bitcoin's Creator And The Alleged Founder Of The Silk Road http://read.bi/1b1M1eS     
    
    
    Snowden spyware revelations: we need to unmask the five-eyed monster http://bit.ly/194s6Mr     
    
    
    lluminating The Billion Dollar U.S. Intelligence Budget: Project SpyLighter Documents NSA Surveillance Technology http://onforb.es/17QZfyb     
    
    
    How A Delaware Doctor Was Linked To Silk Road Drug Sales http://onforb.es/1b2V1QX  <- fascinating story :)    
    
    
    'radicalizers appear to be particularly vulnerable in the area of authority when their private and public behaviors are not consistent'    
    
    
    @trufae a radare competitor? :P    
    
    
    Kim Jong-un will allegedly "cyber warfare" as one of the three means of warfare http://bit.ly/1bVLRGZ     
    
    
    @osxreverser APT is dead due to an OPSEC failure? :P    
    
    
    I've just migrated a server from nginx+apache+mod_wsgi to nginx+lighthttpd+uwsgi. Oh man, life is beautiful    
    
    
    @revskills por ahora uso lighthttpd con fastcgi para PHP y uwsgi para django    
    
    
    @xtremesecurity memory. Apache is a memory monster    
    
    
    For Nearly Two Decades the Nuclear Launch Code at all Minuteman Silos in the United States Was 00000000 http://bit.ly/19bvCVy  <- ¿?    
    
    
    Britain targets Guardian newspaper over intelligence leaks related to Edward Snowden http://wapo.st/19bvNQD     
    
    
    Your Product is Bullshit and you’re Going to Fail if you Don’t Ask Users to Pay http://bit.ly/1b5Cxni     
    
    
    @grey_area yes, I'm not sure if it's true    
    
    
    Can anyone ask Linus his opinion about gendered pronouns in code? #dareifyoucan    
    
    
    Red-Haired Women Pick The Best Passwords, Bearded Men the Worst http://ti.me/1fYHlhK  <- this is what I was looking for    
    
    
    Akamai to Buy DDoS Protection firm Prolexic for $370 Million http://bit.ly/1eGYEAl  <- uff Akamai pushes hard    
    
    
    @Napaboy they already offer an anti-DDoS service, but I guess they want to have the client side as well    
    
    
    It seems that Akamai wants to add client side DDoS protection to their existing antiDDoS portfolio    
    
    
    @areino almost all telcos offer that service, but not precisely cheap :)    
    
    
    @krypt3ia ??    
    
    
    @krypt3ia I didn't know about it. You have ruined my life now :p    
    
    
    The Insidiousness of Facebook Messenger's Mobile App Terms of Service http://huff.to/18hez4f  <- better features than a trojan :)    
    
    
    @FraudBlogger AFAIK many EU banks are blocking foreign charges by default in all cards due to the high fraud rates in non EMV countries    
    
    
    Cyber Readiness Index http://bit.ly/1cnHHLw  <- really interesting work by Melissa Hathaway analyzing 35 countries cybersecurity commitment    
    
    
    Perhaps it is a universal truth that the loss of liberty at home is to be charged to provisions against danger,real or pretended,from abroad    
    
    
    Last quote by James Madison, fourth President of the United States (1809–1817)    
    
    
    @ahmad_aabed no idea at all :)    
    
    
    @torremochaj @diegomarino @Aquilino @inakib @jlhortelano homeland security.their product is good and their engineers top-notch    
    
    
    Group-IB assists to suppress the activities of a “Blackhole” exploit-kit author, “Paunch” is arrested http://bit.ly/1hCw4Ew     
    
    
    Governments planning to control security tech exports http://zd.net/18dYJfQ  <- no comments :(    
    
    
    Kudos to @CERT_Polska_en for their superb job tracking and taking down some malware incidents    
    
    
    After playing for some days with SAML IdPs and Service Providers I only can say that it is PITA :)    
    
    
    "SAML is the Windows XP of Identity. No funding. No innovation. People still use it. But it has no future"    
    
    
    "There is no future for SAML. No one is putting money into SAML development. NO ONE is writing new SAML code. SAML is dead.”    
    
    
    @lsaiz I'm not frustrated, but happy :) I don't like SAML at all.there is only one thing that I hate more: a SAML Java implementation :)    
    
    
    Mozilla Revoking Trust in one ANSSI Certificate http://mzl.la/1byJz43  <- well done bit the entire model should be rebuilt    
    
    
    @ssantosv for you and for me and the entire human race :)    
    
    
    Tiny Kentucky Town Agrees to Pay Only Police Officer In Bitcoin http://bit.ly/1jHGlPl     
    
    
    Long day today with mixed feelings. It was great to meet so many friends agains but some mistakes were made    
    
    
    @hectorsm jajaja 100% verdad    
    
    
    @alonsocandado gracias Alonso! :)    
    
    
    @roman_soft @Kachakil xDDDD what happens in Majadahonda, stays in Majadahonda  :P    
    
    
    Internet-wide efforts to fight email phishing are working http://bit.ly/19LMann     
    
    
    "More specifically, the 91.4% of the authenticated non-spam emails sent to Gmail users come from senders that have adopted DKIM or SPF"    
    
    
    Security guru Bruce Schneier to leave employer BT http://bit.ly/19NDInt     
    
    
    The inevitable move - 64-bit ZeuS has come enhanced with Tor http://bit.ly/1k8NZCk     
    
    
    Apple blocks bitcoin payments on secure messaging app Gliph http://bit.ly/1dIVviv     
    
    
    Hmm it seems that I will finally meet @Packetknife soon    
    
    
    @Packetknife it's not the spanish style. It will be more sibylline :P    
    
    
    DGA Changer Malware Able to Modify Domain-Generation Seed on the Fly http://bit.ly/18RCojl  <- cool :)    
    
    
    @trufae I've been using Threema, but it is not open source. Telegraph looks nice    
    
    
    @trufae @jakoubek then I will keep using Threema ;)    
    
    
    @jakoubek @trufae true, but it is a good option nowadays    
    
    
    Impressive. 400 million of monthly active WhatsApp users. http://bit.ly/1fq2jD5     
    
    
    @alyepez congrats! It seems 2014 will be an awesome for the AlienVault's team :)    
    
    
    @0xabad1dea excellent UI? Some of them have fancy images but their UI is horrible    
    
    
    I'm looking for a spare @shmoocon ticket, just in case someone can not make it    
    
    
    Talo + txistorra + sidra = WIN #SantoTomas2013    
    
    
    @mikko well done.    
    
    
    If I were a malicious state sponsored group I'd use UDP and RC6 right now!    
    
    
    Exfiltrate, exfiltrate, exfiltrate!    
    
    
    @matalaz @reversemode que rule    
    
    
    Wow if it's true that @FireEye has acquired @Mandiant it is really a shocking movement    
    
    
    'FireEye now has a $5 billion market capitalization, despite the fact it has yet to turn a profit.'    
    
    
    IMHO @Mandiant acquisition by @FireEye is a really smart one, but let's see how products and services bundle together    
    
    
    A billion bucks. It was the same amount FaceBook offered to the SnapChat guys. :)    
    
    
    “@nicoleperlroth: Um, something amiss at the WSJ copy desk??? "Mandiant, a computer security firm known for fingering Chinese hackers."” LOL    
    
    
    Lyndsey Scott Tells Us What It's Like To Be A Victoria's Secret Model Who Codes In Her Free Time http://read.bi/1ix6Bwz     
    
    
    Oops I didn't notice this one: Bluecoat acquires Norman Shark http://bit.ly/1hYNokG     
    
    
    @lsaiz who cares about that ? :p    
    
    
    @lsaiz mandiant yes, but Fireeye is more global    
    
    
    @avillalbap :)    
    
    
    @alex_lanstein I guess they wanted to say mon Dieu! :P Btw, congrats!    
    
    
    @DennisF which state?    
    
    
    No #BadHypervisor :p    
    
    
    @osxreverser nothing to see here. Please disperse    
    
    
    @mjg59 a wine shower? Here in Spain you have some wine spa treatments :)    
    
    
    Facebook sued for scanning 'private' messages for profit http://bit.ly/19SDxYm     
    
    
    @Infinityindies @noticiashacker1 @roman_soft ya lo veo complicado :)    
    
    
    whatsapp://send?text=Hello%2C%20World!    
    
    
    WhatsApp hooks in iOS http://bit.ly/14y8mTO     
    
    
    @0xroot es lo primero que pensé!    
    
    
    OVH compromised. http://bit.ly/16Ve65X     
    
    
    I haven’t log on in the Apple Developer section for some months, and today I needed to. Kudos to Murphy :)    
    
    
    The Secret Service Agent Who Collared Cybercrooks by Selling Them Fake IDs http://bit.ly/18wXcOB  <- kingpin reloaded :)    
    
    
    The thin line of entrapment    
    
    
    The Challenge Posed by Chinese Psychological Warfare http://herit.ag/163Wi9F     
    
    
    How Would the U.S. Respond to a Nightmare Cyber Attack? http://bit.ly/11bv810     
    
    
    @mobiplayer :)    
    
    
    Cisco to buy cybersecurity firm Sourcefire for $2.7 billion http://cnb.cx/17AJGZ9  /via @areino    
    
    
    Now you can't tell that Cisco has a crappy IDS :)    
    
    
    But at the end of the day, an IDS is like an AV, it helps you to detect some bad stuff, but just some.    
    
    
    At least IDS allow you to set up and tailor the rules    
    
    
    @DennisF @cBekrar xDD    
    
    
    Is Cisco going to keep the Sourcefire brand (I hope so) or it will be renamed as Cisco IPS2 or some obscure acronym?    
    
    
    Sorry for being so pessimist,but is there any success story of a security product acquisition by Cisco? #pun    
    
    
    Phone and texting app ‘Viber’ hacked by Syrian Electronic Army [update: Viber comments] http://bit.ly/15e0XXS     
    
    
    ‘Today the Viber Support site was defaced after a Viber employee unfortunately fell victim to an email phishing attack'    
    
    
    @ateixei hmm somehow yes    
    
    
    @briankrebs add Viber    
    
    
    Good morning twitverse!    
    
    
    @Packetknife @krypt3ia are there people beyond US borders? :)    
    
    
    @peepdf @EternalTodo I want one! :)    
    
    
    @Packetknife @0xabad1dea the problem is that there are really good alternatives on Europe    
    
    
    Hmm there aren't big headlines from #Defcon, just a mention that Will Smith was there. #strange    
    
    
    Germans’ fear of American spying surges - http://on.ft.com/154W2Vq     
    
    
    German Minister on EU Company Ban For Privacy Violation http://bit.ly/1ctjUez     
    
    
    10 PRINT "Hello World!"
20 GOTO 10    
    
    
    @cBekrar @csoghoian can we have the two of you in the same panel? It would definitely a success :)    
    
    
    @jeremiahg @Beaker @hpsecurity @CiscoSecurity hehe they removed the post.    
    
    
    Hmm I'm getting many promoted tweets by @Sourcefire. For me it is like receiving a spam email, but on Twitter.    
    
    
    MS: Windows Phone 8 Wi-Fi Vulnerable, Cannot Be Patched http://bit.ly/13ISCfw     
    
    
    @ecasbas congratulations! Let's see if we can meet there soon! :)    
    
    
    @kylemaxwell @briankrebs good contacts in the industry and clients.    
    
    
    @jlhortelano xD cierto    
    
    
    @hacktimes @Groove es flipante.    
    
    
    Silent Mail also shuts down its service, fearing the 'Lavabit experience' http://bit.ly/17bp60t     
    
    
    But Silent Circle should also take care about the rest of their products, they are on the same page.    
    
    
    At the end of the day, there is a huge opportunity for a non-US secure email service provider.    
    
    
    @Packetknife I'd say that with their products they could “be complicit in crimes against the American people.”    
    
    
    @Packetknife Caiman Islands is a great place to live in :)    
    
    
    @Packetknife time will tell. I hope rationality survives    
    
    
    A concept that I really hate: Next Generation SOC #derp    
    
    
    @mikk0j it just has a NG before the word SOC :P    
    
    
    The SOC/CSIRT/CERT concept/hype has caused a lot of damage in the security industry.    
    
    
    @VS_ @Packetknife the hole thing. Very few companies take advantage of the investment and make them really useful    
    
    
    Counting down to the launch of ardusat – world’s first open source satellite (based on arduino) http://bit.ly/15WW99H     
    
    
    Slight shift seen in official Chinese attitude on cybersecurity http://bit.ly/19d4fMz     
    
    
    @areino mola :P    
    
    
    Veo mucha histeria con el tema de Lavabit o SilentMail pero no veo a (casi) nadie que use PGP/GPG o sMIME    
    
    
    Police nab alleged DDoS extortion gang at Heathrow Airport http://bit.ly/17iRfTy     
    
    
    Estonian Intelligence Official Confesses to Spying for Russia http://bit.ly/18pScL1     
    
    
    London Turns Off Snooping Trash Cans That Tracked Pedestrians' Phones  http://bit.ly/1d242hG     
    
    
    If You Use Gmail, You Should Have 'No Legitimate Expectation Of Privacy' http://read.bi/14akbuz     
    
    
    @martibk @TheCookie_es the other day I tried the honey cookey with almonds and was great!    
    
    
    Congrats to the @Trusteer guys for the acquisition. They were really doing a great job. Another success for a security startup in Israel    
    
    
    @Packetknife @Wh1t3Rabbit read it again and put yourself in a non-US citizen's shoes. I haven't got any words to describe the article :(    
    
    
    @Wh1t3Rabbit I have the same feeling after watching the movie ‘Independence day’ :)    
    
    
    Bletchley - A collection of practical application cryptanalysis tools http://bit.ly/17Xqe7c     
    
    
    United Internet (1&1) acquires Spanish webhosting and cloud specialist Arsys http://bit.ly/150uDZp     
    
    
    Why Some Startups Say the Cloud Is a Waste of Money http://Wired.com  http://bit.ly/1cT982d  <- not some big enterprises too    
    
    
    @rafaorga safe trip!    
    
    
    LastPass Vulnerability Left IE Passwords Exposed, Update Now http://bit.ly/1cTsowH     
    
    
    Come on, it's 2013 and the adduser command still asks for Room Number, Work and Home phone.How come is not asking for a twitter account? :)    
    
    
    So after @Trusteer acquisition by IBM, my bet is that the next israeli security startup to be acquired is @seculert    
    
    
    Changing IP address to access public website ruled violation of US law  http://ars.to/17ZLYzk     
    
    
    @Packetknife @georgiaweidman @jadedsecurity I’ve also seen @rik_ferguson    
    
    
    From hackers to entrepreneurs: The Sino-US cyberwar veterans going straight http://bit.ly/13RNsdR     
    
    
    @DennisF nice pic at the header :P    
    
    
    German IT officials reportedly deem Windows 8 too ‘dangerous’ to use http://bit.ly/19z6qdq     
    
    
    Introducing a brand new way to share everything: PRSM - The Sharing Network http://bit.ly/12rLZxc  :)    
    
    
    After some years, the 0.7.3 version of Yersinia is out!! Thanks to Alfredo :) https://github.com/tomac/yersinia     
    
    
    @CipherLaw there isn’t AFAIK.    
    
    
    Si vis pacem, para bellum    
    
    
    It's great to see that Yersinia runs perfectly on OSX 10.8 (the ncurses GUI)    
    
    
    @osxreverser where have you read that?    
    
    
    @5ean5ullivan actually, that specific registrar offers antiphishing solutions :P    
    
    
    “@officialmcafee: JOHN MCAFEE TELLS ALL / RAW: http://bit.ly/1dPPORD ” <- finally the truth :)    
    
    
    The Password is dead. Long live The Password!    
    
    
    @trufae I’ve used for several months and it works great    
    
    
    @NecronoiD @francisco_oca skate or die! :p    
    
    
    Is This the Leader of the Syrian Electronic Army? (Update) http://bit.ly/15jFbFS     
    
    
    Glyph should be the most hated word in the world today for iOS and OSX users (including me!!)    
    
    
    CTGlyphRun::CloneRange(CTRun const*, CFRange, TRun::SubrangingStyle) + 142    
    
    
    I see glyphs everywhere    
    
    
    Dark Patterns: inside the interfaces designed to trick you http://bit.ly/15pefO6  <- nice article    
    
    
    Former White House 'copyright czar' appointed CEO of powerful tech lobby group http://bit.ly/18pxSaz  <- oops    
    
    
    @mgesteiro @pof but kicking a connected guy out of the network is a crime :P    
    
    
    @carlosdomingo @tomiahonen yes, I was also waiting for his comments about Elop :)    
    
    
    AlienVault Announces $26.5 Million in Series D Funding Led by GGV Capital to Accelerate Rapid Growth 
http://on.mktw.net/13iEF7E     
    
    
    Why Silicon Valley Funds Instagrams, Not Hyperloops http://bit.ly/1fE5Rjz  <- nice article    
    
    
    @suffert we are all doomed :)    
    
    
    The NSA should go to Pamplona next July to participate in the running of the bulls    
    
    
    @avilarenata it depends of your definition of safe enough, but I’d stay away from software from the US if I were paranoid    
    
    
    My last RT shows the an smart configuration for privacy, but it has a huge problem:it entirely relies on TrueCrypt    
    
    
    The Cowboy of the NSA Keith Alexander http://bit.ly/18Inmgb     
    
    
    ExecScent: Mining for New C&C Domains in Live Networks with Adaptive Control Protocol Templates http://bit.ly/15dyjYf     
    
    
    CrowdStrike Closes $30 Million In Series B Financing, Led By Accel Partners http://prn.to/1awIOu5  <- wow offensive bubble? :)    
    
    
    “@matthew_d_green:I received a request from my Dean this morning asking me to remove all copies of my NSA blog post from University servers.    
    
    
    @DennisF I’m running with some similar sandals and once you get used, they are really great. Also for normal activities    
    
    
    @DennisF not at all, but I spent some days until I managed to find the best configuration    
    
    
    NSA and Israeli intelligence: memorandum of understanding – full document http://bit.ly/1b6puDj     
    
    
    "Kleptography: persuading the party to be intercepted to use a  form of crypto that the attacker knows they can break."    
    
    
    @victor_mb :P    
    
    
    Cybersécurité: les ministres interdits de smartphones http://bit.ly/17sIBmX     
    
    
    "From now on any highly classified information must only be transmitted over specially encrypted telephones "    
    
    
    "and all electronic documents can only be transferred using the government’s secure ISIS system"    
    
    
    "not to insert a USB key unless they know exactly where it came from and that it is safe"    
    
    
    "and not to click on any attachments in messages without checking them first."    
    
    
    @cedricpernet I can read it but not speak it though :P    
    
    
    The iPhone 5s fingerprint reader: what you need to know http://bit.ly/15Wi8eu     
    
    
    New Details in How the Feds Take Laptops at Border http://nyti.ms/15WSg8n     
    
    
    @ronaldotcom no :P    
    
    
    @hacktimes :)    
    
    
    Microsoft Warns of New IE Zero Day http://bit.ly/19bqMbt     
    
    
    This seems to be one of those days when you can't distinguish who are the good and the bad guys    
    
    
    @acadenas then I do not know if I will like the result :)    
    
    
    Updated SSL/TLS Deployment Best Practices deprecates RC4 http://bit.ly/1aIByIj     
    
    
    @hacktimes @CamaradaBakunin @javierM :)    
    
    
    Apple #hNR6    
    
    
    "Torvalds was also asked if he had ever been approached by the U.S. government to insert a backdoor into Linux. " http://www.eweek.com/developer/linus-torvalds-talks-linux-development-at-linuxcon.html#sthash.9IDrJYmf.dpuf …"    
    
    
    "Torvalds responded "no" while shaking his head "yes," as the audience broke into spontaneous laughter."    
    
    
    Counter-Forensics: Pair-Lock Your iOS 7 Device with Apple’s Configurator  http://bit.ly/1eYlJlP  <- nice advice    
    
    
    The FireEye bubble    
    
    
    Talking about proactive security in Copenhagen pic.twitter.com/DF4DZfYKlX    
    
    
    So this week @ElevenPaths is presenting in such remote countries like Argentina and Denmark    
    
    
    My warmest welcome to the @ElevenPaths team to @holesec and @Kachakil #hackers    
    
    
    How a Crypto 'Backdoor' Pitted the Tech World Against the NSA http://Wired.com  http://bit.ly/1dGcy5x     
    
    
    Great sessions in Copenhagen.I did emphasized the importance of being proactive vs being reactive by monitoring and profiling your attackers    
    
    
    It is important to detect and analyze the tools and methods your attackers are using against other targets. At least the known unknowns :)    
    
    
    But it is important to comply with the privacy laws, so you’d better check them before gathering intelligence about your attackers    
    
    
    So today was an strange day. First I bumped into a friend at Schipol airport    
    
    
    Then I bough a train ticket with discount but I wasn't eligible for it. At the train, they were about to give me a fine, but a nice guy    
    
    
    said that I was going with him and that I could use his discount card. Karma++ for that gentleman    
    
    
    And finally, in the same wagon, there was a small fight between 2 guys, that forced me to jump onto the next wagon    
    
    
    Holland, I like you so much :)    
    
    
    BlackBerry's future -- or what's left of it -- is in messenger services, not devices http://bit.ly/15S5OzP  <- I totally disagree    
    
    
    @TheJumpshot @avast_antivirus congrats! Let’s see when you come to San Sebastián to celebrate it!    
    
    
    Big security vendors are so lost when talking about security. Small boutique vendors are always a gem    
    
    
    @areino yes, that is also true, but they can get rid of it by talking to customers and other companies    
    
    
    A European security company proposing to hack back as a good approach. Please don’t do that    
    
    
    I hate the term ‘public-private partnership’ when talking about security.    
    
    
    And it won’t work unless the public and the private companies share the same rules of the game    
    
    
    @infosecadvocate :p    
    
    
    @Antoniojojojo solo odio su forma de presentar :)    
    
    
    @arkaist Public sector is constrained by jurisdiction and legal issues. Private companies are not always constrained by them.    
    
    
    @arkaist opinions are always welcome :)    
    
    
    @frovirosa :p    
    
    
    @acrtn true    
    
    
    @antonio_ramosga @ISACAMadrid @MarlonMolina no prezi nooooo :P    
    
    
    Me he vuelto un master del git.    
    
    
    @antonio_ramosga @ffranz claro!    
    
    
    Shadowy data-mining startup Palantir closed over $196 million in funding http://bit.ly/14QVB5Y  <- wow!!!!!    
    
    
    @acrtn is overrated :)    
    
    
    I have some fears about how some companies are using Palantir, but its stealthiness is really worrying    
    
    
    CTV footage of a hi-tech bank robbery in Sweden http://bit.ly/18j8sOA     
    
    
    "In the year 2012, over 160 baby girls in the U.S. were legally named "Khaleesi""    
    
    
    Long week still ahead but a very positive attitude :)    
    
    
    LogEntries Secures $10M Led By Polaris Ventures To Scale Log Management For SMEs
 http://bit.ly/16cnN49     
    
    
    You won’t believe what email provider Lavabit did to avoid giving the US government its data http://tnw.co/1a1VzYJ     
    
    
    iOS 7 adds multipath TCP http://bit.ly/1c9unfb     
    
    
    Yahoo quick response to the big bounty critics http://bit.ly/1bAx0Eb  <- great! Nice job Ramses!    
    
    
    Experian Buys 41st Parameter For Web Fraud Detection http://bit.ly/18yEDdd  <- $324M for $20M revenue OMG    
    
    
    Acquisitions of companies like SilverTail or 41stParameter are interesting, but I prefer the distributed model of @siftscience    
    
    
    Contrary to what you’ve heard, Android is almost impenetrable to malware http://bit.ly/175HSF2  <- sure?    
    
    
    Threats to Mobile Devices Using the Android Operating System (leaked FBI document) http://bit.ly/17AmxrI     
    
    
    @EddyWillems @gcluley buuuhhhhh!! :P    
    
    
    @georgiaweidman you should definitely check it.    
    
    
    Ola ke ase, ase IPO o ke ase    
    
    
    @J0Milan Initial Public Offering    
    
    
    Russia to monitor 'all communications' at Winter Olympics in Sochi http://bit.ly/17boCHb     
    
    
    I’m thinking about creating a section in the Yersina website about screenshots of yersinia running with info. Any volunteers?    
    
    
    It seems that @alienvault is triying to convince me of something :) pic.twitter.com/CBLjxyl7co    
    
    
    Doubt: many students in China knows SELinux very well, but I'm not sure of the same in Europe/America    
    
    
    How the NSA might use Hotmail or Yahoo cookies to identify Tor users http://bit.ly/15RQSn3     
    
    
    "Can we exploit nodes? Probably not. Legal and technical challenges"    
    
    
    @krypt3ia do you mean Iñigo? :p    
    
    
    @krypt3ia who knows :O    
    
    
    @dkarg @alienvault hmm sort of :)    
    
    
    On my way. I hate waking up at 4:30am.  Not a good time for thinking about code.    
    
    
    Loooong day today, from 4:30am and now leaving the office #exhausted    
    
    
    Hmm reviewing the number of spanish advisors of Europol EC3.... zero #fail    
    
    
    21 advisors from almost any country in Europe (but Spain) http://bit.ly/1amXKWR     
    
    
    @_alt3kx_ ya :P    
    
    
    "run-of-the-mill tech pwnage + intel / insight/evidence gleaned from informants cultivated from within the target site's probable user base"    
    
    
    @InfosecManBlog who knows :)    
    
    
    @InfosecManBlog that's the reason to say it is a fail. I'm not blaming EC3 :)    
    
    
    Here we go back this is the moment tonight is the night we'll fight t'll it's over    
    
    
    @hacktimes @InfosecManBlog yeah, it could be    
    
    
    @lorenzoplanas @InfosecManBlog I'd say that there are many.    
    
    
    How the NSA Thinks About Secrecy and Risk http://bit.ly/1ab57PO  <- 'old' but nice article by Mr Schneier    
    
    
    ¿Qué opináis? O quizás ya me esté volviendo demasiado paranoico :)    
    
    
    @areino indeed :)    
    
    
    @hacktimes @areino pero por otros motivos no? :)    
    
    
    @areino @hacktimes xDDDDDD    
    
    
    @lsaiz @areino beer++ :)    
    
    
    PGP inventor doesn't use PGP "because it doesn't run well on a Mac" http://aol.it/GIklnP  :)    
    
    
    @Carlos_Perez @GPGTools I guess he has, but I think he really means his software, PGP and not GPG    
    
    
    @jordi_prats screen o tmux son obligatorias :)    
    
    
    TSA Loudspeakers Threaten Travelers With Arrest For Joking About Security http://bit.ly/1hKaxW9  <- ¿?¿?    
    
    
    Reverse Engineering a D-Link Backdoor http://bit.ly/1hNwraV  <- great!    
    
    
    xmlset_roodkcableoj28840ybtide    
    
    
    #FreeJoel    
    
    
    @Packetknife @thegrugq @TheDailyShow any link?    
    
    
    Why Android SSL was downgraded from AES256-SHA to RC4-MD5 in late 2010 http://bit.ly/16Jr0Zb     
    
    
    If you care about your company, stop treating yourself like shit. http://bit.ly/19K283Z  <- true    
    
    
    Lessons from Silk Road: don't host your virtual illegal drug bazaar in Iceland http://bit.ly/17H8MmW     
    
    
    Is it recommended a detached signature of a self signed CA?    
    
    
    @JoseSelvi congratulations! Well done!    
    
    
    @jchernandcastro @veorq and ROT13 can also be mentally calculated in real time :)    
    
    
    @matalaz :p    
    
    
    @roman_soft @bquintero @fjserna Google is evil    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife can you please talk properly for us, the foreign citizens of the world? :)    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife much appreciated :)    
    
    
    @krmaher @Packetknife I’ve written down everything so that I can say it in my next speech :)    
    
    
    Do we have the % of Spanish GSEs compared to the rest of the world? /cc @JoseSelvi @taddong    
    
    
    @JoseSelvi @taddong @Angelill0 @jdortiz well done guys!!    
    
    
    .@qustodio is looking for a Customer Service Manager in Barcelona http://bit.ly/1fHGx0s     
    
    
    The presentation about iMessage privacy by @quarkslab is really great http://bit.ly/1gpK8Br  [PDF]    
    
    
    @osxreverser :P    
    
    
    Sueñozzzzzz    
    
    
    @acrtn a mi me mola, pero nunca consigo meter la palabra :)    
    
    
    Can we please set up as a good practice to offer Spanish ham and boletus in any security event cocktail?    
    
    
    @SantityKi indeed!    
    
    
    The Cybersecurity Industry Is Hiring, But Young People Aren’t Interested http://bit.ly/H4cktF     
    
    
    @SantityKi prueba a ver :)    
    
    
    @pof @cryptax +1 :)    
    
    
    @GSICoruna @Tarlogic pics or it didn’t happen :)    
    
    
    @BraianBressan si :)    
    
    
    National Cyber Security Strategies in the World http://bit.ly/1g4FvvM     
    
    
    A (relatively easy to understand) primer on elliptic curve cryptography http://bit.ly/Hkf2vw     
    
    
    @Groove xDDD    
    
    
    Edward Snowden: public indifference is the real enemy in the NSA affair http://bit.ly/18ryHPN     
    
    
    @sergiohernando @spiralstairs they need gel with their LDAP trees :)    
    
    
    Bypassing security scanners by changing the system language http://bit.ly/17njXb0     
    
    
    Barcenas file wiper by @rampa http://bit.ly/Hr5uhK  :)    
    
    
    @fjserna @ExodusIntel @aaronportnoy great picture at @rootedcon!    
    
    
    I've just received my first LINE message in the last 12 months and it's a fake woman trying to scam me!    
    
    
    @enelpc ;)    
    
    
    Australia Says Broadband Ban on Huawei Stays http://bit.ly/16iIg70     
    
    
    MongoHQ Security Breach http://bit.ly/1aKLGB7     
    
    
    @mattgemmell wow, enjoy one of the most beautiful islands!    
    
    
    Lockheed Martin Brings FireEye, Red Hat And Splunk To Its Cyber Security Alliance http://on.wsj.com/1gfiiqO     
    
    
    @trufae and use some kind of IRM too    
    
    
    @txipi espero que no sea nada!    
    
    
    Pinczakko's Guide to AMI BIOS Reverse Engineering - Pinczakko Official Website http://bit.ly/HjLU7t  #BadBIOS    
    
    
    DON'T BREW THAT CUPPA! Your kettle could be a SPAMBOT http://bit.ly/19XF69m     
    
    
    Liberty Reserve co-founder pleads guilty to money laundering http://cnet.co/1f8Qkdg     
    
    
    Bad BIOS, whatcha want
Watcha want, whatcha gonna do?
When sheriff John Brown come for you
Tell me whatcha wanna do, whatcha gonna do?    
    
    
    Probabilistic Programming and Bayesian Methods for Hackers http://bit.ly/19t6eha     
    
    
    iPads banned from Cabinet meetings over fears Chinese spies could use them as covert bugs to listen in on ministers http://dailym.ai/1aXUnYX     
    
    
    @jpmens ejabberd?    
    
    
    Former DHS/NSA Official Attacks Bruce Schneier With Bizarre, Factually Incorrect, Non-sensical Rant http://bit.ly/1874o1F     
    
    
    @JuanMLSanta @jatorre any interesting big data visualization companies apart from Pallantir?    
    
    
    GCHQ data snooping has "destroyed trust in British tech" http://bit.ly/1iRGbS4     
    
    
    Operation Ephemeral Hydra: IE Zero-Day Linked to DeputyDog Uses Diskless Method http://bit.ly/1bt0fI4     
    
    
    Malicious PDF Analysis Evasion Techniques http://bit.ly/18lfEHW     
    
    
    Trustwave acquires data security provider Application Security, Inc. http://bit.ly/17ZFWmA     
    
    
    Quantum Spying: GCHQ Used Fake LinkedIn Pages to Target Engineers http://bit.ly/16W9zEw     
    
    
    Tech companies respond to reports of NSA tracking switched-off mobile phones http://bit.ly/1aAKaNK     
    
    
    @cesarcer @e_kaspersky using XP maybe? :)    
    
    
    It seems that @psaneme and @segofensiva are doing great with their WhatsApp research. Well done!    
    
    
    Renault introduces DRM for car batteries http://bit.ly/1bmozJT     
    
    
    Arbor cloud to offer third-layer of defence against DDoS attacks http://bit.ly/1bBoq7d     
    
    
    Amazon's new virtual desktop is a good product, but it is only Windows based :(    
    
    
    @andrewsmhay BeOS maybe :p    
    
    
    Brazil and Germany issue joint UN resolution on Digital Privacy http://bit.ly/HStyuO     
    
    
    New OSX/Crisis or Business Cards Gone Wild http://bit.ly/1aVm5HF     
    
    
    I've just discovered Norvig's spelling collector in 21 lines of Python http://bit.ly/HP6xsh  <- awesome read. /via @aitorciki    
    
    
    @MoebiuZ my fault! :p    
    
    
    I meant spelling correctors, not collectors in my last tweet :p    
    
    
    Being awake since 4am is not the best way to start a busy as a bee Friday    
    
    
    @acrtn Ex nihilo nihil fit. :)    
    
    
    @J0SM1 seguro que te gusta :)    
    
    
    Why Companies Are Thinking Twice About Buying American http://ti.me/1al2ZZx     
    
    
    EMET 4.1 Uncovered by @0xdabbad00 [PDF] http://bit.ly/1aBaKde     
    
    
    So it seems that vBulletin was compromised http://bit.ly/1bJa6eV     
    
    
    CDNs are better managed by fraudsters than by legit applications    
    
    
    Dynamic generation of malicious APK-as-a-service #concept    
    
    
    @daniel_rome @corelanc0d3r @rootedcon @pwntester @patowc +1    
    
    
    There were some attempts to compromise my GitHub account, coming from a Jakarta ip address.    
    
    
    If you connect to that ip address, there is a router web configuration panel with admin/admin :(    
    
    
    Langner’s final Stuxnet analysis comes with surprises http://bit.ly/17LLLG2  <- recommended    
    
    
    @Beaker where is its official web page? :)    
    
    
    @andrewsmhay @Beaker resilience will be valuable too :)    
    
    
    Family of alleged Silk Road operator Ross Ulbricht launches legal defense fund http://bit.ly/1b8GUj3     
    
    
    The kidnapping in Milan CIA OPSEC fiasco is a fascinating story about phone metadata :)    
    
    
    1.Combine the man-in-the-middle BGP hijacking attacks described by @renesys with a CA compromise
2.???
3.PROFIT    
    
    
    @fjjariego I disagree. Even when in tribes your privacy scope was the tribe, and no other tribe knew anything private about you    
    
    
    Google Account Recovery Vulnerability http://bit.ly/I7hMge     
    
    
    Tools for fingerprinting and exploiting Amazon cloud infrastructures http://bit.ly/1elLlWr  <- impressive by @w3af    
    
    
    @segofensiva @w3af how was your presentation? Are the slides available? :) Have fun both of you there!    
    
    
    @w3af @segofensiva Yes, I got them. I was also asking for Jaime's slides :)    
    
    
    Yesterday in the plane I read the RFC 2660 about 'Secure HTTP' (not HTTPS) that had some advantages over https http://bit.ly/I4dR3h     
    
    
    After a quick look, it seems that there aren't any sHTTP implementation in any browser or server.    
    
    
    OMG Safari push notifications http://bit.ly/I7Ic1m     
    
    
    @lsaiz more flexibility, non repudiation, better proxy or virtual hosts support etc.    
    
    
    @lsaiz old crypto yes, but some interesting features as well :p    
    
    
    “@ForbesTech: Hackers broke into the computers of Syria's secret police. And found porn. http://bit.ly/Iast1Q ” :-O    
    
    
    I've just watched 'Startup..com' and I'm shocked after finding out that it's a documental and not a movie :-O    
    
    
    @leonardonve and kids? :)    
    
    
    @msuiche @thegrugq @snare Irún is a legit Spanish city :)    
    
    
    @_Angelucho_ congrats :)    
    
    
    PE-Parse: A PE parser resistant to malformed or maliciously crafted PE files http://bit.ly/1gcrREe     
    
    
    @diervo indeed! :P    
    
    
    @nicowaisman big lebowski lo aprobaría :)    
    
    
    @cynicalsecurity I'm a heavy user of all those apps (including Threema), but what does Nagios to do with them? :)    
    
    
    @cynicalsecurity ahh got it.    
    
    
    Brazil, Argentina push for joint cyber shield for South America http://bit.ly/IdGlaT  <- it will work if they don't talk about football :)    
    
    
    There Is A 'Very Surprising' Connection Between Bitcoin's Creator And The Alleged Founder Of The Silk Road http://read.bi/1b1M1eS     
    
    
    Snowden spyware revelations: we need to unmask the five-eyed monster http://bit.ly/194s6Mr     
    
    
    lluminating The Billion Dollar U.S. Intelligence Budget: Project SpyLighter Documents NSA Surveillance Technology http://onforb.es/17QZfyb     
    
    
    How A Delaware Doctor Was Linked To Silk Road Drug Sales http://onforb.es/1b2V1QX  <- fascinating story :)    
    
    
    'radicalizers appear to be particularly vulnerable in the area of authority when their private and public behaviors are not consistent'    
    
    
    @trufae a radare competitor? :P    
    
    
    Kim Jong-un will allegedly "cyber warfare" as one of the three means of warfare http://bit.ly/1bVLRGZ     
    
    
    @osxreverser APT is dead due to an OPSEC failure? :P    
    
    
    I've just migrated a server from nginx+apache+mod_wsgi to nginx+lighthttpd+uwsgi. Oh man, life is beautiful    
    
    
    @revskills por ahora uso lighthttpd con fastcgi para PHP y uwsgi para django    
    
    
    @xtremesecurity memory. Apache is a memory monster    
    
    
    For Nearly Two Decades the Nuclear Launch Code at all Minuteman Silos in the United States Was 00000000 http://bit.ly/19bvCVy  <- ¿?    
    
    
    Britain targets Guardian newspaper over intelligence leaks related to Edward Snowden http://wapo.st/19bvNQD     
    
    
    Your Product is Bullshit and you’re Going to Fail if you Don’t Ask Users to Pay http://bit.ly/1b5Cxni     
    
    
    @grey_area yes, I'm not sure if it's true    
    
    
    Can anyone ask Linus his opinion about gendered pronouns in code? #dareifyoucan    
    
    
    Red-Haired Women Pick The Best Passwords, Bearded Men the Worst http://ti.me/1fYHlhK  <- this is what I was looking for    
    
    
    Akamai to Buy DDoS Protection firm Prolexic for $370 Million http://bit.ly/1eGYEAl  <- uff Akamai pushes hard    
    
    
    @Napaboy they already offer an anti-DDoS service, but I guess they want to have the client side as well    
    
    
    It seems that Akamai wants to add client side DDoS protection to their existing antiDDoS portfolio    
    
    
    @areino almost all telcos offer that service, but not precisely cheap :)    
    
    
    @krypt3ia ??    
    
    
    @krypt3ia I didn't know about it. You have ruined my life now :p    
    
    
    The Insidiousness of Facebook Messenger's Mobile App Terms of Service http://huff.to/18hez4f  <- better features than a trojan :)    
    
    
    @FraudBlogger AFAIK many EU banks are blocking foreign charges by default in all cards due to the high fraud rates in non EMV countries    
    
    
    Cyber Readiness Index http://bit.ly/1cnHHLw  <- really interesting work by Melissa Hathaway analyzing 35 countries cybersecurity commitment    
    
    
    Perhaps it is a universal truth that the loss of liberty at home is to be charged to provisions against danger,real or pretended,from abroad    
    
    
    Last quote by James Madison, fourth President of the United States (1809–1817)    
    
    
    @ahmad_aabed no idea at all :)    
    
    
    @torremochaj @diegomarino @Aquilino @inakib @jlhortelano homeland security.their product is good and their engineers top-notch    
    
    
    Group-IB assists to suppress the activities of a “Blackhole” exploit-kit author, “Paunch” is arrested http://bit.ly/1hCw4Ew     
    
    
    Governments planning to control security tech exports http://zd.net/18dYJfQ  <- no comments :(    
    
    
    Kudos to @CERT_Polska_en for their superb job tracking and taking down some malware incidents    
    
    
    After playing for some days with SAML IdPs and Service Providers I only can say that it is PITA :)    
    
    
    "SAML is the Windows XP of Identity. No funding. No innovation. People still use it. But it has no future"    
    
    
    "There is no future for SAML. No one is putting money into SAML development. NO ONE is writing new SAML code. SAML is dead.”    
    
    
    @lsaiz I'm not frustrated, but happy :) I don't like SAML at all.there is only one thing that I hate more: a SAML Java implementation :)    
    
    
    Mozilla Revoking Trust in one ANSSI Certificate http://mzl.la/1byJz43  <- well done bit the entire model should be rebuilt    
    
    
    @ssantosv for you and for me and the entire human race :)    
    
    
    Tiny Kentucky Town Agrees to Pay Only Police Officer In Bitcoin http://bit.ly/1jHGlPl     
    
    
    Long day today with mixed feelings. It was great to meet so many friends agains but some mistakes were made    
    
    
    @hectorsm jajaja 100% verdad    
    
    
    @alonsocandado gracias Alonso! :)    
    
    
    @roman_soft @Kachakil xDDDD what happens in Majadahonda, stays in Majadahonda  :P    
    
    
    Internet-wide efforts to fight email phishing are working http://bit.ly/19LMann     
    
    
    "More specifically, the 91.4% of the authenticated non-spam emails sent to Gmail users come from senders that have adopted DKIM or SPF"    
    
    
    Security guru Bruce Schneier to leave employer BT http://bit.ly/19NDInt     
    
    
    The inevitable move - 64-bit ZeuS has come enhanced with Tor http://bit.ly/1k8NZCk     
    
    
    Apple blocks bitcoin payments on secure messaging app Gliph http://bit.ly/1dIVviv     
    
    
    Hmm it seems that I will finally meet @Packetknife soon    
    
    
    @Packetknife it's not the spanish style. It will be more sibylline :P    
    
    
    DGA Changer Malware Able to Modify Domain-Generation Seed on the Fly http://bit.ly/18RCojl  <- cool :)    
    
    
    @trufae I've been using Threema, but it is not open source. Telegraph looks nice    
    
    
    @trufae @jakoubek then I will keep using Threema ;)    
    
    
    @jakoubek @trufae true, but it is a good option nowadays    
    
    
    Impressive. 400 million of monthly active WhatsApp users. http://bit.ly/1fq2jD5     
    
    
    @alyepez congrats! It seems 2014 will be an awesome for the AlienVault's team :)    
    
    
    @0xabad1dea excellent UI? Some of them have fancy images but their UI is horrible    
    
    
    I'm looking for a spare @shmoocon ticket, just in case someone can not make it    
    
    
    Talo + txistorra + sidra = WIN #SantoTomas2013    
    
    
    @mikko well done.    
    
    
    If I were a malicious state sponsored group I'd use UDP and RC6 right now!    
    
    
    Exfiltrate, exfiltrate, exfiltrate!    
    
    
    @matalaz @reversemode que rule    
    
    
    Wow if it's true that @FireEye has acquired @Mandiant it is really a shocking movement    
    
    
    'FireEye now has a $5 billion market capitalization, despite the fact it has yet to turn a profit.'    
    
    
    IMHO @Mandiant acquisition by @FireEye is a really smart one, but let's see how products and services bundle together    
    
    
    A billion bucks. It was the same amount FaceBook offered to the SnapChat guys. :)    
    
    
    “@nicoleperlroth: Um, something amiss at the WSJ copy desk??? "Mandiant, a computer security firm known for fingering Chinese hackers."” LOL    
    
    
    Lyndsey Scott Tells Us What It's Like To Be A Victoria's Secret Model Who Codes In Her Free Time http://read.bi/1ix6Bwz     
    
    
    Oops I didn't notice this one: Bluecoat acquires Norman Shark http://bit.ly/1hYNokG     
    
    
    @lsaiz who cares about that ? :p    
    
    
    @lsaiz mandiant yes, but Fireeye is more global    
    
    
    @avillalbap :)    
    
    
    @alex_lanstein I guess they wanted to say mon Dieu! :P Btw, congrats!    
    
    
    @DennisF which state?    
    
    
    No #BadHypervisor :p    
    
    
    @osxreverser nothing to see here. Please disperse    
    
    
    @mjg59 a wine shower? Here in Spain you have some wine spa treatments :)    
    
    
    Facebook sued for scanning 'private' messages for profit http://bit.ly/19SDxYm     
    
    
    