Browser stats, IE 42%, FF 28%, Chrome 22% - looks like they'll all settle at 30-35% of market share each at Christmas.    
    
    
    According to the ICC test ranking predictor South Africa can become the #1 test nation before England play again. http://bit.ly/5tci57     
    
    
    But the ICC predictor http://icc-cricket.yahoo.net/match_zone/test_predictor.php … - was clearly not tested by someone who uses the tab key    
    
    
    @Andy_Still @intechnica    
    
    
    @andy_still ICC predictor http://bit.ly/5tci57  - was clearly not tested by someone who uses the tab key    
    
    
    Pedantic bug spot #283: on fantasy.premierleague.com if you click on 'i' to view a player, when that player is already  displayed the value    
    
    
    After reading this blog http://bit.ly/q5euTR  my 35 hours positive flex balance this month suddenly seems a bit selfish    
    
    
    Also the quote "If you screw up at your job you can always get another one, but if you screw up your family… (cont) http://deck.ly/~ZQ3fJ     
    
    
    Had a dejavu moment thinking it was Christmas, but Christmas is 14 weeks away - this is puzzling    
    
    
    So drive is out this week: http://www.drive-movie.co.uk/  defo a weekend trip to the cinema.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin Amazing in my opinion. It's slow paced but that's not a bad thing for me. I loved it.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin Amazing in my opinion. It's slow paced but that's not a bad thing for me. I loved it.    
    
    
    Pet hate No: 68. The British class system. No one will tell me what class I am. If I want to be upper, middle or lower I will be. I'm free!    
    
    
    Man, permissions in #umbraco #v5 ROCK! =) #justsayin    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin not yet. Will try and write a blog post over the weekend though =)    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin as promissed http://m4tt.me/vfPuw4  Let me know what you think.    
    
    
    I've signed up to movember and intend to grow a handlebar moustache!  http://mobro.co/amelvin     
    
    
    Rio Ferdinand changes mobile payment 'pain points'?  http://rww.to/tLoAbe  @rioferdy5 - interesting look at evolving mobile payment patterns    
    
    
    Yay, I've passed 3,000 rep on Stackoverflow.  http://bit.ly/rPggw3     
    
    
    Listening to a Stone Roses playlist http://spoti.fi/vOaf11  - takes you back!    
    
    
    IE market share now under 50%, As Android and Safari Mobile have 5% already, IE must be hoping for big gain… (cont) http://deck.ly/~LRuue     
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin as promissed http://m4tt.me/vfPuw4  Let me know what you think.    
    
    
    Is Tower Heist an appropriate film to take my 11 year-old son to tomorrow (as an alternative to his Star Wars / Minecraft obsessions)?    
    
    
    Old school video game deaths - a good use of 2/3 minutes of a Friday afternoon  http://kottke.org/11/11/classic-video-game-deaths …    
    
    
    The shame - only 5/7 on the BBC's computer quiz http://bbc.in/v0LbAJ     
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin I got the same. Amazing Grace and Lettuce caught me out.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin @rsleggett If that quiz has taught me anything its that I need to write a programming language called Lettuce ASAP.    
    
    
    Movember end - will there be a surge in demand for high quality facial emollients tonight? http://bit.ly/uDdkIu  http://yfrog.com/oc9xqomj     
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin @Matttlloyd that would definitely draw the wrong crowd (Sanj)    
    
    
    @rsleggett Ah, its also private - @mrsanj should ask @katiemaymanc for tips on how the twitter works (right account this time)    
    
    
    @antony_melvin @rsleggett You got the wrong one. Tis @mr_sanj    
    
    
    5 big tech surprises of 2011 - http://rww.to/uH5wdv  - but no Twitter #newlook !?    
    
    
    Wow, #dontmesswiththebigman unless you want to be, literally, thrown off a Scottish train - http://youtu.be/eKKADFIEX84     
    
    
    Nice implementation of oEmbed by twitter - http://bit.ly/s0PIFX     
    
    
    Listening to Boo Radleys - "Giant Steps" album on spotify, pure unadulterated genius #beforetheywentcommercial    
    
    
    @rsleggett @building_blocks - You don't have to be cool to be relevant; no reference to Maslow and metamotivation?    
    
    
    I was rather critical of the new BBC homepage, but It's grown on me. Still think its too white though.    
    
    
    @tomhackett @stevesage @raymosley Does anyone remember how the pool went during last night's Salford Odyssey? (@rsleggett)    
    
    
    .NET/Sql developers needed at Intechnica in Manchester (no agencies please) lnkd.in/zVgSEN    
    
    
    I got 95/100 in this html5 kerning game http://type.method.ac  <-- nice designers game if you have 2 minutes spare    
    
    
    Viz @Ed_Miliband 's 'Blackbusters' gaffe at least the #twittergeneration will remember something he did during his time as Labour leader    
    
    
    Good news about the UK IT Curriculum http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/education-16493929 … I changed A-Level college to find one that did proper Computer Science.    
    
    
    Is EC2 a rip-off @intechnica ? http://bit.ly/AkQhH1     
    
    
    So when does sex count as a work related injury? http://bit.ly/tc4Gqe     
    
    
    Very concerning that FaceBook is now selling every mention of phrases (inc. ones in 'private' messages) - what next? http://rww.to/zjOZkT     
    
    
    I quite like the new BBC Sport look - but the 404 page needs work http://yfrog.com/odhlehkj     
    
    
    @rsleggett Pool table sounds good - but why JSP?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin the answer to everything: Tridion    
    
    
    @rsleggett I'm booked in for the MCTS 70-515 exam next week - have you done it?    
    
    
    Interesting call to arms for a real tech startup scene to become established in Manchester http://bit.ly/wk3iD0     
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin the answer to everything: Tridion    
    
    
    @ManUmbMeetup Wish I'd known about this earlier!    
    
    
    Now I now why #umbraco on Azure was failing so oddly yesterday and overnight - http://bit.ly/w2LwDB     
    
    
    Yesterday, February 28th, 2012 at 5:45 PM PST Windows Azure operations became aware of an issue impacting the compute service    
    
    
    February 28th, 2012 at 5:45 PM PST == 1:45 AM on 19 February in Australia, so I guess they called in a leap day bug on Azure first    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin Not guilty. I had no control over the music at that time. It was music I was talking about. Not dropping fart bombs.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin @tomhackett  nah he is off as he has herpes in his eye. It was towey    
    
    
    Chester Road building fire: police refuse to rule out Mario Balotelli - http://bit.ly/yNUkkA     
    
    
    @raymosley Just spoken to red-eye @tomhackett - you've got to wonder what 'exotic' things he may have caught while away    
    
    
    Experts-Exchange has a hyphen in it because otherwise it would be ExpertSexChange.    
    
    
    Just loaded MetroTwit because TweetDeck has been annoying me for ages. Really liking it so far. http://bit.ly/bazdFI     
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin It's only in the Pro version by the looks of things and it's only in beta.    
    
    
    Interesting article demonstrating that poor performance equals lower sales at Walmart http://bit.ly/yc64G9     
    
    
    A new Pegged competition: name the movie and you could win a @moviepeg http://bit.ly/yjcz8D  (via @MoviePeg)    
    
    
    Upcoming BCS events on the use of IT and technology at #mancity & #manutd http://bit.ly/yYeb1s  http://bit.ly/zudfh0     
    
    
    Linked in have bought Rapportive - which is a good gmail add-on (I use it) - but $13m, whoa?  Bubble bubble.    
    
    
    Thoughtworks expanding in Manchester - the decision said to be infuenced by the BBC 's move - http://bit.ly/w88HTb     
    
    
    Definitely getting more stupid as time goes on.    
    
    
    Can't stop thinking that the petrol panic buying will push GDP up slightly and avoid a technical recession being declared #machiavelli    
    
    
    Just seen a newly raised bug that the cursor blink rate in a text box is different in IE and Firefox #wordsfailme    
    
    
    @TomHackett is there an agenda for tonight?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin negative. We'll be heading somewhere local at bout 6. SMS @stevesage for geo-location laterzzz    
    
    
    NIESR has predicted Q1 growth of 0.1% so the UK has narrowly avoided a return to recession - petrol panic buying FTW! http://bit.ly/HpkebL     
    
    
    Video of me in action yesterday: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_PFWiarAfBw … I'm at 14:33, blink and you'll miss it. Thanks to @Antony_Melvin for the footage.    
    
    
    I'm looking for sponsorship for the MS Society in the Manchester 10K in a couple of weeks if anyone has spare cash http://bit.ly/IV7HvC     
    
    
    Can't wait until driving cars is an outdated pastime - http://bbc.in/IUmBsz  - and the road deaths that come with them are all but lost too    
    
    
    Nice to see two nice middle-aged men renewing their vows after a couple of years together - but on a factory floor? #timeshavechanged    
    
    
    Good to see mN is thriving http://bit.ly/Je0vh5  - 90% non-website work shows the first generation digital agencies can compete differently    
    
    
    Good article by Martin Fowler on why ORMs are a necessary evil http://bit.ly/KKuE5f     
    
    
    Is this the greatest tech recruiter around: http://bit.ly/KQaaYS     
    
    
    Facebook trialling 'pay to post'  http://bbc.in/J51Y6u  - not sure why I'd go back TBH    
    
    
    Interesting Google Interview - http://bit.ly/IVUC5Z     
    
    
    Scaling a dev team - stage 2 > 3 is very tricky - http://bit.ly/l42fOd     
    
    
    Clay man finds his new home on my desk http://instagr.am/p/Krlp0crXcp/     
    
    
    Just watched this Labach cover of Sympathy for the Devil - which has a simultaneously disturbing and funny video http://youtu.be/JjPi-Vvz2FA     
    
    
    In the Mcr10K I finished just outside the top 15,000 with a time of 59:21 http://bit.ly/J86FNC-  thanks to sponsors: http://bit.ly/J86JwQ     
    
    
    Facebook shareprice now 12% down in two days - a few billion lost for investors, fragile confidence knocked in the tech sector - #dislike    
    
    
    From http://businessinsider.com  (http://read.bi/LWA3tl ) - just how complicated the social media marketplace now is http://yfrog.com/esu4datj     
    
    
    New @bitly redesign is nice - took me by surprise. Like most redesigns, might take a little getting used to it. :-)    
    
    
    Still the best song about graphic design (I'm not sure how many there are TBH)  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5AxwaszFbDw …    
    
    
    @spikeydave101 How's ATOS going?  Are you up for a bowl of MT this month?    
    
    
    Deleted LinkedIn after password leak (mine was leaked). I don't think it's done anything for me except open me up to recruiter spam. So yay!    
    
    
    I haz all teh social mediaz but ... Facebook - no interest; Pinterest - meh; LinkedIn - spammy; Google+ - meh++; only Twitter abides    
    
    
    Glad I read this post before betting the house on an #Umbraco 5 decision http://our.umbraco.org/forum/core/umbraco-5-general-discussion/32361-Umbraco-5-readyness?p=0#comment119101 …    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin that's bad considering the Umbraco lot have been banging on about how great 5 is    
    
    
    @37signals - Where can I find the Basecamp API key for my account?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin If you're using the new version of Basecamp, we're not using an API key anymore. In Classic, it's on your My Info page.    
    
    
    NIESR says UK GDP up 0.1% http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/120612_151104.pdf … "UK economy has ceased to contract" "expect economic recovery to begin to take hold in 2013"    
    
    
    Just read that there's been an announcement from someone at #cg12 that #Umbraco 5 development has stopped - is this true?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin it’s true. See the the #cg12 tag for link to the Keynote    
    
    
    #Umbraco have a naming convention problem in scrapping 5 - will we see U++  or Umb2014 or 4.10 in a couple of years    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin True. But I think the consequenses would be bigger if they didn’t kill it because of the perfomance issues    
    
    
    New job, new fantasy Football League - forgotten pin - tried to recover ... why did Sky want to record my mothers maiden name?    
    
    
    Mr Roy and his secret tortoise ancestry    
    
    
    Nice one @SiKenyon - does shocking tweet?    
    
    
    Good to catch up with @Antony_Melvin for Nandos at lunch. Interesting times lie ahead.    
    
    
    @SoerenS Does ucommerce support http://www.realexpayments.co.uk/  as a payment provider? #umbraco    
    
    
    @SiKenyon @Antony_Melvin Yes, shall we say Tuesday, in Spinningfields?    
    
    
    @dbamber Wednesday OK?    
    
    
    Recruiting developers - are technical interviews working? -  http://techcrunch.com/2011/05/07/why-the-new-guy-cant-code/ …    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin interesting read. But the person administering the test has to be competent, or it's all a big fat waste of time...    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin interesting read. But the person administering the test has to be competent, or it's all a big fat waste of time...    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin you're correct didn't mean it to sound like I was dismissing those elements Mad skillz dont necessarily make someone suitable    
    
    
    #umbraco 6-8 week contract development role in central Manchester - working on a household name website rewrite? DM me if interested.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin yes, defo    
    
    
    @danielbowden @SteveSage mentioned that you might be up for some #umbraco contract work in Manchester?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin Aww, what a nice chap is that @SteveSage, terrible dancer though. Unfortunately I'm not available right now. Sorry.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin Think that was after me. I think 2010 was the end of my stint there.  Is Sanj still there?    
    
    
    Just been to Nandos and queued behind @RioFerdy5 - nice to see footballers that are not afraid to mix    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin You shoulda jumped ahead of him in the queue to see he woulda thrown himself to the floor holding his face.    
    
    
    Chris Moyles leaving the R1 Breakfast Show - hope they take a chance on a 20yo preferably without friends #MoylesBlackburnMayoReadEdmonds    
    
    
    One of the lads I play football with on Monday has the following job title: Dreaming Room Facilitator (Michael E Gerber Certified)  ?!?    
    
    
    It’s time to stop blaming Internet Explorer http://www.nczonline.net/blog/2012/07/11/its-time-to-stop-blaming-internet-explorer/ … <-- headline says it all    
    
    
    Just taken responsibility for 2 #umbraco sites that were written in 4.7.1 with no packages and no umbraco:macros - do I win £5?    
    
    
    http://java.dzone.com/articles/most-pressed-keys-various … <-- 'e' the most common English letter is the most pressed keyboard key - the things you learn!    
    
    
    Should keys like ( ) < > : ! [ ] become non-shifted characters for programmers given how often they're needed?    
    
    
    Heard on xfm that there is a tram broken down at Stretford - metrolink site isn't very helpful though #nosurprises pic.twitter.com/4ZuLdfZc    
    
    
    Clicked through to see the detail on today's disruptions, you have to wonder if this page shouldn't just be the hompage pic.twitter.com/OG384iHk    
    
    
    Nice chatting to some #umbraco people like @CGaskell @suedeapple and guys from @blueprintweb last night at @ManUmbMeetup    
    
    
    Lumme missed @jamessimm off my roundup of #umbraco types (how do you pronounce umbracians?)    
    
    
    Been forced into Hatties on Deansgate to ease my way into the morning    
    
    
    You'll be pleased to know this morning in the Pyrenees is grey & misty like Manchester. Will be glad of it when I'm climbing Luz Ardiden.    
    
    
    You'll be pleased to know this morning in the Pyrenees is grey & misty like Manchester. Will be glad of it when I'm climbing Luz Ardiden.    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin are you using Progressive for your contract role?    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin are you using Progressive for your contract role?    
    
    
    SA batters grinding runs could cost them time to win; 600 all out in 150 overs would have been better than 637/2 in 189 overs #bbccricket    
    
    
    Impressive work in fixing the google map datatype by #umbraco community - it broke just in time for a demo I was trying yesterday! #typical    
    
    
    Impressive work in fixing the google map datatype by #umbraco community - it broke just in time for a demo I was trying yesterday! #typical    
    
    
    Impressive work in fixing the google map datatype by #umbraco community - it broke just in time for a demo I was trying yesterday! #typical    
    
    
    Impressive work in fixing the google map datatype by #umbraco community - it broke just in time for a demo I was trying yesterday! #typical    
    
    
    Impressive work in fixing the google map datatype by #umbraco community - it broke just in time for a demo I was trying yesterday! #typical    
    
    
    The more I think of the problems in the economy the more I'm convinced that appointing Ossie Osbourne as Chancellor was a mistake    
    
    
    He should have stuck with the Black Sabbath stuff    
    
    
    @SiKenyon @SteveHocking - lunch tomorrow?    
    
    
    @SiKenyon @SteveHocking - lunch tomorrow?    
    
    
    Nice article on why many programmers doubt themselves - and why they shouldn't http://simpleprogrammer.com/2012/08/12/the-myth-of-the-super-programmer/ …    
    
    
    I see that IE6 has dipped below 1% usage in the UK - http://www.ie6countdown.com/  - its already in the unsupported list in my functional specs!    
    
    
    I see that IE6 has dipped below 1% usage in the UK - http://www.ie6countdown.com/  - its already in the unsupported list in my functional specs!    
    
    
    @rsleggett, have you ever looked at @klout ? http://klout.com/rsleggett?n=tw&v=invite …    
    
    
    My new fave country name is "Co-operative Republic of Guyana", do i get @TheCooperative divis for all purchases there? http://www.pcgn.org.uk/Country_names.htm …    
    
    
    “@deanwho: @mrgarethbrooks Xfm has crashed, the world is ending."

Should be back on now...    
    
    
    How will Mcr Metrolink write a Win8 app announcing tram delays if they can't use the word 'metro'? http://arstechnica.com/information-technology/2012/08/windows-8-store-will-reject-all-apps-with-word-metro-in-title/ …    
    
    
    I just earned the 'I Believe in IPA!' badge on @untappd! http://untp.it/NsoIS1  #ibelieveinIPA    
    
    
    Just started using http://zapier.com/  to push Jira tasks onto Basecamp as messages - must say, was very impressed with the integration    
    
    
    Just saw a job ad of StackOverflow for "Coder (C#, web stuff, agile, foosball & Mexican food)" - is the free food an indication of the pay?    
    
    
    I love twitter, but if Twitter continues to crack down on developers then where will the innovation come from? Not twitter thats for sure.    
    
    
    I liked this approach to c# caching http://www.dotnetguy.co.uk/post/2010/03/29/c-httpruntime-simple-cache/ … - the simplicity appeals!    
    
    
    Think I just broke the record for the largest number of incorrect username/password attempts    
    
    
    Starting to think that do-not-track will be strangled at birth by the money men http://www.itwriting.com/blog/6519-adobes-roy-fielding-patches-apache-to-ignore-ie10-do-not-track-privacy-request.html …    
    
    
    #Umbraco 4.9 - editor focused changes look good http://umbraco.com/follow-us/blog-archive/2012/9/7/introducing-umbraco-49-party-like-it%E2%80%99s-2004-just-bigger!.aspx … - but after the #5 debacle, I have #umbracoupgradeanxiety    
    
    
    An oldie but a goodie - app_offline.htm still works after all these years - http://weblogs.asp.net/scottgu/archive/2005/10/06/426755.aspx …    
    
    
    Max suicide risk now 35-44 yo, self harm/mental health issues - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-19523881 … - #what20yearsinITdoestoyou    
    
    
    RT @mrgarethbrooks: Shagging in the Athletes Village? #London2012 #shagging
Did you see TwentyTwelve?  http://www.bbc.co.uk/comedy/clips/p00r7fxp/twenty_twelve_sexual_health_campaign_featuring_mini_steppah/ …    
    
    
    RT @mrgarethbrooks: Shagging in the Athletes Village? #London2012 #shagging
Did you see TwentyTwelve?  http://www.bbc.co.uk/comedy/clips/p00r7fxp/twenty_twelve_sexual_health_campaign_featuring_mini_steppah/ …    
    
    
    That's the last time I nip for a quick drink with @SiKenyon and JonMurray before an #umbraco meetup that I miserably failed to go to    
    
    
    #spoty has to be a shootout between Wiggins, Mo Farah and Murray - despite the massive Olympics coverage, only Mo stands a chance    
    
    
    That's the last time I nip for a quick drink with @SiKenyon and JonMurray before an #umbraco meetup that I miserably failed to go to    
    
    
    @darrenferguson thanks for the level two course - very useful!    
    
    
    @darrenferguson thanks for the level two #umbraco course - very useful!    
    
    
    Have passed #umbraco level 2 exam, phew - thanks for a great course lead by @darrenferguson - with @azamitch @suedeapple @andrewjknox etc    
    
    
    Is this even legal?  Orf with their heads!  https://fbcdn-sphotos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash4/246423_454468867926745_45378697_n.jpg …    
    
    
    @rsleggett Perhaps the BBS article followed this one on RWW http://www.readwriteweb.com/enterprise/2012/09/readwriteweb-technology-deathwatch-qr-codes.php …    
    
    
    @Queen_UK Like the new coin design  https://fbcdn-sphotos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-ash4/246423_454468867926745_45378697_n.jpg …    
    
    
    Gartner analysis of paid-for CMS (http://www.sdl.com/campaign/wcm/gartner-2012.html …) suggests that sitecore/SDL Tridion are good choices pic.twitter.com/QWFUDaGd    
    
    
    Review of a truly funny radio show - http://www.thepoke.co.uk/wp-content/uploads/2012/09/Hwdlz.jpeg …    
    
    
    Its hard enough to run a half marathon (I'm guessing for obvious reasons) - but to juggle a ball for 5 hours is amazing http://www.harrowtimes.co.uk/news/localnews/9912112.Freestyler__chuffed__with_20km_keepy_uppy_world_record_attempt/?ref=mmsp …    
    
    
    Good work in raising £400 for Scope @stevesage and running the Great North Run!    
    
    
    Are the @DarwinAwards still going - this tragic story seems eligible?  http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/09/13/ervin-mckinness-driving-drunk-tweet-yolo-dies-car-crash-dui-_n_1880348.html …    
    
    
    Google app discontinue support for IE8 - http://googleappsupdates.blogspot.ca/2012/09/supporting-modern-browsers-internet.html … - I know chrome makes them biased, but this still seems too early    
    
    
    Good work in raising £400 for Scope @stevesage and running the Great North Run!    
    
    
    Kudos to the entrepreneurs who benefit from reduced regulation and red tape in the food industry - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-19622903 … #RatOnToast    
    
    
    Excellent short article on why good coders are often poor employees to have to  manage http://mikecr.it/ramblings/coding-skill-vs-employee-skill … - I'm naming no names!    
    
    
    Excellent short article on why good coders are often poor employees to have to  manage http://mikecr.it/ramblings/coding-skill-vs-employee-skill … - I'm naming no names!    
    
    
    @myleshocking Did you get a steer on tracking app downloads?    
    
    
    I swear The XX are a ploy to sell Boss RV-3s to emaciated art students.    
    
    
    Good work in raising £400 for Scope @stevesage and running the Great North Run!    
    
    
    Anyone use a good site checking tool - for verifying images have alts, pages titles/metadata etc; is WebCeo (http://www.webceo.com ) overkill?    
    
    
    Good work in raising £400 for Scope @stevesage and running the Great North Run!    
    
    
    @sqf_illingworh --> RT @MVFCLR22 Would I be able to become a Newcastle reporter for you guys?    
    
    
    @stevesage My mistake, the search is working on the sourcemotion staging version of pr - but broken on the pr dotnet site    
    
    
    @stevesage This looks like a good website test of good search engine practice  http://yast.n3o.co.uk/     
    
    
    I've always really enjoyed my iPhones, but Apple's walled garden is too high now - charger, cables, maps, app store #AppleThinkDifficult    
    
    
    Oh the genius of the angry local newspaper column http://apiln.blogspot.co.uk/  <-- the fifty shades of grey photographer is talented!    
    
    
    @andrewdoran how's it all going - still in the Northern Quarter?    
    
    
    Should an older man be stripping off for a local newspaper? http://apiln.blogspot.co.uk/2012/09/half-naked-mobility-scooter-theft-anger.html …    
    
    
    @andrewdoran how's it all going - still in the Northern Quarter?    
    
    
    Integrate Basecamp and Jira?  http://stackoverflow.com/questions/4254991/integrating-basecamp-with-jira/12175797#12175797 … - I've started using #zapier and that works well.    
    
    
    How to make progress bars appear quicker to users  http://uxmovement.com/buttons/how-to-make-progress-bars-feel-faster-to-users/ …    
    
    
    England 0/1 after one over against Afghanistan - oh dear.    
    
    
    Heh, cool. When did codeproject go all metro :) http://m4tt.me/PPJnQo     
    
    
    Good article on why Apple Maps failed and how to fix http://blog.telemapics.com/?p=399  . Have testers look at maps, before customers?    
    
    
    I agree with 16 of these 20 supposedly 'controversial' programming opinions: http://programmers.blogoverflow.com/2012/08/20-controversial-programming-opinions/ …    
    
    
    Anyone use a good site checking tool - for verifying images have alts, pages titles/metadata etc; is WebCeo (http://www.webceo.com ) overkill?    
    
    
    Hope the NIESR are right and the economy is finally starting to grow again http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/070912_121136.pdf …    
    
    
    I've just got to 4000 reputation on Stack Overflow http://stackoverflow.com/users/261798/amelvin … - yay me    
    
    
    Nu MySpace does look like it was 'influenced' by Pinterest - but does look intriguing http://www.digitalspy.co.uk/tech/news/a408031/myspace-shows-off-new-look-watch-video.html …    
    
    
    I've just got to 4000 reputation on Stack Overflow http://stackoverflow.com/users/261798/amelvin … - yay me    
    
    
    This is an exciting street view - I know its raining but ... https://maps.google.com/maps?q=heron+island+resort&hl=en&ll=-23.442896,151.906584&spn=0.008357,0.016512&sll=-23.442794,151.915555&layer=c&cid=17997865933213515154&panoid=CWskcsTEZBNXaD8gG-zATA&cbp=13,13.3,,0,-4.97&gl=us&hq=heron+island+resort&t=m&z=17&cbll=-23.442896,151.906584 …    
    
    
    Best Google Street View ever - I can hear Moses frantically hammering away at his boat from here ... https://maps.google.com/maps?q=heron+island+resort&hl=en&ll=-23.442896,151.906584&spn=0.008357,0.016512&sll=-23.442794,151.915555&layer=c&cid=17997865933213515154&panoid=CWskcsTEZBNXaD8gG-zATA&cbp=13,13.3,,0,-4.97&gl=us&hq=heron+island+resort&t=m&z=17&cbll=-23.442896,151.906584 …    
    
    
    @SteveHocking @Antony_Melvin Check this out. http://www.kernelmag.com/topic/the-kernel-recruitment-report/ … Pretty damning about recruiters in general.    
    
    
    Don't put the following search into Google: "what is a c# string"    
    
    
    Free for lunch @SteveHocking @SiKenyon ?    
    
    
    Free for lunch @SteveHocking @SiKenyon ?    
    
    
    @pimoroni How do I buy that raspberry pi case?    
    
    
    Free for lunch @SteveHocking @SiKenyon ?    
    
    
    Free for lunch @SteveHocking @SiKenyon ?    
    
    
    Townshend Speaks Out On Child Porn Arrest: The Who's Pete Townshend has spoken out about his attempt to expose t... http://bit.ly/PcBp38     
    
    
    Free for lunch @SteveHocking @SiKenyon ?    
    
    
    Do Americans really not use the word 'fortnight' and are they really moving towards dd/mm/yyyy ? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-19670686 …    
    
    
    #ff Mcr tech types @myleshocking @SiKenyon @SteveHocking @stevesage    
    
    
    Got a raspberry pi delivered at the weekend - my son wants a career in design or programming - nice that it worked so well from boot    
    
    
    But which language to set my son off on - python seems so 2010, and not java, C seems too much for a 12 year old. I think html/javascript.    
    
    
    Amazing http://theamazingios6maps.tumblr.com/post/32188676002/las-vegas-is-melting …    
    
    
    BCC optimistically report 0.5% Q3 growth in UK http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-19795642 … , NIESR have also reported growth in July & Aug - is recession over?    
    
    
    Seems sensible to charge people extra if they leave 'portfolio' houses empty for 2+yrs  http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-19790896 … - should extend to commercial    
    
    
    Fantastic article on the making of the #raspberrypi http://www.wired.com/opinion/2012/09/raspberry-pi-insider-exclusive-sellout-to-sell-out/ …    
    
    
    A bit of z-index fail for the BBC's new survey request at http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/cricket/ … pic.twitter.com/AUiwMvn5    
    
    
    Good article on how to make software once you are experienced enough to make software http://gorban.org/post/32873465932/software-architecture-cheat-sheet …    
    
    
    Expect soon to have a request to build a website that looks good on a clay tablet or as a tattoo on an elephant's arse http://www.codeproject.com/Lounge.aspx?msg=4388079#xx4388079xx …    
    
    
    Which circle of hell is reserved for people who auto-DM you after you follow them and include an advert for a website in the message?    
    
    
    Zuckerberg created 500 million fakebook accounts  http://www.thepoke.co.uk/2012/10/05/mark-zuckerberg-created-over-500-million-fake-facebook-accounts/ …  The Poke > Facebook!    
    
    
    This liquid nitrogen story / stomach removal story sounds awful - hope she recovers http://www.bbc.co.uk/newsbeat/19866191 … #NHS4Ever    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/i/10ddY  time for some cheeky sunbathing in my Manchester suntrap... in October!!    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/i/10ddY  time for some cheeky sunbathing in my Manchester suntrap... in October!!    
    
    
    @SiKenyon I would recommend ublogsy for #umbraco - very flexible, plays nicely with CMSImport (if you need to import old content)    
    
    
    @SiKenyon Everything going well at @computerlovers    
    
    
    @SiKenyon I got a nudge from Mark Sharp last week - unfortunately not currently available - thanks for the thought!    
    
    
    That's fun - search on google for the word 'askew' - really its funny    
    
    
    100 followers - a little embarrassing esp after watching Malcolm Tucker saying that tweeting to 511 followers is like whispering to a tramp    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/i/10ddY  time for some cheeky sunbathing in my Manchester suntrap... in October!!    
    
    
    After reading this I'm thinking of going home without doing unpaid overtime tonight  http://thecodist.com/article/yes_i_still_want_to_be_doing_this_at_56 …    
    
    
    Can't believe that a cannabis plant could grow to this size without being raided by local teens #ApatheticYouth http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-beds-bucks-herts-19868327 …    
    
    
    File under #DarwinAwards - US man dies after cockroach eating competition - hoped to win the star prize of a python http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-19879379 …    
    
    
    NIESR forecast UK came out of recession in Q3 2012 http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/091012_142954.pdf … +0.8% Q3 growth aided by special factors (+0.2/0.3% underlying)    
    
    
    NIESR growth forecast states that Q3 2012 showed the strongest quarterly UK growth since just after the last election http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/091012_142954.pdf …    
    
    
    When it comes to the anal kingdom picture - its the kids I feel sorry for http://www.thepoke.co.uk/wp-content/gallery/the-year-in-pictures_1/anal-kingdom.jpg …    
    
    
    Humour on the London Underground - it won't catch on... http://imgur.com/a/lUWTG     
    
    
    @antony_melvin What's your skype name? Mine is si.keny0n    
    
    
    Still makes me laugh http://www.guardian.co.uk/media/2008/jul/23/mediamonkey …    
    
    
    How tou pay a £200 bill without money (or at least avoid paying it) ... pure genius ... http://www.27bslash6.com/overdue.html     
    
    
    If you don't know what to do with your @raspberrypi try the great @TheMagP1 magazine - and copy programs from the mag #BackToTheFuture    
    
    
    @Xfm What about when New Order rewrote Blue Monday for a Sunkist advert - http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tta6bAeN_Tk …    
    
    
    I like Starbucks coffee and I like Costa Coffee - but if Starbucks is going to cost me by avoiding UK Corp Tax then I'll go to Costa    
    
    
    "The Guardian will stop printing in a few years" http://www.telegraph.co.uk/finance/newsbysector/mediatechnologyandtelecoms/media/9614953/Guardian-seriously-discussing-end-to-print-edition.html … - sad #signofthetimes    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong may or may not have cheated - but his cancer survivors legacy is safe, I'll always wear a #livestrong band    
    
    
    A twitter list of past and present mN people https://twitter.com/leekelleher/mn     
    
    
    Same judge who gave 6 months for disrupting boat race, gave 12 weeks to a titled lady convicted of £90k benefit fraud http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-1324957/Widow-helped-swindle-90-000-taxpayers-cash-housing-benefit-fraud-jailed-12-weeks.html …    
    
    
    Man hires woman to slap him whenever he looks at Facebook during the day - http://www.telegraph.co.uk/technology/facebook/9616910/Man-slapped-when-he-looks-at-Facebook-to-increase-productivity.html … - surely leaving FB is cheaper/better    
    
    
    I think tesco are doing some round-the-back testing http://www.tesco.com/direct/search-results/results.page?catId=4294967294&searchquery=silentnight+reno&SrchId=4294967294&_requestid=858522 … pic.twitter.com/2PG522di    
    
    
    The tesco direct javascript popup only appears in IE9 http://www.tesco.com/direct/search-results/results.page?catId=4294967294&searchquery=silentnight+reno&SrchId=4294967294&_requestid=858522 …    
    
    
    New #umbraco website live at http://www.silentnight.co.uk     
    
    
    New #umbraco website live at http://www.silentnight.co.uk     
    
    
    @silentnightbeds you can see your latest tweets etc on  http://www.silentnight.co.uk/social-media/     
    
    
    New #umbraco website live at http://www.silentnight.co.uk     
    
    
    @Wolfbyte @HackManchester Surely there are 10 type of error; those caused by other devs code and those caused by too little caffeine?    
    
    
    Has the SNP already won the debate on Scotland if the rest of the UK is excluded from the debate and the vote?    
    
    
    Think I might back this the @pimoroni case was excellent    
    
    
    Think I might back http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/pimoroni/picade-the-arcade-cabinet-kit-for-your-raspberry-p … the @pimoroni case was excellent    
    
    
    New #umbraco website live at http://www.silentnight.co.uk     
    
    
    The #AskStevieG shambles today is a great example of how horribly naive some social media 'experts' must be    
    
    
    @mrgarethbrooks - have a look at the #AskStevieG stuff if you want to get a jump on just about every amusing drive time radio show    
    
    
    #AskStevieG in at number one with a bullet pic.twitter.com/MGuhYCSR    
    
    
    … and then emails me to ask have I got everything… Grrr!    
    
    
    In case anyone's bothered all Christmas advertising is fine after bonfire night - but not before.    
    
    
    If UK politicians can't get tax from Amazon, Starbucks, Google etc - can we get some new ones that can? http://www.guardian.co.uk/business/2012/nov/12/amazon-google-starbucks-diverting-uk-profits …    
    
    
    Always take care where you steal 'inspiration' from - Apple pay out £14m for copying the Swiss Railways clock design http://www.theaustralian.com.au/news/breaking-news/apple-pays-swiss-rail-a202m-over-clock/story-fn3dxix6-1226514435784 …    
    
    
    @rsleggett I think your last attempt at movember made you look like a 1970s Yorkshire police constable - is that the look you're rocking?    
    
    
    Someone just tweeted a great link about how to stop procrastinating, I will definitely read it tomorrow - if I'm not busy    
    
    
    Someone just tweeted a great link about how to stop procrastinating, I will definitely read it tomorrow - if I'm not busy    
    
    
    @myleshocking Was the mobile app you were demonstrating the fantastic #Olympic one - #AllBetsAreOff #YoureInLondonNowLad    
    
    
    @SteveHocking @SiKenyon - do you want to do lunch today?    
    
    
    @SteveHocking @SiKenyon - do you want to do lunch today?    
    
    
    @jgreghall Yes but I need your FB email address    
    
    
    Good lunch with @SiKenyon  and @SteveHocking - not at AlmostFamous though!  Are people from Code going to http://hbfsmanchester.eventbrite.com/?ebtv=C  ?    
    
    
    Good lunch with @SiKenyon  and @SteveHocking - not at AlmostFamous though!  Are people from Code going to http://hbfsmanchester.eventbrite.com/?ebtv=C  ?    
    
    
    Is there a reference doc with #umbraco reserved node ids?  eg content recycle bin -20, media recycle bin -21 and so on    
    
    
    The Christmas Market in Manchester appears to be pretty much the same as last year - just not as full #DontDrinkOnMondayLunch    
    
    
    My wife and I had great fun with on Sunday with my 10-y-o niece calling a certain band 'one dimension' & 'no direction' #LongWinterNights    
    
    
    Upgraded from Win XP to Win 8 at the weekend - I've always liked MS products but it is the worst MS OS in yrs, 7 > XP > Vista > 8 > 2K    
    
    
    Twitter, send me your very worst emo lyrics. 

Thanks in advance.    
    
    
    Upgraded from Win XP to Win 8 at the weekend - I've always liked MS products but it is the worst MS OS in yrs, 7 > XP > Vista > 8 > 2K    
    
    
    Booked Mused ticked on the @gigsandtours website this morning - the site worked really well #SatisfiedCustomer    
    
    
    ...go! Question 1: Why do some lions climb trees? #QIXXL    
    
    
        
    
    
    @BTCare should BT take people's money if they have such rubbish internet security? http://www.theverge.com/2012/11/27/3696466/bt-website-insecure-premium-services-order-fraud-bt-vision … #FixItFixItFixIt    
    
    
    If min unit prices help pubs then I'm all for it, reduce pub taxes and increase supermarket drink taxes to compensate #WeLose12PubsAWeek    
    
    
    #BBC Could buoyant buildings beat flooding? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-20502736 …  Yes, they're called boats.    
    
    
    A brilliant 4 minute guide to writing a massive music hit - astounding https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=oOlDewpCfZQ# … (it's more than 4 minutes but ...)    
    
    
    The results were disappointing, the love is quite limited and highly conditional, and big brother is grumpier than ever @Antony_Melvin    
    
    
    The results were disappointing, the love is quite limited and highly conditional, and big brother is grumpier than ever @Antony_Melvin    
    
    
    More rum porter with the like of @SteveHocking and @SiKenyon ... *hic*    
    
    
    My mac arrives next week #joinedthecoolclub    
    
    
    My mac arrives next week #joinedthecoolclub    
    
    
    They fuck you up, your mum and dad. They may not mean to, but they do. They fill u with the faults they had & add some extra, just for you.    
    
    
    But they were fucked up in their turn By fools in old-style hats and coats, Who half the time were soppy-stern & hf at 1 another's throats.    
    
    
    Man hands on misery to man.
  It deepens like a coastal shelf.
Get out as early as you can,
  And don't have any kids yourself.    
    
    
    Philip Larkin - genius! Was reminded of him after reading about Wiggo's childhood    
    
    
    @XFM if you're not mentioning the royal pregnancy - that should also include not saying 'we're not talking about the royal pregnancy'    
    
    
    If this service comes as standard GoDaddy looks like a good option for a virtual datacenter http://www.godaddyguides.com/2011/11/01/what-is-go-daddys-virtual-datacenter/ …    
    
    
    If this service comes as standard GoDaddy looks like a good option for a virtual datacenter http://www.godaddyguides.com/2011/11/01/what-is-go-daddys-virtual-datacenter/ …    
    
    
    In 2010 austerity was planned to last for five years, in 2012 its planned to last for another six - I've spotted a pattern and its not good    
    
    
    Another £100m lost on The Daily - Does NewsCorp understand these new fangled technologies and what people will pay?  http://readwrite.com/2012/12/03/the-daily-drops-dead-what-this-means-for-ipad-publishing …    
    
    
    The #GeorgeOfThrones meme is going well - Joffrey's personality seems apt, but is GO destined to be shortlived king/PM?    
    
    
    Ever felt that too many tasks at work rely on you?  Good article on how to de-clutter your career http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2012/08/the_disciplined_pursuit_of_less.html …    
    
    
    NIESR today reported UK growth was 0.1% in both Oct and Nov http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/071212_114747.pdf … #tripledip if Dec disapoints? #WhenWillItGetBetter?    
    
    
    @xfm I always liked spiderman as a child - but the spiderman films are a bit childish    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin A group of hypothetical devs set up a hypothetical agency/dev shop, who's the customer?    
    
    
    Only 45% of Londoners are now white British http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-20677515 … - Britain has changed rapidly in the new century    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin A group of hypothetical devs set up a hypothetical agency/dev shop, who's the customer?    
    
    
    Do any security bills ever stick to just stopping the 'evil' in society, too much monitoring already IMHO http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-20668953 …    
    
    
    LinkedIn tip - make minor adjustments to your profile every couple of months to keep your director from forgetting you    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin A group of hypothetical devs set up a hypothetical agency/dev shop, who's the customer?    
    
    
    Good @Umbraco meetup in Mcr, but a drink too many in the Brit!  @CGaskell @blueprintweb @andrewjknox @PeteDuncanson @SiKenyon - & 25 others!    
    
    
    After @CGaskell going through @getcassette last night - I think it needs to be one of many new TODOs    
    
    
    Good @Umbraco meetup in Mcr, but a drink too many in the Brit!  @CGaskell @blueprintweb @andrewjknox @PeteDuncanson @SiKenyon - & 25 others!    
    
    
    Thankfully the angled insanity has gone from the @umbraco tips http://24days.in/umbraco/2012/remember-the-editors/ …    
    
    
    @peteduncanson good @umbraco advice in http://24days.in/umbraco/2012/optimise-for-speed/ … - glad you got them to drop that nasty slanty design    
    
    
    #3 on the BBC's most popular news list 'unnamed page' has made me feel a lot better about my numerous failings today pic.twitter.com/xfSkDN3o    
    
    
    Instagram is not going to sell your photos http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-20777616 … - but truth is Facebook has sold its right to be trusted as a default    
    
    
    A great, grown up post on how to accept that your great software will eventually be chip paper at best http://sstephenson.us/posts/you-are-not-your-code …    
    
    
    #3 on the BBC's most popular news list 'unnamed page' has made me feel a lot better about my numerous failings today pic.twitter.com/xfSkDN3o    
    
    
    I'm really struggling to get a project finished this week - to be perfectly honest the Mayan Apocalypse on Friday could be a life saver    
    
    
    @TheProphetBlog Not a great day for musical prophets    
    
    
    @peteduncanson @blueprintweb @andrewjknox That Azure Leap Day bug I mentioned at the @umbraco meetup http://blogs.msdn.com/b/windowsazure/archive/2012/03/09/summary-of-windows-azure-service-disruption-on-feb-29th-2012.aspx …    
    
    
    I was developing my first and only (to date) @umbraco website on Azure when that Leap Day bug struck - typical!    
    
    
    Pocket change for the Sheikh, get him signed. 

#mcfc pic.twitter.com/h4NRDgNR    
    
    
    Bit busy today, so if the world does end I might not be monitoring twitter - any tips for spotting the onset of #EndOfTheWorld ?    
    
    
    Started Breaking bad from series 1 again last night. Looking forward to it all over again with @Miss_SVLH    
    
    
    One last beer and sausage trip to the markets tomorrow @SiKenyon and @Antony_Melvin ?    
    
    
    One last beer and sausage trip to the markets tomorrow @SiKenyon and @Antony_Melvin ?    
    
    
    Merry Christmas, everybody.    
    
    
    The BBC's CMS has messed up again & they've published an old story as 'latest' this time repeating 2011's 'Balotelli given another chance'    
    
    
    This #FiscalCliff sounds even grimmer than a panto featuring a festive Cliff Richard    
    
    
    Rodgers on Suarez - 'No 10', 'Floating 9', 'Reverse Winger' #ClicheBingo http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/football/20909538 …    
    
    
    @CGaskell still up for some kebab action at lunchtime? :)    
    
    
    A bit of wispy snow in the air in Manchester - but nothing much really. #uksnow    
    
    
    Following the @MartinSLewis charity offer to a landmark follower, I'm happy to offer £100 to the charity of my 1,000,000th follower    
    
    
    Liked this one http://blog.assembla.com/assemblablog/tabid/12618/bid/87899/Seven-Things-I-Hate-About-Agile.aspx … - seven things to hate about agile    
    
    
    Dreams sale now on! http://uk.news.yahoo.com/silentnight-owner-awakens-interest-dreams-155736166--finance.html … Sky News reporting "any buyer...is likely to put [Dreams] through a form of bankruptcy" #TripleDip    
    
    
    New reclaim campaign. Have u got/had a bank acc which charges a mnthly fee? If it wasn't suitable, u may be owed £100s: http://bit.ly/144AOJV     
    
    
    Good points about entry level IT recruitment http://blog.trustiv.co.uk/2013/01/offshoring-fuelling-it-skills-crisis …    
    
    
    Has social media slashed vandalism rates? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-21041160 … - interesting, given the contradiction of social media being blamed for riots    
    
    
    @CGaskell Did you demonstrate using PreInit to switch master pages at the last #umbraco mcr meetup to build a responsive design for Betta?    
    
    
    @CGaskell Did you demonstrate using PreInit to switch master pages at the last #umbraco mcr meetup to build a responsive design for Betta?    
    
    
    Sheesh the economy has shrunk for the 4th quarter in the last 5 - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-21193525 … #TripleDip - forget EU - obsess about growth not EU    
    
    
    @XFM Free NELSON Mandela - Special AKA?    
    
    
    @umbraco mysql != umbraco - I guess its chicken & egg though, if the win platform installer encouraged mysql installs it would be different    
    
    
    @umbraco Interesting that the most popular country to respond to the poll is the UK - covering 1/3 of responses so far    
    
    
    @umbraco Interesting that the most popular country to respond to the poll is the UK - covering 1/3 of responses so far    
    
    
    Will houses in Didsbury rattle when the HS2 trains flies past?  
https://www.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/69037/hs2-msg-wm0-zz-dr-rt-40014.pdf …    
    
    
    @CGaskell Let me know when I can pick your brains for 5 minutes on skype    
    
    
    @myleshocking Are you interested in http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Web-Performance-Group/events/98705442/ … - or are you still schlepping across London every day?    
    
    
    @mikemoorhouse about your email, are you on skype?    
    
    
    Trying to edit a 2000 line css file in Visual Studio and failing miserably.    
    
    
    Trying to edit a 2000 line css file in Visual Studio and failing miserably.    
    
    
    I've now heard the expression 'showrooming' twice in a week - its clearly hitting the mainstream    
    
    
    Will houses in Didsbury rattle when the HS2 trains flies past?  
https://www.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/69037/hs2-msg-wm0-zz-dr-rt-40014.pdf …    
    
    
    Nice list of software dev security checks - basically always test and mistrust external inputs (forms fields, APIs) http://images.infoworld.com/d/application-development/safeguard-your-code-17-security-tips-developers-211339 …    
    
    
    Just started my first build of an #umbraco6 website - pulled through nuget, a couple of odd installer errors but otherwise OK    
    
    
    Delayed a few weeks after completion by Barclaycard admin but http://www.pocketspringbed.co.uk  is live and uses #ucommerce and #umbraco #golive    
    
    
    OH: "the beauty of Bury is that nobody eats vegetables"    
    
    
    I have only run 18km in 2013 ( http://app.strava.com/athletes/436311  ) - if I'm not going to wobble round the Mcr 10K I need to get moving (literally).    
    
    
    Going for a run after work tonight, then i'll stuff my face with pancakes #gluttony    
    
    
    So Republic is reported to be the next High Street casualty http://www.thebusinessdesk.com/yorkshire/news/430850-republic-likely-to-be-latest-high-street-victim.html?news_section=253059# … - will we avoid #TripleDip ? - answers on a postcard    
    
    
    NIESR reckons economic growth in Nov - Jan was 0.0% (http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/070213_151616.pdf …) - which is an improvement on -0.3%! Does it mean #NoTripleDip ?    
    
    
    Apple iWatch will cost £479 + contract (or £429 if you only want to tell the time when using WiFi) - deffo won't be a flash watch #iGuess    
    
    
    @seetal_j Like the new(ish) @intechnica website http://www.intechnica.co.uk/  - (congrats only a couple of months late) @umbraco    
    
    
    Sadly after 13yrs at @FromPaperchase in Mcr my wife was made redundant (MailOrder moved to Ldn), she was one of the original art floor staff    
    
    
    Badly after 13yrs at @FromPaperchase my wife's new company has had no reply to two reference requests. Paperchase: lazy or incompetent?    
    
    
    @SteveHocking Looking at your LinkedIn advert - change of heart?    
    
    
    Bought webceo for $499 KB costs $10 pcm extra; website - 'optional, needed for accuracy' - but w/o KB updates webceo stops working #conned    
    
    
    @SteveHocking Looking at your LinkedIn advert - change of heart?    
    
    
    Why the romantic stories of the Great Train Robbers? The 2 beaten railway drivers never recovered & died 7 (age 63) & 9 (age 34) years later    
    
    
    @SuperBrandsUK Nice to see @Silentnightbeds retains its spot in UKs top70 brands http://www.superbrands.uk.com/silentnight-beds … - not enough manufacturers though!    
    
    
    The future of proper journalism probably requires paywalls, better that than The Guardian sacking dozens of journos http://www.bullhornreach.com/article/view/52659 …    
    
    
    Microsoft fined €561m for coding an if-then-else wrongly - lumme its time to buy that Hebridean crofters smallholding http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2013/mar/06/microsoft-fined-browser-error …    
    
    
    Just invented a new database server in a JDBC connection string: SDL Server - Think it's a sign of too much Tridion! :-)    
    
    
    The fab new Rest Assured #umbraco website is nearly ready - great work guys!  @moonsharkdesign @mikemoorhouse @positivedm @dennydante    
    
    
    Upgrade to a great new @Silentnightbeds Classics bed with free storage - find a stockist here http://www.silentnight.co.uk/classicsupgrade/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    IsitOK to tweet a screenshot of a Google Street View where the Google car has seen something it shouldn't have done in the red light area?    
    
    
    IsitOK to tweet a screenshot of a Google Street View where the Google car has seen something it shouldn't have done in the red light area?    
    
    
    Dear O2, trying to watch a revolution on a moving train on my iPhone 4 is not working for me. Please fix.    
    
    
    Egypt, 31 years as Pres; Hosni Mubarak of the National Democratic Party. What is it about untrustworthy parties containing word 'Democrat'    
    
    
    Nice article on the Apple ][ - with revelation that the '/' key in Excel in '13 does the same as Visicalc did in '81 http://www.jakesavin.com/2013/03/07#a1459 …    
    
    
    RT @blackdogbowl: Do you recognise the streets of your favourite city in this film? #bowling #anewbreed http://ow.ly/iJf5v     
    
    
    Brilliant way to interview someone - takes a lot more involvement than usual! http://www.brandingmagazine.com/2013/02/20/heineken-the-candidate/ …    
    
    
    Fat footers aren't all bad (no, really) - but should they ever be more than a full screen like DFS? http://www.dfs.co.uk/inspirational-room-designs/bedroom/ …    
    
    
    Manchester #umbraco scene getting stronger - meetup mostly full within minutes of being announced http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Umbraco-Meetup/events/108900142/ …    
    
    
    Manchester #umbraco scene getting stronger - meetup mostly full within minutes of being announced http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Umbraco-Meetup/events/108900142/ …    
    
    
    Manchester #umbraco scene getting stronger - meetup mostly full within minutes of being announced http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Umbraco-Meetup/events/108900142/ …    
    
    
    Considered getting a lease car until I realised i've only got a year of no claims and the insurance quote was absolutely insane *cries*    
    
    
    Unless March is a cracker the NIESR data (http://www.niesr.ac.uk/pdf/120313_135629.pdf …) suggests that #tripledip is probable - the government must BOOST GROWTH    
    
    
    Considered getting a lease car until I realised i've only got a year of no claims and the insurance quote was absolutely insane *cries*    
    
    
    Ridiculously simple SEO stuff in IIS 7.5 url rewrite section. Force lowercase? force canonical? append slash? pic.twitter.com/kR8fgS2HE4    
    
    
    @building_blocks Nice work in providing so much for the Mcr #umbraco Meetup, was at BB in 2010, but not been to the new offices #exciting    
    
    
    Love Bowie - Hunky Dory is his best album for me - but #1 Bowie #2 Bon Jovi screams out that the music business desperately needs a new punk    
    
    
    Can't believe the weather reports from over the Pennines - nice sping day in Manchester - cool, dry, sunny with no wind    
    
    
    Radio news suggesting that budget is good for 'drinkers and drivers' - what about other law breakers, what's in it for burglars and muggers?    
    
    
    off to #manchester then    
    
    
    En route to Manchester! #umbraco    
    
    
    En route to Manchester! #umbraco    
    
    
    Is this an acceptable hack 10 mins before go-live? fusiontabledata = fusiontabledata.replace(/NaN/g, '');    
    
    
    Waiting for the thumbs up/down on a go-live ... - http://www.buzzfeed.com/mattbellassai/45-people-you-wont-believe-actually-exist-6z51 …    
    
    
    @building_blocks Nice work in providing so much for the Mcr #umbraco Meetup, was at BB in 2010, but not been to the new offices #exciting    
    
    
    @computerlovers Good chat with Tim Peel last night - another ex-Silentnight Brand dev! #AnyoneWhoIsAnyone    
    
    
    @SteveHocking How's contracting going?    
    
    
    @peteduncanson Great entertainment as ever last night - you were worth the entry money on your own #umbraco    
    
    
    @SteveHocking How's contracting going?    
    
    
    @blueprintweb mentioned to me at the Mcr #umbraco meetup that a LinkedIn search for Umbraco Manchester puts me at the top #NoIdeaWhy    
    
    
    @blueprintweb mentioned to me at the Mcr #umbraco meetup that a LinkedIn search for Umbraco Manchester puts me at the top #NoIdeaWhy    
    
    
    @timpeel Good talking last night, it was good to see someone pointing at the elephant in the room that is moving #umbraco between servers    
    
    
    @timpeel Good talking last night, it was good to see someone pointing at the elephant in the room that is moving #umbraco between servers    
    
    
    @timpeel Good talking last night, it was good to see someone pointing at the elephant in the room that is moving #umbraco between servers    
    
    
    @samuelcotterall Good to see you at the @umbraco meetup - you still have the best twitter biog around!    
    
    
    Fantastic news - my great sports (?!?) tweet has won me an invite to earn cash by reviewing pr0n - what could possibly be dodgy about that?    
    
    
    I've never been accused of it playing football - but StackOverflow has now tarred me with the 'sportsmanship' brush http://stackoverflow.com/badges/805/sportsmanship?userid=261798 …    
    
    
    Did enjoy reading this http://www.highrankings.com/useless-seo-tactics-303 … after another SEO agency ran their software over an inherited legacy site    
    
    
    TBH I wonder which software suggests that the 'title' attribute is a key SEO indicator? #sheesh #snakeoil    
    
    
    I wonder if recruiters, SEO experts & estate agents occasionally move between their non-jobs to maintain their general air of cluelessness    
    
    
    @timpeel Good talking last night, it was good to see someone pointing at the elephant in the room that is moving #umbraco between servers    
    
    
    Unhappiest places to live in the UK - http://www.guardian.co.uk/money/2013/mar/27/harrogate-happiest-town-live-uk-rightmove?CMP=twt_gu … - are basically London, Essex & Dudley (not the same since Lenny Henry left)    
    
    
    Whenn did bowling suddenly become trendy? #manchester #hipsterbowling    
    
    
    @drobar got client asking does imagegen support http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lossless_compression … ??    
    
    
    @drobar got client asking does imagegen support http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lossless_compression … ??    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin - The new Rest Assured site is looking good :) http://www.rest-assured.co.uk/     
    
    
    My Twitter value is $6.11, according to http://www.twalue.com ... What about yours? #twalue    
    
    
    We have 40 Tech.Days Mugs to giveaway, just tweet using #techedchallenge. #PrettySimpleToDo    
    
    
    I do like Rebel Mouse https://www.rebelmouse.com/amelvin/     
    
    
    Christmas markets open in just seven months - the appropriate weather appears to have arrived a touch early this year    
    
    
    Who do they manage? Why do digital agencies get to the point where they have more people with "manager" in their job title than without?    
    
    
    The BBC's class calculator http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-22000973 … is interesting. I was never going to be classified as 'elite' as I dont have a BBC B Micro    
    
    
    so a recruiter sends me a CV of someone I know (unsolicited). I can go to them direct right #ethics    
    
    
    Be careful what you tweet!  http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-berkshire-22017567 …  I've often thought that shortened links are dangerous - time for pr0n.ly ?    
    
    
    Media seem obsessed with the scum at the bottom of society and the thieves at the top - but its the rest of us that pay for their lifestyles    
    
    
    Odd for people in Croydon claim to be 'Londoners' nevermind that they want to relieve Cumbria of 'Lake District' tag http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-22027322 …    
    
    
    Good article http://readwrite.com/2013/04/03/3-tips-for-attracting-a-technical-co-founder … - although it's laughable to suggest that a few days coding & a suit will be able to speak 'techie'    
    
    
    God save me from any more bible-based inspiring tweets    
    
    
    On a london tourist bus in the rain with no coat #livingthedream    
    
    
    We have 40 Tech.Days Mugs to giveaway, just tweet using #techedchallenge. Or to win a trip to TechEd Europe visit http://spr.ly/6015n2Oc     
    
    
    Good article by @CharltonBrooker that touches on Gray/Keys sexism row http://bit.ly/fMAD6d they're knobs, but what kind of world do we want?    
    
    
    We have 40 Tech.Days Mugs to giveaway, just tweet using #techedchallenge. Or to win a trip to TechEd Europe visit http://spr.ly/6015n2Oc     
    
    
    #Irony101 Clicked article about how bad full page facebook ads will be - only to get an ad? http://readwrite.com/2013/04/17/new-facebook-ads-go-big-but-get-less-social-users-will-hate-them … pic.twitter.com/sviYZo9bwo    
    
    
    Toddlers leaving nursery 'with no sense of purpose' is not a problem - interfering, meddling, nanny state governments are a problem    
    
    
    Not sure where I found this razor tip:  if (kount % 4) { @:</tr><tr> } - but it's a good one (the colon matters!)    
    
    
    Are we in a #tripledip recession? It doesn't feel like a recession - but then again it doesn't feel like we have a government. #LiesAndStats    
    
    
    The UK needs growth so +0.3% is a start - some quarters of consecutive growth will be good; but real wage rises will be better!    
    
    
    Think I may need to take @Antony_Melvin up on his offer of a beet root shot before my next run!    
    
    
    Good to see that @umbraco is issuing security alerts - good confidence booster (errors happen - wishing they wouldn't is fools talk)    
    
    
    since @MartinSLewis mentioned the Telephone Preference Service, its website must be over run with people because its running so slowly!    
    
    
    I'm fundraising for MS Society & I'd love your support! Text MELV68 £5 to 70070 to sponsor me today. Thanks. http://www.justgiving.com/antonymelvin     
    
    
    An EU directive to be happy about! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-22335520 … - banning chemicals linked to wild bee decline #EUNotUtterlyHopeless    
    
    
    Like its news! On StackOverflow the top brains are over 37 http://news.ncsu.edu/releases/wms-murphyhill-age-2013/ … - those younger simply have less breadth of knowledge    
    
    
    Interesting story about 'Game Dev Studio' game, where the devs created a cracked, crack of the game themselves http://www.greenheartgames.com/2013/04/29/what-happens-when-pirates-play-a-game-development-simulator-and-then-go-bankrupt-because-of-piracy/ …    
    
    
    The content of this page is so far up its own arse it brings tears to my eyes - but the design is challenging http://pitchfork.com/features/cover-story/reader/savages/ …    
    
    
    Got an interesting Experis IT job survey this morning. London & SE saw 70% of applications, but Mcr & NW is now clearly next choice    
    
    
    Twice as many IT job seekers in NW England than in Scotland & Wales put together.    
    
    
    @watsoncomedian Try the following Google search, append a word from the tweet: site:http://twitter.com  +watsoncomedian status    
    
    
    @watsoncomedian eg...    site:http://twitter.com  +watsoncomedian status +apr +2012    
    
    
    It's only show 3 of Channel 4's @10OClockLive today and I've already run out of subtle ways of mentioning that it's on.    
    
    
    It's only show 3 of Channel 4's @10OClockLive today and I've already run out of subtle ways of mentioning that it's on.    
    
    
    Dangerous store locators - http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-mo-ben-jerrys-20130409,0,6918019.story … - lumme best not push that feature too hard in future    
    
    
    So that was summer then...    
    
    
    Twitter trends - most of the top 10 in the UK are now variations on a Ferguson theme #SAF #fergieretires #thankyousiralex Man U #MUFC Utd    
    
    
    I reckon that there is a growing pool of worried people who've spent 20+ years in development roles http://readwrite.com/2013/05/06/how-to-thrive-in-the-tech-industry-for-decades …    
    
    
    NIESR calculations suggest that UK economic growth improved again in April with GDP 0.8% higher than in Jan #GoodNews http://www.niesr.ac.uk/sites/default/files/publications/gdp0513.pdf …    
    
    
    Police say Savile 'not protected' #bollocks    
    
    
    The thunder & darkness in Spinningfields suggests that the Man Utd victory parade may be a soggy one    
    
    
    There is genuinely snow in the air in central Manchester (that and sleet & hailstones) - the big man's not happy about something    
    
    
    @CGaskell Do you think that there will be a June umbraco Mcr event?  I'd heard a rumour that it might be on a boat.    
    
    
    @CGaskell Do you think that there will be a June umbraco Mcr event?  I'd heard a rumour that it might be on a boat.    
    
    
    Don't know what the word 'pretentious' means? Why not read the definition on the inner label of Waitrose Truffle Oil. @TwopTwips    
    
    
    Can we have a £10 per month internet license fee for an ad-free version of the internet - with fees given to websites?  Please?    
    
    
    Nice pattern to stop open redirect attacks in ASP.Net MVC 3 - and how it can be retro'd into MVC 1 & 2 by writing a IsLocalUrl helper method    
    
    
        
    
    
    This might sound odd but I've been asked if it's possible to print off every page in an @umbraco site in one go - any ideas?    
    
    
    Yay my Stackoverflow reputation has passed 5,000.  http://stackoverflow.com/users/261798/amelvin …    
    
    
    Man who 'slowed the internet down' suffering from curable monobrow issues http://www.guardian.co.uk/technology/2013/may/20/man-accused-breaking-the-internet …    
    
    
    This might sound odd but I've been asked if it's possible to print off every page in an @umbraco site in one go - any ideas?    
    
    
    @drobar Do you know when / if there will be Level 1 @umbraco training in Manchester next?    
    
    
    I keep hearing about a £4bn cost for the gay wedding bill - I didn't realise that Elton John was getting married again?    
    
    
    @drobar Do you know when / if there will be Level 1 @umbraco training in Manchester next?    
    
    
    @drobar Do you know when / if there will be Level 1 @umbraco training in Manchester next?    
    
    
    @drobar Do you know when / if there will be Level 1 @umbraco training in Manchester next?    
    
    
    GIF or JIF - in Britain only pedantic geeks would use jif, because people would laugh & make jokes about pancake day http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-22620473 …    
    
    
    And the South Manchester tram line with it's Didsbury tram stop is now open. Exciting times. Bye-bye to getting the Magic Bus into town!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Daily Mail 'cut down in a hail of bullets' and juxtaposing celebs & bloody hatchets #JustWrong http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2329470/Michael-Adebolajo-named-Woolwich-killers.html … pic.twitter.com/zAQOXM8tz0    
    
    
    RT @n3odigital New website launched. My Sofa Beds. http://bit.ly/16QquZX  #umbraco #ucommerce #mobile #umblaunch    
    
    
    Xbox One: Ever wish you could chat with a friend on Skype while watching a movie?  Me: No.    
    
    
    Xbox One: Instantly and effortlessly jump back and forth between a game, TV, music, and apps.  Me: No thanks, sounds too tiring    
    
    
    Xbox One: Xbox One was designed to be the most advanced gaming console ever, and the best entertainment console. Me: That comma is wrong pal    
    
    
    UKIP will be unhappy as most of the Gloucester cheese-rolling events were won by foreign 'tourists' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-gloucestershire-22681708 …    
    
    
    @simonpegg Dad's Army    
    
    
    @simonpegg Porridge    
    
    
    Once again the Mcr Umbraco Meetup is almost full a few minutes after announcement - http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Umbraco-Meetup/ … - #MissItMissOut !!    
    
    
    Three hours on a boat cruise with @umbraco types - what can possibly go wrong? http://www.meetup.com/Manchester-Umbraco-Meetup/ …    
    
    
    Exactly a year at Silentnight - I certainly sleep well at night #GoodTimes    
    
    
    Good article on the Everton badge debacle from a designers POV - http://www.designweek.co.uk/editors-view/evertons-branding-own-goal/3036546.article … - warning headline contains an obvious cliched idiom    
    
    
    Excel password warning: 'keep a list of passwords ... in a safe place' - does this include a post-it stuck on desk? pic.twitter.com/DvEOUSt3C1    
    
    
    Genius - how much will football fans take from their club?   http://thesunshineroom.com/2013/05/30/bullshit-rodeo/ …    
    
    
    #bbccricket The England tail getting a run a ball through the last 10 overs has turned a poor batting display into an OK one    
    
    
    Going to start recruitment process for a new web dev next week; 24-28k pref umbraco experience - can't wait for the recruiter calls!    
    
    
    Stunned at plans to close the MOSI (Museum of Science & Industry in Manchester) - this must be stopped http://www.manchesterconfidential.co.uk/News/MOSI-To-Close-News-And-Comment …    
    
    
    @therealboon Do you think that the closure of MOSI to concentrate museum cash in London is a good idea? http://www.manchesterconfidential.co.uk/News/MOSI-To-Close-News-And-Comment …    
    
    
    @stephenfry Is closing York Railway Museum, Bradford Media & Mcr MOSI to save another London Museum a good idea? http://www.manchesterconfidential.co.uk/News/MOSI-To-Close-News-And-Comment …    
    
    
    Starbucks asking for my name was bad enough but Coke incorrectly guessing my name is even worse. Will someone try to guess my weight next?    
    
    
    Interesting maps - more detail on the UK would be good https://blog.twitter.com/2013/geography-tweets-3 …    
    
    
    @thekeithchegwin Surely @Mattallwright former regular partner in crime(-fighting) was a biker (etc) - does Cheggers wear leather tonight?    
    
    
    #bbcsportsday Instead of wage cap: Have contracts where unused players are released from contract with no compensation to club or player    
    
    
    Has MCTS 70-515 exam been deprecated? The notice I expected doesn't appear on the MS learning page? http://www.microsoft.com/learning/en/us/exam.aspx?ID=70-515#fbid=XYt_olYkJ6z …    
    
    
    @timpeel Ah the #CodeLaunch hashtag now makes sense - new website looks good - http://www.codecomputerlove.com/     
    
    
    @timpeel Ace site - good progressive design, even the homepage load on android works well before the images load. Hats off indeed!    
    
    
    News saying that service stopping cold sales calls doesn't work - not my experience at all, it works for me http://www.tpsonline.org.uk/tps/index.html     
    
    
    NIESR estimate more UK economy growth in the last 3 months (0.6%) & earlier upward revisions  #VeryPromising http://niesr.ac.uk/publications/june-2013-gdp-estimates#.Ubc-JfmsiSp …    
    
    
    NIESR last 6 months UK GDP growth estimates (earliest first) - -0.3%, -0.2%, 0.1%, 0.3%, 1.0%, 0.6% - official Q2 figures should be good    
    
    
    Infographic: Silentnight Top Mobile / Tablet Devices -  http://infogr.am/Top-Mobile--Tablet-Devices … via @infogram    
    
    
    Brilliant waste of time - dynamically photoshopping people waiting for a bus into the advert at the bus stop 
http://uk.news.yahoo.com/bus-stop-photoshop-prank--adobe-youtube-stockholm-sweden-111806199.html?vp=1#khKqmMK …    
    
    
    Just read a @guardian article in G2 on why Apple is ditching skeuomorphism - which is now in my top 10 favourite words    
    
    
    @rsleggett @ryansroberts seen this? http://www.thoughtworks.com/events/evening-martin-fowler …    
    
    
    QR codes - any evidence that they work?  We've been running campaigns and they don't seem to generate much interest.    
    
    
    Whoah I thought it was just me! How to Successfully Pretend to Work Hard as Software Developer? 
http://www.sw-engineering-candies.com/blog-1/how-to-successfully-pretend-to-work-hard-as-software-developer …    
    
    
    Watched the start of that French drama 'The Returned' - got to say I was filling up when Camille returned, absolutely compelling TV    
    
    
    http://devopsreactions.tumblr.com/post/49078186169/go-live-day … Go live day #brilliant    
    
    
    Lumme Essex are 15/7 against Lancs    
    
    
    #bbcsportsday A recover by Essex from the depths of 15/8 they've now pushed on to 20/8 with an individual 10 from Mickleburgh    
    
    
    Lumme Essex are 15/7 against Lancs    
    
    
    @spikeydave101 Essex need a kick - 20/9 is just a silly score - the Lancs number 11 scored 30 odd an hour or two ago    
    
    
    @spikeydave101 Essex 273 & 20 v Lancashire 398 - that is bizzarre    
    
    
    Just tried to comment on a @RWW article, clicked on Twitter to sign in and Disqus wants me to register with them - why? #RegistrationBloat    
    
    
    Lumme 15 months in jail for Stuart Hall - will he survive it at his age? Wouldn't be surprised if it's a knockout to his health TBH.    
    
    
    NZ must be hoping that Sri Lanka get out for 210-220 - too many for Aus to get in 25 overs but too few to defend over 50 #bbccricket    
    
    
    #bbccricket Eng need Aus to get over 164 or its Eng/Ind in the SF; NZ need a 50 over Aus win - Aus could damage Eng & NZ with 150 all out!    
    
    
    @rsleggett Were you 15 when that photo was taken? http://www.building-blocks.com/about/people  - fun way to do an about us page    
    
    
    Love it when recruiters know what they're talking about. Unfortunately, I don't have any Embraco experience so looks like I'm out :(    
    
    
    Phil Tufnell: 'England will be thanking the tossing gods' - wow that's a god the teens can really pray to!    
    
    
    @peteduncanson I have talked to your wife - you and @Steroberts89 is allowed to go to the #teacommerce training and become certified :)    
    
    
    Looking for a new permie Umbraco web dev to replace @dennydante - who is moving on to pastures new - no recruiters (except PSL).    
    
    
    Lancs bowled Essex out for 20 the other day & now have Northants 9/3 - Chapple is a marvel to be still opening the bowling after 22 seasons    
    
    
    What's happened on Oxford road across from the Cafe Nero? Closed off with police tape and police tents?    
    
    
    so i asked v simple question on episerver forum about link to broken sample code page 24hrs still no answer!!!!    
    
    
    It's distressing to find silver flecks of hair when your 26...    
    
    
    so i asked v simple question on episerver forum about link to broken sample code page 24hrs still no answer!!!!    
    
    
    It's distressing to find silver flecks of hair when your 26...    
    
    
    It's distressing to find silver flecks of hair when your 26...    
    
    
    This week I've been paid, had a big self assessment refund and managed to leave my wallet at head office 50 miles away #2outof3aintbad    
    
    
    RT @CGaskell: Wow the 4th Need in 24 hours added to @needhq has just landed << good work Chris, you'll be a recruiter before the months out!    
    
    
    If the new Kardashian sprog marries a Mr North - it will be a sub-ed field day!    
    
    
    RT @sweepcat9: @MartinSLewis Yep, the warehouse has started receiving the Christmas decoration deliveries...#jinglebells    
    
    
    @peteduncanson I have talked to your wife - you and @Steroberts89 is allowed to go to the #teacommerce training and become certified :)    
    
    
    @McrUmbMeetup Great times onboard HMS Umbraco, good work @blueprintweb ! When will the slides go online?    
    
    
    Photos up from last nights meet including showing Sam inebriated! http://bit.ly/14bRb8b  @McrUmbMeetup @CGaskell @blueprintweb    
    
    
    @rsleggett How did the Audience with Martin Fowler go?    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Good patterns for kids web registration on the latest alistapart article  http://bit.ly/fUwKK8    
    
    
    Sainsburys debacle over not serving a woman using a mobile phone: sounds to me like the customer was arrogant rather than the worker    
    
    
    65 years of the NHS - seems unlikely that the grand old institution will last another 65    
    
    
    Tried & failed to buy Arctic Monkeys tickets this morning - seems like they must have sold out Manchester by 9:20 this morning    
    
    
    Cool Google blog on the oldest programmable computer - http://googleblog.blogspot.co.uk/2013/06/youve-come-long-way-baby-remembering.html … - a replica is at MOSI. Well until austerity cuts close MOSI.    
    
    
    Only three teams in history have scored 200+ in the fourth innings to win at Trent Bridge #ashes http://stats.espncricinfo.com/ci/engine/stats/index.html?class=1;filter=advanced;ground=34;innings_number=4;orderby=team_score;result=1;template=results;type=team;view=innings …    
    
    
    England lead by 103 with 6 wickets left #ashes - unless the second new ball is decisive it all seems set up for a 200+ Aus run chase    
    
    
    England now lead by 201 with 4 wickets left in #ashes - still Australia's to lose, but another 50 runs and England may well be favourites    
    
    
    The universal benefits cap isn't a bad idea but it needs to be coupled with a universal rental cap; cap base rents at 33% of average income?    
    
    
    Life affirming article about the homeless and gangsters playing cricket in LA - http://bbc.in/hqgp5d - when does the film come out?    
    
    
    #bbccricket Another couple of drives and Anderson will have more runs than Cook, Root, Pieterson & Prior - will he also have keep wicket?    
    
    
    #bbccricket Australia yet to use a review - it seems that Lehmann is becoming dangerously useful to Australia - #DontTakeTheMickey    
    
    
    Mcr has the UKs 2nd most digital companies (behind Ldn), Mcr has 50-100% more than Birm, Reading/Brack, Brighton etc http://niesr.ac.uk/sites/default/files/publications/SI024_GI_NIESR_Google_Report12.pdf …    
    
    
    UK Growth at 0.6% is lovely! But companies are about to face an explosion in suppressed wage demands, esp. when interest rates rise in 2014    
    
    
        
    
    
    Boris Johnson really is funny when he wants to talk about big blue cocks http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-23448832 … - the line about Cameron is good as well    
    
    
    Writing a thing for the paper about how I'm still writing things for the paper. It's a bit like an out-of-body experience.    
    
    
    Getting few clients seeing 'Oops: this document is published but is not in the cache (internal error)' errors on sites, any known reasons?    
    
    
    My new @Silentnightbeds is rather comfy! Not too badly priced, and their website is in #umbraco too #qualitybuild @Antony_Melvin    
    
    
    #BBCCricket #Ashes I think people are being very hard on Clarke for not declaring earlier ... and I see no reason why anyone should stop.    
    
    
    Cool map showing which areas have fans that tweet for certain clubs - the west/east split of Manchester for example http://oxfordinternetinstitute.github.io/football-mapping/#riv0 …    
    
    
    GA Event Tracking, anyone got a definitive answer on whether just using onclick="_gaq.push(['_trackEvent' on internal link is ok?    
    
    
    We might change our Twitter background image again - hope nobody reads too much into it. WARNING: another change is coming! #THFC    
    
    
    can #Umbraco contour be used for form calculations as well as just data entry ? Need to create a payment calculator.    
    
    
    Signed up for a free wifi account at moto - they emailed me the username & pasword in plain text & suggested I write them down #SecurityFail    
    
    
    @andrewdoran Are you on holiday?    
    
    
    My 10 year-old niece continues to bite every time I mis-name a certain band as either one dimension or no direction - try it, it's fun!    
    
    
    #BBCCricket Aus choked on 8 of their last 10 chases in excess of 200. So sounds about right, Eng will win 80% with Aus chasing 299    
    
    
    80yo man was #yewtree arrested, teh interwebz has quickly listed Messrs Caine, Bough & McCallum as octoganerian Lahndeners #WhoKnowsTruth?    
    
    
    80yo man was #yewtree arrested, teh interwebz has quickly listed Messrs Caine, Bough & McCallum as octoganerian Lahndeners #WhoKnowsTruth?    
    
    
    80yo man was #yewtree arrested, teh interwebz has quickly listed Messrs Caine, Bough & McCallum as octoganerian Lahndeners #WhoKnowsTruth?    
    
    
    Are there any decent maps for the upgraded Manchester cycle routes - found this - but its rubbish http://cycling.tfgm.com/velocity/Velocity2025_vision.pdf …    
    
    
    Can't someone come up with a better model that the tube mapping model? Timperley, Sale & Broadheath aren't all at right angles to Brooklands    
    
    
    For cycling to work in the UK the simplest answer for me is to convert the middle of major roads with a physical barrier from cars & lorries    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tough questions to answer in 140 characters #284: What are the sovereignty differences of Gibraltar, Hong Kong, Bermuda & Falklands?    
    
    
    Tough questions to answer in 140 characters #284: What are the sovereignty differences of Gibraltar, Hong Kong, Bermuda & Falklands?    
    
    
    @RWW Why can't I leave a comment on your website without registering my email address/password with disqus - why not login via twitter?    
    
    
    @RWW How is creating yet another registration account 'a more steamlined sign-in process'? pic.twitter.com/DZKzDMNCeV    
    
    
    For cycling to work in the UK the simplest answer for me is to convert the middle of major roads with a physical barrier from cars & lorries    
    
    
    For cycling to work in the UK the simplest answer for me is to convert the middle of major roads with a physical barrier from cars & lorries    
    
    
    Rather than HS2 trams for Leeds & Liverpool is a good idea http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-23587557 … - know how good they've been for Mcr (if sometimes crap)    
    
    
    If all the world economies now grow or contract at the same time - won't that make the booms bigger & the busts badder?    
    
    
    Trying not to be pedantic but I'm losing track of how many 'professional' companies misspell Silentnight - FYI no space, no capital N    
    
    
    Trying not to be pedantic but I'm losing track of how many 'professional' companies misspell Silentnight - FYI no space, no capital N    
    
    
    Well played to the @mailonline in putting aside party loyalties to question a large bequest banked by the coalition political parties    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin thought you would enjoy this http://seeingredonline.com/shut-up-luis/     
    
    
    @SigmoidFx Is Late Rooms going well?    
    
    
    An excellent Tumblr. Daily Mail pictures of people looking sad standing next to the thing that made them sad. http://hearmewail.tumblr.com/     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin thought you would enjoy this http://seeingredonline.com/shut-up-luis/     
    
    
    If I want to add social sharing buttons to the bottom of an umbraco page is there a specific #umbraco package that people actually use?    
    
    
    Yay 1000 tweets from me!  ... not convinced anyone cares, but hey-ho.    
    
    
    Is it true that Michael Gove has been advising the Liberia Education Ministry? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-africa-23843578 …    
    
    
    #bbcsportsday Ashes; your average Aus player rating is 6.54 with 6.45 for Eng so I assume Aus edged the Ashes? Did I miss their 2-1 win?    
    
    
        
    
    
    #BBCSportsday England scored more runs, took more wickets & won the #Ashes 3-0 - my word Australia clearly have the momentum    
    
    
    The past is another country, the future is another world    
    
    
    #BBCSportsday England scored more runs, took more wickets & won the #Ashes 3-0 - my word Australia clearly have the momentum    
    
    
    Missed this strike by graphic designers whilst on holiday http://lnkd.in/9twPvV  - did everyone cope?    
    
    
        
    
    
    If I want to add social sharing buttons to the bottom of an umbraco page is there a specific #umbraco package that people actually use?    
    
    
    Good to hear that Glen Chapple is staying at Lancs for another season http://www.bbc.co.uk/sport/0/cricket/23879045 … - 1,000 first class wickets must be the target    
    
    
    Now Rolf Harris is charged ... #CanYouSeeWhat ... no don't go there    
    
    
    Looks like Lancs have got Hanpshire about ready to follow on    
    
    
        
    
    
    #BBCSportsday If Lancs complete victory against Hants, they need an absolute max of 30 points from 3 games for promotion, 40 to top div 2    
    
    
    I can see why this article on 'why http://Microsoft.Net  failed' has been published where it can't have comments! http://www.infoworld.com/print/225817     
    
    
    £34m lost in universal credit IT system with an "unfamiliar project management approach" http://lnkd.in/6pgH96  - was it agile?    
    
    
    @TwopTwips CRIMINALS: Avoid unnessary stress and ask Manchester Police which crimes won't be investigated before setting out tonight    
    
    
        
    
    
    Due a client conf call at 10am; 9:59am some arborist starts chainsawing a tree nearby... great, thanks! :-|    
    
    
    @Silentnight Sleep Clinic is now accepting entries until 13 Sep - there's still time to get your sleep problems fixed http://www.silentnight.co.uk/sleep-clinic/     
    
    
    Great two days @teacommerce training with @mattbrailsford @Neil_Hodges @Antony_Melvin @andersburla - highly recommended to all #umbraco devs    
    
    
    Great two days @teacommerce training with @mattbrailsford @Neil_Hodges @Antony_Melvin @andersburla - highly recommended to all #umbraco devs    
    
    
    Lancs need a max points win this week to secure the div 2 title - 19pts max for promotion (will be less as Essex are struggling)    
    
    
    Two types of blog comment really make the commenter look like an idiot, which may not be the intention - so I'll help out ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    #2 fact nitpicking - so what if there is the odd typo? If pro bono copywriting is for you, keep it to yourself - most people do'nt care    
    
    
    "Where you from?"

"Cheshire"    
    
    
    In case anyone isn't feeling the cold, the Christmas markets will open in 9 weeks.    
    
    
    After 30 months of flatlining UK GDP - the last 6 really suggest we've turned a corner - long way from boom though pic.twitter.com/nYg1OhzaeO    
    
    
    Nice to see that taxpayers money is wasted chasing benefits cheats who actually claim too little money! http://www.manchestereveningnews.co.uk/news/officials-who-caught-benefits-cheat-1284342 …    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis Is there any prospect that high pension management charges/transfer fees  could result in PPI like claims?    
    
    
    Just booked tickets for me & @positivedm at NUX2 conference next month http://uxmanc.co.uk/     
    
    
    The Myth of the Rockstar Developer http://www.hanselman.com/blog/TheMythOfTheRockstarProgrammer.aspx … <-- Rockstar is an ugly adjective    
    
    
    Is everything being dumbed down? Dead popes can now become saints without the second 'miracle' http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-24330204 … #SuspendDisbelief    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats! Elastoplast have been voted to be a Consumer Superbrand for 2014, get in touch for dets :)!    
    
    
    Note to self: Don't assume hosting company have configured .net/IIS properly next time you see a 500 on a new server - run aspnet_regiis -lv    
    
    
    @tonyfoggett @timpeel Thanks for your support of the Umbraco meetup - really appreciated    
    
    
    @ryan_durkin @rsleggett Great chat last night at the @umbraco Manchester meetup    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sleep needed to clear the brain of toxins - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/health-24567412 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Cheapest place to buy an iPad / iPad Mini please?

#asktwitter    
    
    
    @rsleggett Are you going to nux2 today?    
    
    
    How quickly have Breaking Bad themed items (t-shirts etc) turned from cool -> ironic -> cheesy - I'll have to wait for post-irony I guess    
    
    
    Anyone going to nux2 today?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @grantshapps To misquote slightly the BBC helps put the Great in Great Britain - if you hate the BBC you hate Britain.    
    
    
    #bbcsportsday Broad didn't edge to first slip - he edged to the 'keeper who parried it to first slip    
    
    
        
    
    
    We're hiring! Looking to add a web developer to grow our permanent digital development team to five. Interested? pic.twitter.com/oG0Oc41rRE    
    
    
    We're hiring!  I have a PSL in place to handle permanent development requirements - so speculative recruiter calls are pointless.    
    
    
    Today's Money Saving Expert poll suggests that most people want adverts on the BBC rather than license fee - http://www.moneysavingexpert.com/poll/29-10-2013/should-the-tv-licence-fee-be-scrapped-oct2013 …    
    
    
    Should the BBC licence fee be scrapped, shared amongst other broadcasters or protected? PLEASE VOTE... http://bit.ly/1aQYsdO     
    
    
        
    
    
    I am one of the Working Dead Zzzombies this #halloween! Find out more at http://www.silentnight.co.uk/world-war-zzzzz/ …    
    
    
    Clegg: Paxman treats all politicians as "rogues and charlatans" - is Nick Clegg under the delusion that some politicians aren't?    
    
    
    Damn you @Claire_SNbeds bringing in Krispy Kreme's!! After a pub lunch as well ...    
    
    
    Too excited #doctorwho - Will Capaldi be #13? Now we've seen Paul McGann's (#8) regeneration into John Hurt (#9) - http://www.bbc.co.uk/iplayer/episode/p01lhhv4/Doctor_Who_Mini_Episode_The_Night_of_the_Doctor/ …    
    
    
    Looking at new Odeon design to see what's on http://www.odeon.co.uk/cinemas/manchester/11/ … - the design is good, but the navigation UX feels all wrong.    
    
    
    This BBC article http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/blogs-magazine-monitor-24992518 … reports that http://kleargear.com  damaged someones credit rating for posting a bad review!    
    
    
    You search for a tech answer; you end up on StackOverflow; then find that you knew the answer a couple of years ago. #gettingold    
    
    
        
    
    
    IT issues like RBS - the experts on the BBC say insource, outsource or blame people (http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-24962989 …)    
    
    
    Must say that @ResignManchestr seems to be a better 'cause' than @ResignLondon - leaves more gravy for the rest of us    
    
    
    It does beg the question is the gravy/no-gravy chip option analogous with mayo/salad-cream debate - another food-stuff class-war marker?    
    
    
    The joys of maintenance programming http://bit.ly/hgyRCA <-- Good article on why greenfield dev neither suits or is good for all devs    
    
    
    Just got email from a disaster recovery firm who guarantee you'll 'be up and running in 60 minutes, minimum'  #itsnotmeitsyou    
    
    
    Damn just realised that parents (where do I put the apostrophe?) evening is on #pancakeday - straight from work to school = no pancakes :(    
    
    
    I thought IE6 was below 5% of market - but Microsoft say its still 12% http://bit.ly/huceoG - but want people to move on!    
    
    
    Been on this Sharepoint 2010 course this week - 44WW27 - Developing for SharePoint 2010 - Sharepoint really looks like a good, usable produ…    
    
    
    Pointless applying for a job at expensify.com if you have a sniff of .net on your CV - http://bit.ly/ih8rH6 - doesn't sound like a big prob    
    
    
    BRITAIN. Don't switch over to a +1 channel at 1am as you may destroy the space-time continuum. /via @Alan_Machnik    
    
    
    Good project management Q&A site - from the StackOverflow people - http://pm.stackexchange.com/    
    
    
    I don't get people protesting at Fortnam & Mason. A world without the option of luxury is not a world I want to live in.    
    
    
    Preparing for the nightshift - coffee, sugar, matchsticks... if I get really pissed off, then I'm gonna start the lawnmower up at 3am.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    AV pluses - ends tactical voting, fewer votes are wasted and as a result elects least-worst MP on offer.    
    
    
        
    
    
    There are a LOT of children on this flight. Am re-thinking the "gin is not for breakfast" rule.    
    
    
    "Nice little racket . . . Job for life . . . Don't even need to bother to try to get a majority . . . " Clegg urges us to vote Yes.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @agentgav If the US Congress has a lower approval rating now than the the British Crown had at Independence ... isn't only fair to ...    
    
    
    @agentgav ... allow the US people a referendum to become a British dependency?    
    
    
    Can't see the @InjunctionSuper twitter account lasting long - claiming to show all super injunctions about footballers etc    
    
    
    Intechnica has two job openings in Manchester centre at the moment, the first is an Office Manager ... http://lnkd.in/2e_pT7    
    
    
    This LinkedIn animation showing your contacts appearing on a timeline is very interesting - http://lnkd.in/MmZAp2    
    
    
    I don't use Facebook, but even so I have my suspicions about my latest Friend request from Mr Eff McOff. http://yfrog.com/h63hxtp    
    
    
    Hanging out with @istacey on Google+ . It's the end of Facebook. Hooray!    
    
    
    @Antony_Melvin either I'm not allowed to or I can't find that button.    
    
    
    Is it possible to insult anyone you see who's bought the NotW until buying it becomes as nasty as reading it    
    
    
    Viz NotW closure, I feel sorry for the paper's journalists with sound morals unconnected with scandals ... <insert gag here>    
    
    
    