@mikehadlow i've been in erlang for the last 6 weeks. Not missing the static typing much at all.    
    
    
    @mikehadlow the class of bugs that the compiler catches are easily found with the tests, which i need anyway    
    
    
    @chadmyers with EC2, you are charged for running instances, regardless of usage    
    
    
    @chadmyers @sbohlen ec2 pricing starts at 2c per hour, so about 15 bucks a month    
    
    
    @mikehadlow alas, all under nda at the mo, but it is a *very* productive environment    
    
    
    @mhenders might be interested in one of the macbooks for the in-laws - what are the specs and how much you looking for?    
    
    
    Stupid windows with your slashes round the wrong way    
    
    
    @adlanelm Bash, emacs etc. Should be on linux really, but one of our dependencies is windows-only :(    
    
    
    @tanukidata Do you guys supply hardware components? I'm in need of a power supply for a motherboard….    
    
    
    @tanukidata cool, where are you? Could I drop by sometime tomorrow?    
    
    
    @tanukidata Hey Joey, having problems with that ram module - any chance you'd be able to drop by my office so we can test the others?    
    
    
    @tanukidata I've already left for the day, but should be in anytime after 9.30 tomorrow    
    
    
    Thanks to @tanukidata for sorting out my hardware woes this week :)    
    
    
    Not tweeted for ages, been insanely busy. System goes live in less than a week, going through final acceptance tests. All looking good :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney we've been building a large cloud-based audio transcoding and archiving system for Reuters, been under nda the whole time    
    
    
    @joe_carney but they've just filed a patent on the technology used, so guess it's official public domain now ;)    
    
    
    @joe_carney you on the coast at the mo or travelling? If the former, we should grab a coffee sometime    
    
    
    @tanukidata @joe_carney I think it'll be cold by the time I get there :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney @tanukidata so if you're midway through, that means you'll be wanting a break midweek - coffee on Wednesday?    
    
    
    @joe_carney that's where my office is, so works for me :) sometime in the morning?    
    
    
    @joe_carney @tanukidata not sure yet, depends on kids and school    
    
    
    @hhariri @joe_carney go on dude, you know you want to :)    
    
    
    @hhariri Welcome back :)    
    
    
    @awashtell Got the S, not the S2. Hate it.    
    
    
    @awashtell Not used a 2, so perhaps it's much better. It needs to be, mine was pretty crap out of the box, very slow, very laggy    
    
    
    @awashtell Installing a custom rom helped, but I really don't expect to have to mess about with such things. Roll on iPhone 5 for me    
    
    
    @incongruousm @awashtell The problem with the S wasn't hardware, it was the screwed up Android install that samsung did    
    
    
    @seanparsons @awashtell @incongruousm guess they sorted out the filesystem they were using, or the h/ware is *so* fast it doesn't matter :)    
    
    
    @RoyOsherove TeamViewer works ok    
    
    
    @NJenman I'm on a custom one, not one of Samsung's.  About 9 months old now, but not sure I can be arsed to go through the upgrade pain :)    
    
    
    @NJenman way too busy to spend time upgrading phones, particularly when it should have worked without the upgrade :)    
    
    
    @tanukidata Hey, do you have any laptop drives in stock? Friend of mine has just had one die in his MBP...    
    
    
    @tanukidata no need to reply, he's on the phone with you right now :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney @hhariri so you boys up for a coffee tomorrow?  Place and time?    
    
    
    @lazycoder take a look at "Not Even Wrong" for an alternative view on string theory. It is a bit heavy going though, quite a lot of theory    
    
    
    «@RonJeffries «@zeminlu UNIX' Russian Roulette: sudo [ $[ $RANDOM % 6 ] == 0 ] && rm -rf / || echo “You live”»»    
    
    
    @joe_carney quick lunch before you head to nueva andalusia? You know anywhere good? I'm up at the copper-tower end of town    
    
    
    @joe_carney that'll work, the port is about 10mins from my office    
    
    
    @joe_carney looks good, call me when you're near and I'll meet you there    
    
    
    @hhariri @joe_carney we'll have to sort out tapas one night #keepsayingthat    
    
    
    Been using backbone.js today, quite liking it but surprised how much boilerplate code needed in a collection view's render method    
    
    
    @joe_carney you anywhere nearby? Just sat down for a coffee at trilla    
    
    
    @joe_carney hope you get things working and get some sleep :) Catch you Friday    
    
    
    @joe_carney We good for lunchtime?    
    
    
    Just leaving for gatwick. Short week in the uk coming up...    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof @ade_oshineye @ecomba a cup of coffee?    
    
    
    Thinking that a hot curry two hours before the flight perhaps wasn't such a great idea    
    
    
    Fancy infinite storage? http://www.bitcasa.com/beta-signup?share=2513632736 … Tempting to pipe /dev/random to them and see how it goes ;)    
    
    
    First experience of Win8 "Your internet security settings prevented the file from being opened". This is a file on a CD. #fail    
    
    
    @srstrong Being fair to Win8, looks like it might have been a VM issue    
    
    
    @martinstillman doubt the great unwashed would be installing in a VM in the first place :)    
    
    
    @martinstillman that said, I was very un-impressed. Been installing early windows betas since Win95, and this one was the least exciting    
    
    
    @martinstillman busy :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins not used it, been doing all our templating on the client. Zotonic makes heavy use of erlydtl which implements django templates    
    
    
    @petebouch any idea where the fire is? Lots of choppers flying over us as well but no smoke visible    
    
    
    An evening with backbone.js, backbone.memento and backbone.modelbinding.  This stack feels *very* nice.    
    
    
    @dagda1 it goes straight to the ast, there's no hql string generation going on    
    
    
    @dagda1 @jagregory it is an hql ast, so i guess you could claim that you werr right all along ;)    
    
    
    @jagregory @dagda1 lol :)    
    
    
    @hhariri ouch :(    
    
    
    @neil_rees @awashtell not sure t gsa t the cassini licence allows you to redistribute; I'd check if it was for commercial use    
    
    
    @neil_rees @awashtell there's also something with either webmatrix or lightswitch that is similar, but don't recall the details    
    
    
    @jamesogden @neil_rees @awashtell that's the chap    
    
    
    Anyone know of a place for rent in Chamonix over Christmas / New Year, ideally 3 bedrooms...    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho teamviewer and skype, works really well both on win & osx    
    
    
    Forgot how much fun the underground is on a Monday morning    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn at Olympia at a streaming media conference where we are exhibiting. Checkout www.streamappliance.com    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn how you doing? Still at rbs?    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn here until Wednesday,  fly back Thu morning. What you doing after rbs?    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn not today, just doing setup :) tomorrow or wednesday would be fine    
    
    
    @gbzrce hi Rob, long time! We're doing this www.streamappliance.com    
    
    
    @gbzrce doing quite a bit in the streaming space and saw a hole in the market. Fingers crossed :)    
    
    
    Launched yesterday www.streamappliance.com - it's been a busy few weeks :). Lots of early interest, so will sleep well tonight!    
    
    
    Anyone in London fancy a couple of beers? #geekbeers    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn check in at around 6am - guessing that's a bit early :)    
    
    
    @seanparsons arse, should have tweeted earlier!    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn yes, it would indeed. With the launch, this week has been pretty mental, hopefully the next trip will be more sane    
    
    
    Any opinions on low-cost website load test tools?    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall nice one, thanks :)    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall @mikehadlow @Keith_bloom thanks for the suggestions chaps :)    
    
    
    Proper thunderstorm going on, had no power for about an hour now    
    
    
    @joe_carney forgot to turn on the API server yesterday; bit tricky now with no power!    
    
    
    @joe_carney :)    
    
    
    An afternoon of webmachine, monads and mongo :)    
    
    
    Big new function added, big refactor done to support it, and all the tests are passing again. I'll take today :)    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn Now that sounds like a plan :)    
    
    
    Any ideas for a good Sunday lunch on the costa?    
    
    
    @joe_carney how much a head?    
    
    
    @joe_carney iphone got ordered yesterday btw ;)    
    
    
    @philiphendry groan ;)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins good luck, let's hope you don't regret that tomorrow ;)    
    
    
    @joe_carney taken your advice :) http://twitpic.com/7874sg     
    
    
    Beef. Lamb. Pork. Turkey. Ham. Damn, that was a good lunch, now bring on the apple pie :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney most excellent, thx for the tip    
    
    
    @philiphendry disappointed there was no duck ;)    
    
    
    @adymitruk @dagda1 +1 for zeromq, a breathe of fresh air after the complexities of most of the others    
    
    
    Tweet about a good lunch and some checky sod sends me a link to a diet website. These bots have no social skills!    
    
    
    @dagda1 rabbit is pretty good, used it extensively on the last project. But really like the simplicity of zeromq, very appealing    
    
    
    @marknijhof how do you find the bookbook? Enough space in it for cards etc? New iPhone on the way, so in the market for a good case...    
    
    
    @sermoa Ooo, looks lovely, be very interested in one of them when they get released :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Oh, that's pretty cool, didn't look like it would take that much stuff. Very tempted :)    
    
    
    monthly invoicing run done.  Accounting is *very* dull, but the numbers look good at the end :)    
    
    
    @hhariri @marknijhof just remember to take the iPhone out first ;)    
    
    
    Lunch :) http://twitpic.com/79c5j0     
    
    
    @hhariri hehe, forgot all about that! Of course, I don't work there anymore so not my problem ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri I'll remind Mr. Watson and get him to sort something    
    
    
    @hhariri fine by me, just send in the invoice and see what happens :)    
    
    
    @hhariri lol :) think you might be right!    
    
    
    @intellectdk very spoilt :)    
    
    
    Yay, new iPhone is here. Can finally turn of my samsung hunk of junk :)    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn that is a fine question sir.  And one I'd rather you didn't ask ;)    
    
    
    Friday night, and I'm in ikea. Damn, I really know how to party.    
    
    
    @joe_carney going well thanks, you? Wed would be great but alas I'm in the uk all week :(    
    
    
    @kkozmic wouldn't call myself a guru, but it looks safe to me    
    
    
    @hhariri please say you're joking :)    
    
    
    Yesterday was our first end to end test of our erlang system, big customer demo due on wednesday, all looking good :)    
    
    
    I'm guessing that a C# version of what we're building would be 2-4 times as much code    
    
    
    @ironshay :)    
    
    
    @gmciw ask adrian about it, it's our favourite new toy :)    
    
    
    @ironshay learning the lang is pretty simple, but on it's own it looks a bit nasty; some of the syntax is plain horrible    
    
    
    @ironshay I'd say it's taken about 4-6 weeks on a real project to get properly up to speed and to really appreciate the lang/vm/libraries    
    
    
    @ironshay and I think I'd only try on a project that needed it (distributed and fault tolerance are the 2 key aspects of my current project)    
    
    
    @ironshay trying to learn it on a project where you don't get the full benefits would probably be quite frustrating    
    
    
    @ironshay that said, now I know it I can't really imagine using anything else for server-side code    
    
    
    @ironshay I'd be happy to    
    
    
    England. And it's pissing it down. #noraincoat #stupid    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! Bon Voyage! http://4sq.com/uEAWDt     
    
    
    @hhariri you might get a call from a company in London that I've been helping out this week - they are in need of some IntelliJ love...    
    
    
    Crazy week in london. Heading home now, thank goodness. Although would be better if I didn't have to perform a system upgrade tonight!    
    
    
    Having spent a couple of days deep in java, j2ee, ejb's etc, looking forward very much to be back in world of erlang next week    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn we really aren't timing this well ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri no probs. we should do tapas sometime ;)    
    
    
    We appear to be taking off. Guess I should turn on flight mode...    
    
    
    I just ousted @niconlyone as the mayor of Marbella British School on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/b7e67A     
    
    
    Have a contact in Gibraltar who's looking for a senior java dev (strong c# skills would be fine as well) - ping me if interested, please rt    
    
    
    @hhariri you know any good java or web front end chaps down here that might be interested in a gig in gib?    
    
    
    @intellectdk at this stage, employment. If they fail to find anyone, then contract maybe an option    
    
    
    @joseph_carney stood somewhere on your street. Turns out I don't have your number...    
    
    
    @nicchick Not of the top of my head - guess I still need to write that thing I promised you months ago...    
    
    
    @joseph_carney @calendapp (blush)    
    
    
    @joseph_carney plenty of space in the office if you ever wanted to camp here for a bit :)    
    
    
    @joseph_carney :)    
    
    
    Not sure I've ever been this busy, loads of very fun projects underway and less than 24 hours before flying to the alps. Happy days :)    
    
    
    Parsing / writing binary formats in #erlang is *so* much easier than any other language I've ever used - I'd almost call it pleasurable!    
    
    
    Wondered what the sauce was that's on the table at the Chinese. So dipped my finger in and had a suck. Now have an inferno in my mouth...    
    
    
    Think it was some form of molten lava    
    
    
    @nicchick Nope, in the UK I'm afraid :(    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Superstar" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/AgdAH4     
    
    
    @hhariri :) damn them for tweeting without asking!    
    
    
    @hhariri btw, it's 0615 on a Sunday - what the hell are you doing reading twitter?!    
    
    
    @martinstillman yeah, early flight out of Geneva, did suck somewhat!    
    
    
    @joseph_carney this morning, I call myself "knackered"    
    
    
    Just signed up for SourceNinja, anyone got access to it? Does it work? Subscribe link is http://www.sourceninja.com/sign-up.html?ref=hkm3w …    
    
    
    @awashtell don't do it. Life is too short...    
    
    
    @dagda1 I feel your pain; now that the honeymoon period is over, I feel much the same about my galaxy s    
    
    
    @joseph_carney :)    
    
    
    @joseph_carney for the right job, I think it's fantastic. It's not perfect for everything, and the learning curve is pretty steep    
    
    
    @joseph_carney but  for the right problems it's a great tool    
    
    
    Anyone in London fancy beers? #shortnotice    
    
    
    @oakinger yeah, thinking 9:30 was probably too late to be asking ;) Next time maybe...    
    
    
    Been with a potential blue chip client tonight.  Apparently they do "agile". Their sprints are 9 months long. Go figure :D    
    
    
    @neil_rees :) that was #ReallyShortNotice - back at my desk in Spain now    
    
    
    @neil_rees how r things going with u? Having fun with the new venture?    
    
    
    @neil_rees hehe, yeah, was a bit of a flying visit this one.  And I know what you mean ;)    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of La Fishita on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/wy6d31     
    
    
    @NeilRobbins it is indeed :)    
    
    
    I just ousted @josema_ms as the mayor of Aqua Wellness Center on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/qo963e     
    
    
    @oakinger a friend of mine is running Ubuntu as the host; he's looking forward to getting a mac to get a better ui...    
    
    
    @oakinger I do 75% of my dev in osx, then switch to an Ubuntu vm for the remaining; it feels pretty painless and gets the bobw    
    
    
    @oakinger I barely use the mouse, but then I spend pretty much all day in iterm and emacs. What kbd shortcuts were you missing?    
    
    
    @oakinger that I can understand. I pretty much avoid java where possible; much prefer a language that is portable ;) #erlang    
    
    
    @NJenman I thought that when I got mine a couple of months back; would gladly swap for an iphone now. How r u guys?    
    
    
    Just fixed a bug that I've been chasing for three days.  Fix involved changing 3 bits.  Glad I'm not measured by loc/day...    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall done a couple - pretty basic, not sure I'd go as far as calling them applications, but they are certainly a single page    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins best coffee in the world. Only had bad coffee here once; it was in an English restaurant...    
    
    
    Arrived in gib early for my meeting. 25 1/2 hours early, to be precise    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn @neilrobbins @s_delcroix well, it certainly won't cost you much on bleach :p    
    
    
    Boo, #uksnow  has scuppered my plans to get to the company xmas party :( Going for a ruby instead    
    
    
    @ampgt @MarkNijhof people get distracted because they are human. Addressing that root cause is, um, complicated :)    
    
    
    Merry xmas & cheers to all at iMeta from Elaine :) http://plixi.com/p/64460217    
    
    
    So frikin' lame when a website emails me my password :(    
    
    
    Spent the last two months porting a large windows system to Linux, don't think I've ever worked so hard. One subsystem left, the end of...    
    
    
    ... the tunnel is in sight :)    
    
    
    Any good java devs out there that would be interested in a gig in London? Please rt...    
    
    
    @seanparsons lol :)    
    
    
    @seanparsons @awashtell @tpeplow guess I could stick out a call for average-to-poor java devs and see how that goes... ;)    
    
    
    @mikehadlow Ouch :( Hope you're feeling better soon    
    
    
    For the first time since January, we just did a successful end-to-end run of our system. Linux port almost there :)    
    
    
    @nicchick i think it got thrown out of court as ridiculous. No reference for you though, so might be imagining it    
    
    
    My daughters is eating chips with chocolate spread. It's so wrong.    
    
    
    @colinramsay chips as in fries. Really wrong, in my book    
    
    
    @JFXJames cheeky sod :)    
    
    
    Carrot, mince pie and a glass of juice prepared for Santa. Quick check with NORAD on progress, now time to get the girls to bed...    
    
    
    @DavidGouge tell me about it. We suggested something "stronger" but the kids insisted :(    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn Think I missed the "happy birthday" thing - hope you had a good one!    
    
    
    If the compiler's so damn smart at spotting my typos, why doesn't it fix them?    
    
    
    To the person that came up with the idea of using wire to package kids toys - I HATE YOU. Happy xmas btw :)    
    
    
    Splendid xmas lunch, happy xmas folks!    
    
    
    writing multi-thread C blows so many chunks after being in #erlang for the last 2 years!    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn *might* be in town Thursday lunchtime - fancy a coffee?    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn cool :) got a meeting near bishopsgate at 11am, suspect I'll be done in an hour or so. Where are you based?    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn how would a late lunch work? 2ish?    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn Cool - whereabouts?  Heading towards picadilly is no problem...    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn now that sounds like a plan :) dm me your mobile so I can let u know if I'm running late    
    
    
    Great to see some of the iMeta chaps tonight, a great bunch and I really miss them.    
    
    
    @Godders83 there was Simon, James W & James A, Stavros, Phil & Ben. 'twas good to catch up :)    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn twitter's managed to loose your dm, so don't have you number. Stood by the entrance to lillywhites...    
    
    
    Mmm, Saturday evening in the company of Wireshark.  It's just *so* rockstar...    
    
    
    @thisisspain since xmas and boxing day fell on the weekend, the bank holidays carry over to mon & tue. Back to normal tomorrow    
    
    
    Looking for someone for a dev support role based in Marbella - ideally keen and young, we will provide the training / mentoring, please RT    
    
    
    Role will involve web and erlang dev and support - prior experience not needed, but huge enthusiasm is a must! Degree etc not needed    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof nope, you're not too old, just too expensive ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri :)    
    
    
    @hasankhanbilal nope, applicants would need to be able to work in Spain/EU    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof :)    
    
    
    @neil_rees there we go. What twat thought that was a good idea?    
    
    
    Off to NYC in a week - somehow, I've never been before so quite excited :)    
    
    
    @hhariri odd that he feels he should ban something that he believes is impossible in the first place. Bunch of idiots. #landofthefree    
    
    
    Something very wrong in uk education - currently at a geek party in NYC and about 40% of the attendees are women...    
    
    
    In the UK, I'd be real surprised if the number was half that, to the detriment of the industry    
    
    
    Galaxy S has been away from it's charger for 5 whole hours now. Guess I shouldn't be suprised that it's about to die :( #sucks    
    
    
    If anyone wants to swap a factory-unlocked iPhone4 for a galaxy s, we should talk ;)    
    
    
    Apologies for the superflous "'" in a previous tweet; I hate it when I do that    
    
    
    @agross ah, maybe it was that seti thing I installed ;)    
    
    
    @oakinger www.currenciesdirect.com - I use them all the time and find them very good    
    
    
    @silverSpoon No bloatware here - I'm running a 2.2 rom without any operator crap at all.  I can get 3-4 days no prob.  If I don't use it.    
    
    
    @oakinger I've always been happy with them.  No commission and typically a better exchange rate than you get from the bank    
    
    
    @silverSpoon I'd normally get a day - I think something went rogue this morning; it got quite warm for an hour or so, but never tracked...    
    
    
    @silverSpoon down which app was at fault. Rebooted it and back to normal, but the damage was done.  On charge now, it'll be happy soon :)    
    
    
    Anyone on the costa-del-sol know where to get guitar strings from?    
    
    
    Griff Rhys Jones looking much better with shorter hair and goatee beard type thing    
    
    
    Modkit Micro: The Easiest Way to Program Microcontrollers by Modkit — Kickstarter http://kck.st/JZwGkR  via @kickstarter    
    
    
    @kkozmic I think I'd tend towards false    
    
    
    @hhariri @kkozmic but perhaps it's *not* incorrect design; perhaps it's reasonable for the calling code to have a null key    
    
    
    @hhariri @kkozmic where the api can do something semantically sensible (in the case, returning false), then I'd avoid the exception    
    
    
    @hhariri @kkozmic not really the place of api's to second guess if I'm writing bugs or not    
    
    
    @hhariri @kkozmic for something like Add, where the api can't sanely deal with a null key, then throw is clearly the right choice    
    
    
    @NJenman other way round, switched from iphone to gakaxy s. Don't much like it, can't wait for contract to renew so i can switch back :(    
    
    
    Happy 2011!    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 so far, 2011 appears to be much the same ;)    
    
    
    Gotta say London, those are some good fireworks    
    
    
    @awashtell Maybe they'll let you pay the 2d price if you don't take in the funny glasses...    
    
    
    Mmmm, 16GB of retina goodness on its way to Spain :)    
    
    
    @Imaji stood in a very slow queue at the airport. Nothing to do and then the apple store came back online :)    
    
    
    @Imaji didn't go for the fastest processor, 250 for an extra .1 GHz seemed excessive; also didn't bother with the 750GB disk    
    
    
    @Imaji yeah, but it's tax-deductible which helps a lot :)    
    
    
    Mmm, weather in London is delicious today :( But this time I *do* have my umbrella :)    
    
    
    @hhariri do you remember that really good burger menu that we found when we were at the science park?    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho much much clearer    
    
    
    @neil_rees über-cool :)    
    
    
    @jagregory been using sparrow for a few weeks, quite liking it    
    
    
    @jagregory throw erlang into the mix. 4 months now and still loving it    
    
    
    @alfredapp Since Sep 29, 2010, @alfredapp has been shown 1,084 times. Average 11.3 times per day    
    
    
    @alfredapp and I'm using way more now than I used too, so the average is probably misleadingly low    
    
    
    @jagregory sure - I'm using html/js/jquery templates and access the server via a rest interface using webmachine (a nice rest framework)    
    
    
    @jagregory we're using mnesia but have pretty modest needs. Woyld use couch if needed something bigger    
    
    
    @jagregory no real reason, mongo would be fine as well. It's also got apis available for mysql etc if you need relational    
    
    
    @jagregory No probs, let me know if you do use any - I'm pondering a .net to erlang course and will need guinea pigs ;)    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall @jagregory cool, I'll keep you posted :)    
    
    
    @jagregory guessing it won't be as easy - the learning curve is a bit steep but i think the benefits are enormous (imo, of course!)    
    
    
    @jagregory you on osx? If I recall, they were pretty straightforward - install erlang, bit wm and mochiweb from bitbucket, run make...    
    
    
    @jagregory but it was some time ago, so may be forgetting some steps. Don't bother trying on windows until you're used to things :)    
    
    
    @jagregory versioning is fun (as always) I've got clones of wm & mw here http://j.mp/gIPmRo - suspect they're out of date, but they work    
    
    
    @jagregory good plan, I've been building everything from source and found that relatively painless    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho sure, works just fine    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho need to have the mac on, at least on y setup I do...    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho agreed, that would be much better. Think it only works like that for music at the mo, although not tried that    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho ooo, interesting - will need to lookout for those. You had to buy DVDs for those? (but presumably not need to rip them)    
    
    
    @hhariri sounds like the world is attempting to recreate lisp, yet again :)    
    
    
    @hhariri hehe :)    
    
    
    @ecomba how often are you in madrid vs winchester?    
    
    
    @mhenders my 2012 mbp can see USB devices on my thunderbolt display just fine. Doubt that helps you much though :(    
    
    
    @mhenders that sucks :( you would have thought they'd have tested that combo a bit more    
    
    
    @IntelMediaSDK adding my vote for QuickSync SDK on Linux. Some positive news on this would be great    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri the mistake some make is to think that they are the same. Hosting gives SLAs, cloud gives flexibility but    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri typically at the expense of any useful SLA. If the flexibility is of value, you have to engineer your own SLA    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri our biggest cloud deployment to date (which maxed at 768 active servers) didn't even notice the AWS problems    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri and yes, it is hosted on AWS before you make wisecracks :)    
    
    
    @hhariri @howardvrooijen yup, i'd agree with that for sure    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri also agree - we're spread across 5 of the AWS data centers    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen @hhariri and when we find another provider that can do what we need, we'll be using them as well :)    
    
    
    @oakinger imagine how England would have looked!    
    
    
    @oakinger yeah, good point :)    
    
    
    @kkzmc I tend to switch caps-lock (which I never use) and Ctrl (which I use all the time).  Take a day or so to get used to, but works well    
    
    
    @tanukidata There's a restaurant there that does a really good chips + chilli.  Can't remember the name tho, so that's not much use :)    
    
    
    @adymitruk @adronbh bah, recently been working on a project that had over 6000 lines in a stored proc.  Truly horiffic!    
    
    
    @adymitruk @adronbh sad thing is that some folk didn't see what the problem was :(    
    
    
    @tanukidata yup, in atlanta. Spent some time there a few years ago    
    
    
    @tanukidata stone mountain park is nice, and it's a great walk up to the top    
    
    
    @tanukidata the 6-flags theme park isn't bad, and rafting on the chatanooga river is a blast (on the border with south carolina)    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen Looking good :)    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen Very well thanks, yourself? A Ringwood sounds like a fine plan - I'm over next week but fully booked, perhaps in Feb?    
    
    
    @JohnnoNolan *nothing's* gonna help that code ;)    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall Try redirecting the output (ruby -e 'puts "\342\202\254"' > o.txt).  Suspect if you then open o.txt in notepad it'll look ok    
    
    
    Any suggestions for good food near victoria?    
    
    
    @tpeplow you know that I don't drink. Oh, ok then, just this once. Tue, wed or thu eve next week?    
    
    
    @hhariri I've used it on occasion and found it useful    
    
    
    My Twitter BFFs: @hhariri @fabiomaulo @ben_hall @neilrobbins @nathangloyn @fransbouma @tpeplow. Find yours @ http://twitterbffs.com    
    
    
    @tpeplow Not sure I'm planning a trip into town this time, so Southampton would be preferable    
    
    
    @seanparsons Southampton for this trip, not sure I'll be making it into town    
    
    
    @garyshort Pretty sure that the can only see the 3.6GB.  Feel free to send me the other 12GB that you're not using :)    
    
    
    @neil_rees @null_loop @AntGardiner Have fun you guys, feel like I know half the company :)    
    
    
    @adean Ick, thought you'd been quiet.  Hope you're feeling better now, I guess I won't ask if you had a good xmas!    
    
    
    @alfredapp and it's installed already :)  BTW, any thoughts of putting task switching stuff in, ala Witch?    
    
    
    @neil_rees lol :)    
    
    
    @ironshay I'm using touiteur which is ok. How you finding battery on you galaxy? Mine sucks :(    
    
    
    @scottkowalczyk I think I gave up and moved to nunit.  If I get chance I'll spin up a project and see if it's started to behave    
    
    
    anyone know how to dynamically add a node to an erlang distributed application? #erlang    
    
    
    @greengar any plans for your whiteboard app to support collaboration over the Internet not just a LAN?    
    
    
    @awashtell just bind to the local address, then no one external will be able to even see you. Much like the casini web server does    
    
    
    @hhariri yeah, i think you're probably right :-)    
    
    
    @davidsb @hhariri lol :-)    
    
    
    @awashtell yeah, that would be the whole site. Nothing to stop you hosting multiple sites though, one public one private    
    
    
    @awashtell they could share either via back-end database or just transfer info via the request/response. Session would be harder :)    
    
    
    #olympicceremony nice one Mr Atkinson :)    
    
    
    #olympicceremony do they still need hard hats? Is the stadium not really finished?    
    
    
    #olympicceremony that, frankly, is the dogs    
    
    
    @gregyoung agreed, been playing with it for a week and it is very good    
    
    
    Installing the desktop experience feature on my Windows Server. Why? Because the flash encoder *command line* app needs it    
    
    
    The flash encoder GUI app works just fine without it. Adobe really are just shockingly crap.    
    
    
    @alfredapp Wow! Looks like you've had a busy day, but it's well deserved since Alfred rocks :)    
    
    
    To anyone with a Galaxy S, it's worth installing the One Click Lag Fix from the market. Awesome stuff, much faster    
    
    
    @mikehadlow Yeah, sorry about that :( It's top of my list    
    
    
    If anyone from the SQL Server Setup team is listening: I HATE YOU. That's all, bye.    
    
    
    @metcarob Yup, but the OneClickLagFix app includes a root function, so it should be pretty simple    
    
    
    Off to UK tomorrow, and Galaxy S now successfully unlocked. No roaming charges for me :)    
    
    
    Plus, helpfully there's just enough space between the case & the battery to stash the other sim card    
    
    
    Guess my warranty is shot to bits now.  Rooted, new rom + unlocked. Thinking that a warranty from telefonica ain't worth much anyhow :)    
    
    
    Had been playing with differencing disks on VirtualBox to save some disk space (Win7Base -> Dev Env -> Customer Dev Env)    
    
    
    It was working fine.  Until it decided to forget the differences. Loading up my Customer Dev Env to find vanilla Win7 was a real shame :(    
    
    
    @developerluke Yeah, had done that. The setup has been working for weeks, just decided to through a hissy fit this morning :(    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 I like it. It needed a few tweaks to get it running properly, but now I've done them it's running really nicely    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 I'd say that it's not quite as polished as an iphone, but it's great for a techy    
    
    
    @tpeplow No probs, will try to do a London evening on next trip    
    
    
    @incongruousm For now, just a stock Samsung rom (2.1); wanted to get rid of all the carrier crap that it came with    
    
    
    Morning coffee at malaga airport. Feel like I've been mildly robbed    
    
    
    working on tfs-backed project whilst offline. Preparing myself for world of pain later    
    
    
    @hhariri what you need is a secure voting platform :)    
    
    
    Bloody french airtraffic strike is going to waste at least 3 hours of my life stuck in malaga airport. Wonder if I can sue them...    
    
    
    Looks like I get to fly today, only 3 hours late    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn if all goes well, will be in the office soon after 5    
    
    
    London. Lappy battery lasted whole flight :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney :) was actually coding in a vm, very surprised it lasted    
    
    
    @jagregory until friday, but in southampton for most of the time    
    
    
    @jagregory Looks good, nice one :)    
    
    
    @jagregory Pex might help out if you want to test behavioural aspects.  But if doing so makes you rich, remember poor old me :)    
    
    
    @hhariri There's a yotel a T4 heathrow.  Don't know which side of security, but I'm sure http://www.yotel.com  will tell you    
    
    
    @hhariri @dbelcham Came up as 67quid when I tried; that's about what I normally pay at Gatwick    
    
    
    @tweetmarbella more hours in the day would be good!    
    
    
    @tweetmarbella don't think there's an "techy appeal" prob, for me it's just a lack of time    
    
    
    Wish Amazon AMI images built a bit quicker.  Seem to have spent most of the last couple of days imaging machines :(    
    
    
    @jagregory lol :)    
    
    
    Any recommendations for an free SSH server for Windows? There seem to be a number to choose from...    
    
    
    @KeithSpitalnick what do you need? Got some desks & chairs, a filling cabinet and a meeting table + chairs    
    
    
    @jagregory @jeremyskinner I also run everything in OSX other than VS, SQL etc which are in VMWare. VM's have between 1 & 1.5GB. Works fine.    
    
    
    One song would have been enough George, just one song.    
    
    
    @philiphendry at least he stopped when he did!    
    
    
    Wonder how much Liam pays his hair stylist?    
    
    
    They've let a fucking gun in!! Where was security??    
    
    
    It's official. Eric can sing better than Macca.    
    
    
    Fabulous :)    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner @jagregory :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof fantastic read :)    
    
    
    @NJenman very jealous :)    
    
    
    @NJenman guess there's nothing that travels to Aus that can take that sort of weight ;)    
    
    
    Awesome, got erlang running on my phone :)    
    
    
    @CAMURPHY those off-by-one bugs are the worse    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner one word. Emacs.    
    
    
    @jagregory @JeremySkinner i wasn't really joking about emacs. If you're going to spend the time to learn a new editor, might as well (cont)    
    
    
    @jagregory @JeremySkinner learn one that is on many sysyems. That pretty much narrows it down to emacs or vim; both are excellent editors    
    
    
    @jagregory @JeremySkinner ditto; always found the overhead of unity unnecessary    
    
    
    @AndaluciaWD that does look cool :)    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho teamviewer is the best i've found    
    
    
    @markrendle :)    
    
    
    @radtech Just seen the wavejamr - very cool.  Do you know if it works with the Audi MMI system?    
    
    
    Senior developer? Looking for a new challenge? Does this sound like a dodgy ad? :) We (iMeta) are recruiting, so if you're interested...    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Nope, you don't need to send it again, and Nick (the chap who runs with such things) will be in touch shortly to have a chat :)    
    
    
    To those asking where to send CV's, sstrong at imeta dot co dot uk will work just fine.    
    
    
    And for those asking for job descriptions, we're looking for a senior role. Coding, design, test, talking to customers etc would all be...    
    
    
    part of it. Trying to write that sort of thing in a doc is to restrictive imo, and I'd much rather just have a chat about what we need...    
    
    
    ... what you could bring and then we both see if the overlap is good or not. Make sense? :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Way better than my effort :)    
    
    
    @mikehadlow Hum, yeah, Spain might be tricky.  And alas I've never yet managed to work from the beach. Must aim to do that next year :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof LOL You're hired, when can you start :)    
    
    
    Just bit the bullet and tried to take my TFS solution back online. Guess what? It screwed up :(    
    
    
    @JYoung1756 The feeling is mutual    
    
    
    @averyj Not that I've found; if you find something please let me know!    
    
    
    @FransBouma thanks for the RT :)    
    
    
    Backup dir. Delete workspace. Create new workspace. Get latest. Point winmerge at backup and new dir. Merge. Run tests. Commit. Thanks TFS.    
    
    
    RIP Neil Armstrong :(    
    
    
    Any Ember experts fancy taking a look at this http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12186089/nested-view-not-being-destroyed-when-transitioning-to-parent … ?  Thanks for any help :)    
    
    
    Any #emberjs experts got time to take a read of this http://stackoverflow.com/questions/12186089/nested-view-not-being-destroyed-when-transitioning-to-parent … and see if I'm on the right track? #noob    
    
    
    Good meeting in london and great food at the mango tree nr victoria. Now to gatwick for the flight home    
    
    
    @joe_carney I've stayed at the Art hotel in budapest, which was just fine.it was a few years back tho and don't remember if it had wifi    
    
    
    Just put a region in my code.  Shoot me now.    
    
    
    OH: OData - more bloated than video    
    
    
    Splendid day of remote pairing.  Although not perfect, VNC appears to be much better than SharedView    
    
    
    @jagregory Maybe they need some more memory...    
    
    
    Editing my .emacs file with Vim.  Doesn't feel right, somehow    
    
    
    The girls have topped the chips & chocolate sauce fiasco. Tonight's delight is naan bread with strawberry angel delight. Feel quite sick.    
    
    
    @WendyRees @neil_rees now that's plain nasty :)    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner yup, i also see the same    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner @jagregory Exactly the same here, need to quit it to get it to refresh automatically    
    
    
    @hhariri What's problem?    
    
    
    @alfredapp Installed, initial "smoke" test looks just fine    
    
    
    I've said it before and I feel it's time to say it again. I'm not a big fan of OData. #beingPolite    
    
    
    @adjames Not so much Atom, more the model when developing a custom provider.  It's just horrible.    
    
    
    @adjames Now that would be hard to describe in chunk of 140 chars :)  I'll happily email you if you want...    
    
    
    Hmm, might be pulling our little one out of school today; they seem to be doing some very odd things. #difficultDecisions    
    
    
    @hhariri Lucy. They have got too many kids and rather than creating a new class or putting some on a waiting list    
    
    
    @hhariri they are instead cramming kids of all ages into the classrooms. Lots of very upset parents at the mo    
    
    
    @tweetmarbella cool, I like that one :) cc: @jfxjames    
    
    
    @nicchick they are messing around with class sizes and she ranges. And not consulting with Amy of the parents. Pretty dumb, imo    
    
    
    @GoodCoffeeCode it does suck but fortunately there are dome good alternatives. Just hassle that we could do without though    
    
    
    @grahunt private :(    
    
    
    @nicchick I think it's a bit worse than disorganized, plus the current problems are more the final straw rather than the only issue    
    
    
    @grahunt @hhariri agreed, I think that's exactly what's happened    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner i've found nothing as goog as wlw. I use ecto, but it's not great    
    
    
    @nicchick if only I did always know best, life would be so much easier :)    
    
    
    @hhariri yup, I think it's sorted. Its been quite a couple of days, definitely getting the beer out tonight    
    
    
    @youeee if you want to read books, get a kindle. If you want to read, play games, watch movies, browse the web, get an ipad    
    
    
    @hhariri yup. Just had a chat with the head; she's out of there    
    
    
    @hhariri looking like the British school marbella, she starts monday    
    
    
    @hhariri @garyshort I've stopped playing and just left it to itself; seems to work best that way http://bit.ly/cy6JdW    
    
    
    @KeithSpitalnick if the weather's nice we will probably head in early (2 young girls, so can't be late!)    
    
    
    @olivers @shanselman I don't think lynx has it yet ;)    
    
    
    Looks like I'll be moving my office to marbella next week, will be just 5 mind walk from Lucy's new school. Quite excited!    
    
    
    Wow. Head out for a kiddies birthday party and a chinese meal, and return to find a minor war taking place in the twitterverse.    
    
    
    Spent most of the day telling Elaine "tonight I must do xxx", "tonight I must do yyy". Now it's tonight, and I can't remember a single thing    
    
    
    "Microsoft Visual Studio 2010 has stopped working"  Guess I will as well then, at least for the next few minutes.    
    
    
    Wish that my monthly UK trip had conincided with the Winchester #coderetreat, would love to have gone to that    
    
    
    Don't see that a Guaro #coderetreat is all that likely.  At least, not one with > 1 attendees    
    
    
    Trying to remember the last time I saw Emacs / VIM crash...    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 Chad & Scott having a slightly heated, um, discussion    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn pretty much my entire stream for the last hour has been occupied by 2 people. Quite an entertaining debate though :)    
    
    
    @chadmyers @adymitruk But we do have France right next to us... ;)    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 Ouch, hope you're ok :(    
    
    
    @nmerrigan Scott and Chad having, um, let's call it a discussion :)    
    
    
    @nicchick Splendid!  I knew if I waited long enough someone would do the thing that I'd promised you :)    
    
    
    @nicchick doesn't that website do what you need?    
    
    
    My first Ruby project just shipped.    
    
    
    Just to clarify, My first Ruby "project" consisted of one file. It just outputs some values from an XML file. Little acorns and all that :)    
    
    
    Although a little more seriously, the next big project that I'm about to embark on will be my first non-.Net commercial proj for ~10 years    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins :)    
    
    
    So what are the good dev podcasts at the mo? Not just .net, anything would be good    
    
    
    @ironshay dude, a Turing machine could build the same website, but who would want to program that ;)    
    
    
    @emadb Lost would be too strong a word; 90% of what we do is still pure .Net / Windows stuff    
    
    
    @emadb But we are about to embark on a big project (>200k) that may well not have a line of .Net in it, which is a big change for us    
    
    
    Contract signed for new office, move in on Wednesday :)    
    
    
    Well, that's some butt-ugly code I've just written.  Need to sleep on it then tidy it up in the morning.  It does work, though :)    
    
    
    @hhariri Dude, quick question - if I've got a big TFS CI setup, how hard to migrate that to TeamCity?    
    
    
    @neslekkim Written in Ruby & Java, I believe. Claims to be cross-platform    
    
    
    Love it when sql schema files can just be run over & over, and they just work.  Removes lots of pain.    
    
    
    That said, the very last thing this project needs is a schema, but the customer gets what the customer wants.    
    
    
    Hmm.  My Windows VM appears to have hung whilst installing updates during a reboot.  Reset it, and risk the wrath of Redmond, or wait...    
    
    
    And ever now and then, it flashes it's virtual disk light #teasing    
    
    
    Phew, the VM came back.  That took *ages*    
    
    
    Off to #dotnetdevnet tonight, just need to stay awake on the M4    
    
    
    Somewhat ashamed that my last NHibernate commit was the 7th July. How do folk find enough time for OSS projects?    
    
    
    @jagregory I neglected physical wellbeing some time ago    
    
    
    @jagregory It's got to be incompetence. I'm gonna leave OSS for a bit and build that darn time machine. It doesn't matter how long it takes.    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins Isn't that some green bird with a blokes hand up its arse?    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins :)    
    
    
    Finally done some Linq-NH work.  Now time for sleep    
    
    
    Loving the new office :)    
    
    
    So what's the story for async coding in #ruby?  Can I do async web requests? Would rather not be spinning off threads by hand...    
    
    
    can't believe the size of the node.js ecosystem http://github.com/ry/node/wiki/modules So much stuff for one so young!    
    
    
    Hitting the road for #dotnetdevnet...    
    
    
    @neil_rees Here's a couple: Software Engineering Radio, Herding Code, DotNetRocks (if you can stand it), This Developers Life    
    
    
    @GuySmithFerrier just thought, I've only got a dvi cable - if the projector is VGA do you have an adapter?    
    
    
    McVitie's Jamaica Ginger Cake is awesome    
    
    
    @WendyRees just straight from the packet :)    
    
    
    @GuySmithFerrier yup, Mac with mini-display port. I've got a display port to dvi adapter    
    
    
    Crazy indeed. But then... RT @MarkNijhof Blogged: A Crazy Idea: http://cre8ivethought.com/blog/2010/09/22/a-crazy-idea/    
    
    
    It appears that I am in the process of joining a 5-a-side football team. Those that know me will appreciate how ridiculous that is.    
    
    
    Fizzler rocks. But still can't get over the amount of stuff written for node.js. Really highlights the poor state of .net oss    
    
    
    @neil_rees cheeky sod :)    
    
    
    tree processing code is sometimes *so* elegant. It can also get shockingly bad    
    
    
    Anyone want Lock Modes in Linq to NHibernate?    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 just implementing a .LockMode extension method.  Fun bit is working out exactly what you want to apply the lockmode to    
    
    
    @GuySmithFerrier no worries, got it sorted :)    
    
    
    Successful evening, actually got some NH work done.  Commit tomorrow if all goes well    
    
    
    Looking for one or maybe two contractors for a short term project (~6weeks). Anyone interested?    
    
    
    @jasondentler Congrats!    
    
    
    The Nissan juke. That's one *ugly* car. Sort of thing that only its designer could love    
    
    
    @robconery whatever's best to solve the problem, assuming I know it enough to not f*** it up    
    
    
    @CAMURPHY agreed. Everytime I see an X6, I almost feel sorry for the mug that just spent a packet on it.    
    
    
    @theprogrammer you going to post it? Would be interested to see what makes the grade    
    
    
    @tigermain If he can send me a CV + contact details, that would be cool.  sstrong at imeta dot co dot uk    
    
    
    @fabiomaulo Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    @kkozmic there's one big difference - MS. Ruby doesn't have that and I think it makes a difference    
    
    
    @hhariri ? Not aware I wad blaming anyone for anything. Simply commenting on why I think oss is less well adopted    
    
    
    @hhariri and oss is only half the story; ms has all the other stuff (vs, biztalk, sqlserver etc)    
    
    
    @hhariri I for sure object when any big corp buys a smaller company just to squash them.    
    
    
    @hhariri so you're talking about when ms (or any other company) produce a product similar to one that's already commercially available?    
    
    
    @hhariri like, for example, reproducing r# functionality inside vs    
    
    
    @hhariri cos if so, that's very different to oss. With oss, Ms can adopt. They can't do that with commercial software    
    
    
    @chrissie1 well, that depends. If the deal was "here's a pile of cash, now go away" then that is of course just fine    
    
    
    @chrissie1 if the deal is "love your product, we're going to put lots of effort into it" and then it gets killed, not so good    
    
    
    @hhariri agreed. I well understand why ms don't adopt oss more, and I don't even think they are being "evil"    
    
    
    @hhariri I do think that their lack of oss adoption, with their preference to rebuild, has an impact on the oss ecosystem    
    
    
    @hhariri never said evil, you're putting words in my mouth.    
    
    
    @hhariri with oss they *could* adopt, they just choose not to (which is their right)    
    
    
    @hhariri with commercial, they have much less choice    
    
    
    @hhariri :)    
    
    
    @ironshay you still struggling with it? I just mount it as a mass storage device...    
    
    
    @ironshay settings / about phone / USB settings    
    
    
    @hhariri @joseph_carney :)  so you boys doing lunch sometime?    
    
    
    @AntGardiner Oh crap, that doesn't sound much fun :(    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen the guy on the Segway is a freaking loon!    
    
    
    Someone's cooking toast #smellsSoGood    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Glad you enjoyed it!  Thanks for a great night, hope the new job goes well    
    
    
    Love it when customers send me server logons with passwords via email #securityFail    
    
    
    love some folks idea of comments.  Class name = "TableOperationRequest", comment = "request for table operations". Awesome, thanks for that.    
    
    
    Even more awesome, just found a single class spread over 29 different files! SoC people, SoC!!!    
    
    
    @rogue_code :D    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Luckily for him, no, not one of ours    
    
    
    @RobAshton @Daneel3001 Oh, they use #region too.  Some of the 29 partial classes are just a bit too big to be seen in one go :(    
    
    
    @nicchick :(  Gonna be in Germany then.  Maybe the November one...    
    
    
    @ironshay cool, so the code I wrote 10 years ago is back in fashion :)    
    
    
    @tomasekeli well, a good map would help no end to find my way around the code :)    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 How are they doing that?    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 Yuck, that's nasty.  Really poor form.    
    
    
    Random Question: Anyone know of a UN speaker that does talks to primary schools?    
    
    
    Changing the case of a directory under git control is slightly dull in Windows    
    
    
    @jagregory @adlaneelm Seems to have worked - renamed to a temp name, commited changes, renamed again, commit again. Phew :)    
    
    
    Good evening's work.  Added about 20% more function to the project with 2% more LoC.    
    
    
    @kkozmic I agree; I find that even well written unit tests make refactoring hard. Of course, maybe my idea of "well written" is at fault :)    
    
    
    @alfredapp No idea if they have an API available, but if so getting Spotify support into the Powerpack would be great    
    
    
    @alfredapp Nice, I missed that.  I've added my vote :) And as a paid-up Megasupporter, I expect it tomorrow ;)    
    
    
    I change 4 .cs files, and TFS thinks I've deleted a .xml & changed all the .csproj files.  Nice.    
    
    
    @alfredapp Ouch, that's a mess. Hope the whiplash clears quickly    
    
    
    Simply one of the most exciting days I've had in my life. And no, I can't tell you why. Watch this space...    
    
    
    @ironshay used it some time ago    
    
    
    @hhariri One word. Yotel. Cheaps rooms by the hour in the South Terminal...    
    
    
    @ironshay I actually thought it was quite a good model, it just never got adoption.    
    
    
    Apparently 2 pancakes wasn't enough for breakfast #soHungry    
    
    
    @sarkie_dave Done that. Now I need a pee    
    
    
    @alfredapp Nope, keep 'em coming :)    
    
    
    Seem to have spent way too many days pounding a square peg into a round hole.  Nearly there though...    
    
    
    @dagda1 It does indeed; hql can handle way more than ICriteria    
    
    
    @hhariri Which I've never heard of, so guess we don't use it as often as you do :)    
    
    
    Thanks to Julian Maughan for his constant work in #NHibernate's #JIRA (via @fabiomaulo)    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @alfredapp Biggest new feature for 0.7.2 is persistent (through reboot) / searchable Clipboard History for Powerpack users! :)    
    
    
    @hhariri what's up with the lappy?    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen i'm using ecto, but it's not a patch on wlw    
    
    
    @hhariri doh, that's a bit of a shocker :(    
    
    
    @incongruousm Congrats :)    
    
    
    NHibernate 3.0 Cookbook is published!  http://bit.ly/9kxHK6  Table of contents & a sample chapter are online. (via @jasondentler)    
    
    
    Late night, and off to Germany tomorrow.  Time to pack...    
    
    
    Malaga airport. 1st leg to gatwick, then on to munich. Roll on the weekend!    
    
    
    @tanukidata  I see you're at the airport, fancy a coffee?    
    
    
    @neil_rees good picky :)    
    
    
    @tanukidata :) No probs.  I actually work in Marbella near the Copper Tower and am always up for a coffee if you're passing    
    
    
    Ok, 12 sausages was too many last night...    
    
    
    @WendyRees No such luck - 3 days of meetings. And 12 sausages in one sitting *is* too many :)    
    
    
    @elainestrong hehe, since when did you start reading twitter? :)    
    
    
    OH: question: What do Microsoft call their pre-alphas? answer: Releases    
    
    
    Office I'm at this week has got a 4Gb internet link; quite mental :)    
    
    
    Tax returns done with a full 2 weeks to spare :)    
    
    
    Finally home. That's been quite an intense week but got tons done    
    
    
    @tanukidata now that sounds like a plan :)    
    
    
    @hhariri 2.5 hour delay for me, but looks like we might be about to leave    
    
    
    Hmm.  Gone midnight, and we're editing the Erlang VM. Probably should be stopping about now...    
    
    
    @serialseb oh that sucks badly, bastards :(    
    
    
    @kkozmic mikogo works ok for that    
    
    
    Anyone out there used the ec2 create-tags command through the Query API? Can't get the damned thing to work and google is failing me...    
    
    
    @srstrong Nailed it - the library I was using had the version number wrong    
    
    
    Our first WP7 app goes public http://bit.ly/c0ic8f    
    
    
    My Twitter value is $266.95, according to http://www.twalue.com ... What about yours? #twalue    
    
    
    @pollingj Versions is very pretty, but I tend to just use svn from the command line    
    
    
    @neil_rees Nice one :)  How was the first day?    
    
    
    @gmciw I remember you gordon :) it's been a long time, how are things?    
    
    
    Got an mp3 file open in emacs, so much fun :)    
    
    
    Highly recommend the Food Poisoning diet, lost 6 pounds in 2 days. Side effects are a bit shitty though    
    
    
    Anyone on the costa del sol want a desktop case with cpu, memory & graphics? Just needs power + disks to work as far as i know    
    
    
    @GaryTapp it was a media center, so aluminum case, core 2 CPU, 2gb ram, good motherboard & gpu    
    
    
    @GaryTapp should make a good pc, should easily play hd movies. Probably not up to the latest games    
    
    
    @hhariri lol :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins it's more like 7 languages in 7 hours, but still a good intro to them    
    
    
    @jagregory Second one. At least I'd know where I stood    
    
    
    @jagregory 1st. If you do the second, you're probably breaking everything    
    
    
    @jagregory Assuming, of course, that the system supports incremental change    
    
    
    @jagregory In my experience, incremental changes offer better consistency    
    
    
    @jagregory Depends on the changes, depends on the system. Do I sound like a consultant?    
    
    
    @jagregory lol :)    
    
    
    @hhariri Mmm, insulated walls, double glazing, central heating. I'm toastie.  Must get gas later though, or the heating bit might stop :)    
    
    
    Thinking how much time I've wasted today scrolling past a certain conversation. Wonder how much time they've, um, spent on it    
    
    
    Awesome. Rackspace Cloud Servers API is currently unavailable. But they do apologize for the inconvenience, which is nice.    
    
    
    Wonder how long the #rackspace API will be down. Not seen this behaviour on AWS...    
    
    
    Anyone looking to relocate? http://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=4448655807027&set=a.1069593052570.12456.1008396985&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    @GaryTapp Graphics card is Gigabyte ATI Radeon 2600    
    
    
    @GaryTapp CPU is a Core 2 Duo 6600 if I recal    
    
    
    @GaryTapp And yes, as far as I'm aware it just needs a power supply + hard disk, everything else is, I think, fine    
    
    
    @GaryTapp It was a media center pc, but I've not had the time to fix it and I don't really need it now (Sky+ kind of took over)    
    
    
    @GaryTapp And I don't need another PC, so it's just sat in the shed. If no one wants it, it'll end up in the bin but that seems a shame    
    
    
    @GaryTapp I'm not looking for any cash or anything, just to put it to use rather than dumping it    
    
    
    @Ben_Hall I normally throw or log it in the Finalizer is Dispose wasn't called    
    
    
    @ben_hall is == if    
    
    
    @GaryMcAllister No, no nested stuff; kind of hard to do in HQL. Of course, if your entities have nested stuff then they will work just fine    
    
    
    @GaryMcAllister Getting full nested support is something that is/was on my wish list, but it's pretty hard to do    
    
    
    @ironshay @hhariri siesta? I wish!    
    
    
    @GaryTapp and disks, don't forget the disks! Based in marbella    
    
    
    Anyone know where i can buy stamps in marbella on saturday?    
    
    
    Missing #ddd9 :( Hope you all have a great time    
    
    
    @awashtell don't know tbh    
    
    
    id3as are recruiting:  https://docs.google.com/a/id3as.co.uk/document/d/1Z0_A36vflXbgcbj-7fY4ZPzmE0zqNiwc7yuQwbo4pJ0 … and https://docs.google.com/a/id3as.co.uk/document/d/1kD-iN5V5rEOmKfEO6ieKeUnO61WhMWvdh2Ikh6FoSeY …    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins @ferventcoder been using ec2 for some time, current project scales up to 300 concurrent servers. Not seen any big issues    
    
    
    @hhariri @jagregory i'm with James; mbp is 2 1/2 years old and i still get a good two hours when working it hard in a vm    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins :) It's a sweet one, for sure. Can't wait for the nda to lift so i can talk about it properly    
    
    
    @EhsanGhanbari @adean I remote-pair all the time.  Desktop sharing still a bit flacky; best is probably TeamViewer if you're happy to pay    
    
    
    @EhsanGhanbari @adean the other one we've started using is Chrome Remote Desktop; not quite as good at multi-monitor support but is free    
    
    
    Been playing with sql server, postgres, zootonic & websockets. Hugely frustrating at times, but the result rocks    
    
    
    @Imaji I found both 2009 & 2010 to be excellent; 2009 I paid for myself and didn't regret it    
    
    
    @Imaji I doubt I'll be going, although would like to. Compared to TechEd or PDC, I'd definitely go for NDC    
    
    
    @Imaji That said, if you go & 2011 is crap, don't blame me ;)    
    
    
    @Imaji :)    
    
    
    @hhariri btw, how's that chair you bought?    
    
    
    @hhariri what make/model is it?    
    
    
    @hhariri Might be interested, but want to sit in several first to see what suits best - where around here stocks this kind of thing?    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof I think I'd find that tough :)    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner I think I'd call that an adapter.  But I do like the answer from @FransBouma :)    
    
    
    Mmmm, access violations (c0000005) from SQL Server. Gotta love it :(    
    
    
    Although, to be fair, this is an unpatched Sql 2000 install. Off to see if some service pack somewhere sorts it out...    
    
    
    @hhariri I quite like my holidays :)    
    
    
    long shot - anyone got distributed transactions working between SQL 2000 & Postgres 9?    
    
    
    @hhariri awesome :)    
    
    
    @hhariri LOL! Yes, I really hope you're kidding!    
    
    
    Can't beat an evening curled up on the sofa with a good hex editor patching broken video files by hand :)    
    
    
    And in other news, welcome aboard to @MarkNijhof who has singlehandedly increased our head count by 33%    
    
    
    @hhariri @MarkNijhof pretty far? It's a mere stroll down the road ;) seriously, whilst mark's here we should do lunch - how r u next week?    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof http://emacsformacosx.com/     
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Being fair, never tried the brew install version.  But that web link always has pretty much the latest...    
    
    
    tmux rocks.  That's all.    
    
    
    @joseph_carney not on osx (although 'brew install tmux' works well) - using it when ssh'd into servers since it survives lost connections    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 Congrats!    
    
    
    @alfredapp @sparrowmailapp awesome! Love both apps :)    
    
    
    Any recommendations for good accountants on the costa del sol, ideally near Marbella?    
    
    
    @martinstillman I know them, but they don't do dull stuff like tax returns, just looking for a basic book-keeper down here    
    
    
    @hhariri Happy Birthday Dude!    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 @hhariri ROTFL! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MarkNijhof :)    
    
    
    @hhariri I'm sure I told the fricking thing to not tweet it    
    
    
    Apologies for the foursquare tweet, I'll try not to do it again ;)    
    
    
    @AdrianRoe :)    
    
    
    Excellent. Plane parks at south terminal. Bus now taking me to north terminal. Where I can then get the train back to south to get my car.    
    
    
    Oh yeah, it's frickin freezing as well. I think Spain has made me softer(er)    
    
    
    And for a technical tweet, tdd sucks, never could get on with it. bdd, however, rocks. Amazing what a subtle shift in thinking does.    
    
    
    The platform for the gatwick monorail would benefit from patio heaters.    
    
    
    @joe_carney what are you after?    
    
    
    Quite a day. After almost 11 years, I just made public my resignation from iMeta.    
    
    
    Still a director & shareholder and still very excited about the direction the company is heading in, but for day to day stuff...    
    
    
    ... I can add more value elsewhere. Emotional but also very exciting times.    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins thanks, me too :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney does the back end *have* to be php?    
    
    
    @joe_carney lol :) my preferred back-end is Erlang, it's just crazy-productive...    
    
    
    @joe_carney if that's an option then perhaps we should have a chat. If it needs to be php, then that puts me out since i've never used it!    
    
    
    @tpeplow thanks :)    
    
    
    @FransBouma new startup, suspect I'll get a blog out with details in the next week or two when the dust has settled    
    
    
    @joe_carney fly back Friday night, around most of next week. My office is in marbella    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner @mikehadlow thanks guys :)    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn details in a few days I should think, there's certainly a lot going on!    
    
    
    @joe_carney sounds good - Wednesday work for you?    
    
    
    @andyboyne lots lined up, shall probably blog about it sometime soon    
    
    
    @sbohlen thanks, fun times ahead :)    
    
    
    @mikeblakeuk really gonna miss the #footballthursday ;)    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen excellent post. We must try to fit a beer in on my next trip    
    
    
    @HowardvRooijen yeah, exciting times ahead :)    
    
    
    @neil_rees hehe, something like that ;) We must do a curry or something soon, it would be great to catch up    
    
    
    @AdrianRoe @neil_rees now now, let's not be rude    
    
    
    @neil_rees yeah, suspect I'll be over fairly often still. You don't get rid of me that easy :)    
    
    
    @incongruousm Thanks :)    
    
    
    @JYoung1756 All in good time :)    
    
    
    First patent application filed, bottle of beer opened :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof glad you're enjoying it :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof have we presented any evidence to date of being polite? I suspect not :)    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn @marknijhof You fucking cheeky bastard ;)    
    
    
    webex, why are you so shit?    
    
    
    @philiphendry thanks! It's been a long time - things good with you?    
    
    
    @mikehadlow wouldn't say it's focused on erlang, but for server side code I can't imagine choosing anything else at the mo    
    
    
    @mikehadlow more the approach to distributed processing and resilience, the functional nature is just an extra bonus    
    
    
    #github problems again?  Status page says all is good, my command line says otherwise :(    
    
    
    #github and now the status page is updated.  Somehow it feels better that it's not just me :)    
    
    
    Seriously, if you have the ability and inclination to do a big DDoS, aren't there more interesting targets than #github?    
    
    
    Really hoping that the DDoS attack isn't me hitting Cmd-R in my browser...    
    
    
    @darrenkopp hehe, entirely possible :)    
    
    
    @awashtell Loctite?    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof you bastard. I'm so tired now. @docker, you rock, love it :)    
    
    
    My god, what a day.  QA tests are passing though, and system goes live tomorrow :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    First inter-cloud failover from Amazon to rackspace done today - distributed erlang ftw :)    
    
    
    And yes, the customer was worried about the whole of Amazon going offline, hence the need to transparently failover to another cloud!    
    
    
    @FransBouma Hehe, yes, it is quite funny :)    
    
    
    Really wish one could image cloud VMs faster. Takes about 30 mins, which sucks when you're testing first-time-boot code    
    
    
    So that's probably about the 300th amazon server spun up today.  Stress testing this stuff is fun :)    
    
    
    @hhariri iPhone?    
    
    
    @hhariri Currently got a galaxy s.  Can't wait to switch back to iPhone    
    
    
    @incongruousm @hhariri Just don't like it much, nothing specific. It's nothing like as fast as it should be :(    
    
    
    @hhariri For the first month, it was great, but I think it was just "new toy" syndrome. Lacks the polish of iphone, imo.    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof it's good exercise :) We've only just got in, suspect there will be two grumpy girls up here tomorrow!    
    
    
    @ironshay I'd swap mine for an iPhone without hesitation :(    
    
    
    First auto-failover of telephone call worked like a treat - even when listening really carefully, could barely hear the transition    
    
    
    And none of your fancy high-speed lans here, the failover was from a rackspace server in Chicago to an Amazon one on east coaat    
    
    
    @tpeplow hehe, nay, patent quite unrelated. This is a customer project, but the details are all under nda so can't tweet details    
    
    
    @tpeplow Cheeky bugger ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri LOL :)    
    
    
    Loving our new website, thanks to @MarkNijhof.  For the first time in my career, it's a website I'm happy with :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof damned TTLs - no id3a what ours is set to...    
    
    
    Stunningly good day today, excellent meetings and interesting times ahead methinks    
    
    
    @awashtell @incongruousm It could be argued that benefiting the employer is an (indirect) benefit to the employee    
    
    
    @awashtell @incongruousm Although I would agree that there is relatively little direct benefit to the employee    
    
    
    @AmbientJobs I'd like to have a chat about that IT developer / manager role that you tweeted about earlier...    
    
    
    Windows Explorer is truly a piece of shit. Tried to copy a small directory from a share, and it just sits there "discovering"    
    
    
    after 5 minutes, it discovered that I could click the cancel button, and do the same job from the command line in ~10 seconds    
    
    
    Really not quite sure how you can get it that badly wrong    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins currently rewriting a c++ app in c - it's now *so* much easier to read. Although that may be c++'s fault rather  that OO ;)    
    
    
    @awashtell hehe :) Agreed on pretty much all points    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof now that's just cheeky :) Not ignoring you, just been insanely busy this week. Maybe a Skype chat next week?    
    
    
    @nmerrigan alas no; would have liked to but have no spare time at the mo. Maybe next year, if they'll have me back    
    
    
    @nmerrigan gonna feel very jealous in june watching the tweet stream :(    
    
    
    @StClairJohn @nmerrigan :)    
    
    
    @robinhoodinn when do you guys open?    
    
    
    @ironshay there is a Mac equivalent, a sort of grey transparency style thing. Same reasons, but osx makes it look pretty    
    
    
    @jagregory *very* nice :)    
    
    
    @AmbientJobs Hi, not spoken to anyone yet - I'm guessing Karl is the chap I need to speak to - what's the best number & time?    
    
    
    @hhariri I believe that would influence most things negatively :)    
    
    
    @dagda1 you getting some erlang love as well?    
    
    
    @hhariri suspect chip and pin is going to cause them some problems in europe!    
    
    
    @hhariri makes me sick, these people who steal all our good ideas ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri we really should do some tapas soon. We can come up with some more ideas and then watch others do them :)    
    
    
    @hhariri "ideas" - now that's just a fantastic name for a company    
    
    
    @joseph_carney @hhariri hehe; we try not to focus on that bit on the letterhead :)    
    
    
    @hhariri @joseph_carney @MarkNijhof is it day or evening?    
    
    
    @hhariri @joseph_carney @MarkNijhof maybe up for that - @AdrianRoe is here as well, so depends if we've done enough work    
    
    
    @dagda1 Been heavily into it for the last 5 months now. My biggest issue with it is that I didn't start using it 10 years earlier    
    
    
    @dagda1 More the distributed & resilience characteristics, although soft-realtime side is a happy side-effect    
    
    
    @dagda1 What we've really found is the "crash early" approach dramatically changes code, very much for the better    
    
    
    @adymitruk Windows 2000 upwards: http://technet.microsoft.com/en-us/sysinternals/bb896768 …    
    
    
    Success. After a day of rebuilding the boiler, we have hot water again :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof my bad, crazy busy week.  But I've not forgotten :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof latency is really bad here :)    
    
    
    learning Dvorak. Slow going at the mo!    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof was that post that set me off; going for dvorak since there's more support for it. I remote a lot, so want a common layout    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof cos if I go for colemac, i'd need to install a keyboard layout on each machine i remote into. And I remote a lot!    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof plus, for a couple of erlang files that i analyzed, the difference between colemac & dvorak was minimal    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof :)    
    
    
    @philiphendry hehe, not vi, I'm an emacs person :)    
    
    
    Is anything open on the coast today? #costadelsol    
    
    
    So MS kill Axum http://blogs.msdn.com/b/maestroteam/archive/2011/02/28/the-state-of-axum.aspx … - the only thing they had in the pipe that looked really interesting. Bad call, I'd say.    
    
    
    Just hit 20 words per minute on the new keyboard layout. It's starting to gel nicely :)    
    
    
    @jamesogden rsi :( hoping that moving away from querty might help a little    
    
    
    @petebouch love that place, looks real sci-fi    
    
    
    @jamesogden throwing my code at some analysis software suggested that Dvorak or colemak would reduce finger movement by 50%    
    
    
    @jamesogden yeah, passwords could be fun :)    
    
    
    @AdrianRoe @jamesogden ooo, a zero *in the middle* Damn, that's gotta be some heavy stuff you're protecting to go to that trouble    
    
    
    @AdrianRoe @jamesogden um, potential customers will never ever read this, right?    
    
    
    Insanely busy. Barely time to read tweets, let alone post any. Current project is NDA'd, which is a shame, since it rocks    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn still alive :)  Things actually v.good, just completely snowed under. Not that I'm complaining, prefer busy to the alternative    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Looking forward to it.  Really must prepare that soon :)    
    
    
    4 weeks with no IDE, no debugger and no type safety. Can't say I'm missing it, feeling very productive    
    
    
    +1 Love it! RT @joefeser: Great Image found on the Github blog entry about dropping the database. ;)  http://yfrog.com/jwr3xp (via @hhariri)    
    
    
    @derickbailey We're having a lot of success with TeamViewer; trivial setup and seems pretty fast    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Using Erlang, which is helping enormously.  Nothing against .Net, btw, just not a good fit for this project    
    
    
    @seanparsons Got runtime safety :)    
    
    
    @diegose Still a .Net-head, just this one project that's doing something different.  It's requirements don't really fit the .Net model well    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn It's not the prettiest language in the world; it's syntax for records truly stinks. But the combo (lang + runtime + libs) rocks    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Erlang.  Still very much a noob, but enjoying it a lot    
    
    
    @awashtell :)    
    
    
    @seanparsons Erlang    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Maybe, depends if I've got anything demo-able :)    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn could maybe do a 10-minute session if there's time. Hello World is tricky, since it doesn't really show the strengths    
    
    
    @sermoa I'll let you know how I get on; inspired by your blog post, so you get the credit!    
    
    
    @JakCharlton I'd say they've pitched it about perfect; leapfrog the competition without pissing off existing users    
    
    
    @hhariri you went to europapark last year, right? How would it be for 3-5 year olds? Suitable or waste of time?    
    
    
    @serialseb @hhariri we're both still here - if you manage to pass by, would be great to grab a beer    
    
    
    @serialseb Really sorry to hear that, that sucks. There're some right twats in this world    
    
    
    TeamViewer just rocks    
    
    
    @sbohlen congrats!    
    
    
    @bitterSTAR really? We're getting really good perf, way better than anything else we've tried. What are you using?    
    
    
    @joe_carney just a quicky, you got any recommendations for osx programming resources (books etc)? Ideally low-level stuff rather than UI    
    
    
    @bitterSTAR Ah, the ipad app is indeed slower.  We're primarily on Windows & OSX, where it seems to work fine    
    
    
    If anyone's got either a high speed cloning process or a timemachine, please get in touch #fuckmeimbusy    
    
    
    @hyrmn lol :)    
    
    
    @Imaji awesome, let me know when you're done    
    
    
    Can't wait!: R15 may have structures (an alternative to records)! #euc2010 (via @samuel_rivas)    
    
    
    Damn you erlang.  I'm now sticking full stops at the end of my lines of C code.  Compiler getting really pissy with me :)    
    
    
    full stops changed to semicolons, C compiler now happy.  Lots of code done today, big integration tomorrow. This is *so* much fun    
    
    
    @Imaji ipad is currently 3.something; 4.2 due out in the next few days    
    
    
    @nicchick went to one a couple of years ago, total waste of time imo.  Plus, quite funny that their website has "lorem ipsum" on it :)    
    
    
    Initial impressions of firefox 4 are good, particularly like the tab groups. Only shame is the memory usage which is insanely high    
    
    
    Cracking morning with our designer, really liking the stuff she's doing. Hopefully soon be able to put something decent on the website    
    
    
    Really wish Rackspace could image & launch new servers faster. Testing first-time-boot code is tedious in the extreme    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks I doubt there's much you can do here, I know that imaging etc takes time. Just wish it were faster!    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks One thing you can talk to me about though is why I get so many failures when launching a new server from an image    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks I've had 2 failures tonight so far, having only successfully launched 5 or 6. Not a great success rate    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks Good to hear :) My current scenario is some code that only runs on first boot.  So to test it, I need to (cont)    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks edit the code, burn a new image, launch a server from the image, check the results (cont)    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks Turn around time is about 30 minutes, which is really dull.  A faster way to replicate first-boot conditions (cont)    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks would be cool!    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks Currently working on a really big system (around 300 servers at it's peak) with a blue-chip customer    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor @mwilbanks email sent, looking forward to seeing where this goes!    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Not forgotten, just me being crap :(    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof A kicking was deserved, I'd say.  I'll try harder :)    
    
    
    After an initial tweet for something that isn't really their problem, Rackspace are being very responsive and engaging in good conversation    
    
    
    Steve's Law: Big bugs are always found < 24 hours before a big demo    
    
    
    Debian or Ubuntu? Or another? For a headless-server.  Any opinions out there?    
    
    
    gotta love c: "warning: no return statement in function returning non-void" - how can that only be a warning?!    
    
    
    @jasonleegodwin Hey mate, long time! I've got a friend who uses your email service - is it possible for her to get her iphone to connect?    
    
    
    @jasonleegodwin I tried to guess a couple of settings, but no luck; can't see anything on the website - help!    
    
    
    @jasonleegodwin we must do lunch as well; I'm in marbella now so should be easier, be great to catch up    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MarkNijhof ping. You on Skype? Showing you offline at the mo    
    
    
    anyone had problems with the query slider (v1.8.11)? I'm getting really weird values from it, it looks pretty broken    
    
    
    @hhariri What was the joke? The natural language compile or php storm? :P    
    
    
    @hhariri :)  Drove almost pass your place today, if I hadn't been running late I'd have called in for a coffee.  We must do the tapas...    
    
    
    @hhariri Ah, coffee with your wife would have be even better :D    
    
    
    Twitter has just suggested that I'm similar to @martinfowler. That's either a huge compliment, or an indication of how flawed they are :)    
    
    
    @fulljames Done :)    
    
    
    I though the sql server install was bad. Turns out the intellisense support is even worse    
    
    
    Mmmm, emacs has a sql-ms mode.  Goodbye, Management Studio...    
    
    
    @neil_rees Have you seen emacs ;)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins No need for cygwin, it works just fine on its own http://ftp.gnu.org/gnu/emacs/windows/emacs-23.3-bin-i386.zip …    
    
    
    @gmciw it's owned by some friends, so got to help with the publicity. Plus they are going to have real beer :)    
    
    
    @JeremySkinner thought it was in xcode 3 as well    
    
    
    Sat in the notary. Very bored, this is taking forever :(    
    
    
    Still in notary. Wonder how many man-hours are wasted doing this each day?    
    
    
    @hhariri @DeveloperDame other than asserts of course ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri Trying to setup team city with github - you wouldn't have 2 ticks would you?    
    
    
    @hhariri Any chance you can ping @AdrianRoe and lend him 2 mins - think it's just noob stuff and suspect you'll get a thru it in no time    
    
    
    @stack72 Thanks for the offer - luckily for you Hadi showed :)    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    Up at 4am to get to airport. Going to be a very long day    
    
    
    Spent the weekend in France, ate far too much bread and cheese, played with the kids lots and worked on my driver code. Perfect :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins what sort of probably are you having?    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins lol! Frickin autocorrect mis-correcting my typos :) was wondering what problems you were having with f#...    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins @Imaji ah, that makes sense :)    
    
    
    @hotgazpacho not many options :( try Mars edit or exto, they seem the best. Last time i blogged, I just used textmate...    
    
    
    1 hour sat in this damn queue. Gib & Spain really need to sort out the frekin border    
    
    
    Wonder if I can invoice gib or Spain for the time they have wasted?    
    
    
    Now parked right in the middle of the runway. Let's hope there are no flights due    
    
    
        
    
    
    @hhariri also, suspect Spain couldn't afford to pay :)    
    
    
    Yeah! Across the border :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins not been to Belgium for sometime; trips to landing are still fairly frequent - you ever back there?    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins let me know when you have dates and I'll try to sync my trips, would be good to have a jar or two.    
    
    
    One hell of a storm up in these mountains tonight, lightning flashing all around and some stonkingly loud cracks of thunder    
    
    
    One hell of a storm up in these mountains tonight, lightning flashing all around and some stonkingly loud cracks of thunder    
    
    
    Quite amusing reading some of the #aws stories. People, if you want resilience you *have* to be geographically distributed    
    
    
    Don't go bellyaching when one AZ goes down; you'll see there are 4 others, all of which were working fine    
    
    
    Only using one? Then I think the problem is more yours than Amazon's. I know a good little consultancy shop that may be able to help you ;)    
    
    
    @hhariri It's just their US East region that is having problems. US West, EU West and both APACs regions are fine    
    
    
    @hhariri If you care about resilience, you should have servers in more than one region    
    
    
    @philiplaureano It's not all down, not even close    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mikehadlow Erlang (full vm, language, database etc) comes in at 85MB. No IDE, but emacs is only another 35MB :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mikehadlow @hadleyhope But the main reason for that is I'm running OSX Lion, and Fusion does't work on that yet    
    
    
    @ironshay I use crashplan, seems to work well    
    
    
    The sun is finally out again, and the wife and kids should arrive home tomorrow :)    
    
    
    @ironshay I use it for about 5 computers; got a big external drive in my office that they all backup to    
    
    
    @ironshay us-east is still having problems, although improving. everything else is fine    
    
    
    Whoops http://blog.us.playstation.com/2011/04/26/update-on-playstation-network-and-qriocity/ …    
    
    
    @jamesogden Really quite spanky isn't it.  They really should get sued for negligence.    
    
    
    @NathanGloyn Damn glad they've not got any of my info!    
    
    
    @darachennis Beer will help, ei is lots of fun :)    
    
    
    Daughter has just asked the difference between spots & polka dots - um, help!    
    
    
    @RobGibbens @dylanbeattie awesome, thanks guys :)    
    
    
    @hhariri ooo, shall give that a spin layer on    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins Guess you like it then :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins That would be an interesting exercise, wonder how well the concepts would map over...    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins Also no clue, done almost no F#.  And yes, I'm sure you'd learn loads!    
    
    
    EC2 deployments now completely automated through some erlang scripts, working like a peach and going to save a ton of time :)    
    
    
    @mteper for scripting ec2? Almost no advantages, just that the rest of the system is erlang so it keeps things consistent    
    
    
    Got webmachine running behind nginx doing authentication with client certs, another job ticked off the list :)    
    
    
    First real load test today; at the peak we had around 750 servers running on EC2    
    
    
    @MarkNijhof can't say until it's gone live :(    
    
    
    Marmite man rocks!    
    
    
    Off to the beach    
    
    
    @KeithSpitalnick just down the road from you at El Rosario. What a fantastic day :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Using Knockout.js.  Simply awesome.  Great job @stevensanderson, I owe you a beer    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ironshay dude, I know it's late but...    
    
    
    Little one managed to fall off the slide this morning, so now down the hospital :(    
    
    
    @d2consulting lol :)    
    
    
    What a week. One horrific system-killng bug after another. Except now it's Friday, and they are all fixed. A beer tonight, methinks    
    
    
    @mworrell very cool, really impressed with the activity on the zotonic mailing list of late, lots of great progress    
    
    
    Can't believe I missed #tweetmarbella again, sounded like a good one. Maybe next month    
    
    
    @TimBarcz surely around 50% of (integer) results are multiples of 2 ;)    
    
    
    @martinstillman that one made me smile :)    
    
    
    @JakCharlton been running lion for about three months now, and even the dev upgrades have been painless    
    
    
        
    
    
    Any thoughts on a good advanced Javascript book?    
    
    
    @seanparsons A happy coincidence - made an otherwise dull journey most enjoyable. Hope you have a good week off, and say Hi to Tom tomorrow    
    
    
    TeamCity rocks.  That's all.  Night night folks.    
    
    
    @ismangil Are you still involved with pjsip?    
    
    
    @ismangil Thought so :)  Would you have a few minutes to talk about some jitter problems? We'll be buying a commercial licence etc    
    
    
    @ismangil Email on its way :)    
    
    
    @sermoa it's a good book, I think you'll have fun going through it    
    
    
    @sermoa shout if you need any help on the erlang chapter    
    
    
    @joe_carney new one on me. First impressions?    
    
    
    @joe_carney interesting stuff, shall take a look next week    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn mail in lion is reasonable, the other one I quite like is sparrow, which is great for gmail    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins how goes the erlang experience?    
    
    
    @Daneel3001 pretty sure they'll got swapped to disk if needed, can't think why they'd need to be fixed in physical memory    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins eunit does take some getting used to, but it appears to do the job, pretty much all we're using for all our tests    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins it took me around 2-4 weeks to start getting comfortable with it, quite a lot longer than other languages    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins that sounds like a job for foldl,  comprehensions rock but sometimes aren't the right tool    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins yeah, that was pretty much full time; I'm a slow learner though. Worth every hour, imo,  wish i'd learnt it years ago    
    
    
    @awashtell hehe, yeah, access is what you want :) that said, used properly Access isn't all that bad for simple stuff    
    
    
    @awashtell depending on your version, there's also SQL reporting services out of the box    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins How about https://gist.github.com/1023313     
    
    
        
    
    
    @srstrong erlang prefers to add to the head of the list; that's very fast    
    
    
        
    
    
    @NeilRobbins much as the fold version is smaller, for this problem I think a straight recursive fun is easier to read https://gist.github.com/1023380     
    
    
    @awashtell Doesn't sound mental, but also something I've never needed to do :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins https://gist.github.com/1023631  :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins BTW, don't for one instance take my solutions to be best practice! I'm still learning myself :)    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins it's not as bad as it looks - the bit that prepares the initial list and turns it into a square is a bit nasty,    
    
    
    @NeilRobbins is fairly straightforward. Thinking of a better way to make the square, since I don't much like that fun :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MarkNijhof @neilrobbins lol :)    
    
    
    @nicchick thanks!    
    
    
    @joe_carney ouch ;)    
    
    
    @ironshay @hhariri @jagregory @joe_carney @jongalloway first one lasted about a year. I expect the 2nd will fail as well sometime soon    
    
    
    @ironshay @hhariri @jagregory @joe_carney @jongalloway but it's so freakin fast that I wouldn't switch back. My backup rocks as well :)    
    
    
    Excellent sunday lunch at the robin hood inn, although it's blowing a gale down here on the coast    
    
    
    Hmm, seem to have clocked up almost 188,000 hours of Amazon compute time in the last two months #itsureaddsup    
    
    
    @hhariri @NeilRobbins hehe, yes, that would be a shocker :)    
    
    
    @hhariri probably cos it's a wmv...    
    
    
    @hhariri oops, forgot about that! I'll try to find out when it needs to be in the uk. In-laws are driving up in August so maybe take it then    
    
    
        
    
    
    @hhariri :)    
    
    
    @pdincau what's your blog's URL?    
    
    
    @pdincau cool, thx    
    
    
    @AntGardiner sounds like a blast :)    
    
    
    @philiphendry @tommyjmquinn you swapped from git to svn? Say it ain't true ;)    
    
    
    @tommyjmquinn @philiphendry But presumably not to move to svn ;p    
    
    
        
    
    
    @JYoung1756 @tommyjmquinn Now that's almost libellous :)    
    
    
    Distributed database and hot-spare clustered application researched, prototyped and deployed in under 3 hours. #erlang #rocks    
    
    
    Today has been distributed databases. Tomorrow is direct show filters and serial port control.software. Love the crazy variety in my job :)    
    
    
    Gecko in the house. Damn, those things are fast :)    
    
    
    @AndaluciaWD no chance of getting rid of it, have no clue where it raced off to :)    
    
    
    My little girl just won the school prize for Spanish #soproud :)    
    
    
    I may have broken my body #kitesurfing #firstlesson. Tons of fun though :)    
    
    
    Should be at customer site. Actually sat outside garage waiting for mechanic to arrive. Car not happy. Me not happy.    
    
    
    The customer visit was to do some sharepoint work. Perhaps the car is trying to save me.    
    
    
    @GaryMcAllister it wouldn't be my first choice, but the customer has it already so no real option to throw it out    
    
    
    Found a 7MB sharepoint config database.  With a 12GB logfile!!!    
    
    
    @karlseguin for concurrency, distributed systems and fault tolerance, go erlang. If perf is all you care about, try C ;)    
    
    
    To the man next to me in the traffic jam - why would you buy a *brown* Aston Martin? Lovely car, but brown???    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @duomark send me some id's please - I've not found many erlangers to follow on g+ yet!    
    
    
    @duomark I'm srstrong at gmail    
    
    
    @neil_rees getting into github? We're about 9 months in and I'd rather stick pins in my eyes than go back to tfs :)    
    
    
    Fighting with a soundcard on some custom hardware we're building - any opinions on the best Linux distro for broad soundcard support?    
    
    
    @sermoa lettuce soup is fantastic :)    
    
    
    Anyone running 8gb on a late 2008 unibody MBP (15", 2.8GHz)? If so, where did you buy it?    
    
    
    @wannabe_goddess If reading in bright sunlight is a must, get the kindle.  Otherwise (ignoring price) get the iPad; it's just awesome!    
    
    
    Geez.  Just signed up to a website that thought this was a weak password: cot2on7ju6wok8 - what the hell constitutes a string one?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Imaji Plenty of places with the ram, just trying to see how much I can cram in; seems to be vague as to whether mine will take 8 or not...    
    
    
    @jamesogden Dude! It's 14 long! 36^14 should be enough for anyone :)    
    
    
    Currently downloading winamp on an EC2 server.  Finding it quite odd    
    
    
    @stevemgentile Ah, ok. Google seems to suggest that although yours can take 8gb, mine is probably limit to 6    
    
    
    An evening of audio codecs, decompression, bit rates yadda yadda. Slowly getting my C foo back.  Not sure if that's a good thing...    
    
    
    @mikehadlow i've been in erlang for the last 6 weeks. Not missing the static typing much at all.    
    
    
    @mikehadlow the class of bugs that the compiler catches are easily found with the tests, which i need anyway    
    
    
    @chadmyers with EC2, you are charged for running instances, regardless of usage    
    
    
    @chadmyers @sbohlen ec2 pricing starts at 2c per hour, so about 15 bucks a month    
    
    
    @mikehadlow alas, all under nda at the mo, but it is a *very* productive environment    
    
    
    @mhenders might be interested in one of the macbooks for the in-laws - what are the specs and how much you looking for?    
    
    
    Stupid windows with your slashes round the wrong way    
    
    
    @adlanelm Bash, emacs etc. Should be on linux really, but one of our dependencies is windows-only :(    
    
    
    @tanukidata Do you guys supply hardware components? I'm in need of a power supply for a motherboard….    
    
    
    @tanukidata cool, where are you? Could I drop by sometime tomorrow?    
    
    
    @tanukidata Hey Joey, having problems with that ram module - any chance you'd be able to drop by my office so we can test the others?    
    
    
    @tanukidata I've already left for the day, but should be in anytime after 9.30 tomorrow    
    
    
    Thanks to @tanukidata for sorting out my hardware woes this week :)    
    
    
    Not tweeted for ages, been insanely busy. System goes live in less than a week, going through final acceptance tests. All looking good :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney we've been building a large cloud-based audio transcoding and archiving system for Reuters, been under nda the whole time    
    
    
    @joe_carney but they've just filed a patent on the technology used, so guess it's official public domain now ;)    
    
    
    @joe_carney you on the coast at the mo or travelling? If the former, we should grab a coffee sometime    
    
    
    @tanukidata @joe_carney I think it'll be cold by the time I get there :)    
    
    
    @joe_carney @tanukidata so if you're midway through, that means you'll be wanting a break midweek - coffee on Wednesday?    
    
    
    @joe_carney that's where my office is, so works for me :) sometime in the morning?    
    
    
    @joe_carney @tanukidata not sure yet, depends on kids and school    
    
    
    @hhariri @joe_carney go on dude, you know you want to :)    
    
    
    @hhariri Welcome back :)    
    
    
    @awashtell Got the S, not the S2. Hate it.    
    
    
    @awashtell Not used a 2, so perhaps it's much better. It needs to be, mine was pretty crap out of the box, very slow, very laggy    
    
    
    @awashtell Installing a custom rom helped, but I really don't expect to have to mess about with such things. Roll on iPhone 5 for me    
    
    
    @incongruousm @awashtell The problem with the S wasn't hardware, it was the screwed up Android install that samsung did    
    
    
    @seanparsons @awashtell @incongruousm guess they sorted out the filesystem they were using, or the h/ware is *so* fast it doesn't matter :)    
    
    
    @RoyOsherove TeamViewer works ok    
    
    
    @NJenman I'm on a custom one, not one of Samsung's.  About 9 months old now, but not sure I can be arsed to go through the upgrade pain :)    
    
    
    