I'm at the UVa-Navy basketball game courtside. Will be blogging tonight on AFP.... http://fb.me/1rAYHGwxU     
    
    
    First TV timeout: UVa 7-2 lead, 15:18. Not much happening yet. Mike Tobey gets start, hits first two shot. Joe... http://fb.me/2XPj8BBnJ     
    
    
    Second media timeout: UVa 15-7, 10:31. Joe Harris 7 points (3-4 FG), Mike Tobey 6 points (3-3 FG)... http://fb.me/ZGgAXucW     
    
    
    Third media timeout: UVa 15-12, 7:50. Modest 5-0 Navy run. http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uva-basketball-vs-navy/ …    
    
    
    Final media timeout of first half: UVa 27-12, 3:34. UVa on extended 12-0 run. http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uva-basketball-vs-navy/ …    
    
    
    Half: UVa 32-17  http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uva-basketball-vs-navy/ …

Major Internet glitches on press... http://fb.me/6A7meHBHn     
    
    
    First media timeout: Virginia 41-22, 14:18. No drama. Virginia has outscored Navy 25-10 since the 8-minute mark of... http://fb.me/N1W499AK     
    
    
    Second media timeout: Virginia 47-27, 11:07. Anthony Gill 10 points (5-6 FG) http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uva-basketball-vs-navy/ …    
    
    
    Third media timeout: UVa 54-36, 7:26. Joe Harris with 11 and Mike Tobey with 10 to lead the 'Hoos.    
    
    
    Final media timeout: Virginia 62-42, 3:15. Navy is 36 percent from the field, staying in the game (such as they... http://fb.me/6tBhSJoKu     
    
    
    Final: Virginia 67-42. Anthony Gill 18 points (8-9 FG), Joe Harris 16 points (7-8 FG), Malcolm Brogdon each with... http://fb.me/6obstI4C7     
    
    
    Virginia rolls to easy 67-42 win over Navy http://bit.ly/1arrPak     
    
    
    CAPSAW receives grant to provide free tax preparation services http://bit.ly/1dfRcj4     
    
    
    Report: Virginia is improving healthcare coverage for children http://bit.ly/1dg8YCA     
    
    
    Capricious Capers at WTA’s Gateway http://bit.ly/17MUhzc     
    
    
    JMU basketball drops home opener to Detroit, 71-67 http://bit.ly/1c2DOtu     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball escapes with a 61-60 victory at Liberty http://bit.ly/1c2DOtA     
    
    
    O, Canada! Virginia opens Agricultural Trade Office in Canada http://bit.ly/1c2DOJS     
    
    
    Augusta County Historical Society program focuses on Jack Jouett http://bit.ly/1c2DOK0     
    
    
    Capricious Capers at WTA’s Gateway http://bit.ly/1atT6ZD     
    
    
    FMS PG Basketball Today: Caissons sweep another weekend set http://wp.me/p3Su4c-193     
    
    
    FMS PG Basketball Today: Caissons sweep another weekend set http://bit.ly/1c2Z8zc     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Dec. 5 http://bit.ly/1dZErp2     
    
    
    Musical Murder Mystery Dinner Theater – Nov. 22-23 http://bit.ly/1bRzizV     
    
    
    History Lecture: Medicine in Waynesboro – Nov. 21 http://bit.ly/1bRziQh     
    
    
    Schools could benefit from change to Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credit http://bit.ly/1c3v46k     
    
    
    Tim Kaine introduces Senate bill to boost tourism at national parks http://bit.ly/1dipUbP     
    
    
    The latest on the stabbing of State Sen. Creigh Deeds http://bit.ly/1e0gKgf     
    
    
    Warner, Kaine introduce bill to authorize Petersburg battlefield expansion http://bit.ly/1diDyeW     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Invest in the young http://bit.ly/18QYan2     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Keeping up with the Kardashians … at Sears? http://bit.ly/1diUO3A     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Which mash is your match? http://bit.ly/1dj0HxJ     
    
    
    Waynesboro Lions Club to Support DSMP http://bit.ly/17OtsL1     
    
    
    Waynesboro Approves VPAS Tax Relief Request http://bit.ly/17OtuCO     
    
    
    Balloon Volleyball a Hit at Timberville Broadway Senior Center http://bit.ly/17OtuT2     
    
    
    Waynesboro Lions Club to Support DSMP http://bit.ly/1dj2gM8     
    
    
    William and Mary basketball loses to High Point, 80-69 http://bit.ly/1e3RPs4     
    
    
    VMI basketball rolls past D3 Bridgewater, 112-86 http://bit.ly/1e3RRQZ     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Manning vs. Brady, again http://bit.ly/1bUEbrK     
    
    
    Introducing Bluetooth Technology-Enabled Digital Hearing Aids http://bit.ly/17QMjoQ     
    
    
    Becca & the Cherokee Revival – Dec. 7 http://bit.ly/1c6GE0F     
    
    
    State Board of Education approves A-F school grading system http://bit.ly/1fnS9Wt     
    
    
    Senate votes for nuclear option, ending filibuster on judicial nominations http://bit.ly/1fnS9WE     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Lee Harvey Oswald, JFK, and the lone gunman theory http://bit.ly/1c7mofr     
    
    
    Farmers told sequester will result in payment cuts http://bit.ly/1azjeCq     
    
    
    VDOT: Route 727 bridge in Mount Crawford to open on Friday http://bit.ly/1azjeCw     
    
    
    Statement by Sens. Warner, Kaine on SCC finding on healthcare coverage http://bit.ly/1c7tkZO     
    
    
    JMU baseball announces four newcomers as fall signees http://bit.ly/1c7tj8m     
    
    
    Catholic pulls away for 85-66 win over Bridgewater women’s basketball http://bit.ly/1foXBbF     
    
    
    ODU basketball tops Presbyterian, 69-51 http://bit.ly/18UyPsj     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball wins 78-68 at Richmond http://bit.ly/18UyPsn     
    
    
    American Shakespeare Center’s 2013 Fall Season closing soon http://bit.ly/1fp5he1     
    
    
    Andy Schmookler: I’m betting on Mark Obenshain acting honorably http://bit.ly/1fpjJCH     
    
    
    Warner, Kaine introduce legislation to protect military whistleblowers http://bit.ly/1fpjJCJ     
    
    
    C. Robert Dickerman: Letter from 1963 views John F. Kennedy from afar http://bit.ly/17Un5Ge     
    
    
    Me to Crystal Abbe Graham: "Tomorrow will be fun. You probably haven't been to a UVa. basketball game in a... http://fb.me/2WYKRx54B     
    
    
    Former JMU basketball player A.J. Davis to make D-League debut http://bit.ly/17VwSf6     
    
    
    Rockingham County Fair receives international awards http://bit.ly/1dpr2dK     
    
    
    Gov.-elect McAuliffe announces Aubrey Layne as Secretary of Transportation http://bit.ly/1dpr1qc     
    
    
    CAPSAW releases request for proposals for grant funding http://bit.ly/1dpr2u4     
    
    
    JAUNT provides new service due to additional funding http://bit.ly/1dpr2u8     
    
    
    Chris Graham: No dishonor if Mark Obenshain contests AG race http://bit.ly/17VKjf3     
    
    
    @NL_CoryMull @NL_Sports it was 2000. Al Groh was the Jets coach.    
    
    
    #1 UVa. women’s soccer downs Georgetown, 1-0, now in NCAA Sweet 16 http://bit.ly/1bZsWhN     
    
    
    Bob Goodlatte: House Judiciary Committee to hold hearing on asylum system abuse http://bit.ly/1bZsWhP     
    
    
    Staunton Public Library invites public input http://bit.ly/1bZsWhR     
    
    
    Turnovers plague UVa. football in 45-26 loss at Miami http://bit.ly/1ceBXSl     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Another new low for UVa. football? http://bit.ly/1ee2LUb     
    
    
    This is not a typo: UNC football routs ODU, 80-20 http://bit.ly/1aHtcSl     
    
    
    Virginia basketball cruises past Liberty, 75-53 http://bit.ly/1aHzHEO     
    
    
    Valparaiso sweeps past James Madison men’s basketball, 81-49 http://bit.ly/1ef8KIn     
    
    
    Second-half meltdown costs VMI against Bucknell, 35-23 http://bit.ly/1ef8JnI     
    
    
    Bridgewater men’s basketball pulls away, defeats Greensboro, 73-56 http://bit.ly/1c1F2XU     
    
    
    Bridgewater women’s basketball holds on for 63-54 win over Guilford http://bit.ly/1c1F4Po     
    
    
    William and Mary football playoff hopes take serious ding with 31-20 loss to UR http://bit.ly/1fAc98k     
    
    
    UVa.-Virginia Tech football game time set for 3:30 p.m. Saturday http://bit.ly/1fAc98o     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices ticking back upward in advance of Thanksgiving travel http://bit.ly/191kt9L     
    
    
    Tim Kaine: Press forward in pursuit of peace with Iran deal http://bit.ly/1fAc8l1     
    
    
    Chris Graham: UVa.’s defense strangely stellar in giving up 45 to Miami http://bit.ly/180k5rN     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Greener ways to frack for natural gas? http://bit.ly/Ie5Mtz     
    
    
    VDOT road report: Nov. 25-29 http://bit.ly/1chDFCu     
    
    
    Staunton Rotary Club sponsors student from Denmark for International Youth Exchange http://bit.ly/1chDG9J     
    
    
    Battlefields Foundation raising funds to preserve Third Winchester http://bit.ly/1chDGq3     
    
    
    McDonnell announces milestone to advance Interstate 66 improvements http://bit.ly/Ie5O4D     
    
    
    A different kind of Black Friday in Charlottesville http://bit.ly/1iHZXlT     
    
    
    WVPT to present Ethan Bortnick Live in Concert: The Power of Music http://bit.ly/1jySEdO     
    
    
    RMH hosting American Red Cross Blood Drive Nov. 25-27 http://bit.ly/1jySEdS     
    
    
    Virginia men’s soccer tops St. John’s in NCAA Tourney, 2-0 http://bit.ly/1jySEdU     
    
    
    Penn State basketball defeats Longwood, 93-67 http://bit.ly/1i6Mpm8     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball tops Alcorn State, 87-42 http://bit.ly/1erX3ih     
    
    
    The streak is over! UVa. tops Virginia Tech, ends years-long losing skid … in wrestling http://bit.ly/1i71Uua     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball suffers a 68-58 road loss at West Virginia http://bit.ly/1i71Uuc     
    
    
    Taking the wind, not the ball? Bill Belichick's are made of brass.    
    
    
    Early winter weather possible Tuesday http://bit.ly/1cl90UT     
    
    
    JMU fires football coach Mickey Matthews after 15 seasons, national title http://bit.ly/1cllegn     
    
    
    State Board of Elections certifies Mark Herring winner in attorney general race http://bit.ly/1clYw7N     
    
    
    Stayin Country: http://youtu.be/-Lj7d6hMITs?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Augusta Free Press produces video commercial for Rawhide Productions’ Stayin’ Country Concert Tour http://wp.me/pPq8c-15y     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press produces video commercial for Rawhide Productions’ Stayin’ Country Concert Tour http://bit.ly/1cmaCxT     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press produces video commercial for Rawhide Productions’ Stayin’ Country Concert Tour http://bit.ly/1cmdxGO     
    
    
    Help the Bridgewater College golf teams help the Special Olympics http://bit.ly/1euJ3nZ     
    
    
    Price Rotary Senior Center Celebrated Thanksgiving Potluck Style http://bit.ly/1iMzlAa     
    
    
    JMU Sorority Raised Money for Meals http://bit.ly/1iMzlAe     
    
    
    Timberville Broadway Senior Center Advisory Council Meets http://bit.ly/1iMzmEe     
    
    
    SAW CDSME Steering Committee Meets http://bit.ly/1jDq1MC     
    
    
    SAW Centers to Distribute Prescription Cards http://bit.ly/1jDpZEu     
    
    
    SAW Centers to Distribute Prescription Cards http://bit.ly/1ia4uzM     
    
    
    SAW Centers to Distribute Prescription Cards http://bit.ly/1iMCcsJ     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press produced this video commercial for the Stayin' Country Concert Tour, featuring country music... http://fb.me/6vwub4AZp     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Surprised by JMU sacking Mickey Matthews? Not at all http://bit.ly/1iatpDl     
    
    
    Maybe now The Daniel changes the Redskins name not to be politically correct, but to try to create distance from this clunker of a season.    
    
    
    Augusta Free Press produced this video commercial for the Stayin' Country Concert Tour, featuring country music... http://fb.me/2Nuwqj8Wd     
    
    
    SMAC breaks records at Fall Invite Swim Meet http://bit.ly/1evS0NR     
    
    
    Winter storm complicates Thanksgiving travel http://bit.ly/1aR7njk     
    
    
    Update: Winter Weather Advisory in effect through 4 p.m. Tuesday http://bit.ly/1jGqFsN     
    
    
    VDOT: Use caution on roads in Shenandoah Valley, Central Virginia http://bit.ly/1crTtTm     
    
    
    International students add to culture at Fishburne Military School http://bit.ly/1crTruN     
    
    
    Mark Obenshain to ask for recount in attorney general race http://bit.ly/Imo9N9     
    
    
    YMCA Homeschool Fitness: http://youtu.be/OYALFO9qO68?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Waynesboro YMCA offers homeschool fitness program http://bit.ly/1idHTSL     
    
    
    Press Conference: Virginia Tech football coach Frank Beamer http://bit.ly/1idHTSP     
    
    
    Augusta Health Turkey Classic winners http://bit.ly/1eyEdGh     
    
    
    UVa. basketball routs Hampton, 69-40 http://bit.ly/1eyEf0R     
    
    
    State Corporation Commission adjusts Dominion Virginia Power rate of return http://bit.ly/1idHU9d     
    
    
    DuPont Community Credit Union wins top honors for commitment to community http://bit.ly/1idOvkd     
    
    
    City of Waynesboro to begin leaf collection on Dec. 2 http://bit.ly/1eyJAVO     
    
    
    Massanutten Resort to open ski area this weekend http://bit.ly/1idOvAt     
    
    
    Warner, Kaine call on administration for leadership to fix http://Healthcare.Gov  http://bit.ly/1idOyfP     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Turkey Carcass Soup http://bit.ly/1idOvAz     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Restaurants charge wait staff for dine-and-dash? Really? http://bit.ly/1ctmVIM     
    
    
    Becca & the Cherokee Revival – Dec. 7 http://bit.ly/1aV4RIR     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Dec. 5 http://bit.ly/1aV4QVn     
    
    
    I just don't see how this will sell memberships http://fb.me/2WJyhVzMi     
    
    
    Show Your Y Boxer-Waynesboro YMCA: http://youtu.be/St_gLYJ6SIY?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Show Your Y Boxer http://youtu.be/St_gLYJ6SIY  http://fb.me/KCCVw7b7     
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxers: Waynesboro YMCA Rings in the Holidays: http://youtu.be/e02b_ZpKJPk?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxer ... the Waynesboro Family YMCA is offering a Black Friday special. No joiner's fee, no... http://fb.me/2U8WO4Czz     
    
    
    New website for Blue Ridge Driving School produced by Augusta Free Press http://wp.me/pPq8c-15C     
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxer: Waynesboro Family YMCA riffs on viral video http://wp.me/pPq8c-15G     
    
    
    New website for Blue Ridge Driving School produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1eAXTJD     
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxer: Waynesboro Family YMCA riffs on viral video http://bit.ly/1igb5Ze     
    
    
    New website for Blue Ridge Driving School produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/Ik7idd     
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxer: Waynesboro Family YMCA riffs on viral video http://bit.ly/1boX0Fi     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Turkey Day sports http://bit.ly/1igqZTu     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Beyond Thanksgiving Day http://bit.ly/1eBeAol     
    
    
    My Clean Kitchen: Tips for a Happy Thanksgiving in the Kitchen http://bit.ly/1eBexsy     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell sets date for special election in Virginia House District 11 http://bit.ly/1igqZTy     
    
    
    Reddick scores 24 to lead Bridgewater basketball to win http://bit.ly/1igqXuV     
    
    
    UVa., Virginia Tech both have quarterback problems http://bit.ly/1aWBpSN     
    
    
    Bridgewater College releases updated Speakers Bureau listing http://bit.ly/1cxpOs6     
    
    
    Holiday farmers markets are ready for business http://bit.ly/1cxpMAr     
    
    
    Thoroughbred horse farm now grazes grass-fed beef herd http://bit.ly/1cxpOIs     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Forget Mike London, change needs to come in the culture at UVa. http://bit.ly/Il5D7e     
    
    
    JMU basketball loses at Winthrop, 69-57 http://bit.ly/1bpPnOZ     
    
    
    Show Your Joe Boxer: Waynesboro YMCA Promotes Black Friday: http://youtu.be/S5W2P2qRt0E?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    VMI basketball loses at William and Mary, 97-67 http://bit.ly/1iirVGZ     
    
    
    Thanksgiving Shopping: Major stores to open doors during the holiday http://bit.ly/1eDkC7L     
    
    
    #3 Tennessee rallies, defeats UVa. women’s baskeball, 76-67 http://bit.ly/1bsOWn3     
    
    
    AMC TV series seeks background actors http://bit.ly/Ioqiar     
    
    
    Chris Graham: No Black Friday for me, thanks http://bit.ly/1jP9Z28     
    
    
    Show Your Joes: And Give the Gift of Health and Fitness This Black Friday

http://youtu.be/S5W2P2qRt0E  http://fb.me/16li7vcfO     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Cleaning up local waterways http://bit.ly/1eGikop     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell to host statewide transportation conference ‘Road to the Future’ http://bit.ly/1il7FEL     
    
    
    Mark Herring announces Inaugural Committee co-chairs http://bit.ly/1eGikoz     
    
    
    Obama administration: Virginia seniors save $197M in prescription costs under ACA http://bit.ly/1il7FV8     
    
    
    Parking lot perils prevail on Black Friday, Christmas shopping season http://bit.ly/1cDx45N     
    
    
    Chris Graham: UVa. football actually does know how to beat Virginia Tech http://bit.ly/IwH0VG     
    
    
    Are behind the ear hearing aids right for you? http://bit.ly/1cDx4mf     
    
    
    Full results for the 2013 Turkey Trot at the Waynesboro Family YMCA: http://www.waynesboroymca.com/events/2013-turkey-trot/ …    
    
    
    625 on the squat    
    
    
    Internet here still down. #Comcast is about to lose a customer.    
    
    
    If we leave #Comcast this time, it will be the last time. #needinternetthatworks    
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball falls to Kansas State, 49-46 http://bit.ly/1j2Arb4     
    
    
    UVa. women’s soccer reaches College Cup with 2-1 win over Michigan http://bit.ly/1imA4KK     
    
    
    James Madison women’s basketball downs UCLA, 77-67 http://bit.ly/1imIaTA     
    
    
    UVa. basketball holds off stubborn SMU, 76-73 http://bit.ly/1imI91P     
    
    
    Virginia will be competitive today. If it's a game heading into the fourth quarter, it could get interesting. Big if there, though.    
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsVirginiaTech football http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uvavsvirginiatech-football/ … http://fb.me/1FBE5jrdW     
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsVirginiaTech football http://bit.ly/1cHeEB1     
    
    
    Way to go, Duke!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Pregame greeting for the two teams: It's about 60-4o UVa. fans.    
    
    
    Quick strike: Virginia Tech gets a 22-yard field goal from Erik Kristensen at 9:45 in the first quarter. Virginia... http://fb.me/PDeIlV4Z     
    
    
    Virginia responds: Alec Vozenilek good from 36 yards. Game tied at 3-3, 6:14.... http://fb.me/OKayJjvq     
    
    
    Virginia defense holds again in the red zone: Another Eric Kristensen field goal makes it 6-3 Virginia Tech at... http://fb.me/3hrurWKmj     
    
    
    One thing is for damn sure: Virginia isn't going to let Virginia Tech bully them around.    
    
    
    Virginia flirts with disaster: Indecision on whether to go for fourth-and-one. Alec Vozenilek connects from 30... http://fb.me/2OzB3vWP2     
    
    
    Third field goal for VT: Erik Kristensen's knuckleball makes it through the uprights from 38. Virginia Tech 9,... http://fb.me/21lfT2icB     
    
    
    Wow. Tech recovers onside kick. Ballsy call.    
    
    
    Sack/strip: Logan Thomas fumbles, Virginia recovers at the Tech 34.    
    
    
    Tech touchdown: Logan Thomas connects over the middle with Trey Edmunds on a 26-yard catch-and-run TD. Virginia... http://fb.me/6l7E9yKE2     
    
    
    First half stats: Virginia Tech 253 total yards. Virginia 165 total yards. Logan Thomas: 10-22, 205 yards, 1 TD.... http://fb.me/1BNRjMSoZ     
    
    
    Official attendance: 52,069    
    
    
    If I don't know you well, friendly trash talk is not friendly trash talk. It's just trash talk, and it makes no sense.    
    
    
    Greyson Lambert is warming up on the sidelines. Too little, too late?    
    
    
    Fast moving game. There are 28 seconds left in the third quarter, and it's not 6 p.m. yet.    
    
    
    Lambert in(effective): Greyson Lambert gets his first series of the game. An 0-for-3 three-and-out.    
    
    
    A group of very drunk, very annoying UVa. fans are in the row directly in front of the press box. It's getting to... http://fb.me/6tGvAcQul     
    
    
    End 3: Virginia Tech 16, Virginia 3. Stats: Virginia Tech 329 yards total offense, Virginia 213 yards.    
    
    
    Virginia is still in this game, but Virginia Tech has the ball at the UVa. 38. A TD here, and obviously the game is over.    
    
    
    Penn State is having a down year at 6-5. Two years after suffering the harshest sanctions in NCAA history.... http://fb.me/2wLszEAlq     
    
    
    I like the idea of being Greyson Lambert in the game. But you can't have Greyson Lambert running David Watford plays.    
    
    
    Virginia Tech's job on this next possession is to at worst get a couple of first downs and eat 3:30-4:00 off the... http://fb.me/QslC8jny     
    
    
    Virginia's job, conversely, is to force a three-and-out. Tech should still run the ball at least on first and... http://fb.me/2C8HrneTJ     
    
    
    Virginia has shown nothing since its first two drives in terms of ability to move the ball. Tech just needs to... http://fb.me/2DgdhtFqQ     
    
    
    Go for it here, and you get it, great. Tech runs the clock inside 6:30 at worst. Don't get it, and Virginia gets a spark. I kick it.    
    
    
    Virginia doesn't have two scoring drives in them right now. Why give them a chance?    
    
    
    Smart football by Frank Beamer. There's something new.    
    
    
    Kendall Fuller INT probably seals it: Greyson Lambert way off target after after a Parks' 48-yard run gets Virginia into VT territory.    
    
    
    This one goes to 10: Virginia Tech wins slugest with UVa., 16-6 http://bit.ly/1jVU0zi     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Tech fans serenade Virginia with ‘Ten More Years!’ chant http://bit.ly/1j5JesM     
    
    
    Job status of Mike London appears secure despite 2-10 campaign http://bit.ly/IvsNrD     
    
    
    @WHSVjaywebb @AFPChrisGraham Seems like he should be done, but that will come next year    
    
    
    James Madison men’s basketball comes up short at Richmond, 68-53 http://bit.ly/1bAMB9B     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball falls 65-52 to Mississippi State http://bit.ly/Ix8M3X     
    
    
    UVa. basketball tops Missouri State, 83-63, to win Corpus Christi Challenge http://bit.ly/1bAMzym     
    
    
    Local libraries help Food Bank, reduce overdue fines http://bit.ly/1bAMBq3     
    
    
    Mark Warner: Fix our bridges, roads and other infrastructure http://bit.ly/Ix8Oc0     
    
    
    Fishburne hosts Best Western Plus 2013 Caisson Shootout basketball tournament http://wp.me/p3Su4c-197     
    
    
    Fishburne hosts Best Western Plus 2013 Caisson Shootout basketball tournament http://bit.ly/1cJX3Z5     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: December 2013 Schedule http://wp.me/p3V9v2-lS     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: December 2013 Schedule http://bit.ly/1iqaG6K     
    
    
    Augusta Health Hospice of the Shenandoah annual Christmas Benefit Concert http://wp.me/p3V9v2-lU     
    
    
    Salvation Army benefit concert http://wp.me/p3V9v2-lX     
    
    
    Waynesboro High School Concert Choir performs on Dec. 15 http://wp.me/p3V9v2-lZ     
    
    
    Becca and the Cherokee Revival at WTA's Gateway Saturday, Dec. 7 http://wp.me/p3V9v2-m3     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: December 2013 Schedule http://bit.ly/IxFq5u     
    
    
    Augusta Health Hospice of the Shenandoah annual Christmas Benefit Concert http://bit.ly/IxFnX8     
    
    
    Salvation Army benefit concert http://bit.ly/IxFqlK     
    
    
    Waynesboro High School Concert Choir performs on Dec. 15 http://bit.ly/IxFqlM     
    
    
    Becca and the Cherokee Revival at WTA’s Gateway Saturday, Dec. 7 http://bit.ly/IxFnXc     
    
    
    The Concise Dickens’ Christmas Carol at WTA’s Gateway Theatre in Waynesboro http://wp.me/p3V9v2-m5     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: December 2013 Schedule http://wp.me/p3V9v2-m9     
    
    
    Salvation Army benefit concert http://bit.ly/1eMPJxU     
    
    
    Waynesboro High School Concert Choir performs on Dec. 15 http://bit.ly/1iqgqxf     
    
    
    Becca and the Cherokee Revival at WTA’s Gateway Saturday, Dec. 7 http://bit.ly/1eMPLWo     
    
    
    The Concise Dickens’ Christmas Carol at WTA’s Gateway Theatre in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1eMPLWw     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: December 2013 Schedule http://bit.ly/1eMPLWE     
    
    
    The Concise Dickens’ Christmas Carol at WTA’s Gateway Theatre in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1jYHGyo     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: December 2013 Schedule http://bit.ly/1j8t1mI     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball loses on buzzer-beater to Wright State http://bit.ly/IDGBRn     
    
    
    Down a man, UVa. men’s soccer advances to Elite Eight with 3-1 win over Marquette http://bit.ly/IDGB3Y     
    
    
    UVa. men’s soccer plays host to UConn. Friday in NCAA Quarterfinals http://bit.ly/1isyLty     
    
    
    Affordable Care Act helps National Health Service Corps increase access to healthcare http://bit.ly/1ePtaZl     
    
    
    RMH to host 27th annual Bereaved Parents Memorial Tree Service http://bit.ly/1ePtck4     
    
    
    Staunton Augusta Art Center December classes http://bit.ly/1cPDX3Y     
    
    
    Bridgewater College Equestrian Club hosts 12th annual Horses’ Christmas http://bit.ly/1cPDX42     
    
    
    ACC Football Players of the Week: Dec. 2 http://bit.ly/IHypQ2     
    
    
    Anthony Harris highlights four UVa. football All-ACC honorees http://bit.ly/IHypQ4     
    
    
    Local libraries: It’s time to get your geek on http://bit.ly/IHypQ6     
    
    
    Santa Claus to visit Churchville Library on Tuesday http://bit.ly/IHEg8d     
    
    
    Healthy Connections health event at Boys & Girls Club http://bit.ly/1cPLhwt     
    
    
    Supreme Court won’t hear case on state law prohibiting ballot petitions http://bit.ly/1cPLhMN     
    
    
    Small Business Saturday gives small businesses big boost http://bit.ly/1cPLhMS     
    
    
    Fishburne ranked second in national PG basketball poll http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19j     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Mike London stocks the cupboard for his successor http://bit.ly/1cQ0Q7c     
    
    
    Fishburne ranked second in national PG basketball poll http://bit.ly/1cQ0OfO     
    
    
    Waynesboro streetscape project update http://bit.ly/1jhFODr     
    
    
    Report: Virginia top 20 agricultural products in 2012 http://bit.ly/1k7dbX5     
    
    
    McDonnell announces major step forward in widening I-64 from Richmond to Newport News http://bit.ly/1k7oj6d     
    
    
    Augusta Health renews marketing relationship with Augusta Free Press http://wp.me/pPq8c-15L     
    
    
    Augusta Health renews marketing relationship with Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/IKshXv     
    
    
    Augusta Health renews marketing relationship with Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1eTEHqB     
    
    
    Shenandoah Area Agency on Aging has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://wp.me/pPq8c-15N     
    
    
    Virginia Fly Fishing & Wine Festival has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://wp.me/pPq8c-15Q     
    
    
    Shenandoah Area Agency on Aging has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/IKXr0J     
    
    
    Virginia Fly Fishing & Wine Festival has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1cTI6no     
    
    
    Shenandoah Area Agency on Aging has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1k81fV8     
    
    
    Virginia Fly Fishing & Wine Festival has new website produced by Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1k81hMI     
    
    
    Chris Graham: UVa. football woes are hurting my favorite website http://bit.ly/ILcVls     
    
    
    Richmond gives green light to traffic cameras http://bit.ly/1jj0s61     
    
    
    Risk manager offers steps to better market crops, livestock http://bit.ly/1jj0s64     
    
    
    Tickets available for Governor’s Holiday Hoops Classic http://bit.ly/1jj0uLp     
    
    
    Puppet Pandemonium offers holiday fun for entire family http://bit.ly/1eUlHrZ     
    
    
    Richard Adams Variety Show – Dec. 6 http://bit.ly/1kaLHA1     
    
    
    Bridgewater women’s basketball falls to Randolph-Macon, 99-81 http://bit.ly/1jlCOWK     
    
    
    VMI basketball loses at Elon, 87-70 http://bit.ly/1jlCQOa     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Mental health needs going unmet http://bit.ly/1kaXgqR     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Dec. 5 http://bit.ly/1eW8CyD     
    
    
    The Homecoming: Dec. 27 – 28 http://bit.ly/1eW8CP2     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special: Dec. 20-22 http://bit.ly/1eW8Aqg     
    
    
    Concise Christmas Carol: Dec. 13 – 14 http://bit.ly/1izsoVq     
    
    
    Former Waynesboro General Erik Kratz traded to MLB’s Toronto Blue Jays http://bit.ly/1eWJVSt     
    
    
    UVa., Virginia Tech women’s soccer in Women’s College Cup http://bit.ly/1iA6y42     
    
    
    Medicaid expansion and Virginia’s job gap http://bit.ly/1kbUykY     
    
    
    Chris Graham: McAuliffe, the inaugural and lobbying dollars http://bit.ly/1jmGhnH     
    
    
    Live Blog #UVavsWisconsin http://augustafreepress.com/live-blog-uvavswisconsin/ … http://fb.me/2Q2cyXM8y     
    
    
    Lots of empty seats less than a minute before pregame intros.    
    
    
    First media timeout: UVa. 6, Wisconsin 2    
    
    
    Second media timeout: UVa. 13, Wisconsin 11    
    
    
    Justin Anderson=LeBron James blocking layups on fast breaks. You have to know that going in.    
    
    
    This game is settling into the hockey game that we all expected going in.    
    
    
    Under-8 media timeout: Tied at 14. Akil Mitchell has three fouls.    
    
    
    Akil Mitchell with 3 fouls, Darion Atkins with 2. Good thing Tony Bennett has depth in the frontcourt this year.... http://fb.me/1vRlmnRHM     
    
    
    Feels like a Wisconsin run is coming. Wisconsin up 17-15, 4:37    
    
    
    8-1 Wisconsin run, Badgers lead 19-15, 3:34/1st    
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsWisconsin http://bit.ly/1jnkoop     
    
    
    The football refs they're using for this game don't seem to mind letting shooters get hit while putting the ball up on the rim, do they?    
    
    
    Half: Wisconsin 25, UVa. 20    
    
    
    The Internet on press row today is spotty at best. Almost as ugly as this basketball game.    
    
    
    A loss here tonight, and the best that you'll be able to grade the November-December portion of UVa.'s season is a... http://fb.me/R0ykG1Ir     
    
    
    Wisconsin controls on D, ups lead to 10: Badgers on a modest 5-0 run out of the locker room, up 30-20. UVa. calls... http://fb.me/P4Zjkjrp     
    
    
    Wisconsin 37, UVa. 23, 10:05 to go. UVa. has 10 points in the last 23:13. This game is over. Virginia will not get to 37.    
    
    
    My in-game stats aren't working. Not much here associated with UVa. is working tonight.    
    
    
    That three by Josh Gasser will be the dagger. Wisconsin 42-30, 6:19    
    
    
    Virginia has 30 points in 34 minutes. The 'Hoos need to outscore Wisconsin by 12 in the last six to win. Don't see it happening tonight.    
    
    
    My two seatmates on press row are from Badger Nation. i feel like I'm in the movie "Fargo" with the accents.... http://fb.me/1ZRBWsIif     
    
    
    UVa. still down 11 with 3:56 to go, and has 32 points in 36:04. A comeback here would be a miracle, and... http://fb.me/6qiSIiIGE     
    
    
    Virginia is 3-15 from the field this half and has made just 5 of its last 30 shots overall.    
    
    
    Just not enough possessions left. Wisconsin would have to go ohfer the rest of the way.    
    
    
    Four fouls in 20 seconds? Are you kidding me?    
    
    
    When a Virginia player gets hit shooting the ball, it's not a foul. When a Wisconsin kid is hand-checked 40 feet away, it's a foul.    
    
    
    One more Wisconsin basket, and it's over. Cavs have cut the deficit to 44-38 with 1:40 to go, but too much has to... http://fb.me/3ewGptcQP     
    
    
    And conversely, Wisconsin has to really screw up. A turnover, a foul on a three-point shooter, etc.    
    
    
    Duck your shoulder, run through a UVa. defender, and it's a foul.    
    
    
    Final analysis: You don't win too many games with 11 made field goals.    
    
    
    Nor do you lose too many games holding the other team to 28.8 percent shooting from the field. Except tonight.    
    
    
    Final: #8 Wisconsin 48, Virginia 38 http://augustafreepress.com/8-wisconsin-bludgeons-punchless-uva-basketball-48-38/ … http://fb.me/14bUvOI28     
    
    
    #8 Wisconsin bludgeons punchless UVa. basketball, 48-38 http://bit.ly/1jnCRkG     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Grading the UVa. basketball season http://bit.ly/1cYFvbS     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball wins at Pitt, 71-61 http://bit.ly/1bifQw9     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The bungled JMU football coaching search http://bit.ly/1f0mh7P     
    
    
    Prepare your trees for potential ice storm this weekend http://bit.ly/1iDTuec     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Conference title time http://bit.ly/1iDTwmn     
    
    
    Bob McDonnell to speak at Greater Augusta Regional Chamber of Commerce reception http://bit.ly/1f0mhoh     
    
    
    CDSME Presented Information to Virginia Power Retirees http://bit.ly/1iDTuuA     
    
    
    Fishburne takes control in second half, defeats Miller School, 107-87 http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19r     
    
    
    Fishburne takes control in second half, defeats Miller School, 107-87 http://bit.ly/1blsquw     
    
    
    Virginia women’s basketball falls 73-53 to Michigan in the Big Ten/ACC Challenge http://bit.ly/ITzowH     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Double-dosing on bone broth http://bit.ly/1jstfW3     
    
    
    AG’s office uses $245,000 taken from criminals to buy bulletproof vests for Virginia law enforcement http://bit.ly/1khyBkz     
    
    
    Applications for Conservation Stewardship Program due Jan. 17 http://bit.ly/1jstiRw     
    
    
    Wynonna and The Big Noise at The Paramount Theater http://bit.ly/1jsthx8     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell unveils mew Virginia is for Lovers license plate http://bit.ly/1jstiRE     
    
    
    Christmas story returns with Night of Miracles nativity village http://bit.ly/1blOsNG     
    
    
    Boise State's Chris Petersen to the University of Washington. UW wins ...... http://fb.me/1GvAoyyUG     
    
    
    Update - Holiday Giving Campaign #constantcontact http://conta.cc/1cf0oNZ     
    
    
    Chris Graham: What is a fair minimum wage? http://bit.ly/1d5ozAy     
    
    
    ODU hires former JMU football assistant Ulrick Edmonds http://bit.ly/IVIRDU     
    
    
    Terrible deal for Seatlle ... 10 years for a 31-year-old in the post-PED era. He might be worth $24 million a... http://fb.me/2yGU2UPck     
    
    
    Mathers Construction update on Valley Businesses Give Back http://bit.ly/1juzxUU     
    
    
    Mary Baldwin College physical therapy program meets key benchmark http://bit.ly/1kjNUsM     
    
    
    Waynesboro couple arrested in sophisticated marijuana grow operation http://bit.ly/1kjYMHi     
    
    
    Winners and Losers: A busy, busy sports day http://bit.ly/1juWYgZ     
    
    
    McDonnell: Virginia preparing for possible significant ice storm http://bit.ly/1d63MwF     
    
    
    Waynesboro Moose Lodge provides Thanksgiving to Vector Industries http://bit.ly/1bnI6gM     
    
    
    Pending ice storm cancels Bridgewater College Horses’ Christmas http://bit.ly/IWyLT5     
    
    
    National Weather Service issues Winter Storm Watch for Shenandoah Valley http://bit.ly/IWHXXA     
    
    
    JMU basketball losing streak now at five http://bit.ly/1d7MAXP     
    
    
    UVa. women’s soccer loses in PKs in College Cup semis http://bit.ly/IY3xLt     
    
    
    UVa. men’s soccer advances to College Cup with 2-1 win over UConn. http://bit.ly/1d7MyPt     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Greener holidays http://bit.ly/1da6QrG     
    
    
    VDOT preparing for coming Valley snow and ice storm http://bit.ly/J0awU3     
    
    
    Covering the Fishburne-Kiski postgrad basketball game. Bryant Stith (ODU) and Bruce Weber (Kansas State) are here.    
    
    
    Can't believe the #Kiski coach is still here. He got teed up arguing a call, then went into an extended tirade in... http://fb.me/2Pf0B8l6H     
    
    
    #Kiski leads #Fishburne 42-41 at half.    
    
    
    I sat for the first half with my former sports editor at the News Virginian, Jim Gordon, and the current sports... http://fb.me/6AHfMnpXX     
    
    
    #2 Fishburne rallies, knocks off Kiski, 76-63 http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19v     
    
    
    #2 Fishburne rallies, knocks off Kiski, 76-63 http://bit.ly/1iKZz8v     
    
    
    Bridgewater basketball upsets #20 Hampden-Sydney, 65-57 http://bit.ly/1brDczB     
    
    
    Sam Rasoul wins Democratic Party nomination in 11th House District http://bit.ly/1brDfeD     
    
    
    VMI basketball tops Wright State, 94-74 http://bit.ly/1brDfeJ     
    
    
    UVa. basketball loses at Green Bay, 75-72 http://bit.ly/1db9gX9     
    
    
    Chris Graham: What’s wrong with UVa. basketball? http://bit.ly/1iLl4Gq     
    
    
    Kansas State coach Bruce Weber in Waynesboro to watch FMS recruit Tre’ Harris http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19A     
    
    
    Kansas State coach Bruce Weber in Waynesboro to watch FMS recruit Tre’ Harris http://bit.ly/1kofeX4     
    
    
    Winter Storm Warning: Shenandoah Valley braces for ice storm http://bit.ly/1iMIevW     
    
    
    VDOT crews ready for winter storm http://bit.ly/1f9GV5s     
    
    
    AAA offers winter storm safe driving advice http://bit.ly/1ddqMdp     
    
    
    High school basketball event to raise money for American Cancer Society http://bit.ly/J3rq49     
    
    
    JMU basketball losing streak at six with 70-57 loss to Stephen F. Austin http://bit.ly/1ddqMtD     
    
    
    Like Augusta Free Press on Facebook. Thanks! http://fb.me/2Z7tDH2fs     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices retreat after recent uptick http://bit.ly/1desDP6     
    
    
    Report: Ken Cuccinelli rules out U.S. Senate run http://bit.ly/1bux2Pc     
    
    
    Mark Obenshain: Republican Advance http://bit.ly/1deQjCV     
    
    
    Virginia Tech headed to Sun Bowl vs. UCLA http://bit.ly/1deQiPk     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Baseball-Softball Academy winter clinics http://bit.ly/1deQiPp     
    
    
    VDOT roads report: Dec. 9-13 http://bit.ly/1buEXvW     
    
    
    Crime prevention gets a boost with new mobile reporting app http://bit.ly/1buEXMd     
    
    
    Staunton Senior Center Wraps Itself in Christmas http://bit.ly/J4NDyX     
    
    
    Christmas Tea kicked off the Holiday Season at Price Rotary Senior Center http://bit.ly/1buNj6P     
    
    
    Staunton Senior Center Wraps Itself in Christmas http://bit.ly/1buNkaF     
    
    
    Church Helps Seniors in SAW Region http://bit.ly/1deZDqc     
    
    
    ACC sends record 11 teams to football bowl games http://bit.ly/1jC3SAV     
    
    
    Waynesboro Senior Center Closed/No Meals on Wheels: Monday, December 9, 2013 http://bit.ly/1iOhrzi     
    
    
    Center Closed Dec 9 http://bit.ly/1dfpqPg     
    
    
    More winter: 5 inches of snow possible Tuesday http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWk     
    
    
    Democrats uniting behind Sam Rasoul in Roanoke House race http://bit.ly/1jEcIya     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press offers new feature: Message Boards http://bit.ly/1jEcIyb     
    
    
    More winter: 5 inches of snow possible Tuesday http://bit.ly/1jEcIyk     
    
    
    Shenandoah Processing to invest $2.2M, bring 102 jobs to Harrisonburg http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWu     
    
    
    Shenandoah Processing to invest $2.2M, bring 102 jobs to Harrisonburg http://bit.ly/1ktp7T7     
    
    
    We’re #1: Fishburne postgrad basketball tops national rankings http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWx     
    
    
    We’re #1: Fishburne postgrad basketball tops national rankings http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19E     
    
    
    McDonnell proposes new funding to help efforts to reduce homelessness http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWB     
    
    
    We’re #1: Fishburne postgrad basketball tops national rankings http://bit.ly/J8bWvP     
    
    
    McDonnell proposes new funding to help efforts to reduce homelessness http://bit.ly/1dizlUd     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe announces Inaugural Committee http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWH     
    
    
    Virginia Tech’s Jarell Eddie ACC Player of the Week http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWJ     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe announces Inaugural Committee http://bit.ly/J8xkkt     
    
    
    Virginia Tech’s Jarell Eddie ACC Player of the Week http://bit.ly/J8xicn     
    
    
    JMU basketball’s Jackson Kent Sslected as CAA Rookie of the Week http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fWM     
    
    
    JMU basketball’s Jackson Kent Sslected as CAA Rookie of the Week http://bit.ly/1jFPiZs     
    
    
    Winter Storm Warning now in effect: 3-6 inches of snow expected http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXo     
    
    
    Winter Storm Warning now in effect: 3-6 inches of snow expected http://bit.ly/1djMYCE     
    
    
    BIG NEWS coming next week about the Stayin' Country Concert Tour. Congrats to our good friends at Rawhide... http://fb.me/6z11VePZN     
    
    
    FSU’s Jameis Winston named Heisman Trophy finalist http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXq     
    
    
    Report: Wake Forest set to hire former Richmond football coach Dave Clawson http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXt     
    
    
    FSU’s Jameis Winston named Heisman Trophy finalist http://bit.ly/1jGXQPD     
    
    
    Report: Wake Forest set to hire former Richmond football coach Dave Clawson http://bit.ly/1jGXQPK     
    
    
    Center closed Tuesday, Dec. 10 http://bit.ly/1dljSTt     
    
    
    Please take a moment and like SaraJane McDonald on Facebook. SaraJane, from Rockbridge Baths, has been added to... http://fb.me/1dSSrNnIZ     
    
    
    VMI basketball races past UVa.-Lynchburg, 110-78 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXx     
    
    
    SMAC's Remedy Rule competes at USA Swimming Winter Nationals http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXA     
    
    
    McDonnell budget includes money for prisoner re-entry, restoration of rights http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXE     
    
    
    VMI basketball races past UVa.-Lynchburg, 110-78 http://bit.ly/1iTgeXE     
    
    
    SMAC’s Remedy Rule competes at USA Swimming Winter Nationals http://bit.ly/1fgGTZA     
    
    
    McDonnell budget includes money for prisoner re-entry, restoration of rights http://bit.ly/1fgGRRx     
    
    
    Senate confirms Patricia Millett for appeals court http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXJ     
    
    
    McDonnell announces new funding for mental health system http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXN     
    
    
    Senate confirms Patricia Millett for appeals court http://bit.ly/JbFzwp     
    
    
    McDonnell announces new funding for mental health system http://bit.ly/JbFCrU     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe applauds McDonnell's mental health initiatives http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXP     
    
    
    Everyday drugs in the ototoxic category http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXS     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: House passes legislation to help small businesses http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXU     
    
    
    McDonnell continues commitment to K-12 education reform http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXW     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe applauds McDonnell’s mental health initiatives http://bit.ly/J3m1cI     
    
    
    Everyday drugs in the ototoxic category http://bit.ly/J3m3S4     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: House passes legislation to help small businesses http://bit.ly/J3m3S6     
    
    
    McDonnell continues commitment to K-12 education reform http://bit.ly/J3m48m     
    
    
    House, Senate reach tentative budget deal http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fXY     
    
    
    Waynesboro Symphony Orchestra to perform in Waynesboro this weekend http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fY1     
    
    
    House, Senate reach tentative budget deal http://bit.ly/1fijhUn     
    
    
    Waynesboro Symphony Orchestra to perform in Waynesboro this weekend http://bit.ly/1fijhUp     
    
    
    Waynesboro Symphony Orchestra to perform in Waynesboro this weekend http://wp.me/p3V9v2-mc     
    
    
    The Concise Dickens’ Christmas Carol at the Gateway in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fY5     
    
    
    American Shakespeare Center rings in the holidays http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fY9     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The tweeting lawyer and Jameis Winston http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYc     
    
    
    The Concise Dickens’ Christmas Carol at the Gateway in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1do6HB9     
    
    
    American Shakespeare Center rings in the holidays http://bit.ly/1do6HBb     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The tweeting lawyer and Jameis Winston http://bit.ly/1do6HBc     
    
    
    I have 679 Facebook friends. Right now, 276 of you like my AFP Facebook page. That's pitiful. We can do better. http://fb.me/6vJ3HuVAO     
    
    
    Waynesboro Symphony Orchestra to perform in Waynesboro this weekend http://bit.ly/J4oTWO     
    
    
    The Homecoming: Dec. 27 – 28 http://bit.ly/1jNnHFC     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special: Dec. 20-22 http://bit.ly/J5LQsK     
    
    
    Concise Christmas Carol: Dec. 13 – 14 http://bit.ly/1jNnHW5     
    
    
    Blog: 2014 marketing trends http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYi     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Busy time in Virginia politics http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYk     
    
    
    McDonnell announces $2 million in Industrial Revitalization Fund grants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYm     
    
    
    Blog: 2014 marketing trends http://bit.ly/1iWSwtF     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Busy time in Virginia politics http://bit.ly/1fk5RHm     
    
    
    McDonnell announces $2 million in Industrial Revitalization Fund grants http://bit.ly/1iWSwK2     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Behind the scenes with the Redskins move with RG3, Cousins http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYp     
    
    
    Raymond Tanter: Iranian hunger strikers gaining unity and resilience http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYr     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Behind the scenes with the Redskins move with RG3, Cousins http://bit.ly/1dqWtzN     
    
    
    Raymond Tanter: Iranian hunger strikers gaining unity and resilience http://bit.ly/1dqWrIq     
    
    
    Andy Schmookler: Would you want to know http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYt     
    
    
    Andy Schmookler: Would you want to know http://bit.ly/1jPnGRJ     
    
    
    Hurt introduces bill to level playing field for generic drug manufacturers http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYy     
    
    
    LeeAnn Hall: Living wage job gap calls for charting a new course for U.S. economy http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYA     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Let’s hash it out! http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYC     
    
    
    All-ACC Football Coaches Team announced http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYE     
    
    
    McDonnell’s budget to continue commitment to making college more affordable http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYH     
    
    
    Hurt introduces bill to level playing field for generic drug manufacturers http://bit.ly/Jg3x9A     
    
    
    LeeAnn Hall: Living wage job gap calls for charting a new course for U.S. economy http://bit.ly/Jg3zys     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Let’s hash it out! http://bit.ly/1drz55k     
    
    
    All-ACC Football Coaches Team announced http://bit.ly/Jg3zOL     
    
    
    McDonnell’s budget to continue commitment to making college more affordable http://bit.ly/Jg3zOQ     
    
    
    Video: Wreaths Across America http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYJ     
    
    
    Video: Wreaths Across America http://bit.ly/1jQpQjS     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Army vs. Navy http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYN     
    
    
    Warner leads effort in Senate to exempt first responders from healthcare mandate http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYQ     
    
    
    Gov.-elect McAuliffe announces two Cabinet appointments http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYS     
    
    
    McDonnell proposes $11M for Richmond slavery and freedom heritage site http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYU     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Army vs. Navy http://bit.ly/1bI9cQ5     
    
    
    Warner leads effort in Senate to exempt first responders from healthcare mandate http://bit.ly/1bI9cQ9     
    
    
    Gov.-elect McAuliffe announces two Cabinet appointments http://bit.ly/1bI9d6p     
    
    
    McDonnell proposes $11M for Richmond slavery and freedom heritage site http://bit.ly/1bI9bf0     
    
    
    JMU baseball alum Kevin Munson selected by Phillies in MLB Rule 5 Draft http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fYW     
    
    
    Two Virginia schools in top five of Kiplinger’s 'Best Values in Public Colleges' http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZ0     
    
    
    UVa. researchers aim to slash number of donated lungs that go to waste http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZ2     
    
    
    JMU baseball alum Kevin Munson selected by Phillies in MLB Rule 5 Draft http://bit.ly/1bIvZvc     
    
    
    Two Virginia schools in top five of Kiplinger’s ‘Best Values in Public Colleges’ http://bit.ly/1dutVpb     
    
    
    UVa. researchers aim to slash number of donated lungs that go to waste http://bit.ly/1bIw2a5     
    
    
    Canceled: Gateway Theatre’s Concise Christmas Carol http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZ4     
    
    
    Canceled: Gateway Theatre’s Concise Christmas Carol http://bit.ly/1duCFM9     
    
    
    State Health Department forecasts arrival of seasonal stomach flu http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZ6     
    
    
    Farmers’ 2013 income up, but so are production expenses http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZ9     
    
    
    Poultry litter furnace test producing fertilizer and heat on farm http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZc     
    
    
    McDonnell announces additional $4.1M in Community Development Block Grants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZf     
    
    
    State Health Department forecasts arrival of seasonal stomach flu http://bit.ly/1duL16n     
    
    
    Farmers’ 2013 income up, but so are production expenses http://bit.ly/Jk696x     
    
    
    Poultry litter furnace test producing fertilizer and heat on farm http://bit.ly/1duL2qM     
    
    
    McDonnell announces additional $4.1M in Community Development Block Grants http://bit.ly/1duL16p     
    
    
    Augusta County man arrested after Waynesboro standoff http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZh     
    
    
    Goodlatte votes for, then criticizes, congressional budget deal http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZj     
    
    
    Augusta County man arrested after Waynesboro standoff http://bit.ly/1jVd5Ve     
    
    
    Goodlatte votes for, then criticizes, congressional budget deal http://bit.ly/1jVd5Vj     
    
    
    Harrisonburg/Rockingham County art teachers to exhibit work at Bridgewater College http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZm     
    
    
    Public hearing on improvements to Route 610 in Augusta County scheduled http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZo     
    
    
    Harrisonburg/Rockingham County art teachers to exhibit work at Bridgewater College http://bit.ly/JfgbVW     
    
    
    Public hearing on improvements to Route 610 in Augusta County scheduled http://bit.ly/1jX9HsV     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Starving government, stifling progress in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZr     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Starving government, stifling progress in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1j3i8VQ     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Cheaper natural gas lowering carbon dioxide emissions http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZt     
    
    
    McAuliffe nominates Brian Moran to serve as Secretary of Public Safety http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZv     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Cheaper natural gas lowering carbon dioxide emissions http://bit.ly/1dxpJVN     
    
    
    McAuliffe nominates Brian Moran to serve as Secretary of Public Safety http://bit.ly/1bM2LeO     
    
    
    Here we go again? Snow in the forecast for Shenandoah Valley http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZA     
    
    
    Here we go again? Snow in the forecast for Shenandoah Valley http://bit.ly/1dy01Ap     
    
    
    I was once a contestant on this show. Our Wilson Memorial High team finished second on the Central Virginia... http://fb.me/36aRoQUHT     
    
    
    Parrott Interior Video: http://youtu.be/e--gzL9FUrw?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Augusta County Library hosts annual Gingerbread House Workshop http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZC     
    
    
    DaVita Made $1,000 Donation to HR Meals on Wheels http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZF     
    
    
    Local Business Held Fundraiser for HR Meals on Wheels http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZH     
    
    
    McAuliffe Inaugural Committee announces Inaugural Parade participants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZJ     
    
    
    Augusta County Library hosts annual Gingerbread House Workshop http://bit.ly/JoOYRd     
    
    
    DaVita Made $1,000 Donation to HR Meals on Wheels http://bit.ly/1dyuMW2     
    
    
    Local Business Held Fundraiser for HR Meals on Wheels http://bit.ly/1dyuLkM     
    
    
    McAuliffe Inaugural Committee announces Inaugural Parade participants http://bit.ly/JoOYRl     
    
    
    North Central defeats Bridgewater basketball, 60-51 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZM     
    
    
    Maryland defeats UVa. men's soccer 2-1 in College Cup semis http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZO     
    
    
    North Central defeats Bridgewater basketball, 60-51 http://bit.ly/1jZJIRQ     
    
    
    Maryland defeats UVa. men’s soccer 2-1 in College Cup semis http://bit.ly/Ji1p0r     
    
    
    JMU women's basketball defeats Prairie View A&M http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZQ     
    
    
    EMU women's basketball wins at snowy Mt. Aloysius , 76-62 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZS     
    
    
    Greater Augusta Regional Chamber of Commerce to host legislative breakfast http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZU     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball defeats Prairie View A&M http://bit.ly/1k2jhuw     
    
    
    EMU women’s basketball wins at snowy Mt. Aloysius , 76-62 http://bit.ly/1kKozZm     
    
    
    Greater Augusta Regional Chamber of Commerce to host legislative breakfast http://bit.ly/1kKozZn     
    
    
    Bridgewater basketball downs Virginia Intermont, 84-69 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZW     
    
    
    James Madison men’s basketball streaks past High Point, 84-69 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-fZY     
    
    
    Bridgewater basketball downs Virginia Intermont, 84-69 http://bit.ly/1dCcrY1     
    
    
    James Madison men’s basketball streaks past High Point, 84-69 http://bit.ly/1bQ7V9z     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices continue to fall http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g00     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices continue to fall http://bit.ly/JvdkJ7     
    
    
    McDonnell’s budget to continue commitment to improving foster care adoption http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g02     
    
    
    Bob Goodlatte: Focusing on a pro-growth, pro-jobs agenda http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g04     
    
    
        
    
    
    VDOT roads report: Dec. 16-20 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g09     
    
    
    McDonnell’s budget to continue commitment to improving foster care adoption http://bit.ly/Joc1Lt     
    
    
    Bob Goodlatte: Focusing on a pro-growth, pro-jobs agenda http://bit.ly/Joc4XH     
    
    
    McDonnell’s budget to provide $55 million in funding for public safety http://bit.ly/1k4Nl8Z     
    
    
    VDOT roads report: Dec. 16-20 http://bit.ly/Joc21P     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball defeats St. John’s, 64-51 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0c     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball defeats St. John’s, 64-51 http://bit.ly/JpuabM     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special at WTA's Gateway http://wp.me/p3V9v2-me     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special at WTA's Gateway in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0h     
    
    
    Home for the Holidays with Earl Hamner's Homecoming http://wp.me/p3V9v2-mh     
    
    
    Home for the Holidays with Earl Hamner's Homecoming http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0j     
    
    
    Gov. Bob McDonnell unveils 2015-2016 state budget http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0m     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe comments on McDonnell budget http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0o     
    
    
    Staunton completes major grant-funded tree planting project http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0q     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special at WTA’s Gateway http://bit.ly/1k8n4qk     
    
    
    Home for the Holidays with Earl Hamner’s Homecoming http://bit.ly/1k8n3Ti     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special at WTA’s Gateway in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/JrTw8U     
    
    
    Home for the Holidays with Earl Hamner’s Homecoming http://bit.ly/JrTwpt     
    
    
    Gov. Bob McDonnell unveils 2015-2016 state budget http://bit.ly/JrTwFM     
    
    
    Gov.-elect Terry McAuliffe comments on McDonnell budget http://bit.ly/JrTz4z     
    
    
    Staunton completes major grant-funded tree planting project http://bit.ly/1k8oGR3     
    
    
    I'm a Dookie for a day. Going to the Duke vs Gardner-Webb game tonight with my friend Jerry Carter. In Durham now.    
    
    
    Me at the Duke Chapel http://fb.me/6pVQgRe8z     
    
    
    MBC Occupational Therapy Doctoral Program earns candidacy for accreditation http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0t     
    
    
    MBC Occupational Therapy Doctoral Program earns candidacy for accreditation http://bit.ly/1kRZZFQ     
    
    
    Recount, day one: Mark Herring increases lead in AG race http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0w     
    
    
    Recount, day one: Mark Herring increases lead in AG race http://bit.ly/1dKawkm     
    
    
    Area teacher writes, illustrates children’s book set in Staunton http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0z     
    
    
    Fishburne Military School varsity basketball wins Caisson Classic http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0B     
    
    
    Area teacher writes, illustrates children’s book set in Staunton http://bit.ly/1kSj3nm     
    
    
    Fishburne Military School varsity basketball wins Caisson Classic http://bit.ly/1kdwzVe     
    
    
    In the holiday spirit http://wp.me/pPq8c-15U     
    
    
    Open for business http://wp.me/pPq8c-15X     
    
    
    Political ad designed for candidate http://wp.me/pPq8c-160     
    
    
    Winter Y Magazine sent to printer http://wp.me/pPq8c-163     
    
    
    In the holiday spirit http://bit.ly/Jxyaa0     
    
    
    Open for business http://bit.ly/1kdY0OG     
    
    
    Political ad designed for candidate http://bit.ly/1kdY2pI     
    
    
    Winter Y Magazine sent to printer http://bit.ly/1kdY2pQ     
    
    
    Help Wanted: East Rockingham Senior Center http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0G     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press designs holiday cards for Vector Industries http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0I     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press designs holiday cards for Vector Industries http://wp.me/pPq8c-166     
    
    
    Jake’s Bar and Grill has new promotional rack cards produced by AFP http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0L     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press designs Roanoke Tribune ad for House candidate Sam Rasoul http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0P     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press puts wrap work on next Waynesboro YMCA magazine http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0S     
    
    
    Help Wanted: East Rockingham Senior Center http://bit.ly/1fCOmlU     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press designs holiday cards for Vector Industries http://bit.ly/1jfZMAM     
    
    
    Jake’s Bar and Grill has new promotional rack cards produced by AFP http://bit.ly/1jfZLgt     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press designs Roanoke Tribune ad for House candidate Sam Rasoul http://bit.ly/1fCOpho     
    
    
    Augusta Free Press puts wrap work on next Waynesboro YMCA magazine http://bit.ly/1jfZMAW     
    
    
    EMU women's basketball wins at Washington College, 58-55 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0V     
    
    
    UVa. women's basketball tops Maryland-Eastern Shore, 81-46 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0X     
    
    
    EMU women’s basketball wins at Washington College, 58-55 http://bit.ly/JG7cOh     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball tops Maryland-Eastern Shore, 81-46 http://bit.ly/JG7cOj     
    
    
    Mark Herring lead widens in state AG race http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g0Z     
    
    
    Waynesboro police: Nearly 50 vehicle break-ins since Thanksgiving http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g11     
    
    
    Could it be over? Painting work to wrap Waynesboro downtown streetscape http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g13     
    
    
    Damn.... http://fb.me/6AjPigch2     
    
    
    Mark Herring lead widens in state AG race http://bit.ly/1jh3M4i     
    
    
    Waynesboro police: Nearly 50 vehicle break-ins since Thanksgiving http://bit.ly/1jh3OZG     
    
    
    Could it be over? Painting work to wrap Waynesboro downtown streetscape http://bit.ly/1fDNwVX     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Jan. 2 http://bit.ly/JHvHum     
    
    
    The Homecoming: Dec. 27 – 28 http://bit.ly/1dNIUL1     
    
    
    Radio Hour Christmas Special: Dec. 20-22 http://bit.ly/JHvHuw     
    
    
    10th District Congressman Frank Wolf announces retirement http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g15     
    
    
    Andrew McKnight & Beyond Borders – Jan. 25 http://bit.ly/1khKMjT     
    
    
    Camille Moran: We can’t build a strong economy on a weak minimum wage http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g18     
    
    
    McDonnell announces $26.3M investment in Lynchburg, Campbell County http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1a     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Term limited http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1c     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: Bipartisan budget agreement http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1e     
    
    
    Gov.-elect McAuliffe taps Bill Hazel as Secretary of Health and Human Resources http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1g     
    
    
    Camille Moran: We can’t build a strong economy on a weak minimum wage http://bit.ly/1fEXtT2     
    
    
    McDonnell announces $26.3M investment in Lynchburg, Campbell County http://bit.ly/1jigwHL     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Term limited http://bit.ly/1jigwHU     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: Bipartisan budget agreement http://bit.ly/1fEXtT3     
    
    
    Gov.-elect McAuliffe taps Bill Hazel as Secretary of Health and Human Resources http://bit.ly/1jigzTX     
    
    
    Chris Graham: We almost let JFK happen again http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1k     
    
    
    Chris Graham: We almost let JFK happen again http://bit.ly/1kikjmg     
    
    
    Sam Rasoul endorsed for 11th District House seat by Sen. Mark Warner http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1o     
    
    
    Report: Mark Obenshain to concede AG race http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1q     
    
    
    Sam Rasoul endorsed for 11th District House seat by Sen. Mark Warner http://bit.ly/1c1r6NK     
    
    
    Report: Mark Obenshain to concede AG race http://bit.ly/1dOCyuO     
    
    
    One dead after small plane crash near Charlottesville airport http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1u     
    
    
    One dead after small plane crash near Charlottesville airport http://bit.ly/1dP6LtH     
    
    
    Vector Industries benefits from McKee Foods shopping spree http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1x     
    
    
    UVa.’s Anthony Harris named to SB Nation All-America team http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1A     
    
    
    ODU football adds seven in mid-year signing period http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1D     
    
    
    Mike Papi, Brandon Downes named to NCBWA Preseason All-America team http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1F     
    
    
    Virginia Organizing hosts ObamaCare forum in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1H     
    
    
    14:57 ... 14:58 ... 14:59 ...... http://fb.me/2XvELAygK     
    
    
    Vector Industries benefits from McKee Foods shopping spree http://bit.ly/JE3mo4     
    
    
    UVa.’s Anthony Harris named to SB Nation All-America team http://bit.ly/1kjIS2v     
    
    
    ODU football adds seven in mid-year signing period http://bit.ly/JE3mof     
    
    
    Mike Papi, Brandon Downes named to NCBWA Preseason All-America team http://bit.ly/JE3nbO     
    
    
    Virginia Organizing hosts ObamaCare forum in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1kjISiN     
    
    
    Speed limit to increase on stretch of I-64 in Albemarle County http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1J     
    
    
    Staunton awarded emergency food, shelter grant http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1L     
    
    
    OK, now I argue the other side of this. What he said was vile, but ... suspended indefinitely? Seriously? Ah, yes.... http://fb.me/Rg6ueum7     
    
    
    Speed limit to increase on stretch of I-64 in Albemarle County http://bit.ly/1fGoW6X     
    
    
    Staunton awarded emergency food, shelter grant http://bit.ly/1jjQXGc     
    
    
    Some big news about an upcoming Summer 2014 local concert featuring Morgan Frazier will be coming in the next few... http://fb.me/2GU44FgH8     
    
    
    Chris Graham: "Duck Dynasty" star suspension get us talking … about "Duck Dynasty" http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1N     
    
    
    Chris Graham: "Duck Dynasty" star suspension get us talking … about "Duck Dynasty" http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1N  http://fb.me/1AF9nQUIY     
    
    
    UNCG’s strong second half stops JMU, 78-65 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1P     
    
    
    JMU women's basketball nipped by Vanderbilt in OT, 89-85 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1R     
    
    
    Chris Graham: “Duck Dynasty” star suspension get us talking … about “Duck Dynasty” http://bit.ly/1kkgqgI     
    
    
    UNCG’s strong second half stops JMU, 78-65 http://bit.ly/1kkgqgK     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball nipped by Vanderbilt in OT, 89-85 http://bit.ly/JEEkoW     
    
    
    Senate passes budget compromise http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1U     
    
    
    Senate passes budget compromise http://bit.ly/1kknnhV     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Let the bowls begin http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1X     
    
    
    Fishburne drops to #3 in national postgrad basketball poll http://wp.me/p3Su4c-19M     
    
    
    Fishburne drops to #3 in national postgrad basketball poll http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g1Z     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Let the bowls begin http://bit.ly/1dS8caM     
    
    
    Fishburne drops to #3 in national postgrad basketball poll http://bit.ly/JLIITV     
    
    
    Alpha Vision Films documentary to debut on WVPT, RFD-TV http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g23     
    
    
    Nigeria ripe for direct foreign investment http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g27     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Holiday smoothie ideas http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g29     
    
    
    Christmas and New Year's refuse pickup schedule in Staunton http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2b     
    
    
    Monthly appointments with pharmacists improve medication adherence http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2d     
    
    
    McAuliffe announces Haymore, Ward for Cabinet posts http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2f     
    
    
    Virginia Trees for Clean Water http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2h     
    
    
    Farmers, USDA make case for funding conservation programs http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2j     
    
    
    Cuccinelli secures $33M for victims of illegal mortgage servicing practices http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2l     
    
    
    Monthly appointments with pharmacists improve medication adherence http://bit.ly/1c51Whg     
    
    
    McAuliffe announces Haymore, Ward for Cabinet posts http://bit.ly/1dTiG9Y     
    
    
    Virginia Trees for Clean Water http://bit.ly/1dTiGa3     
    
    
    Farmers, USDA make case for funding conservation programs http://bit.ly/1dTiGa7     
    
    
    Cuccinelli secures $33M for victims of illegal mortgage servicing practices http://bit.ly/1c51WxG     
    
    
    Staunton News Leader Donated Backpacks to SSC http://bit.ly/1jnmAPh     
    
    
    Report: JMU to name Ohio State DC Everett Withers as new football coach http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2o     
    
    
    Virginia releases 2014 men’s lacrosse schedule http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2r     
    
    
    Massanutten WaterPark and EAUS Toy Drive exceeds expectations http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2t     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The War on Christmas http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2w     
    
    
    Report: JMU to name Ohio State DC Everett Withers as new football coach http://bit.ly/1knMAYV     
    
    
    Virginia releases 2014 men’s lacrosse schedule http://bit.ly/1kZDLSy     
    
    
    Massanutten WaterPark and EAUS Toy Drive exceeds expectations http://bit.ly/1kZDLSA     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The War on Christmas http://bit.ly/1kZDM8Q     
    
    
    Sebelius approves hardship exemption for those with healthcare plans canceled http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2y     
    
    
    Sebelius approves hardship exemption for those with healthcare plans canceled http://bit.ly/1kZJsje     
    
    
    Richmond Squirrels announce Hot Stove Celebrity event guest list http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2A     
    
    
    East Carolina rides second-half run to 103-94 win over VMI http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2D     
    
    
    Sens. Warner and Kaine introduce Military Retirement Restoration Act http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2G     
    
    
    UVa.-Notre Dame football date announced for 2015 season http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2I     
    
    
    Waynesboro Police searching for wanted teen http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2K     
    
    
    McAuliffe announces Admiral John C. Harvey for Secretary of Veterans Affairs http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2O     
    
    
    East Carolina rides second-half run to 103-94 win over VMI http://bit.ly/1l1pHb7     
    
    
    Sens. Warner and Kaine introduce Military Retirement Restoration Act http://bit.ly/1l1pFjA     
    
    
    UVa.-Notre Dame football date announced for 2015 season http://bit.ly/1kq59M2     
    
    
    Waynesboro Police searching for wanted teen http://bit.ly/1l1pHru     
    
    
    McAuliffe announces Admiral John C. Harvey for Secretary of Veterans Affairs http://bit.ly/1kq5a2l     
    
    
    Just a drill: No baby abduction at Augusta Health http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2R     
    
    
    Just a drill: No baby abduction at Augusta Health http://bit.ly/JQpVGV     
    
    
    Staunton Senior Center Abounds with Holiday Atmosphere http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2T     
    
    
    SAW Receives Grant for DSMP http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2W     
    
    
    VPAS Represented at Staunton Community Health Fair http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g2Y     
    
    
    Elks to Deliver Food Baskets to Waynesboro Seniors http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g30     
    
    
    Staunton Senior Center Abounds with Holiday Atmosphere http://bit.ly/1fMKM8J     
    
    
    SAW Receives Grant for DSMP http://bit.ly/1jqSwCj     
    
    
    VPAS Represented at Staunton Community Health Fair http://bit.ly/1jqSv1d     
    
    
    Elks to Deliver Food Baskets to Waynesboro Seniors http://bit.ly/1fMKMpm     
    
    
    Staunton Senior Center Abounds with Holiday Atmosphere http://bit.ly/1cGY1E4     
    
    
    UVa. women's basketball loses to Tulane in OT http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g32     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball loses to Tulane in OT http://bit.ly/1fNf23p     
    
    
    625 squat    
    
    
    Greenway walk on a sunny Saturday.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6qAyUmW4y     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6A3kDXCqk     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2qrZiESZN     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1JHJBdmyc     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2wHhRAWGH     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/RWVpKvxL     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/18dcIbYuk     
    
    
    Wanted Waynesboro teen turns himself in http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g35     
    
    
    Wanted Waynesboro teen turns himself in http://bit.ly/1ktUFLx     
    
    
    At the UVa-Northern Iowa basketball game. Go 'Hoos!    
    
    
    I wrote two weeks ago about how this would be a tough game. At that time, Northern Iowa was 3-5, but coming off... http://fb.me/3bDRhhMWo     
    
    
    Study in contrast: On Monday, I was in Durham for the Duke-Gardner Webb game at Cameron. The school had finished... http://fb.me/2M7UXt8rZ     
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsNorthernIowa http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g39     
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsNorthernIowa http://bit.ly/1cbCKFW     
    
    
    UVa. basketball overcomes sluggish start in 57-43 win over Northern Iowa http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3d     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Quick hits from the UVa.-Northern Iowa game http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3i     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Teaching kids about climate change http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3k     
    
    
    McDonnell sets date for special election in Senate District 33 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3m     
    
    
    UVa. basketball overcomes sluggish start in 57-43 win over Northern Iowa http://bit.ly/1cm2pNY     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Quick hits from the UVa.-Northern Iowa game http://bit.ly/1cJuObx     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Teaching kids about climate change http://bit.ly/1cm2q4d     
    
    
    McDonnell sets date for special election in Senate District 33 http://bit.ly/1cJuObD     
    
    
    JMU wins in Holiday Hoops Classic over Hampton, 55-49 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3p     
    
    
    Karen Kwiatkowski: Congress is the problem http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3s     
    
    
    JMU wins in Holiday Hoops Classic over Hampton, 55-49 http://bit.ly/1cmnfwr     
    
    
    Karen Kwiatkowski: Congress is the problem http://bit.ly/1cJKYS7     
    
    
    McDonnell applauds efforts to aid Syrian refugees http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3v     
    
    
    McDonnell applauds efforts to aid Syrian refugees http://bit.ly/1fQaedt     
    
    
    Virginia women’s basketball downs Florida Gulf Coast, 85-56 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3y     
    
    
    Virginia women’s basketball downs Florida Gulf Coast, 85-56 http://bit.ly/1co8Ekj     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices falling again http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3A     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices falling again http://bit.ly/1jwOpF1     
    
    
    What You Believe About Homosexuality Doesn't Matter http://fb.me/1av7pFYBk     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Can we leave Tony Romo alone now? http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3C     
    
    
    Holiday Hoops Classic raises over 100 tons of food for Virginia’s food banks http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3E     
    
    
    VDOT road report: Dec. 23-Jan. 3 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3G     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Can we leave Tony Romo alone now? http://bit.ly/1cfcs5G     
    
    
    Holiday Hoops Classic raises over 100 tons of food for Virginia’s food banks http://bit.ly/1e3JwfO     
    
    
    VDOT road report: Dec. 23-Jan. 3 http://bit.ly/1e3Jzbp     
    
    
    Local Wendy’s franchise donating $4,000 to help feed local families http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3I     
    
    
    Work to begin on Interstate 64 upgrades in the Shenandoah Valley http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3K     
    
    
    Local Wendy’s franchise donating $4,000 to help feed local families http://bit.ly/1kxfvJW     
    
    
    Report: JMU to name Ohio State DC Everett Withers as new football coach : Augusta Free Press http://fb.me/1ZHvygMa4     
    
    
        
    
    
    George Mason basketball loses to #17 Iowa State, 79-67 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3R     
    
    
    Is it just me, or has George Mason taken a huge step back since Jim Larranaga left and Paul Hewitt took over? http://fb.me/2BXI2ybH7     
    
    
    George Mason basketball loses to #17 Iowa State, 79-67 http://bit.ly/1kxQKNM     
    
    
    I still think this is, as we call it in wrestling, a "work." And I think we'll all find out around the time of... http://fb.me/1fB7i2bF0     
    
    
    We Americans do like to "declare war" on things. Lately, mostly, sadly, each other. http://fb.me/3kjAHKRed     
    
    
    As the economy improves, gas prices go up. Which causes the economy to not improve as much. Which causes gas... http://fb.me/AXMqPcuX     
    
    
    Watercolor classes at Staunton Augusta Art Center http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3T     
    
    
    Watercolor classes at Staunton Augusta Art Center http://bit.ly/1kzogTO     
    
    
    Holiday Greetings http://bit.ly/1l9H2Pl     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: Showing appreciation for our troops this holiday season http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g3X     
    
    
    Court of Appeals finds Johnathon Montgomery innocent http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g41     
    
    
    Robert Hurt: Showing appreciation for our troops this holiday season http://bit.ly/19aro3L     
    
    
    Court of Appeals finds Johnathon Montgomery innocent http://bit.ly/1980PJs     
    
    
    Big news from our friends at the Stayin' Country Concert Tour http://fb.me/T4IqQnot     
    
    
    Terry McAuliffe Inaugural Committee announces additional parade participants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4e     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Video highlighting asthma care improvements wins national award http://bit.ly/1kA2a3L     
    
    
    Continued problems with my #Comcast Internet. This has been ongoing for two months now. #ridiculous    
    
    
    Reporter, Staunton native Chris Lassiter publishes first book, You're Grounded http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4j     
    
    
    JMU's Ron Curry selected CAA Men’s Basketball Player of the Week http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4n     
    
    
    JMU's Brown, Carroll draw preseason baseball All-America recognition http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4p     
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsNorfolkState http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4r     
    
    
    U.S. Sen. Tim Kaine hails passage of defense bill http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4t     
    
    
    Surviving the holidays: Think before you drink http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4y     
    
    
    JMU’s Ron Curry selected CAA Men’s Basketball Player of the Week http://bit.ly/1fW73AY     
    
    
        
    
    
    Live Blog: #UVavsNorfolkState http://bit.ly/1jBXtIz     
    
    
    U.S. Sen. Tim Kaine hails passage of defense bill http://bit.ly/1jBXvjy     
    
    
    Surviving the holidays: Think before you drink http://bit.ly/1jBXtIL     
    
    
    Virginia holds off pesky Norfolk State, 66-56 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4B     
    
    
    Quick Hits: How Virginia held off Norfolk State http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4E     
    
    
    Virginia holds off pesky Norfolk State, 66-56 http://augustafreepress.com/virginia-holds-pesky-norfolk-state-66-56/ … http://fb.me/XYjQkIRd     
    
    
    Quick Hits: How Virginia held off Norfolk State http://augustafreepress.com/quick-hits-virginia-held-norfolk-state/ … http://fb.me/2um3duWJU     
    
    
    Virginia holds off pesky Norfolk State, 66-56 http://bit.ly/1fWNY1E     
    
    
    Quick Hits: How Virginia held off Norfolk State http://bit.ly/1jCMoXC     
    
    
    Virginia Adopts: Campaign for 1,000 achieves goal http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4I     
    
    
    Frank Clemente: This Christmas, help the unemployed, not Wall Street http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4K     
    
    
    Federal court denies motion to dismiss in Virginia marriage case http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4R     
    
    
    Virginia Adopts: Campaign for 1,000 achieves goal http://bit.ly/19dTJGx     
    
    
    Frank Clemente: This Christmas, help the unemployed, not Wall Street http://bit.ly/19dTJGB     
    
    
    Federal court denies motion to dismiss in Virginia marriage case http://bit.ly/19dTLOD     
    
    
    EMU women’s soccer makes cookies for RMH holiday bake sale http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4U     
    
    
    Bill O’Reilly: Duck Dynasty’s Robertson wrong to condemn gays, lesbians http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g4W     
    
    
    Chris Lassiter is a solid feature writer. I have a review copy of this book sitting on my desk. I look forward to... http://fb.me/RCYMY9v7     
    
    
    Bill O'Reilly is a favorite target of progressives, but he is a relative voice of reason on Fox News. Big of him... http://fb.me/2g4h7gAWc     
    
    
    The upshot of this: You have the right to remain silent ... NOT!... http://fb.me/32O9vCE8r     
    
    
    EMU women’s soccer makes cookies for RMH holiday bake sale http://bit.ly/1e8TBYG     
    
    
    Bill O’Reilly: Duck Dynasty’s Robertson wrong to condemn gays, lesbians http://bit.ly/1e8TzA7     
    
    
    Richard Adams Variety Show – Jan. 3 http://bit.ly/1e97QwH     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Jan. 2 http://bit.ly/1fZ5jqN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Non-traditional meals for Christmas leftovers http://bit.ly/1cnnHJv     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Sure, Virginia, there’s a Santa Claus, why not? http://bit.ly/1kEAISk     
    
    
    Chris Graham: The three wise guys, and the first Christmas http://bit.ly/19ftX1l     
    
    
    George Mason basketball stages comeback to top Saint Mary’s, 65-63 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g58     
    
    
    George Mason basketball stages comeback to top Saint Mary’s, 65-63 http://bit.ly/1jJPsl0     
    
    
    McDonnell releases report on Creigh Deeds tragedy http://bit.ly/1jJPqJX     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Week 17 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5d     
    
    
    McDonnell announces results of regulatory reform initiative http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5g     
    
    
    Woodrow Wilson Birthday Celebration this weekend http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5k     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Startup Weekend offers unique platform for entrepreneurs http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5o     
    
    
    Poll: 113th Congress is worst ever http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5q     
    
    
    Waynesboro Police Department investigating rash of vehicle thefts http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5u     
    
    
    Del. Dickie Bell to chair House education subcommittee http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5w     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Startup Weekend offers unique platform for entrepreneurs http://bit.ly/1cTSz0z     
    
    
    Poll: 113th Congress is worst ever http://bit.ly/1cTSz0E     
    
    
    McDonnell announces results of regulatory reform initiative http://bit.ly/1cTSz0K     
    
    
    Waynesboro Police Department investigating rash of vehicle thefts http://bit.ly/1cTSAle     
    
    
    Del. Dickie Bell to chair House education subcommittee http://bit.ly/1cBCcuH     
    
    
    650 on the squat. Record for the year.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Chris Graham: So, UVa. paid Mike London $1.09 million per win? http://bit.ly/1kJYFHU     
    
    
    Cynthia Hudson named chief deputy attorney general of Virginia http://bit.ly/1kJYFI0     
    
    
    Great evening with the family: sister StacyMarie Walton, brother in law Chris M Walton, nieces Kayla Sparks,... http://fb.me/RuYllUdT     
    
    
    Bridgewater baseball ranked in preseason Top 25 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5H     
    
    
        
    
    
    Business Beat: Is it really all on UPS? http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5K     
    
    
    Business Beat: Is it really all on UPS? http://bit.ly/1g5q4kw     
    
    
        
    
    
    Politics Beat: No free speech for Virginia legislators? http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5M     
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices jump double digits in some parts of Virginia http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5Q     
    
    
        
    
    
    AAA: Gas prices jump double digits in some parts of Virginia http://bit.ly/19os3yH     
    
    
    Star Scientific CEO Jonnie Williams resigns, company changes name http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5T     
    
    
    Star Scientific CEO Jonnie Williams resigns, company changes name http://bit.ly/1jQCIZL     
    
    
    Health Beat: The sad, sad case of the tonsillectomy gone wrong http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g5X     
    
    
    Health Beat: The sad, sad case of the tonsillectomy gone wrong http://bit.ly/1kNefTe     
    
    
    What’s on TV: Facts and figures on Duck Dynasty http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g60     
    
    
    What’s on TV: Facts and figures on Duck Dynasty http://bit.ly/19pG92V     
    
    
    Dixie Gas & Oil makes donation to Blue Ridge Area Food Bank http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g62     
    
    
    Dixie Gas & Oil makes donation to Blue Ridge Area Food Bank http://bit.ly/19oUoC1     
    
    
    Update: Why A&E caved on Duck Dynasty http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g65     
    
    
    Update: Why A&E caved on Duck Dynasty http://bit.ly/19p80gm     
    
    
    Earth Talk: Dark factories http://bit.ly/1jU4Hrr     
    
    
    Da Bears. http://fb.me/1dojP9UKc     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball defeats Coppin State, 70-45 http://bit.ly/1lpzk3q     
    
    
    Now watching World's Strongest Man. I need some tractor tires and boulders to train with.    
    
    
    UVa. men’s basketball travels to Tennessee Monday night http://bit.ly/19vDTnK     
    
    
    Military vet blasts Bob Goodlatte on military retirement cuts http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6j     
    
    
    Washington Redskins fall in finale, expected to fire Mike Shanahan http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6l     
    
    
    Military vet blasts Bob Goodlatte on military retirement cuts http://bit.ly/1cNk1lW     
    
    
    Washington Redskins fall in finale, expected to fire Mike Shanahan http://bit.ly/1d1vxF3     
    
    
    UVa. women's basketball tops Princeton, 69-57 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6o     
    
    
    JMU women's basketball drops Ohio, 56-33 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6q     
    
    
    UVa. women’s basketball tops Princeton, 69-57 http://bit.ly/1gel25k     
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball drops Ohio, 56-33 http://bit.ly/1jY6jR0     
    
    
    William and Mary basketball falls to West Virginia, 82-45 http://bit.ly/1cOdNSS     
    
    
        
    
    
    NFL playoff field set: Who’s in, and who will advance? http://bit.ly/1cOxzO7     
    
    
        
    
    
    Shenandoah National Park Byrd Visitor Center open on weekends http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6D     
    
    
        
    
    
    Shenandoah National Park Byrd Visitor Center open on weekends http://bit.ly/1h9cmAj     
    
    
    Randy Forbes: A constitutional command http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6F     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://wp.me/p3V9v2-ml     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6K     
    
    
    2014 Countdown for WTA's Talent Night in Waynesboro http://wp.me/p3V9v2-mo     
    
    
    2014 Countdown for WTA's Talent Night in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6N     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell announces matching tourism grants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6P     
    
    
    Family Night at the Richard Adams Show in Waynesboro http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6U     
    
    
        
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://wp.me/p3V9v2-ms     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g6X     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://bit.ly/1d3Iw9j     
    
    
    2014 Countdown for WTA’s Talent Night in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1cQsW6j     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell announces matching tourism grants http://bit.ly/1cQsZ1K     
    
    
    Family Night at the Richard Adams Show in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1cQsZ1P     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://bit.ly/1d3Iuy4     
    
    
    Waynesboro Public Library: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://bit.ly/1h9Cifg     
    
    
    2014 Countdown for WTA’s Talent Night in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1d3YBvI     
    
    
    Family Night at the Richard Adams Show in Waynesboro http://bit.ly/1h9CivA     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley Art Center: January 2014 Calendar of Events http://bit.ly/1d3YCQr     
    
    
    Notre Dame's Eric Atkins, Syracuse's Tyler Ennis named ACC players of the week http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g71     
    
    
    Sen. Warner calls for hearing into Target consumer data breach http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g73     
    
    
    JMU’s Kirby Burkholder collects third CAA Player of the Week accolade http://bit.ly/1k11UwX     
    
    
    Notre Dame’s Eric Atkins, Syracuse’s Tyler Ennis named ACC players of the week http://bit.ly/1k11UNj     
    
    
    Sen. Warner calls for hearing into Target consumer data breach http://bit.ly/1ajog2O     
    
    
    More partnerships between doctors. hospitals strengthen coordinated care for Medicare beneficiaries http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g77     
    
    
        
    
    
    Wheels falling off the bus: Tennessee blasts UVa., 87-52 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7a     
    
    
    Suddenly hot JMU men's basketball defeats Ball State, 73-68 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7d     
    
    
    JMU women's basketball dominates Norfolk State, 94-50 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7f     
    
    
    Virginia State Police emphasize New Year's Eve holiday safety http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7h     
    
    
    State, university leaders welcome FAA decision to test unmanned aircraft http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7j     
    
    
    Terry McAuliffe Inaugural Committee announces ceremony participants http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7m     
    
    
        
    
    
    JMU women’s basketball dominates Norfolk State, 94-50 http://bit.ly/1cSIg23     
    
    
    Virginia State Police emphasize New Year’s Eve holiday safety http://bit.ly/1cSIdU0     
    
    
    State, university leaders welcome FAA decision to test unmanned aircraft http://bit.ly/1cSIg28     
    
    
    Terry McAuliffe Inaugural Committee announces ceremony participants http://bit.ly/1cSIdUb     
    
    
    Chris Graham: Yes, Virginia, that Tennessee game just happened http://bit.ly/1cSIg2b     
    
    
    Work of SAW VICAP Counselors Recognized http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7v     
    
    
    American Shakespeare Center announces lineup for 2014-2015 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7x     
    
    
    Late Clemson run pushes Tigers to 80-50 win over VMI http://bit.ly/1hczAFD     
    
    
    Work of SAW VICAP Counselors Recognized http://bit.ly/1d6BPU6     
    
    
    American Shakespeare Center announces lineup for 2014-2015 http://bit.ly/1d6BQas     
    
    
    Work of SAW VICAP Counselors Recognized http://bit.ly/1d6CRPR     
    
    
    Center closed New Year’s Day 2014 http://bit.ly/1d6CRPU     
    
    
    Florida State extends Jimbo Fisher’s contract to 2019 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7D     
    
    
    Shenandoah Valley on edge of major northeast snowstorm http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7G     
    
    
    Florida State extends Jimbo Fisher’s contract to 2019 http://bit.ly/19Ghmro     
    
    
        
    
    
    Valley Exxon Donated $220 in Gift Cards http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7J     
    
    
    CDSME Coordinator Enrolled in Business Smarts http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7L     
    
    
    That INT-Pick Six thrown by Virginia Tech was maybe the dumbest play that I saw in college football this year.... http://fb.me/2Kj1H4kA0     
    
    
    Valley Exxon Donated $220 in Gift Cards http://bit.ly/1gkRByO     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ultimate Warrior: Stories on merchandise request inaccurate http://wp.me/p3OEoF-QO     
    
    
    Rob Van Dam to appear at Booker T indy show http://wp.me/p3OEoF-QR     
    
    
    Should TNA go back to monthly pay-per-views? No way http://wp.me/p3OEoF-QU     
    
    
    AAA: Best and Worst in Transportation 2013 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7R     
    
    
    Our Community Place marks Second Saturday Night Out! in January http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7U     
    
    
    Dinner Diva: Resolve to get back to the dinner table http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7W     
    
    
    Augusta Health issues call for fine art entries http://bit.ly/1glFC3R     
    
    
    AAA: Best and Worst in Transportation 2013 http://bit.ly/1k6gza4     
    
    
    Our Community Place marks Second Saturday Night Out! in January http://bit.ly/1glFC3V     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ken Plum: Legislative resolutions http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g7Z     
    
    
    Ken Plum: Legislative resolutions http://bit.ly/1cY73So     
    
    
    Republican Party of Virginia survey does not ask about Medicaid http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g81     
    
    
        
    
    
    Republican Party of Virginia survey does not ask about Medicaid http://bit.ly/1gn9bCa     
    
    
    Trailer for new movie featuring WWE’s Goldust http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Rb     
    
    
    So what about the recent heel turn of Daniel Bryan? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Re     
    
    
    SMAC sets new team records at Pittsburgh Christmas meet http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g84     
    
    
    First 2014 baby at Augusta Health http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g88     
    
    
    SMAC sets new team records at Pittsburgh Christmas meet http://bit.ly/1daIwnT     
    
    
    First 2014 baby at Augusta Health http://bit.ly/1daIvjO     
    
    
    New plans for Royal Rumble with Bray Wyatt, Dave Batista? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Rg     
    
    
        
    
    
    Video: Triple H comments on 2014, returns of Brock Lesnar, Batista http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Rm     
    
    
    The lure of the gold: Pro athletes covet WWE title belt http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Rq     
    
    
    Take the 7 Day Eat Clean Challenge http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8c     
    
    
    UVa. soccer’s Jordan Allen signs MLS Homegrown Contract with Real Salt Lake http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8f     
    
    
    Take the 7 Day Eat Clean Challenge http://bit.ly/1k8RPhf     
    
    
        
    
    
    John Morrison: Possible return to WWE? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-RN     
    
    
    Poll: Who should Undertaker face at WrestleMania 30? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-RQ     
    
    
    New Year’s Resolution: Get your business moving in 2014 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8m     
    
    
        
    
    
    Golf pro John Rogers online with new website from Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1aqHMdJ     
    
    
    New Year’s Resolution: Get your business moving in 2014 http://bit.ly/1kbkUIZ     
    
    
    Golf pro John Rogers online with new website from Augusta Free Press http://wp.me/pPq8c-16d     
    
    
        
    
    
    Golf pro John Rogers online with new website from Augusta Free Press http://bit.ly/1d1Asv5     
    
    
    Jennifer McClellan: General Assembly session preview http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8o     
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Championship weekend http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8r     
    
    
    UVa. basketball's Amanda Fioravanti planning to transfer http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8v     
    
    
    William and Mary basketball defeats ODU, 74-68 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8x     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Weekend Watchdog: Championship weekend http://bit.ly/19MWnmZ     
    
    
    UVa. basketball’s Amanda Fioravanti planning to transfer http://bit.ly/19MWnDj     
    
    
    William and Mary basketball defeats ODU, 74-68 http://bit.ly/19MWte9     
    
    
    Training session turns real: UVA medical student saves man’s life http://bit.ly/19MWted     
    
    
    TNA Impact Preview: Coronation ceremony for new TNA Champ Magnus http://wp.me/p3OEoF-RW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Bill Apter interviews Matt Hardy: Will Matt ever team with Jeff Hardy again? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-S1     
    
    
    WWE News: Eva Marie nominated for Maxim Hot 100 http://wp.me/p3OEoF-S4     
    
    
    The Rock gives LeBron James WWE title belt as birthday gift http://wp.me/p3OEoF-S7     
    
    
    John D’ Earth – Jan. 11 http://bit.ly/19MkMFV     
    
    
    Richard Adams Variety Show – Jan. 3 http://bit.ly/19NsDX0     
    
    
    Open Mic Talent Night – Jan. 2 http://bit.ly/19NsDX2     
    
    
    Wilson Fairchild – Jan. 31 http://bit.ly/1d2jGMd     
    
    
    Andrew McKnight & Beyond Borders – Jan. 25 http://bit.ly/1d2jHQq     
    
    
    WWE News: Mick Foley weighs in on Daniel Bryan heel turn http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sb     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell announces 64 new jobs in Pulaski County http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8B     
    
    
    Wind Chill Advisory in effect: Surprise snow http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8E     
    
    
    McAuliffe nominates Maurice Jones as Secretary of Commerce and Trade http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8G     
    
    
    #10 UNC women's basketball defeats JMU, 74-71 http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8I     
    
    
    Attorney General-elect Mark Herring announces senior staff http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8L     
    
    
    New WWE T-shirt: ‘If Cena Wins, We Complain Online’ http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sf     
    
    
    WWE: The latest on Stone Cold Steve Austin and WrestleMania 30 http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sj     
    
    
    Rowdy Roddy Piper music project to help cancer charities http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sn     
    
    
    Undertaker-Lesnar at WrestleMania? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sq     
    
    
    Gov. McDonnell announces 64 new jobs in Pulaski County http://bit.ly/1deF23Y     
    
    
    Wind Chill Advisory in effect: Surprise snow http://bit.ly/1d3cXlk     
    
    
    McAuliffe nominates Maurice Jones as Secretary of Commerce and Trade http://bit.ly/1d3cW0D     
    
    
    #10 UNC women’s basketball defeats JMU, 74-71 http://bit.ly/1deF1Nq     
    
    
    Attorney General-elect Mark Herring announces senior staff http://bit.ly/1d3cXlt     
    
    
    Spike TV looking to land WWE Smackdown? http://wp.me/p3OEoF-Sx     
    
    
    Want a job in WWE? Joey Styles tells you how to get one http://wp.me/p3OEoF-SB     
    
    
    McDonnell announces task force on mental health services http://wp.me/pn9VJ-g8N     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    McDonnell announces task force on mental health services http://bit.ly/1gtzoyY     
    
    
    EMU women’s basketball loses at Johns Hopkins, 67-58 http://bit.ly/1kdLnWx     
    
    
    Roll out the New Year with a Bright Idea: $10K in grants available http://bit.ly/1gtzpmv     
    
    
        
    
    
    George Mason men’s basketball sneaks past Penn, 80-77 http://bit.ly/1d3QMeM     
    
    
        
    
    
    