Wonder how this approach compares to what Chen and Karger advocated in their SIGIR 2006 paper http://lnkd.in/vCs6vK  #sigir2013    
    
    
    A room full of people with strong opinions about IR evaluation metrics is a dangerous thing! But very entertaining. #sigir2013    
    
    
    "It's in the references, so we read it." #sigir2013    
    
    
    Back to the industry track to hear @gsingers talk about open source search FTW #sigir2013    
    
    
    @daniel_bilar I was paraphrasing this presentation: http://prezi.com/ghpvsbgr0dv8/one-metric-to-rule-them-all-a-general-evaluation-measure-for-information-access-tasks/ …    
    
    
    Nice to see academic IR community increasingly embracing Lucene. Great way to bridge gap between academia and industry #sigir2013    
    
    
    "you owe it to yourself to find something that you can be excited about" Amen.
http://lnkd.in/bxPXiA     
    
    
    @JimiShan Followed by karaoke? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now up: Øystein Torbjørnsen (http://lnkd.in/hrJQVp ) on uniting enterprise search with database technology #sigir2013    
    
    
    People want usability & flexibility of a search engine combined with the robustness of a database. And joins. I just want a pony. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last talk: @hugo_zara on some of the problems and applications of opinion analysis #sigir2013    
    
    
    Reminder to all #sigir2013 presenters and especially industry track colleagues: please post your slides! Ours are at http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    @saadmissen Hopefully he'll post them.    
    
    
    Nice to see interface that encourages explicit feedback -- critical for machine-learned classifier deployed in enterprise setting #sigir2013    
    
    
    Best application of sentiment analysis: identifying entertaining content. But labor-intensive, machine learning wasn't enough #sigir2013    
    
    
    And it's a wrap! Time for the #sigir2013 closing session and then a drink at the pub http://lnkd.in/jamXca     
    
    
    And of course #sigir2013 closes with a Harlem Shake.    
    
    
    @dpatil Congrats, just got back from the pub and saw the news! And nice catch for @relateiq!    
    
    
    1 more day of #sigir2013! Attending workshop on modeling user behavior for IR evaluation http://lnkd.in/z3XXms     
    
    
    Workshop on modeling user behavior for IR eval: program/proceedings online at http://lnkd.in/z3XXms  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Improve IR evaluation by simulating interaction and incorporating explicit user models into effectiveness measures #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: Ben Carterette on user variability in system-based information retrieval evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Test collection + evaluation measure is supposed to model user interacting with search engine #sigir2013    
    
    
    Rank-biased precision as parameterized user model http://lnkd.in/b7uVmd  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Expected Reciprocal Rank for Graded Relevance http://lnkd.in/xnBdvE  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation implies variability, but most IR eval doesn't model it. Let's fix that, eg by modeling user patience as parameter #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can significantly improve IR system effectiveness by tuning systems to optimize for user variability #sigir2013    
    
    
    TREC Session Track categorizes searches as known-subject,interpretative,known-item,exploratory  http://lnkd.in/Pz5Tku  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Mine click logs to infer distribution of searcher impatience #sigir2013    
    
    
    Let's leverage user variability to improve search engine effectiveness. Which means incorporating variability into evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Falk Scholer on observing users to validate models #sigir2013    
    
    
    Falk Scholer: heat maps mask complexity, eg only 40% of users look at top search result first and users backtrack to prev results #sigir2013    
    
    
    Falk Scholer: how badly do we need to damage the search results in order to see measurable differences in user behavior? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Vu Tran on Markov modeling for user interaction in retrieval #sigir2013    
    
    
    Probability ranking principle for interactive information retrieval http://lnkd.in/D_vBVE  #sigir2013    
    
    
    System can determine when expected utility of query reformulation is higher than examining lower-ranked results for current query #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: incorporating efficiency in evaluation. And a cute kitten. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now up, with the best title ever, Leif Azzopardi on "The Assimilation of Users" #sigir2013    
    
    
    "User studies are like sex, and simulation is like masturbation. Or is it like drugs?" Leif's just getting started #sigir2013    
    
    
    Kal's ECIR 2011 keynote: http://lnkd.in/DxSixi  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Nick Belkin's ECIR 2008 keynote: http://lnkd.in/AYFsdZ  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Leif's characterization of modeling problem cites George Box but makes me think of http://lnkd.in/TDf3pp  #sigir2013    
    
    
    "Cranfield paradigm = original sim." Leif keeps them coming at #sigir2013    
    
    
    "Whenever there's a model, there's a simulation waiting to happen" #sigir2013    
    
    
    Abstraction suppresses details to make models tractable, while idealization uses something patently false to make the models work #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation can explore many different kinds of questions: which, what-if, how, and why #sigir2013    
    
    
    SimInt 2010 workshop on simulation of interaction http://lnkd.in/TusGdt  #sigir2013    
    
    
    How do we create simulations that reflect users' predictable irrationality? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Wish there were some kind of best speaker award. Leif is showing us how it's done #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation shows how a user's information seeking strategy affects information-seeking effectiveness #sigir2013    
    
    
    What are we evaluating? System? Application? User? Strategy? How do we delineate? Should we try? #sigir2013    
    
    
    The (Nick) Belkin test: a Turing test for simulated users #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can simulated searchers replace real ones? Can we create homo simulus? #sigir2013    
    
    
    'Irrational' searchers and IR-rational researchers http://lnkd.in/KJnxnT  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: Jiepu Jiang on simulating user selections of query suggestions #sigir2013    
    
    
    User judgments of query quality differ from system-oriented metrics like nDCG #sigir2013    
    
    
    A Comparison of User and System Query Performance Predictions http://lnkd.in/6cFSkv  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Query suggestions help when users face cold-start problem and can't (re-)formulate queries - Diane Kelly, SIGIR 2009 #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Arjumand Younus on personalization for difficult queries #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can we study personalized search with simulated users? Discuss. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last talk before lunch: Ben Carterette on user judgments of document similarity #sigir2013    
    
    
    Does cosine similarity actually reflect human judgments of document-document similarity? Correlation is less than 0.2 #sigir2013    
    
    
    Should we get better at simulating users? Or should we try to get users to better simulate simulated users? #sigir2013    
    
    
    @andrew_clegg Workshop program and proceedings are at http://www.mansci.uwaterloo.ca/~msmucker/mube2013/ …    
    
    
    #sigir2013 attendees sitting on Trinity College steps with their laptops: "it's more social" pic.twitter.com/izB4EcEXPE    
    
    
    Want to learn how LinkedIn search works? Check out our slides from #sigir2013 http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    Back from lunch for Mikhail Ageev on task-based snippet evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Challenge in evaluating snippets: don't want to penalize good abandonment #sigir2013    
    
    
    Measure snippet quality by predicted search session success rather than by CTR #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Peter Bruza on modeling information seeking users by he decisions they make #sigir2013    
    
    
    Quantum cognition: using quantum theory to model human cognition http://lnkd.in/VmhpjM  #sigir2013    
    
    
    The key to understanding the conjunction fallacy is the incompatibility of subspaces of the cognitive decision space #sigir2013    
    
    
    A Quantum Theoretical Explanation for Probability Judgment Errors http://lnkd.in/chCAdc  #sigir2013    
    
    
    @mounialalmas I'm not sure if I can be sure and know if I'm sure at the same time. If I figure it out, I might collapse!    
    
    
    Next: Ke Zhou on evaluating heterogeneous information access #sigir2013    
    
    
    Need to incorporate user behaviors into system-oriented measures for evaluating heterogeneous information access #sigir2013    
    
    
    Eye Tracking on Universal and Personalized Search http://lnkd.in/rVghhr  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last paper: Colin Wilkie on measures and models of findability #sigir2013    
    
    
    Need a findability measure that considers both retrieval and navigation within the same model #sigir2013    
    
    
    Discussion topics for #mube: validation, reusability, variability, modeling user intent, whole-session eval, interactive measures #sigir2013    
    
    
    Validation questions: what to include in test collection, minimum number of users, component performance vs end-to-end experience #sigir2013    
    
    
    Reusable test collections: add logging of CTRL-F, abandonment; judge summaries; multiple per-topic sessions with tracking #sigir2013    
    
    
    Intent: can games bridge gap btwn natural & imposed intents? Can we project intent into vector space & map to behavioral outcome? #sigir2023    
    
    
    Interaction: what do we want to measure? Holistic UX or components? Engagement? Happiness vs accuracy? What data to collect? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Whole session eval: how do we calculate cost & gain? Interaction model relies on intent model. Sum cost & gain over interactions #sigir2013    
    
    
    And it's a wrap! Thanks everyone for an awesome #sigir2013    
    
    
    Céad míle fáilte to the @SIGIR2013 organizers for an outstanding conference! #sigir2013    
    
    
    @msweeny You're most welcome! Thanks are really due to the @SIGIR2013 organizers who delivered an amazing conference.    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna You're welcome!    
    
    
    On my way back from a great #sigir2013 in Dublin to home sweet Mountain View.    
    
    
    Up for pool-side karaoke? Come to my birthday party next Saturday. But make sure to RSVP! http://lnkd.in/nnBTKu     
    
    
    Nice post by @bencasnocha on applying Kahneman's science of hedonic psychology (experience vs memory) to daily life. https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130804220552-659753-memories-make-your-life-meaningful-here-s-how-to-have-more-of-them …    
    
    
    Search: What's Cooking in the Lab - reflections on the #sigir2013 conference  https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130805134105-50510-search-what-s-cooking-in-the-lab …    
    
    
    My #sigir2013 conference report: a focus on entities, users, evaluation http://lnkd.in/7j8KsW     
    
    
    @skamille Thanks for the feedback. Definitely a use case we need to handle, so it's on our to-do list. cc @r39132    
    
    
    @srchvrs You're most welcome! Thanks for joining us for lunch.    
    
    
    Time for the Carmina Burana sing along! http://mountainview.patch.com/groups/events/p/carmina-burana-singalong_3b946dbd …    
    
    
    Intermission.  Water. ZOMG I haven't had this much fun singing since high school. Oh wait, that is the last time I sang the Carmina Burana!    
    
    
    Just finished singing the Carmina Burana with a concert hall full of people just as crazy. Now I drink in earnest. In taberna! Totus floreo!    
    
    
    The dangers of one-click shopping :-) http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/borowitzreport/2013/08/amazon-founder-says-he-clicked-on-washington-post-by-mistake.html …    
    
    
    Is there an O'Reilly book on information retrieval? If not, there should be, and the animal should be an okapi. http://lnkd.in/JqNSX9     
    
    
    @cavorite I suppose the Scots would push for a Terrier cc @iadh @craig_macdonald @leifos    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Glad that @OReillyMedia has a book on enterprise search. But that's not quite the same as a book on information retrieval.    
    
    
    @wyatt_earp_ Thanks, but I've fulfilled my quota by writing one book in this lifetime!    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna Nice metaphor! But I still think we should honor Stephen Robertson and Karen Spärck Jones with an okapi. http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Okapi_BM25     
    
    
    @IntranetFocus @OReillyMedia I'm sure it's a great book, given the author. But I want something along the lines of Manning/Raghavan/Schütze.    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Been meaning to read both of those. But neither is from @OReillyMedia. And neither has a okapi on the cover. :-)    
    
    
    Never grabbed @TheNoisyChannel Twitter account. Good thing I moved my blog to LinkedIn! https://www.linkedin.com/influencer/50510 …    
    
    
    @naga86 You can. http://help.linkedin.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/33198 …    
    
    
    Excited that @fredkofman is speaking at LinkedIn today. Loved his book on Conscious Business. Watch online: http://lnkd.in/Y3JDqN     
    
    
    Just heard about Spreadsheets: the quantified self, in bed. Seems like it should be a Jawbone feature. cc @mrogati http://lnkd.in/9d4R7C     
    
    
    Don't start a company just for the sake of starting a company; start a company because you believe in an idea. http://lnkd.in/WY7GeU     
    
    
    It's my birthday, and I'll sing if I want to -- come join us if you're in the neighborhood! http://lnkd.in/nnBTKu     
    
    
    @mrogati @strlen @jaykreps Twitter encourages bolder language with the 140-char limit. Be imperative! Screw verbose subjunctives! #lEANiN    
    
    
    Getting ready for pool-side karaoke pic.twitter.com/7e8dMhUvx6    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte @elunca Even if they're real, the question is whether they pay attention to the people they follow.  http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/01/13/a-twitter-analog-to-pagerank/ …    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who made my birthday party the best answer to life, the universe, and everything!    
    
    
    @Alpa Belated congrats! Where to?    
    
    
    @dhh Sadly believable despite the irony. Most enterprise search systems suck. Even the expensive ones. Especially the expensive ones.    
    
    
    @usabart @xamat Sorry to burst your filter bubble :-)    
    
    
    Fantastic lecture by @fredkofman that he gave at LinkedIn last week, now on YouTube! "Your Job Is Not Your Job" http://lnkd.in/q6UXz6     
    
    
    Rest in peace, @HCIR_GeneG. So sad to lose you so young.    
    
    
    Interesting watching a startup whose goal is to beat Endeca at ecommerce search. I feel old! http://lnkd.in/xGE3fS     
    
    
    Remembering Gene Golovchinsky @HCIR_GeneG http://lnkd.in/NpVVv6     
    
    
    My daughter, the dancing queen. pic.twitter.com/ljQ7Oeqcmp    
    
    
    Remembering @HCIR_GeneG - reflections on losing a friend and colleague https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130819070021-50510-remembering-gene …    
    
    
    First day of school! Introducing LinkedIn University Pages http://lnkd.in/cVkMsa     
    
    
    Nice article on technical interviewing: http://lnkd.in/d-9CMP     
    
    
    @naga86 You can. Here's how to hide unwanted endorsements: http://help.linkedin.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/33198 …    
    
    
    Chairing Data Science track at QCon SF w @josh_wills @mitultiwari @xamat & more. Save $100 w SPEAKTUNK100 promo code! http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    Just added Microsoft Core Search Chief Scientist Jan Pedersen to QCon SF track. Save $100 w SPEAKTUNK100 promo code! http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    @adamnash Sorry I missed you. Hope you made it to the S.P.A.Z. (Space Pirates And Zombies) party! http://instagram.com/p/dVcbLOI2DI/     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Please elaborate.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Sure. Or write a post and link to it. :-)    
    
    
    You can't endorse my daughter for Karaoke even with new LinkedIn TOS. But you can endorse me! https://www.linkedin.com/in/dtunkelang  pic.twitter.com/dlCtAqJlVh    
    
    
    @mo_data Any of your connections can choose what they endorse you for.    
    
    
    @tomwilliams Thanks!    
    
    
    Enjoyed a delicious breakfast in LinkedIn's new cafeteria. Props to David Henderson and team for delivering the goods! And the bacon!    
    
    
    @mo_data Some of the more generic skills tend to be over-endorsed. But I'm glad you see the histogram as reasonably accurate -- same for me.    
    
    
    @mo_data Can't provide details but we do have measures to combat abusive SEO / search spam.    
    
    
    Noise is the supreme archenemy of all serious thinkers. http://lnkd.in/gYz6fC     
    
    
    Only 3 more days to sign up for QCon SF and save $700. Save another $100 by using SPEAKTUNK100 as a promo code. http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    Excited to speak at Google next Tuesday Sept 3. If you're a Googler curious about LinkedIn Search, join us at 3:30pm in Asilomar (MTV 1900).    
    
    
    GAO: "software-related patents often had overly broad or unclear claims or both" http://lnkd.in/En4_Zf     
    
    
    Interesting article in IEEE asserting that "The STEM Crisis is a Myth". Discuss. http://lnkd.in/xxh_J2     
    
    
    @adamnash Sure, but no one wants to hire the bottom % of any pool. Wouldn't a scarcity induce employers to raise wages and/or lower the bar?    
    
    
    @adamnash I'm more persuaded by the argument that the amorphousness of how people define STEM allow researchers to cherry-pick data.    
    
    
    @piers_hollott It depends how you define STEM. Not everyone in the software industry studied computer science -- or even a STEM discipline.    
    
    
    @adamnash Touché, top tech employers don't lower the bar -- or don't stay on top. But rest of STEM labor market? Silicon Valley != world.    
    
    
    Software Patents: A Tax on Innovation https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130903133938-50510-software-patents-a-tax-on-innovation …    
    
    
    Glad to see lots of folks share my view that software patents are a tax on innovation http://lnkd.in/pjA9M4     
    
    
    Heading over to Google in a bit to talk about LinkedIn Search. Hope to reconnect with old friends and make new ones!    
    
    
    Information Technology and Innovation Foundation: The Real Story on Guestworkers in the High-skill U.S. Labor Market http://www2.itif.org/2013-guestworkers-high-skill-labor-market.pdf …    
    
    
    Thanks Hrishikesh Aradhye for hosting me at Google today. And thanks to all the Googlers who attended for your attention & great questions!    
    
    
    What To Do If You Get A Patent Troll Demand http://lnkd.in/w49AqH     
    
    
    @lemire Thanks for the recommendation. Just started watching it -- so far so good.    
    
    
    Maybe the US govt would get serious about stopping patent abuse if it weren't immune to patent infringement lawsuits https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schillinger_v._United_States …    
    
    
    Daughter's excuse for not staying in bed last night: "I was talking to a cat on the patio." And of course she's learned the word "nocturnal"    
    
    
    @whita Sometimes I wonder if her primary motivation for learning is coming up with more excuses to stay up late.    
    
    
    Congrats @mrogati and team! http://lnkd.in/bjekDsK     
    
    
    Welcome @avinash to the LinkedIn Influencer program! Check out his first post about the Twitter IPO. http://lnkd.in/bXykyg2     
    
    
    Non-confidential congratulations to all my friends at Twitter on your upcoming IPO!    
    
    
    Are you a data scientist? Want to help a designer & earn $$ for an interview about how you work? Email kim@slicedbreaddesign.com for details    
    
    
    Not that I'd ever trade my iPhone for a Windows phone, but this is freaking hilarious. - http://pulse.me/s/qfhcb     
    
    
    @DtNever Email my twitter handle @ gmail.    
    
    
    Looking at double-walled espresso glasses. Bodum Pavina? Ozeri Moderna? Any coffee geeks have strong opinions you'd be so gracious to share?    
    
    
    @arunbatchu Thanks, glad you like it!    
    
    
    @willwest_ Thanks! Those are certainly my baseline -- pretty happy with Bodum products generally.    
    
    
    The fascinating and sad story of crap coffee http://www.theguardian.com/p/3tmg5/tw     
    
    
    @eric_andersen Cat poop coffee is certainly weird to me. :-) I'd heard of it years ago from an Indonesian friend but never tried it.    
    
    
    Always fun at expense of my Princeton alumni friends when Princeton Engineering Anomalies Research (PEAR) makes news. http://www.themindunleashed.org/2013/09/mind-over-matter-princeton-russian.html …    
    
    
    A good part-of-speech tagger in 200 lines of Python http://lnkd.in/bBzNeNu     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Good is subjective, but the author provides empirical results in the post.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff All I know is what is in the post.    
    
    
    LinkedIn’s Commitment to Transparency About Government Requests for Member Data http://lnkd.in/bNfD_-a     
    
    
    LinkedIn’s Commitment to Transparency About Government Requests for Member Data http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/17/linkedins-commitment-to-transparency-about-government-requests-for-member-data/ …    
    
    
    Love that people are fighting back against patent trolls with the RICO Act. Hope it works. http://lnkd.in/b_WWF7D     
    
    
    @marcprecipice Congrats to you and to @stripe!    
    
    
    @marcprecipice Will keep it warm and sunny for you. Great to have you back!    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Thanks for the shout-out for TunkRank!    
    
    
    @alansaid @arjenpdevries @abellogin Congrats!    
    
    
    Setting the Record Straight on False Accusations - a post by LinkedIn Senior Director of Litigation @blawit http://lnkd.in/baaDCEd     
    
    
    What is a Thought Leader? https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130923140605-50510-what-is-a-thought-leader …    
    
    
    New York regulators cracking down on fake reviews. http://lnkd.in/bd49AAT  But is spontaneity overrated? http://lnkd.in/bTxpHxD     
    
    
    What is a thought leader? Join the conversation at http://lnkd.in/bUc_dZg     
    
    
    Hey Europe: please don't emulate the US by becoming more friendly to patent trolls. http://lnkd.in/bGqdHxk     
    
    
    @panm817 If the input is itself in the dictionary, then you don't have to split it. That's how the problem is defined.    
    
    
    Thrilled that the FTC is finally investigating how patent assertion entities (aka patent trolls) undermine innovatio…http://lnkd.in/brJX6Cu     
    
    
    @mrogati @eminomura Congrats to you both! Expecting great things from @Jawbone data science.    
    
    
    Hey recruiters: cold-call anonymized pitches with requests for phone calls are annoying. If you're serious, disclose & put skin in the game.    
    
    
    Out of Endeca, a new crop of start-ups takes shape in the Boston area. http://lnkd.in/bPDtjeh     
    
    
    @eric_andersen The congrats go to my former colleagues. I've just been a cheerleader and technical advisor. :-)    
    
    
    @tynanwrites IANAL. But as @jim_adler says, laws govern use. But regulating private inference is Orwellian. Creates a class of thought crime    
    
    
    @tynanwrites @jim_adler In that case I think we're in violent agreement.    
    
    
    @communicating Endeca alumni are a formidable talent pool. And Steve Papa is a force of nature -- he's involved with a lot of the startups.    
    
    
    @mrogati Googled [date a scientist] and got http://dating.newscientist.com/  You know we can do better.    
    
    
    @matthewhurst @ian_soboroff He already lives in Washington :-P    
    
    
    @communicating So proud to have been part of that revolution. Still working to carry it through more of the consumer internet.    
    
    
    @climatecorp Congrats David and team, and good luck continuing your mission on an even bigger scale!    
    
    
    @ManningBooks @gsingers @drewfarris @dr_dobbs Congrats! Glad to see practical books on text mining being recognized.    
    
    
    Introducing LinkedIn’s First Recruiter Certification Program http://lnkd.in/bf7qtPW     
    
    
    Congrats @tarunavg and team on launching LinkedIn's recruiter certification program! http://lnkd.in/bf7qtPW     
    
    
    Congratulations to @friedberg and The Climate Corporation on their acquisition! Big data products FTW! http://lnkd.in/bBETyrT     
    
    
    @marcprecipice Welcome back to the land of eternal sunshine! Let me know when you can make it down to the South Bay.    
    
    
    Learn from amazing machine learning & data science practitioners at QCon SF. Use SPEAKTUNK100 code for a $100 discou…http://lnkd.in/bzDU_BU     
    
    
    Been on Spotify for ~2 years now. Hard to imagine I ever listened to music any other way. Thanks @spotify for improving my quality of life.    
    
    
    @PandoDaily Haven't read the patent, but doubt it's as bad as the crap-ton of software patents. At least they're thinking of the children.    
    
    
    Props to Kaspersky Lab for defeating software patent troll Lodsys! http://lnkd.in/bknZQrr     
    
    
    @e_kaspersky to software patent troll Lodsys: Never give up, never surrender! http://lnkd.in/bU4k5jY     
    
    
    Study by Yale professor Ian Ayres questions "Bing-It-On" claim, finding that searchers prefer Google over Bing. http://lnkd.in/bY5tTkV     
    
    
    Sad to be missing the HCIR Symposium this year, but glad that it's generating a healthy social media stream #hcir201…http://lnkd.in/bm8f_Zz     
    
    
    Great catching up about social search with Gayatree Ganu today. Proud to be an external member on her dissertation committee.    
    
    
    If anyone who attended #hcir2013 wants to write a guest post for me, please let me know! Sorry I couldn't be there this year.    
    
    
    @elunca @rcapra3 Would love to bring HCIR back to Bay Area! And LinkedIn is building out more space, so let's see what's possible. #hcir2013    
    
    
    @rcapra3 Missing you guys too. Retweeting isn't the same. Though hopefully my retweets are interesting! #hcir2013    
    
    
    My family is camping w/o me this weekend, so thinking of sneaking out to Blue Max for karaoke tonight. Join me! And endorse me for karaoke!    
    
    
    Why Are There Still So Few Women in Science? http://lnkd.in/bUb_9QU     
    
    
    @hintikka I hope that organizations like @MentorNetTweet can help bring more women into STEM. That's why I signed up as an advisor.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Glad to hear it! Am proud of LinkedIn's efforts to support women in tech, but there's a long way to go for us all.    
    
    
    Great night for karaoke at Blue Max in Sunnyvale. You know you want to. http://m.yelp.com/biz/blue-max-sunnyvale …    
    
    
    Bing rebuts Yale study questioning claims of "Bing It On" challenge http://searchengineland.com/bing-slams-freakonomics-bing-it-on-critique-173486 …    
    
    
    Could it really be true that uber patent troll Intellectual Ventures is running out of cash? Don't get my hopes up! http://lnkd.in/bAf-rjR     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker In theory that's why you centralize management of social CRM. In practice, some data gets lost in translation.    
    
    
    Great piece by @cfchabris on "Why Malcolm Gladwell Matters (And Why That's Unfortunate)" http://lnkd.in/bHS58M7     
    
    
    @tomwilliams @cfchabris It's tempting to dismiss mediocre pop science as entertainment. But bestsellers have consequences.    
    
    
    Even if you dislike Ed Snowden, I hope you agree with @schneierblog that NSA attacks on internet must be made public http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2013/oct/04/nsa-attacks-internet-bruce-schneier …    
    
    
    Awesome catching up with @mrogati about the cool data science her team is doing at Jawbone. And Spotify   Jambox = music happiness!    
    
    
    @edchi Was your #hcir2013 keynote recorded? And are the slides available online?    
    
    
    @edchi Cool. Sorry I couldn't experience it live, but hope the slides make their way onto the interwebs soon.    
    
    
    @mikeolson @hmason Bunch of us been saying this for a while. e.g., http://thenoisychannel.com/2008/05/01/privacy-through-difficulty/ … But we're finally at the point where people care.    
    
    
    @peteskomoroch @hmason @mikeolson Problem is public's right to know vs individual right to privacy. I like @jim_adler's answer: regulate use    
    
    
    @hmason @mikeolson True that. And it's nice that our friends at the NSA have helped bring more public attention to the issue.    
    
    
    Before you go after the long tail, optimize for the short snout https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131007130344-50510-optimize-for-the-short-snout …    
    
    
    How I learned to stop worrying about the long tail and optimize for the short snout https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131007130344-50510-optimize-for-the-short-snout …    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Can you elaborate? Perhaps in more than 140 chars?    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Hope @gsingers & @LucidWorks are listening. I know they're trying to build great products, so they should hear your feedback    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker How would you react as a recruiter or hiring manager if a candidate asked you for the company's compensation spreadsheet?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker But do you expect them to disclose their present compensation if you won't disclose the company's present compensation info?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Candidate can try to learn this info from H1B filings. But usually the information asymmetry favors employer over candidate.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Maybe not the entire balance sheet, but at least the distribution of compensation for candidate's peer group at the company.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker So does that mean you make an offer before you know candidate's current compensation? If not, how do you avoid anchoring?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker If current comp has little weight, then it's best not to insist on it. Many recruiters insist on knowing, then anchor on it.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Sadly true. When I find great recruiters I treasure them.    
    
    
    Honored to be a keynote at CIKM Workshop on 
Data-driven User Behavioral Modeling & Mining from Social Media http://lnkd.in/bNgZ3St     
    
    
    Looking forward to #cikm2013! I'm keynoting DUBMOD workshop; my colleague @StatGuru1 is in industry track http://www.cikm2013.org/     
    
    
    @IR_oldie Congrats to Dave and to the @bing team -- that's a big win!    
    
    
    Impressive, scary material from team at iSEC Partners. You'll never see your cell phone the same way again. http://lnkd.in/b84rJ5A     
    
    
    Glad the CPJ is holding the Obama administration accountable for its lack of transparency. http://lnkd.in/bwf_Nzq     
    
    
    @jeremyphoward Congrats and keep us posted! Good luck in your next play!    
    
    
    Curious about EHCR ruling on anonymous commenters. Personally never been a fan of anonymous comments. http://lnkd.in/bUMY7fw     
    
    
    I just need 3 more endorsements for Karaoke to get it ahead of Data Science. Happy to earn them with a performance, via Skype if necessary.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha If ads keep the internet "free", then what are advertisers paying for? Attention/time is money.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha Granted, most consumers don't see it that way and prefer to spend a lot attention/time rather than a little cash.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha I use an ad blocker and pay for ad free content when it's available. To each their own.    
    
    
    @leifos @alansaid @jkonstan That's why I wrote a blog post in defense of recall. Someone's gotta stand up for it. http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/07/17/in-defense-of-recall/ …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I prefer science fiction to fictional science. Preferences don't commute. Besides, I hate commuting.    
    
    
    Google CIO Ben Fried bans Dropbox because it holds company data in another company's data center. Irony much? http://lnkd.in/bZu8mxu     
    
    
    Netflix #customerservicewin! Like Picard, rep showed intelligence, courage, integrity, compassion, courtesy. …http://lnkd.in/byr2fNu     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker I finally met @fredkofman in person when he spoke at LinkedIn. Incredible talk. Watch it on YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IdMvWLARF1w …    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Frank Flynn taught several leadership classes at LinkedIn that I was fortunate to attend. Highly recommend him as a teacher.    
    
    
    @jkonstan @leifos @alansaid Guess I had to be there. I concede measuring recall may be meaningless if your ground truth is too incomplete.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker I plan to -- unless someone else does it first! -- but I'm not sure when. I want to spend enough time on it to do it right.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @jkonstan @leifos @alansaid I believe it's "I'm so happy with what I got, I want more!" http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/madonna/more.html …    
    
    
    @alansaid Would totally sing Madonna's "More" as karaoke if you could find a bar that stocked it. Might have to go custom.    
    
    
    @alansaid Sorry, not attending #recsys2013. Been trying to do less jet-setting and more family time. But a bunch of LinkedIn folks are there    
    
    
    @alansaid I'll be at #cikm2013 in a few weeks. Working on my slides for the DUBMOD workshop keynote. https://sites.google.com/site/umsocial2013/keynote-speakers …    
    
    
    @alansaid Acceptable, but I need to learn song better first since it doesn't track lyrics word by word. Request it at my next karaoke party!    
    
    
    @alansaid @xamat @mitultiwari I'm not really a #recsys guy -- am more of a search guy. Though #recsys is just search with a null query. :-)    
    
    
    Niche search engine I just discovered: MillionShort only shows results from long tail of less popular sites. http://millionshort.com/     
    
    
    The Pseudo-Profundity of Malcolm Gladwell http://lnkd.in/bD68e5g     
    
    
    Folks who developed MillionShort also built MillionTall to search only the short snout (top 1K - 1M) of sites http://lnkd.in/b8MDnWH     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Ok, I give up -- I'll stick to classic karaoke IR. Like that Frankie Goes To Hollywood song about query relaxation.    
    
    
    Executives Need Press Training Too https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131014122821-50510-executives-need-press-training-too …    
    
    
    @lizgannes I'd love to see the full text of the interview. My sources at Google tell me you misrepresented Ben in the article. Discuss?    
    
    
    @lizgannes Can follow up privately if you want. DM best way to get in touch.    
    
    
    @lizgannes My friend claimed context was cut that would have made Ben's position seem more nuanced. Hence my curiosity about the full text.    
    
    
    @lizgannes But if they're unwilling to make their objections publicly, then I'm inclined to take everything in your article at face value.    
    
    
    @mauralyn You're the best. Come out to Mountain View someday, and I'll take you to my favorite local karaoke joints!    
    
    
    Just finished drafting slides on "Social Search in a Professional Context" for the DUBMOD workshop #cikm2013 http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @adityagp @xamat @pankaj @mitultiwari @greglinden @amt_shrma Speaking of interfaces, dear Twitter please figure out a better group chat soln    
    
    
    Just adopted new setting so anyone who follows me can DM me. Good move on Twitter's part to roll this out. http://www.theverge.com/web/2013/10/15/4840190/twitter-direct-messages-from-any-follower-option …    
    
    
    @harper Always seemed odd that Twitter expected users to follow numbers much greater than Dunbar's but required it for DM. Problem solved!    
    
    
    @harper Maybe, I think I'm a real person, but I haven't been genetically verified. For all I know, I could be a clone. Or a simulation.    
    
    
    @zenogantner @xamat @mitultiwari @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma I buy that information access is a multidimensional multiplayer game.    
    
    
    Delighted to see Google CIO Ben Fried clarify his remarks about Dropbox to @lizgannes http://lnkd.in/b86-EXh     
    
    
    @lizgannes My apologies for questioning whether you'd misrepresented Ben Fried in your interview. Glad to see his public clarification.    
    
    
    Just heard Bill Gates speak at Sequoia event at AirBnB. Inspired and humbled by his work and his humility. Honored, awed to talk to him 1:1.    
    
    
    And thank you Jessica Long for giving me a tour of the AirBnB office. You have an amazing space and culture. Not to mention a great product!    
    
    
    @Sequoia_Capital @BillGates Thank you for a truly inspiring evening. You've set an extraordinary bar to aspire to.    
    
    
    Thrilled that New York Airbnb hosts are standing up for themselves and for the rest of us. http://lnkd.in/bDctpRd     
    
    
    Excited to hear @reidhoffman talk with Eric Ries about lean startups. Follow the stream at http://lnkd.in/b6hPb7Z  #inspeaker    
    
    
    Core idea of lean startup: optimize for speed of learning through rapid experimentation  #inspeaker http://lnkd.in/bhNpv3p     
    
    
    Eric Ries on key challenge of innovation: if we don't know what's supposed to happen, how do we measure if we're making progress? #inspeaker    
    
    
    Eric Ries: No matter how long you wait, you will be embarrassed by the first version of your product. Get customer feedback ASAP. #inspeaker    
    
    
    Eric Ries: as an engineer you may have a point of view about quality. But customers are the ultimate arbiters of product quality. #inspeaker    
    
    
    Thanks Eric Ries for answering my q about managing uncertainty: use business model to rule out impossible; learn inputs over time #inspeaker    
    
    
    @jerepick As Eric answered, the key is to treat innovation as hypothesis testing. cf. http://thenoisychannel.com/2012/04/25/science-as-a-strategy/ …    
    
    
    @jerepick Hypothesis generation is how you decide what to try. But learning comes from hypothesis testing and analyzing results.    
    
    
    @jerepick Hopefully you're continually doing both in a virtuous cycle.    
    
    
    @jerepick Completely agree with you there. I know, I'm no fun.    
    
    
    Successful orgs are those with workers in charge of the management http://lnkd.in/bXG26hM  Better yet http://lnkd.in/j4AVTT     
    
    
    Happy Bosses Day! Please celebrate by giving your boss a performance review. http://lnkd.in/j4AVTT     
    
    
    We've been trying to get @Comcast to restore our broadband service for 3 days. Anyone else know how to get customer service from them? #fail    
    
    
    @scottopia Thanks, will try that.    
    
    
    @comcastcares We've been trying to get Comcast to restore our broadband for 3 days. Your reps have misdirected us, and no-showed w/o a call.    
    
    
    @comcastcares It's hard to fit all of our frustration into 140 chars but you get the idea. Can you help? Happy to send more details by DM.    
    
    
    @peterleonard In Mountain View @comcast is one of the few options. But will look into @sonicnet. Thanks!    
    
    
    Congrats @kmlake, @ericcolson, and the whole Stitch Fix team on your $12M Series B! http://lnkd.in/ban7kqE     
    
    
    I, for one, welcome our new Data Elite overlords. http://lnkd.in/bA5qDpv     
    
    
    Good news: the government shutdown is over. Bad news: an example in my slides is now a bit dated. #cikm2013 http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @ComcastMelissa We still have no service. We have an appointment at 7am tomorrow. We had to book it in person your office.    
    
    
    @ComcastMelissa Believe me I will. Thank you for responding. ButI hope you understand I'm not a Comcast fan right now.    
    
    
    Honored to be keynoting ACM @WebSciConf 2014 along with @DameWendyDBE and @jobsworth. http://www.websci14.org/     
    
    
    @flojee Thanks!    
    
    
    @elunca @arunbatchu Thanks!    
    
    
    Congrats to my friends at Google on a great Q3! http://lnkd.in/b9nsW3m     
    
    
    "Google’s business continues to be the one thing for which it’s best known—search." -- @mims http://lnkd.in/ba6QiHC     
    
    
    Last chance to sign up for QCon SF! Register before 10/25 to save $400, and $100 more with SPEAKTUNK100 code. http://lnkd.in/b_yafvi     
    
    
    Despite previous frustration with @Comcast, I was very impressed with tech Dominic Martinez who restored service this AM. cc @ComcastMelissa    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker True that. I see so many people who randomly walk through the professional graph without figuring out what they really want.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie By CS journals do you mean compilations of extended versions of year-old CS conference papers?    
    
    
    Sorry I missed today's workshop at Stanford on Reputation, Trust, and Authority. Hope slides will be posted. http://lnkd.in/bpaWJYV     
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who endorsed me for Karaoke and helped place it in my top 10 skills!    
    
    
    @paulwehner Absolutely. Thanks!    
    
    
    I now have more endorsements for karaoke than for recommender systems. Which is a great excuse for not making it to #recsys2013 :-)    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks for sharing. Feels like consumer version of my @TTIVanguard talk on interacting with big data https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130502234056-50510-big-data-we-have-a-communication-problem …    
    
    
    Loser pays for frivolous lawsuits by patent trolls? Please SCOTUS, grant us this small favor. http://lnkd.in/b_Z3pXi     
    
    
    @techmilind I see karaoke as part of my professional identity. :-)    
    
    
    Scott Adams argues that passion is the result of success. Interesting. Passion motivates me to pursue success …http://lnkd.in/bu8CiNa     
    
    
    Taste in food is personal and subjective. Except for bacon. http://lnkd.in/bNG8tU5     
    
    
    I, for one, welcome our new robot barista overlords. http://lnkd.in/bd4VhHA  http://lnkd.in/b9mgftu     
    
    
    @friedberg: doing a startup means having a deserving problem & being passionate about changing the world http://lnkd.in/bVEVgnJ     
    
    
    You're the Boss of You https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131021125257-50510-you-re-the-boss-of-you …    
    
    
    You're the boss of you: your responsibility as an employee to your manager, your employer, and yourself http://lnkd.in/bJ_gH_i     
    
    
    Thanks @hmason for posting the full set of videos from DataGotham 2013 on YouTube! http://lnkd.in/dXKFS5p     
    
    
    Congrats to @datariver, @jrgoldman, @anutewary & Level Up on acquisition by Intuit! http://lnkd.in/dV7X8Dc     
    
    
    Interesting move posted on LinkedIn but not in tech press: @nathanfolkman left CTO post at @path to join @samsung https://www.linkedin.com/pub/nathan-folkman/0/400/3a2 …    
    
    
    Congrats to @sarahtavel, @jrauser, @jeremyl and everyone at Pinterest on your $225M round! http://lnkd.in/d-5DfvD     
    
    
    Are you a manager who thinks it's enough to tell employees "your door is always open"? Here's a good read. http://lnkd.in/dVQ4Xqy     
    
    
    @kellan A data scientist never reveals his secrets. :-)    
    
    
    @jerepick Fair enough. But it was a dumb promise. Instead they should've promised to be as user-first as possible with an ad-supported model    
    
    
    Love the great speakers at LinkedIn. Today: Brad Stone talking about history of Jeff Bezos & Amazon. Watch at http://lnkd.in/6RV89M     
    
    
    Impressed by the intensity of Amazon's culture & Jeff Bezos's idealism. But not sure I could ever work there. http://lnkd.in/dC_SDvU     
    
    
    First time I've heard of the "Amazon.love" memo. Protip: don't Google "amazon.love" at work. http://lnkd.in/d8sBk8D     
    
    
    @jerepick I'm sure you can. :-)    
    
    
    @whita I'm just glad I didn't try to "feel lucky" with that particular search.    
    
    
    @astrobiased @mrogati @Jawbone Congrats!    
    
    
    Proud of the engineering team that built LinkedIn Intro for iOS. Check out the updated @LinkedInEng blog post http://lnkd.in/dxZ6NrT     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Then don't use it :-) It's opt-in and very clear about how it works.    
    
    
    Only 3 more days til #cikm2013! Excited to talk about Social Search in a Professional Context on Monday. http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @pankaj Hey, that's what weekends are for. :-)    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Please elaborate. Perhaps in a forum that provides more than 140 characters to express your thoughts. :-)    
    
    
    "One chord is fine. Two chords are pushing it. Three chords and you're into jazz." RIP, Lou Reed. http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/27/showbiz/lou-reed-obit/ …    
    
    
    Taught my daughter selection sort vs insertion sort today. Hoping she'll pick up quicksort before she turns 6. #DevelopHer    
    
    
    Looking forward to Gayatree Ganu's defense: Understanding Preferences & Similarities from User-Authored Text http://lnkd.in/dGv_2YY     
    
    
    @maui314159 I think recursive approach is more intuitive, but I'll let her decide when we get there. She tends to have strong opinions. :-)    
    
    
    @marcozag Thanks, will check it out.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff She did great. O(n^2) but she's getting the constant down. :-)    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff To be clear, we're still just working through the algorithms. Coding will come later.    
    
    
    @AmbassadorToyPA She's got over a month.    
    
    
    @gstam I'm sure it will be after she passes her defense and publishes the dissertation.    
    
    
    @elunca Sorry the community is fragmented between conferences this week. On my way (by train) to #cikm2013. Enjoy #dagEIR!    
    
    
    @gingdottwit @ebuie We all miss @HCIR_GeneG. Fortunately his ideas don't have to choose between conferences -- his influence is ubiquitous.    
    
    
    @elunca Just another beautiful day in the valley. :-) http://www.weather.com/weather/tenday/Burlingame+CA+94010:4:US …    
    
    
    Getting started at the DUBMOD workshop at #cikm2013 https://sites.google.com/site/umsocial2013/ …    
    
    
    Now up at the DUBMOD workshop: @pankaj giving a keynote on User Modeling at Twitter #cikm2013    
    
    
    Interesting: Twitter has power law for out-degree, not just in-degree. Especially since attention is finite http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/01/13/a-twitter-analog-to-pagerank/ … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Interested in paper @pankaj cited: On the Precision of Social and Information Networks #cikm2013 http://stanford.edu/~rezab/papers/precision.pdf …    
    
    
    @tomwilliams No objection as long as you do it in a way that accounts for gaming. At least if anyone is paying attention to the numbers.    
    
    
    Never managed to use Twitter lists effectively but glad they're useful for mining what people are known for and user interests. #cikm2013    
    
    
    @tomwilliams I hear you. But I think the problem is harder than it looks.    
    
    
    Ordinary language is powerful -- the fundamental lexical hypothesis. #cikm2013 http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lexical_hypothesis …    
    
    
    Didn't know that Twitter built a topic hierarchy. Would love to use it to follow topics or people-topic pairs rather than people. #cikm2013    
    
    
    Hubs and authorities on list-members bipartite graph beats topic-sensitive PageRank on follow graph for identifying topic experts. #cikm2013    
    
    
    Love that "chatter" is an identifiable topic on Twitter. Hope ASONAM 2013 paper is available online. cc @pankaj #cikm2013    
    
    
    Back from coffee break for short talks. First up: eBay research on Session Modeling to Predict Online Buying Behavior #cikm2013    
    
    
    Next: Twitter Anticipates Bursts of Requests for Wikipedia Articles #cikm2013    
    
    
    Twitter leads, Wikipedia lags. But only by about an hour. #cikm2013    
    
    
    And now research on Pinterest data: Automatically Linking Pinterest Pins to Online Webshops #cikm2013    
    
    
    Last talk before lunch & before my keynote: Content-boosted Maximum Margin Matrix Factorization for Flickr Group Recommendation #cikm2013    
    
    
    Hope everyone had a nice lunch. Giving my keynote at DUBMOD workshop in a few minutes on Social Search in a Professional Context #cikm2013    
    
    
    @xamat I'll log out in a few minutes if you promise to live-tweet my talk :-)    
    
    
    @ahbugdayci We'll see. I envision an arms race between the difficulty of technical phone screen questions and her speed of learning.    
    
    
    @pankaj Thanks! Enjoyed yours as well.    
    
    
    Attending the workshops / tutorials at #cikm2013? Bunch of us are going to the Elephant Bar afterward. Join us! http://www.elephantbar.com/location/burlingame …    
    
    
    Social Search in a Professional Context - my #cikm2013 slides https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131029000013-50510-social-search-in-a-professional-context …    
    
    
    @xamat Come over any time, we're here!    
    
    
    @xamat Unfortunately not. But we shouldn't need a conference to catch up. Worst case, see you at QCon in a couple of weeks. :-)    
    
    
    Thanks Jalal Mahmud, James Caverlee, Michelle Zhou for inviting me to #cikm2013 DUBMOD workshop. My slides: http://lnkd.in/dZXQeGH     
    
    
    For anyone I didn't get to meet at #cikm2013, LinkedIn is hiring! Please talk to my colleagues to learn more, or reach out to me personally.    
    
    
    @ramnathb Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Happy National Cat Day! http://www.nationalcatday.com/     
    
    
    The NSA may lack a conscience, but is making up for it in competence. At least if Snowden et al are telling the truth http://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/nsa-infiltrates-links-to-yahoo-google-data-centers-worldwide-snowden-documents-say/2013/10/30/e51d661e-4166-11e3-8b74-d89d714ca4dd_story.html?Post+generic=%3Ftid%3Dsm_twitter_washingtonpost …    
    
    
    An interesting take on "pro-social gossip" in the workplace by Wharton professor Adam Grant. http://lnkd.in/dKvSiqd     
    
    
    Sorry to miss rest of #cikm2013. Will follow tweet stream. Posted my keynote slides on LinkedIn / Slideshare http://lnkd.in/dZXQeGH     
    
    
    Have you read my faceted search book? If so, could you please leave me a review on Amazon? Thanks! :-) http://lnkd.in/ds4vye6     
    
    
    @vagabondjack Grab a copy from the bookshelf by my desk. :-)    
    
    
    @msbernst @iadh Probably. Most authors are kind enough to post PDFs of their papers somewhere easy to find. :-)    
    
    
    @jongovi Thanks for the review!    
    
    
    @msbernst @iadh I could have sworn I had a USB drive with the proceedings, but I can't find it. Worst case, email the authors.    
    
    
    Attending #cikm2013? Want to learn more about search at LinkedIn? Be sure to find my colleague @abhimanyulad and swing by our sponsor booth.    
    
    
    Dear friends at @Google, happy to offer you my stash of prior art on associative search engines. Call me :-) http://lnkd.in/dnx3xAH     
    
    
    @dannysullivan Agreed, there's prior art in both industry and academia on this. Happy to send references if you're curious -- DM / email me.    
    
    
    My daughter on Halloween. Baby, she's a firework! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=olnaTZYf8vQ …    
    
    
    Great meeting #cikm2013 attendees at LinkedIn today! Contact me if you'd like to learn more. http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    @marcprecipice I think they make irony supplements. Then again, most of what you read online is fortified with a full day's supply of irony.    
    
    
    Just signed 30-day notice to my apartment complex. Hopefully our house is ready for us in time. If not, the office has comfy chairs...    
    
    
    No response from @google. Hope their in-house prior art search is better than this: http://www.google.com/patents/related/text#c=0&d1&d2=02%2F12%2F1997&t=1associative%20search%20engines ….    
    
    
    Count me as a Bill Gates fanboy. Curing diseases that kill millions is higher priority than global broadband. http://lnkd.in/dVZ55aA     
    
    
    Nothing wrong with PhDs that aren't career investments -- if students are informed and universities disclose. http://lnkd.in/dSn6Kaq     
    
    
    @jonathankoren I'm all for global hedonic optimization. But should we optimize for experienced or remembered utility? http://eprints.lse.ac.uk/22750/1/04064.pdf …    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks. She had a blast. I think all kids should get lit up for Halloween. :-)    
    
    
    @daringfireball I'm no Google fanboy - my household is 100% Apple. But don't equate Google's defensive tactics to MS+Apple's offensive ones.    
    
    
    RIP, Cliff Nass. Thank you for teaching us so much about computers and human beings. http://lnkd.in/dqG6-dg     
    
    
    Was reflecting on Cliff Nass as I read great performance feedback from my manager. Here's what Cliff said: http://lnkd.in/5WePvf     
    
    
    Congratulations to Dr. Gayatree Ganu on her successful dissertation defense! http://lnkd.in/byh9xuQ     
    
    
    @informor Not sure I follow. Why don't you send me an email -- might be easier to explain in more than 140 chars.    
    
    
    Congratulations to my friends at Twitter -- enjoy the big and well-earned day! #TWTR #TwitterIPO    
    
    
    @tomwilliams No, I hadn't -- thanks for the link! Looks fun, but will wait for reviews -- am a bit skeptical of auto-filtering vocals.    
    
    
    En route to #qconsf! Looking forward to presentations & conversations & esp to machine learning / data science track! http://qconsf.com/track/applied-machine-learning-and-data-science …    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna I'm not aware of any. But I expect that many (hopefully all) presenters will share their slides.    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna Recorded videos of presentations will be released (but not live-streamed) at http://www.infoq.com/qcon/presentations …    
    
    
    If you're not attending #qconsf, you can follow tweet stream. Now on: creator of Clojure @richhickey on Design, Composition, and Performance    
    
    
    Good design = separating into things that can be composed, making each component about one thing, composing them to solve a problem #qconsf    
    
    
    Full orchestration vs. just the melody and chord changes -- great metaphor for variation in specificity of design by @richhickey #qconsf    
    
    
    Love where @richhickey is taking design-as-music metaphor: programming languages as instruments with deliberate design constraints #qconsf    
    
    
    Software designers can learn from electronic instrument designers: build human interfaces on top of machine interfaces - @richhickey #qconsf    
    
    
    Take-away from @richhickey's keynote: Design like Bartok, Code like Coltraine #qconsf    
    
    
    Thrilled to be speaking with @sankarsearch at Strata 2014 on "Socializing Search. Professionally." http://lnkd.in/d2WUrJA     
    
    
    Attending architecture track at #qconsf. Starting with @jedberg on how Netflix architects for survival http://qconsf.com/track/architectures-youve-always-wondered-about …    
    
    
    Not new but worth repeating: @jedberg on how Netflix's simian army improves reliability and availability http://techblog.netflix.com/2011/07/netflix-simian-army.html … #qconsf    
    
    
    Culture of incident reviews focused on understanding rather than blame is key to institutional learning from mistakes -- @jedberg #qconsf    
    
    
    Back from coffee break for @dmarsh on "From Code to Monkeys: Continuous Delivery at Netflix" http://qconsf.com/presentation/code-monkeys-continuous-delivery-netflix … #qconsf    
    
    
    Back from lunch for more architecture at #qconsf. Now up: Brenden Matthews on Data & Infrastructure at Airbnb http://qconsf.com/presentation/data-infrastructure-airbnb …    
    
    
    More coffee, more talks! Now up: @collidr on "Scaling the Operations Organization at Facebook" http://qconsf.com/presentation/growing-few-many-scaling-operations-organization-facebook … #qconsf    
    
    
    Attending @mikeyk's talk on "How a Small Team Scales Instagram" #qconsf http://qconsf.com/presentation/how-small-team-scales-instagram …    
    
    
    Take-aways from @mikeyk: do simple things first, every infra moving part is another thread for your team to manage, simple != hacky #qconsf    
    
    
    Last talk of the #qconsf architecture track: @yashh and @marty_pinterest Scaling Pinterest http://qconsf.com/presentation/scaling-pinterest …    
    
    
    @snoble If you're optimizing for speed of learning, optimal strategy seems to be to overbuild just enough to buy the time to rebuild.    
    
    
    Last talk of the day at #qconsf: @hackingdata on the evolution of machine learning from science to software http://qconsf.com/keynote/evolution-machine-learning-science-software …    
    
    
    Oryx machine learning library for Hadoop released by Cloudera today: https://github.com/cloudera/oryx  #qconsf    
    
    
    @kriswager Didn't plan it that way. Added a second LinkedIn speaker when one of my other speakers bailed. But both will be excellent. :-)    
    
    
    Excited to kick off the Applied Machine Learning & Data Science track with speakers from Cloudera, Google, LinkedIn, and Netflix! #qconsf    
    
    
    On to the morning keynote: Facebook's Keith Adams on "The Unreasonable Effectiveness of Tuning" http://qconsf.com/keynote/unreasonable-effectiveness-tuning … #qconsf    
    
    
    Is tuning a system based on user data analogous to machine learning? In search, "tuning" often opposite of machine-learned approach. #qconsf    
    
    
    I love many of Keith's analogies. But wondering if his argument is more about human learning than machine learning. #qconsf    
    
    
    "The experimental method does not absolve you from your responsibility for thinking"-- Keith Adams http://qconsf.com/keynote/unreasonable-effectiveness-tuning … #qconsf    
    
    
    I liked Keith's answer to my question -- elide the distinction between humans and machines. We're just human computers. :-) #qconsf    
    
    
    First up in the Applied Machine Learning & Data Science track: @xamat on Machine Learning & Recommender Systems at Netflix Scale #qconsf    
    
    
    Netflix's shift from DVDs to streaming changed incentive to give feedback -- lower cost of selecting a movie you don't like - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    Netflix has moved beyond inferring ratings, providing personalized explanations and social support for its recommendations. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    Netflix recommendations use explicit and inferred preferences, and similarity based on content and collaborative filtering. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    Big Data @ Netflix: 40M subscribers, 5M ratings/day, 3M searches/day, 50M plays/day, 5B hours in Q3 2013. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    @randyshoup @QConSF Fair enough. And, as @hackingdata explained in his keynote, most of the work in machine learning is feature engineering.    
    
    
    Common-sense reminder: popularity is the natural baseline for personalized recommender systems. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    More data or better models, who wins? Depends on problem dimensionality. At low dimension, data size has diminising return. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    More details on the offline / online / nearline computation archietecture @xamat is describing in his #qconsf talk: http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/03/system-architectures-for.html …    
    
    
    Fallback strategy crucial for online recommender systems that require low latency, eg fall back to stale or unpersonalized. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    Not enough for a better model to improve recommendation performance. Business value also has to justify cost / complexity. - @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    Netflix uses human labeling instead of machine learning because problem is human-scale and people still better than machines- @xamat #qconsf    
    
    
    About to start next Data Science talk at #qconsf: @gloriatlau on "Data Science for Hire Ed". Blame me for the pun. http://qconsf.com/presentation/data-science-hire-ed …    
    
    
    Students and recent graduates are fastest growing segment on LinkedIn, which offers guidance based on career outcomes. - @gloriatlau #qconsf    
    
    
    Data standardization key to build data products. Entity resolution more tractable when you add social network features - @gloriatlau #qconsf    
    
    
    Best way to improve data quality is to not have to: invest in typeahead interface to collect starndardized data upfront -@gloriatlau #qconsf    
    
    
    LinkedIn built Notable Alumni product by matching name & standardized school data with Wikipedia, then crowdsourced eval-@gloriatlau #qconsf    
    
    
    More machine learning / data science! @mitultiwari on Large-Scale Social Recommender Systems at LinkedIn http://qconsf.com/presentation/large-scale-social-recommender-systems-linkedin … #qconsf    
    
    
    @kstirman I can't speak for @xamat, but I suspect it's the former. Netflix claims recommendations drive 75% of views. http://techblog.netflix.com/2012/04/netflix-recommendations-beyond-5-stars.html …    
    
    
    LinkedIn delivers news recommendation using explore / exploit: optimize predicted CTR vs data to improve predictions - @mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    Feature engineering key for LinkedIn's People You May Know, e.g. modeling organization overlap http://www.cs.utexas.edu/~cjhsieh/fp086-hsieh.pdf … - @mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    Lower structural diversity increases invitation rate for LinkedIn People You May Know. Contrast to 2012 Facebook study -@mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    Here's the CIKM 2012 paper that @mitultiwari is citing about LinkedIn's related searches recommendations: http://www.azreda.org/paper/cikm2012.pdf … #qconsf    
    
    
    The story of LinkedIn endorsements: extract from profile -> standardize -> infer people's skills -> viral data product -@mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    LinkedIn skill endorsements have produced valuable data, eg. identifying the skill set associated with data scientists -@mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    The open-source stack LinkedIn uses to recommend at scale: Kafka, Hadoop, Azkaban, Voldemort http://data.linkedin.com/opensource  - @mitultiwari #qconsf    
    
    
    If you're curious to learn more about how LinkedIn built Skills & Endorsements, check out these Strata slides http://www.slideshare.net/s_shah/strata-endorsements … #qconsf    
    
    
    Now up in the machine learning & data science track: Hrishikesh Aradhye on Large Scale Discovery Systems for YouTube and Google Play #qconsf    
    
    
    Some YouTube data challenges: video thumbnail extraction, adult content classification, Content ID, video annotation -Hrishi Aradhye #qconsf    
    
    
    Learn more about Hrishi's YouTube annotation research from the publications he's posted at http://research.google.com/pubs/author37818.html … #qconsf    
    
    
    Been getting a full house for machine learning / data science talks at #qconsf. Great to see so much interest in the topic among developers!    
    
    
    Should I pipe videos of my daughter (or me?) singing karaoke through Hrishi's algorithms to judge quality? http://static.googleusercontent.com/external_content/untrusted_dlcp/research.google.com/en/us/pubs/archive/41422.pdf … #qconsf    
    
    
    Discoverability on Google Play: short/clear/unique title; functional & vivid description; real screenshots; video previews, reviews #qconsf    
    
    
    Google Play's typeahead search interface blends navigational instant results (labeled with icons) with suggested search completions. #qconsf    
    
    
    Google Play sees 6M+ unique phrases searched monthly. 50% of them are misspelled. -Hrishi Aradhye #qconsf    
    
    
    Features to gain / retain users for Google Play apps: design for tablets, helpful web anchors, small footprint, get reviews. #qconsf    
    
    
    If you liked @hackingdata's data science keynote last night then be sure to attend @josh_wills's talk: "From the Lab to the Factory" #qconsf    
    
    
    Last data science talk of the day starting in 5 mins: Cloudera's @josh_wills on "From the Lab to the Factory" http://qconsf.com/presentation/lab-factory-building-production-machine-learning-infrastructure … #qconsf    
    
    
    Data scientists: aspire to be mathematicians, others think we do data viz, but really we spend our time cleaning data - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Business people want data scientists to produce actionable insights. But analysis rarely translates to simple decisions -@josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Data science in the factory vs the lab: data products are about operational analytics, not just investigative analytics -@josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Lab vs factory data science: questions vs metrics, interactive vs automated, ad hoc vs systematic, fixed data vs fluid - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Biggest difference between lab & factory data science: whether output is a report or is part of a shipped data product - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    "All products of any consequence will become data products." - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Being able to iterate quickly is more important than how well you do the first time. Optimize for speed of iteration. - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Before you invest in a complex solution, do the simplest thing that could possibly work. - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Human Cloning: The Data Scientist Bottleneck Resolved via @josh_wills http://www.slideshare.net/datasciencelondon/ds-ldn-dr-alex-farquhar-forwardtek … #qconsf    
    
    
    "Data Science needs DevOps" - @josh_wills #qconsf    
    
    
    Useful links about online experimentation from @josh_wills http://research.google.com/pubs/pub36500.html … , http://www.exp-platform.com/Pages/default.aspx … , http://www.deaneckles.com/blog/596_lossy-better-than-lossless-in-online-bootstrapping/ … #qconsf    
    
    
    For those wondering about the Coldplay problem @josh_wills is struggling with, here's a fun blog post of mine http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/02/24/how-recommendation-engines-quash-diversity/ … #qconsf    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who attended the Applied Machine Learning and Data Science #qconsf track today! And special thanks to the great speakers!    
    
    
    @gstam With flying colors :-)    
    
    
    LinkedIn will be out in force at Strata 2014: 7 of us delivering 4 sessions. Register now to save up to $500 http://lnkd.in/dxKQXZE     
    
    
    Machine Learning as a Metaphor: what I learned at #qconsf https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131118140237-50510-machine-learning-as-a-metaphor …    
    
    
    Thanks to @floydmarinescu and the whole #qconsf team for a great conference! Posted some of my reflections: http://lnkd.in/d4mV9db     
    
    
    Reverse engineering of Klout score by Sean Golliher: it's basically the log of your retweets (R2 = 0.94). http://lnkd.in/djmCKB5     
    
    
    Former @klout Chief Scientist @dzhou disputes analysis, claims biased sample. Discussion in LinkedIn comment thread: https://www.linkedin.com/nhome/updates?topic=5808403622249529344 …    
    
    
    Take out the popcorn for Newegg vs. patent troll TQP. Whitfield Diffie takes "expert witness" to a new level. http://lnkd.in/d4JXQ_Y     
    
    
    @russell_hanson For the log of the retweets, but who's counting? :-)    
    
    
    @russell_hanson Silicon Valley firewater! :-)    
    
    
    Tweeting about how Klout scores are mostly a function of retweets got me over 60 retweets. And raised my Klout score. How droll.    
    
    
    Noticed unusual activity on my Twitter account in last 24 hours. Just changed my password. Please let me know if you saw anything suspicious    
    
    
    @jiongwang Congrats to you and the team on the enhancements!    
    
    
    @ipeirotis Don't underestimate the power of a weak tie!    
    
    
    Last weekend of apartment living. https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.448081635302439.1073741835.433030823474187 …    
    
    
    @sumade @josh_wills "That's making me hungry" -- my almost-6-year old daughter, who like me is a devout Bacontarian.    
    
    
    @jadler One life event at a time. :-)    
    
    
    @ade_oshineye Right now it's by invitation only, the list being curated by @danroth and his team.    
    
    
    @FindTheBest Congratulations on the victory, and good luck with the rest on the war.    
    
    
    Sad day in software patent litigation as Newegg loses round to a patent troll. Hoping they win on appeal. http://lnkd.in/drJKRnY     
    
    
    Home is where I want to be, but I guess I'm already there.    
    
    
    @jonathanglick For more context, moved into new house today. But I do love that song. And I know a local karaoke bar that has it. :-)    
    
    
    Blade Runner: The Aquarelle Edition http://youtube.com/watch?v=SLwmlMezS3U …    
    
    
    @cornett Maybe they should have stuck with Endeca. :-) I did the same query on other Endeca-powered retail sites and got better results.    
    
    
    Dear Twitter friends, please help me decide which Chromebook to buy my daughter. She's almost 6 & eager to have her own non-tablet computer.    
    
    
    @joelgrus Hah. Still wonder what Google was thinking.    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks. Will look at the Black Friday / Cyber Monday specials for sure. But so many choices.    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks, much appreciated!    
    
    
    @communicating Right now my top candidate is the 2GB Acer C720. $199 on Amazon and doesn't seem to have any major negatives.    
    
    
    @emilbronikowski @hnshah @kubafilipowski I've definitely seen web design that reminds me of human feces. :-)    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks, food for thought. Want to keep price low since it's for a kid plus I'm sure tech will evolve rapidly in next 2 years.    
    
    
    @nkamensky I'm honored by the request, but unfortunately I'm already overcommitted.    
    
    
    The Changing Face of Exploratory Search http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131202060444-50510-the-changing-face-of-exploratory-search …    
    
    
    Entities, knowledge graphs, and search assistance -- coming together to change the face of exploratory search. http://lnkd.in/drGVw9M     
    
    
    @esammer @hmason Perhaps the Free Masons are a scalable open-source alternative.    
    
    
    Jeff Bezos to world: "What's cooler than a self-driving car?" http://lnkd.in/dfh5RnD     
    
    
    Am curious to see what Apple will do with Topsy -- always liked those guys. http://lnkd.in/diXTaeW     
    
    
    @markmadsen I've reached out to Laxmi Patel (@laxbmss / https://www.linkedin.com/in/laxmipatel ), who owns the group. Hopefully he can make it stop.    
    
    
    @markmadsen It didn't surface in my feed -- I searched for it.    
    
    
    How would the world of computer science be different if sorting were lower bounded by n^2? http://www.quora.com/Computer-Science/How-would-the-world-of-computer-science-be-different-if-sorting-were-lower-bounded-by-n-2 …    
    
    
    One step forward in the war against patent trolls. http://lnkd.in/dRKbWCt     
    
    
    @jinyunyan You can always pay for them. Would be an interesting experiment to see how robust Klout and other measures are to gaming.    
    
    
    Supreme Court to decide whether software is patentable. Hoping the outcome is at least a move towards sanity. http://lnkd.in/didj5ug     
    
    
    @leonpalafox @iskander Given the competition for machine learning talent and the quality of NIPS attendees, it's a brilliant recruiting move    
    
    
    "I like every color in the world!" -- my daughter, while opening her birthday presents. pic.twitter.com/VScOy4s4mI    
    
    
    @stephenlee0 Thanks!    
    
    
    Birthday girl on her throne. Thanks to the kids who partied with us & to the parents for lack of casualties. pic.twitter.com/fxhLG9d7Bz    
    
    
    This is Lily. Those are her friends. And they're here to pump you up. pic.twitter.com/5fZFo4CCCX    
    
    
    “@xamat: Probably interesting RT @newsycombinator: BayesDB - a Bayesian database table http://probcomp.csail.mit.edu/bayesdb/ ” - don't be naive.    
    
    
    @jadler Why were you cooking your left thumb? And do you always tweet while cooking your extremities?    
    
    
    @zephoria So much for their big words about internalizing the open-access culture of @Mendeley after acquiring them.    
    
    
    @hmason Did you mean to tweet, "Smile if you're working on tooth-mounted sensors"?    
    
    
    Key Takeaway Points and Lessons Learned from QCon San Francisco 2013 - by Abel Avram http://lnkd.in/dbAtqey     
    
    
    Grace Hopper on David Letterman in 1986, just before she turned 80. Inspiring -- and very entertaining. http://lnkd.in/dBsqkYR     
    
    
    Proud not to have any of top 10 overused words in my LinkedIn profile: "responsible","strategic","creative"...http://lnkd.in/dZc6z3j     
    
    
    @adamnash I don't believe anyone here (or elsewhere) has done that analysis. But I can say that they aren't what people search for.    
    
    
    @adamnash Would be fun to run a controlled experiment. But unlikely that members would appreciate it. :-)    
    
    
    Happy to see Michelle Lee, former Google patent chief, take charge of USPTO. Hope she can do some good there. http://lnkd.in/dJuwukk     
    
    
    I don't always commend Google for its actions, but when I do it's because they've earned my love and respect. http://lnkd.in/dfxqj8K     
    
    
    Crossed 5k followers before I crossed 10k tweets. Hopefully that means I'm doing something right.    
    
    
    @MatthewZadrozny I thought the whole point of caching the images is that the senders won't know that.    
    
    
    @MatthewZadrozny You're right:"In some cases, senders may be able to know whether an individual has opened a message"https://support.google.com/mail/answer/145919 …    
    
    
    @JeffD Congrats! They're lucky to have you.    
    
    
    My daughter getting an early start in local politics -- as mayor for the day, she lit the Mountain View holiday tree https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I4ReGFrxrYM&t=31m50s …    
    
    
    "It is too damn hard to keep up. And most of what's out there is crap." http://lnkd.in/dfmaiKA     
    
    
    Come hear @sankarsearch & me talk about LinkedIn Search at Strata, and save 20% with SPEAKER20 discount code. http://lnkd.in/d2WUrJA     
    
    
    Introducing a New Way to Search for Influencer Content on LinkedIn http://lnkd.in/d8-tfx8     
    
    
    President Obama meeting w tech brain trust tomorrow, including couple of my friends. Hope he listens to them. http://lnkd.in/dKZ6nPb     
    
    
    Nice analysis of Twitter follower distribution by O'Reilly data journalist @JonBruner http://lnkd.in/dCRq6AZ     
    
    
    @BigDataSc @bradleyvoytek To be fair, academia often isn't aligned with disruptive innovation that tries to change the rules of the game.    
    
    
    @BigDataSc @bradleyvoytek I suspect most investors are even worse at recognizing and valuing innovation than academic reviewers.    
    
    
    Better late than never: the UK posthumously pardons computer science hero Alan Turing and formally apologizes http://lnkd.in/d82iFN5     
    
    
    @communicating Likewise. Merry Christmas / winter holiday of your choosing and a happy new year!    
    
    
    My daughter is loving her new Chromebook. Already checked her email and now is playing Duolingo.    
    
    
    @eric_andersen Spanish. She's in a dual immersion Spanish / English kindergarten so the first lessons are pretty easy for her.    
    
    
    @fmanjoo @WSJ Won't others always have the power to override a sharer's desire for instant deletion by posting permanent copies themselves?    
    
    
    @mrogati Congrats on being featured in the @HuffingtonPost for @Jawbone's work on analyzing sleep patterns! http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/12/26/2013-the-year-in-sleep-in_n_4473343.html …    
    
    
    @fmanjoo @WSJ Less often for sure. But I think of how Deja News unburied Usenet posts. Or how deleted tweets have a way of sticking around.    
    
    
    @fmanjoo @WSJ I suppose I've largely given up on privacy through difficulty. The internet is increasingly efficient at creating permanence.    
    
    
    Planning to have an early, casual family-friendly New Year's Eve party. Local friends, ping me for details.    
    
    
    Curious how the management experiments at Medium and Zappos turn out. Let's all benefit from what they learn. http://lnkd.in/dqpQVCZ     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Why do companies that benefit from information asymmetry insist on even more of it in negotiation? Just because they can?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker How would you react to "I'd rather not anchor our discussion by giving you a number." Or this advice: http://www.forbes.com/sites/shenegotiates/2012/06/04/ask-for-way-too-much-and-close-your-wage-gap-the-script/ …    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Does that also mean that the candidate's current comp is not an input into the offer? In that case you could disclose first.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker No need for such an elaborate pretext for coffee. :-)    
    
    
    Congrats to @arampell on Yub's acquisition by http://Coupons.com ! http://lnkd.in/dbzixm2     
    
    
    Beautiful mash-up of "Let It Go" & "Defying Gravity". @JamieMaletz may not be Idina Menzel but she has a great voice https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U9e48hL1DO8 …    
    
    
    @lizgannes Happy new year, and congrats to you and the @recode team on the new adventure! Looking forward to great reporting and analysis.    
    
    
    @dannysullivan Agreed. That kind of class act seems rare these days -- thanks for calling it out.    
    
    
    Wonder how this approach compares to what Chen and Karger advocated in their SIGIR 2006 paper http://lnkd.in/vCs6vK  #sigir2013    
    
    
    A room full of people with strong opinions about IR evaluation metrics is a dangerous thing! But very entertaining. #sigir2013    
    
    
    "It's in the references, so we read it." #sigir2013    
    
    
    Back to the industry track to hear @gsingers talk about open source search FTW #sigir2013    
    
    
    @daniel_bilar I was paraphrasing this presentation: http://prezi.com/ghpvsbgr0dv8/one-metric-to-rule-them-all-a-general-evaluation-measure-for-information-access-tasks/ …    
    
    
    Nice to see academic IR community increasingly embracing Lucene. Great way to bridge gap between academia and industry #sigir2013    
    
    
    "you owe it to yourself to find something that you can be excited about" Amen.
http://lnkd.in/bxPXiA     
    
    
    @JimiShan Followed by karaoke? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now up: Øystein Torbjørnsen (http://lnkd.in/hrJQVp ) on uniting enterprise search with database technology #sigir2013    
    
    
    People want usability & flexibility of a search engine combined with the robustness of a database. And joins. I just want a pony. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last talk: @hugo_zara on some of the problems and applications of opinion analysis #sigir2013    
    
    
    Reminder to all #sigir2013 presenters and especially industry track colleagues: please post your slides! Ours are at http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    @saadmissen Hopefully he'll post them.    
    
    
    Nice to see interface that encourages explicit feedback -- critical for machine-learned classifier deployed in enterprise setting #sigir2013    
    
    
    Best application of sentiment analysis: identifying entertaining content. But labor-intensive, machine learning wasn't enough #sigir2013    
    
    
    And it's a wrap! Time for the #sigir2013 closing session and then a drink at the pub http://lnkd.in/jamXca     
    
    
    And of course #sigir2013 closes with a Harlem Shake.    
    
    
    @dpatil Congrats, just got back from the pub and saw the news! And nice catch for @relateiq!    
    
    
    1 more day of #sigir2013! Attending workshop on modeling user behavior for IR evaluation http://lnkd.in/z3XXms     
    
    
    Workshop on modeling user behavior for IR eval: program/proceedings online at http://lnkd.in/z3XXms  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Improve IR evaluation by simulating interaction and incorporating explicit user models into effectiveness measures #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: Ben Carterette on user variability in system-based information retrieval evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Test collection + evaluation measure is supposed to model user interacting with search engine #sigir2013    
    
    
    Rank-biased precision as parameterized user model http://lnkd.in/b7uVmd  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Expected Reciprocal Rank for Graded Relevance http://lnkd.in/xnBdvE  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation implies variability, but most IR eval doesn't model it. Let's fix that, eg by modeling user patience as parameter #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can significantly improve IR system effectiveness by tuning systems to optimize for user variability #sigir2013    
    
    
    TREC Session Track categorizes searches as known-subject,interpretative,known-item,exploratory  http://lnkd.in/Pz5Tku  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Mine click logs to infer distribution of searcher impatience #sigir2013    
    
    
    Let's leverage user variability to improve search engine effectiveness. Which means incorporating variability into evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Falk Scholer on observing users to validate models #sigir2013    
    
    
    Falk Scholer: heat maps mask complexity, eg only 40% of users look at top search result first and users backtrack to prev results #sigir2013    
    
    
    Falk Scholer: how badly do we need to damage the search results in order to see measurable differences in user behavior? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Vu Tran on Markov modeling for user interaction in retrieval #sigir2013    
    
    
    Probability ranking principle for interactive information retrieval http://lnkd.in/D_vBVE  #sigir2013    
    
    
    System can determine when expected utility of query reformulation is higher than examining lower-ranked results for current query #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: incorporating efficiency in evaluation. And a cute kitten. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now up, with the best title ever, Leif Azzopardi on "The Assimilation of Users" #sigir2013    
    
    
    "User studies are like sex, and simulation is like masturbation. Or is it like drugs?" Leif's just getting started #sigir2013    
    
    
    Kal's ECIR 2011 keynote: http://lnkd.in/DxSixi  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Nick Belkin's ECIR 2008 keynote: http://lnkd.in/AYFsdZ  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Leif's characterization of modeling problem cites George Box but makes me think of http://lnkd.in/TDf3pp  #sigir2013    
    
    
    "Cranfield paradigm = original sim." Leif keeps them coming at #sigir2013    
    
    
    "Whenever there's a model, there's a simulation waiting to happen" #sigir2013    
    
    
    Abstraction suppresses details to make models tractable, while idealization uses something patently false to make the models work #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation can explore many different kinds of questions: which, what-if, how, and why #sigir2013    
    
    
    SimInt 2010 workshop on simulation of interaction http://lnkd.in/TusGdt  #sigir2013    
    
    
    How do we create simulations that reflect users' predictable irrationality? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Wish there were some kind of best speaker award. Leif is showing us how it's done #sigir2013    
    
    
    Simulation shows how a user's information seeking strategy affects information-seeking effectiveness #sigir2013    
    
    
    What are we evaluating? System? Application? User? Strategy? How do we delineate? Should we try? #sigir2013    
    
    
    The (Nick) Belkin test: a Turing test for simulated users #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can simulated searchers replace real ones? Can we create homo simulus? #sigir2013    
    
    
    'Irrational' searchers and IR-rational researchers http://lnkd.in/KJnxnT  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Now: Jiepu Jiang on simulating user selections of query suggestions #sigir2013    
    
    
    User judgments of query quality differ from system-oriented metrics like nDCG #sigir2013    
    
    
    A Comparison of User and System Query Performance Predictions http://lnkd.in/6cFSkv  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Query suggestions help when users face cold-start problem and can't (re-)formulate queries - Diane Kelly, SIGIR 2009 #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Arjumand Younus on personalization for difficult queries #sigir2013    
    
    
    Can we study personalized search with simulated users? Discuss. #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last talk before lunch: Ben Carterette on user judgments of document similarity #sigir2013    
    
    
    Does cosine similarity actually reflect human judgments of document-document similarity? Correlation is less than 0.2 #sigir2013    
    
    
    Should we get better at simulating users? Or should we try to get users to better simulate simulated users? #sigir2013    
    
    
    @andrew_clegg Workshop program and proceedings are at http://www.mansci.uwaterloo.ca/~msmucker/mube2013/ …    
    
    
    #sigir2013 attendees sitting on Trinity College steps with their laptops: "it's more social" pic.twitter.com/izB4EcEXPE    
    
    
    Want to learn how LinkedIn search works? Check out our slides from #sigir2013 http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    Back from lunch for Mikhail Ageev on task-based snippet evaluation #sigir2013    
    
    
    Challenge in evaluating snippets: don't want to penalize good abandonment #sigir2013    
    
    
    Measure snippet quality by predicted search session success rather than by CTR #sigir2013    
    
    
    Next: Peter Bruza on modeling information seeking users by he decisions they make #sigir2013    
    
    
    Quantum cognition: using quantum theory to model human cognition http://lnkd.in/VmhpjM  #sigir2013    
    
    
    The key to understanding the conjunction fallacy is the incompatibility of subspaces of the cognitive decision space #sigir2013    
    
    
    A Quantum Theoretical Explanation for Probability Judgment Errors http://lnkd.in/chCAdc  #sigir2013    
    
    
    @mounialalmas I'm not sure if I can be sure and know if I'm sure at the same time. If I figure it out, I might collapse!    
    
    
    Next: Ke Zhou on evaluating heterogeneous information access #sigir2013    
    
    
    Need to incorporate user behaviors into system-oriented measures for evaluating heterogeneous information access #sigir2013    
    
    
    Eye Tracking on Universal and Personalized Search http://lnkd.in/rVghhr  #sigir2013    
    
    
    Last paper: Colin Wilkie on measures and models of findability #sigir2013    
    
    
    Need a findability measure that considers both retrieval and navigation within the same model #sigir2013    
    
    
    Discussion topics for #mube: validation, reusability, variability, modeling user intent, whole-session eval, interactive measures #sigir2013    
    
    
    Validation questions: what to include in test collection, minimum number of users, component performance vs end-to-end experience #sigir2013    
    
    
    Reusable test collections: add logging of CTRL-F, abandonment; judge summaries; multiple per-topic sessions with tracking #sigir2013    
    
    
    Intent: can games bridge gap btwn natural & imposed intents? Can we project intent into vector space & map to behavioral outcome? #sigir2023    
    
    
    Interaction: what do we want to measure? Holistic UX or components? Engagement? Happiness vs accuracy? What data to collect? #sigir2013    
    
    
    Whole session eval: how do we calculate cost & gain? Interaction model relies on intent model. Sum cost & gain over interactions #sigir2013    
    
    
    And it's a wrap! Thanks everyone for an awesome #sigir2013    
    
    
    Céad míle fáilte to the @SIGIR2013 organizers for an outstanding conference! #sigir2013    
    
    
    @msweeny You're most welcome! Thanks are really due to the @SIGIR2013 organizers who delivered an amazing conference.    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna You're welcome!    
    
    
    On my way back from a great #sigir2013 in Dublin to home sweet Mountain View.    
    
    
    Up for pool-side karaoke? Come to my birthday party next Saturday. But make sure to RSVP! http://lnkd.in/nnBTKu     
    
    
    Nice post by @bencasnocha on applying Kahneman's science of hedonic psychology (experience vs memory) to daily life. https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130804220552-659753-memories-make-your-life-meaningful-here-s-how-to-have-more-of-them …    
    
    
    Search: What's Cooking in the Lab - reflections on the #sigir2013 conference  https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130805134105-50510-search-what-s-cooking-in-the-lab …    
    
    
    My #sigir2013 conference report: a focus on entities, users, evaluation http://lnkd.in/7j8KsW     
    
    
    @skamille Thanks for the feedback. Definitely a use case we need to handle, so it's on our to-do list. cc @r39132    
    
    
    @srchvrs You're most welcome! Thanks for joining us for lunch.    
    
    
    Time for the Carmina Burana sing along! http://mountainview.patch.com/groups/events/p/carmina-burana-singalong_3b946dbd …    
    
    
    Intermission.  Water. ZOMG I haven't had this much fun singing since high school. Oh wait, that is the last time I sang the Carmina Burana!    
    
    
    Just finished singing the Carmina Burana with a concert hall full of people just as crazy. Now I drink in earnest. In taberna! Totus floreo!    
    
    
    The dangers of one-click shopping :-) http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/borowitzreport/2013/08/amazon-founder-says-he-clicked-on-washington-post-by-mistake.html …    
    
    
    Is there an O'Reilly book on information retrieval? If not, there should be, and the animal should be an okapi. http://lnkd.in/JqNSX9     
    
    
    @cavorite I suppose the Scots would push for a Terrier cc @iadh @craig_macdonald @leifos    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Glad that @OReillyMedia has a book on enterprise search. But that's not quite the same as a book on information retrieval.    
    
    
    @wyatt_earp_ Thanks, but I've fulfilled my quota by writing one book in this lifetime!    
    
    
    @hmvprasanna Nice metaphor! But I still think we should honor Stephen Robertson and Karen Spärck Jones with an okapi. http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Okapi_BM25     
    
    
    @IntranetFocus @OReillyMedia I'm sure it's a great book, given the author. But I want something along the lines of Manning/Raghavan/Schütze.    
    
    
    @IntranetFocus Been meaning to read both of those. But neither is from @OReillyMedia. And neither has a okapi on the cover. :-)    
    
    
    Never grabbed @TheNoisyChannel Twitter account. Good thing I moved my blog to LinkedIn! https://www.linkedin.com/influencer/50510 …    
    
    
    @naga86 You can. http://help.linkedin.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/33198 …    
    
    
    Excited that @fredkofman is speaking at LinkedIn today. Loved his book on Conscious Business. Watch online: http://lnkd.in/Y3JDqN     
    
    
    Just heard about Spreadsheets: the quantified self, in bed. Seems like it should be a Jawbone feature. cc @mrogati http://lnkd.in/9d4R7C     
    
    
    Don't start a company just for the sake of starting a company; start a company because you believe in an idea. http://lnkd.in/WY7GeU     
    
    
    It's my birthday, and I'll sing if I want to -- come join us if you're in the neighborhood! http://lnkd.in/nnBTKu     
    
    
    @mrogati @strlen @jaykreps Twitter encourages bolder language with the 140-char limit. Be imperative! Screw verbose subjunctives! #lEANiN    
    
    
    Getting ready for pool-side karaoke pic.twitter.com/7e8dMhUvx6    
    
    
    @EdwardTufte @elunca Even if they're real, the question is whether they pay attention to the people they follow.  http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/01/13/a-twitter-analog-to-pagerank/ …    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who made my birthday party the best answer to life, the universe, and everything!    
    
    
    @Alpa Belated congrats! Where to?    
    
    
    @dhh Sadly believable despite the irony. Most enterprise search systems suck. Even the expensive ones. Especially the expensive ones.    
    
    
    @usabart @xamat Sorry to burst your filter bubble :-)    
    
    
    Fantastic lecture by @fredkofman that he gave at LinkedIn last week, now on YouTube! "Your Job Is Not Your Job" http://lnkd.in/q6UXz6     
    
    
    Rest in peace, @HCIR_GeneG. So sad to lose you so young.    
    
    
    Interesting watching a startup whose goal is to beat Endeca at ecommerce search. I feel old! http://lnkd.in/xGE3fS     
    
    
    Remembering Gene Golovchinsky @HCIR_GeneG http://lnkd.in/NpVVv6     
    
    
    My daughter, the dancing queen. pic.twitter.com/ljQ7Oeqcmp    
    
    
    Remembering @HCIR_GeneG - reflections on losing a friend and colleague https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130819070021-50510-remembering-gene …    
    
    
    First day of school! Introducing LinkedIn University Pages http://lnkd.in/cVkMsa     
    
    
    Nice article on technical interviewing: http://lnkd.in/d-9CMP     
    
    
    @naga86 You can. Here's how to hide unwanted endorsements: http://help.linkedin.com/app/answers/detail/a_id/33198 …    
    
    
    Chairing Data Science track at QCon SF w @josh_wills @mitultiwari @xamat & more. Save $100 w SPEAKTUNK100 promo code! http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    Just added Microsoft Core Search Chief Scientist Jan Pedersen to QCon SF track. Save $100 w SPEAKTUNK100 promo code! http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    @adamnash Sorry I missed you. Hope you made it to the S.P.A.Z. (Space Pirates And Zombies) party! http://instagram.com/p/dVcbLOI2DI/     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Please elaborate.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Sure. Or write a post and link to it. :-)    
    
    
    You can't endorse my daughter for Karaoke even with new LinkedIn TOS. But you can endorse me! https://www.linkedin.com/in/dtunkelang  pic.twitter.com/dlCtAqJlVh    
    
    
    @mo_data Any of your connections can choose what they endorse you for.    
    
    
    @tomwilliams Thanks!    
    
    
    Enjoyed a delicious breakfast in LinkedIn's new cafeteria. Props to David Henderson and team for delivering the goods! And the bacon!    
    
    
    @mo_data Some of the more generic skills tend to be over-endorsed. But I'm glad you see the histogram as reasonably accurate -- same for me.    
    
    
    @mo_data Can't provide details but we do have measures to combat abusive SEO / search spam.    
    
    
    Noise is the supreme archenemy of all serious thinkers. http://lnkd.in/gYz6fC     
    
    
    Only 3 more days to sign up for QCon SF and save $700. Save another $100 by using SPEAKTUNK100 as a promo code. http://qconsf.com/     
    
    
    Excited to speak at Google next Tuesday Sept 3. If you're a Googler curious about LinkedIn Search, join us at 3:30pm in Asilomar (MTV 1900).    
    
    
    GAO: "software-related patents often had overly broad or unclear claims or both" http://lnkd.in/En4_Zf     
    
    
    Interesting article in IEEE asserting that "The STEM Crisis is a Myth". Discuss. http://lnkd.in/xxh_J2     
    
    
    @adamnash Sure, but no one wants to hire the bottom % of any pool. Wouldn't a scarcity induce employers to raise wages and/or lower the bar?    
    
    
    @adamnash I'm more persuaded by the argument that the amorphousness of how people define STEM allow researchers to cherry-pick data.    
    
    
    @piers_hollott It depends how you define STEM. Not everyone in the software industry studied computer science -- or even a STEM discipline.    
    
    
    @adamnash Touché, top tech employers don't lower the bar -- or don't stay on top. But rest of STEM labor market? Silicon Valley != world.    
    
    
    Software Patents: A Tax on Innovation https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130903133938-50510-software-patents-a-tax-on-innovation …    
    
    
    Glad to see lots of folks share my view that software patents are a tax on innovation http://lnkd.in/pjA9M4     
    
    
    Heading over to Google in a bit to talk about LinkedIn Search. Hope to reconnect with old friends and make new ones!    
    
    
    Information Technology and Innovation Foundation: The Real Story on Guestworkers in the High-skill U.S. Labor Market http://www2.itif.org/2013-guestworkers-high-skill-labor-market.pdf …    
    
    
    Thanks Hrishikesh Aradhye for hosting me at Google today. And thanks to all the Googlers who attended for your attention & great questions!    
    
    
    What To Do If You Get A Patent Troll Demand http://lnkd.in/w49AqH     
    
    
    @lemire Thanks for the recommendation. Just started watching it -- so far so good.    
    
    
    Maybe the US govt would get serious about stopping patent abuse if it weren't immune to patent infringement lawsuits https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schillinger_v._United_States …    
    
    
    Daughter's excuse for not staying in bed last night: "I was talking to a cat on the patio." And of course she's learned the word "nocturnal"    
    
    
    @whita Sometimes I wonder if her primary motivation for learning is coming up with more excuses to stay up late.    
    
    
    Congrats @mrogati and team! http://lnkd.in/bjekDsK     
    
    
    Welcome @avinash to the LinkedIn Influencer program! Check out his first post about the Twitter IPO. http://lnkd.in/bXykyg2     
    
    
    Non-confidential congratulations to all my friends at Twitter on your upcoming IPO!    
    
    
    Are you a data scientist? Want to help a designer & earn $$ for an interview about how you work? Email kim@slicedbreaddesign.com for details    
    
    
    Not that I'd ever trade my iPhone for a Windows phone, but this is freaking hilarious. - http://pulse.me/s/qfhcb     
    
    
    @DtNever Email my twitter handle @ gmail.    
    
    
    Looking at double-walled espresso glasses. Bodum Pavina? Ozeri Moderna? Any coffee geeks have strong opinions you'd be so gracious to share?    
    
    
    @arunbatchu Thanks, glad you like it!    
    
    
    @willwest_ Thanks! Those are certainly my baseline -- pretty happy with Bodum products generally.    
    
    
    The fascinating and sad story of crap coffee http://www.theguardian.com/p/3tmg5/tw     
    
    
    @eric_andersen Cat poop coffee is certainly weird to me. :-) I'd heard of it years ago from an Indonesian friend but never tried it.    
    
    
    Always fun at expense of my Princeton alumni friends when Princeton Engineering Anomalies Research (PEAR) makes news. http://www.themindunleashed.org/2013/09/mind-over-matter-princeton-russian.html …    
    
    
    A good part-of-speech tagger in 200 lines of Python http://lnkd.in/bBzNeNu     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Good is subjective, but the author provides empirical results in the post.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff All I know is what is in the post.    
    
    
    LinkedIn’s Commitment to Transparency About Government Requests for Member Data http://lnkd.in/bNfD_-a     
    
    
    LinkedIn’s Commitment to Transparency About Government Requests for Member Data http://blog.linkedin.com/2013/09/17/linkedins-commitment-to-transparency-about-government-requests-for-member-data/ …    
    
    
    Love that people are fighting back against patent trolls with the RICO Act. Hope it works. http://lnkd.in/b_WWF7D     
    
    
    @marcprecipice Congrats to you and to @stripe!    
    
    
    @marcprecipice Will keep it warm and sunny for you. Great to have you back!    
    
    
    @PFCdgayo Thanks for the shout-out for TunkRank!    
    
    
    @alansaid @arjenpdevries @abellogin Congrats!    
    
    
    Setting the Record Straight on False Accusations - a post by LinkedIn Senior Director of Litigation @blawit http://lnkd.in/baaDCEd     
    
    
    What is a Thought Leader? https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130923140605-50510-what-is-a-thought-leader …    
    
    
    New York regulators cracking down on fake reviews. http://lnkd.in/bd49AAT  But is spontaneity overrated? http://lnkd.in/bTxpHxD     
    
    
    What is a thought leader? Join the conversation at http://lnkd.in/bUc_dZg     
    
    
    Hey Europe: please don't emulate the US by becoming more friendly to patent trolls. http://lnkd.in/bGqdHxk     
    
    
    @panm817 If the input is itself in the dictionary, then you don't have to split it. That's how the problem is defined.    
    
    
    Thrilled that the FTC is finally investigating how patent assertion entities (aka patent trolls) undermine innovatio…http://lnkd.in/brJX6Cu     
    
    
    @mrogati @eminomura Congrats to you both! Expecting great things from @Jawbone data science.    
    
    
    Hey recruiters: cold-call anonymized pitches with requests for phone calls are annoying. If you're serious, disclose & put skin in the game.    
    
    
    Out of Endeca, a new crop of start-ups takes shape in the Boston area. http://lnkd.in/bPDtjeh     
    
    
    @eric_andersen The congrats go to my former colleagues. I've just been a cheerleader and technical advisor. :-)    
    
    
    @tynanwrites IANAL. But as @jim_adler says, laws govern use. But regulating private inference is Orwellian. Creates a class of thought crime    
    
    
    @tynanwrites @jim_adler In that case I think we're in violent agreement.    
    
    
    @communicating Endeca alumni are a formidable talent pool. And Steve Papa is a force of nature -- he's involved with a lot of the startups.    
    
    
    @mrogati Googled [date a scientist] and got http://dating.newscientist.com/  You know we can do better.    
    
    
    @matthewhurst @ian_soboroff He already lives in Washington :-P    
    
    
    @communicating So proud to have been part of that revolution. Still working to carry it through more of the consumer internet.    
    
    
    @climatecorp Congrats David and team, and good luck continuing your mission on an even bigger scale!    
    
    
    @ManningBooks @gsingers @drewfarris @dr_dobbs Congrats! Glad to see practical books on text mining being recognized.    
    
    
    Introducing LinkedIn’s First Recruiter Certification Program http://lnkd.in/bf7qtPW     
    
    
    Congrats @tarunavg and team on launching LinkedIn's recruiter certification program! http://lnkd.in/bf7qtPW     
    
    
    Congratulations to @friedberg and The Climate Corporation on their acquisition! Big data products FTW! http://lnkd.in/bBETyrT     
    
    
    @marcprecipice Welcome back to the land of eternal sunshine! Let me know when you can make it down to the South Bay.    
    
    
    Learn from amazing machine learning & data science practitioners at QCon SF. Use SPEAKTUNK100 code for a $100 discou…http://lnkd.in/bzDU_BU     
    
    
    Been on Spotify for ~2 years now. Hard to imagine I ever listened to music any other way. Thanks @spotify for improving my quality of life.    
    
    
    @PandoDaily Haven't read the patent, but doubt it's as bad as the crap-ton of software patents. At least they're thinking of the children.    
    
    
    Props to Kaspersky Lab for defeating software patent troll Lodsys! http://lnkd.in/bknZQrr     
    
    
    @e_kaspersky to software patent troll Lodsys: Never give up, never surrender! http://lnkd.in/bU4k5jY     
    
    
    Study by Yale professor Ian Ayres questions "Bing-It-On" claim, finding that searchers prefer Google over Bing. http://lnkd.in/bY5tTkV     
    
    
    Sad to be missing the HCIR Symposium this year, but glad that it's generating a healthy social media stream #hcir201…http://lnkd.in/bm8f_Zz     
    
    
    Great catching up about social search with Gayatree Ganu today. Proud to be an external member on her dissertation committee.    
    
    
    If anyone who attended #hcir2013 wants to write a guest post for me, please let me know! Sorry I couldn't be there this year.    
    
    
    @elunca @rcapra3 Would love to bring HCIR back to Bay Area! And LinkedIn is building out more space, so let's see what's possible. #hcir2013    
    
    
    @rcapra3 Missing you guys too. Retweeting isn't the same. Though hopefully my retweets are interesting! #hcir2013    
    
    
    My family is camping w/o me this weekend, so thinking of sneaking out to Blue Max for karaoke tonight. Join me! And endorse me for karaoke!    
    
    
    Why Are There Still So Few Women in Science? http://lnkd.in/bUb_9QU     
    
    
    @hintikka I hope that organizations like @MentorNetTweet can help bring more women into STEM. That's why I signed up as an advisor.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Glad to hear it! Am proud of LinkedIn's efforts to support women in tech, but there's a long way to go for us all.    
    
    
    Great night for karaoke at Blue Max in Sunnyvale. You know you want to. http://m.yelp.com/biz/blue-max-sunnyvale …    
    
    
    Bing rebuts Yale study questioning claims of "Bing It On" challenge http://searchengineland.com/bing-slams-freakonomics-bing-it-on-critique-173486 …    
    
    
    Could it really be true that uber patent troll Intellectual Ventures is running out of cash? Don't get my hopes up! http://lnkd.in/bAf-rjR     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker In theory that's why you centralize management of social CRM. In practice, some data gets lost in translation.    
    
    
    Great piece by @cfchabris on "Why Malcolm Gladwell Matters (And Why That's Unfortunate)" http://lnkd.in/bHS58M7     
    
    
    @tomwilliams @cfchabris It's tempting to dismiss mediocre pop science as entertainment. But bestsellers have consequences.    
    
    
    Even if you dislike Ed Snowden, I hope you agree with @schneierblog that NSA attacks on internet must be made public http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2013/oct/04/nsa-attacks-internet-bruce-schneier …    
    
    
    Awesome catching up with @mrogati about the cool data science her team is doing at Jawbone. And Spotify   Jambox = music happiness!    
    
    
    @edchi Was your #hcir2013 keynote recorded? And are the slides available online?    
    
    
    @edchi Cool. Sorry I couldn't experience it live, but hope the slides make their way onto the interwebs soon.    
    
    
    @mikeolson @hmason Bunch of us been saying this for a while. e.g., http://thenoisychannel.com/2008/05/01/privacy-through-difficulty/ … But we're finally at the point where people care.    
    
    
    @peteskomoroch @hmason @mikeolson Problem is public's right to know vs individual right to privacy. I like @jim_adler's answer: regulate use    
    
    
    @hmason @mikeolson True that. And it's nice that our friends at the NSA have helped bring more public attention to the issue.    
    
    
    Before you go after the long tail, optimize for the short snout https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131007130344-50510-optimize-for-the-short-snout …    
    
    
    How I learned to stop worrying about the long tail and optimize for the short snout https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131007130344-50510-optimize-for-the-short-snout …    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Can you elaborate? Perhaps in more than 140 chars?    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog Hope @gsingers & @LucidWorks are listening. I know they're trying to build great products, so they should hear your feedback    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker How would you react as a recruiter or hiring manager if a candidate asked you for the company's compensation spreadsheet?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker But do you expect them to disclose their present compensation if you won't disclose the company's present compensation info?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Candidate can try to learn this info from H1B filings. But usually the information asymmetry favors employer over candidate.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Maybe not the entire balance sheet, but at least the distribution of compensation for candidate's peer group at the company.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker So does that mean you make an offer before you know candidate's current compensation? If not, how do you avoid anchoring?    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker If current comp has little weight, then it's best not to insist on it. Many recruiters insist on knowing, then anchor on it.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Sadly true. When I find great recruiters I treasure them.    
    
    
    Honored to be a keynote at CIKM Workshop on 
Data-driven User Behavioral Modeling & Mining from Social Media http://lnkd.in/bNgZ3St     
    
    
    Looking forward to #cikm2013! I'm keynoting DUBMOD workshop; my colleague @StatGuru1 is in industry track http://www.cikm2013.org/     
    
    
    @IR_oldie Congrats to Dave and to the @bing team -- that's a big win!    
    
    
    Impressive, scary material from team at iSEC Partners. You'll never see your cell phone the same way again. http://lnkd.in/b84rJ5A     
    
    
    Glad the CPJ is holding the Obama administration accountable for its lack of transparency. http://lnkd.in/bwf_Nzq     
    
    
    @jeremyphoward Congrats and keep us posted! Good luck in your next play!    
    
    
    Curious about EHCR ruling on anonymous commenters. Personally never been a fan of anonymous comments. http://lnkd.in/bUMY7fw     
    
    
    I just need 3 more endorsements for Karaoke to get it ahead of Data Science. Happy to earn them with a performance, via Skype if necessary.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha If ads keep the internet "free", then what are advertisers paying for? Attention/time is money.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha Granted, most consumers don't see it that way and prefer to spend a lot attention/time rather than a little cash.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker @segdeha I use an ad blocker and pay for ad free content when it's available. To each their own.    
    
    
    @leifos @alansaid @jkonstan That's why I wrote a blog post in defense of recall. Someone's gotta stand up for it. http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/07/17/in-defense-of-recall/ …    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff I prefer science fiction to fictional science. Preferences don't commute. Besides, I hate commuting.    
    
    
    Google CIO Ben Fried bans Dropbox because it holds company data in another company's data center. Irony much? http://lnkd.in/bZu8mxu     
    
    
    Netflix #customerservicewin! Like Picard, rep showed intelligence, courage, integrity, compassion, courtesy. …http://lnkd.in/byr2fNu     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker I finally met @fredkofman in person when he spoke at LinkedIn. Incredible talk. Watch it on YouTube: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IdMvWLARF1w …    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Frank Flynn taught several leadership classes at LinkedIn that I was fortunate to attend. Highly recommend him as a teacher.    
    
    
    @jkonstan @leifos @alansaid Guess I had to be there. I concede measuring recall may be meaningless if your ground truth is too incomplete.    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker I plan to -- unless someone else does it first! -- but I'm not sure when. I want to spend enough time on it to do it right.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff @jkonstan @leifos @alansaid I believe it's "I'm so happy with what I got, I want more!" http://www.azlyrics.com/lyrics/madonna/more.html …    
    
    
    @alansaid Would totally sing Madonna's "More" as karaoke if you could find a bar that stocked it. Might have to go custom.    
    
    
    @alansaid Sorry, not attending #recsys2013. Been trying to do less jet-setting and more family time. But a bunch of LinkedIn folks are there    
    
    
    @alansaid I'll be at #cikm2013 in a few weeks. Working on my slides for the DUBMOD workshop keynote. https://sites.google.com/site/umsocial2013/keynote-speakers …    
    
    
    @alansaid Acceptable, but I need to learn song better first since it doesn't track lyrics word by word. Request it at my next karaoke party!    
    
    
    @alansaid @xamat @mitultiwari I'm not really a #recsys guy -- am more of a search guy. Though #recsys is just search with a null query. :-)    
    
    
    Niche search engine I just discovered: MillionShort only shows results from long tail of less popular sites. http://millionshort.com/     
    
    
    The Pseudo-Profundity of Malcolm Gladwell http://lnkd.in/bD68e5g     
    
    
    Folks who developed MillionShort also built MillionTall to search only the short snout (top 1K - 1M) of sites http://lnkd.in/b8MDnWH     
    
    
    @ian_soboroff Ok, I give up -- I'll stick to classic karaoke IR. Like that Frankie Goes To Hollywood song about query relaxation.    
    
    
    Executives Need Press Training Too https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131014122821-50510-executives-need-press-training-too …    
    
    
    @lizgannes I'd love to see the full text of the interview. My sources at Google tell me you misrepresented Ben in the article. Discuss?    
    
    
    @lizgannes Can follow up privately if you want. DM best way to get in touch.    
    
    
    @lizgannes My friend claimed context was cut that would have made Ben's position seem more nuanced. Hence my curiosity about the full text.    
    
    
    @lizgannes But if they're unwilling to make their objections publicly, then I'm inclined to take everything in your article at face value.    
    
    
    @mauralyn You're the best. Come out to Mountain View someday, and I'll take you to my favorite local karaoke joints!    
    
    
    Just finished drafting slides on "Social Search in a Professional Context" for the DUBMOD workshop #cikm2013 http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @adityagp @xamat @pankaj @mitultiwari @greglinden @amt_shrma Speaking of interfaces, dear Twitter please figure out a better group chat soln    
    
    
    Just adopted new setting so anyone who follows me can DM me. Good move on Twitter's part to roll this out. http://www.theverge.com/web/2013/10/15/4840190/twitter-direct-messages-from-any-follower-option …    
    
    
    @harper Always seemed odd that Twitter expected users to follow numbers much greater than Dunbar's but required it for DM. Problem solved!    
    
    
    @harper Maybe, I think I'm a real person, but I haven't been genetically verified. For all I know, I could be a clone. Or a simulation.    
    
    
    @zenogantner @xamat @mitultiwari @alansaid @greglinden @amt_shrma I buy that information access is a multidimensional multiplayer game.    
    
    
    Delighted to see Google CIO Ben Fried clarify his remarks about Dropbox to @lizgannes http://lnkd.in/b86-EXh     
    
    
    @lizgannes My apologies for questioning whether you'd misrepresented Ben Fried in your interview. Glad to see his public clarification.    
    
    
    Just heard Bill Gates speak at Sequoia event at AirBnB. Inspired and humbled by his work and his humility. Honored, awed to talk to him 1:1.    
    
    
    And thank you Jessica Long for giving me a tour of the AirBnB office. You have an amazing space and culture. Not to mention a great product!    
    
    
    @Sequoia_Capital @BillGates Thank you for a truly inspiring evening. You've set an extraordinary bar to aspire to.    
    
    
    Thrilled that New York Airbnb hosts are standing up for themselves and for the rest of us. http://lnkd.in/bDctpRd     
    
    
    Excited to hear @reidhoffman talk with Eric Ries about lean startups. Follow the stream at http://lnkd.in/b6hPb7Z  #inspeaker    
    
    
    Core idea of lean startup: optimize for speed of learning through rapid experimentation  #inspeaker http://lnkd.in/bhNpv3p     
    
    
    Eric Ries on key challenge of innovation: if we don't know what's supposed to happen, how do we measure if we're making progress? #inspeaker    
    
    
    Eric Ries: No matter how long you wait, you will be embarrassed by the first version of your product. Get customer feedback ASAP. #inspeaker    
    
    
    Eric Ries: as an engineer you may have a point of view about quality. But customers are the ultimate arbiters of product quality. #inspeaker    
    
    
    Thanks Eric Ries for answering my q about managing uncertainty: use business model to rule out impossible; learn inputs over time #inspeaker    
    
    
    @jerepick As Eric answered, the key is to treat innovation as hypothesis testing. cf. http://thenoisychannel.com/2012/04/25/science-as-a-strategy/ …    
    
    
    @jerepick Hypothesis generation is how you decide what to try. But learning comes from hypothesis testing and analyzing results.    
    
    
    @jerepick Hopefully you're continually doing both in a virtuous cycle.    
    
    
    @jerepick Completely agree with you there. I know, I'm no fun.    
    
    
    Successful orgs are those with workers in charge of the management http://lnkd.in/bXG26hM  Better yet http://lnkd.in/j4AVTT     
    
    
    Happy Bosses Day! Please celebrate by giving your boss a performance review. http://lnkd.in/j4AVTT     
    
    
    We've been trying to get @Comcast to restore our broadband service for 3 days. Anyone else know how to get customer service from them? #fail    
    
    
    @scottopia Thanks, will try that.    
    
    
    @comcastcares We've been trying to get Comcast to restore our broadband for 3 days. Your reps have misdirected us, and no-showed w/o a call.    
    
    
    @comcastcares It's hard to fit all of our frustration into 140 chars but you get the idea. Can you help? Happy to send more details by DM.    
    
    
    @peterleonard In Mountain View @comcast is one of the few options. But will look into @sonicnet. Thanks!    
    
    
    Congrats @kmlake, @ericcolson, and the whole Stitch Fix team on your $12M Series B! http://lnkd.in/ban7kqE     
    
    
    I, for one, welcome our new Data Elite overlords. http://lnkd.in/bA5qDpv     
    
    
    Good news: the government shutdown is over. Bad news: an example in my slides is now a bit dated. #cikm2013 http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @ComcastMelissa We still have no service. We have an appointment at 7am tomorrow. We had to book it in person your office.    
    
    
    @ComcastMelissa Believe me I will. Thank you for responding. ButI hope you understand I'm not a Comcast fan right now.    
    
    
    Honored to be keynoting ACM @WebSciConf 2014 along with @DameWendyDBE and @jobsworth. http://www.websci14.org/     
    
    
    @flojee Thanks!    
    
    
    @elunca @arunbatchu Thanks!    
    
    
    Congrats to my friends at Google on a great Q3! http://lnkd.in/b9nsW3m     
    
    
    "Google’s business continues to be the one thing for which it’s best known—search." -- @mims http://lnkd.in/ba6QiHC     
    
    
    Last chance to sign up for QCon SF! Register before 10/25 to save $400, and $100 more with SPEAKTUNK100 code. http://lnkd.in/b_yafvi     
    
    
    Despite previous frustration with @Comcast, I was very impressed with tech Dominic Martinez who restored service this AM. cc @ComcastMelissa    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker True that. I see so many people who randomly walk through the professional graph without figuring out what they really want.    
    
    
    @IR_oldie By CS journals do you mean compilations of extended versions of year-old CS conference papers?    
    
    
    Sorry I missed today's workshop at Stanford on Reputation, Trust, and Authority. Hope slides will be posted. http://lnkd.in/bpaWJYV     
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who endorsed me for Karaoke and helped place it in my top 10 skills!    
    
    
    @paulwehner Absolutely. Thanks!    
    
    
    I now have more endorsements for karaoke than for recommender systems. Which is a great excuse for not making it to #recsys2013 :-)    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks for sharing. Feels like consumer version of my @TTIVanguard talk on interacting with big data https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130502234056-50510-big-data-we-have-a-communication-problem …    
    
    
    Loser pays for frivolous lawsuits by patent trolls? Please SCOTUS, grant us this small favor. http://lnkd.in/b_Z3pXi     
    
    
    @techmilind I see karaoke as part of my professional identity. :-)    
    
    
    Scott Adams argues that passion is the result of success. Interesting. Passion motivates me to pursue success …http://lnkd.in/bu8CiNa     
    
    
    Taste in food is personal and subjective. Except for bacon. http://lnkd.in/bNG8tU5     
    
    
    I, for one, welcome our new robot barista overlords. http://lnkd.in/bd4VhHA  http://lnkd.in/b9mgftu     
    
    
    @friedberg: doing a startup means having a deserving problem & being passionate about changing the world http://lnkd.in/bVEVgnJ     
    
    
    You're the Boss of You https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131021125257-50510-you-re-the-boss-of-you …    
    
    
    You're the boss of you: your responsibility as an employee to your manager, your employer, and yourself http://lnkd.in/bJ_gH_i     
    
    
    Thanks @hmason for posting the full set of videos from DataGotham 2013 on YouTube! http://lnkd.in/dXKFS5p     
    
    
    Congrats to @datariver, @jrgoldman, @anutewary & Level Up on acquisition by Intuit! http://lnkd.in/dV7X8Dc     
    
    
    Interesting move posted on LinkedIn but not in tech press: @nathanfolkman left CTO post at @path to join @samsung https://www.linkedin.com/pub/nathan-folkman/0/400/3a2 …    
    
    
    Congrats to @sarahtavel, @jrauser, @jeremyl and everyone at Pinterest on your $225M round! http://lnkd.in/d-5DfvD     
    
    
    Are you a manager who thinks it's enough to tell employees "your door is always open"? Here's a good read. http://lnkd.in/dVQ4Xqy     
    
    
    @kellan A data scientist never reveals his secrets. :-)    
    
    
    @jerepick Fair enough. But it was a dumb promise. Instead they should've promised to be as user-first as possible with an ad-supported model    
    
    
    Love the great speakers at LinkedIn. Today: Brad Stone talking about history of Jeff Bezos & Amazon. Watch at http://lnkd.in/6RV89M     
    
    
    Impressed by the intensity of Amazon's culture & Jeff Bezos's idealism. But not sure I could ever work there. http://lnkd.in/dC_SDvU     
    
    
    First time I've heard of the "Amazon.love" memo. Protip: don't Google "amazon.love" at work. http://lnkd.in/d8sBk8D     
    
    
    @jerepick I'm sure you can. :-)    
    
    
    @whita I'm just glad I didn't try to "feel lucky" with that particular search.    
    
    
    @astrobiased @mrogati @Jawbone Congrats!    
    
    
    Proud of the engineering team that built LinkedIn Intro for iOS. Check out the updated @LinkedInEng blog post http://lnkd.in/dxZ6NrT     
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Then don't use it :-) It's opt-in and very clear about how it works.    
    
    
    Only 3 more days til #cikm2013! Excited to talk about Social Search in a Professional Context on Monday. http://lnkd.in/b8S_QF2     
    
    
    @pankaj Hey, that's what weekends are for. :-)    
    
    
    @techmatchmaker Please elaborate. Perhaps in a forum that provides more than 140 characters to express your thoughts. :-)    
    
    
    "One chord is fine. Two chords are pushing it. Three chords and you're into jazz." RIP, Lou Reed. http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/27/showbiz/lou-reed-obit/ …    
    
    
    Taught my daughter selection sort vs insertion sort today. Hoping she'll pick up quicksort before she turns 6. #DevelopHer    
    
    
    Looking forward to Gayatree Ganu's defense: Understanding Preferences & Similarities from User-Authored Text http://lnkd.in/dGv_2YY     
    
    
    @maui314159 I think recursive approach is more intuitive, but I'll let her decide when we get there. She tends to have strong opinions. :-)    
    
    
    @marcozag Thanks, will check it out.    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff She did great. O(n^2) but she's getting the constant down. :-)    
    
    
    @ian_soboroff To be clear, we're still just working through the algorithms. Coding will come later.    
    
    
    @AmbassadorToyPA She's got over a month.    
    
    
    @gstam I'm sure it will be after she passes her defense and publishes the dissertation.    
    
    
    @elunca Sorry the community is fragmented between conferences this week. On my way (by train) to #cikm2013. Enjoy #dagEIR!    
    
    
    @gingdottwit @ebuie We all miss @HCIR_GeneG. Fortunately his ideas don't have to choose between conferences -- his influence is ubiquitous.    
    
    
    @elunca Just another beautiful day in the valley. :-) http://www.weather.com/weather/tenday/Burlingame+CA+94010:4:US …    
    
    
    Getting started at the DUBMOD workshop at #cikm2013 https://sites.google.com/site/umsocial2013/ …    
    
    
    Now up at the DUBMOD workshop: @pankaj giving a keynote on User Modeling at Twitter #cikm2013    
    
    
    Interesting: Twitter has power law for out-degree, not just in-degree. Especially since attention is finite http://thenoisychannel.com/2009/01/13/a-twitter-analog-to-pagerank/ … #cikm2013    
    
    
    Interested in paper @pankaj cited: On the Precision of Social and Information Networks #cikm2013 http://stanford.edu/~rezab/papers/precision.pdf …    
    
    
    @tomwilliams No objection as long as you do it in a way that accounts for gaming. At least if anyone is paying attention to the numbers.    
    
    
    Never managed to use Twitter lists effectively but glad they're useful for mining what people are known for and user interests. #cikm2013    
    
    
    @tomwilliams I hear you. But I think the problem is harder than it looks.    
    
    
    Ordinary language is powerful -- the fundamental lexical hypothesis. #cikm2013 http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lexical_hypothesis …    
    
    
    Didn't know that Twitter built a topic hierarchy. Would love to use it to follow topics or people-topic pairs rather than people. #cikm2013    
    
    
    Hubs and authorities on list-members bipartite graph beats topic-sensitive PageRank on follow graph for identifying topic experts. #cikm2013    
    
    
    Love that "chatter" is an identifiable topic on Twitter. Hope ASONAM 2013 paper is available online. cc @pankaj #cikm2013    
    
    
    Back from coffee break for short talks. First up: eBay research on Session Modeling to Predict Online Buying Behavior #cikm2013    
    
    
    Next: Twitter Anticipates Bursts of Requests for Wikipedia Articles #cikm2013    
    
    
    Twitter leads, Wikipedia lags. But only by about an hour. #cikm2013    
    
    
    And now research on Pinterest data: Automatically Linking Pinterest Pins to Online Webshops #cikm2013    
    
    
    Last talk before lunch & before my keynote: Content-boosted Maximum Margin Matrix Factorization for Flickr Group Recommendation #cikm2013    
    
    
    Hope everyone had a nice lunch. Giving my keynote at DUBMOD workshop in a few minutes on Social Search in a Professional Context #cikm2013    
    
    
    @xamat I'll log out in a few minutes if you promise to live-tweet my talk :-)    
    
    
    @ahbugdayci We'll see. I envision an arms race between the difficulty of technical phone screen questions and her speed of learning.    
    
    
    @pankaj Thanks! Enjoyed yours as well.    
    
    
    Attending the workshops / tutorials at #cikm2013? Bunch of us are going to the Elephant Bar afterward. Join us! http://www.elephantbar.com/location/burlingame …    
    
    
    Social Search in a Professional Context - my #cikm2013 slides https://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131029000013-50510-social-search-in-a-professional-context …    
    
    
    @xamat Come over any time, we're here!    
    
    
    @xamat Unfortunately not. But we shouldn't need a conference to catch up. Worst case, see you at QCon in a couple of weeks. :-)    
    
    
    Thanks Jalal Mahmud, James Caverlee, Michelle Zhou for inviting me to #cikm2013 DUBMOD workshop. My slides: http://lnkd.in/dZXQeGH     
    
    
    For anyone I didn't get to meet at #cikm2013, LinkedIn is hiring! Please talk to my colleagues to learn more, or reach out to me personally.    
    
    
    @ramnathb Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Happy National Cat Day! http://www.nationalcatday.com/     
    
    
    The NSA may lack a conscience, but is making up for it in competence. At least if Snowden et al are telling the truth http://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/nsa-infiltrates-links-to-yahoo-google-data-centers-worldwide-snowden-documents-say/2013/10/30/e51d661e-4166-11e3-8b74-d89d714ca4dd_story.html?Post+generic=%3Ftid%3Dsm_twitter_washingtonpost …    
    
    
    An interesting take on "pro-social gossip" in the workplace by Wharton professor Adam Grant. http://lnkd.in/dKvSiqd     
    
    
    Sorry to miss rest of #cikm2013. Will follow tweet stream. Posted my keynote slides on LinkedIn / Slideshare http://lnkd.in/dZXQeGH     
    
    
    Have you read my faceted search book? If so, could you please leave me a review on Amazon? Thanks! :-) http://lnkd.in/ds4vye6     
    
    
    @vagabondjack Grab a copy from the bookshelf by my desk. :-)    
    
    
    @msbernst @iadh Probably. Most authors are kind enough to post PDFs of their papers somewhere easy to find. :-)    
    
    
    @jongovi Thanks for the review!    
    
    
    @msbernst @iadh I could have sworn I had a USB drive with the proceedings, but I can't find it. Worst case, email the authors.    
    
    
    Attending #cikm2013? Want to learn more about search at LinkedIn? Be sure to find my colleague @abhimanyulad and swing by our sponsor booth.    
    
    
    Dear friends at @Google, happy to offer you my stash of prior art on associative search engines. Call me :-) http://lnkd.in/dnx3xAH     
    
    
    @dannysullivan Agreed, there's prior art in both industry and academia on this. Happy to send references if you're curious -- DM / email me.    
    
    
    My daughter on Halloween. Baby, she's a firework! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=olnaTZYf8vQ …    
    
    
    Great meeting #cikm2013 attendees at LinkedIn today! Contact me if you'd like to learn more. http://lnkd.in/UU-Vkc     
    
    
    @marcprecipice I think they make irony supplements. Then again, most of what you read online is fortified with a full day's supply of irony.    
    
    
    Just signed 30-day notice to my apartment complex. Hopefully our house is ready for us in time. If not, the office has comfy chairs...    
    
    
    No response from @google. Hope their in-house prior art search is better than this: http://www.google.com/patents/related/text#c=0&d1&d2=02%2F12%2F1997&t=1associative%20search%20engines ….    
    
    
    Count me as a Bill Gates fanboy. Curing diseases that kill millions is higher priority than global broadband. http://lnkd.in/dVZ55aA     
    
    
    Nothing wrong with PhDs that aren't career investments -- if students are informed and universities disclose. http://lnkd.in/dSn6Kaq     
    
    
    @jonathankoren I'm all for global hedonic optimization. But should we optimize for experienced or remembered utility? http://eprints.lse.ac.uk/22750/1/04064.pdf …    
    
    
    @communicating Thanks. She had a blast. I think all kids should get lit up for Halloween. :-)    
    
    
    @daringfireball I'm no Google fanboy - my household is 100% Apple. But don't equate Google's defensive tactics to MS+Apple's offensive ones.    
    
    
    