This is what's left of the cake which had to undergo emergency surgery pic.twitter.com/LBTZtHIpih    
    
    
    Seems that storm was somewhat over egged then....    
    
    
    @julienisbet she's a cutie though    
    
    
    Is it normal for your hips to actually creek as you walk up the stairs?    
    
    
    Oops. Left my phone in the car this morning and only just noticed. Went back to retrieve it and poor thing had been ringing its head off    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 is this an Andy audit or a Craig audit ? #justwondering    
    
    
    Double workout today. 3 mile run at lunch time plus an hour circuit training. Blimey I'm becoming one of 'them'    
    
    
    No moon at all tonight. Nearly broke my neck walking the puppies around millennium green @sirhappyfeet    
    
    
    Walked into a bush FFS    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan @julienisbet I haven't but I always like a new challenge    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton which Boney M are we talking here?    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet @RuthStapleton Boney M performed live at my graduation ball. Cool, I know    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton @sirhappyfeet well it was a good few years ago    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I know Ruth. @sirhappyfeet doesn't appreciate good music that's all    
    
    
    Hey @sirhappyfeet leading your daughter astray pic.twitter.com/IV3yUIipel    
    
    
    I need @babynisbet to help me play blackjack mire often. I started with £10 only 15 mins ago. Tripled it pic.twitter.com/vAGbXyRt6A    
    
    
    I think she wants me to play 5 boxes not 3 @babynisbet pic.twitter.com/dkFLPWLsHd    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet she won me £20 what a clever girl. She knows basic strategy now    
    
    
    Stupidly busy at work meaning my fitbit step count is in the red most days. Need more lunchtime runs I think. Or to take my desk out    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet have a cute baby in tow may get us upgraded to 1st class but also may make us look a bit gay!    
    
    
    @davey_mc we can all have one    
    
    
    Pretty impressed with my new now TV which arrived this morning    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet @TASHA_BAYNHAM @stevieguitar40 Christ don't ask me. @Nikkidee2000 is chief bin putter outer    
    
    
    @leanham44 you can get @ahradio on it    
    
    
    I hate chuggers and I particularly hate telephone chuggers. Poor Indian bloke just got it for phoning me. I asked for their charity no too    
    
    
    Today I must have a 'please stop me' sign on. Tramps, chuggers and lost pedestrians all asking for stuff today    
    
    
    @passy73 I gave the tramp 2p - I did feel sorry for him    
    
    
    @edjames we had that in France. The accordion player made us all lol at the stereotypical French man with a striped top and accordion    
    
    
    Tonight I learned that there are about 10,000 satellite channels on a motorised system and that friggin JML sells shit in 500 languages    
    
    
    Ahh the first of the month. The day where most of the money drains from my bank account in one fell swoop.    
    
    
    Managed to get through the night without being called out which is positive.    
    
    
    @The_Robbo those two would need more than 1 bottle though, crazy psycho bleach ladies    
    
    
    @The_Robbo aye they were. TV love mixing extremes though, dirty mingers vs OCD cleaners being a prime example    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton pension as early as you can. I joined mine at 22. Retirement seems a long way off but it compounds so much    
    
    
    Bought my poppy today. Have you got yours yet??    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton there are tax advantages too, get them to cost it up because it can cost very little and your employer has to put £££ in    
    
    
    Can't believe how big @The_Robbo 's dog has grown to in a matter of weeks. Are they feeding it weetabix or sommat ?    
    
    
    Frost! I didn't expect that on my car window    
    
    
    Hahaha. Loved the start of @johnkendal3 show. Thought I was watching corrie    
    
    
    @julienisbet you got the lurgy ?    
    
    
    Hey @The_Robbo do you fancy this? http://www.runnation.co.uk/run-northumberland-half-marathon-2014-99-p.asp …    
    
    
    @The_Robbo yeah that’s the one. I quite enjoyed that one, until the last couple of miles with those stupid hills. But hills are healthy    
    
    
    @FionaAlton we are still in the same queue    
    
    
    What an absolute shambles. Archers Ice Cream parlour firework display. Terrible organisation. 90% of people leaving before fireworks. Boooo    
    
    
    If it wasn't a charity event I'd be asking for a refund    
    
    
    @FionaAlton we gave up at 7:45. The kids were crying, it was cold and there was no info so we just called it a (disappointing) night    
    
    
    @GNairambulance I hope you managed to raise a decent amount of cash from the charity bonfire, but it was a shambles from our point of view.    
    
    
    @leanham44 and you love it    
    
    
    Sat at work, but have got @ahradio on and John Morgan is playing some good tunes today.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 I've left now, I came in at 8. The others came in a bit later and are still around    
    
    
    Very true , I nicked it from Facebook pic.twitter.com/yjU7gAMGHw    
    
    
    @julienisbet apparently rubbing Vicks on your feet and leaving a sock on helps. Worked last time I tried it. No idea how or why    
    
    
    Really successful night at @SpiceLounge11  - raised over £800 I almost left without paying the bill. Yikes that would have made me popular !    
    
    
    @armsta01 @SpiceLounge11 only 1 point in it. Very good effort indeed. Might revisit the sports round next time    
    
    
    Pretty tired this morning after a late night at the @ahradio event. 4 hours of 'Great Line Management'. I will try to be enthusiastic    
    
    
    Giving the fireworks at Hardwick Hall a try out. 100% than archers already and it was only £5. The rides will cost! pic.twitter.com/pcTxBK7ChK    
    
    
    Hardwick Hall pulled it off very wells. 30 minutes of fireworks, only cost £5 for all of us. Kids loved it pic.twitter.com/AUy9Caeb6P    
    
    
    Bollocks! - that is all    
    
    
    Great service from @British_Airways today. Couldn't have been more helpful. Pleased to be jetting off to Vegas in January with them    
    
    
    @British_Airways we will do thanks. It's a 30th birthday Vegas special for @sirhappyfeet first long haul with BA. So far very good    
    
    
    My French class has moved onto the subject of food. A fantastic topic. I want to try a Paris-Brest. Need to get to France I think    
    
    
    This is a Paris-Brest by the way pic.twitter.com/wgIBb7Jkn9    
    
    
    With being uber busy at work and lots of other things going on my running is taking a hot. Need to get out more and get some miles in    
    
    
    I think the only way to start the day is with a large costa. Then we'll go from there    
    
    
    Had my day brightened up by a man who looks like Emmett Brown belly laughing loudly while reading his paper. I'll have what he's drinking!    
    
    
    @gazza_d round the twist !    
    
    
    Faux pas of the day. I accidentally told my boss I'm Leaving. I meant to write, I've put some leave in    
    
    
    Doing a disco for 40 under 8s. All asking for bleedin one direction or someone    
    
    
    @gazza_d @KarlOnSea @amsterdamized @marksuttonbike no no no. People shouldn't be controlled by permit, it has to be a choice. Not northkorea    
    
    
    @gazza_d @KarlOnSea you need a permit at work so they can skim off £20 a month from your salary. They don't care about our parking really.    
    
    
    Good all. Another work day today. Lots to do. I bought chocolate bars to keep the troops going. Only at Darlo unfortunately.    
    
    
    Which pillock at Microsoft is in charge of error messages? No the message wasn't helpful at all. Fools. pic.twitter.com/fNTaw8cT6r    
    
    
    @KarlOnSea @gazza_d I would like to be able to cycle to work, but there is no real safe way for me to do it. I tried it a few weeks ago    
    
    
    Spent a fortune on Xmas shopping today. I think the most valuable purchase was this £1 tape dispenser pic.twitter.com/Rvij5tsOhy    
    
    
    Well, I liked the Marks and Sparks roast beef in red wine gravy. Would get use to this kind of grub. Maybe need a lottery win to keep it up    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan Watching it too    
    
    
    Awww the little girl at the Festival of Remembrance. She got it word perfect.    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @julienisbet OH CHRIST. Why would you do that? I’ve never watched it again, for very good reason.    
    
    
    I wonder if they’ll end with the National Anthem? I love a bit of God Save The Queen    
    
    
    @The_Leechy @julienisbet OH the shame    
    
    
    HERE WE GO. #GodSaveTheQueen    
    
    
    I liked the way the entire audience at the Albert Hall all turned to the face the Queen as the sang the national anthem. That looked nice.    
    
    
    @julienisbet wrapping Xmas presents. Observing a silence at 11am and going for lunch chez @pigglyugg and @pigglyuggswife then to @ahradio    
    
    
    @richardosman did you find it funny that @julienisbet thought The Princess of Wales was called Diana Andrews ?    
    
    
    Well, my breakfast isn't gonna make itself. I suppose I'd better get up, or shout down for @Nikkidee2000 to get the bacon butties on    
    
    
    @davembe name and shame them Dave    
    
    
    @davembe there's no excuse for that.    
    
    
    Her Majesty did a Stirling job once again this morning    
    
    
    @leanham44 I had missed it and now opened that just as I was tucking into my Sunday lunch    
    
    
    The downside of doing the show on my own is I had to run up 2 flights and stairs to the ward with a prize before the song finishes @ahradio    
    
    
    HA, if abba do reunite you'll all be agreeing with me. I said on national telly that I love abba and I will be proved right very soon    
    
    
    Good morning tweets. Today will be interesting if nothing else    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 we have a major new system going live today    
    
    
    Well it's been an interesting half day that's for sure    
    
    
    Prostitutes in rio learning English ahead if World Cup? Surely sucky sucky, me love you long time doesn't take much learning.    
    
    
    @gazza_d and if you borrowed that on an unauthorised overdraft it would be a fortune more than that.    
    
    
    @David_Cameron correct, however It's not right that we send money to a country with a space programme.    
    
    
    Bloody charity telephone chuggers! I wish they’d sod off. I don’t give money to anyone over the phone    
    
    
    £8 a month these charities are asking for. No way.    
    
    
    You can text DEC to 70000 to donate £5 to those poor people in the Philippines    
    
    
    Well I'm off to bed. Goodnight all.    
    
    
    Good morning tweets    
    
    
    @gazza_d yes but by the same argument drivers aren't deliberately diving into cyclists either.    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan and I've volunteered my wife to knock up a Paris-Brest    
    
    
    @afneil I don't give a frack either way    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I don't think anyone would watch your tape. Sorry to disappoint your new entrepreneurial ambitions    
    
    
    @TheNobler @sirhappyfeet that was tweet of the year nobler!    
    
    
    After an initial shock I am now rolling my sleeves up for a pretty impressive comeback @adwatson1984 is gonna have to be the voice of reason    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 haha no I'd forgotten about that one. I'm gonna get a costa machine installed in the dept for instant caffeine relief    
    
    
    @julienisbet find the real job centre twitter account then give them hell    
    
    
    My scales are broken. This is gonna affect my OCD weighing routine. I wonder if salter can fix them.    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 you doing anything in particular?    
    
    
    3rd weekend at work in a row. Actually, quite like Saturdays. Get loads done.    
    
    
    Very productive morning in a bizarre kind of way.    
    
    
    I need to start taking cash to costco. Every time I go I end up spending a fortune. Got some crackin deals though I suppose    
    
    
    @gazza_d these kind of cases are so sad because it could be the driver or the cyclist in the wrong. One is dead the other life ruined.    
    
    
    @gazza_d no one will ever really know what happened. That's the problem.    
    
    
    @julienisbet yes she got an award from the queen you know. Don't you think MI5 had her checked out before inviting her to the palace?    
    
    
    The global warming lobby have jumped on the Philippines storm as being down to climate change when there is no evidence at all.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 this morning I have also encountered a load of pricks. Maybe it's drive like a wanker day and no one told us    
    
    
    I bought 3 packs of rocky bar today. For the price of 1. Living the dream here folks. Rocky anyone?    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I won’t lie to you, I do go in there, but I am a bit of a supermarket whore. I only go where the offers attract me    
    
    
    I just bloody sneezed and pulled a muscle. Owww    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton Remember - eye level is buy level. Always look down for the offers    
    
    
    Meanwhile over on Facebook, everyone is sharing those stupid 'share if you love your mother' and 'if you're proud of your son' etc    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan 10th rings a bell    
    
    
    @leanham44 he's growing up now,
Doesn't wanna be in mam and dad's bed anymore    
    
    
    @gazza_d @individualjs @StripyMoggie Add some garlic and you'd be branded a Frenchman    
    
    
    @leanham44 Well we don’t like to see house guests go hungry.    
    
    
    A stone off since my holidays which is pretty good, but my wedding ring is now hanging off my finger. I want it off my stomach not fingers!    
    
    
    @leanham44 can I just add that @Nikkidee2000 did the cooking, my job was simply to reheat said meal.    
    
    
    @leanham44 the grunter thinks sky is free    
    
    
    @leanham44 @Nikkidee2000 I never said I’d made it. I said I’d bought the beef and whacked it in the slow cooker. There my contribution ends    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan best of luck tomorroe    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: The Fastest Judge Judy Trial Ever - stupid criminals at work  http://view.break.com/2541520     
    
    
    The commute from hell. I can understand why people get stressed out with this kind of traffic    
    
    
    Got home and @Nikkidee2000 has been baking Christmas cakes. Smells lush    
    
    
    Very productive day. Managed to get another step forward on a big project. But tonight I've got French class. Looking forward to weekend    
    
    
    I think they should have a gogglebox show for people watching gogglebox. They are funny to watch.    
    
    
    If the whole IT thing becomes a chore I'm gonna become a professional blackjack player with @sirhappyfeet - doubled our money once again :-)    
    
    
    Time for Dr. Who. Please do not disturb until 9:05    
    
    
    Ice cream parlour you say? Free compensatory ice creams you say? Oh go on then, I'll have a 3 scoop sundae with a flake in and nuts on top    
    
    
    My email is so lucky it’s won the lottery and resigned. Please post letters to me from now on pic.twitter.com/iaU4T4aFRg    
    
    
    Charlotte just announced that in 93 years she’ll be 100. Factually correct and with life expectancy as it is, she’s probably right.    
    
    
    A busy day and tonight I'll be taking the @ahradio quiz to @SpiceLounge11 for a charity quiz.    
    
    
    @TASHA_BAYNHAM ah maybe it was the one I dropped ;-)    
    
    
    I love coming to one of the sites at work. The place is plastered with passive aggressive notes. The kitchen is particularly bad.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 no, I say we go direct aggressive, no need for passiveness    
    
    
    Gotta let the trolls know the don't bother you , Celebrities Read Mean Tweets http://besoci.al/1kUsYp     
    
    
    Christ I think if leg it too, Curse Of Chucky Prank http://besoci.al/WKIVyu     
    
    
    I wonder how much cocaine Nigella put in her chocolate brownies recipe. 290g or 320g ? I can just imagine the scene as she buys it too haha    
    
    
    @KTHopkins I thought the dog was taking an over active interest in this ! pic.twitter.com/t9MrGH6q4N    
    
    
    I'm gonna have to get my Nigella photo swabbed. If her hands have been in it, there could be traces of anything pic.twitter.com/ktJIkgHmFU    
    
    
    Following a very annoying puncture on the M62 I am now say in kwik fit, middle of nowhere branch waiting for a new tyre    
    
    
    Hmmm I think this kwik fit need to review their name. Nothing bloody quick about it    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: This French Tenant Takes Revenge On His Landlord http://view.break.com/2544826     
    
    
    @davey_mc nah it wasn't the trousers,
It was the tip off I phoned in about a dodgy geezer    
    
    
    Yesterday @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc left me a box of Heroes for the long trip back home. This is the result pic.twitter.com/bWXvutwZXz    
    
    
    If you're American, happy thanksgiving. If you're not, crack on, it's just a normal day. And forget all this Black Friday nonsense tomorrow    
    
    
    @davey_mc within the very limited customs regulations of course    
    
    
    @davey_mc taking photos of the plane will guarantee your camera is smashed to pieces and a strip search performed    
    
    
    This is why Facebook is getting shitter, it's full of idiots who post this kind of crap all day pic.twitter.com/fflWpgz4cG    
    
    
    Arrrggghhh my email account is full of Black Friday offers. It's only a Black Friday for me because of the awful weather. *deletes emails    
    
    
    Ha just heard on the news about these losers sleeping outside of the shop to buy a friggin PS4 at midnight. Fools.    
    
    
    @davey_mc what you doing in twitter?? I thought you were trampling loads of crazy bargain hunters in a scrum for a bargain    
    
    
    @KTHopkins she's gonna get struck down with a big bolt of lightening, mark my words    
    
    
    I'm beginning to wonder if I want to go to this mad house. These people ar…, Black Friday Shopping Chaos Compilation http://besoci.al/IfweaC     
    
    
    @The_Robbo @julienisbet aye, she grabbed the limelight when we went in Noel's house party back in the 90's. Isn't that right liane?    
    
    
    @davey_mc sounds too much for our friends in customs anyway    
    
    
    Looks like a police helicopter has come down in Glasgow    
    
    
    I think I need a cookie blocker. Every website I go on has ads which are clearly targeted to my activities. Kids toys and running things    
    
    
    Good morning tweets.    
    
    
    @passy73 the 2 darlings are up and therefore so am I, enjoying Tangled or something! pic.twitter.com/3xdewNyp8w    
    
    
    Ha, I heard the Rainbow TV theme on an advert. I shouted 'aww rainbow', Thomas runs to the window to look for it. Need to educate the kids!    
    
    
    So the government announce a £12 rebate on energy. Whoop whoop. Start thinking £12 PER MONTH and we may notice a slight difference in bills    
    
    
    @davey_mc looks nice. Did it come with chips?    
    
    
    @davey_mc Erm.... It's ok ill pass    
    
    
    Come out to these public events and @Nikkidee2000 knows everyone, including the local druggie it seems. You can tell they're skanky    
    
    
    You see folks, our old friend Karma works in both directions http://www.uptv.com/blog/uplifting-person-of-the-day-waitress-pays-for-customers-lunch …    
    
    
    Popped down @SpiceLounge11 for some grub. The place is heaving. Most popular venue in town it seems    
    
    
    @davey_mc now I like that idea. Porterhouse would be for ne    
    
    
    Well we're into December. I'd better get a haircut I suppose!    
    
    
    Attempting to make a French choux pastry dessert with 2 kids isn't going exactly to plan . Bloody French recipe! pic.twitter.com/VsKshzaw2v    
    
    
    2nd attempt at the Paris Brest. I know,
I forgot to dust with icing sugar before taking the photo pic.twitter.com/FamYtmbHx4    
    
    
    @davey_mc @leanham44 what's wrong with abba ?    
    
    
    #12DaysofJonesDAY1 gotta be in it to win it folks. Come on twitter, @dragonjones    
    
    
    @davey_mc yes that looks fairly decent, i would have that    
    
    
    @davey_mc I dare say it would exceed the recommended daily calorific intake of an adult but it does look nice    
    
    
    @davey_mc @leanham44 @LindsayMc21 ha! Last time I was in the USA I ate a bag that size for breakfast    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 guns and knives being the most bizarre. Oh and 8XL shirts    
    
    
    @davey_mc what the 'fork' is that?? Did you see what I did there? Fork... Erm... I'm here all week    
    
    
    I took the Paris-Brest over to @pigglyugg and @pigglyuggswife house today. They thought it was lush. Hope they're not ill tomorrow :-)    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 had you been here you could have had a slice    
    
    
    Oh well played Npower. Whack your prices right up then charge in as heroes by offering a price freeze for 18 months. We aren't fooled.    
    
    
    I think the energy companies have suddenly realised that they're in danger of becoming the new bankers if they're not careful. Unpopular.    
    
    
    Dear @David_Cameron my energy bill recently went up by £20 per month. Your £12 per year doesn't even touch the sides I'm afraid. Try harder    
    
    
    @CCHQPress very good but let's try and keep the details of the autumn statement private until he stands up in parliament to announce it. Ta.    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis yup it looks like the online app is down too pic.twitter.com/Jd8jCGu4oq    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help come on, what's occurring ??    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK I think they need to turn it on and off again pic.twitter.com/IsEYIzKjgV    
    
    
    @julienisbet you're a star. I'm eating free bacon butties in a posh hotel in Manchester    
    
    
    @julienisbet mammy always gives them to the teacher, I just dump them at the gate lol    
    
    
    @davey_mc I'm sure my balance is £10000 down    
    
    
    @davey_mc no, they compensated me and I backed down    
    
    
    @davey_mc ah yes, coca cola's attempt to sell us Brits tap water. It appears the yanks are still falling for it    
    
    
    Just posted a 5.04 mi run -   #RunKeeper http://rnkpr.com/a4l3sch     
    
    
    @BestProAdvice what is this 7/11 you speak of?    
    
    
    If nigella says she isn't a druggie that's good enough for me.    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK how did you get this information ? The government aren't leaking the autumn statement before hand again are they?    
    
    
    @SkyNewsBreak how did you get this information ?    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: Ultra-Realistic Morgan Freeman Finger Painting - wow http://view.break.com/2546671     
    
    
    @george_osbourne you may as well take the day off mate, most of your speech has been on twitter as usual before you deliver it. Very poor    
    
    
    It's a bit windy outside today.    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK I'd like to hear about it all on the day, from the chancellor, in parliament and not all leaked in advance. It's not acceptable    
    
    
    @BBCBusiness who told you that? The government haven't been leaking again have they?    
    
    
    @theanthonydavis no need to be excited, looks like @George_Osborne has leaked most of it early as usual    
    
    
    Have to say, the autumn statement sounds pretty good so far. Not bad, of course we had already heard most if it in advance    
    
    
    Looks like the river tyne is overflowing into places it shouldn't    
    
    
    @davey_mc perhaps send a mop for the river tyne which is over it's banks    
    
    
    @gazza_d how would you describe the NHS pay freeze ? Not a subsidy to someone  I would suggest    
    
    
    @gazza_d but it was a theoretical tax anyway, it never happened so you can't hypothesise what you could have done with it    
    
    
    @Jim01081 I don't do TV, except pointless of course    
    
    
    @davey_mc so what does giraffe taste like? Chicken I bet    
    
    
    Xmas tree and boxes galore out of the loft. It's gonna take half a day tomorrow to get the house festive. Hope @johnkendal3 has Xmas songs    
    
    
    Good Food HD is showing Nigella Christmas again. Yeah, sweet potato soup and mince pies this episode.    
    
    
    Blimey, the post office are keen. Delivering parcels for Christmas at 7:20am on a Saturday. Lucky I was up    
    
    
    Telling the kids in advance the Christmas tree is going up this morning ensured a 6am wake up call to put it up pic.twitter.com/Ha776kXVL1    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc may end up stranded in the states. Problems with air traffic control. Far too risky to travel    
    
    
    @johnmyersteam walking around it isn't the problem, walking through it is    
    
    
    @davey_mc it's been top news here all day    
    
    
    Kids watching the polar express. I find it an awful, creepy film. Don't like it at all    
    
    
    Hey @julienisbet I was making some French pastry and found your dogs liked to like the bowl, hope that's ok :-) pic.twitter.com/pg4jrDAtfM    
    
    
    I do end up agreeing to the most bizarre stuff. Recording a band in ebbchester or somewhere    
    
    
    Hey @Nikkidee2000 @TopInventionss is now on twitter    
    
    
    Looks like @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc will get home after all. Problems all fixed    
    
    
    @The_Robbo is this one you're fighting on principle or do you have a chance of winning it?    
    
    
    @The_Robbo I am sure you will be able to present a robust and adequate defense in court    
    
    
    @gazza_d no no, our pay review body said 1% and the bastards are trying to wriggle out of that too whilst lining their own pockets. Shocking    
    
    
    Just caught the latest episode of The Tunnel. Now it's getting really good. Lots of twists and turns    
    
    
    My morning took an unexpected turn when I rescued a stray dog with the help of @julienisbet / she is in safe hands now    
    
    
    In the process of louring the dog into the house I managed to give it a pound of @Nikkidee2000 's premium ham. Gotta go to shop how. Oops.    
    
    
    Aww I hope the little doggy I handed into stray aid was ok. Poor thing was all alone.    
    
    
    @George_Osborne @Morrisons did they let you take it home?    
    
    
    I wonder if I can pass off a Gregg's cream bun as a Paris-Brest? I need to get this right and I only have 1 opportunity tonight to make it    
    
    
    @julienisbet you'll be fine. Just go in and knock em dead. Not literally though    
    
    
    @davey_mc yes but I'm not paying those prices. My surname isn't McElhone moneybags    
    
    
    @leanham44 I recommend Las Vegas    
    
    
    @leanham44 then Vegas is in the dessert!    
    
    
    Lure, that's how you spell lure!    
    
    
    3rd attempt at the Paris-Brest and I'm pretty damn impressed with it. The French class had better be begging for more or I'll be upset    
    
    
    Check this out from The Poke: Crazy Naked Guy Streaks On TV.  Read it here:  http://www.thepoke.co.uk/2013/12/06/crazy-naked-guy-streaks-on-tv/ … pic.twitter.com/GXXTQDyogH    
    
    
    Very true pic.twitter.com/lY7zueQ2wM    
    
    
    @gazza_d what I wanna know is, where do I get my membership card? That place looks really cheap    
    
    
    It's always good exercise when @tigerquaker borrows your car. He parks it a mile away from the hospital    
    
    
    Behind the scenes as @nisbetphotos do our Christmas card session pic.twitter.com/do6iTFpxhQ    
    
    
    One Paris-Brest complete. I hope it tastes good and the Frenchies like it pic.twitter.com/K6y6Umri6j    
    
    
    Authentic French meal they said. However we deviated slightly by the fact we had 4 courses of dessert on top of the previous courses #full    
    
    
    Genius marketing. http://youtu.be/zIEIvi2MuEk  - I love this airline and I'd never heard of them before now    
    
    
    Why Learning French isn’t hard — Fluent in 3 months - Language Hacking and Travel Tips - http://www.fluentin3months.com/french-is-not-hard/ …    
    
    
    @UgotMoed ????    
    
    
    Looking at that signer from the Mandela memorial, I could have done a better job    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I want to get our dollars where they get theirs from    
    
    
    Picking up @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc from the airport. I feel like I need a big sign like all the other collectors    
    
    
    I can I just look out for the forklift truck bringing their luggage out    
    
    
    Big bunch of young students outside of college in darlo, puffing away. How do kids of today even think it's good to start smoking?    
    
    
    @ThreeUK do you have problems with data at the moment? Good signal in Darlington very poor 3G. Keeps dropping    
    
    
    Looks like upload is working on @ThreeUK but not download    
    
    
    @ThreeUKSupport I am in the DL3 6HX area    
    
    
    @gazza_d he might have got away with it in asda    
    
    
    Some folks don't age well. Just a general observation    
    
    
    Just read about the three feel at home service. Basically I can use my mobile as if I am at home whilst in Vegas, no extra cost. Fantastic!    
    
    
    @The_Robbo but he is so cute    
    
    
    I've just realised, I haven't had a Christmas card from @David_Cameron this year. #justsaying    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 could have been worse. Could have been 7pm finish. #justsaying    
    
    
    @davey_mc according to three the only thing you need to setup is to turn off euro pass and you're in business    
    
    
    I wish you goodnight tweets. Having an early one.    
    
    
    @armsta01 people who updated their PC and it installed itself    
    
    
    @gazza_d which one    
    
    
    How come Egypt get the snow and we don't get it? What's going on with the weather? Come on its Christmas    
    
    
    @ambigfoot I share that view    
    
    
    Well, that’s @Nikkidee2000 accounts done for another year. Just need to pass to the accountant to vet. I hate doing accounts by the way    
    
    
    @johnprescott maybe a trainee?    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I'm sure the vicar was trying to get his own back on all the folks who don't believe in God, which is equally as weird as Santa    
    
    
    My hip has developed an alarming creaking noise when I walk up stairs. Googling this only causes more worry as to what it could be    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton nice to see the @ahradio one at the top    
    
    
    Our Christmas cards have been done by @nisbetphotos this year. Looking pretty impressive. Will post pic when I've sent my cards to people    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 No, but it makes an awful creaking noise. It is quite disturbing. I think I'm gonna have to go to the docs with this one    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 no it's being doing it a while    
    
    
    @niwise blister plasters work well on nipples and are easy to remove afterwards    
    
    
    @niwise the blister plasters just melt off even the hairiest of folks    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I never had @The_Robbo down as a poundland lass    
    
    
    @AdamWray2 the author of the framework perhaps    
    
    
    @The_Robbo you can buy it in kg tubs in France. I'll get some for you    
    
    
    I wonder if the head chef had access to their twitter account haha pic.twitter.com/RtK4CZ2o76    
    
    
    @julienisbet I like this head chef at the @ploughpub and he shouldn't have been fired I reckon.    
    
    
    @leanham44 from the photos it looked like you enjoyed it    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @sirhappyfeet oh    
    
    
    @julienisbet what when I come to walk the dogs??    
    
    
    I see Eastenders hasn't changed. Caught 15 mins of it and virtually every scene has had a blazing argument. Off to slit my wrists now    
    
    
    Oh now it looks like poor old dot is about to be raped and murdered, or at least robbed.    
    
    
    @gazza_d are you going to the DMH Xmas lunch on Wednesday ?    
    
    
    @gazza_d oh I'd forgotten about that. Due to cuts we may have to repeat last years    
    
    
    @gazza_d or perhaps run it in 10 minute delay so we can add an audience in    
    
    
    And these jokers want more money? Surely they should be arrested for fraud http://pbs.twimg.com/media/Bbo3wAyCAAAnieo.jpg#twimg …    
    
    
    Probably best I log out, I've been in one if those real grouchy moods all night and it's not conducive to happy tweets.    
    
    
    So, if I clocked in for 20 mins, then went home would I still get paid, or more likely I'd get fired!    
    
    
    Thomas looking dapper for his Christmas party at school pic.twitter.com/n1vE97tzwt    
    
    
    I have lost my voice. This will please many people I know    
    
    
    Talk about money laundering! @Nikkidee2000 put my wallet through a full wash cycle.    
    
    
    I'm baby sitting @MillieNisbet @CharlieNisbet and @babynisbet tonight. I bet I get wrong for taking this out pic.twitter.com/yr5bygQKfq    
    
    
    @David_Cameron it makes it easier for the scrounges too unfortunately    
    
    
    @Nikkidee2000 now now dear, I didn't expect such lightning service that's all. Lucky it wasn't full of £££ like normal or I'd be crying    
    
    
    @gazza_d get yourself joined in man, it's Christmas    
    
    
    I love the whole @ploughpub story and fact the guy @chefjimknight  managed to get a new job on the back of it. Well done that lad.    
    
    
    How do people spoof cli when spamming me?? pic.twitter.com/jB0b21epEP    
    
    
    Look @David_Cameron If you stick me in the lords, I’ll claim the £300 every day, but I’ll go there every day and stay all day. Please sort.    
    
    
    @David_Cameron I quite like the sound of Lord Robinson. I can be effective and I reckon the lords needs more people from the street.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 just remember, nobody ever said on their deathbed that they wished they'd spent more time at work.    
    
    
    Yeah yeah, it was just self raising flour you fools - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-25415095 …    
    
    
    I've spent 482.1 hours on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    What's all the fuss about a thief who dies years later? Why the celebrity status anyway? Move on @SkyNews    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 I'll be watching it later    
    
    
    The pier in St. Kilda, Australia where the woman fell offwas right near where me and @Nikkidee2000 stayed on our honeymoon.    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 we will have done too. It was horrendous for about 2 or 3 minutes. So bad it set off several car alarms in our street    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 44 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    Some cracking photos taken by @nisbetphotos pic.twitter.com/iCMJbnEisJ    
    
    
    And another @nisbetphotos picture of the kids pic.twitter.com/InP3RFlbfI    
    
    
    Today I will be mostly doing @ahradio  work with @SimonTemby (he doesn't tweet). Oh and some last minute Xmas shopping online.    
    
    
    The highlight of the broadcasting year will indeed be at 2pm when we take the studio to a packed carol service for some festive spirit.    
    
    
    @gazza_d oh, due to licence restrictions and the fact the streaming server shouldn't be overloaded we have had to restrict the audience ;-)    
    
    
    @ChriswMP problem is, you lot aren't offering any realistic credible alternative    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 46 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    I will be making a personal appearance at Sainsbury's in Bishop Auckland today, bag packing for @ahradio - please don't mob me    
    
    
    Off to the docs to get this noisy hip looked at. I hope they don't recommend I be put down    
    
    
    @edjames I'll suggest that to the doc    
    
    
    Our surgery is in the 21st century. Online appointments. Let's see if this works or if they have no idea I'm coming    
    
    
    Time keeping clearly isn't one of the strengths of this surgery. How can they be so late so early in the morning?    
    
    
    @TheNobler if I can ever get in I'll find out!    
    
    
    I'm not impressed so far. 25 mins after my appointment and someone else just got beeped into the doc I'm meant to be seeing.    
    
    
    And the NHS wonder why people show up at A&E. If the GP service is as crap as this I'm not surprised at all. I'm off shortly, will go to A&E    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 any movement?    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 should I phone and ask the ward to hold off till 24th? There is some hope for the sweepstake yet :-)    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 48 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    @leanham44 I'm full of lurgy too. Typical when I'm off work    
    
    
    Spent 3 hours wrapping presents tonight. A lot of cash doesn't wrap down into much. Not a lot to look at.    
    
    
    @leanham44  sure it will stitch    
    
    
    Still can't get my head round the @TheAtoZofPop show. Santa's sackful or something. Tongue twister that's what it is. It's on @ahradio    
    
    
    @The_Robbo how do you come to that conclusion? This was your idea    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @ambigfoot I was thinking the same    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @ambigfoot changed I'm sure    
    
    
    Metro centre isn't as bad as I thought. All presents now bought, no more is to be spent. On the plus side, the Hilton gold status continues    
    
    
    Due to the spending levels'    
    
    
    I have to admit, doing xmas shopping with @The_Robbo is like going with a bloke, straight in, item picked, straight out. All my stuff got!    
    
    
    @The_Robbo I thought they liked my banter    
    
    
    @KTHopkins @marksandspencer or just make it free and continue with the other items. Simple? Then everyone is happy    
    
    
    Arrrggghhh 4% battery life and no charger    
    
    
    @davey_mc I've got one. I done have enough of the daft power leads to carry about.    
    
    
    @leanham44 if there's too many for me just whack them in a gift bag ;-)    
    
    
    I see the south is gonna get a bit of wind and rain l. Oh, wait, we've had that all week and it didn't make the national news. Softies    
    
    
    Apparently my hip problem wasn't a hip problem, it was my knee grinding. I have patellofermoral syndrome. (Runner's Knee) would you believe!    
    
    
    @davey_mc is it busy or have you got off lightly ?    
    
    
    Got my new blackberry z10 - not a bad device    
    
    
    Sometimes you have a lucky escape, it's only later when you realise how lucky it was.    
    
    
    With all this bad weather around, The Daily Express newsroom must be in a state of constant tantric arousal    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help Hi, you've sent me a new debit card with contactless on. How do I get one without this technology please?    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help thanks. I don't fancy the idea of dropping my card and someone spending a penny on it without a pin, let alone £20    
    
    
    @The_Robbo I popped into sainsburys to get some supplies for our works buffet tomorrow. The place has been ransacked!    
    
    
    @johnmyersteam the BBC have been saying 'local radio' not the normal local BBC offering.    
    
    
    Ok, ok. I'm starting to thaw out a bit and am now feeling very festive. Hope you all have a fantastic Christmas Eve    
    
    
    @julienisbet no I am just thawing my cold heart and getting in the spirit    
    
    
    The dog which I found wandering on the main road and took to Stray Aid is back again on the loose. I've reported it and hopefully will be ok    
    
    
    We are run off our feet today pic.twitter.com/bdEZ9TwNpQ    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 someone has to hold the fort    
    
    
    Dosey me. Pick up the phone and help someone at 3:59 and it turns into a nightmare #shouldhaveletitring    
    
    
    Unfortunately that's the biggest glass we could find for @The_Robbo pic.twitter.com/CjGLJ3rAKl    
    
    
    @leanham44 wait till you see what we bought for hank    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet well as you know I'm not a drinker, but a pre Christmas warmer would go down well    
    
    
    @gazza_d @NoradSanta I will admit I've had it on all day on the Mac mini at work, Santa has been a busy boy    
    
    
    @armsta01 no, it went back to the owners in shildon again who clearly just let the poor thing just roam the streets :-(    
    
    
    @gazza_d not as slick as on this mac I bet    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet you need to teach her it's 'ho ho ho' not no no no    
    
    
    We've set a little burst through the door fun for the kids in the morning pic.twitter.com/rHrDhdqsxD    
    
    
    Last year @sirhappyfeet came and put foot prints through the house. Wonder what time he'll be over to do it this year ?    
    
    
    @Stephenlyons8 for you or John ;-) ?    
    
    
    Well campers, I'm off to bed. No doubt the kids will be up at crazy o'clock. See you all on the other side.    
    
    
    Santa has definitely been pic.twitter.com/O2Fh8DH0YS    
    
    
    @julienisbet I've extra wrapped @MillieNisbet present this year so it takes her longer    
    
    
    @The_Robbo wow what a lucky boy @leanham44 is    
    
    
    Wow, everyone has been very generous once again. Very humbled at all the lovely gifts me and the family have received.    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton we will be tuned in    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I didn't hear @ahradio on in the background mind    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton clearly the online listeners are enjoying it pic.twitter.com/mPhrLRyxDq    
    
    
    Morcambe and wise?? Really BBC, how old is this?    
    
    
    Well no one else in the house may be putting Her Majesty on so I'll listen on my iPhone. No respect. Tut tut    
    
    
    @Jim01081 do you have 1 hour or two?    
    
    
    @Jim01081 I've contacted simon to find out what's happened.    
    
    
    @Jim01081 Simon could only find part 1. Where was part 2? It's coming on at 5    
    
    
    @Jim01081 problem solved and your show will be ok the air from 5pm. For some reason your second hour was saved in a folder called 'singles'    
    
    
    I bought a few people a lottery ticket for tonight as a little quirky Christmas stocking filler. I wish them all luck. I didn't get 1 for me    
    
    
    Pleased to see Her Majesty on top form again today. Just got a chance to watch her speech on the iplayer.    
    
    
    I have to admit I had a nap earlier.
This may impede my ability to get to sleep now    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: Random Altruist with Google Glass Gives Gifts to Homeless http://view.break.com/2555802     
    
    
    Happy Boxing Day. Do yourselves a favour, save a few quid and avoid the sales. You'll only end up buying crap you didn't want and don't need    
    
    
    I will be spending the day chez @pigglyuggswife and @pigglyugg enjoying some Christmas Turkey for the 1st time this year    
    
    
    I know people on both sides of this one pic.twitter.com/qGEkOYx1r4    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I would recommend a chill out day, not leaving the house    
    
    
    Oh wow. Childhood memories. Charlotte got screwball scramble for Christmas! I had that as a kid. pic.twitter.com/xQXOWc1IKm    
    
    
    @Londonneur @AsEasyAsRiding the 4 buses in the picture don't count?    
    
    
    Why is it @NatWest_Help that every time I go to your Darlington branch I see this? What the point of having a machine pic.twitter.com/B3bL8t57TY    
    
    
    @leanham44 yeah I will send you the code    
    
    
    That's what I think of my new 'contactless' debit card. No thanks. pic.twitter.com/tN4cBihE5j    
    
    
    @leanham44 use the YouTubemp3 website for that one    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I did apart from the shard which nearly had my eye out    
    
    
    It’s pretty wild out there tonight. I thought the gales were forecast for earlier, but it is ferocious out there right now    
    
    
    @leanham44 I’ve emailed you liam    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 It’s really bad here now. Been fairly quiet all day, but since I got home from work it has been really strong winds    
    
    
    @davey_mc nothing in darlo, in fact clear skies and sunny earlier    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: Fight Fireworks With Fireworks - I wanna go there, please can I go there? http://view.break.com/2556215     
    
    
    Pound Hits Two-Year High Against Dollar - just a tad higher please before me and @sirhappyfeet arrive  http://news.sky.com/story/1187558/pound-hits-two-year-high-against-dollar …    
    
    
    @richardosman it's only because people RT rather than fav. Not scientific enough. I think we need a recount    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 New Benidorm next Thursday!    
    
    
    Just posted a 5.08 mi run - 5 Mile hilly run with Julie  #RunKeeper http://rnkpr.com/a4pbubf     
    
    
    Nice run out of @julienisbet my knee is grinding now like a bag of marbles. Doesn't hurt though just hate he noise    
    
    
    Hmm bought Mr. Muscle daily shower cleaner spray. First instruction, start with a clean shower!! That's why I bought your product, to CLEAN!    
    
    
    That poor dog I handed in to @StrayAid1 is on the loose again, running down a main road. It's gonna get knocked down. pic.twitter.com/0PSmtCl9w3    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @StrayAid1 I couldn't catch it. We had it cornered then it ran off. It's extremely timid.    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @StrayAid1 I did get it off the road    
    
    
    @The_Robbo I went through a pack of ham last time and eventually captured it    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet at least they're letting you in    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I've told them we're coming so I expect the red carpet laying down as we land    
    
    
    @leanham44 via t'interweb ?    
    
    
    So the 2nd ice breaker sent to rescue the scientists has given up. I bet they went trying to prove the ice was melting!    
    
    
    @julienisbet so you'll be pleased I bought you ferrero rocher !    
    
    
    This is why I hate windows. Even saving the most basic of notepad files and this happens pic.twitter.com/XofQhC3y4Y    
    
    
    Another stormy day out there today. Hope it eases off a bit by lunchtime    
    
    
    @julienisbet well you only have one day left to do it    
    
    
    The oldies are the best. Loving Mary Poppins    
    
    
    Ah the kids are out tonight. Me and @Nikkidee2000 are gonna enjoy some peace and quiet and a nice meal from M&S no less. #datenight    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton @ahradio @Jim01081 you on over New Years?    
    
    
    Yumm this M&S food stuff is really nice. Pity I can't afford to do my weekly shop there.    
    
    
    Don't believe it. Kids out for the night and here I am wide awake at 6am. Could have at least managed 7:30 surely!    
    
    
    The New Years honours list is huge, most of the people on it are ordinary folks doing great things. The ones you'll hear about are famous.    
    
    
    @gazza_d you weren't on the list    
    
    
    There must have been some admin error. I've been missed off the Honours list again.    
    
    
    Happy New Year to all those in New Zealand    
    
    
    @ThreeUK  I think you have 3G problems in Darlington town centre. Recently there seems to be 3G but no data. Only in town centre area    
    
    
    I hope the technology holds up for @TheAtoZofPop tonight. @ahradio are providing streaming and telephone service for the special show.    
    
    
    We are laying on a bit of a dinner tomorrow for the family. pic.twitter.com/swLj6Sc4Q9    
    
    
    I'm going to a New Year's Eve party tonight and I'm gonna have to insist they crank up the radio and tune into #NYEBB @TheAtoZofPop    
    
    
    I am now the proud owner of a onesie #justsaying    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 happy work night. It hopefully will be quiet for ya    
    
    
    Chippy tea #NYEBB haha    
    
    
    Thomas is getting into the 2014 spirit already pic.twitter.com/IusTQ1PmKV    
    
    
    @julienisbet yeah it was reference to a song @TheAtoZofPop was  playing, hence the hashtag    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 this is a family twitter feed, no need for onesie viewing    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I certainly won't be going to the ASDA in mine    
    
    
    Bacardi breezer with red bull. @Stephenlyons8 has created a new cocktail    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 @Stephenlyons8 no no, very limited drinking going on here    
    
    
    I have got the @TheAtoZofPop on at this party in Darlington. I can see the hospital from this house, does that qualify for a mention ???    
    
    
    Fascinating interview on @ahradio by @TheA toZofPop - the bradshaws are fab    
    
    
    Well Thomas is fast asleep, but Charlotte is still going strong.    
    
    
    Thank goodness the technology us holding out and the hospital radio network is still on the air. @TheAtoZofPop sounding good from Darlo    
    
    
    London that is how you do a fireworks display!!    
    
    
    I'm off to bed. Lovely hospitality of @Melanielyons6 and @Stephenlyons8 once again. Thanks    
    
    
    Good morning @TheAtoZofPop team. Still going strong. I'll have a look at this phone    
    
    
    Must annoying. The telephone problems on #NYEBB2 are out of my control. It’s at the plusnet end. I’ve logged the call and hope it fixed.    
    
    
    I woke up to this email :  There's only £-5178.38 call credit left on your Broadband Phone account. - ARRGGHH    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 No and unfortunately the guy at plus net didn’t really have any idea what was wrong. It’s a bit frustrating.    
    
    
    Oh yeah. @TheAtoZofPop can sing! Stand by me - fantastic    
    
    
        
    
    
    Blimey @TheAtoZofPop how many calls did you take over the Big Broadcast?? pic.twitter.com/x32Ls1Iko4    
    
    
    @gazza_d @bioracermanuk @Dansegers @ChrisSpencer_v1 how dare you photograph me without permission    
    
    
    @TheAtoZofPop this is heading straight to number one    
    
    
    15 people and 2 dogs for lunch today chez nous. I'm getting into the role pic.twitter.com/itcvdXJH5M    
    
    
    Got one or two over for lunch today pic.twitter.com/0rbMegZi0O    
    
    
    My dog nephew went a bit crazy in the garden and needed a good bath. I haven't shown @Nikkidee2000 the carnage pic.twitter.com/q3SGqTDjjG    
    
    
    I thought 1st April was fools day. This story is bonkers. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-asia-25560771 …    
    
    
    Ok admit it, who shrunk all my clothes??    
    
    
    I've entered the ballot for the 2014 Great North Run. Whilst I hope to get a place, they are slightly taking the P at £50 entry fee now    
    
    
    @ThreeUKSupport great thanks for the update.    
    
    
    @ThreeUKSupport I am going to Las Vegas, USA on 15th Jan. Will my phone automatically work with the feel at home service? Pay monthly iPhone    
    
    
    @TheAtoZofPop don't forget you have an A to Z of pop to do on @ahradio at 2pm. I've heard them say you're coming up soon    
    
    
    I am all to pot with my days. I thought it was Monday. Anyway, @julienisbet has talked me into breaking a habit of a lifetime, 2 runs/1day    
    
    
    @The_Robbo did you clock their reg??    
    
    
    Just posted a 3.99 mi run -   #RunKeeper http://rnkpr.com/a4qkig9     
    
    
    @ThreeUKSupport would it be enabled by default? My phone worked last time I went to France    
    
    
    @leanham44 it's behind bolams    
    
    
    @leanham44 I have to say I have yes    
    
    
    The sun headline of only fools and horses to return is a bit misleading. It's a single sketch for comic relief in March. Hardly a return    
    
    
    @David_Cameron is it true that you are seriously cutting the @EnvAgency budget Dave? Seems a bit daft based on recent weather events    
    
    
    The kids are excited. They're sleeping out at @pigglyuggswife and @pigglyugg tonight with promise of going out for some food. #highlife    
    
    
    Woman in @ASDA decides to give her kid a banana to eat in the trolley on the way around. I hope security nab her on the way out for theft    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet well they can't weight the banana at the till can they??    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet they are by weight or in pre sealed bags, she just took a banana off the shelf and gave it to her kid. Better than Mars bar    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 she was was a tea leaf    
    
    
    Adopt a polarbear ad. Not sure quite how by giving them £3 a month I'm gonna help a mother feed get cub because of melting ice #bigfreezer?    
    
    
    @baytrustradio ah an Easter weekend special    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 it's a good weekend to pick, people off work and a long one for people I hospital who need entertaining    
    
    
    I got doodling during a conference call. Any offers please DM me. Highly exclusive and unique. Serious offers only pic.twitter.com/6tMi93flTj    
    
    
    Oh dear. @LindsayMc21 has got me watching channel 4 with all these freaks dressed as dolls. It's just bloody freaky and weird.    
    
    
    These 2 freaks wouldn't look out of place in a horror flick pic.twitter.com/IkqGPrqddL    
    
    
    Yeah #livingdolls folks wouldn't look out of place as bride of chucky.    
    
    
    Sorry but #livingdolls is BO SELECTA hahaha    
    
    
    He nicked the Maggie thatcher spitting image doll. Someone tell ITV #livingdolls pic.twitter.com/trKVGUjl8i    
    
    
    @afneil Any weather event which is slightly out of the ordinary is now attributed to global warming. It is all a big con.    
    
    
    @davey_mc Yes I’ve ordered mine - this is a preview of what I’m getting : pic.twitter.com/Jcjmw9CmSB    
    
    
    @julienisbet I’m doing them…..apparently    
    
    
    @johnprescott I got 200 points on pointless MBEforME    
    
    
    All I can think is this guy IS a magistrate http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-25626147 …    
    
    
    @passy73 so if I ever get into this situation I can just call you?    
    
    
    @julienisbet it's probably 6 inches tall    
    
    
    I didn't get my great north run place via the daily mirror ballot. Booooo    
    
    
    @SkyNews @jamesmatthewsky what was the package then?    
    
    
    This polar vortex better stay out of Vegas next week, that's all I'm saying    
    
    
    I'd like to know who phoned me at 3:01am and woke up the whole house! I am yawning in my meeting, that said, it could be the meeting    
    
    
    @THShuffle who?    
    
    
    Seeing the news today it looks like people might be finally waking up to the fact that it's sugar that makes you fat NOT fat    
    
    
    Something major kicking off Burtree lane. Loads of police, ambulances and helicopter out. @EchoPeterBarron    
    
    
    Awful seeing someone receiving chest compressions laid on the road. Not a pleasant start to the day.    
    
    
    @EchoPeterBarron I got a mysterious call at 3:01 yesterday morning!    
    
    
    @British_Airways I sent you an email on Sunday and still waiting for reply. Got confirmation reference. Are you guys very busy right now?    
    
    
    @MillieNisbet sorry for letting you out into the dangerous world on your own earlier :/(    
    
    
    @British_Airways hopefully before my flight on Wednesday :-)    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @sirhappyfeet - you fancy a pop over to Vegas next week? If you've got nowt on of course    
    
    
    @nisbetphotos fantastic photos    
    
    
    Hey GBPUSD, what do you think you're playing at. I need you at 2 to the £ before Tuesday pic.twitter.com/nMXHPHQM6S    
    
    
    Ooo the shame. My debit card not authorised at @asda petrol station. Oddly enough it worked in the store 10 mins later. @NatWest_Help    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help @asda phew! I'm having a minor panic at the petrol pump thinking someone had robbed my account. Luckily I had a credit card    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help @BannyPotter my previous debt card worked there alright I have to say    
    
    
    @gazza_d @JeremyClarkson however, if the guy driving the car was on the phone he'd no doubt hit the cyclist which ever part of the road. No?    
    
    
    Can I just publicly shame @MillieNisbet for being a dirty shitty nappy eating minger. That is all.    
    
    
    On the plus side. Last work day until 27th of Jan. Next week is VEGAS    
    
    
    So, labour want to introduce an MOT for teachers. Let's do one for politicians. There'd be a lot of advisories and even more failures!    
    
    
    The kids decided to have a quiet breakfast on their own in the conservatory. pic.twitter.com/g2oGBy7hXc    
    
    
    Check this out from The Poke: How Germans Wait For Traffic Lights.  http://www.thepoke.co.uk/2014/01/10/how-germans-wait-for-traffic-lights/ … pic.twitter.com/6cenBBzcpN    
    
    
    I was gonna sign up for muddy mayhem then I read the press release and my interest has been dashed    
    
    
    It looks so cold outside as if this polar vortex has moved our way. Got relay races this morning. Hope they have cups of tea afterwards    
    
    
    Notice the shorts and the temperature in the same photo pic.twitter.com/yPmdERWkZv    
    
    
    Ah yes @julienisbet found the flapjack stall pic.twitter.com/flmV4fKaIy    
    
    
    And that's why I hate bloody cross country running #goosed pic.twitter.com/4953fCWS2P    
    
    
    I reckon @julienisbet either loves cross country or has superglued a smile on pic.twitter.com/IxU7dhnx02    
    
    
    Yeah the post race endorphins have kicked in. Sorry Miley love pic.twitter.com/zFTTNTq1CV    
    
    
    @theanthonydavis @byronhamburgers ooo i am in London on Tuesday, might try it    
    
    
    Hmm off work and wide awake at 6am. On a work day I can't get out of bed.    
    
    
    Why are @Barclays the most unhelpful bank in the world ever? Business accounts with multiple signatories is an absolute nightmare to  sort!    
    
    
    I think the staff at @Barclays have a competition for how many bleedin forms they can get you to fill in for the same request.    
    
    
    @DurhamCouncil any reason why your parking ticket machines don't give change? It's robbery    
    
    
    I'm not having a very good day so far    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 because @Barclays are rubbish, @DurhamCouncil car park robbed me and I lost my list of jobs to do today. That's for starters    
    
    
    I think poundworld seem to have got muddled up too. Trades description act pic.twitter.com/YX5rXQ8jBb    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I wrote it on a pad and lost he bit of paper somewhere!    
    
    
    @BarclaysOnline change of main address. All forms filled in. Then more forms to update details of existing signatories with info you have    
    
    
    @BarclaysOnline go into branch and they haven't got a clue because they are retail only, pass be onto a number to phone. Simple request    
    
    
    My day gets worse. @Morrisons left me standing at self service checkout. Please wait, the assistant is coming. No one came! I left the stuff    
    
    
    Then the Jeweller in @Morrisons had a sign up saying he opens at 10:15, but he often doesn't turn up at all. Another wasted trip. FFS    
    
    
    I'm going back to bed. The world is full of incompetent fools and idiots this morning. Is it me ? Groan    
    
    
    Anyway I'm gonna stop moaning and chill out. I'm off to Vegas so all these little niggles can go and do one. Nice cup of tea now I think    
    
    
    @BarclaysOnline I phoned up the team who sorted it out for me. I don't know why the Branch staff don't know this stuff too. Thats my point.    
    
    
    @BarclaysOnline bishop Auckland    
    
    
    @British_Airways I've tried phoning that number up and it cuts me off saying you're too busy. Still didn't get a reply from my web query    
    
    
    @julienisbet maybe they can't afford washing powder    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet are we talking us gallons or not?    
    
    
    Right tweets. I will bid you goodnight    
    
    
    Morning campers    
    
    
    And we're off    
    
    
    I've just sent @sirhappyfeet off to get the tea in. I'd go myself but the shock of the price would be too much to handle    
    
    
    @julienisbet @sirhappyfeet I've got a pack of cards so we can practice our blackjack strategy en route    
    
    
    @yorkshiretea as far as tea goes, it's pretty nice #teaonthetrain pic.twitter.com/V9NA2nMJFd    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet @TelePolitics I can think of more reasons. I like their patisseries though    
    
    
    @julienisbet no it will fly by    
    
    
    What I wanna know is, how did my Oyster card end up minus £2 ??    
    
    
    Leicester square. Waiting for @SimonTemby to show up pic.twitter.com/LxMOxqDcPu    
    
    
    Bloody freezing in London so I have located a patio heater type thing to stand next to pic.twitter.com/fiHHMyP0z9    
    
    
    @niwise I'm only here stealing their heat while we wait for @SimonTemby    
    
    
    People of London need to learn how to enjoy life a bit more. They all walk around not smiling. Unlike @SimonTemby who was happy to see us    
    
    
    What can I do with 3% battery life? It's a tough decision. The train is at least 30 mins from the hotel. This isn't good    
    
    
    Morning campers    
    
    
    Gang 'Sells Weed To Primary School Children' - where do the kids get the money from? http://news.sky.com/story/1195251/gang-sells-weed-to-primary-school-children …    
    
    
    Killer Shark Leaves Budgie Cage Diver Red-Faced - budgie cage, really?? http://news.sky.com/story/1195299/killer-shark-leaves-budgie-cage-diver-red-faced …    
    
    
    @gazza_d do you have footage on your cam?    
    
    
    Which cabin are you travelling in today sir. The best you can arrange *wink wink I replied.    
    
    
    Didn't want to share my details so told a couple of porkies to get online pic.twitter.com/KjyEktxjWL    
    
    
    A quick survey of the public wireless shows who are ruling the smart phone market pic.twitter.com/bfUc3d2bkM    
    
    
    @julienisbet years ago, keep up with it Nisbet    
    
    
    Free chocolate baileys pre flight.... Why not    
    
    
    I'm now on the plane, which means for the next 10 hours you'll enjoy some peace and quiet. Unless they upgrade us and turn on the wifi.    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 we can spark up a debate with the fellow passengers    
    
    
    Oh bollocks. The plane has broken down and we have to get off while they fix it. Bugger    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 it requires a part which is not readily available. Oh joy. Back into the terminal we go. But we are seeing the funny side    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet let's hope @britishairways get the plane fixed soon enough    
    
    
    Only on the Las Vegas flight can the passengers run a book on the bloody outcome of our delay    
    
    
    They have fixed the plane and we are back on board. The bad news is on the process of de boarding I've lost my @fitbit #gutted    
    
    
    Ready to fly when all the other passengers get out of the PUB! pic.twitter.com/ZclIQpDBz7    
    
    
    I asked the woman what was wrong with the plane, she said it was a hose reel. I said was it important, she said she didn't know. Erm ok    
    
    
    It's @sirhappyfeet favourite feature, the map pic.twitter.com/mUKVeWnEde    
    
    
    Anyway tweets, I am gonna settle back and watch White House down. Hope it's good. Next stop Vegas pic.twitter.com/Qp1RysTZIT    
    
    
    We have arrived    
    
    
    Where are all the fruit machines in the airport??    
    
    
    Well, that's me adjusted to USA time. Good morning folks. I'm up and ready to take on Vegas. Lets hope the tables are feeling generous    
    
    
    We aren't going anywhere fast. @sirhappyfeet has found his fav slot pic.twitter.com/SDzgWgP7iy    
    
    
    A very healthy diet while we are here @sirhappyfeet pic.twitter.com/M1K2FrStWb    
    
    
    Looking at iPad airs in the apple store with @sirhappyfeet - negotiating a discount at present    
    
    
    I promised myself I wouldn't be one of these people taking photos of good, but on this occasion pic.twitter.com/w2pogHAUTR    
    
    
    I feel physically unable to move after a giant slab of cheesecake. Hoist at table 9 please waiter.....    
    
    
    Natural cheese flavour apparently pic.twitter.com/KYM6hhNX4S    
    
    
    @julienisbet unfortunately we didn't budget for food, so we are on cheesy puffs today. #gamblersanonymous    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 well these are nice enough for 98c a bag    
    
    
    I can't believe the first hand I played at $10 a hand and I got blackjack. Pure luck of course but a good omen I feel    
    
    
    Well it's a good morning from Sunny Las Vegas. I will try to eat a better diet than cheesy puffs, cheesecake and burgers. #heffer    
    
    
    @Remediosjkpw go fuck yourself    
    
    
    No sign of my fitbit in Heathrow Lost Property. Reading through the list I can't believe the things people misplace.    
    
    
    On a plus note, it's 11 degrees above normal here in Las Vegas, according to our weatherman    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 yeah I lost my @FitbitUK while getting on and off the broken airplane the other day    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 yeah but the excess is £50 it's not worth it    
    
    
    Went to @luxorLV for breakfast. Forgot how annoying it is to be approach by timeshare people. Heading back out again. Bye Bye    
    
    
    A winning session on the blackjack and @sirhappyfeet has hot footed us down to the apple store to buy an iPad air.    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 we don't plan on buying much else so it doesn't matter so much. Plus it was way off the limit after we fluttered our eyelashes    
    
    
    @armsta01 @LindsayMc21 well they probably won't but we are within limits anyway so it's not a big deal to them    
    
    
    @armsta01 @LindsayMc21 we have discussed what would happen if we won a million dollars. We need to work out how to export it    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I fall into this category.    
    
    
    Off to Hoover Dam today. It is a miracle of engineering    
    
    
    Now we're talking #kerching pic.twitter.com/oWwA3X70NK    
    
    
    I turn my back for 1 minute and @sirhappyfeet goes onto $10 blackjack. He won $60 pic.twitter.com/OLREAiDHio    
    
    
    @davey_mc it paid out $23    
    
    
    Oh Christ. Not only did @sirhappyfeet tip a latte into the check in computer, he poured a bottle of bud into the auto shuffler on the BJ    
    
    
    Bought our show tickets courtesy of El Cortez casino Las Vegas. Aka our amazing blackjack skills    
    
    
    @davey_mc we booked zumanity and blue man group    
    
    
    I'm sure @sirhappyfeet has some static that means he always wins on slots pic.twitter.com/8XGUE9AwHC    
    
    
    Heading up the stratosphere tower to catch sunset. Worth the extortionate fee for the view. Even if it was paid for by the blackjack    
    
    
    The best way to see Vegas is from the top pic.twitter.com/FtjBWpz3L9    
    
    
    @David_Cameron I'm more keen to ensure you don't screw over our public sector pensions in 2015 to be honest Dave    
    
    
    @gazza_d I saw one cyclist in Vegas. Albeit  at night with no lights on. They don't seem to have the cycling bug here. Lots of cycle lanes.    
    
    
    Not totally comfortable with the fact you can buy dogs in a pet shop in the USA pic.twitter.com/5am4s2UssN    
    
    
    Let the blackjack commence!!    
    
    
    Can't get used to American radio. They say fuckin all the time. It's 2:38pm for crying out loud    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet and a very good deed it was too    
    
    
    @davey_mc we go past it every day but there is a massive queue outside    
    
    
    Had a good time playing blackjack again today. Overall we lost today but we were having so much fun it didn't matter. Off to pawn stars now    
    
    
    @davey_mc we went today but there was such a stupid queue outside we didn't bother going in. When we head downtown tomorrow will look    
    
    
    Having a balanced tea. Onion rings, flipz and chocolate donut holes. That qualifies right?    
    
    
    Today is the last full day in Vegas. I've ordered temperatures of 21degrees and a flurry if winning hands in blackjack. Followed by a steak.    
    
    
    The steak house has come highly recommended and we had to reserve a table so let's hope it's as good as the last time we were here.    
    
    
    If I move to Vegas I could just live off the earnings of blackjack pic.twitter.com/rmrBT9YYTa    
    
    
        
    
    
    Best in Vegas we are told. Let's see. We're ploughing the blackjack profits into this baby pic.twitter.com/GhSSHaUllB    
    
    
    Last day in Vegas can only mean one thing. Back down to El Cortez for single deck blackjack.    
    
    
    Thanks to @ElCortezLV for some fab blackjack during our stay in Vegas. What a great off strip establishment    
    
    
    Another successful blackjack session. Off to the apple store to spend the winnings pic.twitter.com/T5vU58NXfl    
    
    
    Raspberry diet coke. Interesting. I'm gonna try the orange next    
    
    
    BA have over booked our flight and wanted us to stay another 24 hours and be paid for the hassle. I asked for 1st class instead... We wait    
    
    
    Las Vegas airport has free high speed wifi and charging stations everywhere. Come on UK airports this is where you're missing a trick    
    
    
    On the plane and ready to go. Just waiting for taxi. See you on the other side folks.....    
    
    
    This is what's left of the cake which had to undergo emergency surgery pic.twitter.com/LBTZtHIpih    
    
    
    Seems that storm was somewhat over egged then....    
    
    
    @julienisbet she's a cutie though    
    
    
    Is it normal for your hips to actually creek as you walk up the stairs?    
    
    
    Oops. Left my phone in the car this morning and only just noticed. Went back to retrieve it and poor thing had been ringing its head off    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 is this an Andy audit or a Craig audit ? #justwondering    
    
    
    Double workout today. 3 mile run at lunch time plus an hour circuit training. Blimey I'm becoming one of 'them'    
    
    
    No moon at all tonight. Nearly broke my neck walking the puppies around millennium green @sirhappyfeet    
    
    
    Walked into a bush FFS    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan @julienisbet I haven't but I always like a new challenge    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton which Boney M are we talking here?    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet @RuthStapleton Boney M performed live at my graduation ball. Cool, I know    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton @sirhappyfeet well it was a good few years ago    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I know Ruth. @sirhappyfeet doesn't appreciate good music that's all    
    
    
    Hey @sirhappyfeet leading your daughter astray pic.twitter.com/IV3yUIipel    
    
    
    I need @babynisbet to help me play blackjack mire often. I started with £10 only 15 mins ago. Tripled it pic.twitter.com/vAGbXyRt6A    
    
    
    I think she wants me to play 5 boxes not 3 @babynisbet pic.twitter.com/dkFLPWLsHd    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet she won me £20 what a clever girl. She knows basic strategy now    
    
    
    Stupidly busy at work meaning my fitbit step count is in the red most days. Need more lunchtime runs I think. Or to take my desk out    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet have a cute baby in tow may get us upgraded to 1st class but also may make us look a bit gay!    
    
    
    @davey_mc we can all have one    
    
    
    Pretty impressed with my new now TV which arrived this morning    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet @TASHA_BAYNHAM @stevieguitar40 Christ don't ask me. @Nikkidee2000 is chief bin putter outer    
    
    
    @leanham44 you can get @ahradio on it    
    
    
    I hate chuggers and I particularly hate telephone chuggers. Poor Indian bloke just got it for phoning me. I asked for their charity no too    
    
    
    Today I must have a 'please stop me' sign on. Tramps, chuggers and lost pedestrians all asking for stuff today    
    
    
    @passy73 I gave the tramp 2p - I did feel sorry for him    
    
    
    @edjames we had that in France. The accordion player made us all lol at the stereotypical French man with a striped top and accordion    
    
    
    Tonight I learned that there are about 10,000 satellite channels on a motorised system and that friggin JML sells shit in 500 languages    
    
    
    Ahh the first of the month. The day where most of the money drains from my bank account in one fell swoop.    
    
    
    Managed to get through the night without being called out which is positive.    
    
    
    @The_Robbo those two would need more than 1 bottle though, crazy psycho bleach ladies    
    
    
    @The_Robbo aye they were. TV love mixing extremes though, dirty mingers vs OCD cleaners being a prime example    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton pension as early as you can. I joined mine at 22. Retirement seems a long way off but it compounds so much    
    
    
    Bought my poppy today. Have you got yours yet??    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton there are tax advantages too, get them to cost it up because it can cost very little and your employer has to put £££ in    
    
    
    Can't believe how big @The_Robbo 's dog has grown to in a matter of weeks. Are they feeding it weetabix or sommat ?    
    
    
    Frost! I didn't expect that on my car window    
    
    
    Hahaha. Loved the start of @johnkendal3 show. Thought I was watching corrie    
    
    
    @julienisbet you got the lurgy ?    
    
    
    Hey @The_Robbo do you fancy this? http://www.runnation.co.uk/run-northumberland-half-marathon-2014-99-p.asp …    
    
    
    @The_Robbo yeah that’s the one. I quite enjoyed that one, until the last couple of miles with those stupid hills. But hills are healthy    
    
    
    @FionaAlton we are still in the same queue    
    
    
    What an absolute shambles. Archers Ice Cream parlour firework display. Terrible organisation. 90% of people leaving before fireworks. Boooo    
    
    
    If it wasn't a charity event I'd be asking for a refund    
    
    
    @FionaAlton we gave up at 7:45. The kids were crying, it was cold and there was no info so we just called it a (disappointing) night    
    
    
    @GNairambulance I hope you managed to raise a decent amount of cash from the charity bonfire, but it was a shambles from our point of view.    
    
    
    @leanham44 and you love it    
    
    
    Sat at work, but have got @ahradio on and John Morgan is playing some good tunes today.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 I've left now, I came in at 8. The others came in a bit later and are still around    
    
    
    Very true , I nicked it from Facebook pic.twitter.com/yjU7gAMGHw    
    
    
    @julienisbet apparently rubbing Vicks on your feet and leaving a sock on helps. Worked last time I tried it. No idea how or why    
    
    
    Really successful night at @SpiceLounge11  - raised over £800 I almost left without paying the bill. Yikes that would have made me popular !    
    
    
    @armsta01 @SpiceLounge11 only 1 point in it. Very good effort indeed. Might revisit the sports round next time    
    
    
    Pretty tired this morning after a late night at the @ahradio event. 4 hours of 'Great Line Management'. I will try to be enthusiastic    
    
    
    Giving the fireworks at Hardwick Hall a try out. 100% than archers already and it was only £5. The rides will cost! pic.twitter.com/pcTxBK7ChK    
    
    
    Hardwick Hall pulled it off very wells. 30 minutes of fireworks, only cost £5 for all of us. Kids loved it pic.twitter.com/AUy9Caeb6P    
    
    
    Bollocks! - that is all    
    
    
    Great service from @British_Airways today. Couldn't have been more helpful. Pleased to be jetting off to Vegas in January with them    
    
    
    @British_Airways we will do thanks. It's a 30th birthday Vegas special for @sirhappyfeet first long haul with BA. So far very good    
    
    
    My French class has moved onto the subject of food. A fantastic topic. I want to try a Paris-Brest. Need to get to France I think    
    
    
    This is a Paris-Brest by the way pic.twitter.com/wgIBb7Jkn9    
    
    
    With being uber busy at work and lots of other things going on my running is taking a hot. Need to get out more and get some miles in    
    
    
    I think the only way to start the day is with a large costa. Then we'll go from there    
    
    
    Had my day brightened up by a man who looks like Emmett Brown belly laughing loudly while reading his paper. I'll have what he's drinking!    
    
    
    @gazza_d round the twist !    
    
    
    Faux pas of the day. I accidentally told my boss I'm Leaving. I meant to write, I've put some leave in    
    
    
    Doing a disco for 40 under 8s. All asking for bleedin one direction or someone    
    
    
    @gazza_d @KarlOnSea @amsterdamized @marksuttonbike no no no. People shouldn't be controlled by permit, it has to be a choice. Not northkorea    
    
    
    @gazza_d @KarlOnSea you need a permit at work so they can skim off £20 a month from your salary. They don't care about our parking really.    
    
    
    Good all. Another work day today. Lots to do. I bought chocolate bars to keep the troops going. Only at Darlo unfortunately.    
    
    
    Which pillock at Microsoft is in charge of error messages? No the message wasn't helpful at all. Fools. pic.twitter.com/fNTaw8cT6r    
    
    
    @KarlOnSea @gazza_d I would like to be able to cycle to work, but there is no real safe way for me to do it. I tried it a few weeks ago    
    
    
    Spent a fortune on Xmas shopping today. I think the most valuable purchase was this £1 tape dispenser pic.twitter.com/Rvij5tsOhy    
    
    
    Well, I liked the Marks and Sparks roast beef in red wine gravy. Would get use to this kind of grub. Maybe need a lottery win to keep it up    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan Watching it too    
    
    
    Awww the little girl at the Festival of Remembrance. She got it word perfect.    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @julienisbet OH CHRIST. Why would you do that? I’ve never watched it again, for very good reason.    
    
    
    I wonder if they’ll end with the National Anthem? I love a bit of God Save The Queen    
    
    
    @The_Leechy @julienisbet OH the shame    
    
    
    HERE WE GO. #GodSaveTheQueen    
    
    
    I liked the way the entire audience at the Albert Hall all turned to the face the Queen as the sang the national anthem. That looked nice.    
    
    
    @julienisbet wrapping Xmas presents. Observing a silence at 11am and going for lunch chez @pigglyugg and @pigglyuggswife then to @ahradio    
    
    
    @richardosman did you find it funny that @julienisbet thought The Princess of Wales was called Diana Andrews ?    
    
    
    Well, my breakfast isn't gonna make itself. I suppose I'd better get up, or shout down for @Nikkidee2000 to get the bacon butties on    
    
    
    @davembe name and shame them Dave    
    
    
    @davembe there's no excuse for that.    
    
    
    Her Majesty did a Stirling job once again this morning    
    
    
    @leanham44 I had missed it and now opened that just as I was tucking into my Sunday lunch    
    
    
    The downside of doing the show on my own is I had to run up 2 flights and stairs to the ward with a prize before the song finishes @ahradio    
    
    
    HA, if abba do reunite you'll all be agreeing with me. I said on national telly that I love abba and I will be proved right very soon    
    
    
    Good morning tweets. Today will be interesting if nothing else    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 we have a major new system going live today    
    
    
    Well it's been an interesting half day that's for sure    
    
    
    Prostitutes in rio learning English ahead if World Cup? Surely sucky sucky, me love you long time doesn't take much learning.    
    
    
    @gazza_d and if you borrowed that on an unauthorised overdraft it would be a fortune more than that.    
    
    
    @David_Cameron correct, however It's not right that we send money to a country with a space programme.    
    
    
    Bloody charity telephone chuggers! I wish they’d sod off. I don’t give money to anyone over the phone    
    
    
    £8 a month these charities are asking for. No way.    
    
    
    You can text DEC to 70000 to donate £5 to those poor people in the Philippines    
    
    
    Well I'm off to bed. Goodnight all.    
    
    
    Good morning tweets    
    
    
    @gazza_d yes but by the same argument drivers aren't deliberately diving into cyclists either.    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan and I've volunteered my wife to knock up a Paris-Brest    
    
    
    @afneil I don't give a frack either way    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I don't think anyone would watch your tape. Sorry to disappoint your new entrepreneurial ambitions    
    
    
    @TheNobler @sirhappyfeet that was tweet of the year nobler!    
    
    
    After an initial shock I am now rolling my sleeves up for a pretty impressive comeback @adwatson1984 is gonna have to be the voice of reason    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 haha no I'd forgotten about that one. I'm gonna get a costa machine installed in the dept for instant caffeine relief    
    
    
    @julienisbet find the real job centre twitter account then give them hell    
    
    
    My scales are broken. This is gonna affect my OCD weighing routine. I wonder if salter can fix them.    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 you doing anything in particular?    
    
    
    3rd weekend at work in a row. Actually, quite like Saturdays. Get loads done.    
    
    
    Very productive morning in a bizarre kind of way.    
    
    
    I need to start taking cash to costco. Every time I go I end up spending a fortune. Got some crackin deals though I suppose    
    
    
    @gazza_d these kind of cases are so sad because it could be the driver or the cyclist in the wrong. One is dead the other life ruined.    
    
    
    @gazza_d no one will ever really know what happened. That's the problem.    
    
    
    @julienisbet yes she got an award from the queen you know. Don't you think MI5 had her checked out before inviting her to the palace?    
    
    
    The global warming lobby have jumped on the Philippines storm as being down to climate change when there is no evidence at all.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 this morning I have also encountered a load of pricks. Maybe it's drive like a wanker day and no one told us    
    
    
    I bought 3 packs of rocky bar today. For the price of 1. Living the dream here folks. Rocky anyone?    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton I won’t lie to you, I do go in there, but I am a bit of a supermarket whore. I only go where the offers attract me    
    
    
    I just bloody sneezed and pulled a muscle. Owww    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton Remember - eye level is buy level. Always look down for the offers    
    
    
    Meanwhile over on Facebook, everyone is sharing those stupid 'share if you love your mother' and 'if you're proud of your son' etc    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan 10th rings a bell    
    
    
    @leanham44 he's growing up now,
Doesn't wanna be in mam and dad's bed anymore    
    
    
    @gazza_d @individualjs @StripyMoggie Add some garlic and you'd be branded a Frenchman    
    
    
    @leanham44 Well we don’t like to see house guests go hungry.    
    
    
    A stone off since my holidays which is pretty good, but my wedding ring is now hanging off my finger. I want it off my stomach not fingers!    
    
    
    @leanham44 can I just add that @Nikkidee2000 did the cooking, my job was simply to reheat said meal.    
    
    
    @leanham44 the grunter thinks sky is free    
    
    
    @leanham44 @Nikkidee2000 I never said I’d made it. I said I’d bought the beef and whacked it in the slow cooker. There my contribution ends    
    
    
    @waynebarrigan best of luck tomorroe    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: The Fastest Judge Judy Trial Ever - stupid criminals at work  http://view.break.com/2541520     
    
    
    The commute from hell. I can understand why people get stressed out with this kind of traffic    
    
    
    Got home and @Nikkidee2000 has been baking Christmas cakes. Smells lush    
    
    
    Very productive day. Managed to get another step forward on a big project. But tonight I've got French class. Looking forward to weekend    
    
    
    I think they should have a gogglebox show for people watching gogglebox. They are funny to watch.    
    
    
    If the whole IT thing becomes a chore I'm gonna become a professional blackjack player with @sirhappyfeet - doubled our money once again :-)    
    
    
    Time for Dr. Who. Please do not disturb until 9:05    
    
    
    Ice cream parlour you say? Free compensatory ice creams you say? Oh go on then, I'll have a 3 scoop sundae with a flake in and nuts on top    
    
    
    My email is so lucky it’s won the lottery and resigned. Please post letters to me from now on pic.twitter.com/iaU4T4aFRg    
    
    
    Charlotte just announced that in 93 years she’ll be 100. Factually correct and with life expectancy as it is, she’s probably right.    
    
    
    A busy day and tonight I'll be taking the @ahradio quiz to @SpiceLounge11 for a charity quiz.    
    
    
    @TASHA_BAYNHAM ah maybe it was the one I dropped ;-)    
    
    
    I love coming to one of the sites at work. The place is plastered with passive aggressive notes. The kitchen is particularly bad.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 no, I say we go direct aggressive, no need for passiveness    
    
    
    Gotta let the trolls know the don't bother you , Celebrities Read Mean Tweets http://besoci.al/1kUsYp     
    
    
    Christ I think if leg it too, Curse Of Chucky Prank http://besoci.al/WKIVyu     
    
    
    I wonder how much cocaine Nigella put in her chocolate brownies recipe. 290g or 320g ? I can just imagine the scene as she buys it too haha    
    
    
    @KTHopkins I thought the dog was taking an over active interest in this ! pic.twitter.com/t9MrGH6q4N    
    
    
    I'm gonna have to get my Nigella photo swabbed. If her hands have been in it, there could be traces of anything pic.twitter.com/ktJIkgHmFU    
    
    
    Following a very annoying puncture on the M62 I am now say in kwik fit, middle of nowhere branch waiting for a new tyre    
    
    
    Hmmm I think this kwik fit need to review their name. Nothing bloody quick about it    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: This French Tenant Takes Revenge On His Landlord http://view.break.com/2544826     
    
    
    @davey_mc nah it wasn't the trousers,
It was the tip off I phoned in about a dodgy geezer    
    
    
    Yesterday @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc left me a box of Heroes for the long trip back home. This is the result pic.twitter.com/bWXvutwZXz    
    
    
    If you're American, happy thanksgiving. If you're not, crack on, it's just a normal day. And forget all this Black Friday nonsense tomorrow    
    
    
    @davey_mc within the very limited customs regulations of course    
    
    
    @davey_mc taking photos of the plane will guarantee your camera is smashed to pieces and a strip search performed    
    
    
    This is why Facebook is getting shitter, it's full of idiots who post this kind of crap all day pic.twitter.com/fflWpgz4cG    
    
    
    Arrrggghhh my email account is full of Black Friday offers. It's only a Black Friday for me because of the awful weather. *deletes emails    
    
    
    Ha just heard on the news about these losers sleeping outside of the shop to buy a friggin PS4 at midnight. Fools.    
    
    
    @davey_mc what you doing in twitter?? I thought you were trampling loads of crazy bargain hunters in a scrum for a bargain    
    
    
    @KTHopkins she's gonna get struck down with a big bolt of lightening, mark my words    
    
    
    I'm beginning to wonder if I want to go to this mad house. These people ar…, Black Friday Shopping Chaos Compilation http://besoci.al/IfweaC     
    
    
    @The_Robbo @julienisbet aye, she grabbed the limelight when we went in Noel's house party back in the 90's. Isn't that right liane?    
    
    
    @davey_mc sounds too much for our friends in customs anyway    
    
    
    Looks like a police helicopter has come down in Glasgow    
    
    
    I think I need a cookie blocker. Every website I go on has ads which are clearly targeted to my activities. Kids toys and running things    
    
    
    Good morning tweets.    
    
    
    @passy73 the 2 darlings are up and therefore so am I, enjoying Tangled or something! pic.twitter.com/3xdewNyp8w    
    
    
    Ha, I heard the Rainbow TV theme on an advert. I shouted 'aww rainbow', Thomas runs to the window to look for it. Need to educate the kids!    
    
    
    So the government announce a £12 rebate on energy. Whoop whoop. Start thinking £12 PER MONTH and we may notice a slight difference in bills    
    
    
    @davey_mc looks nice. Did it come with chips?    
    
    
    @davey_mc Erm.... It's ok ill pass    
    
    
    Come out to these public events and @Nikkidee2000 knows everyone, including the local druggie it seems. You can tell they're skanky    
    
    
    You see folks, our old friend Karma works in both directions http://www.uptv.com/blog/uplifting-person-of-the-day-waitress-pays-for-customers-lunch …    
    
    
    Popped down @SpiceLounge11 for some grub. The place is heaving. Most popular venue in town it seems    
    
    
    @davey_mc now I like that idea. Porterhouse would be for ne    
    
    
    Well we're into December. I'd better get a haircut I suppose!    
    
    
    Attempting to make a French choux pastry dessert with 2 kids isn't going exactly to plan . Bloody French recipe! pic.twitter.com/VsKshzaw2v    
    
    
    2nd attempt at the Paris Brest. I know,
I forgot to dust with icing sugar before taking the photo pic.twitter.com/FamYtmbHx4    
    
    
    @davey_mc @leanham44 what's wrong with abba ?    
    
    
    #12DaysofJonesDAY1 gotta be in it to win it folks. Come on twitter, @dragonjones    
    
    
    @davey_mc yes that looks fairly decent, i would have that    
    
    
    @davey_mc I dare say it would exceed the recommended daily calorific intake of an adult but it does look nice    
    
    
    @davey_mc @leanham44 @LindsayMc21 ha! Last time I was in the USA I ate a bag that size for breakfast    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 guns and knives being the most bizarre. Oh and 8XL shirts    
    
    
    @davey_mc what the 'fork' is that?? Did you see what I did there? Fork... Erm... I'm here all week    
    
    
    I took the Paris-Brest over to @pigglyugg and @pigglyuggswife house today. They thought it was lush. Hope they're not ill tomorrow :-)    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 had you been here you could have had a slice    
    
    
    Oh well played Npower. Whack your prices right up then charge in as heroes by offering a price freeze for 18 months. We aren't fooled.    
    
    
    I think the energy companies have suddenly realised that they're in danger of becoming the new bankers if they're not careful. Unpopular.    
    
    
    Dear @David_Cameron my energy bill recently went up by £20 per month. Your £12 per year doesn't even touch the sides I'm afraid. Try harder    
    
    
    @CCHQPress very good but let's try and keep the details of the autumn statement private until he stands up in parliament to announce it. Ta.    
    
    
    @MartinSLewis yup it looks like the online app is down too pic.twitter.com/Jd8jCGu4oq    
    
    
    @NatWest_Help come on, what's occurring ??    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK I think they need to turn it on and off again pic.twitter.com/IsEYIzKjgV    
    
    
    @julienisbet you're a star. I'm eating free bacon butties in a posh hotel in Manchester    
    
    
    @julienisbet mammy always gives them to the teacher, I just dump them at the gate lol    
    
    
    @davey_mc I'm sure my balance is £10000 down    
    
    
    @davey_mc no, they compensated me and I backed down    
    
    
    @davey_mc ah yes, coca cola's attempt to sell us Brits tap water. It appears the yanks are still falling for it    
    
    
    Just posted a 5.04 mi run -   #RunKeeper http://rnkpr.com/a4l3sch     
    
    
    @BestProAdvice what is this 7/11 you speak of?    
    
    
    If nigella says she isn't a druggie that's good enough for me.    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK how did you get this information ? The government aren't leaking the autumn statement before hand again are they?    
    
    
    @SkyNewsBreak how did you get this information ?    
    
    
    via @Breakcom: Ultra-Realistic Morgan Freeman Finger Painting - wow http://view.break.com/2546671     
    
    
    @george_osbourne you may as well take the day off mate, most of your speech has been on twitter as usual before you deliver it. Very poor    
    
    
    It's a bit windy outside today.    
    
    
    @ITVLauraK I'd like to hear about it all on the day, from the chancellor, in parliament and not all leaked in advance. It's not acceptable    
    
    
    @BBCBusiness who told you that? The government haven't been leaking again have they?    
    
    
    @theanthonydavis no need to be excited, looks like @George_Osborne has leaked most of it early as usual    
    
    
    Have to say, the autumn statement sounds pretty good so far. Not bad, of course we had already heard most if it in advance    
    
    
    Looks like the river tyne is overflowing into places it shouldn't    
    
    
    @davey_mc perhaps send a mop for the river tyne which is over it's banks    
    
    
    @gazza_d how would you describe the NHS pay freeze ? Not a subsidy to someone  I would suggest    
    
    
    @gazza_d but it was a theoretical tax anyway, it never happened so you can't hypothesise what you could have done with it    
    
    
    @Jim01081 I don't do TV, except pointless of course    
    
    
    @davey_mc so what does giraffe taste like? Chicken I bet    
    
    
    Xmas tree and boxes galore out of the loft. It's gonna take half a day tomorrow to get the house festive. Hope @johnkendal3 has Xmas songs    
    
    
    Good Food HD is showing Nigella Christmas again. Yeah, sweet potato soup and mince pies this episode.    
    
    
    Blimey, the post office are keen. Delivering parcels for Christmas at 7:20am on a Saturday. Lucky I was up    
    
    
    Telling the kids in advance the Christmas tree is going up this morning ensured a 6am wake up call to put it up pic.twitter.com/Ha776kXVL1    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc may end up stranded in the states. Problems with air traffic control. Far too risky to travel    
    
    
    @johnmyersteam walking around it isn't the problem, walking through it is    
    
    
    @davey_mc it's been top news here all day    
    
    
    Kids watching the polar express. I find it an awful, creepy film. Don't like it at all    
    
    
    Hey @julienisbet I was making some French pastry and found your dogs liked to like the bowl, hope that's ok :-) pic.twitter.com/pg4jrDAtfM    
    
    
    I do end up agreeing to the most bizarre stuff. Recording a band in ebbchester or somewhere    
    
    
    Hey @Nikkidee2000 @TopInventionss is now on twitter    
    
    
    Looks like @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc will get home after all. Problems all fixed    
    
    
    @The_Robbo is this one you're fighting on principle or do you have a chance of winning it?    
    
    
    @The_Robbo I am sure you will be able to present a robust and adequate defense in court    
    
    
    @gazza_d no no, our pay review body said 1% and the bastards are trying to wriggle out of that too whilst lining their own pockets. Shocking    
    
    
    Just caught the latest episode of The Tunnel. Now it's getting really good. Lots of twists and turns    
    
    
    My morning took an unexpected turn when I rescued a stray dog with the help of @julienisbet / she is in safe hands now    
    
    
    In the process of louring the dog into the house I managed to give it a pound of @Nikkidee2000 's premium ham. Gotta go to shop how. Oops.    
    
    
    Aww I hope the little doggy I handed into stray aid was ok. Poor thing was all alone.    
    
    
    @George_Osborne @Morrisons did they let you take it home?    
    
    
    I wonder if I can pass off a Gregg's cream bun as a Paris-Brest? I need to get this right and I only have 1 opportunity tonight to make it    
    
    
    @julienisbet you'll be fine. Just go in and knock em dead. Not literally though    
    
    
    @davey_mc yes but I'm not paying those prices. My surname isn't McElhone moneybags    
    
    
    @leanham44 I recommend Las Vegas    
    
    
    @leanham44 then Vegas is in the dessert!    
    
    
    Lure, that's how you spell lure!    
    
    
    3rd attempt at the Paris-Brest and I'm pretty damn impressed with it. The French class had better be begging for more or I'll be upset    
    
    
    Check this out from The Poke: Crazy Naked Guy Streaks On TV.  Read it here:  http://www.thepoke.co.uk/2013/12/06/crazy-naked-guy-streaks-on-tv/ … pic.twitter.com/GXXTQDyogH    
    
    
    Very true pic.twitter.com/lY7zueQ2wM    
    
    
    @gazza_d what I wanna know is, where do I get my membership card? That place looks really cheap    
    
    
    It's always good exercise when @tigerquaker borrows your car. He parks it a mile away from the hospital    
    
    
    Behind the scenes as @nisbetphotos do our Christmas card session pic.twitter.com/do6iTFpxhQ    
    
    
    One Paris-Brest complete. I hope it tastes good and the Frenchies like it pic.twitter.com/K6y6Umri6j    
    
    
    Authentic French meal they said. However we deviated slightly by the fact we had 4 courses of dessert on top of the previous courses #full    
    
    
    Genius marketing. http://youtu.be/zIEIvi2MuEk  - I love this airline and I'd never heard of them before now    
    
    
    Why Learning French isn’t hard — Fluent in 3 months - Language Hacking and Travel Tips - http://www.fluentin3months.com/french-is-not-hard/ …    
    
    
    @UgotMoed ????    
    
    
    Looking at that signer from the Mandela memorial, I could have done a better job    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I want to get our dollars where they get theirs from    
    
    
    Picking up @LindsayMc21 and @davey_mc from the airport. I feel like I need a big sign like all the other collectors    
    
    
    I can I just look out for the forklift truck bringing their luggage out    
    
    
    Big bunch of young students outside of college in darlo, puffing away. How do kids of today even think it's good to start smoking?    
    
    
    @ThreeUK do you have problems with data at the moment? Good signal in Darlington very poor 3G. Keeps dropping    
    
    
    Looks like upload is working on @ThreeUK but not download    
    
    
    @ThreeUKSupport I am in the DL3 6HX area    
    
    
    @gazza_d he might have got away with it in asda    
    
    
    Some folks don't age well. Just a general observation    
    
    
    Just read about the three feel at home service. Basically I can use my mobile as if I am at home whilst in Vegas, no extra cost. Fantastic!    
    
    
    @The_Robbo but he is so cute    
    
    
    I've just realised, I haven't had a Christmas card from @David_Cameron this year. #justsaying    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 could have been worse. Could have been 7pm finish. #justsaying    
    
    
    @davey_mc according to three the only thing you need to setup is to turn off euro pass and you're in business    
    
    
    I wish you goodnight tweets. Having an early one.    
    
    
    @armsta01 people who updated their PC and it installed itself    
    
    
    @gazza_d which one    
    
    
    How come Egypt get the snow and we don't get it? What's going on with the weather? Come on its Christmas    
    
    
    @ambigfoot I share that view    
    
    
    Well, that’s @Nikkidee2000 accounts done for another year. Just need to pass to the accountant to vet. I hate doing accounts by the way    
    
    
    @johnprescott maybe a trainee?    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 I'm sure the vicar was trying to get his own back on all the folks who don't believe in God, which is equally as weird as Santa    
    
    
    My hip has developed an alarming creaking noise when I walk up stairs. Googling this only causes more worry as to what it could be    
    
    
    @RuthStapleton nice to see the @ahradio one at the top    
    
    
    Our Christmas cards have been done by @nisbetphotos this year. Looking pretty impressive. Will post pic when I've sent my cards to people    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 No, but it makes an awful creaking noise. It is quite disturbing. I think I'm gonna have to go to the docs with this one    
    
    
    @johnkendal3 no it's being doing it a while    
    
    
    @niwise blister plasters work well on nipples and are easy to remove afterwards    
    
    
    @niwise the blister plasters just melt off even the hairiest of folks    
    
    
    @sirhappyfeet I never had @The_Robbo down as a poundland lass    
    
    
    @AdamWray2 the author of the framework perhaps    
    
    
    @The_Robbo you can buy it in kg tubs in France. I'll get some for you    
    
    
    I wonder if the head chef had access to their twitter account haha pic.twitter.com/RtK4CZ2o76    
    
    
    @julienisbet I like this head chef at the @ploughpub and he shouldn't have been fired I reckon.    
    
    
    @leanham44 from the photos it looked like you enjoyed it    
    
    
    @The_Robbo @sirhappyfeet oh    
    
    
    @julienisbet what when I come to walk the dogs??    
    
    
    I see Eastenders hasn't changed. Caught 15 mins of it and virtually every scene has had a blazing argument. Off to slit my wrists now    
    
    
    Oh now it looks like poor old dot is about to be raped and murdered, or at least robbed.    
    
    
    @gazza_d are you going to the DMH Xmas lunch on Wednesday ?    
    
    
    @gazza_d oh I'd forgotten about that. Due to cuts we may have to repeat last years    
    
    
    @gazza_d or perhaps run it in 10 minute delay so we can add an audience in    
    
    
    And these jokers want more money? Surely they should be arrested for fraud http://pbs.twimg.com/media/Bbo3wAyCAAAnieo.jpg#twimg …    
    
    
    Probably best I log out, I've been in one if those real grouchy moods all night and it's not conducive to happy tweets.    
    
    
    So, if I clocked in for 20 mins, then went home would I still get paid, or more likely I'd get fired!    
    
    
    Thomas looking dapper for his Christmas party at school pic.twitter.com/n1vE97tzwt    
    
    
    I have lost my voice. This will please many people I know    
    
    
    Talk about money laundering! @Nikkidee2000 put my wallet through a full wash cycle.    
    
    
    I'm baby sitting @MillieNisbet @CharlieNisbet and @babynisbet tonight. I bet I get wrong for taking this out pic.twitter.com/yr5bygQKfq    
    
    
    @David_Cameron it makes it easier for the scrounges too unfortunately    
    
    
    @Nikkidee2000 now now dear, I didn't expect such lightning service that's all. Lucky it wasn't full of £££ like normal or I'd be crying    
    
    
    @gazza_d get yourself joined in man, it's Christmas    
    
    
    I love the whole @ploughpub story and fact the guy @chefjimknight  managed to get a new job on the back of it. Well done that lad.    
    
    
    How do people spoof cli when spamming me?? pic.twitter.com/jB0b21epEP    
    
    
    Look @David_Cameron If you stick me in the lords, I’ll claim the £300 every day, but I’ll go there every day and stay all day. Please sort.    
    
    
    @David_Cameron I quite like the sound of Lord Robinson. I can be effective and I reckon the lords needs more people from the street.    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 just remember, nobody ever said on their deathbed that they wished they'd spent more time at work.    
    
    
    Yeah yeah, it was just self raising flour you fools - http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-london-25415095 …    
    
    
    I've spent 482.1 hours on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    What's all the fuss about a thief who dies years later? Why the celebrity status anyway? Move on @SkyNews    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 I'll be watching it later    
    
    
    The pier in St. Kilda, Australia where the woman fell offwas right near where me and @Nikkidee2000 stayed on our honeymoon.    
    
    
    @LindsayMc21 we will have done too. It was horrendous for about 2 or 3 minutes. So bad it set off several car alarms in our street    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 44 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    Some cracking photos taken by @nisbetphotos pic.twitter.com/iCMJbnEisJ    
    
    
    And another @nisbetphotos picture of the kids pic.twitter.com/InP3RFlbfI    
    
    
    Today I will be mostly doing @ahradio  work with @SimonTemby (he doesn't tweet). Oh and some last minute Xmas shopping online.    
    
    
    The highlight of the broadcasting year will indeed be at 2pm when we take the studio to a packed carol service for some festive spirit.    
    
    
    @gazza_d oh, due to licence restrictions and the fact the streaming server shouldn't be overloaded we have had to restrict the audience ;-)    
    
    
    @ChriswMP problem is, you lot aren't offering any realistic credible alternative    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 46 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    I will be making a personal appearance at Sainsbury's in Bishop Auckland today, bag packing for @ahradio - please don't mob me    
    
    
    Off to the docs to get this noisy hip looked at. I hope they don't recommend I be put down    
    
    
    @edjames I'll suggest that to the doc    
    
    
    Our surgery is in the 21st century. Online appointments. Let's see if this works or if they have no idea I'm coming    
    
    
    Time keeping clearly isn't one of the strengths of this surgery. How can they be so late so early in the morning?    
    
    
    @TheNobler if I can ever get in I'll find out!    
    
    
    I'm not impressed so far. 25 mins after my appointment and someone else just got beeped into the doc I'm meant to be seeing.    
    
    
    And the NHS wonder why people show up at A&E. If the GP service is as crap as this I'm not surprised at all. I'm off shortly, will go to A&E    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 any movement?    
    
    
    @adwatson1984 should I phone and ask the ward to hold off till 24th? There is some hope for the sweepstake yet :-)    
    
    
    Today's stats: I've spent 48 minutes on Twitter, according to the SocialClock app. See how much you have: http://goo.gl/pxO8Ve     
    
    
    @leanham44 I'm full of lurgy too. Typical when I'm off work    
    
    
    Spent 3 hours wrapping presents tonight. A lot of cash doesn't wrap down into much. Not a lot to look at.    
    
    
    @leanham44  sure it will stitch    
    
    
    Still can't get my head round the @TheAtoZofPop show. Santa's sackful or something. Tongue twister that's what it is. It's on @ahradio    
    
    
    @The_Robbo how do you come to that conclusion? This was your idea    
    
    
    