Should be interesting. http://fplus.me/p/f55     
    
    
    Concept of owning something should include tinkering with it. http://fplus.me/p/flk     
    
    
    horror movie "encourages viewers to download a free app that delivers second screen content during the movie." http://fplus.me/p/fnb     
    
    
    Must watch! How it feels when you're detained in Beijing! http://fplus.me/p/fIB     
    
    
    Google Glass becoming more real for me. http://fplus.me/p/fMu     
    
    
    Just bought my T4i not long ago. Argh. http://fplus.me/p/fTU     
    
    
    Announced today: Google Keep note taking app. http://fplus.me/p/fTT     
    
    
    Cool crowd sourcing research from YouTube. http://fplus.me/p/fUp     
    
    
    Insane skier video of a drop into a chute. http://fplus.me/p/fUA     
    
    
    I'm ashamed to say that I'm from Minnesota. Even O'Reilly says Bachmann is ridiculous: http://fplus.me/p/gfX     
    
    
    This scares the shit out of me. If you have women in your life, must read. http://fplus.me/p/gwG     
    
    
    Apple. two step authentication. about time. http://fplus.me/p/gxP     
    
    
    understating is better than overstating. http://fplus.me/p/gxO     
    
    
    how does any of the social networks avoid being pushed aside? good question. http://fplus.me/p/gy4     
    
    
    Must read if you are a computer Geek. Botnet to scan the entire internet. http://fplus.me/p/gzx     
    
    
    Must watch. Largest calving glacier event ever recorded. http://fplus.me/p/gF0     
    
    
    Crazy Congress trying to do science for scientists again. http://fplus.me/p/gFa     
    
    
    Must read about guns and john Lennon and yoko. And beautiful via. http://fplus.me/p/hrm     
    
    
    Must watch. How to unload a truck quickly. http://fplus.me/p/hDZ     
    
    
    Coding using voice. Wow. http://fplus.me/p/hEY     
    
    
    Interesting exchange. Kudos. http://fplus.me/p/hEZ     
    
    
    See number 40 and 52 in this collection. http://fplus.me/p/hFL     
    
    
    Cool story about a lost camera at sea showing up six years later in Taiwan. http://fplus.me/p/hTr     
    
    
    Super cool high speed photography. http://fplus.me/p/hYB     
    
    
    A new silly way to fill potholes in the road. http://fplus.me/p/i3Y     
    
    
    Looks like something out of the Star Wars movies. http://fplus.me/p/iRE     
    
    
    The ending to the lost camera story. http://fplus.me/p/jI4     
    
    
    Must read. Funny stuff. http://fplus.me/p/kgq     
    
    
    Privacy and Trust are actually very different, even if they're the two sides of the same coin. http://fplus.me/p/kgE     
    
    
    Bullying on social networks is getting out of hand. It's interesting to read how Facebook handles it: http://fplus.me/p/kk1     
    
    
    Monopolies in media is particularly damaging to young democracies like taiwan. http://fplus.me/p/kr4     
    
    
    Spying via RAT tools and webcams. Scary stuff. http://fplus.me/p/ksY     
    
    
    Must watch video about graphene and how it can be turned into a battery that will change the world. http://fplus.me/p/ktN     
    
    
    This is pretty amazing video of how far character animation has come. Just think about Toy Story and what is repr... http://fplus.me/p/l4v     
    
    
    Wow. Map reduce is free from patent issues. http://fplus.me/p/l8P     
    
    
    Totally worth reading just for the pure sport of debate and the hilarity of the arguments. On same sex marriage. http://fplus.me/p/l9a     
    
    
    Dashboards for big data analysts to display on big screens. http://fplus.me/p/lfq     
    
    
    Same day delivery from Google in the bay area. http://fplus.me/p/lgb     
    
    
    In the last two weeks, I was invited to give two talks: http://fplus.me/p/lOg     
    
    
    Cool photos of cities with starry night sky. http://fplus.me/p/lV2     
    
    
    Don't install apps from unknown and untrusted sources. http://fplus.me/p/lYH     
    
    
    Scary article about a bad dentist. http://fplus.me/p/meE     
    
    
    Nice community on machine learning! http://fplus.me/p/mib     
    
    
    This is shameful turn of events on the Libor scandal. http://fplus.me/p/mir     
    
    
    social commentary about the state of social mobility in the US. http://fplus.me/p/miS     
    
    
    Interesting article on media influence. http://fplus.me/p/mZ4     
    
    
    Interesting analysis of the gay marriage case that is the talk of the nation. http://fplus.me/p/n01     
    
    
    Fluorescent fish. Kind of crazy, even if it's just for decorative purposes. http://fplus.me/p/nxy     
    
    
    Been waiting for this. Auto full res photo upload for g+. http://fplus.me/p/oFT     
    
    
    Good read on the failures of big data analytics. From my experience, Google and many other companies violates thi... http://fplus.me/p/oG7     
    
    
    @iC @dyahnuri you should be able to invite someone with just an gmail address. But yes, it can be complex.    
    
    
    Nice license plate. http://fplus.me/p/oGE     
    
    
    The apple apology brouhaha. http://fplus.me/p/oXM     
    
    
    @msbernst @joelrbrandt blush.    
    
    
    @aquigley true enough. Got a bug to file against the team.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SNAcourse @davetown101 we were posing, not sure if we answered questions. Dodged is more like it!    
    
    
    Minnesota awesome. http://fplus.me/p/qNh     
    
    
    Oh, foot in the mouth. http://fplus.me/p/qNw     
    
    
    Cool. Should get a pair of these headphones. http://fplus.me/p/qNF     
    
    
    Funny video parody on the Facebook phone. http://fplus.me/p/r8H     
    
    
    Mmmm. I used to be a fan of intuit. http://fplus.me/p/reX     
    
    
    @beh_zod its an sync posting service. It isn't run by g+    
    
    
    RT Quoting: "Employees who ate at cafeteria tables designed for 12 were more productive than those at tables for... http://fplus.me/p/rTZ     
    
    
    Good article on butchery. Made me think more about my food. http://fplus.me/p/rYd     
    
    
    This is foolish censorship at its most ironic. http://fplus.me/p/sb3     
    
    
    The Apple-China saga retraced and compared to other western tech company troubles in China. http://fplus.me/p/sbD     
    
    
    Amazing that our understanding of the phases of solid and liquid is still so poor. http://fplus.me/p/scn     
    
    
    Hack-Tip about modifying your APN settings in your phone: http://fplus.me/p/sdh     
    
    
    Tears in space. http://fplus.me/p/sn5     
    
    
    Interesting reflection on the centrality that Facebook Home is trying to achieve. http://fplus.me/p/spy     
    
    
    Awesome comic to explain web conversations on social media. Someone should do the quant analysis of this. http://fplus.me/p/thp     
    
    
    Must watch snake game. http://fplus.me/p/tnN     
    
    
    @skairam @codinghorror hell banning is my favorite. Not enough people know about this. Delicious made good use of it.    
    
    
    @Ziuabuna they sure do. @skairam @codinghorror    
    
    
    How Thatcher 'lost' the Hong Kong negotiations. http://fplus.me/p/trh     
    
    
    Taxing data collection? Horrible idea. http://fplus.me/p/tJJ     
    
    
    Chromebooks are definitely making more and more sense. http://fplus.me/p/ueU     
    
    
    This is funny but a bit harsh. :) http://fplus.me/p/uf6     
    
    
    Using games to teach programming... Need more education initiatives like this. I wonder how much social interacti... http://fplus.me/p/uoG     
    
    
    Paper money isn't dying anytime soon. http://fplus.me/p/uoH     
    
    
    Brazil not ready for the big event in June. http://fplus.me/p/uIr     
    
    
    On criticism of Thatcher. http://fplus.me/p/uIF     
    
    
    PC sales continue to drop. Windows 8 blamed. Ouch! http://fplus.me/p/vFc     
    
    
    Anything wrong with this sign?! http://fplus.me/p/vVx     
    
    
    I think it is good that Google is doing something about this. http://fplus.me/p/waj     
    
    
    This 1hr special on PBS tells the surprising truth about exercise. It isn't the length of the exercise that matte... http://fplus.me/p/wly     
    
    
    Tiny Chiplets: A New Level of Micro Manufacturing http://technews.acm.org/archives.cfm?fo=2013-12-Apr/Apr-12-2013.html#646799 …    
    
    
    An interesting paradox about when ppl are likely to answer the phone. The more busy they're, the more likely they... http://fplus.me/p/x3e     
    
    
    The YouTube celebrity you have never heard of. http://fplus.me/p/xdW     
    
    
    Hawk-Eye aims for football expansion http://fplus.me/p/xec     
    
    
    cool electric car. http://fplus.me/p/xf3     
    
    
    it's surprising that people don't know about these issues with startups. For every successful startup, there are... http://fplus.me/p/xW9     
    
    
    Hmmm. Guess you shouldn't read this piece. http://fplus.me/p/xZy     
    
    
    We need to issue more H1b visas. http://fplus.me/p/y0j     
    
    
    Some sick drop-ins at this legendary ski location. http://fplus.me/p/yhR     
    
    
    If you think software patent is controversial, read this about DNA patents. http://fplus.me/p/yK8     
    
    
    Hope your loved ones are safe in Boston. http://fplus.me/p/zEO     
    
    
    Cc +***** http://fplus.me/p/zEN     
    
    
    Ouch! Facebook just saps your attention with no nutritional content. http://fplus.me/p/Blu     
    
    
    Stanford is no. 1. http://fplus.me/p/Bm8     
    
    
    The gun lobby won. At least this round. http://fplus.me/p/C6u     
    
    
    Psych'ed out about the CHI2013 conference starting in just over a week in Paris. Lots of new interaction and rese... http://fplus.me/p/DOW     
    
    
    My friend's research at Harvard guesses your age. http://fplus.me/p/DU5     
    
    
    Hahaha! Must see all the photos in this album. http://fplus.me/p/DUp     
    
    
    Interesting rumor about a Microsoft watch. http://fplus.me/p/E9U     
    
    
    Two sad and angry brothers. Nytimes has some details. http://fplus.me/p/E9V     
    
    
    Stories behind the FBI photos. http://fplus.me/p/Ecb     
    
    
    Photo Attack: West London near Notting Hill just after dusk. http://fplus.me/p/Egt     
    
    
    Photo Attack: Found in London - A Fixie. http://fplus.me/p/Egu     
    
    
    Now there should be no arguments about checking certain mentally disturbed individuals from buying guns, right?! http://fplus.me/p/EkX     
    
    
    A very scary analysis of the China development model and the asset bubble there. http://fplus.me/p/EtL     
    
    
    The background on the bombers. http://fplus.me/p/EzV     
    
    
    Must read piece about MOOCs. http://fplus.me/p/EUI     
    
    
    Cool pix of impact crater. http://fplus.me/p/EYQ     
    
    
    Wow. Must watch video on amazing birds. http://fplus.me/p/FoE     
    
    
    Cool chess board. http://fplus.me/p/Fv3     
    
    
    Relief. Tsarnaev is going to get his due process. Proud to be American. http://fplus.me/p/Gk5     
    
    
    @andrikos @HCIR_GeneG @benki @conorlinehan @SinisteResearch That's very funny. Would pay money to get that shirt.    
    
    
    If you're going to #CHI2013, join this G+ event and share your photo. http://fplus.me/p/He5     
    
    
    +Moshe Vardi , editor in chief of CACM, has this to say about big data, and I think it is a very intelligent answer: http://fplus.me/p/He4     
    
    
    A good article about my PhD advisor from grad school: http://fplus.me/p/IgA     
    
    
    @arjenpdevries that's very nice for you to say. John is amazing guy.    
    
    
    US House subcommittee unanimously passes Taiwan Policy Act & President Ma warned http://www.taipeitimes.com/News/front/archives/2013/04/27/2003560820 …    
    
    
    A recent article about Xerox PARC used a picture of me from 12 years ago! http://fplus.me/p/Kar     
    
    
    @ShuminZhai @chi2013 I actually registered everything up to chi2020, becuz we had a squatter at chi2012. Use @Sig_chi instead I think.    
    
    
    Must watch. Outrageous bike. http://fplus.me/p/LgB     
    
    
    @ShuminZhai @clifflampe @sig_chi I wonder if @chiconf is available.    
    
    
    @infolaber yes, lame. Even the paper that talked about circle management did not talk about g+circles.    
    
    
    @infolaber  welcome!  Let's chat. What team are you joining?    
    
    
    I wish I can add your photo to the g+ event! http://fplus.me/p/MnR     
    
    
    Hahaha. I now gave a good appreciation of these differences, having spent a lot of time at Google's g+ division. http://fplus.me/p/Mop     
    
    
    If you're at #CHI2013, join this G+ event and share your photo or thoughts. http://fplus.me/p/He5     
    
    
    @PatrickMeier reminds me of work we did in 2009 called Eddi that summarizes your tweet stream.    
    
    
    Google Now for your iOS devices. http://fplus.me/p/MQP     
    
    
    Too late for sandra to be on the 'right' side of history. http://fplus.me/p/MQO     
    
    
    'locations where locals (blue) vs. tourists (red) take pictures in San Francisco'. http://fplus.me/p/N6R     
    
    
    RT Glad Google is a strong supporter of #CHI2013. +Research at Google http://fplus.me/p/N7m     
    
    
    Read comment on original to see possible dispute on $1B figure for MS Azure. http://fplus.me/p/Nq9     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @gingdottwit I'm sure it was hard to deploy like they did 16 years ago!    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @gingdottwit A cautionary tale of comparing research work over such a long periods of time.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @gingdottwit absolutely. Replicate and extend is a great model for building a good research plan! #replichi    
    
    
    I'm giving the keynote at this conference. http://fplus.me/p/Ns3     
    
    
    Interesting healthcare debate. http://fplus.me/p/NRd     
    
    
    Interesting reason Why MSFT had been going up: http://fplus.me/p/O5A     
    
    
    @saponas @jwiese awesome work. Can't wait to see the next steps of this in products.    
    
    
    @GadgetMan4U @dtapscott its a function of how many active users you follow and how much effort you invest in the social network as an user.    
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @gingdottwit @elenaagp @pernillaq yes. Good idea.    
    
    
    RT Go Google+ Go ! :) http://fplus.me/p/Phr     
    
    
    RT Scientists have found the key to the ageing process - and in a series of experiments, the researchers found th... http://fplus.me/p/Phq     
    
    
    @_CHINOSAUR where were you all week? Cliff Lampe was missing too, which raised suspicions. :-)    
    
    
    Kids drawing on a smart car. So cool. http://fplus.me/p/QTi     
    
    
    Interesting argument on Mount Everest. http://fplus.me/p/Rh1     
    
    
    The services war is just getting started. http://fplus.me/p/Riz     
    
    
    Gorgeous. Taiwan rail station. http://fplus.me/p/Rn3     
    
    
    Cool read. http://fplus.me/p/RsO     
    
    
    What's the song? Amazing that this happened. http://fplus.me/p/Rtx     
    
    
    Well put. http://fplus.me/p/RtS     
    
    
    Good reminder of the human condition even in this modern society. http://fplus.me/p/RzN     
    
    
    Services is where the action is at. http://fplus.me/p/RA2     
    
    
    Oops. Bad form. http://fplus.me/p/RJQ     
    
    
    How does this law make any sense? Cities and jurisdictions should be free to do what they like with the guns afte... http://fplus.me/p/RJP     
    
    
    Holy crap. Swallowed by a hippo? Really?! http://fplus.me/p/SbA     
    
    
    Another sad detail coming out about how the suspects built their bombs in Boston. http://fplus.me/p/Scv     
    
    
    Love this video and the contrast between one who takes care of his health, and the other who doesn't. http://fplus.me/p/UcT     
    
    
    interesting observation about smart tv. http://fplus.me/p/UeD     
    
    
    Presentation given at #CHi2013 on the social annotation effects in news reading. http://fplus.me/p/UrO     
    
    
    A summary of the #CHI2013 paper we presented on social annotations in news. http://fplus.me/p/UsQ     
    
    
    Very cool stair case with slide and bookshelf. http://fplus.me/p/UAc     
    
    
    @iC @lwu wordle is the standard goto option.    
    
    
    RT Latest post on my blog. http://fplus.me/p/VzO     
    
    
    Must read about the color red. http://fplus.me/p/VA0     
    
    
    Cool idea on acclimating students to engineering degree programs and the university. http://fplus.me/p/Wt4     
    
    
    From Science news email letter. http://fplus.me/p/WDz     
    
    
    Nice summary of Vint Cerf's keyote at #CHI2013. http://fplus.me/p/X4h     
    
    
    This post highlights some of the HCI work being done at Google on Day 3 of #CHI2013, if you miss it. http://fplus.me/p/X4g     
    
    
    +Shumin Zhai 's work with his coauthors on extending Fitts' law to fingers and touch is critically important for... http://fplus.me/p/X4t     
    
    
    Reasonable summary of UX. http://lnkd.in/WPbUXE     
    
    
    This is a fun game. Encourages global thinking too. http://fplus.me/p/Y05     
    
    
    I don't understand why we have not yet moved to the smart chip just like Europe. http://fplus.me/p/Y17     
    
    
    Incredible story. Brave parents. http://fplus.me/p/Y1h     
    
    
    @OlivierChapuis smart chip isn't French. They are also cheap. Just a problem with infrastructure of existing card readers.    
    
    
    @smunson I think consumers are eating the cost of these frauds because they did an cost benefit analysis.    
    
    
    @jeffbigham @smunson I think they just transfer the cost to consumers by default. I don't think it is written into law.    
    
    
    Brave woman. Nice op ed. written by Angelina Jolie. http://fplus.me/p/10uq     
    
    
    PNAS article on using bacteria to kill pancreatic cancer cells. Radical. http://fplus.me/p/10vg     
    
    
    +Bongwon Suh did a version of this Wikipedia edit map at my group at PARC. http://fplus.me/p/10vM     
    
    
    Nice interview with Google's new head of android. http://fplus.me/p/10A6     
    
    
    Bacteria all over the news these days. This one is also pretty cool. Stops malaria. http://fplus.me/p/10G6     
    
    
    Oh my god. http://fplus.me/p/10G5     
    
    
    Quick way to figure out what's going on at Google IO is to watch this tagged headline page. http://fplus.me/p/11Mz     
    
    
    At #www2013 in Rio de Janeiro in Brazil. Luis von Ahn just have keynote talk on Captcha and duolingo. Still an in... http://fplus.me/p/11Nb     
    
    
    Paper at #www2013 examines how hashtags spread across distances around the world. Reminds me of our icwsm paper o... http://fplus.me/p/11PE     
    
    
    @brettreasure yes. Look for me around the Google booth during there breaks.    
    
    
    This paper at #www2013 focus on understanding how people use the web as a personal archive via 14 user interviews. http://fplus.me/p/122E     
    
    
    @HCIR_GeneG @ccmarshall  sure is. She worked on this with sian lindley.    
    
    
    This paper describes a model for how users evolve from novice raters to experts. #www2013 http://fplus.me/p/127T     
    
    
    Google Booth at #www2013 and the airport in Rio when we arrived. http://fplus.me/p/13pw     
    
    
    @ricardokawase  thanks. I'm in that room already.    
    
    
    Gala dinner party at #www2013 last night turned out to be a huge carnival party, proceeded by a huge Brazilian BB... http://fplus.me/p/14HB     
    
    
    Nice #www2013 paper on utilizing explicit network relationships to do social reinnervation of products such as mo... http://fplus.me/p/14HU     
    
    
    This #www2013 paper describes a study of brokers (spanners) that bridge across structural holes in networks. http://fplus.me/p/14JN     
    
    
    Our #www2013 paper studies how users notice social annotations on web search and what contacts and query domains... http://fplus.me/p/14RR     
    
    
    Guns that shot chocolates. Brilliant. http://fplus.me/p/1629     
    
    
    Half dome and Yosemite park from my airplane window. http://fplus.me/p/1754     
    
    
    The fact this project exists means an apple #fail for me. I hate the conversion on magsafe. http://fplus.me/p/17c8     
    
    
    Cool Lego clock. http://fplus.me/p/17hz     
    
    
    Instructions for Single column for your G+ stream if you hate the multi-column. http://fplus.me/p/182v     
    
    
    A random sample of 320K tumbler posts show that 83% of the posts are photos. http://fplus.me/p/182w     
    
    
    Thinking twice before I use Skype next time: http://fplus.me/p/18y7     
    
    
    This is an important step forward for android ecosystem. http://fplus.me/p/19W6     
    
    
    G+ Photo search now has some semantic understanding of what is in the photograph. http://fplus.me/p/19Z1     
    
    
    More info: blog post pointing to the new G+ Photo search capability that does some visual recognition. http://fplus.me/p/19Zs     
    
    
    RT This #www2013 paper describes the modeling of the active graph in online social networks. They have a predicti... http://fplus.me/p/19ZZ     
    
    
    RT This #www2013 paper is an descriptive modeling of the Quora question and answer networks. First one I've seen... http://fplus.me/p/19ZY     
    
    
    RT This #www2013 paper is the first outside large scale descriptive model of Google+ social network. http://fplus.me/p/1a00     
    
    
    The killing of a Taiwanese fisherman by Philippine military is causing a lot of yelling and this analysis is pret... http://fplus.me/p/1aek     
    
    
    Shudders. http://fplus.me/p/1alb     
    
    
    Google maps have saved me many times. But not like this. http://fplus.me/p/1aHi     
    
    
    A good summary of the recent #chi2013 paper on Pinterest: http://fplus.me/p/1aSn     
    
    
    @lsinger fplusme fail.  Try: https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/T2fgUCWewMY …    
    
    
    Image Recognition Search Inside Google Plus Photos |  Rich DeMuro http://richdemuro.com/2013/05/22/amazing-upload-photos-to-google-and-it-looks-for-more-than-just-faces-search-for-objects-too/#sthash.WbNYLP99.uxfs … via @sharethis    
    
    
    Fluff piece about Google x. http://bit.ly/10N6GhK     
    
    
    It's been a long time since I've looked at graphics research. They definitely are still at it. http://bit.ly/197BvW3     
    
    
    Yes, we released some research data. http://bit.ly/14Esp04     
    
    
    Finally being talked about publicly. The new image search capabilities. http://bit.ly/189OXdg     
    
    
    Haha. Watch about tax and the apple hearing. http://bit.ly/14HoUWT     
    
    
    I literally just uninstalled Facebook messenger last night. I hate the bubble head that is impossible to dismiss!... http://bit.ly/14L2Kmx     
    
    
    Pictures of Taiwan from 1957 taken by an american soldier. http://bit.ly/Z7coyJ     
    
    
    Top of Windsor hotel. http://bit.ly/12EPTju     
    
    
    The start of dinner tonight. http://bit.ly/18rfwYX     
    
    
    Third course. Lamb chops. http://bit.ly/13T8Em2     
    
    
    Cool science on perception of fast objects. http://bit.ly/11joC3B     
    
    
    Pulled rabbit dish from last night by +***** http://bit.ly/11jtIwV     
    
    
    A permanent marker can trap ants. Here is why. http://bit.ly/11pe5tN     
    
    
    Want. http://bit.ly/10uw2pb     
    
    
    Electric cars and its benefits explained by the guy who made the film. http://bit.ly/13ZpPiz     
    
    
    The new kinect looks amazing. http://bit.ly/12Kn59j     
    
    
    Deep learning explained for computer scientists. http://bit.ly/11m8pur     
    
    
    A good scientific riddle. http://bit.ly/ZqQngw     
    
    
    Duolingual android app released. http://bit.ly/112D4x1     
    
    
    Educational policy simplified. http://bit.ly/1750471     
    
    
    Open Access for all Google papers. http://bit.ly/175R4ym     
    
    
    Love this answer: http://bit.ly/113mSM4     
    
    
    Sky lantern festival in Taiwan. http://bit.ly/17yu4ZI     
    
    
    David Shamma was tagged in Ed Chi's album. http://bit.ly/13lWS1v     
    
    
    Visual analytics of the effective tax rate for companies across different industries: http://bit.ly/ZwaJ8h     
    
    
    More data from Google Research. This time, on the wikipedia infobox. http://bit.ly/17zJnl6     
    
    
    Cool plant that trap bugs. http://bit.ly/17BFvQw     
    
    
    Amazing read. This masterpiece outlines a new way to think about employer-employee relationships. http://bit.ly/12TFiBl     
    
    
    Fluffy piece about the "moto x." http://bit.ly/12THc59     
    
    
    Cool play house for a kid. http://bit.ly/11dG5M0     
    
    
    Dance, baby, dance! http://bit.ly/18FYA0X     
    
    
    Fascinating funeral practices in Indonesia. http://bit.ly/10H2wNh     
    
    
    Fluff piece about the new Google movie - Internship. http://bit.ly/17NGvBd     
    
    
    Awesome kid builds a submarine out of spare parts and $2000. Goes 30ft under and 1.5mph. http://bit.ly/12oImL1     
    
    
    For my bay area friends: http://bit.ly/18JtdCK     
    
    
    Cool idea from Finland on how to reduce infant mortality rates. http://bit.ly/18MvZHo     
    
    
    Hail in Taiwan today! http://bit.ly/17ZIKBz     
    
    
    An analysis of Why Facebook stock hasn't done well. http://bit.ly/18Nh2F8     
    
    
    Facebook losing users, according to this report. http://bit.ly/18Qb7yY     
    
    
    Ouch! Funny read about Verizon. http://bit.ly/186Gk3S     
    
    
    This is pure insanity in Texas. http://bit.ly/18SJkxS     
    
    
    Baidu demonstrating deep learning for similar image search. http://bit.ly/18TGx7G     
    
    
    What if you had the power to explore your DNA? Check out @23andMe. Get 240+ personalized reports using my link. http://refer.23andme.com/a/clk/4V5HLF     
    
    
    23andme is now $99. Prices have really come down. I just got my results back. Makes interesting night time reading. http://bit.ly/18UV17a     
    
    
    Everything I need to say is in this post. http://bit.ly/18UVpCH     
    
    
    Woohoo! Can't go back to iOS because of the android keyboard. http://bit.ly/18eheQF     
    
    
    Pretty cool photos. http://bit.ly/11yGP1J     
    
    
    Student travel scholarships to SOUPS conference! http://bit.ly/15Jgr5s     
    
    
    Like we said already. http://bit.ly/15KvYBZ     
    
    
    +Al Gore hanging out in the science community talking about climate change. http://bit.ly/15KzKuZ     
    
    
    Amazing photo of Grand Canyon and lightning. http://bit.ly/1bkQ5rM     
    
    
    Google collaborates with CMU to create a visualization of our history on this planet. http://bit.ly/13xPxgA     
    
    
    Good question posed by +Thomas Hawk on how image search could work better if search engines make better use of so... http://bit.ly/1boI4lD     
    
    
    I can't help but notice that Apple Safari browser now use a Scrolling Card metaphor for organizing open tabs (jus... http://bit.ly/1bpCfUU     
    
    
    #Geek moment: http://bit.ly/1bpVTQA     
    
    
    Saturday dinner was a grilled salmon, ribeye steak (not pictured), lots of good wine, and a amazing d'Yuqem saute... http://bit.ly/16YLlLI     
    
    
    This is one damn cool light. Want. http://bit.ly/16YMeEf     
    
    
    Amish teens love Facebook. Interesting documentation of their use cases. http://bit.ly/16YZhoX     
    
    
    It's pretty shocking the number of people I run into who don't know about the card index method for evaluating in... http://bit.ly/1br1Ahh     
    
    
    Designer redesigns NSA slides. #needToGoViral http://bit.ly/1a14onq     
    
    
    What it takes to get 'top secret' clearance: http://bit.ly/1a1mrdb     
    
    
    Well said about the FISA request. http://bit.ly/1a1nY2M     
    
    
    Who out there is working in MOOC evaluations? http://bit.ly/1bt9sid     
    
    
    +Jeff Jarvis dissects why the Waze acquisition by Google is interesting. http://bit.ly/1btgJP2     
    
    
    +Joshua Schachter 's company TastyLabs was bought up by Walmart Labs. Missed this news when I was at #www2013 . http://bit.ly/1btXkNY     
    
    
    Siri getting a male voice? Might have interesting implications: http://bit.ly/171gNJm     
    
    
    @jilleduffy it's been a while since I've used an iPhone. Thanks.    
    
    
    OMG. Hilarious. Must see about Jony Ive. http://bit.ly/11X4SDm     
    
    
    Interesting question: Does someone who was born with a hearing loss "hear" an inner voice? http://bit.ly/174aq8c     
    
    
    How do users hold their phones? http://bit.ly/150iYpD     
    
    
    Interesting observation about Facebook's age problem. http://bit.ly/1a86kdY     
    
    
    Am thrilled that one of my papers is selected for "Excellent Paper" that +Research at Google is recognizing acros... http://bit.ly/1a88jim     
    
    
    @hormetic Thanks for the confidence vote. G+ didn't have a say in the selection though, since this is run by ResearchOrg.    
    
    
    If you need an academic paper reading list for the next few months.... http://bit.ly/175Wv1o     
    
    
    Heard about this project internally at least a year ago, glad that they are far along to try out the idea at a la... http://bit.ly/166Yi1J     
    
    
    Serendipity and learning in this one app for Wikipedia. Seems cool. http://bit.ly/12Omhpb     
    
    
    These are some expensive parking spots. Boston parking space sold - $560,000 http://bit.ly/17dnqIx     
    
    
    British PM launches new £1m 'Longitude Prize' http://bit.ly/17dnM1N     
    
    
    X ray scans reveal covered music after 200 years. http://bit.ly/17do4pF     
    
    
    Must read opinion piece by +Jeff Jarvis on the damage done by the Snowden case. http://bit.ly/14H7drh     
    
    
    RT A joke, but a funny joke (from the New Yorker's Borowitz Report) http://bit.ly/16C50gX     
    
    
    Lasers reveals ancient city at Angkor Way. http://bit.ly/11nFz1Y     
    
    
    Harsh advice for Microsoft. It must have taken guts to write this. http://bit.ly/102LB78     
    
    
    Oh my. That's a good response to a cease letter. http://bit.ly/11oNBaX     
    
    
    Finally! http://bit.ly/14n5qFV     
    
    
    Good photo of #Rio protests. http://bit.ly/11S3LpN     
    
    
    The science of applause: It is contagious. http://bit.ly/14n8yl6     
    
    
    Google's PeopleOps head interviewed for what we have learned in managing people. http://bit.ly/11SZzWF     
    
    
    Whoa! This is insane if true. http://bit.ly/11tbo9B    
    
    
    I now have deep appreciation of what Yonatan said in this post. http://bit.ly/10FQyVS     
    
    
    A plant that 'eats' sheep. Unreal. http://bit.ly/11u3RHq     
    
    
    Coffee kiosk in taiwan prints your photo on your latte. http://bit.ly/14q8BfU     
    
    
    Good read about the troubles at the new bay bridge. http://bit.ly/188KAj0     
    
    
    Overheard a debate about threads in python at the sunday lunch table behind me. http://bit.ly/11yxRSE     
    
    
    @munmun10 no kidding!  It was surreal.    
    
    
    This is a depressing read about Taiwan's situation. http://bit.ly/17wQpHu     
    
    
    @clifflampe @jteevan only cliff's tweets needs prior approval. :-)    
    
    
    @jteevan oh, Jaime! That's a good challenge for all talks.    
    
    
    @clifflampe @jteevan yeah cliff's talk would be bleeped out every other sentence.    
    
    
    @dmrussell @clifflampe @jteevan the challenge is talk about one thing that can't tweeted to the world. :)    
    
    
    @jteevan also, don't tweet Joe konstan's address or medical problem!    
    
    
    Snowden case is reading like a live spy novel. Here are details of his stay in hong Kong and his departure. http://bit.ly/17cctDO     
    
    
    Huge step in US legal history. http://bit.ly/17fQ0FZ     
    
    
    Wonderful analysis of the supreme court decision today by +Yonatan Zunger . http://bit.ly/14twD9B     
    
    
    Definitely worth watching. Cool science. http://bit.ly/19K8AXG     
    
    
    What happened to free speech?! http://bit.ly/19KbdbY     
    
    
    +Yonatan Zunger delivers again on a cool physics post. http://bit.ly/12bGuz7     
    
    
    This waterproofing spray I have to try to believe. http://bit.ly/12bHXFC     
    
    
    +Don Norman comments on the Google Glass. http://bit.ly/12bHZxm     
    
    
    Love it that +Jeff Jarvis used the term #ChattyGhosts . I think that hashtag should go viral. http://bit.ly/1aXUjYQ     
    
    
    Ironic read. http://bit.ly/1aXWY4V     
    
    
    What an amazing read on that period of web search history. http://bit.ly/19KVCJ8     
    
    
    Been thinking about buying a fixie. There are some inexpensive choices, as it turns out. http://bit.ly/12wL7am     
    
    
    Capture Camera Clip v2 by Peter Dering http://kck.st/17L2c5a  via @kickstarter    
    
    
    @beh_zod I like bullhorns myself. But that tends to be custom it seems.    
    
    
    Some explanation is needed here. What the hell is going on? http://bit.ly/11VYzVm     
    
    
    @beh_zod why do you think steel is better than aluminum?    
    
    
    Snowden is now a human hot potato. http://bit.ly/14KL0a5     
    
    
    @beh_zod I see. Good advice. Thanks.    
    
    
    @RojaBandari I don't think they will be okay with it when they find out.    
    
    
    Sadly, Snowden is not getting good legal advice. Just because one doesn't have a valid passport, one isn't a 'sta... http://bit.ly/14KZoz3     
    
    
    @beh_zod  Super useful info. You rock!    
    
    
    Someone blogged about our research on Pages vs. Cards in tab switching at chi2013 in Chinese! http://bit.ly/12cSXBA     
    
    
    Spot on. It's amazing how little computer scientist part attention to user behavior sometimes. http://bit.ly/12cSXBF     
    
    
    Whoa! 3D doodling. http://bit.ly/12l14gt     
    
    
    System geeks should pay attention. http://bit.ly/10zJpUR     
    
    
    RIP, Engelbart. http://bit.ly/19UxAeV     
    
    
    I'm sad to report that collaborative filtering and social recommender pioneer, and my phd advisor, +John Riedl ha... http://bit.ly/19UCicm     
    
    
    @aquigley  Thanks, and all thoughts and prayers goes to his family.    
    
    
    @ken_hinckley that was a big event. John have chosen thus far too be much more low key. Either way, it's incredibly sad.    
    
    
    Lean on train window and hear adverts. Whoa! http://bit.ly/12eNRop     
    
    
    Circeln?! Really? http://bit.ly/18yNWvO     
    
    
    @ken_hinckley he just slipped into a coma. :(    
    
    
    Worth watching. Rocket landing vertically. http://bit.ly/1a0ptNI     
    
    
    Official word from Asiana. http://bit.ly/11rnl1p     
    
    
    Video of the crash yesterday. http://bit.ly/13DW63I     
    
    
    @reidpr really?!  I had no idea. Sounds like time for some Google searches.    
    
    
    I need to Google these cases and learn these stories. http://bit.ly/12c4Ysk     
    
    
    @smc90 excellent point. She was robbed.    
    
    
    This is fair criticism of US govt blunder in Egypt. http://bit.ly/14DfNXq     
    
    
    Computer vision takes a huge step with this work. http://bit.ly/13xSBND     
    
    
    @lsinger works for me. Are you on gplus? It redirects to a post there.    
    
    
    #icwsm is one of the good social computing conferences. Sadly, I can't be there this year due to a conflict in my... http://bit.ly/13xTcPh     
    
    
    @lsinger  not sure why the attachment is missing. It was http://googleresearch.blogspot.com/2013/06/fast-accurate-detection-of-100000.html …    
    
    
    Great xkcd. http://bit.ly/16lqagF     
    
    
    Smartphone growth to slow due to saturation? What would your bet be? http://bit.ly/16ls29d     
    
    
    Artificial waves in a man-made lagoon. Crazy. http://bit.ly/16lu2OG     
    
    
    Egypt coup or revolution? Wikipedians trying to decide. http://bit.ly/184LHxu     
    
    
    More summaries from #icwsm. http://bit.ly/12fY2uj     
    
    
    Discovery of interesting content via your friends is one of the best way to build a recommender. Launching today... http://bit.ly/12fYAjQ     
    
    
    @KristinaLerman unfortunately no. I'm heading to mpls to see my advisor john riedl who is at the tail end of his battle with melanoma.    
    
    
    @danjarratt algorithm could highlight the user with higher influence score.    
    
    
    I've been going paperless as much as possible at home and this should help my workflow to scan papers from odds a... http://bit.ly/16t3hrR     
    
    
    @smc90 @vgr @HooverSteve well, hello. How all is well.    
    
    
    Bummed that I missed this. http://fplus.me/p/2sB7     
    
    
    @MrTonyCostello if you believe in the internet service model, then you have to give trust to someone eventually. Question is who.    
    
    
    @KristinaLerman if you believe in the internet service model, then you have to give trust to someone eventually. Question is who.    
    
    
    Now Snowden wants to stay in Russia. http://fplus.me/p/2tQj     
    
    
    @MrTonyCostello  That's not a bad idea. We need creative solutions that fundamentally change how trust is given.    
    
    
    Sadly, a boy is dead and no one seems to be responsible. http://fplus.me/p/2uLt     
    
    
    Must read about Microsoft's recent reorganization. http://fplus.me/p/2uMG     
    
    
    @jonfroehlich totally agree.    
    
    
    This is certainly an unexpected turn of events in the Snowden saga. Russia now wants to do more net surveillance. http://fplus.me/p/2uUo     
    
    
    Must read about subtle and not-so-subtle gender discrimination. http://fplus.me/p/2uX1     
    
    
    This is so obvious but no one seems to be doing it. I would buy a phone like this in a second. http://fplus.me/p/2v1K     
    
    
    A good analysis of the Zimmerman trial. http://fplus.me/p/2v2g     
    
    
    there are no iron atoms in the metal odors: http://fplus.me/p/2vl4     
    
    
    Minnesota in the Fall. http://fplus.me/p/2vni     
    
    
    Found in the woods near Minneapolis. http://fplus.me/p/2vnh     
    
    
    Remembering +John Riedl, my phd advisor, who passed away an hour ago. http://fplus.me/p/2vNO     
    
    
    @anneohirsch  Thanks, Anne.  Hope you get a chance to read his papers, and get to know him via his work.    
    
    
    @beh_zod  He was brilliant, and the world is a little less bright today.    
    
    
    @jennthom  His life is an example to many of us.    
    
    
    @MrTonyCostello  Thanks, Tony.    
    
    
    @KristinaLerman he was an amazing man.    
    
    
    This ablation experiment result shows the effectiveness of search ads on mobile. Very interesting, but I want to... http://fplus.me/p/2woY     
    
    
    Cool robotic video. http://fplus.me/p/2wA4     
    
    
    Wow. Read with care. You might be offended. http://fplus.me/p/2xyW     
    
    
    Parody of Gangnam Style in Klingon! Must watch! http://fplus.me/p/2yoN     
    
    
    Want to see how well this really works. http://fplus.me/p/2yrU     
    
    
    Geeky fun. http://fplus.me/p/2ytH     
    
    
    More details on urban police beating #watermelon vendor to death in China. Shocking. http://fplus.me/p/2yxG     
    
    
    Police beats #watermelon vendor to death in China. http://fplus.me/p/2yxF     
    
    
    Cool electric bike conversion. http://fplus.me/p/2yyG     
    
    
    Cool vis of 50k Twitter user follow graph. http://fplus.me/p/2z5D     
    
    
    Interesting examples of graph search. http://fplus.me/p/2ziG     
    
    
    Found. Want. http://fplus.me/p/2ziU     
    
    
    Awesome mobile coverage maps. Looks like part of their data is crowdsourced. http://fplus.me/p/2zzn     
    
    
    Thinking seriously about getting out of contact and going prepaid. Wondering about tmobile's $30 data plan compar... http://fplus.me/p/2zEg     
    
    
    @mandriy the T-Mobile $30 data plan?  Awesome! Good to know.    
    
    
    Haha! #sharkWithLaser http://fplus.me/p/2zQ5     
    
    
    Getting a sense of the scale of data center is hard, but this gives a glimpse. http://fplus.me/p/2AmC     
    
    
    This is why ethnographers had a field day with Facebook. It's endless source of research material. http://fplus.me/p/2AsZ     
    
    
    Tesla is challenging how cars are sold in the United States. Dealerships apparently can add 30% in costs of a new... http://fplus.me/p/2Avi     
    
    
    A creative engineer creates dams for glaciers to irrigate in the spring. Cool idea. http://fplus.me/p/2BI1     
    
    
    This is an important move by the Geo in making maps super useful for both search and recommendation. http://fplus.me/p/2BKt     
    
    
    well, this is one way to do a gender difference study in this age of social media and big data analytics. http://fplus.me/p/2Cg6     
    
    
    Already ordered a #chromecast. This was a no brainer. http://fplus.me/p/2Cwv     
    
    
    Yes, we try to make information universally accessible, including understanding how teens search. http://fplus.me/p/2D06     
    
    
    For those having been annoyed by random g+ event invites: http://fplus.me/p/2DSE     
    
    
    Got to love #science. http://fplus.me/p/2Exi     
    
    
    The obit for my PhD advisor. http://fplus.me/p/2ExW     
    
    
    An interesting idea to educate people about their own digital safety. http://fplus.me/p/2EHC     
    
    
    Interesting social science research showing why being overly generous is disliked. Fascinating. http://fplus.me/p/2EHV     
    
    
    Better understanding of happiness and meaning in your life. Reminds me of Maslow's hierarchy of needs. http://fplus.me/p/2LnJ     
    
    
    Mind still blown about WashPost being sold to Bezos. http://fplus.me/p/2Mn4     
    
    
    Some 122K people have added this AKB48 Translator account so that they can get AKB48 information in their languag... http://fplus.me/p/2MDn     
    
    
    Food Porn. http://fplus.me/p/2N0u     
    
    
    More food porn. http://fplus.me/p/2N1p     
    
    
    I love easter eggs. http://fplus.me/p/2N7t     
    
    
    The same advice can be applied to anything you do in life. Convince yourself that it is worth doing. Then do it.... http://fplus.me/p/2NCH     
    
    
    Extra dose of food porn from Barcelona. http://fplus.me/p/2NGn     
    
    
    Very cool review of ways to preserve your wine bottles after opening it. http://fplus.me/p/2Oix     
    
    
    This study examines the effect of up and down votes on a news website. Very interesting implications for recommen... http://fplus.me/p/2Ojq     
    
    
    Some analysis into Jeff Bezos' purchase of Washington Post. http://fplus.me/p/2Q8m     
    
    
    In awe of the universe as well as the science and technology that brings us this close to it... http://fplus.me/p/2Q8n     
    
    
    I see a lot of helicopter parenting in my culture, with kids not knowing how to do anything on their own. As a re... http://fplus.me/p/2Q8l     
    
    
    Food porn. http://fplus.me/p/2QaO     
    
    
    @gumption thanks for the feedback. I use g+ mainly, and find twitter's ability to have conversation limited. Not liking 140 char limit.    
    
    
    @gumption I like twitter for quick fix to know what's going on, but conversations are, well..., truncated. :-)    
    
    
    @gumption no problem. Been thinking how to post in g+ so that it shows up nicely in twitter. Want finer control of truncation algo.    
    
    
    New finding in visual perception on how it works. Brain integrates info more more than we thought. http://fplus.me/p/2Qes     
    
    
    Exercise changes your cells and how the genes operate within them. http://fplus.me/p/2Qtq     
    
    
    RT French soldiers held in a Nazi prison camp during World War II managed to smuggle in parts to construct a movi... http://fplus.me/p/2QtL     
    
    
    Travel photography. http://fplus.me/p/2QxS     
    
    
    My GoPro video: water rafting the famous Tunnelshoot run. http://fplus.me/p/2Qy2     
    
    
    Useful trick. How to coil your headphone cables tangle-free. http://fplus.me/p/2QI8     
    
    
    Good comments by +Dan Gillmor on the Manning case http://fplus.me/p/2RaR     
    
    
    Go look at these pictures and think about nature, and the responsibility we have to our environment. http://fplus.me/p/2Rb9     
    
    
    @_CHINOSAUR @5tuartreeves @luiciolfi ouch! Haha!    
    
    
    Grappling story about the journalists who received information from Snowden. http://fplus.me/p/2RAq     
    
    
    Yes, Google has started making some good hardware. http://fplus.me/p/2RW1     
    
    
    my dinner today http://fplus.me/p/2RXZ     
    
    
    Auto-awesome smiles in your group photos. http://fplus.me/p/2RYO     
    
    
    Oh my god. Lolz. http://fplus.me/p/2RZ3     
    
    
    A particularly good update and opinion piece on the Taiwan-US-China relationship issues. http://fplus.me/p/2Sc6     
    
    
    Must read NPR story about the history of Carnegie libraries and the concept of public information access. http://fplus.me/p/2ScD     
    
    
    Rocket science explained. Why atmosphere is the most important element in a rocket launch. http://fplus.me/p/2Sd1     
    
    
    @reidpr that's strange. Just tried the link and it works fine both in the g+ app as well as chrome.    
    
    
    Why Shannon entropy is bad for cryptography. http://fplus.me/p/2Sf7     
    
    
    Holy sh*t. Amazing image of water sprouts. http://fplus.me/p/2Sfy     
    
    
    G+ new app updates a decent amount of stuff! http://fplus.me/p/2Sh2     
    
    
    Google personal search made better for the things in your life. http://fplus.me/p/2SMz     
    
    
    Vegetable farm in a Tokyo office building. Cool. http://fplus.me/p/2T0m     
    
    
    This is a disturbing video from China that has gone viral there. Watch with caution. http://fplus.me/p/2Tny     
    
    
    This study says that the more time you spend on Facebook, the more you're less satisfied with life. Quotes a bunc... http://fplus.me/p/2Tqp     
    
    
    Tried the camera translation feature recently in Barcelona to read a menu. Very cool! http://fplus.me/p/2Ttr     
    
    
    Area 51 does exist after all. http://fplus.me/p/2Upi     
    
    
    If you are involved in social research, it is not a surprise that social stream systems use sophisticated techniq... http://fplus.me/p/2UBp     
    
    
    What do the usable security researchers think about this? https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/MQAQDuEycXE …    
    
    
    .@rhemalinder Very surprised and honored that I tied with @benbendc. Amazing company to keep.    
    
    
    @jeffbigham only if you trust your kids and coworkers won't play a practical joke on you!!    
    
    
    @jeffbigham wait till she is sixteen!  :). Just kidding.    
    
    
    @jeffbigham @syardi @benbendc @landay @rhemalinder now that would be a surprise party!    
    
    
    The lack of originality is breathtaking in these book covers. http://goo.gl/m3av0A     
    
    
    @gingdottwit didn't know #glassing is a verb already.    
    
    
    I'm happy to announce a new feature for G+:Translate Google+ posts and comments with… http://goo.gl/Ub9Qti     
    
    
    A few weeks I was in Sorrento, Italy for a day during my family vacation.  What an… http://goo.gl/hYbjLs     
    
    
    In Philadelphia for the CSCW Program Committee meeting, while worrying and working… http://goo.gl/mzn1Hc     
    
    
    @berniezang would have been possible last nite. next time!    
    
    
    A planet of boiling lava with an 8-hour yearKepler-78b orbits its star so closely… http://goo.gl/kZmRpe     
    
    
    Interesting account of security incident over at Facebook. http://goo.gl/fW3rZt     
    
    
    People use social media to express their emotions, and i think this is particularly… http://goo.gl/Uzv0Rx     
    
    
    One of several news articles covering our launch of g+ translate. http://goo.gl/g6o8Sh     
    
    
    Meanwhile, Google bounty for bugs goes up to $5k. http://goo.gl/aT293x     
    
    
    The NextWeb coverage of G+ translate launch yesterday:http://goo.gl/BzUnXu  http://goo.gl/sTAlPw     
    
    
    Another nice and positive coverage of our launch of G+… http://goo.gl/QjdaEW     
    
    
    A good longer article covering not just our G+ Translate launch but also all of the… http://goo.gl/ZvM8lm     
    
    
    CNet and Engadget both also covered our launch, and I somehow missed their short… http://goo.gl/8HX4xX     
    
    
    http://goo.gl/I2nKDw     
    
    
    Hopeful?  Depends on how much Microsoft's problems come from the top, but certainly… http://goo.gl/GdVmN8     
    
    
    Can't stop yourself from using Facebook?  These students have some funny ideas. http://goo.gl/rIzADy     
    
    
    Someone hired a girl to #slap him every time he used Reddit and Facebook. His… http://goo.gl/L2p5Jf     
    
    
    Nice $16M house in Taiwan. Wow. http://on.wsj.com/1d61L6S     
    
    
    @RojaBandari would have to do another experiment to answer that question. :)    
    
    
    In a few weeks, Zürich will host the International Symposium on Wearable Computers… http://goo.gl/xksCIU     
    
    
    Tesla outselling many car brands. Impressive. http://goo.gl/iCQ7qz     
    
    
    Bear rescue.     ღ ☨ ღ"We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals."… http://goo.gl/IcCOcJ     
    
    
    BBC covers the knife massages given in Taiwan. Never tried it, but looks interesting. http://goo.gl/kMZl9A     
    
    
    Sign up to participate in Google usability studies! http://bit.ly/17YX34UDesigning …… http://goo.gl/Xz0vXe     
    
    
    Nicely done photos and recordings of MLK's "I have a dream" speech made 50 years… http://goo.gl/MRqVo3     
    
    
    Street Photography attack: Shopkeeper in Sorrento, Italy. http://goo.gl/We9kJe     
    
    
    In response to the railroad strikes of 1877, the Gatling Gun Co. made a sales pitch… http://goo.gl/6yVEku     
    
    
    Samsung's Galaxy Gear smartwatch will clock in on September 4. How will Sony's… http://goo.gl/Sfktbc     
    
    
    Facebook and govt information requests revealed a bit more. http://goo.gl/nZLeLw     
    
    
    Fascinating report about Marissa http://goo.gl/BsoMGs     
    
    
    We live in a sick sick world. Hate reading news like this in the morning. http://goo.gl/StBV0K     
    
    
    Richter 1985 The New Yorker (Richter 1985 The New Yorker) http://goo.gl/PU2JbA     
    
    
    We developed the wireless sensors and protectors used in the Taekwondo matches at… http://goo.gl/QU0YuH     
    
    
    This move to legalize marijuana is long overdue. We have wasted too much resources… http://goo.gl/dvWCGg     
    
    
    Love this comic from a few days back. http://goo.gl/ITKppo     
    
    
    Amazing video about Google Glass and how it changed one person's life. Via… http://goo.gl/W6Qkng     
    
    
    Amazing result here, adding iodine to salt raised IQ by a std dev (in the 25% of the… http://goo.gl/DQz05e     
    
    
        
    
    
    Google Play services help deliver new functionalities to your phone, this defrags… http://goo.gl/qkrnat     
    
    
    'It is hotter than anywhere I've ever been': London skyscraper melts cars, fries… http://goo.gl/N5d4k2     
    
    
    Open plan offices don't work, study says. http://goo.gl/ocC762     
    
    
    I've wanted to say this about big data analytics for a long time. Via… http://goo.gl/ipV8YI     
    
    
    In Graz, Austria to give a keynote.  The town is gorgeous and the weather is great. http://goo.gl/Re86tT     
    
    
    Underground ice barrier will be used to seal off Fukushima's nuclear accident site. http://goo.gl/4zdfb6     
    
    
    The Map That Lincoln Used to See the Reach of Slavery"This map, made by the U.S.… http://goo.gl/60b8TR     
    
    
    Following onto my previous re-share of my old Damascus album, some of my images from… http://goo.gl/tffphe     
    
    
    My news... (Going beyond Siri and Watson: Microsoft co-founder Paul Allen taps Oren… http://goo.gl/hDGB6h     
    
    
    @fabien_gandon often in our analysis, the first step is trying to filler out the bots as they are often spam.    
    
    
    Ngrok looks like an amazing resource for hacking and understanding traffic to your… http://goo.gl/iFqAAK     
    
    
    @fabien_gandon most of those bots fight spam or deliver automated messages, so for understanding native user behavior we filter.    
    
    
    My ETERNAL gratitude to +http://goo.gl/BRwmtt  for this.Really, I am just going to… http://goo.gl/nSvaXs     
    
    
    Lunch at the Google Zurich office today.  #lifeisgood  #throughglass   http://goo.gl/UJYAFE     
    
    
    Street Photography attack:Shopkeeper in Sorrento, Italy.Reposted because the… http://goo.gl/8i6Xm2     
    
    
    @MrTonyCostello there have been papers somewhat on the same theme. There is also that book about "the selfish gene".    
    
    
    "The move by Google is among the most concrete signs yet that recent revelations… http://goo.gl/2GQnzr     
    
    
    #throughglass (#throughglass) http://goo.gl/YnfkHV     
    
    
    #throughglass (#throughglass) http://goo.gl/MHifzj     
    
    
    @benhanrahan where did you go?    
    
    
    @benhanrahan Krung Thai is one of the better Thai food around. Shana nearer downtown mv is good too.    
    
    
    These are pretty funny and mostly true :) http://goo.gl/dN1MBu     
    
    
    Amusing and true... (23 Things That Could Only Exist In Silicon Valley) http://goo.gl/uXmwaC     
    
    
    Cute upcoming paper by some Googlers looks at some of the differences between… http://goo.gl/FckuCL     
    
    
    I want... I mean, I need a library like this. Yes, the B2 Hotel just besides the… http://goo.gl/d4HTkN     
    
    
    Google Zurich at night. Probably the coolest Google office I've ever been in. http://goo.gl/quKl1N     
    
    
    A corner of Google's Zurich office. Amazing. http://goo.gl/ty4fQO     
    
    
    Do you trust the guy in this photo? Does he look suspicious?White men can… http://goo.gl/X7kovj     
    
    
    2013 edition of Shanghai academic ranking of world universities (ARWU) is out. Most… http://goo.gl/sCWVWT     
    
    
    Isaac Asimov&rsquo;s 1964 Predictions About What the World Will Look 50 Years Later… http://goo.gl/Dxb5eB     
    
    
    Earlier, Google announced open registration for Introduction to Web Accessibility… http://bit.ly/18SsdKo     
    
    
    @journik have not yet received the router from almond yet.    
    
    
    Wieniawski, Henryk op.6 Souvenir de Moskou for violin + piano http://goo.gl/K87pOG     
    
    
    Secretary of State Kerry had a very interesting conversation with… http://goo.gl/mSK4En     
    
    
    Wearable Computing research with +http://goo.gl/OoEDtThis  week, Zürich hosts the… http://goo.gl/LYIVqh     
    
    
    Very long but fun piece on how UPS optimizes route planning for its truck drivers.… http://goo.gl/nVb0JX     
    
    
    This 9/11, not the first, is the one when I feel most hopeless about our nation. On… http://goo.gl/XIdMnr     
    
    
    A good summary of US gov't's pivot to Asia and what it means to #Taiwan. http://goo.gl/xUJCMf     
    
    
    @jdfoote @barrywellman as this conversation attest, it is hard to keep everyone else interested in the conversation. G+ would work better.    
    
    
    @katypearce @raisecain @barrywellman @jdfoote @mattthomas  tw is so limited, so a waste of my time. So i just post links for info sharing.    
    
    
    @mattthomas @katypearce @raisecain @barrywellman @jdfoote also known as pain in the ass. Haha.    
    
    
    Kleiner Perkins Has Invested In A Stealth Startup To Improve Battery Power By 300%,… http://goo.gl/D3AvrN     
    
    
    Google街景團隊已抵台，以人體背包深入太魯閣國家公園拍攝錐麓古道...令人期待！辛苦了，這些拔山涉水的工作人員！ http://goo.gl/jGNmMm     
    
    
    We can see on this animations the airplanes commercial flight everyday.The main… http://goo.gl/mgbxWZ     
    
    
    Functioning 'mechanical gears' seen in nature for the first… http://goo.gl/CwLVuN     
    
    
    Cameras in phones had become really good. This is a glimpse of great things to come. http://goo.gl/DC4iAU     
    
    
    The Great Language Game: This site plays you a sample of a language, and you have to… http://goo.gl/DfQMkj     
    
    
    Organ TransplantForty-six years ago South African surgeon Christiaan Barnard… http://goo.gl/60f9gF     
    
    
    The irony. What we have forgotten is this: Freedom does not need protection. It… http://goo.gl/XIdMnr     
    
    
    A good summary of US gov't's pivot to Asia and what it means to #Taiwan. http://goo.gl/xUJCMf     
    
    
    Whoa! This is huge. Finding gears in nature for the first time. http://goo.gl/CwLVuN     
    
    
    If you haven't seen this yet: awesome visualization of flights around the world. http://goo.gl/mgbxWZ     
    
    
    Google went to Taiwan with the street view image camera on a backpack. http://goo.gl/jGNmMm     
    
    
    Battery advancement would really change the world. http://goo.gl/D3AvrN     
    
    
    Cameras in phones had become really good. This is a glimpse of great things to come. http://goo.gl/DC4iAU     
    
    
    definitely try this to get an appreciation of the world's languages. http://goo.gl/DfQMkj     
    
    
    Whoa! Transporting a donor heart while it is beating. Wow! http://goo.gl/60f9gF     
    
    
    Wanna psyched about the new ski season?! Watch this! http://goo.gl/LcRMVW     
    
    
        
    
    
    The amazing archive of ignorance from twitter on Miss America. #readandweep http://goo.gl/OANwgc     
    
    
    Cool video demonstrating angular momentum. http://goo.gl/ODHAlC     
    
    
    @wslasecki truly amazing.    
    
    
    This is why we see half of g+ traffic on mobile. http://goo.gl/BMgEQp     
    
    
    Very cool experiment on addiction and drugs. On rats. http://goo.gl/Yv7Ybu     
    
    
    rampage and 13 ppl dead.  "Police records showed that he had been arrested at least… http://goo.gl/1fPGld     
    
    
    Wow.  There is beauty in this world. http://goo.gl/6bMyei     
    
    
    How did or immigration policy become so convoluted? Read on for some commentary… http://goo.gl/ZTRG5m     
    
    
    Excellent article on how to respond to the surveillance state and policies. http://goo.gl/qxGQIE     
    
    
    Must read if you are a computer scientist who think about efficiency. Agree that We… http://goo.gl/rzBsww     
    
    
    For those of you who realized that you might not make the CHI2014 deadline, there is… http://goo.gl/1MQwpY     
    
    
    This is one of the coolest things Google does. http://goo.gl/RNJbmY     
    
    
    Hehe. Good read on data centers. http://goo.gl/C4U8oC     
    
    
    Must watch video of a great prank. http://goo.gl/wIjgkI     
    
    
    Would love to hear thoughts from Microsoft folks on this news. http://goo.gl/YVrfNR     
    
    
    Will heart-shaped dishes also induce romance? That's the million dollar question. http://goo.gl/7gEgzv     
    
    
    I support the LA Cancer Challenge for pancreatic cancer research! Join me & donate today http://rpx.me/1/dufq     
    
    
    Free! Edit MSOffice files on your mobile device! http://goo.gl/vuMFqB     
    
    
    Some of these captions are awesome. http://goo.gl/HTBa65     
    
    
    Why Chinese eCommerce sites are always so busy?! The reason for this is a subtle… http://goo.gl/8D0HsM     
    
    
    This is why we must continue to invest in machine translation. http://goo.gl/6nKVCH     
    
    
    @denzil_correa interesting. Never heard some of these things.    
    
    
    Ouch! (With iOS 7 Apple has tossed 30 years of progress out the window) http://goo.gl/9Ao39O     
    
    
    I did not know how close we were in nuking ourselves. http://goo.gl/Q7O5W4     
    
    
    Good advice about giving talks and the first 60 seconds of those talks. http://goo.gl/D0sSbX     
    
    
    A predictable and interesting development in submarine drones for warfare. http://goo.gl/xRQ3DU     
    
    
    Hahaha. http://goo.gl/IQqiFv     
    
    
    So the coin toss and soon are not even bets. Interesting! http://goo.gl/V8Aybb     
    
    
    A good rainy day for making fresh pasta. http://goo.gl/DFyXnT     
    
    
    The wine line up tonight.  :)  +Austin Chang this is how I roll. :) http://goo.gl/5QLl2P     
    
    
    Reading this seems appropriate right after the wine debauchery last night. http://goo.gl/I0DVmk     
    
    
    Heaven rained last night.   Dauvisaant grand cru with clams in white wine sauce. http://goo.gl/t3EC5L     
    
    
    Must read about the Snowden case. Details and history here that most people don't… http://goo.gl/MQB2wF     
    
    
    Average faces are, well, beautiful. http://goo.gl/N923zP     
    
    
    @naz_andalibi exactly! Also the reason that diversity creates beauty.    
    
    
    Long video of a self driving car from CMU. Good to browse thru the video to get a… http://goo.gl/BTEriN     
    
    
    Do any of my followers have two different colored eyes? It'd be cool if I do. http://goo.gl/FH5Qrv     
    
    
    Finally, the rules for devices on airplanes might be changing. http://goo.gl/CKahKX     
    
    
    Haha! Funny picture. Can giraffes really do this? http://goo.gl/nHUYhY     
    
    
    A good article analyzing the mess in Egypt from two months ago.   The press cycle… http://goo.gl/j9s2gL     
    
    
    HCI designers for mobile phones should take note of this experiment in Japan. The… http://goo.gl/DisWu0     
    
    
    Must read article on the relationship between industry and academia.   "There is a… http://goo.gl/gFq0Js     
    
    
    Visualization of the civil war in one chart. http://goo.gl/AdrhOX     
    
    
    User generated content can be some of the best content on the web.  See this example… http://goo.gl/fRrifG     
    
    
    Let's highlight the good in the world.   Joey gave a customer $20 out of his own… http://goo.gl/cmTjPR     
    
    
    This can only be seen to be believed. Wow! Incredible 4yo piano player. http://goo.gl/X0SBNe     
    
    
    Better comments in YouTube would be a welcome change for sure. http://goo.gl/ijuvg5     
    
    
    If successful, this would have huge implications for energy generation for… http://goo.gl/qIgKHE     
    
    
    Cool animation showing a specific projection of earth onto a 2d plane. http://goo.gl/Ipb8qI     
    
    
    More evidence that artificial sweeteners are bad for you. They actually make you… http://goo.gl/NcqZyt     
    
    
    Business is hard because it changes depending on the cultural context. China is… http://goo.gl/B8uu6I     
    
    
    Coffee bar in Sorrento, Italy. http://goo.gl/UeTwSJ     
    
    
    Naples, Italy. July, 2013. http://goo.gl/hILXgO     
    
    
    Street photography attack.   Naples, Italy. July 2013. http://goo.gl/OtPpX1     
    
    
    http://goo.gl/dpX5Lm     
    
    
    Hehe. Giant rubber duck in Taiwan harbors. http://goo.gl/Q8MP6C     
    
    
    Giving a talk at Stanford on Social Interactions Research on Friday: … http://goo.gl/YQlle3     
    
    
    Sorrento, Italy. July 2013. http://goo.gl/FvWu4P     
    
    
    Corner store.   Sorrento, Italy. July, 2013. http://goo.gl/H7lvWt     
    
    
    @naz_andalibi that one, no.  Canon. :-)    
    
    
    @LetsClearItUp sigh. Don't know whom to believe.    
    
    
    Amazing NatGeo video. http://goo.gl/pf0dS1     
    
    
    Is there a big twitter phishing going on?  My recent direct messages are all spam!… http://goo.gl/hp30xu     
    
    
    @LetsClearItUp thanks for the link. Will retweet.    
    
    
    My #chi2012 co-chair, +Kristina Höök , comes to visit me from Sweden and we messed… http://goo.gl/bIWhIh     
    
    
    Very interesting video of Steve Ballmer on stage saying his goodbyes to the company… http://goo.gl/OsR6GU     
    
    
    Awesome photo of a driveway under the trees. http://goo.gl/J1WNGi     
    
    
    What an interesting guy.   Via +***** http://goo.gl/BBB53a     
    
    
    Risk jail when you retweet in China.   'Anyone whose message is re-tweeted more than… http://goo.gl/GueUJS     
    
    
    These images are haunting.   We should all fight for Human Rights. http://goo.gl/wkLpwd     
    
    
    Human memory is a funny thing. Wouldn't want to live without it, but it sure is… http://goo.gl/GbQ078     
    
    
    Personality tests considered harmful. http://goo.gl/ibqX5E     
    
    
    Musicians are better at correcting mistakes.   Hmmm...   Is this because musicians… http://goo.gl/YgHiLz     
    
    
    Good read for thinking about what tech folks should focus on doing in their companies. http://bit.ly/18LfQkV     
    
    
    Dialog, not war, leads to prosperity.  One evidence:  "Iran's stock exchange reacted… http://bit.ly/18LfQl1     
    
    
    I hate meetings. They are necessary and efficient sometimes, but often they are not.… http://bit.ly/18LfP0c     
    
    
    +Google Glass in the news locally here in palo alto. http://goo.gl/vlp90Z     
    
    
    Giving the Keynote talk at HCIR conference on Thursday, October 3.  Blurring of the… http://goo.gl/mtZLg7     
    
    
    #HCIR2013 workshop is honoring +Gene Golovchinsky today with a special session, who… http://goo.gl/vPzJPh     
    
    
    This is brilliant. http://goo.gl/KKwEys     
    
    
    Whole load of days in Twitter's IPO filling, including user numbers, spam, revenue,… http://goo.gl/S0UQfO     
    
    
    Hahahaha (The Adventurey Report: National Parks to Reopen With Grant From Google |… http://goo.gl/NZg1ls     
    
    
    Worth reading: ephemeral exchanges in social media. http://goo.gl/rV19Wb     
    
    
    Wow! Lion hug caught on #gopro camera. http://goo.gl/Fs2lFU     
    
    
    +Yonatan Zunger explains about a decade worth of network science research in… http://goo.gl/wvoVVv     
    
    
    @MrMeritology yeah, damn typo.    
    
    
    Are social media sites inherently faddish?  Twitter's IPO highlights the risk. http://goo.gl/mHSOLg     
    
    
    What changes might be coming for the board of Microsoft? This article gives a glimpse. http://goo.gl/umWHL9     
    
    
    More shameful coverage of the Watergate case in Taiwan. http://goo.gl/hBn5ur     
    
    
    @noshir @terrigriffith this is the Pamela Hinds seminar that you are referring to, eh?    
    
    
    Views of the Amazon warehouses. http://goo.gl/rr3VDY     
    
    
    This robot is part of the DARPA's robot mule program for helping humans carry heavy… http://goo.gl/rFbkMA     
    
    
    @dtunkelang no and no, for now. I'll ask to get the slides released by Google.    
    
    
    I didn't know this about the space pen. 
Space Pens vs. Pencils  Via +I fucking love… http://goo.gl/N58Rbe     
    
    
    This is a good move by t-mobile (eliminating intl. roaming fees for data and text). http://goo.gl/bvJ15U     
    
    
    Good bottle tonight.   Glad that it wasn't expensive. :-)   sancerre don't make many… http://goo.gl/9k2fRc     
    
    
    Hopeful warmth in Taipei ~ 期待黎明的溫暖  或許，我這個人有點奇怪，我對小時候的事情記憶特別深刻…… http://goo.gl/TODKy0     
    
    
    Holy sh*t. This is funny. 
So, you all (hopefully) saw my photos yesterday; if you… http://goo.gl/5CiP2E     
    
    
    Love Kiva. (A loan in Cambodia) http://goo.gl/OqY5UL     
    
    
    A bunch of search tips from my friend +Dan Russell . http://goo.gl/tCTYIX     
    
    
    This is the huge duck that is docked (pun intended) in Taiwan's southern port of… http://goo.gl/alH63A     
    
    
    G+翻譯有一個小改變：  我們希望你能放心轉貼訊息給你的聽眾, 即使原來的訊息是用不同的語言寫的。我們在過去的一個月左右, 終於解決了這個問題。 … http://goo.gl/PxOCC3     
    
    
    A small update from G+  Translate:  We hope you can reshare to your audiences, even… http://goo.gl/8EYNJl     
    
    
    What a sad story. 
In China, where aid is scarce and family loyalty is a cornerstone… http://goo.gl/pmMxTH     
    
    
    Very funny, and often true. 
The Science News Cycle  This week's Best of PHD Theme:… http://goo.gl/p7Ck6H     
    
    
    Absolutely horrible. European Union has to do something about this migration route. http://goo.gl/1Guxbz     
    
    
    Of course, China would oppose. What a bully. http://goo.gl/KW7nAl     
    
    
    The not-yet-released Tesla Model X on display at the Palo Alto showroom today.  … http://goo.gl/bYo0gV     
    
    
    Now this is shocking to me. Didn't realize how easy rules can be changed in congress… http://goo.gl/s1grFy     
    
    
    Electric motorcycles haven't taken off as much as I expected. Here is another effort. http://goo.gl/ImMDdB     
    
    
    Robots helping to install solar panels. Cool. http://goo.gl/uMcqbq     
    
    
    This is depressing fat news. We are getting fatter as a country and that's going to… http://goo.gl/5nvGSg     
    
    
    Drive, baby, drive. (Saudi women show defiance by driving) http://goo.gl/9bs7Rd     
    
    
    Good read on the effects of image editing on fashion and body image. 
What is it… http://goo.gl/gFqkli     
    
    
    Absolutely incredible story. Brings tears to my eyes. 
For more than a quarter… http://goo.gl/oVRwCV     
    
    
    The longer version of the Google Map reunion story.   Via +Amogh Asgekar http://goo.gl/6zGKlJ     
    
    
    I'm ashamed of Taiwan's foreign ministry in releasing statements like this. http://goo.gl/yYk9Js     
    
    
    A primer on the budget chaos. (Confused by what’s happening in Washington? Here’s a… http://goo.gl/GfMgEa     
    
    
    And the primer on the debt ceiling. http://goo.gl/8l0HpE     
    
    
    Now that's an American hero. (Medal of Honor recipient braved gunfire to retrieve… http://goo.gl/1SwQ4o     
    
    
    Cool slo-mo video of golf ball hitting steel at high speed. 
I never realised a golf… http://goo.gl/0dUL37     
    
    
    From Quora: What is the most important thing you have learned about leadership? … http://goo.gl/4Ec9E7     
    
    
    Cool video of automated drone mapping of a famous mountain. 
This is cool work: fly… http://goo.gl/UGS1ua     
    
    
    Finally... Debt ceiling raised, mmmm... so we can fight about it again next quarter.… http://goo.gl/SeZYRs     
    
    
    This is a great idea for Halloween. 
Best Costume ever. http://goo.gl/Svjfku     
    
    
    Must watch video about Grace Hopper. What an amazing woman!
Seeing +Liz Krane's… http://goo.gl/ypJPwe     
    
    
    High fat and high sugar foods are just as addictive as cocaine!? Wow. http://goo.gl/tZlVEJ     
    
    
    In re-reading this article, I was wondering how one could use techniques for… http://goo.gl/SvYo7q     
    
    
    I challenge you to not watch this for at least 1minute with your jaw wide-open.
… http://goo.gl/JPrj2i     
    
    
    I had hoped this would happen to academic publishing, but I didn't think we would… http://goo.gl/uwWE8L     
    
    
    Holy crap! I hope my macbook air isn't affected. 
I am really scared about this... I… http://goo.gl/lHZSfV     
    
    
    Interesting cultural visualization on names.   Cc +Martin Wattenberg 
GIF for the… http://goo.gl/IFiQy1     
    
    
    Must watch funny video about chicken cam. It's Steady!
Can a Chicken Be a Better… http://goo.gl/Zf4duy     
    
    
    There are a number of isolationists in the US who advocate the rash decision to… http://goo.gl/v5o5v9     
    
    
    Cool read about a NYC restaurant's operation. 
Here's something else interesting for… http://goo.gl/5cd4gi     
    
    
    I'm in Japan with some jet leg, so this was good reading on how our sleep patterns… http://goo.gl/1Pf6pc     
    
    
    For me, this is straight out of science fiction, as this paints a future of drones… http://goo.gl/8t0lXY     
    
    
    Guinness wins advertising this week.  Maybe this year. http://goo.gl/TNPocX     
    
    
    This is very cool sleep research.  If the neurons shrink during sleep, I wonder if… http://goo.gl/IIy808     
    
    
    Economist published an amazing article on the problem of replication of studies in… http://goo.gl/ekYJ0v     
    
    
    Good points about company culture and how to measure and nurture it. 
The true test… http://goo.gl/61yCtU     
    
    
    Good YouTube video of a spoof on the Matrix movie. 
This is pretty great... a little… http://goo.gl/33yJNm     
    
    
    Classic computer science advice in an op-Ed column in WSJ.   Love it. 
i.e. expect… http://goo.gl/x0KJbX     
    
    
    Weibo translation in the WSJ news (video).   Like us, others are also thinking about… http://goo.gl/X2LNkd     
    
    
    Visiting Yokohama Bay with +Lichan Hong at #cyberworlds2013.
I rode that… http://goo.gl/tnuYul     
    
    
    A bicycle repair shop in #Chinatown in #Yokohama. http://goo.gl/2qh4sf     
    
    
    Japanese TV in the making. It does look very yummy.   Chinatown, Yokohama. 
The girl… http://goo.gl/EGpfMX     
    
    
    @narulka22000 that's a tough problem, usually solved using models of network diffusion.    
    
    
    Good analysis on MSFT. 
"Microsoft is continuing to fire on all cylinders with its… http://goo.gl/pUEZBf     
    
    
    T-Mobile shaking up the industry again. 
I didn't see that one coming  +T-Mobile Wat… http://goo.gl/r1v2ZE     
    
    
    The amazing pano view from Google's office building in Roppongi Hills. 27th floor at… http://goo.gl/1MtKR5     
    
    
    109 Building. Shibuya, Tokyo.   This is the trendy fashion place to shop. http://goo.gl/RgD1aL     
    
    
    Reflections.  Meiji Jinja (shrine).  Tokyo, Japan. http://goo.gl/E1xTVh     
    
    
    Always love going to Tokyo, because the food is so amazing. I want to be able to… http://goo.gl/ZJd1kv     
    
    
    Custom URLs for g+ profiles. 
Expanding the availability of custom URLs  Custom URLs… http://goo.gl/r2Dxgs     
    
    
    Facebook continues to do well against as analysts' expectations. 
Agreed,  +Greg… http://goo.gl/MxAk3g     
    
    
    Wikipedia and edit wars over Chinese content. Nytimes. http://goo.gl/Wg7WGo     
    
    
    Haha! "@xamat: simple predictor: if @edchi and @smolix are authors in a paper, do not use smallest room #cikm2013 pic.twitter.com/E7bihSqD5O"    
    
    
    Our CIKM paper presentation was jammed packed today with people sitting on floors.… http://goo.gl/lJy5Yl     
    
    
    Just shared a photo #throughglass pic.twitter.com/fUMnwbtfAO    
    
    
    Street photography attack.      A girl passing out flyers at a corner of Akihabara… http://goo.gl/zj8hAB     
    
    
    @CKoaser because you can't even get it anywhere right now. It's by invitation only.    
    
    
    @xamat I haven't seen that paper yet. Will definitely read it. Thanks for the notification.    
    
    
    Woot! Nexus 5 is out!
Boo! Just in time for Halloween, we’re serving up two new… http://goo.gl/msxZYt     
    
    
    Facebook confirms slowing usage by teenagers, which I've been hearing anecdotally… http://goo.gl/lBsOGL     
    
    
    Rows and columns at    Meiji Jingu, Tokyo. http://goo.gl/MUR0dm     
    
    
    Direction of Dog tail wags is the indicator of the mood.      "When the animals saw… http://goo.gl/ZwmfU1     
    
    
    Hahaha! Patrick Stewart is awesome!
The. Best.  :D    #PatrickStewartIsAwesome   … http://goo.gl/nXNfRq     
    
    
    @stoweboyd you mean academic papers?    
    
    
    @iSocialWatch hmmm.  Interesting point. Will observe using this new lens for a while.    
    
    
    Awesome bridge. And the physics behind it. 
The Slauerhoffbrug Flying Tail Bridge in… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/SsS46Uhxqf2 …    
    
    
    Yep, life isn't fair! Genes identified showing why some people can eat all they want… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/PE1xrVSc9KC …    
    
    
    Town uses giant mirrors to get sunlight into the town square. Love it!
A town in… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/EJ8xhKbzkM1 …    
    
    
    Good read. Bill Gates definitely knows his principles.      I also agree with his… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/K5V9P6Tk6wz …    
    
    
    Lunch at the New England Lobster company near SFO airport.      Lobster roll,… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/6k4aJWHHFGG …    
    
    
    PInterest's success is pretty obvious to me as a HCI researcher, but I'm surprised… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/MnpbeEvShaQ …    
    
    
    Now very curious about this interview.      I've had the pleasure of meeting … https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/Y48Lg4ZRQdq …    
    
    
    This is cool science on something mundane: How people move out of the way while… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/6DcyMWtSUq5 …    
    
    
    A fish(ing) restaurant near Yokohama, Japan.      Not necessary for the faint of the… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/gWiiioroFBu …    
    
    
    Very interesting story about the human dynamic of shame and secrets. 
A strong… https://plus.google.com/110563789211679581171/posts/2qFcEwS371p …    
    
    
    @barrywellman yes, I wonder why they felt necessary to try something different looking. ☺    
    
    
    Cliff Nass, HCI researcher and Stanford professor of communications dept, died this… http://goo.gl/QInZAI     
    
    
    Yahoo's changes are being watched.  This is already an improvement to where they… http://goo.gl/Jv8g6c     
    
    
    @CKoaser because only a very small number of devices were given out. Very very small, no more than 3 digits.    
    
    
    Interesting use of GPS. 
One company has developed a way for police to shoot GPS… http://goo.gl/5qUhg3     
    
    
    Internet archive in trouble. Scanning center burned down. 
This sucks! A good part… http://goo.gl/3XRczN     
    
    
    Ice was instrumental in the construction of the forbidden city. 
Fifteenth-century… http://goo.gl/e9NAM0     
    
    
    If there's one story to read/watch today...     This is an extraordinary account of… http://goo.gl/hqz7B7     
    
    
    Pelicans from today's Kayaking trip with Google Research's offsite.     Elkhorn… http://goo.gl/jPQ1Yq     
    
    
        
    
    
    What teenagers might be turning to after Facebook. http://goo.gl/4TVKQs     
    
    
    Great opinion piece about China. Pretty accurate based on my own observations.… http://goo.gl/P2dgiQ     
    
    
    Amazing. Fruit fly G tridens transparent wings have an ant design on them complete… http://goo.gl/jPe6WH     
    
    
    Getting fresh seafood at a harbor in Taiwan.      You buy from the vendors and then… http://goo.gl/sY4EQY     
    
    
    Must read piece about rape in India. Powerful and grappling. http://goo.gl/iycwIE     
    
    
    Hopefully they are running on Google app engine or something elastic to accommodate… http://goo.gl/MByT3T     
    
    
    This is how you bring performance art into the real world. 
How I wish I was there… http://goo.gl/GuVGHF     
    
    
    @reidpr my research actually shows that most ppl don't pay attention to those annotations. Ironic.    
    
    
    I have been using this #AutoAwesome video feature for some personal photos and… http://goo.gl/xVL9D3     
    
    
    My answer to What counts more- Master of Design from IDC, IIT Bombay or MS in HCI from renowned Universities in Unit… http://qr.ae/Gpdix     
    
    
        
    
    
    Incredible video when I couldn't even understand a word in it. http://goo.gl/54cjlz     
    
    
    30 Of The Most Powerful Images Ever http://goo.gl/aBQTJz     
    
    
    Google Book vs. Author's Guild finally came thru in favor of Google. Wow. 
Big news. http://goo.gl/gHhLnY     
    
    
    Our obit for Cliff Nass.
Remembering Cliff Nass Posted by +Ed Chi, Google Staff… http://goo.gl/Kpjht6     
    
    
    A good write up on p-value in science publications.  via +Sean McCullough  http://goo.gl/e41wPa     
    
    
    Seakayaking with Sea Otters and baby seal in the Wild.  June 2013.  Monterey, CA. http://goo.gl/Lnq3Am     
    
    
    China's one-child policy explained. http://goo.gl/o4Lo45     
    
    
    Reform ECPA: Tell the Government to Get a Warrant http://wh.gov/lBibY     
    
    
    Some cool products here. 
From robots to DNA, these six futuristic technologies may… http://goo.gl/L0LOCM     
    
    
    Whoa!  A lung inflated. 
Watch cat lungs incredibly expand with air like a balloon … http://goo.gl/d5sMrp     
    
    
    This is a hilarious animated gif. 
Every time I hit a pot hole!  #lol   … http://goo.gl/zQ5YUJ     
    
    
    Saturday night dinner.   Home made pasta over Olive oil, white wine, parsley,… http://goo.gl/LbnGDp     
    
    
    Amazing violin performance that left me speechless. 
Crazy ～ watch… http://goo.gl/8c87qa     
    
    
    Irony and family backstabbing in VP Dick Cheney's household. 
Schadenfreude. http://goo.gl/acDbXk     
    
    
    Stolen Jewish goods, such as art, from WWII can't find their way back to their… http://goo.gl/yIlBFO     
    
    
    Very Cool that this 360 view camera is making it to the market. 
Amazingly… http://goo.gl/vGFpPH     
    
    
    I never quite understood why Taiwan uses money to buy diplomatic ties. They don't… http://goo.gl/8rb87d     
    
    
    Scary! (Private firms selling mass surveillance systems around world, documents show) http://goo.gl/XRkAXB     
    
    
    Some of these sports are quite entertaining! http://goo.gl/fDf1tg     
    
    
    Wow! This is appalling. 
Remember that story about the NYC cabbie who got angry at a… http://goo.gl/yPV8FI     
    
    
    Tuesday night dinner.   Ox tail mushroom carrot tomato sauce over homemade egg… http://goo.gl/lKcK4W     
    
    
    Sigh.. And haha! Copyediting is fun!
This makes me want to drive to SF immediately.… http://bit.ly/18nWkgW     
    
    
    Watchdog in action for web security. Google fairs well in this report. 
Useful chart… http://bit.ly/18nWhS8     
    
    
    Amazing photos of the gestation of a horse. 
In its earliest, undifferentiated days,… http://goo.gl/2gG0Q1     
    
    
    Scary food additives in the US but banned elsewhere. http://goo.gl/fV4DDa     
    
    
    Long but interesting read on tech industry trends. 
Henry Blodget this week about… http://goo.gl/r26n4X     
    
    
    Cool work examines how to identify the most potential citation references in an… http://goo.gl/km3sP4     
    
    
    G+ caught up to Twitter in this chart on social network usage based on a… http://bit.ly/1iysTMT     
    
    
    @hmslydia looking for dan weld. can you bring him back to the apartado room?    
    
    
    Can't seem to solve a coding problem? Maybe you should have a drink.ï»¿ http://goo.gl/ktGOnI     
    
    
    Surprise! Man finds himself in audience full of people he saved as children from… http://goo.gl/FwMfII     
    
    
    A/B testing international aid.  Quoting: "Test ... strategies for increasing school… http://goo.gl/0O7eGW     
    
    
    Nat King Cole -- For Sentimental Reasons - Legends In Concert http://goo.gl/DlAvJl     
    
    
    The final analysis of Stuxnet by Ralph Lagner.The report is full of new information,… http://goo.gl/0i0rrH     
    
    
    Today's update to the Google+ app includes the following features:- Full size… http://goo.gl/qx5Uoy     
    
    
    This Harvard student did a very successful prank on Yale. Watch and see how he… http://goo.gl/UUO4ha     
    
    
    Some good correction to the recent science story on the cancer cure using HIV-like… http://goo.gl/Gial3k     
    
    
    the Pentagon is the only federal agency that has not complied with annual audits.… http://goo.gl/TPKfT6     
    
    
    sort of video (53 secs) that might strike a chord with… http://goo.gl/ATHfpI     
    
    
    Tension building over the East China sea again. ï»¿ http://goo.gl/krFx5f     
    
    
    The first paragraph is brilliant.  Read it, then check out the author. http://goo.gl/D5RoHl     
    
    
    It's rare that I disagree with Bruce Schneier, but I think he's viewing the… http://goo.gl/n8LCFv     
    
    
    The Betrayer's Banquet (http://goo.gl/jRKm5H ) is a game-theory--themed dinner,… http://goo.gl/GY38jb     
    
    
    Controversy around 23andme and the FDA regulations. Via +http://goo.gl/bKja9k  http://goo.gl/8DMFJ4     
    
    
    Our camera roundups continue with our look at high-end pocketable compacts. We hope… http://goo.gl/EhTRjE     
    
    
    Average NFL football game shows 11 minutes of play and 100 commercials.Average… http://goo.gl/RrKTVo     
    
    
    "Nothing like this has ever been attempted before" - a decade behind schedule, the… http://goo.gl/qPC4f9     
    
    
    Should computer scientists and engineers work for the NSA or its contractors? Some… http://goo.gl/lbDV84     
    
    
    The project features more than 7,000 school lunch photos, accompanied by often witty… http://goo.gl/ak3Q77     
    
    
    It seems that the media has discovered the existence of e-cigarettes, and we are now… http://goo.gl/K3ipHA     
    
    
    Vent Vert by Edward Suzuki Associates.  [via http://goo.gl/ZEBcr0 ] http://goo.gl/2BMA9E     
    
    
    About time.... (Berlusconi expelled from Italy&rsquo;s Senate - The Boston Globe) http://goo.gl/4Wg3jk     
    
    
    Someone needs to educate the German courts the concept of social web and… http://goo.gl/q6XDZ2     
    
    
    Japanese man discovers that he is switched at birth after 60 years. Amazing story… http://goo.gl/jLNpvi     
    
    
        
    
    
    For 20 Years the Nuclear Launch Code at US Minuteman Silos Was 00000000 http://goo.gl/Y1Do5M     
    
    
    Restaurant confronts China&rsquo;s moral crisis with free food http://goo.gl/sk6aPs     
    
    
    My friend +http://goo.gl/HApBw1  worked on this interesting wearable computing… http://goo.gl/wUdVhu     
    
    
    There's a valuable petition circulating on http://goo.gl/J63B , asking the… http://goo.gl/0RGlTo     
    
    
    Let's overrule FDA's decision to bar 23andMe from selling their diagnostic kits. http://wh.gov/lKu2R     
    
    
    @reidpr I think Google Ventures invested in 23andme very early, but I don't know any of the details.    
    
    
    @reidpr point taken. But maybe not with twitter 140 char limit.    
    
    
    This looks very relevant to our work. +http://goo.gl/V3quDO  +Sagar Jain… http://goo.gl/psEqUV     
    
    
    Great article on FoldIt and DragonBox.  I particularly recommend DragonBox, it's a… http://goo.gl/7r2DQU     
    
    
    One of the greatest stories of science: the meridian line and Cassini helped prove… http://goo.gl/YKoxW6     
    
    
    I don't follow material sciences much, but this is worth noting, "speeding up the… http://goo.gl/mI7U2t     
    
    
    From a past info visualization researcher's POV, these all look very infographic to… http://goo.gl/PgjLXR     
    
    
    From a past info visualization researcher's POV, these all look very infographic to… http://goo.gl/3i2KVe     
    
    
    This definitely would have caused a ruckus.  http://goo.gl/MyeYOr     
    
    
    Cyber Monday Special&nbsp;-&nbsp;O'Reilly Media http://goo.gl/icVWuo     
    
    
    Punctuation is powerful!An English professor wrote the words: "A woman without her… http://goo.gl/QsKsRA     
    
    
    We owe you an apology.I want to apologize to our customers and fans for the issues… http://goo.gl/RZjFV6     
    
    
        
    
    
    Free Language Lessons for ComputersPosted by +http://goo.gl/nH8mlR , Google… http://goo.gl/hrWfUb     
    
    
    @Kunaal_ CMU, uw, gatech.    
    
    
    I am excited about Andy Rubin's next project.  His last big bet, Android, started… http://goo.gl/8FBvLN     
    
    
    @Kunaal_ IU has their strengths in design, but they are not traditional hci schools. I don't know anything about Iowa state and HCI.    
    
    
    Bi-Directional Gear http://goo.gl/qF3k5A     
    
    
    U.S. government agencies claim they don't need a warrant to ask for private… http://goo.gl/0JzVNN     
    
    
    Wow. (This Commercial Totally Nails the Double Standard for Men and Women) http://goo.gl/EFhedK     
    
    
    Early work and a bit of a hack, but scary cool: "the authors first determined the… http://goo.gl/lep8XZ     
    
    
    Google Play Store gets more social.  http://goo.gl/1Mrkoj     
    
    
    Journey by Andrew WalkerAmazing #timelapse: http://vimeo.com/80871338  http://goo.gl/xYu80Y     
    
    
    Eight tech giants have sided with citizens over spies, but it's not enough http://goo.gl/RCDpEs     
    
    
    Check (In) Yo&rsquo; Self Before You Wreck Yo' Self: Why Foursquare Users Check In… http://goo.gl/yA3jYK     
    
    
    Dan Ariely might as well be an HCI researcher. http://goo.gl/9MHdfr     
    
    
    How 23andme saved a woman's life... http://goo.gl/jM5QYf     
    
    
    A rather unfortunate name for an Apple employee. Via +http://goo.gl/1ZTDXz  http://goo.gl/gXDR1h     
    
    
    Sadly, ex president Chen of Taiwan is clearly not receiving the best medical… http://goo.gl/dkIuWX     
    
    
    The Taiwan data center sounds amazing. Am very happy that Google chose Taiwan as a… http://goo.gl/hrq1vd     
    
    
    Face palm! (Terrible real estate agent photographs) http://goo.gl/Lqfmd1     
    
    
    This AWS vs. GCE list sounds very interesting.    Not having used either… http://goo.gl/rd3ECU     
    
    
    What that guy was actually signing during the ceremony. Omg! http://goo.gl/7qYEmL     
    
    
    This move by the Republicans is worth watching. http://goo.gl/pWSfPP     
    
    
    Ballmer's regrets: Longhorn is at the top of the list.  http://goo.gl/t7CUkv     
    
    
    Good explanation of the 'duon' DNA story that's making the rounds.  http://goo.gl/KnQBgc     
    
    
    Multilingual social media behavior is understudied. Am glad to see differing… http://goo.gl/oHTFkm     
    
    
    Oh! Of course, I should have predicted that this would happen! http://goo.gl/6V71Eb     
    
    
    Good reasons to exercise! (Exercise as Potent Medicine) http://goo.gl/z47H1M     
    
    
    Very cool. (THE GIFT OF GIVING: Instead of spending time and money on a holiday… http://goo.gl/SzzV8j     
    
    
    Wonderful  entertaining read on how to cycle in a skirt. The comments are great… http://goo.gl/ccg376     
    
    
    Total cloud immersion at Grand Canyon. http://goo.gl/jgnWBb     
    
    
    Great satire piece about how we don't bike to work. http://goo.gl/ivcVGz     
    
    
    Cool origami Yoda! (Yoda Origami #DIY 
Origami Jedi Master Yoda (Fumiaki Kawahata)) http://goo.gl/C3kmNl     
    
    
    Needed ruling. (Judge: NSA program is likely unconstitutional) http://goo.gl/Rdfbd5     
    
    
    Wow! (Mandatory Credit: Photo by HAP/Quirky China News/REX (3429492c)

Man has… http://goo.gl/tImJoE     
    
    
    This is pretty powerful read, and the words are so simple. http://goo.gl/2dFrpw     
    
    
    A quiet night here in Hong Kong,Happy holidays to all of my followers! http://goo.gl/O63tmq     
    
    
    Good catch! http://goo.gl/VtA5Bo     
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy (Bokeh) Holidays #2.My attempt at demonstrating both foreground and background… http://goo.gl/MnFwmi     
    
    
    No issues. Worth every penny. http://goo.gl/Q0D9L8     
    
    
    Using your phone to check Your Cholesterol Level. Clearly the FDA is going to get… http://goo.gl/oxkHvS     
    
    
    Does Snowden deserve amnesty? (Who broke the law, Snowden or the NSA?) http://goo.gl/L7x78M     
    
    
    Facebook and self censorship analysis. http://goo.gl/3xbbyU     
    
    
    Should be allowed goal, because it is so freaking awesome. http://goo.gl/GxjgWj     
    
    
    Rubber-band gun, super sized. Via +http://goo.gl/Gpc5tQ  http://goo.gl/s2rN0a     
    
    
    I've learned from talking to a few "secrecy" followers of mine, while attending… http://goo.gl/hS7gdx     
    
    
    @MLrecruiting4MS that's true for my twitter f, but the feedback was from g+ users. ☺    
    
    
    Sad that I missed this at Google this week. http://goo.gl/2RLAlZ     
    
    
    The signals and optics of this Facebook move is indeed puzzling. http://goo.gl/p8qKpa     
    
    
    Reflection. (Reflection.) http://goo.gl/Ki08K3     
    
    
    My favorite band is now on g+ http://goo.gl/VlYeyM     
    
    
    Customer happiness not correlated to companies' success?! http://goo.gl/jmih27     
    
    
    Very creative skateboarding. (Gou Miyagi does not skateboard how most people… http://goo.gl/qYXrdY     
    
    
    Cool photographs. (Smeared Skies Made from Hundreds of Stacked Photographs by Matt… http://goo.gl/nZSaFG     
    
    
    This dialect identification work was done by one of my former interns… http://goo.gl/AA7xSx     
    
    
    You might have NSA fatigue, but this is about as scary as it gets. This completely… http://goo.gl/qd68NM     
    
    
    Don't forget that social media is a very fast communication medium, especially when… http://goo.gl/U336HS     
    
    
        
    
    
    Pawn shop and a bicycling man. Hong Kong.  http://goo.gl/LFHsBN     
    
    
    This analysis of Taiwan's fate isn't inaccurate, just that it assumes rational… http://goo.gl/A3WPmH     
    
    
    Finally, Alan Turing is pardoned.  It's about time.  http://goo.gl/KtvHMo     
    
    
    Still pretty fats to choose what my next phone would be.  http://goo.gl/7G7U8C     
    
    
    Flying in economy class is becoming inhumane. Literally. http://goo.gl/6Vs27L     
    
    
    This is exactly how I feel about RSA's statement on their collaboration with NSA.  http://goo.gl/UQL5M6     
    
    
    A good way to think about those less fortunate than us is Kiva. http://goo.gl/RNw9hz     
    
    
        
    
    
    I don't think they meant it the way I interpret it. :)Found yesterday in the Bangkok… http://goo.gl/cttpgF     
    
    
    Propane Delivery Man.Bangkok, Thailand. http://goo.gl/r5xUmW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Sleeping in the midst of Chaos.Driving by street vendors in Bangkok, Thailand. http://goo.gl/I9f1lZ     
    
    
    Definitely worth watching (Hawaii volcano in action). http://goo.gl/dbDrBK     
    
    
    The theatrical turn in the judgment of the lawfulness of mass surveillance. http://goo.gl/Q7duYr     
    
    
    This should be obvious, but it isn't too most people. http://goo.gl/c779WN     
    
    
    Good read about MSR.   Cc +http://goo.gl/rlFkU3  http://goo.gl/2MukuF     
    
    
    Don't be fooled. The next MS CEO would be crazy to break up the company, but it does… http://goo.gl/yL4k1B     
    
    
    This confirms what we've known for a while: Teens have stopped using Facebook.  http://goo.gl/xzfrV9     
    
    
    @barrywellman @DannyAnth the original post http://theconversation.com/facebooks-so-uncool-but-its-morphing-into-a-different-beast-21548 … seems to be quoted verbatim by these new outlets, so why the backpeddling?    
    
    
    @barrywellman @DannyAnth indeed, quotes can often be taken out of context, but the spirit of the interpretation wasn't far off from the OP.    
    
    
    Good read on the new slogans in China. http://goo.gl/i8Ol1T     
    
    
    It's about time. (Boy Scouts To Accept Gay Youth Starting January 1) http://goo.gl/ol7Imf     
    
    
    Why innovation happen in a network: http://goo.gl/CBFGC2     
    
    
    Always enjoyed reading about +http://goo.gl/1SY2Hh  work at his lab at… http://goo.gl/eswCca     
    
    
    Tibetan Buddhist art. Created and destroyed. Amazing.  http://goo.gl/dznHWH     
    
    
    Reflections in your eye could be used to recover scene information. http://goo.gl/87Rvmi     
    
    
    @barrywellman using managefliter to cross post from g+. I find twitter too limiting. Doesn't clicking thru to g+ help avoid paywall issue?    
    
    
    Frozen soap bubbles. This is the coolest photography project I've seen in a while.  http://goo.gl/rix2Jq     
    
    
    Could there be a chance for Hillary Clinton in 2016 after all? http://goo.gl/31TLMb     
    
    
    a somewhat interesting rambling post about Apple's lack of presence on social media. http://goo.gl/1PgXFm     
    
    
    A good way for academic researchers to get into the Google Glass research scene. http://goo.gl/DQVUoV     
    
    
    Ed Chi - Google+ - This confirms what we've known for a while: Teens have&hellip; http://goo.gl/IT63En     
    
    
    @jeffbigham have you been following the details? It's pretty amusing.    
    
    
    Strong evidence. (Ten Years After Decriminalization, Drug Abuse Down by Half in… http://goo.gl/ZyOzaq     
    
    
    Oh no! (Giant yellow duck explodes in Taiwan...again) http://goo.gl/Ma9WIl     
    
    
    Never had this problem with my android devices. It just works. http://goo.gl/d3FLnH     
    
    
    Nytimes calling for pardon for Snowden.   Via +http://goo.gl/Xgqq2F  http://goo.gl/CJMsMe     
    
    
    Android OS release process for a handset.  http://goo.gl/HEQhkk     
    
    
    Ed just created his first match. Give $1 to 'Send a Child to School in Rural Haiti'… http://goo.gl/vmp5Cj     
    
    
    First rule in rescuing other people: make sure you are safe first. Oops.  http://goo.gl/hdyGim     
    
    
    Nice research work that extended our work on Wikipedia edit wars and reverts from… http://goo.gl/Iuf8tX     
    
    
    New SEO. Social Engine Optimization.  http://goo.gl/xakxmu     
    
    
    Should be interesting. http://fplus.me/p/f55     
    
    
    Concept of owning something should include tinkering with it. http://fplus.me/p/flk     
    
    
    horror movie "encourages viewers to download a free app that delivers second screen content during the movie." http://fplus.me/p/fnb     
    
    
    Must watch! How it feels when you're detained in Beijing! http://fplus.me/p/fIB     
    
    
    Google Glass becoming more real for me. http://fplus.me/p/fMu     
    
    
    Just bought my T4i not long ago. Argh. http://fplus.me/p/fTU     
    
    
    Announced today: Google Keep note taking app. http://fplus.me/p/fTT     
    
    
    Cool crowd sourcing research from YouTube. http://fplus.me/p/fUp     
    
    
    Insane skier video of a drop into a chute. http://fplus.me/p/fUA     
    
    
    I'm ashamed to say that I'm from Minnesota. Even O'Reilly says Bachmann is ridiculous: http://fplus.me/p/gfX     
    
    
    This scares the shit out of me. If you have women in your life, must read. http://fplus.me/p/gwG     
    
    
    Apple. two step authentication. about time. http://fplus.me/p/gxP     
    
    
    understating is better than overstating. http://fplus.me/p/gxO     
    
    
    how does any of the social networks avoid being pushed aside? good question. http://fplus.me/p/gy4     
    
    
    Must read if you are a computer Geek. Botnet to scan the entire internet. http://fplus.me/p/gzx     
    
    
    Must watch. Largest calving glacier event ever recorded. http://fplus.me/p/gF0     
    
    
    Crazy Congress trying to do science for scientists again. http://fplus.me/p/gFa     
    
    
    Must read about guns and john Lennon and yoko. And beautiful via. http://fplus.me/p/hrm     
    
    
    Must watch. How to unload a truck quickly. http://fplus.me/p/hDZ     
    
    
    Coding using voice. Wow. http://fplus.me/p/hEY     
    
    
    Interesting exchange. Kudos. http://fplus.me/p/hEZ     
    
    
    See number 40 and 52 in this collection. http://fplus.me/p/hFL     
    
    
    Cool story about a lost camera at sea showing up six years later in Taiwan. http://fplus.me/p/hTr     
    
    
    Super cool high speed photography. http://fplus.me/p/hYB     
    
    
    A new silly way to fill potholes in the road. http://fplus.me/p/i3Y     
    
    
    Looks like something out of the Star Wars movies. http://fplus.me/p/iRE     
    
    
    The ending to the lost camera story. http://fplus.me/p/jI4     
    
    
    Must read. Funny stuff. http://fplus.me/p/kgq     
    
    
    Privacy and Trust are actually very different, even if they're the two sides of the same coin. http://fplus.me/p/kgE     
    
    
    Bullying on social networks is getting out of hand. It's interesting to read how Facebook handles it: http://fplus.me/p/kk1     
    
    
    Monopolies in media is particularly damaging to young democracies like taiwan. http://fplus.me/p/kr4     
    
    
    Spying via RAT tools and webcams. Scary stuff. http://fplus.me/p/ksY     
    
    
    Must watch video about graphene and how it can be turned into a battery that will change the world. http://fplus.me/p/ktN     
    
    
    This is pretty amazing video of how far character animation has come. Just think about Toy Story and what is repr... http://fplus.me/p/l4v     
    
    
    Wow. Map reduce is free from patent issues. http://fplus.me/p/l8P     
    
    
    Totally worth reading just for the pure sport of debate and the hilarity of the arguments. On same sex marriage. http://fplus.me/p/l9a     
    
    
    Dashboards for big data analysts to display on big screens. http://fplus.me/p/lfq     
    
    
    Same day delivery from Google in the bay area. http://fplus.me/p/lgb     
    
    
    In the last two weeks, I was invited to give two talks: http://fplus.me/p/lOg     
    
    
    Cool photos of cities with starry night sky. http://fplus.me/p/lV2     
    
    
    Don't install apps from unknown and untrusted sources. http://fplus.me/p/lYH     
    
    
    Scary article about a bad dentist. http://fplus.me/p/meE     
    
    
    Nice community on machine learning! http://fplus.me/p/mib     
    
    
    This is shameful turn of events on the Libor scandal. http://fplus.me/p/mir     
    
    
    social commentary about the state of social mobility in the US. http://fplus.me/p/miS     
    
    
    Interesting article on media influence. http://fplus.me/p/mZ4     
    
    
    Interesting analysis of the gay marriage case that is the talk of the nation. http://fplus.me/p/n01     
    
    
    Fluorescent fish. Kind of crazy, even if it's just for decorative purposes. http://fplus.me/p/nxy     
    
    
    Been waiting for this. Auto full res photo upload for g+. http://fplus.me/p/oFT     
    
    
    Good read on the failures of big data analytics. From my experience, Google and many other companies violates thi... http://fplus.me/p/oG7     
    
    
    @iC @dyahnuri you should be able to invite someone with just an gmail address. But yes, it can be complex.    
    
    
    Nice license plate. http://fplus.me/p/oGE     
    
    
    