@R_Lukaku cannot wait to see you at chelsea! from a belgian ex-pat in london    
    
    
    @farhanlalji it's unavoidable I guess after a while in Switzerland to start using loads of cheese-related words..    
    
    
    @MrsLRCooper  exactly - it is because with murdoch he had to do damage control for himself    
    
    
    My followers live in the U.K. (34.8%), the U.S. (27%) & Germany (15.7%) [top 3]. Find yours at http://twocation.com/    
    
    
    @nbidon I hear you    
    
    
    A worthwhile discipline: when giving feedback, separate "not for me" from "not for anyone." http://bit.ly/afdxd1    
    
    
    My answer on @Quora to: How can one develop original thinking? http://qr.ae/7s9OB    
    
    
    @danparsonson Thanks Dan! All good? Drop by to see Zoi soon as your schedule allows!    
    
    
    How many PPTs does a PM make during his career? http://markandrewgoetz.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2009/11/tufte-wallpaper.png LOL    
    
    
    :) RT @alaindebotton: One way to keep feeling young is to keep discovering new layers of immaturity.    
    
    
    @yeltzland aah that sucks. Hope it clears up soon    
    
    
    @gtdguy nice pic - hope you have  a good time in my motherland :)    
    
    
    @LoveMyBrownBoys congratulations!    
    
    
    getting my project list up to date    
    
    
    @tarecfighter happy birthday!    
    
    
    at the all hands    
    
    
    @JeanieBuss  loved the commercial - thx for sharing    
    
    
    watching the daily show    
    
    
    in sprint planning    
    
    
    @NCox Great "Task Complete" experience though at least for the example Guy showed me :)    
    
    
    is enjoying a productive day talking to many US colleagues... wish things would always goes this well    
    
    
    waiting for Marina after her first class on programming    
    
    
    ran into daphne doing a course on illustrator... small world    
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal  nitrate rich vegetables    
    
    
    Weekend weekend.... one more conf call    
    
    
    Done for the weekend ... Huray    
    
    
    Watching 24 with the misses    
    
    
    listening to the Q4 earnings call    
    
    
    feeling pretty tired and it is only mid-week    
    
    
    shocking RT @brucel: After assisting News International phone hacking for bribes, the Met Police acts: agains… (cont) http://deck.ly/~99UL9     
    
    
    is at geomob and impressed    
    
    
    damn these delicious snacks and beers at geomob... trying to lose some weight here    
    
    
    Love the Rummble presentation #geomob ... signing up now    
    
    
    been singing the virtues of scrum to some of my old Trados colleagues... wonder if they are going to pick it up    
    
    
    don't you sometimes wish you had a second chance to do a product again with what you know now    
    
    
    @danparsonson guess what - plants vs zombies now on bing: http://www.bing.com/games/online/bing/plvzom/default/en-gb?q=Plants+vs+Zombies&mkt=en-gb&form=pgbar2&cc=gb … :)    
    
    
    Search Pad: Making Online Research Easier: http://tinyurl.com/cb6ty9    
    
    
    I love video conferencing -- so much better sound quality than our conference phones    
    
    
    Of course you have to watch out for looking bored and it is more difficult to multi-task :)    
    
    
    Cool new search engine based on Y! BOSS. Lovely if you touch type which I am sure everyone on twitter does ;) http://pieisgood.org/search/    
    
    
        
    
    
    Finally bought a microwave after being in the UK for 2 years now. As a student could not live without. How times change.    
    
    
    Digging into Selenium    
    
    
        
    
    
    @tcoppel Congrats!    
    
    
    @danawhite Bing has UFC fighters in Visual Search http://www.bing.com/visualsearch?g=ufc_fighters    
    
    
    Trying to get off to a good start    
    
    
    Looking at Comscore data    
    
    
    Watching The Wire (season 1). Lots of catching up to do :)    
    
    
    Why o why did I sign up for a gym class at 7:00 tomorrow morning    
    
    
    Ooh Food for Thought what would lunch time be without you    
    
    
    on quiet train - might actually read something    
    
    
    thinking what to cook for valentine's    
    
    
    Going to see Complicit in the Old Vic next Friday -- can't wait    
    
    
    Just had a swedish massage, some lovely food and a siesta... life can be good    
    
    
    @trealicious love the nick :) welkom op twitter!    
    
    
    Made shepherdess pie but not looking like in the restaurant... took me two and a half hours... have never peeled so many parsnips in my life    
    
    
    Doing my Greek lesson of the day... slow progress... I guess easier to learn when growing up    
    
    
    @irinastar33 hey that's great to hear... can't wait to see it myself :)    
    
    
    @danpeters  stay overnight this time and enjoy the good restaurants!    
    
    
    One episode of Flight of the Conchords and then my Greek lesson of the day...reward before effort :)    
    
    
    Going through long feature list excel sheets... I prefer to work from paper or even an MS Word PRD as these excel files never print out well    
    
    
    That's not to say I don't love lists... I am a GTD fan after all :)    
    
    
    Out for dinner. Have to give it to the italians: insalata pollo e spinachi sounds so much better than chicken salad    
    
    
    Waiting for post mortem to start... same hold music time & again    
    
    
    Big fan of GTD and David Allen @gtdguy is now on twitter    
    
    
    Going to clear my inbox today ... yes I can    
    
    
    @willie266 @cathyma save some Walkers for your search colleagues on the 4th floor...sure we can work out a deal    
    
    
    twinity to go live with a virtual london still this year - http://tinyurl.com/8eobtz    
    
    
    Off to the Phoenix artist club for some drinks    
    
    
    @markbulmer was great fun - thanks for organising    
    
    
    Out of coffee -- how could this happen -- switching to green tea    
    
    
    on my way to the old vic    
    
    
    best evening out in ages - great play + great food n company    
    
    
    .RT @brilliantforge: Are you hiring people who are so creative, intelligent & "different" that they make yo… (cont) http://deck.ly/~0xvIQ     
    
    
    Waiting for Liverpool vs Manchester City to start    
    
    
    in user research session @ Bucks Fizz    
    
    
    Having leftover aubergine & fennel timbale (I am starting to get into vegetarian cooking)    
    
    
    Man U quite dominant in the 1st half -- that's unexpected    
    
    
    Very entertaining game... couple of goals and it is a perfect champions' league evening    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/dyfqmf -- hehe    
    
    
    what a great tool for a relative newbee to london like me http://www.where-can-i-live.com/    
    
    
    What searchers want http://tinyurl.com/c2rqqv    
    
    
    going to see chelsea - wigan this saturday    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great stuff RT @AlBingUKEditor: We've a new campaign on Bing to help those with no access to the internet get online  - http://bit.ly/elC9Iz    
    
    
    Horrible headache... and was so looking forward to my day off    
    
    
    back from yoga class... first time... was really bad but still fun    
    
    
    Or Next Gen RT @codepo8: So, if you want to build a new product - don't call it Buzz - http://vwd.go.ly   RIP Yahoo Buzz, RIP Google Buzz    
    
    
    those Y! birthday cakes have me on a sugar high    
    
    
    Kumo looks quite Return of the Jedi like    
    
    
    local idiot to post comment... just too funny: 
http://tinyurl.com/6hwypl    
    
    
    feeling strangely optimistic today    
    
    
    and the missing url: http://tinyurl.com/cquarp    
    
    
    Prepping for my slew of US conference calls    
    
    
    difficult to avoid sitting next to somebody scoffing down burger king on the train at this time    
    
    
    need to put on ipod full blast to avoid hearing munching noises    
    
    
    ok great - somebody has a mini radio we can all listen along    
    
    
    save me...    
    
    
    @yahnyinlondon always interested in cooking ideas... have fun with it!    
    
    
    @ncox with the traffic in LA Nith better have a comfortable chair to sit in ;)    
    
    
    Time to clean up inbox and get project/task list up to date    
    
    
    @trealicious during normal commute hours it is actually surprisingly civilized -- I call them pro-commuters (and I have been assimilated)    
    
    
    inquisitor baby http://twurl.nl/uw0n8r    
    
    
    is thinking work should give me an iphone so I can evangelize the inquisitor app properly :)    
    
    
    Looking through latest user research deck on local    
    
    
        
    
    
    Greek lesson of the day...    
    
    
    Looking at NUnit    
    
    
    Moving onto XPath    
    
    
    Body balance class @ 11.30 -- mixture of tai chi, pilates and yoga...curious    
    
    
    Siesta time    
    
    
    thinking it's time to start working on my little side project again    
    
    
    Spotify moved in on the 2nd floor of my office building -- very green    
    
    
    going to see watchmen shortly... can't wait    
    
    
    It will be a busy couple of days lots to decide    
    
    
    @wetzelmichael have fun! where is it this year?    
    
    
    Didn't see watchmen yesterday -- got sidetracked watching SNL -- maybe I should read the comic first?    
    
    
    up at 430 today... must be nervous although I feel calm    
    
    
    A whirlwind of meetings today but like to believe progress was mde    
    
    
    on my way to Heatrow - 9 hrs of inbox purging coming up    
    
    
    @trealicious een bepaald artikel dat je stoorde of is de toon in 't algemeen veranderd? Ik moet nog altijd wennen aan de nieuwe layout    
    
    
    Thinking about starting up reorg-now.com: load in your resource list and easily switch between matrix, c-, etc setups incl templated comms    
    
    
    we will just take a cut of supposed cost savings -- value-based pricing baby    
    
    
    @rajatpandit what's the 2nd big milestone? I do not think I every got there...    
    
    
    @rajatpandit i guess that's why they invented pubs -- due to twitter's restrictive format    
    
    
    Start tagging your sites: http://developer.search.yahoo.com/start    
    
    
    wishes he was at the GTD Summit    
    
    
    in full out tourist mode and on the observation deck ocf the space needle    
    
    
    Got myself a hard copy of Founders at Work... looking forward to reading it this weekend    
    
    
    @trealicious he he more dreaming something    
    
    
    feeling left out... I don't have the new FB layout everyone is complaining about....    
    
    
    Man u vs Liverpool ... lots of uncharacteristic errors    
    
    
    so much pressure from man u and no goal...    
    
    
    knee deep in css    
    
    
    thanks! #followmestephen    
    
    
    Later on gonna watch chelsea - man city but first try to get some work done    
    
    
    On today's menu roased mediterrean vegetables with a red pepper sauce and a spinach souffle topping    
    
    
    Want more women in tech? Girls, just do it. And everyone, quit the... http://lnkd.in/SQukMY    
    
    
    Up early on a Monday... have a feeling this will be a strange week    
    
    
    Off to the gym shortly - a bit too many indulgences this weekend    
    
    
    "how bad are we doing if the british have to cheer us up? The country has like 3 hours of sunshine a year" - Jon Stewart-it is sunny now...    
    
    
    serious headache and only 14:00 -- tylenol to the rescue    
    
    
    train cancelled - waiting for slow one into london    
    
    
    thinks its a sign nobody is meant to work on st p's    
    
    
    Wonder how many decks I have written so far - authors get glory but serial deck writers none - nobody says <name> has written 3000 decks-lo    
    
    
    maybe actually it should work the other way around... <name> was responsible for inflicting 3000 decks ont he world    
    
    
    Trying to get my project list up-to-date    
    
    
    RT@nbidon Google launches Street View in UK http://bit.ly/1JMJOU - images so good I can count leaves on my doorstep!cool or scary?"    
    
    
    Feeling the need to travel... looking forward to the Switzerland work trip later this month    
    
    
    i think sunshine and optimism must be strongly connected... hence the nr of startups in cali i guess    
    
    
    or maybe i am just happy that a long awaited pjt of mine seems to be gathering traction    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong yes v sad news it's jade btw    
    
    
    Spend the whole day on my website. Day flew by.    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/cfuabo data eventually becomes a crutch for every decision    
    
    
    listening to working on a dream...great start of the day    
    
    
    made a aubergine, tomato, red pepper and basil soup this wk... delish even if I do say so myself    
    
    
    roasting the veggies first really brings out the flavour    
    
    
    @guyhepworth most of it is gone so next time I promise :)    
    
    
    @cathyma that lightening talk does sound interesting - when does it start?    
    
    
    Looking forward to Y! pr event tonight    
    
    
    Download Inquisitor for your iPhone http://www.inquisitorx.com/iphone/    
    
    
    @vicchi  still guinnestastic here    
    
    
    @danpeters I am big fan of MindMaps - great format for dumping out your thoughts and then re-order/phrase your thinking    
    
    
    @vicchi definitely geo-rific    
    
    
    learning new things about yahoo geo    
    
    
    sad to  hear jan pedersen is no longer with us    
    
    
    @danpeters: what tool are you using? Mindmanager?    
    
    
    Doing Greek lesson of the day or should I say of the week :(    
    
    
    Watching Greece vs Israel -- Greece leads woot    
    
    
    prepping for next week's search summit    
    
    
    @babasave I would say so as it is EU specific in Switzerland but love to start some internet rumours ;)    
    
    
    almost off to Switzerland... actually forgot they are not in the eurozone... man    
    
    
    waiting in terminal 5 and sunny outside    
    
    
    @jochenhummel do you recommend reading "ReWork" then?    
    
    
    @JochenHummel  Ok great. I will get it then. I have been thinking of it for a while but I tend to buy too many books...    
    
    
    Quite impressed with the Swiss cantine -- a truly lovely seabass    
    
    
    looking forward to the cheese fondue tonight at some auberge    
    
    
    @onpm: Search in Y! Mail working fine for me    
    
    
    Struggling to stay focused after a couple of really good days in der Schweiz    
    
    
    playing around with BOSS    
    
    
    @Jonnybones #TotalDomination2011    
    
    
    @saqibs lol - well at least we show fresh results    
    
    
    wrote a little BOSS application with web results / Y! answers side-by-side -- remarkable how good answers is for certain queries    
    
    
    For some reason I don't like the term "The Cloud"  - sounds so pretentious    
    
    
    What do you associate with the Altavista brand? Old school chique waiting for a revamp or so yesterday?    
    
    
    @michaelserisier welcome to twitter dude! how's la loca vida in barcelona?    
    
    
    @salimmitha dead jealous - that was a great game    
    
    
    Local Search Growth Outpaces Overall Online Searchhttp://tinyurl.com/czgrkp    
    
    
    http://tinyurl.com/afr2g3 we know this too    
    
    
    4 days off - life is good    
    
    
    you gotta love BOSS - some new features announced: http://tinyurl.com/djje8g    
    
    
    Watching Hamburg - Man City -- it seems it's good football week    
    
    
    @creativekitty welcome to twitter! enjoy your blog so look forward to your updates    
    
    
    “Back to basics. What do I want? What do I want to see in the world?” And create that. - Ev Williams    
    
    
    new blog post: 6 month rule for big changes http://bit.ly/rWuoxV     
    
    
    finally saw Slumdog Millionaire -- was impressed; much crueller scenes than I had expected though    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong happy easter!#    
    
    
    Yelp will let businesses respond to web reviews: http://tinyurl.com/ce75al    
    
    
    @martrz just trying to entertain :)    
    
    
    chelsea - liverpool .... what a game    
    
    
    feeling incredibly tired and it is just 11    
    
    
    reading a full fledged PRD - has been a while    
    
    
    3 english teams in the semis... come on    
    
    
    @martinet after what they did to Bayern they must have a good shot.... cannot wait for the next games    
    
    
    will be at the y! hackday in london http://www.hackday.org and looking forward to seeing cool BOSS hacks #openhacklondon    
    
    
    @salimmitha http://www.iraqgoals.net/ or http://tinyurl.com/cypplp (I prefer a sopcast channel)    
    
    
    all ready for the game - high hopes for a great game    
    
    
    have a feeling chelsea may win this one    
    
    
    ok quickly proven wrong - lucky that I don't be on sports    
    
    
    @creativekitty Ok ok :( there is basketball later :) - aren't you writing a blog post no procrastinating!    
    
    
    been playing around with Y! Boss - still quite a bit to do, but it works: www.searchdoublr.com    
    
    
    @THE_REAL_SHAQ Detroit has a very experienced team... they could steal one    
    
    
    @creativekitty hey chapter one - cool :)    
    
    
    wow best performance of a bull in boston since michael    
    
    
    this is even better than the song she sang on the show http://tinyurl.com/ca6vpp    
    
    
    Christos anesti    
    
    
    Oracle buying Sun? Wonders what this means for MySQL    
    
    
    @bisping excellent!    
    
    
    New search team member of the Paris office visiting us here. Welcome Gregoire!    
    
    
    @kjbroom updates? this should be your ideal replacement for email - only 140 chars :)    
    
    
    To search or not to search that is the question    
    
    
    Arshaviiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiiin    
    
    
    thinking I left the earnings call too early    
    
    
    Google avoids £100m UK tax http://www.timesonline.co.uk/tol/news/uk/article6122329.ece    
    
    
    @kjbroom you are right in the States everything is bigger: 100-98 ;)    
    
    
    @factlets @JochenHummel lol    
    
    
    @SimonHunterfilm @Raindance Thanks for the great session yesterday    
    
    
    late to the party but just 'discovered' kings of leon    
    
    
    when its sunny london is just the best city    
    
    
    free beer and pizza at all hands screening -- thanks mark    
    
    
        
    
    
    Gaining marketshare is so sweet    
    
    
    having the day off and being very lazy    
    
    
    flashbacks to manchester and drinking cans of lager on the grass & staring at cricket (still don't get the rules)    
    
    
    My Twitter personality: likeable sociable cautious My style: chatty coherent WRITER http://twanalyst.com/intven    
    
    
    new blog post on how to build your own search engine FE in .NET: http://tinyurl.com/c2c42j    
    
    
    Should have worked from home RT @adCenter: Watch out Maidenhead! The @Bing ice cream van is coming your way today - http://adnews.ms/aDx39a    
    
    
    so true RT @alaindebotton: Getting to the top has a miraculous ability to persuade people that the system is OK.    
    
    
    @mitenaghera welcome to twitter dude! did you get big screen tv yet?    
    
    
    will be at local search summit on wednesday    
    
    
    @mitenaghera hey great :) yep all good here. finally some sun, at least occassionally...    
    
    
    reading up on the hyperlocal space    
    
    
    gotta love great indian food    
    
    
    local search summit turning out to be very educational, lots of v applicable research being presented. afternoon google presentation/panel.    
    
    
    got slightly tipsy with google guys but no company secrets spilled    
    
    
    is it too early for beerfriday?    
    
    
    is wishing the economy would pick up already    
    
    
    Looking forward to see Jay & Geraldine later today but first need to make fool of myself in body balance class    
    
    
    Big congrats to Panithinaikos - Euroleague champs :-) - what a finish    
    
    
    cannot believe lakers lost... happy celtics did though    
    
    
    my guess it will be a man u - chelsea final gain    
    
    
    man &*(&&(&&++(*(*(&%$$$&%^^(&&(&*&&( £$%£$%"    
    
    
    Google starting to lead MS in anti-trust lawsuits ;) http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/8033073.stm    
    
    
    not a classic tonight then    
    
    
    @trealicious LOL - dan waren de product namen bij trados maar flauw    
    
    
    layoffs are awful but seeing some striking out on their own will maybe actually help lift the economy    
    
    
    rose-colored glasses I guess    
    
    
    absolutely devastated - chelsea deserved better    
    
    
    @farhanlalji so yahoo isn't delighting the user after all?    
    
    
    really enjoyable lunch at belgo's: Carbonnades de boeuf à la gueuze  + *belgian* fries + nice abbey beer    
    
    
    @beermerchants cool site - now I know where I can get the good stuff ;)    
    
    
    love audiobooks - listen to GTD Fast at gym - good for body and mind :) #gtd    
    
    
        
    
    
    @creativekitty rooting for you    
    
    
    this afternoon heading to #openhacklondon for the demos - excited to see what people came up with    
    
    
    2 mins for a hack demo - would be impossible for a PM #openhacklondon    
    
    
    precious http://kisses.heroku.com/collection/cost #openhacklondon    
    
    
    Belgians at hackday - have a robot to bring them beer - welcome compatriots  #openhacklondon    
    
    
    my favourite so far: http://dharmafly.com/openfreecycle #openhacklondon    
    
    
    what a sucky end to a good day - o lakers why    
    
    
    listening to latest bob dylan album    
    
    
    @creativekitty that's great to hear! i am struggling a bit but going to try seinfeld calendar thing and try to write 15 mins a day at least    
    
    
    like that idea RT @farhanlalji: Flight of the Conchords on Spotify  http://bit.ly/lz0fo Think Timberlake and Samberg need to do an album    
    
    
    New blog post: Seinfeld calendar http://wp.me/pccNa-53     
    
    
    wife's birthday tomorrow -- feel good about the gifts -- hope she likes it    
    
    
    new blog post: Education is a-changing http://wp.me/pccNa-59    
    
    
    TeamWorks! :-) @sdltrados  Deutsches Webinar „#SDL TeamWorks-Connectoren: Workflowmanagement Plus“ – hier registrieren: http://bit.ly/9tJIEZ    
    
    
    new blog post: A light-hearted look at replies to release announcement emails http://wp.me/pccNa-5i     
    
    
    Going to see Agatha Christie's the Mousetrap tonight - looking forward    
    
    
    never noticed this before - Dell site for women: http://content.dell.com/us/en/home/della.aspx protect your investment with a stylish sleeve    
    
    
    enjoyed the play - does feel like a bit of london history    
    
    
    when I was younger I thought all English were like the ones on Agatha Christie novel - half year in manchester set me straight ;)    
    
    
    @gtdguy is this the same two day seminar of the GTD fast CD set?    
    
    
    @gtdguy thanks very much David!    
    
    
    @xenotext hey gerrit welkom op twitter! groetjes aan annelies    
    
    
    wishing he could watch game 6 - damn you time differences    
    
    
    love the reuters video on open hack day http://bit.ly/mrAbz    
    
    
    @ncox all publicity is good publicity :) glad to get some press for a change 15y in industry and`still impressing startups not too shabby    
    
    
    "We were worried, and I said, 'Let's try Yahoo' - and it worked," http://tinyurl.com/qbucan    
    
    
    Still surprises me that little changes like moving desk can give you fresh energy and feel like a fresh start    
    
    
    happy I will be able to watch game 7 lakers rockets as they play early    
    
    
    how long can you resist a marshmallow? ;) http://bit.ly/CHEln    
    
    
    Google protects Colonel Sander's privacy http://bit.ly/5EJIV
 - brilliant    
    
    
    @kateGavin yeah you don't wanna take the stress into the weekend - have a good one :)    
    
    
    twitter and local search http://searchenginewatch.com/3633755    
    
    
    weekly review time #gtd    
    
    
    @kaj33 did you like Bynum's hook? ;)    
    
    
    feeling like its calm before the storm - dont ask why    
    
    
    Looking forward to good friends from Belgium visiting us over the bank holiday wk - impressed they would drive all this way for little me    
    
    
    wondering if twitter will impact companies like Yelp as more and more people seem to use it for local restaurant recommendations or bars    
    
    
    Google backs local newspaper mergers in the UK http://bit.ly/42v2x    
    
    
    jealous of my US colleagues who can watch lakers - nuggets live today    
    
    
    @n0seblunt @kjbroom congrats guys - looks great!    
    
    
    Y! going WOO-hoo instead of Yahoo http://bit.ly/G6el8    
    
    
    Support it further by going to http://www.searchdoublr.com ;) RT @guyhepworth: Y! BOSS bigger than Ask.com http://bit.ly/sL70p    
    
    
    love brainstorming sessions - coming up with product ideas - bliss    
    
    
    @trealicious en dat in de morgen - tututut    
    
    
    dont mess with belgians RT@TechCrunch:Open Source Developer Intends To Block Belgian Government From Using His Technology http://tcrn.ch/2Gs    
    
    
    @trealicious wow ik wist niet dat jullie op 't zelfde bedrijf werken. wat een avontuur he. dat is idd een sante waard    
    
    
    Mr Page said the less data companies like Google were able to hold the "more likely we all are to die". - http://tinyurl.com/oh65d7    
    
    
    Marky Mark buying up the industry ;) RT @SDL_PLC: Mark Lancaster: SDL acquisition of Language Weaver http://bit.ly/bEbxGF    
    
    
    .@farhanlalji good to see you pushed ahead with your start up @adavengers! Best of luck    
    
    
    looks like it is zero inbox day - better get cracking    
    
    
    getting all analytics in order for next week's trip to die Schweiz    
    
    
    @buddhify any chance of a windows phone version soon?    
    
    
    RT@stephanebiz: @gregoire "The Top 10 Mistakes Inventors Make" Do everything yourself, Focus on patents etc. http://tr.im/m4In #innovation    
    
    
    Friends visiting are vegetarians - will try to impress them with recipes from Food for Thought - Tuscan Feast WIN    
    
    
    Wow mobile does change the world RT @guardiantech Talking about a revolution http://bit.ly/OoRIH    
    
    
    @buddhify excellent - thanks for getting back to me!    
    
    
    Just added myself to the http://wefollow.com twitter directory under:  #yahoo #web #computational    
    
    
    @Yuforia your website is not accessible - enjoyed my frozen yoghurt this afternoon though ;)    
    
    
    off to switzerland tomorrow    
    
    
    at the hostellerie - staying in room Manet - quite like the decor    
    
    
    streaming game from hotel wireless - pub was too smokey (not used to it anymore)    
    
    
    #tweekly looking forward to doing weekly review together with other #gtd'ers over twitter    
    
    
    watching carol bartz highlights on D7.allthingsd.com    
    
    
    after all these years I still end up debating product after a couple of beers with colleagues - why - day was over    
    
    
    I often wished for this feature when house hunting digitally RT @babasave: Microsoft Street Slide: http://bit.ly/aTyq20    
    
    
    reading lots of positive comments on Bing - maybe love affair has fizzled enough for users to consider alternatives to Google    
    
    
    all cheaters please report to Yahoo! though - bing is version 1.0 and all that ;)    
    
    
    Really like Y! Connected TV product - impressed with the progress they made since last year- would like a TV now :)    
    
    
    savvy move - lowering barrier for local businesses to advertise http://tcrn.ch/2y7    
    
    
    this weather almost makes me feel like being back in cali. thankful though not none are wearing flip flops to work    
    
    
    not as cool as the howling wolfs t-shirt but still http://site.despair.com/socialmediatee/    
    
    
    new blog post : a different kind of productive  http://bit.ly/dWxa9T    
    
    
    just can't wait to find out how lakers - magic match up    
    
    
    crime scene in front of the office this morning -- heard it was just a fight but lot of blood if only that    
    
    
    weekly review time #gtd    
    
    
    Thanks for all the b-day wishes :)    
    
    
    @michaelserisier hey glad it was helpful. hope things are good :)    
    
    
    @ncox thanks dude - rock the SES as a b-day present ;)    
    
    
    @ncox you celeb you :) http://is.gd/UgoX    
    
    
    my main motivation strategy: "think faster" RT @babasave: Hug a developer today! - http://bit.ly/dBAjd5    
    
    
    Google translator toolkit: http://bit.ly/3GhDC -as an ex-translation tech guy just so excited about what G is and can be doing in this space    
    
    
    tube strike so both mrs and myself wfh - strange - maybe we should do a startup:)    
    
    
    @jeanieBuss 4 - 1 is still good :-)    
    
    
    Man didn't notice. That sucks RT@trealicious: Unfortunately G Translator Toolkit only allows to translate from English into other languages    
    
    
    @danparsonson Thanks Sheldon for an absolutely rocking birthday card! I will drive you to the comic book store as a thank you ;)    
    
    
    AOL enters hyperlocal space http://bit.ly/4TXsL - Local white space primed for innovation    
    
    
    @MissKajlich my condolences... thoughts from London    
    
    
    I am going to play - making a public resolution is my #new365 RT @yeltzland: Something New Every Day: The Rules #new365 http://post.ly/1Pv6H    
    
    
    @trealicious een heel heel gelukkige verjaardag gewenst!!! all remmen los! (in mijn gedachten ben je nog geen dag ouder :) als dat helpt)    
    
    
    Scary... RT @LucyAF: http://bit.ly/g8SAt    
    
    
    @jonnybones I hope Vera wins too. I think the way you beat him hides the fact what a great fighter he is.    
    
    
    v v impressed - I want the mp3 :-) RT @farhanlalji: @davemcdowell can really play  http://is.gd/ZLmm    
    
    
    @gtdguy have you ever taken a look at 750words.com? Seems to tie into the same idea of closing open loops and getting things out off yr mind    
    
    
    Google knows how to deal w large volumes of data so this is gonna be interesting RT @CSA_Research: http://www.tinyfav.com/a492eaa2    
    
    
    just got some tickets for the Chicago Bulls Vs Utah Jazz in the O2 in October - WIN    
    
    
    funny RT @LDN: exploring the hypothesis that newspapers believe that only attractive girls in low cut tops do exams http://bit.ly/cp76r9    
    
    
    @danhardymma game on! Awesome news! Will get me some tickets now :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    aah so great to wake up and find out lakers won the championship    
    
    
    new blog post: You have your clothes on today! http://nickintven.wordpress.com/2012/06/27/you-have-your-clothes-on-today/ …    
    
    
    @danparsonson Glad you like it! Hope you had a great day! (Tweeting this fully dressed)    
    
    
    v funny - steve would be "difficult to work with" RT @babasave: Steve Jobs @ Dragons' Den http://bit.ly/hG7V7O    
    
    
    installed Final Draft (3/365) #new365    
    
    
    Sticking Points http://bit.ly/cxrBYK    
    
    
    up early at 5:00 for listening in to a product demo at 6:00 - nothing like an early start on firdays ;)    
    
    
    cooked dinner in the morning - lasagna :) (4/365) #new365    
    
    
    facilitated a retrospective / post mortem for another feature team (5/365) #new365    
    
    
    love midday naps with a soft breeze coming through the window    
    
    
    feeling quite pleased with how my veggie pastichio turned out    
    
    
    counting off to 3 days off    
    
    
    need to pack, hate to pack    
    
    
    This made my morning - couldn't help laughing along RT @babasave: pretty baked Paul Rudd & Jason Segel interview http://bit.ly/fb2DMp    
    
    
    you are reading it everywhere and maybe it is a self-fulfilling prophecy but quora is really taking off - 10 new followers just today    
    
    
    Went for lunch to Chowki  - yummy http://chowki.com/ (6/365) #new365    
    
    
    weird but good being home - belgie ik heb je gemist    
    
    
    @trealicious dankuwel :-) morgen vertrek ik alweer. een blitsbezoekje!    
    
    
    didn't have a soft drink for over a week and I was a serious diet coke addict (7/365) #new365    
    
    
    @cfidurauk  damn you caught me... I am Belgian after all    
    
    
    @tarecfighter @TeamQuestMMA @GregBradySD @ClinchGear @danhendo Belgium is cheering you on! Go for the Gold :)    
    
    
    Read the same book on my kindle, desktop and mobile - love the  kindle (8/365) #new365    
    
    
    @cathyma sorry to hear that! all the best for the future!    
    
    
    @nbidon Agree -- was in b2b enterprise software space before YHOO and it is completely separate worlds    
    
    
    canada day @ trafalgar sq - pity I already had bought my lunch as I wouldn't have minded trying a bison burger    
    
    
    moved from excel to product studio for scrum work item tracking (9/365) #new365    
    
    
    "Brand is a lagging indicator of a company's culture" -Tony Hsieh @zappos (via @jowyang)    
    
    
    @ncox didn't know you had a blog... great stuff    
    
    
    @gatoradeuk Miami Heat #winfromwithin    
    
    
    @trealicious that's why they call you trealicious - treacool now :)    
    
    
    been nice to Vijay all day long (10/365) #new365    
    
    
    @StefanStruve We kijken er ook naar uit! #kickingass    
    
    
    @darioqa lol - thanks Dario! It wasn't easy    
    
    
    @thisismattball Congrats with the promotion Matt!    
    
    
    @rickygervais looks quite dramatic! cannot wait to see it    
    
    
    great run along the thames - enjoying that nice after-run relaxation feeling    
    
    
    Go Daniel RT @sdltrados: Internationale Suchmaschinenoptimierung - Fachartikel von Daniel Brockmann http://bit.ly/e4VTGL    
    
    
    enjoyed the final but believe roddick deserved better    
    
    
    greek lamb burger at gbk / first free coffee at nero - I usually forget / lose my loyalty card (10/365) #new365    
    
    
    bad day at the office and I had a day off (10/365) #new365    
    
    
    New blog post: the joy of craftsmanship http://bit.ly/b8R7HA    
    
    
    new post: the sorrow of l&H... and belgium http://bit.ly/9JwUgO    
    
    
    That's the company of my old boss - congrats Jochen RT @TechCrunch: No Second Life, Twinity Wins $6m For Real Worlds http://tcrn.ch/5IQ    
    
    
    Support Lance's return to Tour and #LIVESTRONG global cancer fight. Add wristband to your Twitter with 1-click - http://twcauses.com/ls/    
    
    
    #PositiveVibesThursday    
    
    
    Hear hear RT @aseidman:Congrats to the Y! Search Pad team. Some seriously smart note taking capabilities elegantly integrated into Y! Search    
    
    
    new post: cranking widgets http://bit.ly/aSEDDM    
    
    
    longest chat with the most amount of people *eva* (11/365) #new365    
    
    
    new post: myth of meritocracy http://bit.ly/cBPicX    
    
    
    facebook really acting flaky for me at the moment    
    
    
    aah finally on the new twitter - looks nice    
    
    
    wow wonder if productivity will go up all over the US... http://techcrunch.com/2010/09/23/facebook-down/    
    
    
        
    
    
    New post: Mind Mapping to the Rescue http://bit.ly/aDrwOR    
    
    
    Thanks for the retweet RT @Mindjet: RT @intven: New post: Mind Mapping to the Rescue http://bit.ly/aDrwOR    
    
    
    united breaks guitars - shame shame http://bit.ly/rI2ef    
    
    
    The working at MS>5 is a bit of a cheap shot ;)RT @JochenHummel: Who shouldn't do a startup http://slidesha.re/cwLXwz    
    
    
    New Post: Let your team play http://bit.ly/du7Cry    
    
    
    @StuPC  good luck Stuart!!!    
    
    
    reading WSJ's end of management http://bit.ly/a3bEKw    
    
    
    new post: brainstorming trick: write your announcement email at project definition http://bit.ly/9docOo    
    
    
    Each day you're given 86,400 seconds from the time bank. Spend them well. (via @dolectures)    
    
    
    @wetzelmichael what you doing in Seattle? Hope all's well!    
    
    
    @wetzelmichael  nice - well enjoy!    
    
    
    New Post: Value of Authenticity in Presentations http://bit.ly/cZoPkt    
    
    
    good thought for the day RT @ThisIsSethsBlog: Seth's Blog: Next! http://bit.ly/c0V7tl    
    
    
    News post: flavour of the month: company culture http://bit.ly/b2wnpS    
    
    
    So excited - got quoted in the NYT - Don’t Ask? Internet Still Tells http://nyti.ms/T5Z9Iu     
    
    
    @qhardy Thanks for a great article Quentin! Loved it :)    
    
    
    @JochenHummel Thanks Jochen! :D    
    
    
    @s_levaillant thanks! :D    
    
    
    @SEOFACTORYGIRL Thanks Stephanie!!!    
    
    
    @saqibs thanks Saqib! :D    
    
    
    @danparsonson Thanks Dan! :D    
    
    
    @albertobeta @qhardy @mrichtel Very cool!    
    
    
    Seconded :) RT @sdltrados: Wissenstransfer im Unternehmen fördern mit Termbanken – Artikel von Michael Wetzel http://bit.ly/cMpez2 #SDL    
    
    
    New Blog Post: Pomodoro Technique - Timer Magic http://bit.ly/dlWTja    
    
    
    @StuPC Congratulations!    
    
    
    @BillGates  welcome to london! why not drop by the bing offices in soho as well :)    
    
    
    New Post: Incisive Action or Non-Action http://bit.ly/braSyK    
    
    
    .RT @babasave: Take the time and read this! http://bit.ly/aOOO5a    
    
    
    Actually quite liking the new Y! homepage - I have got my Empire, my BBC Sport, TFL, etc - wondering if we will see a drop in FB queries ;)    
    
    
    @danhardymma welcome back outlaw    
    
    
    pre-empted my initial reaction - damn you eric! @ericschmidt Day-to-day adult supervision no longer needed! http://goo.gl/zC89p    
    
    
    "Curse of knowledge" when testing your own product early; UX design and lean startups: http://bforge.me/9QJ8v8 (via @cornett)    
    
    
    Greek lesson of the day... got my trip booked to crete so about 34 days left - wanna do more than smile and say efxaristo this time    
    
    
    Blog post: Getting out of my comfort zone http://nickintven.wordpress.com/2012/12/31/getting-out-of-my-comfort-zone/ …    
    
    
    Happy New Year!!! Have a great one!!!    
    
    
    @codepo8 Congratulations with the new job @mozilla! hope you will enjoy it    
    
    
    @rajatpandit same issue in yhoo mail for me    
    
    
    @RealLamarOdom now that is some great news after a tough week :-)    
    
    
    Really like the new layout of Y! Mail - much lighter feel to it - wish notepad and searchpad shared notes though    
    
    
    My team works on the Bing Autosuggest integration into Facebook. What are the benefits? http://codingplayground.blogspot.co.uk/2013/01/facebook-graph-search-with-bing-web.html …    
    
    
    and the importance of spell correction in search... http://codingplayground.blogspot.co.uk/2013/01/spelling-spelling-spelling-facebook.html …    
    
    
    and finally shortcoming of synthetic queries vs real world http://codingplayground.blogspot.co.uk/2013/01/facebook-graph-search-and-synthetic.html …    
    
    
    And another good one by Antonio Gulli http://codingplayground.blogspot.it/2013/02/facebook-graph-and-need-of-query.html …    
    
    
    Gotta love how easy user testing has become with sites like http://www.usertesting.com/     
    
    
    Happy New Year!    
    
    
    Inbox zero. Aah the joy :D Just for tonight I will try to avoid to look at my task list #gtd    
    
    
    What's the best place in the world to live?    
    
    
    @intven @usertesting thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    Always amazed how a mindmap helps me get through mental blocks #GetItOutOfYourHead #DistributedCognition :D    
    
    
    I didn't even realize a pope can resign    
    
    
    @HaimIQTELL @IQTELL Yep, I would love to try    
    
    
    Loving the podcasts of @LondonRealTV - their @tferriss interview was better than @joerogan 's IMHO    
    
    
    @msmyllie Congratulations!!!!    
    
    
    New blog post: are you busy because you are lazy? http://nickintven.wordpress.com/2013/02/18/are-you-busy-because-you-are-lazy/ …    
    
    
    Free WiFi on the train - first time that I am pleasantly surprised by something FGW does #BegrudginglyThumbsUp    
    
    
    @geoffthompson1 loved your podcast on london real! quite inspiring    
    
    
    Thinking about going on the 4HB diet. Anybody up for a competition for maximum muscle / weight change?    
    
    
    A nice red wine makes me a happy boy    
    
    
    @Clijsterskim Proficiat!!!    
    
    
    time off means reading time - 1st up the 4 hour chef :)    
    
    
    @qhardy 2 minute rounds? :D    
    
    
    @qhardy lol    
    
    
    lol RT @jennyandteets: As a friend I'll always have your back, unless I'm with a group of people whose approval I need and they hate you.    
    
    
    @DanielPink really enjoyed you as a guest on the london real podcast - do you have a reference to the hollywood pitch study?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jgjong support articles in the weekend! now that's dedication :)    
    
    
    Happy Pi Day    
    
    
    Check out Bing's new people search features (US only) - tweet me what you think http://techcrunch.com/2013/03/21/bing-just-got-a-lot-smarter-now-knows-more-about-people-and-places/ …    
    
    
    Some of the biggest questions people have via the magic of Bing! (via @lripsher) @qhardy #harlemshake #fiscalcliff pic.twitter.com/wWHMp5g4SM    
    
    
    Sneak peek into the project I work on at Bing http://www.bing.com/blogs/site_blogs/b/search/archive/2013/03/25/a-deeper-look-at-autosuggest.aspx …    
    
    
    @sonnench haha awesome! Good luck mate!    
    
    
    @XbrainUk ordered some bulletproof coffee earlier today - real curious!    
    
    
    @lripsher Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    So happy Game of Thrones is back!!! :D #Nerd #LovinIt    
    
    
    @viber I have installed windows 8 app but it keeps on saying syncing contacts for the whole day once I connected it to FB. Can you help?    
    
    
    Kim Clijsters is op twitter - cool - US Open terug in Belgische handen :) @clijsterskim    
    
    
    "Talent hits a target no one else can hit; Genius hits a target no one else can see" -Arthur Schopenhauer (via exectweets)    
    
    
    I've #justsponsored Amy Nicholson on @JustGiving. Support them and UK Youth @  http://www.justgiving.com/walkthemonopolyboard?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=socspon&utm_content=walkthemonopolyboard&utm_campaign=post-sponsor-tweet …    
    
    
    Feeling so damn energetic on the slow carb diet. Gotta give it up for @tferriss    
    
    
    Really interested in the area of Quantified Self - anybody else? Either personally or professionally?    
    
    
    :( RT @GarethADaviesDT: Last pic here of injured man in Boston is horrific http://m.theatlantic.com/infocus/2013/04/photos-of-the-boston-marathon-bombing/100495/ … …    
    
    
    @tferriss getting an internal server error Tim    
    
    
    iPhone peeps check it out! RT @paulyiu: Ness 2.0 Is Highly Recommended For Getting Restaurant Recommendations --  http://appadvice.com/?p=403051     
    
    
    Try Yahoo Search guys :-)  much less crowded looking now that GOOG moved their ads to the left    
    
    
    @danawhite best wishes from London #BostonStrong    
    
    
    Ask me a question http://ask.fm/nickintven     
    
    
    @4hbapp @tferriss we need a windows phone 8 version :)    
    
    
    @danawhite love the vlogs :)    
    
    
    @tferriss @paul_langford haha I just bought a new belt at Marks & Spencers as my pants wouldn't stay up :D    
    
    
    @4hbapp I haven't set up a kickstarter project before but I will check it out.    
    
    
    @markdrasutis get well soon    
    
    
    2 weeks to go before heading to crete... looking forward to the sea, food, sun and maybe a raki    
    
    
    sad day for guitar lovers http://bit.ly/t5XTT    
    
    
    @tferriss read all your books but really only applied 4HB and just hit my 10y low weight. Gonna try it all now :) #GonnaBeNewRichBitch    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sunny day in the UK but stuck inside    
    
    
    @danawhite stoked    
    
    
    Very nicely done - using the web as your bilingual dictionary (via Michael Wetzel) : http://www.linguee.com/    
    
    
    Tech giants unite against Google http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/8200624.stm    
    
    
    Love him RT @stephanpastis: My tribute to Anthony Bourdain.  @Bourdain http://twitpic.com/cy3hdb     
    
    
    Just awful. My thoughts are with all my greek friends http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/world/europe/8217433.stm    
    
    
    @danparsonson I know this is awefully late but a very happy birthday to you Sheldon!!!!  come and see us again soon!    
    
    
    check out the new Yahoo search results page http://bit.ly/OMRnb    
    
    
    @danparsonson lol    
    
    
    Amen! RT @tferriss: "A man can never have too much red wine, too many books, or too much ammunition." - Rudyard Kipling    
    
    
    Phil Jackson doing ads - for some serious Zen dollars I am sure http://bit.ly/2R8cCA    
    
    
        
    
    
    @salimmitha olympiacos is from greece - oh i wamt tickets for that one :)    
    
    
    @JonnyBones great idea!    
    
    
    Hack Day today and tomorrow at work! Psyched!    
    
    
    @tferriss any data on replacing 4hb breakfast with bulletproof coffee / butter / oil? An option or better to avoid?    
    
    
    Super excited to attend the TEDxMuenchen event on September 20th! Hope to see some of you there!    
    
    
    really like David Allen's idea of "moves of work" - will test out my green-belt level on my post-holiday email backlog #gtd    
    
    
    lots of new idea & projects I want to get cracking on #fb    
    
    
    well actually RT@eleentso hilarious "As a seasoned engineer, you need to learn control your impulses" http://bit.ly/grGDhC via @codinghorror    
    
    
    Looks like my favourite radio station is gone after upgrading to ITunes 9    
    
    
    holding my fingers crossed for Kimmie tonight #usopen    
    
    
    first run after holidays - auch - but at least I got started again    
    
    
    why didn't we think of pulling something like that http://bit.ly/M0viU    
    
    
    @trealicious LOL :-)    
    
    
    @unepetitegamine @babasave @bing @chelseajfarmer would love to have joined you!    
    
    
    sports sunday - first greece - russia and now some nfl    
    
    
    @bisping Halloween n The Count shirt :) pic.twitter.com/xwmGLAzotx    
    
    
    amazing shot from Federer http://bit.ly/A6qh4    
    
    
    how cute is that http://bit.ly/1avT0p
 congrats @clijsterskim    
    
    
        
    
    
    fabulous dinner @ the roofgarden's Babylon for our wedding anniversary    
    
    
    anybody have a theatre recommendation (london area)?    
    
    
    London office looking for a Dir of Engr http://bit.ly/UGADA    
    
    
    Unbelievable start for Standard    
    
    
    listening to the dead on my way to work - good start to the day    
    
    
    “Perfection is achieved, not when there is nothing more to add, but when there is nothing left to take away.” - Antoine de Saint-Exupe    
    
    
    Check out Y!'s new search results pages - http://uk.search.yahoo.com/    
    
    
    "@jennyandteets: It's such a bummer when you add someone on Facebook only to discover they have an ugly kid." lol    
    
    
    @gtdguy sounds wonderful - haven't been there myself though - welcome to London    
    
    
    Major highlight in my day is a new PPT template - this is my life    
    
    
    Haven't been to a professional stand up gig ever - Janeane Garofalo you better not disappoint tomorrow :)    
    
    
    doing lots of greek vocab drills and feeling like I am back at school    
    
    
    EU has bigger share than US RT @Lionbridge: Global Search Market Draws More than 100 Billion Searches per Month. http://bit.ly/t5YjJ    
    
    
    Looks like fun - anybody writing the first GTD app? http://developer.yahoo.com/yap/metro/ #gtd    
    
    
    very jealous of our German colleagues living it up at the Oktoberfest - I want to scream "jetzt geht's los" too ;)    
    
    
    @mlaaker Thanks for sharing. Really pleasantly suprised :-) That is a My Favourite for sure    
    
    
    Online ad spend overtaking TV in UK http://ow.ly/sjgd    
    
    
    Aaaah, cash4gold commercials coming to the UK :( http://bit.ly/eYyNJ    
    
    
    .RT @stefanweitz: So incredibly proud of the team today-launching the "Goodness Engine". Simply 1 of the bes… (cont) http://deck.ly/~MlUb8    
    
    
    saw my first live Y! ad in the Metro this morning    
    
    
    Cool - Arrested Development movie in the works    
    
    
    going to the NBA Europe game tonight - can't wait    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats! RT @babasave: RT @danpeters: RT @amandajahn:More than 1 billion Q&A posted on Yahoo! Answers http://tumblr.com/xuv3eiapw    
    
    
    bulls leading at half time (and they have stella - sweet)    
    
    
    Boo #worldserver yay #teamworks ;)    
    
    
    wow, eye opening RT @farhanlalji: If you're an NBA fan read these two posts - http://yhoo.it/igCk7A and http://bit.ly/i7RJe4    
    
    
    got an invitation for google wave - tried to stay away from early reviews so I can make up my own mind    
    
    
    @thisismattball actually looks very tasty :)    
    
    
    new blog post: are you writing a fear or greed presentation http://bit.ly/ez1JQn    
    
    
    finally subsegmentmatching in trados :) RT @xenotext: blog post: AutoSuggest - translating in a higher gear
http://bit.ly/4zPmeS    
    
    
    I am curious RT @twinity: get ready for #virtual #London http://ow.ly/uzbl    
    
    
    new blog post: Experiences with Scrum – Part 1: Sprint Demo http://bit.ly/dFpiLo    
    
    
    yesterday had the most PVs so far on my blog and interestingly enough LinkedIn provided almost the majority of referrals    
    
    
    US job losses on a map - press play button to see changes over time: http://bit.ly/fSjmE    
    
    
    really feeling like an in n out burger - why don't the franchises we want come to the UK    
    
    
    The fun theory - http://bit.ly/fY3qG (via @gtdguy)    
    
    
    Crazy RT @cornett: #Defragcon Typical business user is switching application contexts 37 times an hour. Ouch!    
    
    
    kudos to everton fc http://bit.ly/4wqqyi    
    
    
    new post: Beginner's Mind http://bit.ly/gVMyiU    
    
    
    new blog post: shared experiences http://bit.ly/hzoIbF    
    
    
    @danhardymma here's how bruce lee set (hand written) goals: http://goo.gl/JZUmH    
    
    
        
    
    
    hear hear RT @nbidon: congrats to @eileentso @StefanGlaenzer about @passioncapital new seed fund - great new… (cont) http://deck.ly/~jET3p    
    
    
    Bing hiring 3 engineers in Paris - DM me if interested and I will forward specs    
    
    
    hmm RT @NCox: I GIVE UP - Reuters uses txt speak in headlines http://reut.rs/hC2SwL    
    
    
    Microsoft Careers Portal - Interactive Entertainment Business http://lnkd.in/iiFJi4    
    
    
    Old French teacher was a big Camus fan & this one resonates "Real generosity toward the future consists in giving all to what is present."    
    
    
    .RT @babasave: RT @pascalfantou: Breaking News: To outperform social search results, Bing launched the +2 butt… (cont) http://deck.ly/~UX7TF    
    
    
    nice list RT @alleyinsider: Microsoft Mints CEOs: 15 Successful Startups From Ex-Microsofties $MSFT by @MattRosoff http://read.bi/hhWoTN    
    
    
    new blog post: standards http://bit.ly/hnFlhb    
    
    
    presentation secrets of Jobs http://ow.ly/Bay4    
    
    
    quite fun - PM interview questions at Google http://tinyurl.com/yelw33a    
    
    
    @BrockmannDaniel  you are not in any of them!  Disappointed. Camera shy? ;-) Hope all's well    
    
    
    @BrockmannDaniel ah cool - I was wondering where they got the tunes from!    
    
    
    .RT @cfidurauk For anyone who likes codes, see if you can help solve a murder! http://bit.ly/heQ5Ek #cnn    
    
    
    Sitting all by my lonesome in y cafeteria and founder of xoopit asks to join table followed by a long chat on personalization - only in SV    
    
    
    @arielhelwani great interviews as per usual    
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal Hang in there man! Low points are just there to contrast with your great times - victories :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    curious to see if Belgian Van Rompuy will become the 1st EU prez or if Brown will be able to push Blair    
    
    
    I have to admit - pretty cool @JochenHummel RT @Xconomy Using Google Building Maker to Change the Face of Boston http://xconomy.com/?p=51578    
    
    
    Shortcut on Y! Search for Children in Need http://uk.search.yahoo.com/search?rd=r1&p=children+in+need&toggle=1&cop=mss&ei=UTF-8&fr=yfp-t-702    
    
    
    @salimmitha sweet seats - enjoy the game!    
    
    
    gonna try to the pomodoro technique next week http://www.pomodorotechnique.com/ - any advice?    
    
    
    @cschleiden  does it work for you? I have been trying it on and off    
    
    
    @ot_y @cschleiden I meant I haven't been able to stick to it and keep on falling off the wagon :)    
    
    
    Local Social Summit videos now up on YouTube http://www.localsocialsummit.com/lss/local-social-summit-09-videos-up-on-youtube/    
    
    
    .RT @alaindebotton: People only get really interesting when they start to rattle the bars of their cages. #fb    
    
    
    @cschleiden wow that's impressive - got to stick to it then    
    
    
    @JochenHummel yeah always loved that idea of language learning in a virtual world    
    
    
    @ot_y @cschleiden that's pretty amazing. he talks about it in the book but seems to suggest it takes quite a toll on your body    
    
    
    interesting article: Local & Augmented Reality http://www.washingtonpost.com/wp-dyn/content/article/2009/11/20/AR2009112001318.html    
    
    
    Bye bye Borders http://www.guardian.co.uk/business/2009/nov/26/borders-closure-stores-amazon    
    
    
    250 miles on Nike+ :)    
    
    
    December giveaway - 25 prizes in 25 days @ Wahanda (& bonus is you support a UK startup) http://www.wahanda.com/advent/    
    
    
    @livlaliv slainte    
    
    
    please don't click if you are easily offended but looks like @CKLouis new show will be good fun http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5jPZpptlABM    
    
    
    really enjoying the pomodoro technique which I am using in combination with my gtd system - 25 mins sessions just work - thanks @cirillof    
    
    
    @JochenHummel is that the guy who invested into Metaversum?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @livlaliv I feel the same. My mother says the same too. I think it is the human condition ;)    
    
    
    It is not really "selling" if we both win - LOL -   http://www.dilbert.com/strips/comic/2009-12-01/    
    
    
    @nbidon well happy birthday! I am in the Swiss office next week. Look forward to seeing you then.    
    
    
    fingers crossed for london RT @arielhelwani: UFC Returning to England in October (but the question is which city?) -- http://ow.ly/4Ip1X    
    
    
    WOW RT @LDN Google are to shake up the UK property market by allowing anyone to add a sale/rental listing on Maps http://bit.ly/6s2WUN    
    
    
    On my way to rolle - counting on some cheese fondue    
    
    
    I won a flat in virtual london (which I cannot afford in real life :() - anyway you can now visit soho virtually http://bit.ly/8yiqV2    
    
    
    @nbidon I saw these in JPN a couple of year ago and love the concept    
    
    
    Concepts for the future of social networking: http://bit.ly/5UovSk (via Amanda)    
    
    
    love it that you can see the lake from the conference room - fresh croissants also don't hurt    
    
    
    enjoying @farhanlalji 's updates from #leweb - wish I could be there    
    
    
    cool stuff & cool pic  @StuPC: Is it any wonder... http://wp.me/pkaYu-V8    
    
    
    Big bottle of Leffe for tonite - belgian beer rules all    
    
    
    Simplicity vs. clarity - http://tr.im/Hwrd (via @gtzi)    
    
    
    @farhanlalji didn't realise you were working on a project; very cool and much luck    
    
    
    Leading city bankers destroy £7 of social value for every pound in value the generate - http://tinyurl.com/ye6gvxe (via @JochenHummel)    
    
    
    looking forward to go to inamo for lunch tomorrow with colleagues http://www.inamo-restaurant.com/ - looks pricey but hope it's worth it    
    
    
    2 weeks of blissful holidays await - rejoice :-)    
    
    
    spotted @MasterChefUK 's finalists at Wahaca    
    
    
    not a chance  - the pork pibil was too delish RT @wahaca: @intven We hope they're not putting you off your lunch!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal Awesome! Nick In 't Ven, 11 Bridge Court, Bridge Ave, Maidenhead, Berkshire SL6 1RW, UK (cannot DM as you need to follow me)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @LoveMyBrownBoys @IamTheImmortal I will be wearing it on the 26th of June :)    
    
    
    @cschleiden congrats!    
    
    
    share your screen with skype - very handy http://michaelnozbe.com/productivity-tip-online-screen-sharing-and-co    
    
    
    @ghadjigeorgiou that's pretty sweet - you should definitely post a pic    
    
    
    @ghadjigeorgiou now that is beautiful...    
    
    
    Up early to see the lakers lose against the clips    
    
    
    Need to set some goals for the year...    
    
    
    gonna read @garyvee 's #crushit this weekend - tired of seeing @farhanlalji hyping the book and not knowing what it is about ;)    
    
    
    @gtdguy you made it onto businessinsider's list of 15 books every entrepreneur should read http://tinyurl.com/yapqbb2    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats @salimmitha with the coverage in techcrunch http://bit.ly/69e6lf    
    
    
    @farhanlalji well best of luck with your project! you coming back to the UK?    
    
    
    Belgo's + theatre tonight - one some free tickets via lastminute.com :-)    
    
    
    got myself Wahanda's mobdeal http://bit.ly/7vaRoV - lots of sore muscles that need relief :)    
    
    
    great streaming of man city vs man u on bbc sports - thank you beeb    
    
    
    crazy cube illusion http://j.mp/7XQCSK (via @ebertchicago)    
    
    
    translation fail http://failblog.org/2008/07/22/translation-fail/    
    
    
    Congrats! Impressive RT @saqibs Having a nice relaxing sunday after an awesome @CloudHack yesterday - chuffed to make the final 6.    
    
    
        
    
    
    First InBev is laying off, now Opel is closing down in Antwerp (2600 jobs) - fail fail fail    
    
    
    Watched Precious yesterday and still feel like I was punched in the stomach    
    
    
    @danparsonson A very very happy birthday Dan!!!! Have a fabulous day :)    
    
    
    @arielhelwani it definitely adds some intrigue to the event which is good; but I hate to see marquardt's career ruined (even if not a fan)    
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal I cannot wait to see you win tonight #theimmortalarmy    
    
    
        
    
    
    new blog post: hackdays http://bit.ly/m5xe6d    
    
    
    @danhardymma the big lebowski - the dude rules all    
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal Congrats Matt!    
    
    
    @IamTheImmortal did you get fined in the end? http://bit.ly/lMZzlY or still waiting?    
    
    
    Bing News UK gets refreshed look http://www.techradar.com/news/internet/bing-news-uk-gets-refreshed-look-974581 …    
    
    
    @poll HERE Nick In 't Ven    
    
    
    @poll unsure    
    
    
        
    
    
    bought myself a sensible salad in the morning but gave into a burrito for lunch - weak flesh    
    
    
    mindmapping a project while listening to Crazy Heart soundtrack #bliss    
    
    
        
    
    
    @tarecfighter make belgium proud! (from a fellow belgian ex-pat living in london)    
    
    
    @yeltzland hey - I can see the site: unofficial forum    
    
    
    @tarecfighter  you were phenomenal! congrats! coming out party :)    
    
    
    new blog post: a tale of poor customer experience http://bit.ly/nZAu5l  #davidlloyd #davidlloydgym    
    
    
    Give money to Sports Relief every time you use Bing - http://GiveWithBing.com    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to Yahoo - 15 years...    
    
    
    @kjbroom had to look that one up - you did always teach me new sayings... drinking the kool aid    
    
    
    @JeanieBuss No please don't! Due to time difference, in EU, we watch it on NBA League Pass the next day so try to avoid 2 see the score    
    
    
    