On a fun note, I'm learning how inferior Android Vine is... Good Lord, idk how you put up with it!!!    
    
    
    @aNecessary_Evil @NormFlores Wish I could be there this year!!    
    
    
    @NintendoTweet #TIL, thanks! :)    
    
    
    @TronKnotts I love Creature Comforts!!!    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd WHO?!?!?!?!    
    
    
    Here's the http://www.Dvelop.TV  review for @undeadlabs "State of Decay!" | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47spRhJVlFo …    
    
    
    @Sycoraxic98 Spam?    
    
    
    @davidsgallant Why does this keep happening? Happened with Borderlands 2 as well. :-/    
    
    
    @KittyMeeowMeeow Me! Me! 3265-5677-2904    
    
    
    @KittyMeeowMeeow Woohoo! Wil ladd you here in a bit    
    
    
    Greek Coffee? Yes please. W/ @thetanktheory @ Kostas Cafe http://instagram.com/p/bAVxz4yeb7/     
    
    
    @Hyperfludd so jealous :(    
    
    
    Someone get this woman some sleep!! RT @Pelpina This is how tired I am: I just emailed myself.    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Pre-Welcome to Texas :)    
    
    
    Been putting lots of cool reviews up on the http://www.Dvelop.TV  YouTube channel! Appreciate the views and subs! :) http://youtube.com/dveloptv     
    
    
    @MrBozon I see what you did there...    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham What on Earth do symbols above the door mean?! Have I collected everything or not?… http://instagram.com/p/bCPPjfyeRR/     
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Referring to the first door btw.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Okay, so first door has everything collected then? Appreciate the response! Some things Gold vs Some Things Blue = confusing    
    
    
    @m_borgmeijer @pelpina I'm glad you like them, Morgan! Always fun to meet people with similar interests :D    
    
    
    Seriously, have any of you been outside? Because this is how I feel right now...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8hE727GTFHY …    
    
    
    @laneshill Holy hell - LITERALLY. Couldn't take it if my AC broke, I'm that spoiled. I'd cry man. I'D CRY!!!    
    
    
    @laneshill Not the kitties!! Glad it's back on.. now excuse me as I jump into an ice bath!! :P    
    
    
    @Sycoraxic98 I don't see many games at all launching in July on any platform, seeing something I'm not?    
    
    
    Finally saw the @ConanOBrien E3 segment. Asked Major Nelson to sell the XBOne & he said "The Kinect can see your heart beat" ...Really?    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Not on my worldwide trends it isnt....    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Annddd there it is!    
    
    
    Incoming Animal Crossing New Leaf rant..... So I have this stupid hippo named Hippeaux in my town.... I wanted him to move.    
    
    
    I did everything in my power - which means ignore him completely. He comes up to me finally and says "I'm leaving, just wanted to tell you."    
    
    
    So I was like "Ok, thanks." and he's all shocked that I'm okay with it. Really, Hippeaux?!    
    
    
    So he says "Nevermind, I think we can be better friends. I'm staying." DUDE! I HATE YOU! LEAVE! What kind of crap is that?! #ACNL    
    
    
    Sing it, Kapp'n!! http://instagram.com/p/bG3fgZSeYV/     
    
    
    In honor of @UndeadLabs releasing an update for "State of Decay" - here's our review | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47spRhJVlFo …    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz Dude I haven't seen you in at least 3-4 years. What gives?!?!?! :P :P (In my defense, I live in Dallas)    
    
    
    @RetroCR So in other words, never because the Wii is a last gen platform. Bring it to Wii U :(!!    
    
    
    @laneshill Looks great, share plz.    
    
    
    @davidsgallant Is that Ryan Stiles?    
    
    
    Hey Winston Edmondson!! Want some apple?!? https://vine.co/v/ham3IzhmIi6     
    
    
    @meRyDoon Heard amazing things about this place: http://vimeo.com/16077855   (DiFara, if you don't feel like watching that amazing mini-doc)    
    
    
    I'm sailinnggg awayyyyy... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fAAHuZ3zhjo …    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Dude now I want pizza so badly... lol thanks!! :P    
    
    
    @TedRubin @JSMeudt VIne vs Instagram is like Facebook/Twitter vs Google+. All their friends are already on instagram, so more will use it.    
    
    
    But seriously you guys, I need to sell my turnips!!! #ACNL    
    
    
    Hilarious Mickey Mouse short. Don't ask questions. Just watch it.  http://video.disney.com/watch/disneychannel-no-service-4df889ed3d82b43c9c01a272 …    
    
    
    @Kolma @Hyperfludd @Drzgamer @The_Baconbitz @KittyMeeowMeeow @kyle1point0 Does anyone have turnip prices > 150?    
    
    
    @The_Baconbitz Bummer!!!!    
    
    
    "I can't get high, I have to sing for Jesus tomorrow."    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz agree so much.    
    
    
    TIL there's a website that lets you order and anonymously send cow, elephant, or gorilla poo to someone. Freakin' internet, man...    
    
    
    I'm watching #MonstersU with 375 others on #GetGlue http://getglue.com/movies/monsters_university/dan_scanlon?s=t&ref=ArakniD …    
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs Hahahaha!!! Yesterday was rough... #NuffSaid    
    
    
    @amandablain Hey.. your tweets are starting to repeat! :P    
    
    
    Happy Canada Day! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=0Fn8PW-X8gI …    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers Great game is great. Seems like the original DK game, but you have to make it through the tribute stages to really exp. it.    
    
    
    @buenothebear Perfect. Just.. perfect...    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb You don't HAVE to use 15 seconds. Can be 3-15. Also, everyone's friends are already on Instagram. Why migrate to Vine?    
    
    
    @CobieSmulders First time seeing the trailer, this movie looks great!    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Fail. "and Jeremy Piven"    
    
    
    Manchu Blooper #1: Bless you, Rik Westerink. https://vine.co/v/haLDFYQMDvY     
    
    
    Putting Instagram's cam-stabilizer to the test. I was jogging next to the car in flip flops. Holy shit. http://instagram.com/p/bSKd5FyeWR/     
    
    
    Sizzleeeeeeee @ Mumtaz Indian Cuisine http://instagram.com/p/bSN8BCSeb8/     
    
    
    @PirateHearts Do it!!!!    
    
    
    HOLY MOLY! Amazing @VineApp update brings some awesome features!!! And it works on iOS 7 again! THANK THE MAKER!    
    
    
    "Don't try to fix it. I just need you to listen."  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-4EDhdAHrOg …    
    
    
    Thai Tea with Bubbles, please... @ Fat Straws Bubble Tea & Juice http://instagram.com/p/bUiJrMSeZy/     
    
    
    This place sounds like a  Diablo Cody movie..... https://vine.co/v/hWAF2P69qJ0     
    
    
    Excuse me sir, you're dressed like a Mario Brother. https://vine.co/v/hWA9vixOgE5     
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagram.com/p/bU8lA2yeUM/     
    
    
    No Ice Cream for Morgan Freeman..... https://vine.co/v/hWbrpKHT951     
    
    
    Portrait of JFK made up of smaller portraits of Jackie Kennedy at 6th Floor Museum @ The Sixth Floor… http://instagram.com/p/bW4piTSedx/     
    
    
    Crazy!! #ThanksPels #TeamManchu MT @Pelpina Amazing Mark & I have been working together for 1 yr! It's been an amazing year! #ThankYouMahco    
    
    
    @JonAvalon Is this spam?    
    
    
    @TaylorLumsden Ah man!  @pelpina is out of town, but I'm always game for Ice Cream! :P    
    
    
    Finally starting this show. Long overdue. #MadMen #GetGlue http://getglue.com/tv_shows/mad_men?s=t&ref=ArakniD …    
    
    
    There's a new review up on http://www.Dvelop.TV  - @TheTankTheory reviews Rush Bros |  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C9IrNGydPRM …    
    
    
    Boom Tsh boom Tsh https://vine.co/v/hWYqXFpOzHx     
    
    
    YELP!!!!! https://vine.co/v/h77KbOBUAJH     
    
    
    Get to da choppa!!! http://instagram.com/p/bfJ80wyeXo/     
    
    
    Let's see what's going on in gaming news today... Oh! More Wii U is dead headlines? #HappyMonday!!    
    
    
    Wow, crazy Summer for Giant Bomb.  RIP Ryan Davis.    
    
    
    @kevinlamel blank tweet is blank    
    
    
    Bun Bo Hue @ Phó Tây Dô http://instagram.com/p/bhAqvayeUI/     
    
    
    Manchu Blooper #2: Poor Mark #AudioSyncProblems w/ Pelpina Trip, Rik Westerink https://vine.co/v/h7ebJbBWPH7     
    
    
    On a Train. #VineLapse #Loop https://vine.co/v/h7HDTqBn0eB     
    
    
    A beautiful moment on the train, made dramatic by a couple of people who just got out of jail… http://instagram.com/p/bkH_OISeQl/     
    
    
    @benroethig I beggeth your pardon?!    
    
    
    @benroethig Oh, the train I was riding was part of the DART system "Dallas Area Rapid Transit Rail"    
    
    
    Kidz Bop covering One Direction songs seems a bit redundant.....    
    
    
    This guy is trying WAY too hard to be justdevin but he's just not cool enough... http://instagram.com/p/bmm6ewSeYH/     
    
    
    @gunpeiyokoifan Haha tweeting for all but I definitely had you in mind, fellow Canada-phile.    
    
    
    My little sisters think this cloud looks like a pig howling at the moon.... @jenn_naay @kimberlyzamor03 http://instagram.com/p/bm-yahyedi/     
    
    
    Such a great movie.... https://vine.co/v/h72dnLAl0tU     
    
    
    I like visiting my parents because I get #ThrowbackThursday photos of this bad ass #DatSweaterVest http://instagram.com/p/booySjSeVP/     
    
    
    Man. of. Steel. #ManofSteelMovie #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1353HSR     
    
    
    @davidsgallant Summer Sale turned into Summer Salesman - "Hey, you look like the kind of guy interested in a good deal!"    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Free game? I thought you have to pay for them?    
    
    
    .n4k3dg4m3r & I shot a hilarious vineapp about wanting free Slurpees from @7eleven & getting foiled by… http://instagram.com/p/bpXRI1yeWe/     
    
    
    And that stupid circle arrow doesn't do anything, btw. This is why @VineApp needs Camera Roll Uploads :(    
    
    
    @GameplayDev 101 in my town. NotBad.jpg    
    
    
    Dem Clouds!! pic.twitter.com/FewKtYahai    
    
    
    Just remember.... https://vine.co/v/hZOaFMYU6zF     
    
    
    @swonderlin Did you see Monsters University? I loved it, Revenge of the Nerds for a new generation :)    
    
    
    Shrine of Steel http://instagram.com/p/bucE1xSecG/     
    
    
    Bat Cave http://instagram.com/p/bucNVsyecW/     
    
    
    Headed out of El Paso again, great but short little visit. To those I saw, thanks for good times and… http://instagram.com/p/buqAE6SeXq/     
    
    
    Holy Payphone Batman!!! https://vine.co/v/hZ6ZhxwwYYL     
    
    
    Crazy hearing about @CoryMonteith of Glee fame - RIP    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Hey did you end up ordering a HORI fighting stick? I have a couple review units they sent that I'm NOT using at all    
    
    
    @DtoidChris haven't heard anything specifically about the SCV stick but HORI makes amazing products.    
    
    
    @benroethig @gkdave @calilewis If anything, the sight of disgusting twinkies will only encourage her more.    
    
    
    Hey, Wal-Mart? I don't think this is a reasonable substitute for the drive-thru.... Or anything for… http://instagram.com/p/bwZqhyyeeY/     
    
    
    @digitalphil_ Yes, they're gross!!    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd I've understood about .1% of your tweets today. Why so vague? What are you talking about?    
    
    
    I can't handle the irony of this ad right now. #SpammedBySpam http://instagram.com/p/bxkGHQyefm/     
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys God speed on your quest!!    
    
    
    Mad Max: Soul of a Man gameplay trailer | https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHs0Drqp10U …    
    
    
    Found this gem while visiting the Parents. To the shelf!! #NESMemories nintendoamerica #Metroid http://instagram.com/p/bzVvy8SeZQ/     
    
    
    @LisaFoiles My condolences    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys So? Did you get Chipotle?!    
    
    
    "50's Rock 'n' Roll Radio" on Pandora is basically the best thing ever...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ty31QY5ZGHo …    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Woo woo!!! Looks delishhhhhhh!!! :)    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys A Happy Stomach means a Happy You? ;)    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock It's the story that keeps it so compelling. One of my all-time fav FPS. That nightclub scene - holy shit.    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Can't set number of frames but you can use Assistive Touch to set touch length    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH I'll try to record a quick video demo of how to do that...    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Ok, uploading now. Hope it helps! Can also use this to do hands-free Vines....    
    
    
    @CoreySoup @PHIL_FISH Indeed! Can also use for handsfree Vines if you "record" a long press gesture. Here you go: http://youtu.be/SzckouaxRyE     
    
    
    @CoreySoup @PHIL_FISH And of course, I'm assuming you're on an iPhone - if you're on Android then I'm amazed you're using Vine :P!    
    
    
    Deus Ex: Human Revolution is 10 dollars on Steam. It's sales like this that make me wonder who would wait for the Wii U version? #sigh    
    
    
    @camsicle Haha! Poor guy, I think he had the wrong number ;)    
    
    
    Pacific Rim in IMAX 3D!! Holy shit my brain!!!!! #SensoryExplosion https://vine.co/v/hm7hJj036Bp     
    
    
    My Spoiler-Free Review of "Pacific Rim" | How are they going to make anymore movies??? Del Toro & Co. used all the CGs!!!!!!    
    
    
    Serotonin levels off the chart right now :)    
    
    
    So @innovationenvy, @normflores and I tried shooting a skit on vineapp but "An Error Occured...." @… http://instagram.com/p/b3v6UbyeaV/     
    
    
    Interrogation Room: Part 1 (See Part 2 on @NormFlores Twitter soon...) w/ @innovationenvy @ Starbucks http://instagram.com/p/b3yQQ-Sed8/     
    
    
    @benroethig Hahaha!!! Man... That was trippy....    
    
    
    Rollin' in the Deep @ Life In Deep Ellum http://instagram.com/p/b4xcFvyeZG/     
    
    
    Uber: Dashboard Confessionals http://instagram.com/p/b5KsC6See_/     
    
    
    Uber: Dashboard Confessionals Part 2 http://instagram.com/p/b5K4GTyefP/     
    
    
    Uber: Dashboard Confessionals Part 3 http://instagram.com/p/b5LDW1yefZ/     
    
    
    Uber: Dashboard Confessionals Finalé http://instagram.com/p/b5MfjWSeQ0/     
    
    
    @camsicle Same to you!! Always a blast :)    
    
    
    Am I excited about Earthbound being released for Wii U today? Why, yes. A million times, yes. ...YESSSSSSSSSSSS    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers In reality, the real question should be "Why do these 2 services from the same company have separate libraries/shops?    
    
    
    @songsinAminor @Emi1yRogers Referring to Virtual Console titles, darn Twitter character limits!    
    
    
    @songsinAminor @Emi1yRogers Referring to VC titles mainly, darn Twitter character limits! Apply to any game that can run on both. Look @ PSN    
    
    
    The long-overdue http://www.Dvelop.TV  review for @WayForward's "Mighty Switch Force 2" is finally up! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5LiRxpfx4h8 …    
    
    
    @skidvis And the most fabulous, apparently?    
    
    
    Can someone explain to me why Dominos Pizza is trying to sell me a cell phone?!?! http://instagram.com/p/b7PUhDyeTZ/     
    
    
    I'm just so happy that this is a thing right now. This game means a lot to me. https://vine.co/v/hmDbuDLnQBw     
    
    
    Fuzzy Pickles!! https://vine.co/v/hmIiLFXzUA1     
    
    
    "One Day More" from Les Mis performed by the Muppets... But it's just one guy doing all the voices. JUST WOW   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LYLixfjsjFE …    
    
    
    TGIF  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=myIG9PEwXZw …    
    
    
    Nekter Juice Bar Grand Opening W/ Winston (Thanks for heads-up, @foodbitch) https://vine.co/v/hmT31dItgI7     
    
    
    @mikedmerrill  Oh man, I love @WeinbergersDeli  !!!    
    
    
    Oh my god, this is hilarious.... pic.twitter.com/WqVCv0vLBQ    
    
    
    Save the Clock Tower!! @ Las Colinas Tower II http://instagram.com/p/b-VVrHyeTI/     
    
    
    Oh my God.
It's happening.

#WorldsFinest http://www.npr.org/templates/story/story.php?storyId=204006172 …    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @TheBitBlock I wish more devs were being creative with asymmetric multiplayer.    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb I don't think the camera in my pocket can see the same stuff a cam on my face would.    
    
    
    Is anyone really surprised? "Google+ Still a Ghost Town" http://bgr.com/2013/07/19/google-plus-social-sharing-analysis/ …    
    
    
    Was excited for the new TMNT game based on the TV series until I saw it's not coming to Wii U - wtf, @Activision???    
    
    
    @gunpeiyokoifan Interesting! We've been long time Twitter buddies - strange for this to come now but do what you must! :)    
    
    
    @handynerds :( RIP Astrid! Good on them for recommending alternatives though!    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0T5W-xJWuPE …    
    
    
    The club can't even handle me right now.... https://vine.co/v/hK1P002dbt5     
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH I just think there are too many exceptions to that rule for it to be an actual rule.    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz "That's a cross.."    
    
    
    Arnold Palmer @ Taco Diner http://instagram.com/p/cGIRD7yeeZ/     
    
    
    This short film is making rounds & I'm told it's amazing but can't get past 3:13. Yes, I'm a wimp. No, I don't care http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_u6Tt3PqIfQ …    
    
    
    @TaffetaDarlin Congrats!    
    
    
    .@CobieSmulders is Wonder Woman!!!  ....In the LEGO Movie! Close enough for now :) pic.twitter.com/2kFrkaMuGy    
    
    
    Can't sleep. Mad Men. https://vine.co/v/hKUzVJTqrKj     
    
    
    Google's Press Event is Starting Now!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GZzS6BxHEns#at=1761 …    
    
    
    The new Nexus 7? Yes, I need it. Who wants to buy my old one? :P    
    
    
    #Google is doing an amazing impression of E3 right now. Zzz    
    
    
    FINALLY!! A trailer for 47 Ronin with Keanu Reeves! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47_-pqoPDVQ …    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 hate the title that game got here in NA but glad to know you liked it - I'll have to check it out.    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Maybe writing an article about import titles/region free Nintendo consoles &needed video to embed? Forgot to set it unlisted    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock I think someone made this just for you (or more specifically, for your lady friend) http://i.imgur.com/Tu9QCHm.jpg     
    
    
    @josephmorin I was pleasantly surprised by it! Have fun!    
    
    
    That awkward moment when you remember we disposed of Osama Bin Laden the same way they disposed of Megatron....    
    
    
    @benroethig I agree but have we ever just thrown someone into the sea? That's so random.    
    
    
    @cefilby @benroethig Y'all are smart cookies. You must be Macadamia.    
    
    
    Back in '57.... @ Joe's Italian Café http://instagram.com/p/cK-0H0SeYj/     
    
    
    Normando Flores needs to mind his own damn business... https://vine.co/v/hKVdrbjXnJP     
    
    
    @benroethig It was a really cool looking car, and I respect the dude for rocking a goddamn fedora. He was legit 50's.    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz I'm all out of Xanax but I have some Faxanadu....    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Kevin McAllister said the same thing.... Twice!    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Just one night....    
    
    
    If she acts half as good/personable as she did in "This is 40," then I'm stoked about this new April O' Neil..... http://bit.ly/1aKr5M2     
    
    
    I caught a glimpse of a small, cute puppy... https://vine.co/v/hKl2hOpewAq     
    
    
    @JamieWalton I too am in a similar situation, thankfully with Internet they're always in touch but it's not the same. Cheers, friend!    
    
    
    @JamieWalton Not too bad. One of my local friends is moving to the Netherlands. Sort of far away ;) Other just moved about 4 hours away.    
    
    
    Shadow of the Eternals | Kickstarter is back up with a new goal. $750K and @DavidBHayter in the lead! http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/617502838/shadow-of-the-eternals-0 …    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers On the contrary, "If you can't explain it simply, you don't understand it well enough." -Albert Einstein :P    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Have you seen The Great Gatsby yet? Same director :)    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Love the book but I'm a movie guy myself and I thought the movie was fantastic! Soundtrack is great too    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys I bet it's in the discount theater now, I feel like seeing it too lol :o    
    
    
    Those Colors.. @ Look Cinemas http://instagram.com/p/cNqbeoSedt/     
    
    
    Dear citizens of the world, the year is 2013, why are we still using fax?? E-mail is incredible.    
    
    
    Oh, boy... #TGIF http://instagram.com/p/cPOPkOyefX/     
    
    
    @matthewacowling @mstarktv But... But... He becomes mortal!! He possibly may or may not die this time!!    
    
    
    @matthewacowling I agree, Jackman needs to learn to say no to the role. Enough is enough.    
    
    
    @mstarktv Agree completely. I have high hopes for "Days of Future Past" though.    
    
    
    Oh my god, it's finally here..... https://vine.co/v/hAOJbba1JWX     
    
    
    @shiralazar #TeamTwizzlers!!!! :p    
    
    
    Super stoked about this video shoot!! @ Power House of Dance http://instagram.com/p/cP6M9qyeX9/     
    
    
    Spin It! https://vine.co/v/hAi7AFniUaj     
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Nice!!    
    
    
    Shooting video at Power House of Dance for #DHDF2013 Day 2 @ Power House of Dance http://instagram.com/p/cRfaJ_Seel/     
    
    
    I gave "RIPD" the benefit of the doubt. It was very meh. On the other hand, "World War Z" is one of my fav 2013 movies. A must see!!!    
    
    
    @Sycoraxic98 You're probably not going to like it but in all honesty you're not the target demo. Something to remember.    
    
    
    One more shoot for #DHDF2013 https://vine.co/v/hAwhDiJvmWW     
    
    
    I'm resisting the urge to twerk so hard right now... It's really difficult you guys!!! #TwerkTeam #DHDF https://vine.co/v/hAw9bdHM01w     
    
    
    Oh my god, this group is great.... #dhdf @ Texas Theatre http://instagram.com/p/cSvmoYSeS9/     
    
    
    Yikes, just started listening to Kidd Kraddick's morning show a couple of months ago. Very entertaining, end of an era I'm sure. #RIPKidd    
    
    
    Another crazy fact, while hanging out in Irving last week I was shown Kidd's studios and foundation building. Crazy stuff. #RIPKidd    
    
    
    Wrapped with a pretty long weeke    
    
    
    That last post was supposed to say I wrapped a long weekend shoot. The fact that I totally botched it proves my point. Zzzz.    
    
    
    #HowTo Check Your Mail. WTF with all these bills??? https://vine.co/v/hAtW1eJOH0i     
    
    
    John Denver - Leaving on a Jet Plane | See you soon, @Pelpina & Rik!! https://vine.co/v/hAF20qmObAU     
    
    
    Even with the Internet, overseas good byes don't get any easier @ Dallas/Fort Worth International… http://instagram.com/p/cUmGPlyeea/     
    
    
    Night-time gathering by the Kidd Kraddick studios. #RIPKidd @ Kidd Kraddick in the Morning studio http://instagram.com/p/cVXm85SeZ7/     
    
    
    Lunch Time!! Dear @ChipotleTweets, I love your giant burritos!! https://vine.co/v/hA3Aa0pr6LL     
    
    
    @swonderlin :O! Congrats!    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock I didn't know you were a vegetarian! That's great.    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock that's awesome, mad props - hoping to make the change permanently sometime. I've definitely reduced my meat consumption.    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb that stupid megaphone took me out of the game experience so fast. Still love ACNL though    
    
    
    In case you ever wondered what it feels like to be throttled by T-Mobile after hitting your 5GB… http://instagram.com/p/cYNBp2SeW_/     
    
    
    This is so amazing!  Bioshock, Noire Style.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Mv3FhE6_TK0 …    
    
    
    See @TheTankTheory Review "New Super Luigi U" The latest review for http://www.Dvelop.TV  is up! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZYpeWk-po8 …    
    
    
    What an adorable little box!! http://instagram.com/p/caBFrkSeUG/     
    
    
    This is stupid. https://vine.co/v/hqqu7YWq61P     
    
    
    @KaiserGeiser HEY GET OUT OF MY FRIDGE!    
    
    
    For the love of God, did anyone ever show Foreigner what love is? That was like.. 30 years ago!!    
    
    
    Fun Fact: I used to watch Scooby Doo LITERALLY every single day as a kid. https://vine.co/v/hqh3tMlxpKr     
    
    
    Mystery Inc. Part 1 - Like, who finished the honey, Scoob?!? https://vine.co/v/hqMuZVhM2D9     
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs LMAO, don't agree but that was hilarious    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham @TwoTribesGames Not sure if joking but I think that's the PC port :P    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Haha, okay. Figured as much :P    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham @TwoTribesGames Next time, use a wink-face! Instant Joke-Getting, I promise* :P 

*WARNING: No promises are made.    
    
    
    @NintenDaan I like it!    
    
    
    When a song that's been in your head all morning plays on shuffle!!! #tuttifrutti https://vine.co/v/hqJ5HVY1bTP     
    
    
    @Munch79 @RichIGN This, so much.    
    
    
    It's been too long since I made a new #GeekMusical | "Bulletproof" https://vine.co/v/hq1nPZLgjmw     
    
    
    OMG This looks so hilarious!!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_MSrAwfagG4&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    You guys don't realize how often globesandmaps and I say the same thing at the same time... It's WEIRD… http://instagram.com/p/cc5JhOyeZ7/     
    
    
    @therealcliffyb I'm pretty good at not getting jokes, but if you really want to make that animal stop saying that, talk to Isabelle.    
    
    
    @Splitsite Holy shit! He lives!    
    
    
    Being a block head ain't easy.... #LNPP #LNPPantics https://vine.co/v/hqg50KmO3Qx     
    
    
    @PwneeStudios Today's the day!!! Wii U launch! Excited for y'all. We'll be putting a review up on http://www.Dvelop.TV  soon :-)    
    
    
    Can't blame WB Games for this decision. | Batman Arkham Origins Wii U Doesn't Have Multiplayer Because No Ones There http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/2013-07-31-batman-arkham-origins-multiplayer-skips-wii-u …    
    
    
    OMG YES!!! RT @tombraider: Big news today! A next-generation sequel to Tomb Raider has been confirmed: http://sqex.to/w8e     
    
    
    @meRyDoon At least your heart is in the right place. Dream big, friend. Have fun.    
    
    
    Way to go, @Target | Wii U ad FAIL! https://pbs.twimg.com/media/BQly2unCAAAm4EL.jpg …    
    
    
    @trace501 When did Mashable become Buzzfeed?    
    
    
    @erineestevenson Well I say, I say, I say Goh-Lee!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=n3xDfYNCFBQ …    
    
    
    Attempt @ConanOBrien Monologue Joke | "Latest GTA has been rated 18 yrs & older in Australia. Tell that to the 11 yr old who stole my car."    
    
    
    If you still shop at GameStop, can you just freakin' stop? Seriously. STOP.    
    
    
    Hello Darkness, my old friend... #macro http://instagram.com/p/cfEigOyeZO/     
    
    
    @TheBitBlock That game was incredible and I thought it was cool they let EA use their characters. Shows a good relationship, like LEGO City    
    
    
    @TronKnotts I just really like physical boxes.... Oh well!    
    
    
    @NE_austin @TronKnotts Ugh! I wish this was tweeted earlier. Had 147 before noon    
    
    
    @TronKnotts Good point!    
    
    
    @NE_austin Yup! If you still have 'em tomorrow, I'll let you know! PS: EggBusters is pretty great.    
    
    
    I still don't understand how mixing mayonnaise into stuff makes it "salad." (See: tuna, chicken, egg)    
    
    
    So the new season of "Whose Line" seems pretty hilarious...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EV2lPN9vIvg&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    @thathiphopguy We better ask Time Warner which they prefer.. the bat.. or the bag...    
    
    
    @thathiphopguy They may be running "Zathura" again... So there's that!!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my pal, @SuperMCGamer. May it be plentiful in lapis lazuli.    
    
    
    ROFL, well when you look at it that way... #Earthbound  |http://kondunn.tumblr.com/image/56810156851 …    
    
    
    WOW! It's just amazing to see how far this video technology has come in the past couple of years or so.  http://vimeo.com/67160485#     
    
    
    If you pre-order Rayman Legends on Steam, you get Rayman Origins to play now for free! http://store.steampowered.com/app/242550/     
    
    
    @TaffetaDarlin None of those links are working.    
    
    
    @TaffetaDarlin Sure thing! :D Thanks for fixin'    
    
    
    @hollypoz @camsicle @TheLemonBar @daysies @kyle1point0 @Sweg Have fun! And Happy birthday to @camsicle    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys I'm tryin' SHEESH!    
    
    
    @camsicle Sounds like you had an amazing night! I'll have to make an appearance next time :)    
    
    
    @PirateHearts I feel everyone was expecting him to be another young heart-throb so casting an older man is quite a shock!    
    
    
    @PirateHearts I was honestly hoping for a female.    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH This is pretty sweet! When can we expect an album to drop?    
    
    
    Could you eat a protein bar made of crickets??  http://techcrunch.com/2013/08/04/review-exo-a-cricket-based-protein-bar-that-wont-destroy-your-productivty/ …    
    
    
    This. @Nerdist animated @pattonoswalt's Star Wars Filibuster |  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CvdoLRBudwU …    
    
    
    My review of Animal Crossing: New Leaf is up. What're my thoughts 1 month in? @NintendoAmerica #ACNL | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VDiBCB2Qguc …    
    
    
    Splishhhhh splashhhhhh http://instagram.com/p/co4p-gSeek/     
    
    
    Went to go buy Pikmin 3 at Wal-Mart, I didn't see it on shelves. So I asked if they had it, a new game for the Wii U. "You mean the Wii?"    
    
    
    They tried twice to correct me. I said Wii U, and they insisted it was the Wii.    
    
    
    @AeroEchelon Right? I was like.. really?    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith @NE_austin Didn't @DoubleFine self-publish "The Cave" on the Wii U? I thought I read that...    
    
    
    @hiuhime I considered it for a couple of minutes.    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith @NE_austin Thanks for clarification. Now I feel like playing The Cave    
    
    
    @hiuhime Hahahaha!!! If only it were that simple!! You're making me reconsider though :P    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith Any idea who I'd get in touch with about press contact/possibly reviewing Duck Tales? Thanks ahead of time!    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith Appreciate it! Was going through their site and it kicked me off press page but I'll try again. Thanks! @Capcom_Unity    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith My site (http://www.dvelop.tv ) is very developer/game development-centric, would love to chat with you sometime!    
    
    
    @benroethig @pelpina Thanks, Ben!    
    
    
    @Janisku7 @pelpina Excited about it! :)    
    
    
    @OJessicaNigri I thought I'd be the one to tell you - the link to your Facebook profile doesnt work.    
    
    
    Chris Brown saying he's never going to make music again? "Never say never." -Justin Bieber    
    
    
    @The_Baconbitz Oh! You ended up buying it!! Glad you are playing it either way! I owe you a game gift next time! :) enjoy friend!!!    
    
    
    Oh, hello iOS Beta 5 <3 http://instagram.com/p/crhmGCSebq/     
    
    
    Okay Dallas friends, I need a candy shop that sells amazing honeycomb. Lay it on me. #TooLazyToMakeItMyself    
    
    
    Anyone hoping for games? You know? Some games for the Wii U? MT @NintenDaan #NintendoDirect! What are you guys hoping for?    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers Star Fox - Because the world deserves an amazing Space adventure right now.    
    
    
    Spending my time waiting for Target to open pretty wisely.... https://vine.co/v/hb93uUQAw3J     
    
    
    BOOO!!! "New details on previously announced games for  Wii U" | I'm guessing a bunch of trailers and release dates... #NintendoDirect    
    
    
    @thetanktheory Pikmin 3 this week <3    
    
    
    @kaiz03 That does sound amazing!    
    
    
    Super Smash Bros 4 Wii U & 3DS really doesn't look as good as it should. Models aren't as polished as you'd think :-(    
    
    
    WHAT?! Animal Crossing Plaza looks AMAZING!!!!!    
    
    
    @realmikefox I. WANT. THIS. WHERE?!    
    
    
    OUYA? What's that? ;-) #TeamWiiU RT @Emi1yRogers Wii U indie titles lineup video: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=50GcvuABEHY&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    The Power of Green https://vine.co/v/hbYJ2XjvpMb     
    
    
    I like my women like I like my cheese. Kraft American Singles.    
    
    
    @handynerds Tell him I'm not interested! Appreciate the offer.    
    
    
    Instagram is the first "short-video" service to enable uploads! The war against Vine rages on!    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Oh yeah? Well did you know that a strawberry is not actually a berry but a banana is? TAKE THAT! #SCIENCE    
    
    
    @JATactor I'm embarrassed to admit this is the first time I've ever heard "Popper Stopper" and I love it. Always called it a pop filter.    
    
    
    Talking to a friend who's been playing in the Batman Arkham Origins multiplayer beta. Now I'm really sad Wii U isn't getting MP.    
    
    
    Honestly, as a consumer, it'd be really hard for me to choose the Wii U version of Batman Arkham Origins over other platforms. @WB_Games    
    
    
    But honestly, how do publishers like @WB_Games expect the Wii U version of Batman to sell when it's missing an entire mode? This is stupid.    
    
    
    IDK if it's because it's late and I'm tired, but I'm really frustrated with the Wii U right now. Even with Pikmin 3 sitting in front of me.    
    
    
    @RichIGN You really think DK is a top-seller? The first one, sure - because of nostalgia but will reaction to the sequel will be the same?    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Why are Viners so worried about hate comments? Seriously - the only community I see give haters so much attention. :(    
    
    
    @RichIGN You ever watch Digimon? #NuffSaid    
    
    
    @crankycraig Possibly too many trees in one "acre." That's what it looks like at least. Game limits you.    
    
    
    If you're looking for a fun Summer game, check out @DisneyGames Where's My Mickey? - Here's our review  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aPicU9XeEkc …    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Where'd you see that? Sounds cool. Is it on Netflix?    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Fun fact: 1 word in captcha is random - other is illegibility verification. You're helping read books! Probably Huck Finn.    
    
    
    Had some DVD credits left over on my Red Box account. Can someone tell me how much I'm going to regret this?! https://vine.co/v/hhbKvtDgQd7     
    
    
    @NintenDaan TBD means To Be Determined which is just as frustrating!! :(    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Anytime :-)!    
    
    
    @DisneyGames @DisneyInfinity Hey Team, any idea where I can find a press contact/email? The link on your site is broken. Thanks!    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Vine is a very different type of comedy. VERY. But you're one of the few Viners I think can do really well in that space.    
    
    
    Does anyone know when The Wonderful 101 is coming out? I wish they'd tell us. #TW101Direct #NintendoDirectNA    
    
    
    @RichIGN Idk man, are you sure? Do you have any proof?    
    
    
    UNITE CRAW!!!! #TW101Direct #NintendoDirectNA    
    
    
    Seriously this trailer is too long and really really bad. #TW101Direct #NintendoDirectNA    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Maybe about the demo?    
    
    
    @trintran @PG_kamiya Did you guys announce when the game is releasing?    
    
    
    @Drzgamer Negative. Available for replay though!    
    
    
    Yes, TW101 Demo is out in NA,  but so is Art Academy Sketchpad! Where's the love?! @NintenDaan    
    
    
    @meRyDoon I think so. I had mine tailored to the 20s/60s.    
    
    
    Yes. Basically the best app ever! Thanks @NintendoAmerica #ArtAcademy #WiiU | https://miiverse.nintendo.net/posts/AYMHAAABAAD4UgHp_YeLUw …    
    
    
    Remember my name. Awesome Car Wash promo for @BreakingBad_AMC #BreakingBad @ Blue Wave Express Car Wash http://instagram.com/p/czs8llSeQj/     
    
    
    The Chromecast is dumb. #TrueTechTalk    
    
    
    @mikedmerrill Because you're awesome bro. #GetSwoll    
    
    
    The beat-boxing fiend who insists on turning any classic into techno. https://vine.co/v/hhv6ieDphJn     
    
    
    People keep saying Mad Men is a dark series, but I've been and it seems perfectly okay to me!  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YgvKCfZqxrQ …    
    
    
    @ImageForm Congrats on launch! Where can I send a press request? Would love to review SteamWorld Dig for http://www.dvelop.tv !    
    
    
    @NintenDaan You still posting on GN? Did you see this?? Metroid Fan Film http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/massivestate/metroid-enemies-within-a-metroid-fan-film?ref=recently_launched …    
    
    
    Very Cool!! @MetroidFanFilm on Kickstarter! | http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/massivestate/metroid-enemies-within-a-metroid-fan-film?ref=recently_launched …    
    
    
    @NE_austin gummy worms, Pikmin 3 and editing here.    
    
    
    @iamccardona Thanks for the follow! Wishing you the best on Metroid: Enemies Within    
    
    
    @UltimoRey Yeah, Find Mii 2 >>>>>>>> Find Mii 1    
    
    
    Tomorrow! The beginning of the end. #BreakingBad @BreakingBad_AMC https://vine.co/v/hhp1TeP0dTp     
    
    
    How to Undo a Week of Healthier Eating #Homemade #Tiramisu http://instagram.com/p/c2LkBNSedU/     
    
    
    Just In: Breaking Bad spin-off series where Walt ditches Jesse & cooks with the Barefoot Contessa titled "Breaking Sad" ... Think about it.    
    
    
    Seeing #Werethemillers in theaters? Chat with 208 others and I now on #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/11V6bXZ     
    
    
    @DtoidChris Max Goof! Get it right, sheesh!!! ;)    
    
    
    Comic fan or not! #Deadpool from @HighMoonStudios is a MUST HAVE game this Summer! | A http://www.Dvelop.TV  Review http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EU97h_fcdrs …    
    
    
    @iamccardona :D! Have you sent it to sites like Kotaku, Joystiq, etc? I've shared with a few gaming outlets I know.    
    
    
    If you're looking to get the new Black 3DS XL, Target has it for 175 (cc: @RichIGN ) http://www.target.com/p/nintendo-3ds-xl-console-collection/-/A-14218334#prodSlot=medium_1_8&term=3ds+xl …    
    
    
    I know you're all enjoying your Pikmins and Mario Dream Teams but don't forget! Fireworks every Sunday in @animalcrossing!!!    
    
    
    3 more hours until the end... Sing it, Walter White! SING IT! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=53j4vQ8Un0k …    
    
    
    Even Animal Crossing is getting in on the @BreakingBad_AMC Action. #breakingbad http://instagram.com/p/c418IsSeeF/     
    
    
    Reese is buying blue crystal for a premium today. Breaking Bad #breakingbad https://vine.co/v/hhEx2bDE3gm     
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary HECK YES! I AM THE ONE WHO KNOCKS!    
    
    
    @crankycraig Is AMC on the West Coast on a delay? I watch it synced with a friend of mine from the East. (Central here, formerly Mountain)    
    
    
    @crankycraig Interesting, guess I've always received the East Coast feed no matter where I lived. Thanks for the insight!    
    
    
    Wow. It has begun!! #NintendoTVii    
    
    
    Oh my God. The best show on TV is slowing coming to an end..... Starting NOW #BreakingBad @B... #BreakingBad #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/13cQfTH     
    
    
    Man, AMC really wants us to watch this new show. In between Breaking Bad and Talking Bad, and doesn't even give us a teaser until 1st comm.    
    
    
    One Word to Describe that Breaking Bad premiere: tension. #BreakingBad https://vine.co/v/hhVjrdVETmY     
    
    
    Now it's time to Talk Bad - with @Nerdist and Julie Bowen!!! #TalkingBad #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1cGcbKi     
    
    
    @justdevin Why not buy Amazon season pass or something? So you can see it tomorrow! :)    
    
    
    @justdevin Fair points! :)    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 Indeed there is!!!    
    
    
    @RichIGN Streaming is the future. Also, probably pointless, but if you haven't seen Trigun, get on that.    
    
    
    @RichIGN If you're getting FMAB in JP w/ Eng Sub - Amazon has it for 30.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Chobits is a WONDERFUL manga series, but I hated the anime! Hope you like it more.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Ahhh! Good idea! If you haven't seen Trigun, I'd totally hop on that train as well.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Also, on the Chobits manga: I cannot express how beautiful it is. Here it is for 30$ http://www.amazon.com/Chobits-Boxed-Set-Vol-1/dp/1591828376/ref=sr_1_11?s=books&ie=UTF8&qid=1376287714&sr=1-11&keywords=chobits …    
    
    
    @RichIGN Dude. Avatar, S1 is 22 on amazon and FMA:B is 30! #Math What are you doing!?!    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Hahahahaha!!!! In Chobits?? I think you made it farther than I did! Trigun. DO IT!    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Impressed. I'll check out Gunslinger Girl since it's on Netflix! But you need to see Trigun eventually. (Also on Netflix) :)    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Trigun is told from the point of view of a woman about a very "dangerous" man :-)    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter AND it has Closed Captioning! :-) #WinWin    
    
    
    @RichIGN Nope - the downloadable versions of the episodes. Avatar: http://www.amazon.com/The-Boy-in-the-Iceberg/dp/B000GK68EG/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&qid=1376289549&sr=8-1&keywords=avatar+the+last+airbender … FMAB http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B002TKS0HO/ref=sr_1_2_vod_1_pur_sea?ie=UTF8&keywords=fullmetal%20alchemist%20brotherhood&qid=1376289596&s=instant-video&sr=1-2 …    
    
    
    @RichIGN Of which series? The prices I showed are both for S1. Does iTunes have some kind of bundle pack?    
    
    
    Playing Pikmin 3, watching globesandmaps stream "Brothers", chatting on FB and taking this pic. I need… http://instagram.com/p/c51Ve8SeSN/     
    
    
    If by "soldiers" you mean "Random Inhabitants of a Planet You Crashed On" then yeah, I guess you're right - jerk pic.twitter.com/jLYaQSlS0U    
    
    
    Brothers: A Tale of Two Sons. Review hitting this week on http://www.Dvelop.TV  but just saying wow. cc: @StarbreezeAB @inthedark_isee    
    
    
    Wise words from Chris Ashton Kutcher. @aplusk http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2fepUlDbx5Y …    
    
    
    Pelpina Trip up to her old Trip-Tricks!! | Manchu #Blooper #4 cc: @Pelpina https://vine.co/v/hMBbDwnnZvB     
    
    
    Just coming off the #D23Expo fun & need some Mickey in your life? Check out Where's My Mickey from @DisneyMobile | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aPicU9XeEkc …    
    
    
    Xbox One no longer requires Kinect to be constantly connected. In other words, Microsoft has completely flipped all their stupid decisions.    
    
    
    .@The_Baconbitz You can do more than turn it off. You can now unplug the Kinect entirely from the Xbox One and still use your console.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Knack has me excited because it reminds me of Spyro, as far as design philosophy goes.    
    
    
    HA! As @inthedark_isee & @The_Baconbitz quickly pointed out to me - the only stupid decision left is the price, which hasn't changed.    
    
    
    @shribr @RobertJFClarke Negative, they've flipped on that as well. The Xbox no longer requires a constant online connection.    
    
    
    @Alex_dlc @RobertJFClarke Hahah yes, this is true! And unfortunately you are paying for it.. but at least you it's not constantly watching.    
    
    
    @The_Baconbitz @inthedark_isee @Drzgamer It may not be required, but incl. in the box means more people are likely to plug it in for fun.    
    
    
    "Man, I'm craving a McRib..."  

SAID NO ONE EVER!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!EUYGEUYWGH&*uiehgegfa    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter *high five*    
    
    
    @BreakingNews @rikkipoynter @AP :(    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Sorry, but WMV MUST go! Plenty of conversion tools out there. Maybe this one will serve you well. http://www.h264encoder.com/     
    
    
    @NintenDaan Understandable, but the reason files are smaller is because they are more compressed.    
    
    
    @NintenDaan This compression is then converted to MPEG4 H.264 through YouTube, and thus your result is pixelation.    
    
    
    @Drzgamer Account got hacked?    
    
    
    @Drzgamer I don't think that was @hootsuite | Another company stole your password and used Hootsuite to post that tweet.    
    
    
    You can bet your pretty little faces this is happening right now. Congrats on the launch, @WayForward @IvanDashSmith pic.twitter.com/qBfy58dfjN    
    
    
    @Drzgamer Yes, these attacks are usually not a single-victim crime. I recommend changing your password. I've used Hootsuite for years.    
    
    
    @karajanae @cwgabriel Agreed - a completely emotion experience. A true example of fine gaming.    
    
    
    @Drzgamer @hootsuite Glad you got that sorted. :-) Good luck finding the culprit!    
    
    
    The ups & downs of having a good video workflow? I want to play #DuckTales :-( pic.twitter.com/cwJeZqZexK    
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary What is that I don't even.... Hahaha    
    
    
    Oh, you know, just watching Obama kick the shit out of Hilary Clinton at an Indie Game Dev meet-up... https://vine.co/v/hMi37Bimqdm     
    
    
    Here's a quick tour of the Dallas Makerspace @ Dallas Makerspace http://instagram.com/p/c-d138SeaT/     
    
    
    Also, all this cool stuff was 3D Printed!!! Say WHAT?! @ Dallas Makerspace http://instagram.com/p/c-jMRDyeUz/     
    
    
    Awesome!!! Enjoy! RT @TjuvKlabbe: Your comment was helpful so I bought Animal Crossing: New Leaf! Thanks! pic.twitter.com/P8fXHQ5g6Q    
    
    
    @mikeorren Hey Mike! Consider this a holler back! Would love to learn more and help you out! e-mail: mark @ http://manchu-media.com     
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Sounds like you needed rest. I was in the same boat.    
    
    
    @TjuvKlabbe Great! Looking forward to visiting in the near future! :)    
    
    
    @mikeorren Awesome! Lookin' forward to it! Hope things are well with @yourspeakeasy!    
    
    
    Doing research & wondering: What the heck happened to Pikmin 3's launch? Where's "Iwata Asks?" Or animated shorts? http://www.polygon.com/2013/3/11/4088868/nintendo-tests-the-waters-for-new-cartoon-series-based-on-pikmin …    
    
    
    @mikeorren Mike, I totally thought you meant a metaphorical "video juggler," you know - someone to handle it all! lol.    
    
    
    @mikeorren Hopefully pointed your team in the right direction as I happened to know an actual juggler lol.    
    
    
    @social_sarah @mikeorren Best mix-up ever. It's going in my scrapbook. ;-)    
    
    
    @alexmonney Same here!!! I think I'm getting it on Wii U - what about you?    
    
    
    Looks like no Collectors Edition of Batman Arkham Origins for Wii U! Thanks @WB_Games!!    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Why not use your iPhone? It shoots in 1080p, a great video cam from my experience    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter bummer!! :( hope your computer has a quick recovery. What kind of cam do you normally use?    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Yay Canon! :) good camera.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Heh, those flip screens do come in handy. I use a Canon T3i and XF 100 primarily, both with flip-screens <3 but rarely use it.    
    
    
    God damn it, @Ubisoft MT @Drzgamer It's the same deal with Watch Dogs, no Collector's Edition for Wii U either.    
    
    
    Here's a little artsy-fartsy Instagram Video for you. @ Hilton Anatole http://instagram.com/p/dAhwqWSedw/     
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Not nice... THIEF! If you're ever in Texas, you can use it... But Swiper, no swiping!    
    
    
    Make your voice deep and sing like the "ERMAGERD GERSBERMS" girl. 

You now sound exactly like the lead singer of Creed. 

You're welcome.    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers Have you posted anything from Art Academy Sketchpad to Miiverse? What's your tag?    
    
    
    @DtoidChris First one is private but this sounds pretty good.    
    
    
    @DtoidChris There's also an audio glitch at 1 minute in where you go slow motion! That's weird!    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Oh, that 2nd one is MUCH better. You sound like a tin can in the first. And obviously the levels are messed up :P    
    
    
    @TronKnotts This one maybe? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PlYMZHn-6jA …    
    
    
    @nerdist Haha! Perfect! You look like Chris Hardwick, that guys the biggest of douchebags... Er.... I mean...! (Jk :) )    
    
    
    Don't Attack My Eye! The http://www.dvelop.tv  review for Pikmin 3 is now live! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dXckxe9wEWg … #Pikmin3 @NintendoAmerica    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter I know this feel. >_>    
    
    
    In case you missed it, my Pikmin 3 review is live! Check it! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dXckxe9wEWg …    
    
    
    Later, we have @inthedark_isee's review for @StarbreezeAB's "Brothers: A Tale of Two Sons" | You MUST see this game. OMG.    
    
    
    Well there's one way to take a break from live-streaming all morning..... https://vine.co/v/hMtEqUDwBWl     
    
    
    It's here! The http://www.dvelop.tv  review for @StarbreezeAB's "Brothers: A Tale of Two Sons" Outstanding! | http://youtu.be/tsVlnoElshk     
    
    
    @AdamSessler Yes!! I just published our review! Would love your thoughts http://youtu.be/tsVlnoElshk     
    
    
    .@inthedark_isee Just let me know it's National Relaxation Day, but no worries, I only have 7 more hours left in today's live-stream!    
    
    
    You guys, look at this Frankenstein Video Rig for an iPad. I've never seen anything like this..... @… http://instagram.com/p/dC-ULPSedl/     
    
    
    AMAZING! #SteamWorldDig is #1 in the eShop! Well deserved, congrats to @ImageForm | http://www.dvelop.tv  review hitting this weekend!    
    
    
    Now #SteamWorldDig needs to take over the USA eShop! GO! Make it happen!    
    
    
    @HaileyBright Awesome, I'm running the live video stream! Come say hi!    
    
    
    Wow according to this we've been streaming for almost 11 hours... 1 and a half to go! https://vine.co/v/hMxHl15PLzM     
    
    
    @rikkipoynter If I may, next time can you please not use Best Buy's geek squad? There are plenty of smaller shops that can quickly fix fans.    
    
    
    @DtoidChris in return for some feedback yesterday, can I have some feedback on our reviews? :) http://www.dvelop.tv     
    
    
    PHONE! WHY YOU NO WORK?!    
    
    
    Ohhh, this is why phone no work. T-Mobile outage :-( http://downdetector.com/status/t-mobile     
    
    
    Whoa, this woman's voice is awesome lol.... http://instagram.com/p/dGDV2iSecP/     
    
    
    @GCNStorm Whoa!Been at a video shoot all day& I miss this?! Blown away! GL! So do I contact you for Ninty PR for http://www.dvelop.tv ? :)    
    
    
    @Zachanner Not sure if it's cool but would love some feedback! http://YouTube.com/DvelopTV  :-)    
    
    
    Aspiring artists! @smartiniere is on stage right now talking about how he got into the industy http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8Ye1CI5wWhc …    
    
    
    8 Central!!! Are you ready?! RT @LisaMarieMary: @MrMarkZamora what time is breaking bad on dude?    
    
    
    @JATactor Hey friend! Is that you doing some voices in the new "Disney Infinity" game? If not, sure sounds like you haha    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Agreed - it's so beautiful and SO Disney. Even down to the music. It feels like fireworks night at the parks.    
    
    
    @cwgabriel Mmmm, teal and magenta. One of my favorite color combos. So 80's retro.    
    
    
    I'm wondering how much Disney Infinity content is on the disc. I'm guesing all of it and I really want to know how much they have planned    
    
    
    There are inevitable sequels in the works, I'm sure. Disney Infinity: Princesses? Etc. They're gonna milk this one good, I'm sure.    
    
    
    And just like that, all the characters on the Disney Infinity disc are found! IDK how they are going to make such a small list last.    
    
    
    My guess is we'll see a sequel for the holiday season.. is that too soon?    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith How much are they usually?    
    
    
    @IvanDashSmith Interesting!!! That's quite a good deal... Too bad the launch lineup is pretty weak lol.    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 Thanks for the heads up, I shall.    
    
    
    Happy Sasquatch Tuesday Because I don't need your alliteration.   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dXBWsvs5YdA …    
    
    
    Dat new YouTube App logo..... http://instagram.com/p/dP5CuBSed_/     
    
    
    WTF, Minecraft on Vita?! And not 3DS or Wii U?! That's so lame. :'( @notch    
    
    
    Yes, a little excited about this review... But it's going to take some time. http://instagram.com/p/dQFZ08SeTY/     
    
    
    Spaghetti Carbonara with Meatballs | Made by @thetanktheory http://instagram.com/p/dQSn0FyeWx/     
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Costume Quest! But not on a nintendo platform :(    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Also - Have you had any freezing issues with Disney Infinity? Mine has frozen twice.    
    
    
    Disney Day! Here's an unboxing of Disney Infinity for those wondering what comes in the Starter Pack! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=elWwzNaWzn0 … @DisneyGames    
    
    
    @Nintendo_Okie So far, so great! Alot of fun. Definitely has it's issues but your kids should love it.    
    
    
    @Jeremy_LaMont Game Part varies depending on the playset. Cars playset is a racing game. Pirates = adventure. Incredibles = super hero game    
    
    
    HOLY SMOKES! @RetroCR is coming to 3DS?! I finally get to play it! Day. One. Purchase. For. Me. Thank. You.    
    
    
    What's an anechoic chamber, anyway?? https://vine.co/v/heWBMPvUjMH     
    
    
    @kyle1point0 Before the end of the year, probably Holiday season... aka not soon enough :(    
    
    
    @rainsundrops @kyle1point0 One of the rooms, there's a fancy recording studio as well!! It's all very nice.    
    
    
    Rounding off Disney Day, we have @thetanktheory's review of DuckTales Remastered. Watch it! Woo-oo!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Hz-0Pu_zRw …    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers Super Mario 3D Land was the best Mario gave I've played in a LONG time and glad it's getting the "Big Console" treatment.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham @Emi1yRogers The best levels in Galaxy/Galaxy 2 were the levels designed like Mario 64/3D Land. Gameplay wise, I'm stoked.    
    
    
    In case you missed, here's the http://www.dvelop.tv  review for DuckTales Remastered @WayForward @IvanDashSmith https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Hz-0Pu_zRw …    
    
    
    @trace501 @NatGeo Do you mean Afghan Girl? It's pretty close!!    
    
    
    There are no words. http://instagram.com/p/dUv-dCyeQ_/     
    
    
    @jaimewoo Oh my glob, why would you do that to yourself?! Is it any good? Does NOT look appetizing....    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Killer Instinct? That robot game?    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Question: As someone HOH, do you make the effort to add captions to your own videos? Or rely on YouTubes auto service?    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Also, what about watching? Do you avoid videos where you can't turn CC on?    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Who's PPL? Short for people? Thanks for insight. Going to work on captioning my videos from here on out. Helps with search too    
    
    
    Those hating on Affleck must've never seen Dogma, Good Will Hunting, Argo or The Town. He's a brilliant actor (and director.)    
    
    
    @AngryJoeShow @wowcrendor seems to be on and off. Just uploaded 26 HD videos and each processed just fine.    
    
    
    Hey Disney, how are those "random" disc packs working for you? Oh, me? Don't worry about it... :( http://instagram.com/p/dWusVESeRU/     
    
    
    @Sweg Funny I just left!    
    
    
    Currently listening to the entire Beatles collection on shuffle. Are there any Beatles songs you'd consider to be bad? Can't think of one.    
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs haha seriously?! I have a hard time believing this!    
    
    
    The Summer of Arcade continues with Charlie Murder from @skastudios! Here's @inthedark_isee's review | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w-MGvbqJQpw …    
    
    
    And the award for best drum solo goes to.... http://instagram.com/p/dbLFi9Seb9/     
    
    
    @camilluddington Any info if you'll be Lara again in the sequel?    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay Wut!!!!!! No way! Sidewalks?!?    
    
    
    Just learned my old neighborhood is getting sidewalks. This is a big deal.    
    
    
    Good call, iPod.... Damn good call... http://instagram.com/p/dcX4CDyeWj/     
    
    
    @cwgabriel @DisneyInfinity Unless DLC, nothing new is coming to the game. Even the sets of figures they have planned are already in the game    
    
    
    @GCNStorm @Chad_Concelmo Agree with this 100%. Amazing title. We just published our review for it not too long ago | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tsVlnoElshk …    
    
    
    New Super Luigi U is available today @ retail. Here's the Dvelop.TV Review! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iZYpeWk-po8 …    
    
    
    @Impulse3000 No, there will definitely be a sequel by next year. They've already announced all they have planned for the current Infinity    
    
    
    @Impulse3000 Like I said, unless it's DLC, but the dev has already said that DLC is not familiar enough with the commoner audience.    
    
    
    @NE_austin Your show is fantastic but I just want you to fix the white balance on your camera so badly. Please??    
    
    
    @Zachanner needz moar Shitty Bane    
    
    
    @NE_austin Haha fair enough... but for real, everything is very yellow. See diagram. pic.twitter.com/UFtfKOuP0P    
    
    
    @NE_austin Is the cloth behind you manilla colored? Or is it supposed to be white?    
    
    
    @NE_austin Interesting! Well just trying to help :) Here's some color from things I think are supposed to be white pic.twitter.com/TCRjEx0cvy    
    
    
    @NE_austin Cap of thing in the background, some of your shirt, and eyes.    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Have you had a chance to try the Online for Disney Infinity? Want to give it a go sometime?    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Cool! Let me know when you're interested. Working on a review as well so wanna make sure I try the online portions.    
    
    
    .@LisaMarieMary Oh heck yes! You know we have a new #BreakingBad in 10 mins!!! :) :) :)    
    
    
    AMC - take a God Damn hint. I don't give a single care about Low Winter Sun.    
    
    
    @juliejaynak you mean the millions of people who tuned in for an Nsync reunion? Yeah I think they'll be alright.    
    
    
    .@Hyperfludd Level-5 doesn't know what they're doing with the Layton brand except it's popular so crank out more games. See: Layton Bros.    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Infinity DLC?    
    
    
    @AndrewEisen Wrong, there's one character and 290 skins.    
    
    
    @DtoidChris been looking all over and don't see anything about Disney Infinity DLC.. Elaborate?    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Oh - that doesn't count, it's already built into the game! :P    
    
    
    @DtoidChris I think we've forgotten what DLC stands for then. I refuse to take part in this incorrect use of terminology!    
    
    
    Today in a nutshell. 1.) Young females need better role-models 2.) Old ppl think "molly" is cocaine 3.) America has horrible taste in TV.    
    
    
    If you chose the VMAs over Breaking Bad, there's a part of me that dislikes you. Same rule applies to Honey Booboo & anything Kardashian.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter You may not get breaks there at the auto store, but you might get brakes!! #BadTimeForAGoodJoke    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Hope things pick up! ( And I don't mean no truck! )    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb We can all learn from that first quote. RE: Joss article.    
    
    
    @MeaganFinnerty Dat Lana Del Rey song!    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 1.) Of course I am! 2.) The latest drug on the streets, I feel it's important to know what people are exposed to...    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 3) those aren't pulling as many views as Kardashians, VMAs, etc - unfortunately.    
    
    
    Gatsby by the pool? Alright then. https://vine.co/v/hihbmBBZV0b     
    
    
    So I guess this Smash Bros list is now debunked? http://www.neogaf.com/forum/showpost.php?p=78023917&postcount=3588 …    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay How did you post those?    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers W101 is incredibly easy to market, but company behind their marketing is over-complicating. Hence a 5min "trailer."    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers They're trying to shove too much down the consumers throat, instead of letting them discover for themselves.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers No way, kids love that kind of stuff. Best place to put ads is before things like power rangers, beyblade, etc.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers Power Rangers is on it's 20th season, they were in the Macy's Day Parade, and toys continue to sell like crazy.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers The Power Ranger/TMNT/YuGiOh/Pokemon youth audience is the audience you not only want for W101, but need.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers They are out there and in large abundance. Surely, you must see this.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers Don't you remember when Power Rangers/TMNT/YuGiOh/Pokemon WERE the new weird things? ;)    
    
    
    2DS is very interesting. Slate design appeals to those looking for that "tablet" experience, but brings with it the amazing 3DS/DS Lineup    
    
    
    Since GBA SP, Nintendo has made the clamshell design part of gaming culture. It protects your screen and goes away quietly. Why stray?    
    
    
    If you think 5-8 year old kids aren't already loving their 3DS/DSi - you're out of your mind. The Nintendo 2DS is weird.    
    
    
    The 2DS' design screams "always open" - and parents love the ability to close their kids 3DS and say "it's time for dinner/homework."    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers I agree 100% & trust me - Not saying W101 is going to sell well - it's not. But I blame it's misguided marketing    
    
    
    On the bright side - Wii U is getting a price drop and Wind Waker HD is coming to digital download early.    
    
    
    For someone who was so behind, Nintendo really is doing digital right. Give the digital download gamers some incentive and they will come.    
    
    
    @TronKnotts @Emi1yRogers True that :-) Let's hope that it's at least as memorable as BeetleBorgs - over 15 years and you still remember it!    
    
    
    Make NO mistake - Nintendo feels the pressure from the growing tablet gaming marketplace. See: Wii U & 2DS    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Depends on where you're shipping.    
    
    
    @nadiaoxford @Nintendo_Okie If you don't think 5-8 year olds already love their 3DS or DSi then I think you're a little crazy.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter You'll probably be paying the same amount - best go with flat rate. Flat Rate Box might be cheaper than envelope.    
    
    
    @nadiaoxford @Nintendo_Okie Indeed I did notice that, see my tweets :) agree with you but I think their attention should be elsewhere    
    
    
    @AndrewEisen A single screen Ninty Tablet is more likely than you think. Nintendo is obviously feeling the pressure from the tablet market.    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter success!!!    
    
    
    "She was like 'Why do you have pictures of your penis on your phone?,' well, what is art?" | What?!? #OH #Overheard    
    
    
    @NE_austin What do you mean? It has a sleep switch.    
    
    
    @Xbox @cattaber Cat, are you in this?! Do you voice someone? Say.. April? :O!    
    
    
    @NE_austin Nintendo said explicitly that the 2DS is compatible with MOST DS games. How they handle it, we'll see - but they never said all.    
    
    
    @Cjaxs96 @NE_austin The IGN article said this is the case, but who knows!    
    
    
    Wow! Discovering that @cattaber plays April O'Neil in the new TMNT game. Now she's voiced 2 of my favorite female characters.    
    
    
    What is this? It looks like it WANTS to be a Ninja Turtle but there's no way this is a Ninja Turtle... It's hideous! pic.twitter.com/RVOWGMdGLe    
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs @jrbernsen Don't play dawg, you play too much!!    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 The designs are ATROCIOUS! Reviewing it for my site. Interesting gameplay, much deeper than I expected.    
    
    
    Cleaning my apartment and got bored so I present: Bane's Failed Audition for Grease.... @ Broadway http://instagram.com/p/dlLVvlyeZd/     
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Same.    
    
    
    The Wii U in a nutshell. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tuV8nSlRMhI …    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham @The_Baconbitz So you think kids will WANT the 2DS? Even though they already have 3DS? Or their older siblings have 3DS?    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock @JoolsWatsham Impossible to comment on the build quality of 2DS without playing it. It looks well built and sturdy.    
    
    
    .@trace501 @johnpoz @benroethig @LisaMarieMary This makes me sad. Why kickstart an idea that's been around for years? http://www.zazzle.com/you_suck_at_parking_leave_under_wiper_blade_business_card-240973273195311579 …    
    
    
    @johnpoz @trace501 @benroethig @LisaMarieMary Haha ;)    
    
    
    @RaveofRavendale @e_goldfish Whoa - thanks for the heads up!    
    
    
    @Drzgamer Where are they selling these?    
    
    
    @Drzgamer Bummer! I just want Bulbasaur :-(    
    
    
    Here's an unboxing of some @Pokemon Rumble U NFC Figures. Gotta buy 'em all! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=crkkvzoPk_Y …    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd Haha - just got this camera, I adore it much!    
    
    
    CRAP! I just realized I forgot Sasquatch Tuesday this week. Here's a recent sighting to make up for it.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=yeQ_c0DqQjY …    
    
    
    Here's your Magic 8-Ball answer for today.. Ask it something!! https://vine.co/v/h5zB1BaYZbp     
    
    
    @TjuvKlabbe You know it!! :-)    
    
    
    @camsicle Woo hoo! Thanks, it's a lot of fun :)    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Interesting stance you're taking against the platform when both Cut the Rope AND Mutant Mudds are available on both.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Still, interesting. Can we expect a blog post soon? Would love to hear more of your thoughts. Or where this is coming from :)    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Yeah - I get that. Sorry about confusion - just seemed like you were saying one was a better "starter" exp. than the other.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham But I see now that's not the case. Still a worthwhile discussion.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Yeah, it's pretty sad. Thinking about my childhood we had Mario, Sonic, etc. Now you see Angry Birds everywhere. So different    
    
    
    Summer of Arcade 2013 continues with Flashback from @Ubisoft | The Dvelop.TV Review http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bcOsXYcdKKc …    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay wtf, are you Ness from Earthbound?! #SMAAASSHHH    
    
    
    Guy: I'm on my way
Me: Cool, call when you're close..
Him: That's why I'm calling you now. Be there in 15
Me: Okay, cool!!
40 mins later...    
    
    
    Good bye, Obi-Van Kenobi.... May the force be with you..... Always... :'( http://instagram.com/p/dprk3-Sef4/     
    
    
    Reggie Fils-Aime "Online play is always important!" - Hence NSMB U, DKCR2, Pikmin 3, NintendoLand, etc etc http://www.ign.com/articles/2013/08/30/nintendo-online-play-is-always-important …    
    
    
    Having an A-1 day..... http://instagram.com/p/dr1KqSyeQd/     
    
    
    .@NE_austin Here's a funny glitch I encountered in TMNT Out of the Shadows. I thought you'd get a kick out of it http://youtu.be/ePuWsf2_kvs     
    
    
    This song is stuck in my head.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K1b8AhIsSYQ …    
    
    
    Oh. My. God.  http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/mightyno9/mighty-no-9 …    
    
    
    I just backed Mighty No. 9 on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/1dCQtYV     
    
    
    Felt like doodling.... I love nights like these... http://instagram.com/p/ds0vm8yeRY/     
    
    
    My favorite TMNT glitch so far. Wut is dis?! cc: @NE_Austin http://instagram.com/p/dtMap9SeY1/     
    
    
    @AngryJoeShow I'm putting my money on "Trans4mers"    
    
    
    @Seanba_ Nope, you're absolutely right. I was just talking about this yesterday. No one seems to care anymore :( Sam Fisher needs a reboot!    
    
    
    Dr. Mark here! #HowTo Speak Simlish: Episode 1 https://vine.co/v/h5XUW0Plpml     
    
    
    @Zachanner Congrats! Slowly working my way up to the first 100 on my new channel.    
    
    
    @Zachanner Very kind! Thanks :-)    
    
    
    Truth Time with globesandmaps #BreakingBad #AMC http://instagram.com/p/dvLsBIyeRX/     
    
    
    And herreee we goooooo!!!! #BreakingBad #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1cwF2ho     
    
    
    @AndrewEisen @Capcom_Unity Oh, and Dustforce is such a brilliant game. I'd buy it many times on the Wii U for me and my friends.    
    
    
    #MidnightMusic | @MylaSmith "Slow Down" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BorebWWtDBs …    
    
    
    @Nvader There's a food item I haven't had in forever.....    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Yeah, you have fun with that.. I'm headed to bed zzzzzzzzz    
    
    
    @rikkipoynter Haha "Early to rise, something something wise." #TooEarly and #TooLate at the same time to remember fancy quotes... :)    
    
    
    @HaileyBright It's a friendly reminder: Pumpkin Spice everything at Starbucks: available now! :-)    
    
    
    Oh, you know... Just some nightmares.... https://vine.co/v/h5Qe7jMEEnU     
    
    
    Didn't expect such a cool painting at the Valley View Mall, pretty rad! And very detailed.. @ Valley… http://instagram.com/p/dyMk3Ryebr/     
    
    
    Manchu Blooper #5 | Happy Birthday to @Pelpina!! https://vine.co/v/h5YbFpX77vF     
    
    
    It's #SasquatchTuesday  But instead, I have a video of Sask's cousin, Yeti, jumpin' through trees.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mTddczieNdQ …    
    
    
    @JamieWalton God gave Rock n' Roll to us!    
    
    
    Teaser Trailer for a project I'm working on... Full trailer this weekend... http://instagram.com/p/d0tLBYSeYh/     
    
    
    @trace501 Premiere <3    
    
    
    In case you missed: a teaser trailer for my next project is live on Instagram! Watch & Share? http://instagram.com/p/d0tLBYSeYh/     
    
    
    Coming soon to http://www.Dvelop.TV  (Trying out Pheed!)  http://pheed.com/p/32989102     
    
    
    Today's driving jams. hansonmusic http://instagram.com/p/d2b8N7SeQH/     
    
    
    @WayForward @MrBozon Since 2 Player Prod. has their hands full, you guys need a documentary film maker for your Shantae kickstarter? ;)    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Is jumping to Pheed a solution to this problem?? Hmmmmm ;) (Note: I don't think it is)    
    
    
    Here's the Instagram Teaser for the new project coming to dvelop.tv, uploaded to YouTube for your convenience!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Xdk4ijjl-w …    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Yeah - not implying that, seems weird for everyone to jump to a new platform when social media numbers are low right now :)    
    
    
    @Splitsite Where? Who's they?!    
    
    
    @Splitsite I WANNA PLAY! is it 1.6?    
    
    
    @Splitsite Dude yeah man. YES a million times. I need to get on steam more often... and probably re-download 1.6    
    
    
    @GameplayDev dat crawfish    
    
    
    Good music never dies. Happy Birthday to the late Freddie Mercury | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eQsM6u0a038 …    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay donnttttttttttt    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay :( :( :(    
    
    
    @Jenn_naay Haha :p    
    
    
    @cwgabriel @tychobrahe You all continue to inspire. Thanks for everything.    
    
    
    @AngryJoeShow Wait a minute, you've been in Austin this whole time?! Why did I think you were in Cali? Sup neighbor! (Dallas, TX)    
    
    
    Footballs are back on! I can't believe they had the ball and they were of not scoring! So sad for my team and me.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gdwchohlMjI&list=TLpxE-W-jgPK8 …    
    
    
    Night-time #NoseGuitar is harder than it looks... #loop https://vine.co/v/hJ6v6iZIqZ0     
    
    
    Nice! Wiis are going to fly off shelves now!! #RIPWiiU MT @TheBitBlock NSMB Wii, Super Mario Galaxy 2 & Wii Sports Resort are now $29.99    
    
    
        
    
    
    Someone is excited for Friday!!! https://vine.co/v/hJpJDTM6wKY     
    
    
    Gears. In. Motion.    
    
    
    iOS Gamers! Get yourself some free Batman!  http://www.ign.com/prime/promo/batman-free …    
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary Playing with my new microphone shock mount! Yeah! New toys!! Woo!!    
    
    
    Rap: Then and Now https://vine.co/v/hJQ9vh9nhVK     
    
    
    @TheBitBlock  HOLY COW MAN! LOOK AT THAT SKYBOX!    
    
    
    @Splitsite WUT?! Even Elite is playing?!    
    
    
    @Splitsite Hahaha well I'm downloading CS and I'll be in soon...    
    
    
    @Splitsite Wait.. he's old enough to play now?! .... omg this is trippy.    
    
    
    @Splitsite Hahaha wow. That's just crazy...    
    
    
    Well this wins the internet...  http://www.buzzfeed.com/jenlewis/if-walter-jr-from-breaking-bad-had-instagram …    
    
    
    @GameplayDev That was added in a fairly recent software update if I recall correctly    
    
    
    Does anyone subscribe to some podcasts because they're boring as heck and make you fall asleep? Er, yeah - me either....    
    
    
    Coming soon to http://www.dvelop.tv ! "Castor & Pollux" | A Game Dev Documentary! - Here's the first trailer http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ae1iP7MkhV0 …    
    
    
    @TychoBrahe @cwgabriel @rkhoo @thekiko @PA_Megacorp Yall have inspired me to pursue my passion - so here's Trailer #1 http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ae1iP7MkhV0 …    
    
    
    @Janisku7 Thanks for watching! I'm very excited for this series! It's going to be a fun ride.    
    
    
    @GCNStorm Hey! Just released the first trailer to an episodic mini-doc I'm working on about Student Game Dev http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ae1iP7MkhV0 …    
    
    
    @buenothebear Any interest in a documentary about Student Game Development? :) I've been workin' hard on it! http://youtu.be/ae1iP7MkhV0     
    
    
    Um... So... Just regular pickles? @ May Dragon http://instagram.com/p/eBN-8HSeVN/     
    
    
    Eight Treasures Duck?! Poor Scrooge McDuck never stood a chance :-( @ May Dragon http://instagram.com/p/eBOHXzSeVc/     
    
    
    Bad Morgan Freeman Impression Reads Your Instagram Episode 1: nickynicksrn http://instagram.com/p/eEXdgcyeeS/     
    
    
    Bad Christopher Walken Impression Reads Your Facebook - Episode 1 @innovationenvy http://instagram.com/p/eEZF-rSee4/     
    
    
    Barely Tuesday & reaction to my Game Dev Documentary trailer has been crazy! Thanks for watching/liking/subbing! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ae1iP7MkhV0 …    
    
    
    What!!!! This is awesome!!! https://vine.co/v/h1wzKJWljL2     
    
    
    @NE_austin Pretty typical for a home connection sadly. Time Warner?    
    
    
    @innovationenvy Yup :(    
    
    
    Happy National Video Games Day! Seen this yet? Shares, Likes, and Subscriptions are greatly appreciated!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ae1iP7MkhV0 …    
    
    
    Oh, apparently it's 5 o'clock and I haven't had anything to eat all day? I guess I should eat before I die or something....    
    
    
    Soon...... #dvelopTV http://instagram.com/p/eMXiLByeSn/     
    
    
    This is Anthony Burch (reverendanthony) lead-writer of Borderlands 2 and co-star of "Hey Ash" http://instagram.com/p/eOGOvyyeYm/     
    
    
    @reverendanthony Nice meeting you at UTD today! Great talk, we should have the video ready soon and I'll shoot you an e-mail!    
    
    
    Fanciest coffee I've ever received at someone's house!! http://instagram.com/p/ePnSxkyeQh/     
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Hey are you in Dallas?! Any interest in an interview about Game Dev geared towards students/aspring devs? :-)    
    
    
    It's been a LONG time in the making but I'm pretty excited to announce the website for http://www.dvelop.tv  is up & running! Launch Day!    
    
    
    @cwgabriel @TychoBrahe @rkhoo @thekiko Once again, thanks for the inspiration - my documentary series launched today! http://dvelop.tv/dveloptv/castor-pollux-01-who-are-castor-pollux/ …    
    
    
    @krisstraub @pvponline I thank PA team tons but owe a lot of inspiration to you as well! TY! Today I launched this http://dvelop.tv/dveloptv/castor-pollux-01-who-are-castor-pollux/ …    
    
    
    @markramsey Would love to hear what you think!!    
    
    
    @markramsey It's my favorite show on TV!    
    
    
    @benroethig @markramsey Get on that! I've been tellin' @CaliLewis for what feels like years! :P    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Loved the Wii version, off-line co op and cartoon style ftw!!    
    
    
    The first episode of Dvelop.TV's Student Game Dev Documentary is live! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cziMtUygNDA …    
    
    
    I think we all, as a collective human race, should apologize for "Who Let the Dogs Out?"    
    
    
    It's Breaking Bad Day!!! You know what this means?!?! #BreakingBad https://vine.co/v/hnIVabda1OQ     
    
    
    @NE_austin @TronKnotts @TheBitBlock @slimjedi Not at all new for Mario seeing as it's based on Mario art from NES era games.    
    
    
    Wow. @BreakingBad_AMC    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock Correct, just like we're not allowed to punch him for what he did to Batman, Willy Wonka or Planet of the Apes.    
    
    
    This article has me laughing like @rickygervais .  http://www.buzzfeed.com/daves4/the-dumbest-things-ever-said-on-twitter …    
    
    
    I'm doodling to stay awake all day! Fuel my fire by replying with inanimate objects I can turn into cute little characters! GO!!    
    
    
    People complaining about GTA 5, reviews for stupid reasons. It's really unsettling.    
    
    
    More concerned people claim to have experienced an entire sandbox game in a short amount of time w/ no access to a huge chunk (multiplayer)    
    
    
    Too many people hungry for that embargo release flood instead of giving people a fair review. So sad.    
    
    
    @deanjnorris I want to retweet you so badly, but I can't post Breaking Bad spoilers, man! What's the matter with you!    
    
    
    A little rusty but doing some figure drawing. 30sec/1min gestures. https://vine.co/v/hnVPwlzqT9V     
    
    
    Backtrack in the http://www.Dvelop.TV  series is "Cloudsurfing" by @RothSothy BUY THAT SHIT! http://rothsothy.bandcamp.com/     
    
    
    I'm tired. I had an early morning video shoot in Ft. Worth and now I'm shooting with the Castor & Pollux te... https://vine.co/v/hva2alYPZUP     
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagram.com/p/ebF1ecyec-/     
    
    
    The Dvelop.TV review for Rayman Legends from @Ubisoft is LIVE! Check it out here! http://dvelop.tv/reviews/review-rayman-legends/ …    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd Funny, was thinking of going to get it myself :)    
    
    
    Idk, you guys... I've talked to a few foxes and I've never heard them say that....    
    
    
    Latest episode of the http://www.dvelop.tv  Student Game Dev documentary is up! Check it out, sub and like! Thanks! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8EJFqRNnVDo …    
    
    
    Second to last episode of Breaking Bad.. I'm not ready.. I'M NOT READY!!!!!!    
    
    
    THE END IS NIGH!!!! #BreakingBad #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1cwF2ho     
    
    
    Hey - don't let next week's episode of Breaking Bad be the first you see ever, and that's obvious....    
    
    
    Figure Drawing - 3 Min "Calligraphy Style" @ ATEC Building http://instagram.com/p/en6j06yeYj/     
    
    
    WOW! Just got an e-mail from @iTunes saying they're giving me credit to get the rest of Breaking Bad Season 5! Love them right now.    
    
    
    Not sure why but I thought this was hilarious.... And creepy at the same time...: http://instagram.com/p/esRfqsyeSQ/     
    
    
    Breaking Bad? Or Breaking Fast? Breaking Bad #BreakingBad https://vine.co/v/hr0HZBOv7Z6     
    
    
    Excuse sir, who ya gonna call? #ghostbusters https://vine.co/v/hrYPWX2UDXd     
    
    
    If your first instinct to gaining social media interaction is to spam my e-mail, you're going to have a bad time. Please stop.    
    
    
    Working on the next episode of Dvelop.TV's "Castor & Pollux" for this weekend. Miss Ep 2? Check it! http://dvelop.tv/dveloptv/castor-pollux-02-meet-the-team/ …    
    
    
    Feel good video of the day!  Dat rap doe?  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SHogg7pJI_M&feature=share …    
    
    
    Just broke the hell out of a fast. #Breakfast #JustLikeWaltJr #HashtagsForDays    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Hey Jools, there's a chance I might be in Austin next Sun. for Captivate. Any chance we can sit down for an on-cam interview?    
    
    
    Toca Builders from @tocaboca is available on Google Play today!! Here's our review of the iOS version http://youtu.be/BwmdIMy0meg     
    
    
    @AeroEchelon Sure thing, pal! Good luck, app looks really nice. Need to charge my Nexus so I can try it out.    
    
    
    Switched to iPhone from Android a while ago and I have only one regret! https://vine.co/v/h6OFa7qgweX     
    
    
    Walk like a man... Talk like a man... This. Is. POLLUX!! https://vine.co/v/h6iwOr3XAZK     
    
    
    An ideal to strive towards... #ManofSteelMovie #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1fOM8AA     
    
    
    Watching laurel_leaves at Muddy's @ Muddy's http://instagram.com/p/e01Peoyeak/     
    
    
    My favorite 'Bad' thing comes to an end today... It's still a few hours away but I'm not ready for it to be over.... #BreakingBad    
    
    
    Every girl's crazy 'bout a sharp dressed man so screw it, here's two!! W/ @NormFlores http://instagram.com/p/e2f2tIyeTI/     
    
    
    Before and After #NewRoomate #GoodbyeSpace http://instagram.com/p/e28-CWyec6/     
    
    
    And now it ends. #BreakingBad #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1cwF2ho     
    
    
    And... that's it... :') Bittersweet....    
    
    
    "Take What You Need" - I wonder what the taken choices were... http://instagram.com/p/e4wkglyebn/     
    
    
    Huell is STILL at the safehouse. #BreakingBad https://vine.co/v/hr9D0bvq91W     
    
    
    I think the Government shut down because they wanted to beat the GTA V campaign before GTA Online comes out! I just know it...    
    
    
    For those wondering about the #GovernmentShutdown  - this seems like a good resource.  http://www.npr.org/blogs/itsallpolitics/2013/09/23/225462813/8-things-to-know-about-a-government-shutdown …    
    
    
    Google Web Designer? WOW! This seems incredible! Can't wait to play around with it!!!  https://www.google.com/webdesigner/     
    
    
    Honestly? Mario 3D World looks like it's going to be one of the best Mario games ever. 3D Land was perfect, and this? DO WANT!    
    
    
    Also, SONIC CONFIRMED FOR Smash 4!!!! YES!    
    
    
    Mickey Mouse has always been a fan of popular music.... https://vine.co/v/hgm0BmIAPJv     
    
    
    Getting my blown tire changed... YAY! Grown-up time!! https://vine.co/v/hgKbzn7K0mr     
    
    
    I joined the TMNT Fan Club for exclusive looks at the new series & fan-only experiences and prizes! - http://sot.ag/WZtR     
    
    
    I am genuinely depressed by how broken GTA V Online is. I feel betrayed by @RockstarGames .    
    
    
    This is exactly why I think all those perfect scores GTA V got on launch week were BS. They only played half the game.    
    
    
    I can say that I've put about 1-2 hours into GTA V Online and all of that was spent trying to start the required tutorial.    
    
    
    It hasn't let me play for a single minute. GTA V Online is BROKEN.    
    
    
    GTA V is the first game where I've considered getting my money back 2 days after buying it. Thanks @RockstarGames    
    
    
    @JamesFrancoTV The chop-job of that photo is killing me on the inside.. MS Paint ftw I suppose?    
    
    
    Mode: #Draper    
    
    
    @hiuhime @hominey_hominey Enjoy! You're in for a magnificent TV treat.    
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary Hahahaha dem minisodes are good for those Breaking Bad withdrawals!!!    
    
    
    The Three Amigos, reunited!! W/ @gkdave and @NormFlores #PumpkinSpice #Chai #StarbucksStarbuds @… http://instagram.com/p/fF6_g5yebL/     
    
    
    @LisaMarieMary Hahaha!! How do you do?! I have not had the joy of e-meeting Harumph!    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd very nice! Congrats on the new job!    
    
    
    Hard to tell, but this is @Warren_Spector talking about cool stuff @ The Captivate Conference | w/… http://instagram.com/p/fIWcahyeWJ/     
    
    
    Practicing lighting with pastels. Scene 1: Sunset http://instagram.com/p/fLE7xdyeTG/     
    
    
    More Pastel Practice - Scene 2: Night http://instagram.com/p/fLHM1SyeWX/     
    
    
    And final Pastel Practice for the day - Scene 3: High-Noon http://instagram.com/p/fLKi8GSeau/     
    
    
    Huh.. Government shuts down and gas prices drop to an all-time low?! What a coincidence!!!    
    
    
    Does this remind anyone else of Aperture?? GladOS?!? http://instagram.com/p/fODnR5yeeB/     
    
    
    Round Goes the Water Mill https://vine.co/v/hXlEQ3YeZ1m     
    
    
    New episode of the game-dev documentary I've been working on is out!

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=raAfPbicnJU …    
    
    
    Spoke with @jeriellsworth & tried the CastAR last weekend. Check out my interview and their kickstarter campaign here http://dvelop.tv/gameplay/captivate-conference-castar-by-technical-illusions/ …    
    
    
    In case you haven't been outside for some reason.... http://instagram.com/p/fdOVMiSeaz/     
    
    
    Hopdoddy's | Named so for the hops (beer) and the doddy (Angus beef in Scotland) @ Hopdoddy Burger Bar http://instagram.com/p/fdS5qsyeTc/     
    
    
    Awe man, horrible news :-( RIP Father of the Gummy Bear, Hans Riegel | http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-24539012 … cc: @JohnPoz    
    
    
    Did you get Wind Waker HD? Full review coming soon, but here's an unboxing of the EPIC Ganondorf Figure!  http://dvelop.tv/gameplay/unboxing-legend-of-zelda-wind-waker-hd-collectors-edition/ …    
    
    
    I feel like John McClane... Not heroic or anything... I just have a real bad headache... #WalkingOnGlass    
    
    
    "You want to learn Spanish, go get desperate."    
    
    
    At the Fort Worth Alliance Air Show because #Merica w/ @tiffanysweet27 @gkdave @ Fort Worth Alliance… http://instagram.com/p/fp7-4RyeX8/     
    
    
    This ones for you, @rosslarocco @ Fort Worth Alliance Airport http://instagram.com/p/fqBSxxyeS5/     
    
    
    Inflatable Guns, because #Merica!!!!!!!!! @ Fort Worth Alliance Airport http://instagram.com/p/fqCQS0yeU-/     
    
    
    the guys at AllVetPT gearing up to jump! w! @tiffanysweet27 @gkdave @ Fort Worth Alliance Airport http://instagram.com/p/fqEIYFyeY-/     
    
    
    The guys @AllVetPT gearing up for a jump! w/ @tiffanysweet27 @gkdave @ Fort Worth Alliance Airport http://instagram.com/p/fqEU25SeZX/     
    
    
    What an INCREDIBLE honor to finally see my friend @gkdave jump with the @AllVetPT!!! w/… http://instagram.com/p/fqYPIeSeRl/     
    
    
    I'm-a FIRIN' MAH LAZER!!!! @ Dallas Makerspace http://instagram.com/p/fsi2Yvyeew/     
    
    
    Our house... Was 3D printed @ DMS! @ Dallas Makerspace http://instagram.com/p/fsl7UxyeU0/     
    
    
    @benroethig @digitalphil_ I haven't had a cheeseburger in forever :(    
    
    
    Nice find! RT @pelpina: What I'm doing right now: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=V5t0C_1kgFQ … #AlwaysImprove #LearnNewThings @MrMarkZamora    
    
    
    #Gibson #RogerSterling #MadMen http://instagram.com/p/fv4q2_yebA/     
    
    
    #TruthFact MT @TiffanySweet27 Candice: I think Pokemon started my gambling... 
Mark: Yeah, and my dog-fighting...    
    
    
    @MrJoshGeddes @pelpina Hey there - seems like Dvelop.TV is down too. :-( Not good!    
    
    
    Just learned that I started working on the idea which would eventually become http://www.Dvelop.TV  exactly 1… http://instagram.com/p/fxsCnkSec1/     
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs @jrbernsen @snaveytak yes please.    
    
    
    @benroethig Thanks. man! Its been a busy and exciting year!    
    
    
    An app update I've been waiting anxiously for!! http://instagram.com/p/fyW5SPSeZO/     
    
    
    Grand Theft Auto 5, everyone... Not quite what I was expecting... http://youtu.be/imIkmHCo8Lw     
    
    
    Elvis Radio for the drive home? Okay! Thanks pandora http://instagram.com/p/fy0cp8yeQk/     
    
    
    Cookie Monster wants to know "What does the fox say?" https://vine.co/v/hpeznLDY2b7     
    
    
    Some thing's don't change much... http://instagram.com/p/f3cpmEyeUX/     
    
    
    You sneaky devil! You almost had me this year, Groban... If not for Timehop!! >:-( http://instagram.com/p/f5byVRyeTf/     
    
    
    There are very few decisions I make that I regret immediately, but Java Monster is one of them. #BARF http://instagram.com/p/f5m13tyeVD/     
    
    
    Where to store your Java Monster https://vine.co/v/hpXxTYHutvg     
    
    
    Dem jams doe. | Dem jams doe.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8XQGkYHOzSE …    
    
    
    Motion Capture Lab!! Cool stuff man!! @ ATEC Building http://instagram.com/p/f52ikuSecx/     
    
    
    Her Eye http://instagram.com/p/f6MdjxyeQF/     
    
    
    Wow, this was bad... But I Lol'd... http://instagram.com/p/f8Mi3syefE/     
    
    
    Ah man, it's time to shave.... #ouch https://vine.co/v/hpxugThjQxj     
    
    
    Spending early Sunday morning as any person should. #science http://instagram.com/p/f-LybmyeWK/     
    
    
    Dem bagpipes doe. @ Central Presbyterian http://instagram.com/p/f-gVVHyeYc/     
    
    
    You guys will never understand how hard it was to get that #macro shot... #cat http://instagram.com/p/gEMp0ZSebW/     
    
    
    @KaiserGeiser Hahaha! Good luck! Hire him. @NintendoAmerica    
    
    
    250k+ Followers later, I've earned my Google+ stripes! ... Or is this open to everyone now? http://instagram.com/p/gEdDrRyeSk/     
    
    
    Totally reaping the benefits of cat-sitting. This looks like one of those outrageous portraits you get… http://instagram.com/p/gErDIUyeXZ/     
    
    
    I'll have you know I went to Hobby Lobby and only came out sort-of broke... #BuyAllTheThings    
    
    
    We carved pumpkins! :-) @tiffanysweet27 on top | mine on bottom http://instagram.com/p/gG_B05yeX6/     
    
    
    Roommates Halloween costume... #outrageous https://vine.co/v/hDTxe277l2Z     
    
    
    Streaming Minecraft: Hunger Games! Come watch me be horrible. http://www.twitch.tv/MrMarkZ     
    
    
    Streaming Minecraft: Hunger Games again! Check it out! http://www.twitch.tv/mrmarkz     
    
    
    What an incredible trailer for CoD Ghosts! It ALMOST makes me want to buy the game...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MNxh7umVOZ0 …    
    
    
    #CheeseDust    
    
    
    Tech Smart Folk! I need your assistance! https://plus.google.com/u/0/+MarkZamora/posts/AAMfEWyDK4S …    
    
    
    @babbott1 @TiffanySweet27 Hahaha! You guys...    
    
    
    @TiffanySweet27 That umbrella lady was pro. ;)    
    
    
    The latest episode of our Video Game Dev documentary is live!   This episode is all about the animation!    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cBJqhhEkRYY …    
    
    
    Roommate finally took my advice and started watching Breaking Bad..  1 season and 3 episodes later.... #BestShowOnTV | @BreakingBad_AMC    
    
    
    @babbott1 @TiffanySweet27 Haha! That's Tiff being silly with her awesome umbrella.    
    
    
    CoD Ghosts ending revealed to be exactly the same as Modern Warfare 2. Yeah, I won't be buying it. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5E82ZkHTiVU …    
    
    
    Found on Reddit. I laughed a good laugh. Perfectly relevant with YouTube shoving Google+ down everyone's throats. pic.twitter.com/rAPkj5VxYo    
    
    
    This made me laugh out loud. Silly YouTube!  http://www.theverge.com/2013/11/8/5080630/youtube-co-founder-wonders-why-the-fuck-comments-require-a-google …    
    
    
    Iced Coffee and a paper bag! Wait what?! http://instagram.com/p/ggJOW7yeVn/     
    
    
    #ChalkyPowderDustJunk    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagram.com/p/giz9bnyeSN/     
    
    
    1: My cat scratches all the time.
2: Oh God, cats...
1: What? You don't like cats?
2: No, I like cats, it's just.. Cats.    
    
    
    The reason we haven't seen a "Lost Vikings" game in so many years is because the Vikings are lost. It makes perfect sense.    
    
    
    @adamantium_claw LOL! Nice new Twitter handle!    
    
    
    Apparently Instagram when you're hungry is a bad idea.    
    
    
    We're teaming up with Chili's for some awesome videos! https://plus.google.com/u/0/112102361608067819607/posts/39ZpJwEYBRy …    
    
    
    @camsicle Thanks! I'm pretty excited about it :)    
    
    
    @babbott1 Stringsnot eh? Assignment accepted.... if only for curiosity's sake!    
    
    
    Hahaha! So awesome! RT @social_sarah: Woo hoo! Ran into @mrmarkzamora at the grocery store! #win    
    
    
        
    
    
    Figure #Drawing - Nov 18 2013 - Charcoal on Paper - 2 Hours http://instagram.com/p/g4f1qvSeal/     
    
    
    I think my roommate is a cannibal. He keeps talking about eating "raw men!!" He could at least have the decency to cook them!! #gross    
    
    
    @kyle1point0 ramen. :P    
    
    
    Another gem from Classic Mark #Subs http://instagram.com/p/g-nue4yeeP/     
    
    
    The 90's. No one ever questioned Shaggy, though someone probably should have. #boombastic    
    
    
    You ain't a real man unless you can quote "Bring It On" in a moments notice. #BrrItsColdInHere    
    
    
    Go home, bike. You're drunk. pic.twitter.com/cMWgLN1RQa    
    
    
    These speakers are awesome!!! https://vine.co/v/hUYtX7nZPaT     
    
    
    I declare the national Black Friday theme song "Eleanor Rigby" #AllTheLonelyPeople    
    
    
    Niece: Look at my phone!
Me: Who'ya gonna call? Ghostbusters?
Niece: No
Me: Why not?!
Niece: Because I don't know the number!!!    
    
    
    Give him a smile! http://drawquest.com/s/m99fcd  via @DrawQuest    
    
    
    Normally, this LCD tells me the temperature.... But right now? #ice http://instagram.com/p/hiK3SdSeRB/     
    
    
    15- Minute Clay Sketch | https://vine.co/v/hxD9DTtQr6i     
    
    
    15- Minute Clay Sketch https://vine.co/v/hxD9DTtQr6i     
    
    
    I'm like Batman, I live life by 1 rule and that rule is "I like to party"    
    
    
    Woo hoo! This 3DS Miiverse update is pretty legit! https://miiverse.nintendo.net/posts/AYMHAAACAADRUqFk1vvcbA …    
    
    
    My roommate just got BSOD'd. What is this, 2001?! #Windows8 #BSODSadFace http://instagram.com/p/hu4_X2yeeL/     
    
    
    @TheBitBlock It just sits in the background. Doesnt pop up. Might as well upgrade.    
    
    
    Learned a new head sculpting technique that allowed me to make this in about 15 minutes... I think… http://instagram.com/p/h4sk10yefm/     
    
    
    Progress on my charcoal piece from 3 Weeks ago. I think it's done.
#drawing #art #charcoal #figure… http://instagram.com/p/h6dqwrSeU4/     
    
    
    Once again, Sesame Street wins Vine... https://vine.co/v/hQFdjnqgpjp     
    
    
    Just took the artsy-fartsiest of Snapchats.... http://instagram.com/p/iP74TqyedS/     
    
    
    Merry Christmas to everyone! Hope it's full of family and feels. http://instagram.com/p/iWe-K9SeYO/     
    
    
    We made a gingerbread house! ...From scratch! http://instagram.com/p/iZWt-wyeTO/     
    
    
    Stumbled upon a TV show about hunters on Animal Planet. This feels so wrong to me.... #WhereAreTheAnimals #OhYeahTheyreDead    
    
    
    Marley & Me... Saddest movie ever.... ALL THE FEELS!!! :'( http://instagram.com/p/iaPMF0SeVZ/     
    
    
    Someone give Adele some Tums. #FireStartingInMyHeart    
    
    
    On a fun note, I'm learning how inferior Android Vine is... Good Lord, idk how you put up with it!!!    
    
    
    @aNecessary_Evil @NormFlores Wish I could be there this year!!    
    
    
    @NintendoTweet #TIL, thanks! :)    
    
    
    @TronKnotts I love Creature Comforts!!!    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd WHO?!?!?!?!    
    
    
    Here's the http://www.Dvelop.TV  review for @undeadlabs "State of Decay!" | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47spRhJVlFo …    
    
    
    @Sycoraxic98 Spam?    
    
    
    @davidsgallant Why does this keep happening? Happened with Borderlands 2 as well. :-/    
    
    
    @KittyMeeowMeeow Me! Me! 3265-5677-2904    
    
    
    @KittyMeeowMeeow Woohoo! Wil ladd you here in a bit    
    
    
    Greek Coffee? Yes please. W/ @thetanktheory @ Kostas Cafe http://instagram.com/p/bAVxz4yeb7/     
    
    
    @Hyperfludd so jealous :(    
    
    
    Someone get this woman some sleep!! RT @Pelpina This is how tired I am: I just emailed myself.    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Pre-Welcome to Texas :)    
    
    
    Been putting lots of cool reviews up on the http://www.Dvelop.TV  YouTube channel! Appreciate the views and subs! :) http://youtube.com/dveloptv     
    
    
    @MrBozon I see what you did there...    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham What on Earth do symbols above the door mean?! Have I collected everything or not?… http://instagram.com/p/bCPPjfyeRR/     
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Referring to the first door btw.    
    
    
    @JoolsWatsham Okay, so first door has everything collected then? Appreciate the response! Some things Gold vs Some Things Blue = confusing    
    
    
    @m_borgmeijer @pelpina I'm glad you like them, Morgan! Always fun to meet people with similar interests :D    
    
    
    Seriously, have any of you been outside? Because this is how I feel right now...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8hE727GTFHY …    
    
    
    @laneshill Holy hell - LITERALLY. Couldn't take it if my AC broke, I'm that spoiled. I'd cry man. I'D CRY!!!    
    
    
    @laneshill Not the kitties!! Glad it's back on.. now excuse me as I jump into an ice bath!! :P    
    
    
    @Sycoraxic98 I don't see many games at all launching in July on any platform, seeing something I'm not?    
    
    
    Finally saw the @ConanOBrien E3 segment. Asked Major Nelson to sell the XBOne & he said "The Kinect can see your heart beat" ...Really?    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Not on my worldwide trends it isnt....    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Annddd there it is!    
    
    
    Incoming Animal Crossing New Leaf rant..... So I have this stupid hippo named Hippeaux in my town.... I wanted him to move.    
    
    
    I did everything in my power - which means ignore him completely. He comes up to me finally and says "I'm leaving, just wanted to tell you."    
    
    
    So I was like "Ok, thanks." and he's all shocked that I'm okay with it. Really, Hippeaux?!    
    
    
    So he says "Nevermind, I think we can be better friends. I'm staying." DUDE! I HATE YOU! LEAVE! What kind of crap is that?! #ACNL    
    
    
    Sing it, Kapp'n!! http://instagram.com/p/bG3fgZSeYV/     
    
    
    In honor of @UndeadLabs releasing an update for "State of Decay" - here's our review | http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=47spRhJVlFo …    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz Dude I haven't seen you in at least 3-4 years. What gives?!?!?! :P :P (In my defense, I live in Dallas)    
    
    
    @RetroCR So in other words, never because the Wii is a last gen platform. Bring it to Wii U :(!!    
    
    
    @laneshill Looks great, share plz.    
    
    
    @davidsgallant Is that Ryan Stiles?    
    
    
    Hey Winston Edmondson!! Want some apple?!? https://vine.co/v/ham3IzhmIi6     
    
    
    @meRyDoon Heard amazing things about this place: http://vimeo.com/16077855   (DiFara, if you don't feel like watching that amazing mini-doc)    
    
    
    I'm sailinnggg awayyyyy... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fAAHuZ3zhjo …    
    
    
    @meRyDoon Dude now I want pizza so badly... lol thanks!! :P    
    
    
    @TedRubin @JSMeudt VIne vs Instagram is like Facebook/Twitter vs Google+. All their friends are already on instagram, so more will use it.    
    
    
    But seriously you guys, I need to sell my turnips!!! #ACNL    
    
    
    Hilarious Mickey Mouse short. Don't ask questions. Just watch it.  http://video.disney.com/watch/disneychannel-no-service-4df889ed3d82b43c9c01a272 …    
    
    
    @Kolma @Hyperfludd @Drzgamer @The_Baconbitz @KittyMeeowMeeow @kyle1point0 Does anyone have turnip prices > 150?    
    
    
    @The_Baconbitz Bummer!!!!    
    
    
    "I can't get high, I have to sing for Jesus tomorrow."    
    
    
    @Xavierstuvwxyz agree so much.    
    
    
    TIL there's a website that lets you order and anonymously send cow, elephant, or gorilla poo to someone. Freakin' internet, man...    
    
    
    I'm watching #MonstersU with 375 others on #GetGlue http://getglue.com/movies/monsters_university/dan_scanlon?s=t&ref=ArakniD …    
    
    
    @MichaelKYabs Hahahaha!!! Yesterday was rough... #NuffSaid    
    
    
    @amandablain Hey.. your tweets are starting to repeat! :P    
    
    
    Happy Canada Day! | http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=0Fn8PW-X8gI …    
    
    
    @Emi1yRogers Great game is great. Seems like the original DK game, but you have to make it through the tribute stages to really exp. it.    
    
    
    @buenothebear Perfect. Just.. perfect...    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb You don't HAVE to use 15 seconds. Can be 3-15. Also, everyone's friends are already on Instagram. Why migrate to Vine?    
    
    
    @CobieSmulders First time seeing the trailer, this movie looks great!    
    
    
    @therealcliffyb Fail. "and Jeremy Piven"    
    
    
    Manchu Blooper #1: Bless you, Rik Westerink. https://vine.co/v/haLDFYQMDvY     
    
    
    Putting Instagram's cam-stabilizer to the test. I was jogging next to the car in flip flops. Holy shit. http://instagram.com/p/bSKd5FyeWR/     
    
    
    Sizzleeeeeeee @ Mumtaz Indian Cuisine http://instagram.com/p/bSN8BCSeb8/     
    
    
    @PirateHearts Do it!!!!    
    
    
    HOLY MOLY! Amazing @VineApp update brings some awesome features!!! And it works on iOS 7 again! THANK THE MAKER!    
    
    
    "Don't try to fix it. I just need you to listen."  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-4EDhdAHrOg …    
    
    
    Thai Tea with Bubbles, please... @ Fat Straws Bubble Tea & Juice http://instagram.com/p/bUiJrMSeZy/     
    
    
    This place sounds like a  Diablo Cody movie..... https://vine.co/v/hWAF2P69qJ0     
    
    
    Excuse me sir, you're dressed like a Mario Brother. https://vine.co/v/hWA9vixOgE5     
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagram.com/p/bU8lA2yeUM/     
    
    
    No Ice Cream for Morgan Freeman..... https://vine.co/v/hWbrpKHT951     
    
    
    Portrait of JFK made up of smaller portraits of Jackie Kennedy at 6th Floor Museum @ The Sixth Floor… http://instagram.com/p/bW4piTSedx/     
    
    
    Crazy!! #ThanksPels #TeamManchu MT @Pelpina Amazing Mark & I have been working together for 1 yr! It's been an amazing year! #ThankYouMahco    
    
    
    @JonAvalon Is this spam?    
    
    
    @TaylorLumsden Ah man!  @pelpina is out of town, but I'm always game for Ice Cream! :P    
    
    
    Finally starting this show. Long overdue. #MadMen #GetGlue http://getglue.com/tv_shows/mad_men?s=t&ref=ArakniD …    
    
    
    There's a new review up on http://www.Dvelop.TV  - @TheTankTheory reviews Rush Bros |  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=C9IrNGydPRM …    
    
    
    Boom Tsh boom Tsh https://vine.co/v/hWYqXFpOzHx     
    
    
    YELP!!!!! https://vine.co/v/h77KbOBUAJH     
    
    
    Get to da choppa!!! http://instagram.com/p/bfJ80wyeXo/     
    
    
    Let's see what's going on in gaming news today... Oh! More Wii U is dead headlines? #HappyMonday!!    
    
    
    Wow, crazy Summer for Giant Bomb.  RIP Ryan Davis.    
    
    
    @kevinlamel blank tweet is blank    
    
    
    Bun Bo Hue @ Phó Tây Dô http://instagram.com/p/bhAqvayeUI/     
    
    
    Manchu Blooper #2: Poor Mark #AudioSyncProblems w/ Pelpina Trip, Rik Westerink https://vine.co/v/h7ebJbBWPH7     
    
    
    On a Train. #VineLapse #Loop https://vine.co/v/h7HDTqBn0eB     
    
    
    A beautiful moment on the train, made dramatic by a couple of people who just got out of jail… http://instagram.com/p/bkH_OISeQl/     
    
    
    @benroethig I beggeth your pardon?!    
    
    
    @benroethig Oh, the train I was riding was part of the DART system "Dallas Area Rapid Transit Rail"    
    
    
    Kidz Bop covering One Direction songs seems a bit redundant.....    
    
    
    This guy is trying WAY too hard to be justdevin but he's just not cool enough... http://instagram.com/p/bmm6ewSeYH/     
    
    
    @gunpeiyokoifan Haha tweeting for all but I definitely had you in mind, fellow Canada-phile.    
    
    
    My little sisters think this cloud looks like a pig howling at the moon.... @jenn_naay @kimberlyzamor03 http://instagram.com/p/bm-yahyedi/     
    
    
    Such a great movie.... https://vine.co/v/h72dnLAl0tU     
    
    
    I like visiting my parents because I get #ThrowbackThursday photos of this bad ass #DatSweaterVest http://instagram.com/p/booySjSeVP/     
    
    
    Man. of. Steel. #ManofSteelMovie #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1353HSR     
    
    
    @davidsgallant Summer Sale turned into Summer Salesman - "Hey, you look like the kind of guy interested in a good deal!"    
    
    
    @NintenDaan Free game? I thought you have to pay for them?    
    
    
    .n4k3dg4m3r & I shot a hilarious vineapp about wanting free Slurpees from @7eleven & getting foiled by… http://instagram.com/p/bpXRI1yeWe/     
    
    
    And that stupid circle arrow doesn't do anything, btw. This is why @VineApp needs Camera Roll Uploads :(    
    
    
    @GameplayDev 101 in my town. NotBad.jpg    
    
    
    Dem Clouds!! pic.twitter.com/FewKtYahai    
    
    
    Just remember.... https://vine.co/v/hZOaFMYU6zF     
    
    
    @swonderlin Did you see Monsters University? I loved it, Revenge of the Nerds for a new generation :)    
    
    
    Shrine of Steel http://instagram.com/p/bucE1xSecG/     
    
    
    Bat Cave http://instagram.com/p/bucNVsyecW/     
    
    
    Headed out of El Paso again, great but short little visit. To those I saw, thanks for good times and… http://instagram.com/p/buqAE6SeXq/     
    
    
    Holy Payphone Batman!!! https://vine.co/v/hZ6ZhxwwYYL     
    
    
    Crazy hearing about @CoryMonteith of Glee fame - RIP    
    
    
    @DtoidChris Hey did you end up ordering a HORI fighting stick? I have a couple review units they sent that I'm NOT using at all    
    
    
    @DtoidChris haven't heard anything specifically about the SCV stick but HORI makes amazing products.    
    
    
    @benroethig @gkdave @calilewis If anything, the sight of disgusting twinkies will only encourage her more.    
    
    
    Hey, Wal-Mart? I don't think this is a reasonable substitute for the drive-thru.... Or anything for… http://instagram.com/p/bwZqhyyeeY/     
    
    
    @digitalphil_ Yes, they're gross!!    
    
    
    @Hyperfludd I've understood about .1% of your tweets today. Why so vague? What are you talking about?    
    
    
    I can't handle the irony of this ad right now. #SpammedBySpam http://instagram.com/p/bxkGHQyefm/     
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys God speed on your quest!!    
    
    
    Mad Max: Soul of a Man gameplay trailer | https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHs0Drqp10U …    
    
    
    Found this gem while visiting the Parents. To the shelf!! #NESMemories nintendoamerica #Metroid http://instagram.com/p/bzVvy8SeZQ/     
    
    
    @LisaFoiles My condolences    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys So? Did you get Chipotle?!    
    
    
    "50's Rock 'n' Roll Radio" on Pandora is basically the best thing ever...  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ty31QY5ZGHo …    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys Woo woo!!! Looks delishhhhhhh!!! :)    
    
    
    @selenaa_dayys A Happy Stomach means a Happy You? ;)    
    
    
    @TheBitBlock It's the story that keeps it so compelling. One of my all-time fav FPS. That nightclub scene - holy shit.    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Can't set number of frames but you can use Assistive Touch to set touch length    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH I'll try to record a quick video demo of how to do that...    
    
    
    @PHIL_FISH Ok, uploading now. Hope it helps! Can also use this to do hands-free Vines....    
    
    
    @CoreySoup @PHIL_FISH Indeed! Can also use for handsfree Vines if you "record" a long press gesture. Here you go: http://youtu.be/SzckouaxRyE     
    
    
    @CoreySoup @PHIL_FISH And of course, I'm assuming you're on an iPhone - if you're on Android then I'm amazed you're using Vine :P!    
    
    
    Deus Ex: Human Revolution is 10 dollars on Steam. It's sales like this that make me wonder who would wait for the Wii U version? #sigh    
    
    
    @camsicle Haha! Poor guy, I think he had the wrong number ;)    
    
    
    Pacific Rim in IMAX 3D!! Holy shit my brain!!!!! #SensoryExplosion https://vine.co/v/hm7hJj036Bp     
    
    
    My Spoiler-Free Review of "Pacific Rim" | How are they going to make anymore movies??? Del Toro & Co. used all the CGs!!!!!!    
    
    
    Serotonin levels off the chart right now :)    
    
    
    So @innovationenvy, @normflores and I tried shooting a skit on vineapp but "An Error Occured...." @… http://instagram.com/p/b3v6UbyeaV/     
    
    
    Interrogation Room: Part 1 (See Part 2 on @NormFlores Twitter soon...) w/ @innovationenvy @ Starbucks http://instagram.com/p/b3yQQ-Sed8/     
    
    
    @benroethig Hahaha!!! Man... That was trippy....    
    
    
    