@_mattuna haha    
    
    
    @_mattuna What type of job?    
    
    
    @_mattuna Retail. Fashion. Detail what you want and I'll use some tools to see what's out there.    
    
    
    @_mattuna http://adrianclarke.org/2012/06/13/skillese-the-universal-language-ireland-ought-to-be-speaking-loudly/ … #perspective    
    
    
    CIRO pains    
    
    
    I'm too old for this nonsense #notArsedToTextBack    
    
    
    @mck    
    
    
    #siri #fierce pic.twitter.com/rsT7SCW    
    
    
    Soya yogurt covered peanuts. So wrong but so right.    
    
    
    1213 hours = 6 mins. #business    
    
    
    Reading deeply harrowing biographic memoirs on the persecution of Jews in Nazi Germany. We're not even 100 years on. Ghastly stuff.    
    
    
    @esorkaye GOOD MORNING    
    
    
    The world is a wonderful place when you meet greatly passionate people. Great morning. #PR    
    
    
    Ireland - powerhouse of talent    
    
    
    @LazBat92 Hang in there    
    
    
    @esorkaye I think ill make the second wise pub ha    
    
    
    Casually missed a pub crawl due to a deadline. Deadline 1. Adrian 0. Alcohol 0. Adrian +1M    
    
    
    @niallBADERg Ah that's not true! We  never know the impact of the things we've done sometimes. One of the beautiful things about life.    
    
    
    Reading loads of McKinsey marketing tidbits. #creativeInMeSomewhere    
    
    
    #smoothies http://instagr.am/p/TNsuXInP0p/     
    
    
    @blacknight Story with blacknight & zoho? SMTP ports not working for mail. Invoking servers not working. #SSL    
    
    
    Screw this. Going to Starbucks #productivity    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl ssssh    
    
    
    A young man as always... We need to talk about Kevin.    
    
    
    Had a dream about the LC. This is redic. Woke up wondering if I was ready for the Irish comprehension. I need a holiday.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Samsara is no 37 Dawson but you can't get a seat in there these days. #OfficeXmasPartiesGalore    
    
    
    @rachmoor getting a big walloping Xmas jumper today to force the Xmas spirit into me and radiate it to the world.    
    
    
    Cleaning is exercise too with @fagbones. #SOMETHINGNEW    
    
    
    @shaunnried Creepy.    
    
    
    Open the cassette player of the stereo (first time in years) and find this cassette! #old pic.twitter.com/raXCcD4    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Was out the other night with two old mates both mouldy. They ran after the Coca Cola lorry roaring. #Xmas    
    
    
    I have a strange feeling that tolerance will be required at some point in the next 8 hours. #wisdom    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess @fagbones Yes! Tomorrow!    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda In 4 hours exactly. And - no reason. #wisdom    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Also. Are you singing Loreen? #pretendsToBeTheWind    
    
    
    @_mattuna @pumpitlowda LOL    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I mean... tranny tears?    
    
    
    iPhone battery is redic.    
    
    
    @shaunnried Eww    
    
    
    New twitter filters for photos are kind of cool. However Instagram still home to hipster chic #onionArticle    
    
    
    Stress of Xmas shopping    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess Or in your hand in said photos 😞    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess @fagbones Delish. Ill get pastries.    
    
    
    It's at times like these you have to appreciate being a holozoic mammal.    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess leave.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Going to run it off now.    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess @fagbones 6? #pastries    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda IT ESSAY #CASUAL1ST    
    
    
    I'm pumped. #ProteinShopping #FIT13    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Stench of success    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda It's only 4k words. Get off twitter and hack that.    
    
    
    @eoinodr Yawn Ireland. #POPEisTheReIssueRightNow    
    
    
    Last night happened. #lol    
    
    
    D2B    
    
    
    @Bu_Bu_ haha.    
    
    
    Sometimes he who waits prospers. :)    
    
    
    I am a sickly boy right now. Give me all the vitamin c. :/    
    
    
    @esorkaye Eugh lemsip :/    
    
    
    @SistaSufragete Harrowing stuff - that while library needs to be refreshed with new stuff    
    
    
    Dying. Dying... Of the flu.    
    
    
    7 Lessons from Building a $15-Million-a-Year Lifestyle Business with No Loans, VCs or Angel Money http://lnkd.in/2tqfcT     
    
    
    I like that last link a lot.    
    
    
    “@bullethq: 7 Lessons from Building a $15-Million-a-Year Lifestyle Business with No Loans, VCs or Angel Money http://buff.ly/U4Mp8X ” NICE    
    
    
    Vanilla fudge makes everything better. http://instagr.am/p/TX6AbUnP11/     
    
    
    Bad sign when a recruiter doesn't call on time... #awkward #continuesWithDay    
    
    
    @bonelight "I put cheese on everything"    
    
    
    Small opportunities are often the beginning of great enterprises. - Demosthenes    
    
    
    @esorkaye I shall be convincing everyone to go to lost society tonight cos it's deadly.    
    
    
    @esorkaye Weak    
    
    
    I really should wear Xmas hats around town more. And now late for Xmas dinner. #grand    
    
    
    @POBHerty @pumpitlowda Jesus wept and intervened.    
    
    
    Panda party. Music and a half. Although Lost Society would have been a nice ending to the night :p    
    
    
    @clommy Attempting to write a global Comms strat for an SME. Reality. #2012TaughtMe    
    
    
    Another trade trip to Manchester sorted for Feb. Good start to Thursday.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Hey. Sorry was away in  the land of nod when you tweeted. Yeh how's 1pm? #delicious    
    
    
    @ISayJK This tweet made me lol. #eww    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Perfect. 🐾💁    
    
    
    @TheLiamur WUT    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I mean I any help it that you're so popular & skinny.    
    
    
    Haha #love pic.twitter.com/gIlHNZ0    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl Or not... Let'a all just be happy and continue. Or maybe sheep with kill us all?    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Evening in so, David? 😝😝😝    
    
    
    🎶"This feeling in my bones"🎶    
    
    
    I should pay @PumpItLowda  to make up for all the sleep I miss.    
    
    
    Abercrombie... Dungeon. Like the ambiance. Would be a cool club for shopaholic alcoholics.    
    
    
    @magentafeelings Making a stew?    
    
    
    Casually canning with @TweetTheFridge in a taxi    
    
    
    Check out HAILO - The Dublin Taxi App for iPhone & Android. Hail a cab in 2 taps, pay by cash or card. http://hailocab.com/tl     
    
    
    @_mattuna Someone ate them all. #soz    
    
    
    @_mattuna There are nice people. Look harder. #2k13    
    
    
    “@thejournal_ie: Over 13,000 companies set up in 2012 (but 12,708 shut down) http://jrnl.to/Tazunl ” #ahHere    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Lol. Those green bottles look so good though. #aestheticDrinking    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Heineken! 'Ken'    
    
    
    @_mattuna Open his cage this time of year. #freedomForAllWorkers    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl Order Tesco!    
    
    
    Used hailo app last night - really really handy. Also the taxi driver told me way way too much about their future plans. #gas    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl eugh still have to get the parents their pressies. #cantdeal    
    
    
    Last minute extra Xmas shopping and dinners now mean - home tomorrow! Ha    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Harsh    
    
    
    It's the time of the year when you have to look at your recruitment metrics & luckily I'm happy to say I've set a good benchmark for myself.    
    
    
    In hindsight my 2012 was pretty good. But 2013 plans are pretty frickin' incredible. #LifestyleChoices    
    
    
    Just bought @fagbones his Xmas pressie. Because he deserves one for being the best housemate ever.    
    
    
    You'd need raybans to get through dub today. Wey sunshine    
    
    
    Bumped into my old Irish teacher from Yeats. #hun    
    
    
    Frantically throwing presents and clothes into a case to make a train early. #Weyyy    
    
    
    Read this every Xmas since 2005. #tradition pic.twitter.com/wj7g6ox    
    
    
    @IrishRail Lads - Sligo 3pm service. Leave platform, return to platform. Repeat. Late by 30mins already. #refundEveryone #ridiculous    
    
    
    Adapting the gym plan given to me to include some of this. #painGain pic.twitter.com/ZWFOrrB    
    
    
    @kmckenna90 Talk to mean Feb. I have to make this work. It's an investment.    
    
    
    @bispys @laurashewcar This is genius. And so justified.    
    
    
    @kmckenna90 All ready for Xmas?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kmckenna90 in short... Gas times ahead.    
    
    
    Presumptions are bad. Nothing lost or won. Ah the joys of being 22. #ambiguousTweet    
    
    
    @JohannaClancy market bar so much better... #WhatDylan    
    
    
    @EricTebay Welcome to my world. #sigh    
    
    
    @sensiblestu I mainly like that this tweet came from "highland, highland"    
    
    
    Starting Xmas eve with a run. A run to the fridge.    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @erictebay ha    
    
    
    Sister seemed extra friendly. Asked me to fix her laptop. #TRAP    
    
    
    My fav. uncle just called me to let me know that I don't get my Xmas pressie until I come to London. #pro    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Brazil. 'Expand' your horizons. 'Penetrate' new exotic landscapes. 'Enter' the unknown. 'Push' yourself.    
    
    
    Cher Llyod needs to get the hell out of my spotify suggestions.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Get new material. #dejaVu😝    
    
    
    @johnhewittjones @scottishopera @ayoungertheatre Very good    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Fair. That's like a Script song. Same general idea new word order. 💁💁    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda What's her name? 💁💁💁--> Hun from HR    
    
    
    @johnhewittjones Life is swell John. In London for Xmas?    
    
    
    @ichewsponges You are such a loyal follower @Queen_UK    
    
    
    @ichewsponges haha- ill sort it in a bit    
    
    
    Casually scoffing pastries & Irel coffee.    
    
    
    @shaunnried who even cares? #liquidation13    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess It's pretty Delish    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @infinitejess In bulk in the new year. :)    
    
    
    @shaunnried That's what they pay me to do...    
    
    
    @NarcoDreamer What's mass? *blinks*    
    
    
    @fagbones I lol'd and have had similar thoughts many times.    
    
    
    @_mattuna I said this last year. Including the much coveted #fit12 hash tag. One year later- I'm the same but hitting up for ABERBOD13    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @_mattuna Let's talk when I'm ripped. #SXC    
    
    
    Got to hand it to J.K. Rowling. Sheila milking it in with this wonderbook stuff. #JackPot(ter)    
    
    
    Parents were introduced to Scream & Shout" on the sound system. Their faces were priceless.    
    
    
    @J_S_Klein @infinitejess @_slothgirl You're always invited. You know this.    
    
    
    On behalf of our sponsor... pic.twitter.com/Jj6JOFE    
    
    
    Ryanair - 280 quid for a New Year's Day flight. 1/6th of that two days later. #merryxmasyafilthyanimal    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda heh @lukeyzade #handsy    
    
    
    @SistaSufragete That's redic.    
    
    
    @lukeyzade @pumpitlowda Merry Sexmas. #handsy    
    
    
    Unprotected tweets from here on in. New twitter account coming on stream in Jan. #hastobedone    
    
    
    @lukeyzade You touched me.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda My little sis said the same. I blushed. Mark Little replacement.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I've started a monster.    
    
    
    @rothwelld @lukeyzade Play nice boys. #merryxmas    
    
    
    The Carlsberg ad is good for all the most obvious reasons.    
    
    
    Just back from a carolling concert with the little sis. There's 2 hours I won't be getting back. 🎄🎅🎁🎋🎉🎶    
    
    
    Casual stop over at the Pharmacy sale. #aminoExplosion pic.twitter.com/iBVQ5DBa    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @robertmilling I'll be escaping a party. Coppers after though.  #WEY #NotSoWey    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @pumpitlowda @robertmilling A great way to get rid of less promising Xmas pressies and xchange for even less promising ones!    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @robertmilling You're like the devil. Have you considered a career in sales?    
    
    
    Only 1.9 more days in Sligo ". #aww    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @robertmilling Talk to @HRhun about that. #promotion    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @pumpitlowda Wey #secretagenda    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @pumpitlowda "For it was written so..."    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @_slothgirl It's the hidden dildos in the pressure pile.    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @pumpitlowda @_slothgirl *pressie    
    
    
    @DeirdreMoran6 Pretty twitter profiler    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @pumpitlowda Oh yeh. Lots of socks. (Willy warmers)    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @_slothgirl I know no one else who so casually takes pleasure in using the s word as @PumpItLowda    
    
    
    Right. Xmas dinner round 3. *rings bell*    
    
    
    @DeirdreMoran6 Merry Chrisymas btw. See you over Xmas? 28th?    
    
    
    @DeirdreMoran6 Wey. Nice one. Well I'll see in 13'. Say hi to the cows. 😝    
    
    
    @HannahRyan10 this changes everything.    
    
    
    Have so much to sort before 2013 arrives and all the computer crash. Remember 2000? 2013. Unlucky for some.    
    
    
    @pbarreaud Merci de me suivre    
    
    
    @marmarjosette Weh weh weh    
    
    
    Sitting here helping the little sis with assignments. I can't believe this stuff actually stands as an education. #PLC    
    
    
    @JeffreyHayzlett @linkedin @salesfoundry Casually want to share those? "Global business celebrity" - oh come on...    
    
    
    @ISayJK Let me reiterate with context... Zero textbooks. Zero references. No class on 'how to reference'. Multiple essays. Zero structure.    
    
    
    @JeffreyHayzlett @linkedin @salesfoundry Isn't this the same pic from 25 days ago? #tip    
    
    
    @rachmoor @isayjk Nursing Studies    
    
    
    @rachmoor @isayjk Stepping stone... #points    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @rachmoor @isayjk Disgrace. I don't even...    
    
    
    @Sinead_Whitty Little sis... Assignments. #cries    
    
    
    @thatdanishgirl Recipe. Inbox. Right now. :p #pwease    
    
    
    Richard Branson was not the best looking chap back in the day tbf... but I guess that's not what's important now.    
    
    
    @thatdanishgirl Danke    
    
    
    @Sinead_Whitty haha. The multiplication of alcohol cells in my stomach? :p    
    
    
    @EricTebay Welcome in my suitcase anytime.    
    
    
    @ONOLiathain @templerun I got this yesterday. I'm a gonna take the advice and delete before this becomes a problem.    
    
    
    Well Xmas, its been swell. One more movie & then normality returns.    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl I'm thinking something political...    
    
    
    “@TheOnion: Obama's 19-Year-Old Son Makes Rare Appearance At DNC http://onion.com/VZiScV  #OnionYIR”  GENIUS    
    
    
    @ed_o_c Because I can.    
    
    
    •booked trains. 
•rewards with Ferraro rocher    
    
    
    Really? I had no idea. #•_• pic.twitter.com/hRy5oCd    
    
    
    @rachelbarry http://www.onlinegrinds.ie  #sorted    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I did too. It's live theatre! What's not to like?    
    
    
    Successfully worked though backlog of email and finished a marketing strat. Now to the gym & sauna. Woo #december    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Ha - I was bonding with the family. #scapegoat12    
    
    
    @rachelbarry Yup. You should. But you aren't. So let's all quietly encourage the privatisation of everything. #jokeoftheday    
    
    
    @Jack_Leahy @rachelbarry I feel the same about Trinity.    
    
    
    @rachelbarry @jack_leahy Teachers mismanaged? Also accountability? Non streamed classrooms?    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Quiet you.    
    
    
    There's something nice about having Stephen Fry reading to my ears. #audiobooks    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I have a screenshot of this for blackmail when you're in the autumn of your life (30).    
    
    
    I concur. Who are these people? They're def. not Sligo GAA players... pic.twitter.com/9GzqdaF    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda COME AT ME BRO    
    
    
    @POBHerty http://media.tumblr.com/tumblr_m9nedssS4h1qgh859.gif …    
    
    
    @bispys @irishtimes It's great isn't it? #modernisation    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda What measures? http://www.irishtimes.com/newspaper/ireland/2012/1218/1224327961339.html#FUCKOFFIRELAND …    
    
    
    Packing. 😁    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda This makes me sick.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda *moves to Norway. Bathes in oil. Fucks off world*    
    
    
    @TheOnion Too soon...    
    
    
    “@thejournal_ie: Priest sparks outrage for saying women bring sexual and physical violence on themselves http://jrnl.to/TCBODK ” #LADS    
    
    
    I'm just going to focus on business news from now on. Everything else is just top depressing as of late.    
    
    
    Off to write my 2013 goals. #S.M.A.R.T.    
    
    
    @SistaSufragete Little cousin here an hour ago. He kept crying when 'it' crooned. I took the batteries out. #scrooge    
    
    
    Driving test application for . Check. :)    
    
    
    @robertmilling @_mattuna They are people too. (Not really)    
    
    
    Ah lads. #littleSis'sAssignment #lol pic.twitter.com/wBOrQ1K    
    
    
        
    
    
    Jaysus that's a hairy man. #faircity    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @robertmilling @pumpitlowda Club hopping.    
    
    
    @shaunnried No one in my fam drinks *cough*. *Hops all the wine into various satchels*. Pauses. 'Bristol cream'? GET IN THERE... :p    
    
    
    @shaunnried There I am now after a few. http://a1.ec-images.myspacecdn.com/images02/82/bb34cf5d899741a786f35bf2b3280013/l.jpg …    
    
    
    @shaunnried I've been to the bottom of a glass. It was also nice. #wey    
    
    
    On the basis of what I've learned from ask.fm in the last 5 mins, I see a strong argument for using it in Recruitment. #LOL    
    
    
    Roysh this should be interesting. Ask me a question http://ask.fm/clarkeadrian     
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Prick.    
    
    
    Boxers or briefs? — Boxers. Pref designer. http://ask.fm/a/1mi1d2go     
    
    
    @TweetTheFridge haha. Protected tweets. Also... #lol    
    
    
    @TweetTheFridge Story there?    
    
    
    @TweetTheFridge I keep it to people I know.    
    
    
    Are you a top or a bottom? — I like to end up on top. Good to get to the bottom of crimes. Then again, that's ju... http://ask.fm/a/1mi365em     
    
    
    What's your personal motto? — Decide. Delegate. Disappear. http://ask.fm/a/1mi3cddn     
    
    
    What's your life plan? — Multiply. http://ask.fm/a/1mi39m4i     
    
    
    Really deep questions coming in #askfm    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Oh it seems a snag in the system has meant the q has disappeared. #shame    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @pumpitlowda Thanks. And don't picture things like this too much.    
    
    
    Where do you buy your suits? — Get my jacket off and you might find the labels... http://ask.fm/a/1mi59mok     
    
    
    Do you fancy anyone in Trinity? — Not that I'm aware of. I like to play away from home. http://ask.fm/a/1mi4qj9i     
    
    
    What's the oldest man you've been with? — A businessman. http://ask.fm/a/1mi5e0ql     
    
    
    What is your dream job? — I don't intend on working that long... http://ask.fm/a/1mi4nd77     
    
    
    Is there a God? — Probably. http://ask.fm/a/1mi545n7     
    
    
    What's your ideal date location? — A lounge (busy, entertaining, but not loud) for an aperitif, then food (prefe... http://ask.fm/a/1mi8713b     
    
    
    Are you good at dancing? — I like to waltz with girls - but girls need to learn not to lead.... http://ask.fm/a/1mi8gbi1     
    
    
    @PumpItLowda which one?    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda haha    
    
    
    What's the last thing you bought? — A diary. http://ask.fm/a/1mi09094     
    
    
    You scrambled his eggs? Like, you gave him an abortion? — There's places in London for that kind of thing. #neve... http://ask.fm/a/1micbej6     
    
    
    Crashing laptop. :/    
    
    
    What do you dream about? — Random things. Often foxes actually... don't know why? http://ask.fm/a/1mi08qh5     
    
    
    Right asks now old.    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl @pumpitlowda hmm?    
    
    
    @Bu_Bu_ haha. I've rejected enough Qs tonight to be labeled a spoil sport. But not answering them! Ha    
    
    
    Had just finished doing a short 15min home workout when I got asked about my gym plan on askfm. #creepedout    
    
    
    Was wondering why this mag smelt so good. Aramis sample foldout #helloHandsome    
    
    
    The power of watermelons. http://www.fatburningfurnace.com/blog/watermelon-nutrition-facts-%E2%80%93-health-benefits-of-watermelon/ …    
    
    
    Note to self, buy a blender.    
    
    
    @shaunnried Installing new apps & syncing account over and back over Xmas. #plans    
    
    
    @shaunnried Apologies to all affected. Have some complementary silence on us to ease you through this difficult time. #customerService    
    
    
    @shaunnried Also DELISH    
    
    
    WAR on BISCUITS http://www.menshealth.co.uk/food-nutrition/what-to-eat/biscuits-make-you-angry …    
    
    
    @esorkaye lol #scarleh    
    
    
    @shaunnried Another satisfied customer.    
    
    
    A Short on Dublin... Enjoy & please share. https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=TpvxG7S0rbs …    
    
    
    @bonelight Ahlads...    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda This is gas.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda If you're on the stream, the Qs are public and are listed on google. On learning this, I deleted my a/c.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda haha. I know. But we'd rat you out to the Feds. #.comLife    
    
    
    I am getting up at 6.30 so help me ***    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda I am adamant that the last bout of Qs are someone you know. Been reading back on everyone's Qs for the last 10mins. #psych    
    
    
    @shaunnried "where'd you get your t-shirt".    
    
    
    I have watched every WhiteCollar episode. I now need a similarly clever and entertaining show to watch at 2am    
    
    
    @shaunnried I've lost so many clothes this year. I hope whoever has them is happy.    
    
    
    @ed_o_c I said clever...    
    
    
    @ed_o_c Been there. I'm thinking westwing again, or possibly suits again. Anything else? #priorities    
    
    
    @shaunnried @fagbones sHnake    
    
    
    @ISayJK He's also married & has three kids by surrogacy with his partner. #shocked    
    
    
    2 hours to train time.    
    
    
    Ewww.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Hey sorry phone's charging - I fell asleep leaving music playing all night. If I don't want to what?! WAR ME.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Eugh - using twitter website (gimme a sec - *parks zimmer frame puts on spectacles, puts down gin, whets lips*    
    
    
    @_mattuna Yes. Why the hell not? #hackthesesh    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda LOL David, promise me not to over think things in 2013? I'm going out - I said I was going out, that hasn't changed. #coppers    
    
    
    Screw you trains.    
    
    
    Midnight City is the only tune I need in my ears for the rest of the day.    
    
    
    💁💁💁💁💁💁💁    
    
    
    Bought spotify premium & still getting ads. Not impressed.    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl So easy to get people's numbers :)    
    
    
    @Thayer Lots of good stuff out there. Find it ;)    
    
    
    @Jack_Leahy Kindles are great. I don't have the colour one- but books aren't colour either. #smeh    
    
    
    @rothwelld I like to have a copy just in case our dog litters.    
    
    
    Too wet outside.    
    
    
    @clommy more to life than money. But money really would buy you a fantastic New Year's evening night out. #play    
    
    
    “@UndercoverRec: The Science Behind Persuading People - http://WSJ.com  http://ow.ly/gphyH ” #skillz    
    
    
    @robertmilling WAR    
    
    
    Teeth whitening. #toDo    
    
    
    @POBHerty @robertmilling I'm arriving late. (So help me Jesus- tear my last WAR ever) and @PumpItLowda and @Ste_mcSquared & @albertorw    
    
    
    @EricTebay @pobherty @robertmilling And that guy.    
    
    
    @POBHerty @infinitejess @robertmilling Yeh - ill be at a party otherwise I'd host cans and merriment    
    
    
    @POBHerty @infinitejess @robertmilling WAR. But you know my feelings on it. Then again. WAR can be gas.    
    
    
    @jtlnrj LOL    
    
    
    @POBHerty *spend* said Jesus to Mary at the Christmas sales    
    
    
    @jtlnrj For future ref there's a tool that will auto tweet for you for things like this...    
    
    
    @jtlnrj haha. I should know by now that CS people conifer DIY for life problems. #ifonlyicouldcode    
    
    
    @shaunnried I can see there's wine in thy cup.    
    
    
    This is the latest train ever.    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl If I continue to tweet like this, I'll need a Zimmer frame    
    
    
    @fagbones @pobherty Life facts    
    
    
    Train  boredom: Ask me a question http://ask.fm/clarkeadrian     
    
    
    @NarcoDreamer @infinitejess So specific, so piercing.    
    
    
    What are the most important lessons you’ve learned in... — Always go with guy instinct. Always pay attention to ... http://ask.fm/a/1mi08pp6     
    
    
    What is the most beautiful city you have ever visited? — New York - the people and their energy make it so beaut... http://ask.fm/a/1n0q15f0     
    
    
    How ambitious are you? — As ambitious as I feel. http://ask.fm/a/1n0q9cek     
    
    
    What's your favorite breakfast food? — Full Irish- preferably one I make for @fagbones http://ask.fm/a/1n11b2d1     
    
    
    Where do you go for advice? — John Moriarty http://ask.fm/a/1n121k0b     
    
    
    @ISayJK haha. Nah.    
    
    
    What do you spend most of your money on? — Good food, socialable activities, some quiet investments & long term ... http://ask.fm/a/1n12he8p     
    
    
    What exactly is your job? All I know is that you do "PR" — Head of Global Sourcing & UK Business Development for... http://ask.fm/a/1n1485p8     
    
    
    If you could be another person for a day, who would y... — I'd love to have seen the world brought the eyes of N... http://ask.fm/a/1n13n5cb     
    
    
    Would you ever make a parachute jump? — Nearly did in the US- but had a flight from cali to NY the day it would ... http://ask.fm/a/1n16ehlk     
    
    
    What do you want to know about the future? — The precise peaks and falls pip value data for every Fortune 500 co... http://ask.fm/a/1n170bhf     
    
    
    What are the best holidays you have ever had in your life?... — Any down time spent with @jonvrushi http://ask.fm/a/1n171jb6     
    
    
    Whoever asked me THAT question- please go and find yourself a hole to live in.    
    
    
    What are 5 things you love? — This American Life Xmas episode (my fav. Podcast) http://ask.fm/a/1n17p4om     
    
    
    Where will you go on your next trip? — Edinburgh. :) http://ask.fm/a/1n188ec2     
    
    
    @_JaBuckle @robertmilling Fashion by James ladies & gents. #HURRDID    
    
    
    @NarcoDreamer I didn't answer it.    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess lol. #scissoring    
    
    
    @NarcoDreamer nah just rude & just can't be bothered with bad manners.    
    
    
    @robertmilling One word, one syllable, *thrusts into air*    
    
    
    @ISayJK @fagbones @suttonjenny Fanuary?    
    
    
    “@UndercoverRec: Top 10 Sourcing & Recruiting Blog Posts of 2012 from UK Sourcers http://ow.ly/gpkdU ” #quirks    
    
    
    @bispys It's ok. The shoes are to die for.    
    
    
    @ISayJK @fagbones @suttonjenny Roysh. Dates again? I want to clear that Friday if I can.    
    
    
    @bispys Hush Child.    
    
    
    Right, back to reading about new squats I'll never realistically do without a trainer screaming at me.    
    
    
    Just been reminded of the way people sometimes use oranges in Spar as a means of cleaning needles. #shudder    
    
    
    @clommy The fur fighters outside the fur shop beside maguires fine food emporium will be on you if you're not careful.    
    
    
    @ISayJK @fagbones @suttonjenny Grand. Thanks.    
    
    
    Just Sayin' is really clicking up the YouTube hits. #nice    
    
    
    @parchier I'll do that. And force a friend to join me. It'll be gas.    
    
    
    @fagbones @isayjk @suttonjenny Getting pissed on a plane. Always fun.    
    
    
    @fagbones @isayjk @suttonjenny Squidgy bottles    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess DM    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @InfiniteJess I dunno if these are sending!    
    
    
    Hello coffee me auld pal.    
    
    
    This ask.fm phase is looking like it's here to stay.    
    
    
    Posting in the war group page... #ew    
    
    
    There's nothing like reading drunken texts. Ah youth. *changes pass code to something very complex*    
    
    
    @JohannaClancy @nigella_lawson Yummy mummy    
    
    
    @jonvrushi What were those dates again for January?    
    
    
    @JohannaClancy *darling    
    
    
    Bam    
    
    
    Working out at home while semi-hungover listening to 80s pop. Motivated by all the sag in Wilde last night. #excess    
    
    
    I would be very content with a 911 Carerra 4S coupe. Now where would one casually find £90k.... #jinkies    
    
    
    “@thejournal_ie: The mystery of the Oireachtas member who ran up a €95 bill on one phone call: http://jrnl.to/VqWgTn ” #AhLads    
    
    
    Tonight. #2012Memories    
    
    
    "Right, 2013" http://instagr.am/p/T4s1zvHP3b/     
    
    
    “@scott_dylan: Irish Anti-Gay Commercial, What a load of crap, 7,084 dislikes and only 107 likes, says it all really! http://youtu.be/I0xOGVw3KJE ”    
    
    
    Turn ons? — Cheekiness + playfulness http://ask.fm/a/1o0a3f11     
    
    
    If you could be the leader of your country, what would you cha... — Privatise everything. Publicise responsibility. http://ask.fm/a/1o1aggcd     
    
    
    Finding gas videos in your phone the next day. #thelittlethings    
    
    
    Excited for fireworks with old friends.    
    
    
        
    
    
    #fireworks http://instagr.am/p/T8cJ6unP_O/     
    
    
    Skiing #newYears14    
    
    
    Pumped Up Kicks http://instagr.am/p/T8yYtcnP2N/     
    
    
    @InfiniteJess http://Instagr.am/p/T8yYtcnP2N/     
    
    
    Waking up at 10.20pm thinking its 10.25am    
    
    
    @POBHerty Cassidys is a cute little bar 'z    
    
    
    Tearing into 'The Barracks'. My McGahern season continues.    
    
    
    @InfiniteJess By the way https://twitter.com/inkwellhq/status/286246284631871489 … #2013realisations & thanks for last night    
    
    
    Some of the piano arrangements in Emeli Sandé's music are quite good #allisnotwhatitseems    
    
    
    Paloma Faith is all I need for the next hour. #calm    
    
    
    What is in fashion today? — Tolerance http://ask.fm/a/1odbeeh9     
    
    
    What is art to you? — That piece I saw yesterday eve passing the Apollo gallery that made me instantly smile... http://ask.fm/a/1odbhno2     
    
    
    @sensiblestu I need to stop dancing with girls. How was the gig in Inverness?    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Delighted it went down a treat. Yes for sure.    
    
    
    “@UndercoverRec: How to Use Instagram for Recruitment in 5 Simple Steps http://bit.ly/Oq8ZVc ” trying this soon    
    
    
    Writing my 2013 plans at length. God I need to get out of this city more.    
    
    
    Cleaning the apartment at 12.40am.    
    
    
    Netflix... Disappointing :/    
    
    
    @_mattuna It's ok. I hate them too.    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow @karlaherne , I'd love to hear more about what's on offer with Wayra this year. #2013projects    
    
    
    @fiachrasheil Wey. I will. I think I saw you out last night but hadn't a chance to wish you happy new year.    
    
    
    @fiachrasheil gas night. Won't be out for ages though. I need to recoup energy for life ha    
    
    
    @stephentello Will do.    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @stephentello Also Happy new year! #nearlyForgot    
    
    
    @fiachrasheil Ouch    
    
    
    After week two of January saying happy new year isn't allowed.    
    
    
    Getting up at 7am was cruel. First meeting of 2013 today. #easeYourselfIn Wouldn't want to pull anything.    
    
    
    “@ash__face: Going for a run to clear the head #keepcalmandgoforarun” Plan    
    
    
    @LinkHumans Ha    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @thejournal_ie @SineadOCarroll Oh dear...    
    
    
    “@CareerZoo1: Irish entrepreneurs generated 12,600 new jobs in the past 12 months #E&Y #irishjobs http://bit.ly/T9kqTj ” Yes they did    
    
    
    You can follow me @aidotweets for my personal tweets. Professional tweets all from @clarke_adrian. Thanks for following. #communications    
    
    
    @POBHerty Yep. It's all the things I would say loosely however with zero worries :). Also this a/c is for business. Friends are for banter!    
    
    
    Of you haven't followed @aidotweets , I suggest following @HRhun for light hearted musings on the life of a HR HUN    
    
    
    @POBHerty Yes (charity work).    
    
    
    @MKCollins88 Ah sure lookeh :p    
    
    
    @POBHerty Let's have a meeting over at @aidotweets ;)    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Just keep it to @aidotweets :) lest you want content on Recruitment / HR / PR / Business & websites that I'll be pushing    
    
    
    @sensiblestu haha #nah    
    
    
    @sensiblestu pfft. Just content :)    
    
    
    Unfollowing those who have moved over to @aidotweets    
    
    
    @Bu_Bu_ Nope- follow at @aidotweets Just this account is for professional purposes. Twitter grew since I made it. :)    
    
    
    @RosaPosa7 haha. Just @aidotweets for the gas tweets. :) and from feb it one number. The other is strictly work. And needs to be turned off    
    
    
    @jonvrushi @aidotweets :)    
    
    
    @Jack_Leahy adrian(at)canda(.ie) Always game for a bit of devil's advocate    
    
    
    @Jack_Leahy Email    
    
    
    Caption on the diary my housemate gave me for Xmas. #truethat http://instagr.am/p/UBS33CHP1a/     
    
    
    @AshokaIreland @the_wheel_irl Oh wow!    
    
    
    @suttonjenny @isayjk @fagbones Delish    
    
    
    Ireland back in the game #2013 #recovery    
    
    
    New Skype layout online is really nice. Well done #microsoft #online #comms    
    
    
    Today is comms consulting day. Casually ordering UK phones, devising Skype directs, mobile offices, & multiple CRM systems for sales teams.    
    
    
    Cracking day to be pushing the next. Bring it 2013.    
    
    
    Work hard, rest often, take time to think, breath more, organise in time, leave early, say thanks, listen loads, prioritise: 2013    
    
    
    “@Newstalkfm: Garda Siochana could shed up to 1,000 jobs http://ow.ly/gz0cZ ” Right...    
    
    
    @sensiblestu I quite enjoyed the little hearts on the 'sharing is caring'.    
    
    
    I am winning my CRM set up war #zoho    
    
    
    "Who that?" http://instagr.am/p/UJ166AnP83/     
    
    
    CRM hello again. #sundayWork    
    
    
    Eugh- long night of work stuff ahead. #notenoughhours    
    
    
    My sleep cycle and that of many going hell for leather today, is in bits. #xmasAfters    
    
    
    Push push push. #FTW    
    
    
    Writing my first app for advanced call management with pre authorised code. This is going to be a great system    
    
    
    Well 12 hours later - I'm finished developing a monster. #sales    
    
    
    10 Online Marketing Trends for 2013 http://lnkd.in/-65rAQ     
    
    
    @3online No 3G for business customer today? Any update? #dublin    
    
    
    Client cancelled. #moreCoffeeForMe    
    
    
    Booking more of the latest in #headhunting training. #excited #uk #datamining    
    
    
    @thejournal_ie Can't wait to read this. Haven't read the article yet- but any idea on who consulted on the report?    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda @fagbones @isayjk I'm between minds on Sligo for a break or it. I passed the savoy today thinking... "Tickets probs booked out"    
    
    
    Afternoon of working on Marketing & Video. #FunTimes #businessDevelopment    
    
    
    "Working hard and working smart sometimes can be two different things" - Byron Dorgan    
    
    
    You'll never understand something fully unless you build it from the bottom up, see it break & repair it.    
    
    
    "I want to put a ding in the universe" - Steve Jobs    
    
    
    Find it hilarious that the last network I checked out in the UK was Vodafone. #mightyFallen #MobileComms    
    
    
    Well pretty sure #vodafone will will die out with those tariffs #uk    
    
    
    Marianne Williamson - some powerful words. #fb pic.twitter.com/53KLVFSi    
    
    
    "Work smart, play hard"    
    
    
    Facebook Graph Search. Oh the possibilities. #recruitment    
    
    
    Life right now http://instagr.am/p/UkG8kFnP9G/     
    
    
    Much to do, much to be done    
    
    
    Great meeting with @EnactusTCD last night. #socialEnterprise    
    
    
    Sure it's be rude not to :p pic.twitter.com/BbfKAKFy    
    
    
    @TweetTheFridge bit*h please    
    
    
    Momentum... at last!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Looking forward to this! #recruitment http://lnkd.in/PVJSkB     
    
    
    @johnhewittjones @nytimes Hey John. Will give this a look in a bit. Went away from twitter for a bit.    
    
    
    Afternoon of upskilling in the latest in recruitment technology & trends. #bigData #rpo #recruitment    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Ah what a wonderful morning. #newContracts    
    
    
    Enactus Trinity meetings. #enactus #tcd    
    
    
    Tone is everything.    
    
    
    Another day working on Saudi Markets. Think #global. Think #farAway    
    
    
    Well the UK beat Ireland to gay marriage...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @blacknight Hi Guys, our smtp mail is down and our website.. Is there an issue?    
    
    
    @sensiblestu I love how I continue this saga this eve.. Ha    
    
    
    Taking a jaunt to the #careerzoo this morning in the convention centre.    
    
    
    Have a good feeling about this week #manchester    
    
    
    Work smart. Play hard.    
    
    
    Fantastic morning :)    
    
    
    Looking forward to working with a Facebook marketer #businessDev    
    
    
    @NikolaiTrigoub @isayjk It don't work like that... you have to make yourself active passive talent...    
    
    
    @ISayJK @nikolaitrigoub TeeHee #yet    
    
    
    Rapidly learning Google + an all of its applications.    
    
    
    UK #construction #market on the rise!    
    
    
    Dig deep. Plough forward.    
    
    
    Absolutely great day, afternoon and eve enjoying the company of Enactus Ireland members. Fantastic ideas shared & great concepts learned- f…    
    
    
    Really enjoyed training with Enactus Ireland yesterday on project development & social media. Great food for thought on what Enactus Trinit…    
    
    
    @gradu8ireland Really enjoyed your presentation on #social media at the@enactusIreland training event. @EnactusTCD lived your tips!    
    
    
    @gradu8ireland @enactustcd Greatly appreciated. We just might follow you up on that! Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    I get too excited about food. #CookIngUpAStorm    
    
    
    Back in the country for the weekend. #chillOut #detox #Plans    
    
    
    Beautiful morning    
    
    
    Dad just messaged me from his new iPhone... I'll get him into twitter next. #generationalDivide    
    
    
    Business, more than any other occupation, is a continual dealing with the future; it is a continual calculation, an instinctive exercise in…    
    
    
    Borocca Boost - essential kit!    
    
    
    Loving life, personal life, business & developing the next. #newPursuits #newBusinessFocus    
    
    
    Crazy niche wind sourcing again this morning. Where are these people hiding. #renewables    
    
    
    Checking email at 7am as a rule everyday has today served its purpose really well. #sorted    
    
    
    @LeHandyman exactly.    
    
    
    There's talent pipelining and TALENT pipelining. LONG day ahead #oil&Gas    
    
    
    Women are pretty great. #iwd13    
    
    
    @sensiblestu No. Also sorry for not testing back!    
    
    
    I worry about my generation sometimes. Sigh.    
    
    
    Trinity College Dublin JailBreak has seen over 80 students attempt to travel as far away as possible from Ireland within 36 hours WITHOUT s…    
    
    
    Call Coyle Group today on +44(0)1613751650 to hear of our highly competitive rates. http://lnkd.in/CZNxE5     
    
    
    @mcnulty2293 Classy. Bring it to Eyp.    
    
    
    @mcnulty2293 Please. I was never dead. I was just gathering energy. ;)    
    
    
    Courtesy will take you far in business.    
    
    
    Wonderful work being done by the UKTI team in supporting the advancement of investment from Ireland to the UK.    
    
    
    " you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change" - Wayne Dyer    
    
    
    Maynooth how are you?    
    
    
    In retrospect this week gas been pretty whopper even if I'm wrecked.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Dress in drag and spread glitter on brazilians. 🍹    
    
    
    We all want what we can't have. Sometimes however even the most optimistic thinking cannot make what you want want you. #life    
    
    
    Skype is perhaps my fav. Simple business tool.    
    
    
    Don't forget your buddies across the Atlantic. Interesting advice from Enactus supporters! #enactusChat ;)    
    
    
    @RecruiterKristi lack of GPA really? Is the right candidate always the best student?    
    
    
    @mariedromey ah ha    
    
    
    @marmarjosette Guilt...    
    
    
    @marmarjosette What good looks. #needsGymStat    
    
    
    Banter of train work...    
    
    
    I'm in love with detail.    
    
    
    Create. Create. Create.    
    
    
    Progression is the art of happiness,    
    
    
    Happy Easter all. Particularly to my uncle.    
    
    
    Don't be afraid to fail. Don't waste energy trying to cover up failure. Learn from your failures and go on to the next challenge. It's OK t…    
    
    
    Cracking Monday #workRest    
    
    
    Note to self: Steve Jobs was an intrapreneur first.    
    
    
    “@thejournal_ie: The number of people unemployed in the Eurozone is the highest since records began: http://jrnl.to/11g9fwM ” Oh Hell No    
    
    
    Pitch writing. #FUN    
    
    
    @recruitment Why?    
    
    
    Exercise will make all the difference later! #healthyTuesday    
    
    
    @ryanto86 teehee    
    
    
    Recruitin' | Developin' | Designin' | Managin' #4s    
    
    
    @darahawk The Cheek    
    
    
    @icecoldricky91 WEY    
    
    
    Loves law...    
    
    
    Howiye executive burnout. #R&Rplease    
    
    
    So many options. #ventures    
    
    
    Take calculated risks. That is quite different from being rash. - George S. Patton    
    
    
    Either you run the day or the day runs you - Jim Rohn    
    
    
    @eypfinland Enjoy. Say hi to Jari for me! #YEyp    
    
    
        
    
    
    Marketing - always fun to dip into! #ttuesday    
    
    
    Attitude not perspective.    
    
    
    Think big. Act fast. Help people. Surround yourself by success. Live your principles. Adventure often. Let go. Specialise. Be.    
    
    
    @RiyadhK Ditto #fmal    
    
    
    @RiyadhK haha. I got mine. #motherload It's good to get away from it too though. Not really. Ha    
    
    
    He says it very well: "you can't be a recruiter unless you have an affinity & empathy with people" 
http://lnkd.in/-rszeR     
    
    
    @robertmilling :8    
    
    
    PR + SocialMedia Marketing +Business Media Marketing + Business Development + Vision = the modern recruiter. Goodbye amateurs.    
    
    
    Need this weekend to figure out what's next in the life and times... #plans #ventures #adventures #Cayman #UAE    
    
    
    I will make this run happen @fagbones #FIT13    
    
    
    Getting up t 5. Going to go for a run & make plans. #bucketList. #22.5    
    
    
    Checked my mail. Offered yet another Sourcer job. They think that a "warm desk & access to coffee and snacks" are deal makers. #goaway    
    
    
    @johnhewittjones @jonvrushi   I'm going to make a trip over soon. Scotland's finest malt in return. #r&r    
    
    
        
    
    
    @stephentello The alternatives are equally #useless    
    
    
    Where's the sun? 😒    
    
    
    And now to escape the world with a book and a coffee @starbs    
    
    
    So much money being spent on the EU presidency. #hmm    
    
    
    @RosaLanghammer Sweet. You caught me as I'm just sitting down making plans. #poirfect See DM    
    
    
    @RosaLanghammer Ah yeah. Got it via EYP already. :)    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian @rosalanghammer THanks though    
    
    
    @bispys How's that campaign going? Pop a line here if you'd like anymore tips!    
    
    
    @bispys Sweet!    
    
    
    Trinity is so beautiful at night.    
    
    
    Time to get writing again...    
    
    
    Theme 1 of the next 2 months is self betterment. The betterment of the self, for the betterment of others. Theme 2 is winning.    
    
    
    @fagbones Hope you got home ok?    
    
    
    @fagbones Enjoy. #burrenBoyz    
    
    
    Morning run & it's sunny. #win    
    
    
    Wonderfully sunny day in Dublin. Time for runs, exercise and being health conscience. Sunmer is nearly here!    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Lol    
    
    
    Today is one of those exceptionally important days on our 4.5M blip. Does the world even care? #perspective    
    
    
    @fagbones @pumpitlowda #cantbreathe    
    
    
    You gotta give to get. Why do people use people? It's so rude.    
    
    
    @darahawk You got me off guard. This is my I should leave the rhetorical Qs to my personal twitter! #ha    
    
    
    I really don't know what I'd do without my CRM system #quietEfficiency    
    
    
    Incredibly saddened by the news in Boston. It doesn't matter who did it. It matters that it happened at all.    
    
    
    Busy day.
And now to chill. #bulmersOnIce    
    
    
    @niallBADERg Great for the lower systems...    
    
    
    Push it. Push it. Push it. #projectMgmt    
    
    
    @_SlothGirl haha. Currently advertising jobs on radio. Don't believe the nonsense. There are jobs. #network #digDeep    
    
    
    Digging up media contacts for a mate... The things I do. #giveToGet    
    
    
    Ought to sleep now instead of watching  videos on business, monkeys and new sourcing tech... But the monkeys are winning.    
    
    
    Another one of my recruits moved to a new project for the same client. #delighted #renewables #talentPipeliningWin    
    
    
    @GillianOH There's a girl I ain't seen/heard of in an age. How's the homemaking? #Landan    
    
    
    @GraftonMedia Ultimately? As long as they're ON social media, they're accessible. And that's all that matters. #access    
    
    
    Tender tenders. #ThursdayBanter    
    
    
    Renewable energy; a fresh & lively industry.    
    
    
    @CiaraJohnson22 Congratulations #wellDeserved    
    
    
    Everyone has an invisible sign hanging from their neck saying, 'Make me feel important.' Never forget this message when working with people…    
    
    
    @CiaraJohnson22 Very proud. Catch up soon. :) #Proper    
    
    
    Well last night is starting to come back #twistedPepper    
    
    
    Cool eve spent catching up with mum over dinner out in Sligo. #theLittleThings    
    
    
    UCD Ball. #awkward    
    
    
    @CiaraJohnson22 Announcements...    
    
    
    @CiaraJohnson22 Buying a ticket weeks in advance for bands to be announced on a certain date and then no announcement.. #awkwee    
    
    
    Wonderful day. Now to chill. #morgan    
    
    
    @james_collado @wayrairl @raomal and @dubstarts after...    
    
    
    Great day. Great eve. Great news.    
    
    
    Do the do & get the do done.    
    
    
    Will power is highest in the morning; psychologically proven. So that's all my morning premails sent. #wey    
    
    
    @lukeyzade All ok lukey? Bit sniffly myself today. #weh    
    
    
    Emailing jobvites to mates. #spreadSomePosotiveKarma    
    
    
    *positive    
    
    
    @lukeyzade :/ - yeh going to dose myself in Vit C.    
    
    
    “@irishexaminer: NEWS ... 4-year-old iPad addict gets €18k-a-month treatment | http://www.irishexaminer.com/ireland/4-year-old-ipad-addict-gets-18k-a-month-treatment-229185.html …” #RealityCheck    
    
    
    Another successful outsourcing project complete. If I had my way I'd outsource everything to the east; great workmanship; great timekeeping.    
    
    
    Ad campaign for radio I devised for a client went live today. Phone calls & candidates rolling in. #Delish    
    
    
        
    
    
    Shall be rebranding soon. #funTimes    
    
    
    “@aclinkman: @clarke_adrian I wish there was a button for avoiding any and every discussion with certain keywords” @twitter #YESS    
    
    
    Finding needles in haystacks. #UAE #KSA    
    
    
    Contracts... clause banter #notReally    
    
    
    Wind recruiting will always be my fave. Except perhaps headhunting for medical consultants - they're always good craic.    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Jaysus    
    
    
    Think I've found the niche I need to target. #summerCompanyPlans    
    
    
    Momentum at last. #Thursday    
    
    
    Daft Punk - Get Lucky (Official Audio) ft. Pharrell Williams @ndenno http://youtu.be/5NV6Rdv1a3I     
    
    
        
    
    
    This summer I'll be returning to writing webblog & my book. Except with new angles.    
    
    
    @HubSpot Lads... That actually put me off inquiring about using your system a little tbh #tweetOverload #credibility    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Enjoy th'academia    
    
    
    Market research outsourced successfully. And now I wait & sleep. #newStuff    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Baha - late night texts    
    
    
    Been a good April #metrics #linkedin #rise #keywordWars pic.twitter.com/7rd3HZjdQ2    
    
    
    @esorkaye Having flashbacks of pyg & lost soc while day dreaming. #wired    
    
    
    Yawn twitter feed full of non- issues and hypothetical scenarios. #anyHashtagToAvoidTheElephantInTheFeed    
    
    
    @mariedromey When do you move to Dublina? :p #gin&jogs    
    
    
        
    
    
    @adrianweckler For sale? #hehe    
    
    
    Opportunity knocks...    
    
    
    @jackcantillon Absolutely. But they're nothing on big data.    
    
    
    Found    
    
    
    That awesome moment when you get the match. #headhunt    
    
    
    @nialldevitt Thanks for your follow. Hope all is well at Ahain.    
    
    
    Creative day ahead. #onlineEducation    
    
    
    Actually a bit obsessed with Daft Punk's new jam. #morningTunes    
    
    
    It's May. Christ. #ShiftUpAGear    
    
    
    @sensiblestu @skynews Is this for real?    
    
    
    Getting LinkedIn Certified. #PROGRESS    
    
    
    What a morning #flying    
    
    
    Rebranding day. #banter    
    
    
    Energy buzz. #renewables #energy #power #recruitment    
    
    
    Perfect eve to chill with a bulmers and friends at the @TheWestbury    
    
    
    Love the @ireland account. Great idea. Also great picking up of username. #twitter    
    
    
    @PaulWynne12 @sensiblestu @skynews The transport pollution. #typicalScientist Come over to the dark side... We have cookies...    
    
    
    @paulwynne12 @sensiblestu @skynews Also it seems invigilating gets er'body on twitter    
    
    
    New office in 30 days. Come on June...    
    
    
    @lukeyzade Chin up...    
    
    
    @lukeyzade I actually grimaced :o    
    
    
    After hours of writing and consideration I reckon I've written one of the most cost effective candidate database building strategies. #60k    
    
    
        
    
    
    @recirp Major advantages of your qualification over others? Looking at new courses globally...    
    
    
    @ReferStar Would like to hear more.    
    
    
    New office in one month. New company in 3 weeks & one gas business partner. #consulting    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Thinking fitzwilliam square    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sensiblestu YES    
    
    
    2km run because my body hates me and I need to manage stress better. #smallSteps #cardio #overload    
    
    
    “@seamuu: Someone make me dinner please? I will entertain you and welcome you into my life with open arms” I approve this message. #wrecked    
    
    
    I'm officially cloudified. No need for a laptop or device for storage or work or processing ever again. #futureFit    
    
    
    Personal beaten this morning: German speaking wind role filled with 1 hour of work. Signed sealed delivered. #defyingTheStats #dataMining    
    
    
    KICK ass morning. And ahead on study. #exams #pfft    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ireland is full of opportunities. Global is the new local. #thinkGlocal    
    
    
    @n_bergin Howiye    
    
    
    @n_bergin Hiding. ;)    
    
    
    @n_bergin hell yeah. #banter    
    
    
    @n_bergin too cute    
    
    
    Casually studying the psychology of safety.    
    
    
    Morning coffee meet morning run. Something of a paradox there but I don't care. #healthy    
    
    
    It's 5 days into May. Time is FLYING.    
    
    
    Too early to be in an airport. #manchesterTuesday    
    
    
    Another wind recruitment project delivered on time. Wonderful day in Manchester. #recruitmentBanter    
    
    
    There's always time for a tune! Even on #Linkedin. http://lnkd.in/UNvDvp     
    
    
    @sensiblestu Steaknight?    
    
    
    @sensiblestu Right you are - wrong date in diary. Perfect    
    
    
    Rogues will always dominate entrepreneurship. They're the do it alls, the sales people, the pushers, the shovers and cross-out-the-tasters.    
    
    
    Nom nom nom #Success    
    
    
    Breakfast & emails. The only thing getting me through today is thoughts of Sushi later #nom    
    
    
    Follower requests from 82020 cabs and the Iona institute. I'll pass thanks. #wouldYouEverGoAway    
    
    
    I'd go to the gym now but well.. No.    
    
    
    Little light lunch in the Westbury & lots to et through. #germany #wjnd    
    
    
    Great people. Great opportunities. #onwards    
    
    
    @EndaMullaney Go to munch!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Innovation- the art of business.    
    
    
    Looking like another brilliantly sunny day in Dublin.    
    
    
    Seeking GERMAN speaking safety personnel in the WIND sector immediately.    
    
    
    It's a small world.    
    
    
    Google Alerts have made recruiting on a Sunday bearable. #crisisRecruits #WindEnergy    
    
    
    Watched the entire Shameless Season 11 to catch up. #shocking    
    
    
    Seeking multi-lingual individuals in the wind sector. Apply mit CV to recruit@coyle-group.com #wind #rollen #windenergie    
    
    
    Seeking Senior Principal Engineers in the UK. Feel free to drop an inmail & share.    
    
    
    Gas + Oil Engineers required in the South-East of England. Feel free to like, share or apply directly: recruit@coyle-group.com. Only 1 more…    
    
    
    Weekend- you got here. At last. TGIF    
    
    
    Gas Engineers required - UK. adrian@coyle-group.com for more info. #ukJobs #Engineering #FEED    
    
    
    New dawn, new day, feelin' good.    
    
    
    Looking forward to Breakfast with Connect Ireland... #inwardInvestment    
    
    
    I could live in London forever 😄    
    
    
    “What day is it?"
It's today," squeaked Piglet.
My favorite day," said Pooh.” 
― A.A. Milne    
    
    
    #camden #london #sunshine https://vine.co/v/hBLL9XLQBhB     
    
    
    Health & Safety Supervisors Required - Russian Speaking | UKRAINE. Email: adrian@coyle-group.com for more information. #safety #ukraine #H&S    
    
    
    Fine day for headhunting #talentSearch    
    
    
    Clever... http://lnkd.in/e7mbsW     
    
    
    @HannahRyan10 About 3 minutes. #whoHasTheTime    
    
    
        
    
    
    @HannahRyan10 Nope.
I just get up early. Get my 6 hours. #gand    
    
    
    Recruiting German speaking wind professionals. Please feel free to reply privately. #wind #energy #renewables    
    
    
    #GIS analysts required. #Ireland #spatial #esri #jobfairy    
    
    
    Looking for a new #GIS role? DM for more. #wind #windturbines #windenergy #irishjobs #jobfairy #renewableenergy    
    
    
    @josephcorr Many thanks for your follow. If you know any GIS analysts looking for a new role... I'll be a tweetin' #jobfairy    
    
    
    Planners required #ukjobs #primavera #planner #p6 #jobfairy #Shetland #leverage    
    
    
    @josephcorr Haha. Optimism right there. Took a break from the twitter machine and realised I was spending tok much time on LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Nice morning on the train. Recruiting away. More #GIS Analyst roles #wind. #jobfairy #irishjobs #dublinJobs #Offaly    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TwitterAds Any handy breakdown of rates for ads? #please    
    
    
    Smart UK hotel room will let you check in, control temperature, and order meals from your phone http://flip.it/KBbzz  #cool    
    
    
    #GIS analysts: #jobfairy #SHEQ officers #wind #SAjobs | #gas #engineers #UKjobs #planners #primavera #UKjobs    
    
    
    Late night email catchups & calendar planning. Ah the private sector.    
    
    
    Beautiful beautiful morning. Where've you been hiding Sun?    
    
    
    @robertmilling LOL    
    
    
    I'd quite like iOS7 now. Also iPhone 6. Seriously. Make something extraordinary Apple.    
    
    
    PDF meet word. #officeIssues    
    
    
    @fringePKP I don't wanna jailbreak    
    
    
    @TweetTheFridge @fringePKP I don't have android thanks but if I did...    
    
    
    @sensiblestu See you got lucky. Every time I have an issue I'm out of warranty. Adapter... MacBooks... Drives... #eugh    
    
    
    Another role filled. Time for cake. 👍    
    
    
    @MkCollins01 You've got mail    
    
    
    The art of recruitment is in creating an atmosphere around opportunities. Advertising? What a waste.    
    
    
    @EcofactIreland Thanks for the follow guys.    
    
    
    @marmarjosette You tease. I forgot I'm in GMT for a sec there.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Had a chat with a #zulu South African recruitment is a nice change. #wind #energy    
    
    
        
    
    
    Seeking #wind #crane #operators globally. #ukJobs #ukjobfairy #jobfairy    
    
    
    Seeking #GIS analysts #irishjobs #jobfairy    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @shaunnried tweetpic? #shaunsadventures    
    
    
    @shaunnried I'll just take the jet?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AlisonConnolly1 Enjoy. Would love to be there. #familyDuties    
    
    
    @mariedromey @AlisonConnolly1 Yeh g'wan. I'll be a keyboard warrior and RT them 😁    
    
    
    @InterviewIQ Thanks for your follow. Haven't had a chance to recruit in Oz yet but maybe sometime :)    
    
    
    Running #justBack #dublin #night #running #fitness https://vine.co/v/hW0n377T71J     
    
    
    Fantastic opportunities in India at the moment. #oil&gas    
    
    
    Are you a #mobile #crane #operator in #london ? Large #civil contracts on offer #ukJobs #LondonJobs #UkJobFairy #constructionJobs    
    
    
    @_moojalbahar I have work avail in London. Let me know if this is of interest...    
    
    
    @Sim0nHawkins Have some #mobile #crane #operator openings in London for a large crane operations clients. Interested mate?    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @EsriIreland #GIS #analyst required for project in midlands (#WIND) in #Ireland. #irishjobs #dublinjobs #jobfairy #GISjobs    
    
    
    @localirishbiz Thanks for the RT    
    
    
    Anglo tapes. #notAgain    
    
    
    @ColleagueRS Thanks for the follow. #teamFollowBack    
    
    
    GIS Analyst #JobFairy    
    
    
    Let the weekend begin. :)    
    
    
    It's a great day for Britain.    
    
    
    I am wrecked. #SOmuchON    
    
    
    “@thejournal_ie: You can eat in every 3-Michelin starred restaurant in the world... for €209,000 http://jrnl.to/15Tvadp ” #bargain #derp    
    
    
    @AlisonConnolly1 Weakling    
    
    
    International Energy: Renewables Gain, but King Coal Proves Stubborn Opponent http://lnkd.in/W-2FKS     
    
    
    @JenkinsGlyn Hi Glyn, I wondered if you would be interested in speaking with soonest in relation to an opportunity? #safety    
    
    
    @glyntatasafety Hi Glyn, please pop an email to adrian @ coyle-group . com to hear a little more about an opportunity in safety.    
    
    
    Privavera Planner required - Shetland Islands. Generous Package on offer. #oil #gas #planner http://lnkd.in/AJajAy     
    
    
        
    
    
    Gas Engineer http://lnkd.in/Aeeivb     
    
    
    Good morning & what a beauty she is.    
    
    
    The true art of business is not allowing things to fester. Sort it, agree it, so it, move on. :)    
    
    
    There is so much to be said for embracing change & being underwhelmed by it. #snippets    
    
    
    "Nothing in the world can take the place of persistence. Talent will not; nothing is more common than unsuccessful men with talent. Genius …    
    
    
    @clarke_adrian? g(pvyw    
    
    
    LafYg http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/7-second-meditation-daily/id667197203?ls=1&mt=8 …    
    
    
    #vvt "Relax any storyteller? It parlay in tyour mind for 5 secondstg54 . Smile."c p #gyps http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/7-second-meditation-daily/id667197203?ls=1&mt=8 …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @PumpItLowda Ah now...    
    
    
    @thedaveywavey You ought to be supporting #march4marriage    
    
    
    Infographic: The demographics of social media users http://lnkd.in/kawsjY     
    
    
        
    
    
    @PumpItLowda D Lowry! Sassy!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    What I Learned From Mickie Siebert: Put Your Head Down and Charge http://lnkd.in/g4wkAd     
    
    
    Enactus Enactus TCD http://lnkd.in/MK2sfj     
    
    
    Sometimes you just need some morning music. #music #tunes #jazz #house http://lnkd.in/TDzayt     
    
    
    Adrian:Cummins http://lnkd.in/kRQnpx     
    
    
    Now recruiting: Head of Procurement, Ireland. Consumer electronics / High Tech. adrian@coyle-group.com for direct applications.    
    
    
    Onwards and upwards.    
    
    
    @PumpItLowda #ahHaHa    
    
    
        
    
    
    WIND | Site Supervisors IMMEDIATELY required - ROMANIA, AUSTRIA, GERMANY. Email: adrian@coyle-group.com with CV ASAP.    
    
    
    Adrian:Clarke http://lnkd.in/bZKMpMv     
    
    
    Site Supervisors (WIND, Civil & Safety) - required immediately. Excellent hourly rate on offer. #Germany #Austria #Romania #jobs E.:adrian@…    
    
    
    Currently recruiting WIND & RENEWABLE ENERGY Professionals for projects in Germany. Work with Coyle Group to deliver…http://lnkd.in/bkCKHJP     
    
    
    I'm hiring! Site Supervisor - Wind (Europe) at Coyle Group | Putting People Firs - Hamburg Area, Germany #jobs http://lnkd.in/bPt6YzY     
    
    
    Self-Made Millionaires = High Self-Efficacy http://lnkd.in/bHBV7zx     
    
    
    EHS Advisor: Gas plant (construction phase) - WEXFORD. Accepting CVs immediately for consideration. adrian@coyle-group.com    
    
    
    There's some great talent out there. Delighted to represent so many skilled and professional individuals and looking forward to continuing …    
    
    
    Vacancy: Major Global Client seeking an EHS Manager [EUROPE WIDE] with Kaizen lean management experience. 8  plants (manufacturing). Please…    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hi all, this client is interested in taking on a European trained Senior Process Safety Engineer with strong HSE abi…http://lnkd.in/d5zRQmc     
    
    
    Check joy the O€G opportunities. Refinery based. ABU DHABI.
http://lnkd.in/dbakpQQ     
    
    
    A client in Abu Dhabi requires engineers (all disciplines) or refinery operations. Corrosion, safety, chemical, oper…http://coyle-group.com     
    
    
    EU Recruitment Drive: Want to work in the UAE? Have refinery and petro experience? Apply here.
http://lnkd.in/dbakpQQ     
    
    
    More live roles added today- European candidates particularly sought after for works in Abu Dhabi, UAE.
http://lnkd.in/dbakpQQ     
    
    
    Emirati woman invents car to be driven with no hands | The National http://lnkd.in/d6bX7bX     
    
    
    Expansion continues across the EMEA market: Coyle Recruitment | a division of Coyle Group. 
Oil & Gas - Offshore - Upstream - Renewables - …    
    
    
    Quantity Surveyors- 10 experienced oil & gas professionals (min 10 yrs.) are required for a $7B project in Abu Dhabi…http://coyle-group.com     
    
    
        
    
    
    Safety Manager Role: Northern Ireland (HYDRO POWER STATION). Apply to Coyle Group, now. Year long contract. E.: adri…http://coyle-group.com     
    
    
    