Arduino has arrived! Right, that's my weekend sorted...    
    
    
    @puntofisso An Italian who can't do la erre moscia? Shocked! ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso D'oh, you're quiet correct and I should've spotted that. I shall now beat myself with a copy of "Italian Phonology for Dummies"    
    
    
    @puntofisso It's the only way I'll learn...    
    
    
    More open travel data, woot! Go TfL, shame on you Network Rail... http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2011-08/05/tfl-api …    
    
    
    My first Arduino circuit... http://twitpic.com/16xqqn    
    
    
    Woo! Speakers I thought I broke two years ago now magically work. And yes, I horde broken gadgetry *just in case*. Now smug.    
    
    
    Word(s) of the Day: Riot Wombles! https://twitter.com/#!/search/%23riotwombles …    
    
    
    David Cameron wanting to shut down 'social media' during unrest just shows his utterly lack of understanding of what it is + what it can do    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Hear, hear!    
    
    
    Quietly ripping apart a paper I'm reviewing. I feel bad for the authors - but if you're going to do *that* to data, you can blame yourself    
    
    
    @puntofisso Damn.    
    
    
    @AlrightTit District 9 - Aliens and South African accents, what more could you want? :-)    
    
    
    Waiting for yet another delayed MK bus on the way to @StationX at #bpark . Need a car. This is getting silly.    
    
    
    Cipher book used for secret WW2 communication at #bpark http://twitgoo.com/k6o0l    
    
    
    @Documentally Thanks for the welcome, and good to meet you earlier! See you at the next @StationX at #BPark    
    
    
    @sleicester @StationX is the social media Tweet-Up that happens once a month at Bletchley Park #BPark - come along!    
    
    
    @Retrophile Nope, just forgot to remove it :-) Currently hunting down LCD/LED arrays and wireless connectivity options on eBay - any advice?    
    
    
    @Dr_Black #BPark never fails to intrigue, educate and generally make me feel proud to be geeky :-)    
    
    
    Getting freaked out at how much of my house I can see in Dorset. I can see in in the back window! Into the kitchen! Why Google, why?!    
    
    
    Have I started my first Twitter trend with #Proud2bGeeky after my day at #BPark ?! Not yet you say? Well, we've got work to do then...    
    
    
    "the plural of anecdote is not data" ... @bengoldacre's Bad Science gets quoted at #wherecampeu (via @vicchi)    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Nah, proper research has to have number and graphs, otherwise how do you get a computer to do it for you? ;-)    
    
    
    Maplins has everything it seems (except the components I went in for of course) http://twitgoo.com/kbygx    
    
    
    Just had first wet shave in about a decade - injury-free too. Could get used to this smoothness...    
    
    
    Ahh, I can almost hear the Hadoop cluster chugging away on the other side of the Atlantic, processing my data...    
    
    
    Just realised the date. Beware the eyes of Mars!    
    
    
    Beginning to really dislike the personalised Ask-an-animated-avatar services some companies put on their sites. Usually useless.    
    
    
    UK citizens to be disconnected from the net without any due process. ORG explains what you can do: http://bit.ly/9t4aTO RT! via @tomcoates    
    
    
    Same day response from my MP (Mark Lancaster) re: #DeBill. Pleasantly surprised. Let's hope he can turn his supportive words into actions.    
    
    
    @9600 It's like Hello World in optoelectrical form    
    
    
    Just had the plumbers in to fix immersion. Much breathing-in-between-clenched-teeth and general tutting. I see expense on the horizon.    
    
    
    @40_thieves This was the machine I inexpertly waxed lyrical about during the #BPark tour the other day: http://is.gd/aNkkH (link via @9600)    
    
    
    @mqtran Congrats on the paper acceptance!    
    
    
    @mqtran That'll teach me to read Tweets more carefully!    
    
    
    @ChristianHambly Impressive! Bon appétit...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Whenever I try putting usernames in it reports the same period (23-07) always calculated on exactly 0 tweets (at bottom of page)    
    
    
    @puntofisso OK, it 'works' if I use refresh link at bottom of page. You sleep between 1pm and 9pm?!    
    
    
    Alice in 3D was good, but not stellar. Would probably have been easier on the eyes in 2D, didn't take full advantage of that 3rd dimension    
    
    
    About to make the mistake of going to supermarket on an empty stomach. Will attempt to resist cake.    
    
    
    Best Glee quote ever: http://tinyurl.com/yfkex73 Sue Sylvester Rules.    
    
    
    If I were a terrorist, the last place I'd want to try and attack would be this one: http://tinyurl.com/yl2dr38    
    
    
    Finding this frequency monitor weirdly hypnotic http://tinyurl.com/ykez43f Is it wrong I keep wanting it to edge past either legal level?    
    
    
    Just received a 419 purportedly from the UK House of Lords offering FIVE HUNDRED THOUSANDS UK STERLING. Well, I *assume* it's a 419...    
    
    
    I may never go on a motorway again: http://tinyurl.com/yk72ycx    
    
    
    @barnstormed I was trying to guess what the moniker would be before your second Tweet, and it seems I guessed right. I see nappies...    
    
    
    @gridinoc Want to borrow mine? I got my kit a fortnight ago...    
    
    
    Much of my daily work is just fiddling with massive text files, formatting, reformatting, processing. Surely a machine should be doing this!    
    
    
    Today I shall strictly enforce my To Do lists. Things 'Will Get Done (tm)' and I shall feel achievement. That or curl up in a ball and cry.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Interesting!    
    
    
    @puntofisso I merely added it to my 'toRead:toDO' sublist and assigned it an appropriate priority level ;-)    
    
    
    At #mediaeval2011 in, appropriately, a mediaeval convent in Pisa. Placing Task overview presented, now enjoying other tasks...    
    
    
    Hard-Fi. Suburban Knights. Office escapism.    
    
    
    I do not recognise this version of Milton Keynes. Nuns? Woolworths? http://tinyurl.com/yh4e7vh    
    
    
    Sue Sylvester on 'Sneaky Gays'. Brilliant. http://bit.ly/dpvgqf (via @ahj)    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Or it says that the International Conference on Science Essay deadline is April the 6th ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso Garage Band is very handy for such projects    
    
    
    Using maps to visualise where stuff comes from and how much carbon it costs: http://www.sourcemap.com/     
    
    
    Note re: Yahoo! Maps Web Services, shut down is on the 13th September http://developer.yahoo.com/maps  Check out http://api.maps.ovi.com  The King is dead etc    
    
    
    @Carter_AndrewJ I'd recommend a +4 Mace of Biting Satire.    
    
    
    Eek, just gave a presentation to the Vice-Chancellor of The Open University. Heart was pounding. Fortunately a friendly, knowledgeable guy    
    
    
    @andycodling Keep going, you can do it :-)    
    
    
    @bletchleypark Can #bpark get one of these and let me play with it pls?:-)Wonderful demo of a real Turing Machine http://tinyurl.com/ygd4mhz    
    
    
    @qikipedia Surely that should be "More than 90% of computers hackers *who get caught / brag* are male." :-D    
    
    
    Lunchtime at #ECIR after an interesting morning on machine learning in information retrieval    
    
    
    Completely pooped after long day at #ecir2010. Great keynote by Barry Smyth, social search is officially hot stuff. Phew. That's reassuring.    
    
    
    Multimedia and interaction analysis personal highlights for me today at #ecir . Looking forward to conference banquet tonight at #bpark !    
    
    
    I know I shouldn't be so shocked, but easyJet charge €16 for using a Visa card?! On what planet is that fair trading?    
    
    
    #bpark was perfect conference venue for #ecir banquet last night. Thanks to the guides who gave tours, and organisation staff, great job!    
    
    
    @vicchi Will there be @w3gconf stickers à la WhereCampEU to adorn my rather plain looking laptop? :-)    
    
    
    @vicchi Excellent - just found out some of the stickerage will be Y! stickerage. I shall be geo branded to the hilt...    
    
    
    Looks like #w3g is shaping up to be a great (un)conference, only a few days to go!    
    
    
    Attempting to cope with post conference deluge of stuff that has been on hold this last week. So. Many. Emails.    
    
    
    @barnstormed I evidently work on the wrong floor.    
    
    
    "Bow ties are cool" #opendata from @madprof and the battle to release data at #w3g    
    
    
    Geo apps development, the potential and challenges at #w3g , many of which couldn't have been made without #opendata    
    
    
    @rollohome one word: Harsh ;-)    
    
    
    @rollohome I'm seeing a healthy market for t-shirts with "I'm a flippant geographer" on them... #w3g    
    
    
    @rollohome @vanessa_murdock All in the name of geo science, naturally ;-) Great to meet you Rollo, until the next time!    
    
    
    The Inbetweeners marathon via 4od. Good stuff.    
    
    
    @puntofisso UK/EU having financial problems too, have UK/EU developers/orgs made better job of showing value of open data perhaps?    
    
    
    @puntofisso That's a key point, governments and their auditors aren't great at quantifying social benefit and indirect financial benefits    
    
    
    My 3 year old Macbook Pro is beginning to feel the strain. Time to find a pre-end-of-tax-year budget I can plunder for upgrades.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Echoing a comment on there, gov.uk seems to have forgotten there's more to the UK than just GB. Horrific kerning too!    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Exactly! Tired, unimaginative old themes with nothing to differentiate it from almost everything that has gone before...    
    
    
    @andywasley @sosogay Well done guys!    
    
    
    Either I've stumbled onto the set of Shaun of the Dead 2 or I'm watching commuters heading into Milton Keynes rail station before 8am on a d    
    
    
    Well Barcelona, I'm not impressed with this so-called weather you seem to have at the moment. I expected an actual change from the UK!    
    
    
    To use "themself" or not to use "themself", that is my current grammatical dilemma.    
    
    
    @joshspero How about in the phrase "This is the first step in helping someone to help themself"? If one is trying to be non-gender specific?    
    
    
    Have got to the stage of pre-deadline-experiment-running when I wiggle my fingers at the monitor hoping for H. Potteresque magic to happen    
    
    
    One paper submitted on Sunday, another due on Wednesday. I'm sentence forging like some crazy wordsmith.    
    
    
    Getting confusing signals as to exactly which constituency I'm in after recent boundary changes. Can't find authoritative source #ge2010    
    
    
    Just realising very few of my clothes actually fit properly. I appear to be unfortunately clownish today. Must remedy.    
    
    
    I like my typographical ligatures, but can I get away with "æsthetics" in a science paper?    
    
    
    Seems my local MP said one thing to me in email regard #debill but instead of voting against, merely didn't turn up to vote at all.    
    
    
    Excellent news for Bletchley Park! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-beds-bucks-herts-15171726 …    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Sounds like wise advice to me, and as it's serif, I'm gonna risk it...    
    
    
    Wait- THAT'S Justin Bieber?! THAT'S what all the tweens are swooning over? In my day we'd have wedgied him clean in half. (via @MitchBenn)    
    
    
    Dear Icelandic Volcano, could you ensure you don't belch forth too much ash mid next week as I'd like to get home in one piece, kbaithnx    
    
    
    Slightly Bond villain-esque approach there Iceland. Using a volcano to hold the UK to ransom over a few little banking issues...?    
    
    
    Bad Science Alert: You can't fairly compare between ranks with different members, changes between 2000/9 r meaningless http://bbc.in/h5yevW    
    
    
    Hmm, current phone giving up the ghost, so, iPhone 4[s], Galaxy S II or maybe the Nexus Prime?    
    
    
    Recognising inspirational women in science, maths, tech and engineering - it's Ada Lovelace Day, who are your geek heroines?    
    
    
    It seems gov.uk thinks that "homeoffice.gov.uk/agencies-public-bodies/ips/" is more 'accessible' than "ips.gov.uk" http://www.cabinetoffice.gov.uk/news/hundreds-government-websites-closed …    
    
    
    UK gov saves £1.7m by moving content from multiple domains to one? How much were they paying for domains?! They control .gov.uk anyway no?    
    
    
    @oobr Do you happen to know of open access data set for Barcelona Bicing network? I'm prepared to scrape, would rather reuse...    
    
    
    @oobr Cool, thanks!    
    
    
    @RealBillBailey May I join you? Am stuck here also. Have my own spade and extra baggy trousers with string around ankles.    
    
    
    Seems my magical ability to fix set of speakers by not using them for a few months strikes again. I'm good. Very good. The power is scary.    
    
    
    Getting back into the local swing of things with a siesta. Feel rejuvenated!    
    
    
    Weird, I'm a bit ambivalent about the idea of getting an iPad, yet last night I dreamt I had one, although it appeared to be running WinCE    
    
    
    @gregorybradley I went with the aesc/ash as, ultimately, on balance, taking all things into account, I liked the look of it in this paper:-)    
    
    
    @vicchi My attempt after consultation with an Icelander sounded more like Ear-Full-Of-Yoghurt and so shall it hence be known    
    
    
    Arg. Likelihood of me getting back to the UK tomorrow look increasingly slim. If I don't make it tomorrow, unlikely to return before weekend    
    
    
    Borrowing an Apple Magic Mouse for a bit. I want one of my own now. I really want one. It loves my fingers. If only it were cheaper!    
    
    
    I have, thru prayer to the mighty Ear-Full-Of-Yoghurt, managed to get back to the UK! Plane v. late and half empty, but got me home. Phew.    
    
    
    Everyone vote #LibDem and @Nick_Clegg to make Murdoch Lose Britain (please RT to help boost TT)! (via @carter_andrewj)    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj @marcdonnchadh That tweet was so cringeworthy it's given me a heart murMur, Doctor! 

Yep. Bad, very bad. I'm sorry.    
    
    
    Having to use MS Word for writing a scientific document - utter miserable pain...    
    
    
    Hearing Nick Clegg referring to the "old parties" was telling and subtle enough not to seem too rehearsed. #leadersdebate    
    
    
    Cameron: attempts to sound tough let down by waffle. Clegg: eloquent, talking sense. Brown: better than before, can't make up for 13 years    
    
    
    The deluge of stats regarding who 'won' the #leadersdebate just go to show you really can't trust any one brandishing figures. *shocked*    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Good point, so, both new, trendy and  different whilst also having an established pedigree? :-)    
    
    
    Oh I pity the souls of Customer Representatives who have to deal with me when I'm feeling righteous. "System says no" isn't a valid response    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Good on you - we need to overcome our British sense of not-wanting-to-cause-a-fuss more often...    
    
    
    @jussikarlgren Thru TV debate he's been shown as viable 3rd option, private media now on offensive showing their ties to other parties    
    
    
    Twitter really is small-world, yet more people I didn't realise knew each other messaging. @puntofisso and @PaulDJohnston, I'm looking at u    
    
    
    @Jules_Carey @AliceMorrissey Does the MP profit from this seminar? Surely this info should be freely available and not kept behind paywall    
    
    
    @puntofisso Most kind. Does this mean I have to start making my Tweets interesting?    
    
    
    Just preparing for RIAO2010 in Paris. Printed out Metro map as reminder. Exceedingly pretty. This is what colour printers were designed for.    
    
    
    Just had a colleague attempt to close our open IM conversation by typing 'exit'. At least he didn't try to sudo kill me...    
    
    
    Helping friend with removing comments from a Word doc before sending off. Disliking Word more and more every time I have to use it.    
    
    
    39 #Commonwealth nations make being #LGBT a crime, take a stand with @CommonwealthSec Sharma: Sign now! t.co/HgcVtEs6 #chogm #lgbt #pride    
    
    
    @puntofisso You're welcome ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso I did think it was unusual Y! were sponsoring you to go to the Olympics...    
    
    
    Just seen the last in the current series of Spooks. Absolutely brilliant. Alice Krige, Nicola Walker and Peter Firth, my hat off to you all.    
    
    
    Arg. Must learn to pack the day before an international trip. The blizzard of socks and underwear in my living room is not gonna end well...    
    
    
    I forget just how quick, easy and pleasant using Eurostar is. Glorious mes amis, and far more civilised than flying.    
    
    
    @9600 I'll now be closely inspecting kilts whenever I see them just in case they also have Morse encoded messages in them...    
    
    
    @9600 Have you looked at the (admittedly somewhat buggy) www.qwerted.com for an alternative to the Android onscreen keyboard?    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Sorry to hear that, hope it fixes up quicker than expected.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I'll believe it when I see it. Funny how closed-source, proprietary options get chosen when massive IT companies are involved.    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Still can't *be* a Catholic though. Or, for that matter, when all things are said and done, elected.    
    
    
    @threedaymonk Surely it was the extra X chromosome that precluded people in the past?    
    
    
    @threedaymonk Nah, I think a wet Friday afternoon inadvertently switched on my Pedant Mode...    
    
    
    @iaindodsworth @puntofisso "I'm sorry Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that."    
    
    
    Learning the intricacies of the stats package R on a weekend? That's how thrilling my day has ended up to be…    
    
    
    Ah, good. Just found the number of cups of coffee to make my brain go mental. Noted. Coding pretty quickly though...    
    
    
    This Bank Holiday will mostly be full of lawn mowing, report writing, GIT familiarisation and catching up on email. What, this is a holiday?    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Luxury? In my day we had to nibble the grass with our teeth while Dad thrashed us with broken bottles - if we were lucky!    
    
    
    Just discovered that the fleet of BT OpenReach vans in my streets actually *are* laying fibre optic cable! Should be ready by June! Woo!    
    
    
    John Cleese on proportional representation http://bit.ly/lq6FE plus c'est la même frickin chose, was 1/4 of a century ago (via @bengoldacre)    
    
    
    @barnstormed According to the Lib Dem leaflet through my door they've done Walnut Tree, will do Walton Park and Kents Hill next    
    
    
    @barnstormed I've only heard of those 'areas', and BT are usually useless at providing information on this kind of thing to consumers    
    
    
    “Europe's Web of Debt” (NYT) http://nyti.ms/aiHvZ8 — Greece is tiny! (via @gridinoc) Can we have our cash back now then please you five?    
    
    
    I agreed most with Peter Jones (Liberal Democrats) in Milton Keynes South - how about you? http://bit.ly/9MRs6t @democlub #ge2010 #MKS    
    
    
    Either my ear-muff-like headphones have shrunk or my head has got bigger. Neither possibility is good. I'm top heavy as it is.    
    
    
    Actually interesting insight into colour perception and labelling from the forever humorous XKCD: http://tinyurl.com/32hppy7    
    
    
    @lmontrieux 2. I've only just started drinking the stuff... I know embarrassing!    
    
    
    Interlingual dodgy pun for Swedish readers: Jag måste skaffa en katt, och den ska heta Pejst. Katten Pejst. Så humor! (via @brokep)    
    
    
    Passive sentence of the day: "The United Kingdom Independence Party (UKIP) said the remarks were regretted." By whom, one wonders.    
    
    
    @Documentally I've got meetings tomorrow that I can't shift, but I'll be @StationX at #BPark in spirit if not in person    
    
    
    Dear UK Twitterverse, whoever you vote for, do it because of policy, don't feel you have to be tactical, but most of all, just do it.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Apathy in the face of a broken system methinks, perhaps this time we can nudge it all in the correct direction    
    
    
    @HRBeaman Sorry for the delay, but ta very much! It's such a relief to have gotten through it OK    
    
    
    @markiliffe Hey Mark, sorry for delay, what kind of "context information" do you have in mind? Is this for media collections like imgs/vids?    
    
    
    @markiliffe Try http://research.yahoo.com/pub/3490  as a good start, email me if you have any q's / need more pointers. Perhaps words in SMS~tags on photo?    
    
    
    That last tweet was shameless self-promo, but, well, that kind of thing doesn't happen to me every day.    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Just this Friday gone. They even gave me a complimentary prescription pad and stethoscope. I didn't say anything.    
    
    
    @barnstormed Have fun, I saw it a couple of nights ago, enjoyed it :-)    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Aww, thanks Alice! I should get business cards with that exact title on :-)    
    
    
    20% of the vote gives LDs 9 seats, but 30% gives Labour 76?! Stupid bloody system.    
    
    
    Like to wake up to a breakfast of change with a perhaps a brunch of actual difference-to-the-way-this-country-works. Perhaps I'm optimistic    
    
    
    @john_goss Well done John, we may not be members of the same party, but I applaud your efforts nonetheless :-)    
    
    
    If the majority of the country vote for left-wing parties. Should the country be ruled by a right-wing party? (via @carter_andrewj)    
    
    
    Arg, there exists no tea strong enough to make me feel better about the #ge2010 today. Must be patient and wait for negotiations to happen    
    
    
    The one upside of a Liberal-Conservative coalition would be watching Americans trying to fathom the very concept. (via @MitchBenn)    
    
    
    @puntofisso In some countries I think that would count as cruel and/or unusual punishment ;-)    
    
    
    Rocketing through the damp and luxuriously verdant MK cycle paths on my bike on a Saturday afternoon with loud music on flippin' rules.    
    
    
    Colleague has just shown me how accessing one 12-page article from 1976 online might cost her £805 due to copyright buy-out of publisher    
    
    
    Excitedly downloading Android 2.1 update for my Milestone. Hoping the bugs in other EU releases have been cleared up in the delayed UK one    
    
    
    Every time I look at George Osbourne, I see this: http://imgur.com/o0aYE (via @threedaymonk)    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Is that Ubuntu Netbook Remix I spy? Have you heard about the upcoming Unity version?    
    
    
    Fixed my experiment, analysed and got new results, results look reasonable. Adam is cautiously pleased.    
    
    
    In those slightly eerie minutes when this country doesn't have a Prime Minister. Mere moments betwixt Brown and Cameron.    
    
    
    Heading to Liverpool on the train, seems to be getting damper the further north I go - is this normal?    
    
    
    Liverpool was lovely, sun even shone. Dockside very nice, RC cathedral beautiful, company great :-) Now back to MK...    
    
    
    @vicchi Do these 'clumsiness' incidents happen to coincide with or near the release of new iPhone models at all? :-D    
    
    
    @osbornec Hey Chris, are you OK? A&E!?    
    
    
    Gay marriage among "most insidious and dangerous challenges"? What a bitter world view the Pope has. http://bit.ly/coAWIK -via @threedaymonk    
    
    
    @osbornec Glad things are OK, must have all been very stressful...    
    
    
    Planes, crash tests, Tony Vickers, aerial image analysis, all based on the work involving Alan Turing and @bpark http://tinyurl.com/24qgu8q    
    
    
    Seems my new 20Mbps broadband connection is giving me 160Kbps at the moment. Broadband, this is not. A week on the phone to ISP beckons...    
    
    
    @ch_koula (From the tovima article:) «πνεύμα της περιόδου 1999- 2004» Where things better back then? What was different?    
    
    
    Just realising the full extent of Aperture 3 and Flickr integration - metadata kept in 2-way sync once uploaded? Potentially brilliant    
    
    
    Off to #bpark to practise tour guiding.    
    
    
    @puntofisso My pleasure! I'd even give you a personal guided tour if you like :-) I can practise on you...    
    
    
    Back from #bpark after shadowing an excellent tour and wondering around with my notebook and camera. Still have only scratched the surface.    
    
    
    @puntofisso None whatsoever ;-)    
    
    
    Interested in doing a research internship at Yahoo! Research Barcelona? Check out details and testimonials here: http://barcelona.research.yahoo.net/internships     
    
    
    @ch_koula Sounds like the goal posts are always moving. And did I read right, one guy thinks diplomats keep it going to keep their jobs?!    
    
    
    If you have dusty old valves in your attic, contact the #bpark team. Even incorrect ones can be swapped for right ones, so send 'em in    
    
    
    Mmm, miso soup is like mild Bovril. Without the week long after taste.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Insidious use of the Rule of Three Adjectives. Henceforth PM should be referred to as heartless, right-wing and cruel to balance    
    
    
    @puntofisso Hear, hear! Less point-scoring empty rhetoric and more substantial debate :-) So, now for a plan to change/improve things...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Would I get fed local food? It might just be worth it ;-)    
    
    
    @Documentally I think wearing shorts and sandals at the OU is possibly mandatory, at least judging by late night 70s TV course programs!    
    
    
    Arg, office coffee machines has turned into a lava-dispensing machine with cups that are two sizes too small *sucks scalded fingers*    
    
    
    @seo01 I'm thinking a combination of Prolog and (Microsoft) Seadragon perhaps?    
    
    
    I think @gotofdn and @Raspberry_Pi should get together for another BBC Micro style revolution in UK comp-sci education    
    
    
    @J_JKMi Hey Jen, going well thanks, lots of work, but great lab, lovely people and a bit of sunshine :-) How's KMi doing? Had enough snow?    
    
    
    @xan1112 I think ISPs should be forced yo give minimum service level agreements. No other kind of company can get away with such flam.    
    
    
    Undecided on Olympic mascots. Like the logo they have no major British connection. The cameras for eyes thing is a tad creepy. Swooshy tho.    
    
    
    Lol, quote form BBC Message board re: olympic logos "Are they the result of an unfortunate smelting accident involving Sonic and a Pokemon?"    
    
    
    gov.uk buying into the Myth of Anonymity while selling off valuable, private medical data http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-16021240 …    
    
    
    Absolutely loving the Apple Magic Mouse - 'tis a thing of beauty in my hand. Do keep trying to middle click though.    
    
    
    Having emerged from my glorious duvet cocoon I set forth and hunt brunch and tea...    
    
    
    Cycling down the Grand Union canal in tbe sunshine with mates, stopping off at pubs along the way - utterly glorious    
    
    
    Have now seen Parliament opening, hung out of window of Westminster Palace to see Queen. She waved. Prolly not at me.    
    
    
    Been following the debate on the civil partnership related bill in the House of Lords via @andywasley - thanks for the rolling updates!    
    
    
    For fellow colour theory geeks: Excellent post on generating perception based equidistant scales - http://vis4.net/blog/posts/avoid-equidistant-hsv-colors/ …    
    
    
    Actually, that blog is generally fascinating throughout... http://vis4.net/blog/     
    
    
    @markiliffe Could well be, if the publisher controls the copyright for the paper (as is usually the case). Unfair and needs to change    
    
    
    @markiliffe *Some* publishers allow "pre-prints" 2 b hosted on researchers own sites, effectively same paper but accessible, see small print    
    
    
    @markiliffe A worthy endeavour I support! Difficulty is, current high impact venues are from big publishers, "impact" value needs to evolve    
    
    
    Arg, complicated Spanish grammar screwing with my brain- need a decision tree to help decide when to use the subjunctive in different tenses    
    
    
    Dear DBWorld, can I have a digest of your near daily 2600 line 'digest' email please?    
    
    
    Flippin' stunned by Cameron's speech on how the UK is a "Christian" country - the one I'm a citizen of bloody isn't http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-politics-16224394 …    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Still in Spain, tho goings on at home are making staying around here more appealing…    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Also, I'm good thanks :-) My German stopped at GCSE unfortunately, haven't had much chance to use it recently.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley I'm a fan of continental adventures :-) Go for it! Should be in Ldn around NYE, details TBA, in Dorset a few days before    
    
    
    Spread the word!  Vintage Computer Festival at The National Museum of Computing at Bletchley Park 19 & 20 June #bpark #tnmoc (via @linjones)    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Please do let me know if you're around en España :-) Enjoy the holidays in the meantime...    
    
    
    OK, dignity be damned. Who's having a Eurovision party this weekend?    
    
    
    @vicchi Best of luck in the future Gary! Onwards and upwards...    
    
    
    What happens when the coffee machines breaks down in KMi?  http://twitpic.com/1rs1vo    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Do the diaspora help elect the Irish President at the moment? Who counts as 'diaspora'?    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh I should have realised your thesis would be the go-to place for answering that question :-)    
    
    
    Prbly not a good sign that the review I'm doing for a journal paper is almost as long as the paper itself. It's not full of effusive praise.    
    
    
    Woo, first stage invasion at #eurovision. Though with the get-up the dancers were wearing, was hard to tell.    
    
    
    Eek, lots of booing at Russia tonight at #eurovision    
    
    
    Sniff. The rest of Europe really doesn't like us, does it. #eurovision    
    
    
    @ch_koula *I* like the rest of Europe, even if they didn't vote for us ;-)    
    
    
    @ch_koula Very true, though when has Eurovision voting ever been about the songs? *cough* Cyprus *cough* Greece *cough* The Balkans ;-)    
    
    
    Had a fiddle on the iPad at MK Apple store. Very pleasant. Typing perfectly achievable. Bit underwhelming. eBook reading better on my phone    
    
    
    Arg! The Red Sock of Doom managed to get its way into my white wash. Now have a lot of pink clothes. Can I save them?! I can't pull off pink    
    
    
    @nanubrown I don't even remember buying them! It just spontaneously appeared in my wash, dying everything to salmon pinkness...    
    
    
    @barnstormed Lens cap left on? ;-)    
    
    
    Learning Spanish idioms from fellow KMiers while trying to describe the Google Prediction API    
    
    
    Last night I dreamt I woke up with a Ptarmigan on my pillow - symbolic I'm sure, but of what, I've no idea.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I got a rather nice book cover poster in the main BL shop recently, but the map one also looked pretty cool    
    
    
    I'm on YouTube! I feel so Web 2.0 : Talking about #mediaeval 2011 evaluation forum and the Placing Task I helped run http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vDmNyLvrQXE …    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet On a similar theme, you may like Eivør Pálsdóttir    
    
    
    Completely missed the PM being only metres away from me at the OU. Need to watch Twitter even more closely in future.    
    
    
    Welcome to the War on Debt? RT @shbib: National Debt is the new terrorism. #ou_pm (via @Documentally)    
    
    
    @sleicester Have you been following developments on http://data.gov.uk/ ? Mashupalicious.    
    
    
    @sleicester Hear hear!    
    
    
    @barnstormed There's a tutorial online somewhere on how to turn a normal SIM into a micro with the aid of accurately placed cleaver...    
    
    
    @alexispetridis @marcdonnchadh Wikipedia suggests "Leicesterian" under demonym  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leicester     
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh It sounds like the typical transformation of a description into a label that people then feel no longer describes them    
    
    
    I'm liking Safari 5's new Reader mode. A cunning response to other web browsers' ad-blockers?    
    
    
    @StationX I'll be there at #bpark for the next StationX too - see you then!    
    
    
    @cabinetofficeuk @foreignoffice Or less than one functional QE-class aircraft carrier?    
    
    
    Arg, rewriting this darn paper for the third time, come on man, focus!    
    
    
    Woo! Paper submission deadline extended. It's always the ones I was actually prepared for that get extended though, and never the rest...    
    
    
    @clarkalastair Just because it's in their T&Cs doesn't mean they can remove your right to return, might be worth checking.    
    
    
    Busted coffee machine http://twitpic.com/1va5mk (via @hockeyshooter) Ah, KMi. Home of the geeks.    
    
    
    I utterly adore my new Fatman Red-i valve amp. I keep glancing at it and smiling with electronical/audiological glee :-)    
    
    
    @gridinoc @kidehen @iand geonames.org may help, not sure if there is a SPARQL endpoint tho    
    
    
    @kidehen Cheers, thanks for the info    
    
    
    Doing an emergency proof-read of a friend's paper - let's hope Mr Red Pen doesn't have to used as much as Mr Green Pen...    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet #SOPA will make drinking Grimbergen a crime?!    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Probably because he thinks he's got a better chance of getting the airport named after him...    
    
    
    Hey @demsoc , welcome (in advance) to BCN, a hot-bed of local/national political activity and technology being built to support it!    
    
    
    @puntofisso "This building has encountered a thermal fault and needs to restart. Please vacate."  ?    
    
    
    Just been to the OU Library. To find a book. On actual paper. I even had to use an index! I'm so not used to this anymore...    
    
    
    TfL finally stop claiming timetable data is their commercial secret: it's on bus shelters after all http://dlvr.it/1kDLj (via @bengoldacre)    
    
    
    Paper accepted for a conference in Minneapolis this August. Need to either prune two pages off to meet new limit, or stump up an extra $200    
    
    
    Hands up who's coming to Vintage Computer Fair @ Bletchley Park this weekend? http://bit.ly/duMkzb #bpark #tnmoc #vcf (via @bletchleypark)    
    
    
    Finding out about the Bechdel Test. http://bechdeltest.com/ (via @threedaymonk)    
    
    
    It seems today is the day the anti-histamines stop working. I feel like I look like I've punched in the face :-(    
    
    
    Want to get involved in the #mediaeval2012 multimedia evaluation forum? Into media geography? Fill out the survey: https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/mediaeval2012tasksurvey …    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj FYI The Terry Pratchett Prize: http://www.terrypratchett.co.uk/    
    
    
    Tybed os gall y TSA darllen Cymraeg, nid yn ogystal â deall jôc? http://it.slashdot.org/story/12/01/31/001213/dhs-sends-tourists-home-over-twitter-jokes …    
    
    
    @ebanik The past, present and future of computing ;-)    
    
    
    The Vintage Computer Fair at #tnmoc and #bpark opens to the public!    
    
    
    I've just seen Guitar Hero played on a Commodore 64!    
    
    
    And Twitter running on a ZX Spectrum+! #vcf #tnmoc #bpark    
    
    
    Contemplating a new NAS to allay my data-loss fears. I'm quite attached to my Aperture library...    
    
    
    Must stop doing my Happy Dance in the office when my code starts working. It's beginning to get embarrassing. For everyone.    
    
    
    @vicchi I've been wondering about BCS membership, would you recommend it (barring recent internal ructions)?    
    
    
    @nanubrown I'm considering a Netgear ReadyNAS Duo and their BOGOF offer on hard drives - ever used one of these?    
    
    
    Stupid UK railway companies, wanting to charge me more for a shorter journey on the same route at the same time. Stupidness!    
    
    
    Great social media Tweet-Up @StationX today, coinciding with Alan Turing's birthday. There was cake in his honour.    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Awful news, hope you're not too shaken up.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Thinking of going to Boston? ;-)    
    
    
    @gregorybradley ELQ changes have hit the OU hard in particular, seems silly when we're trying to retrain/reeducate to save the economy!    
    
    
    Um, yes. "Utility Kilt". Not a man dress then. Nope http://tinyurl.com/2wyzc83    
    
    
    Oh! sweet cetirizine hydrochloride, how I love thee. Thou makest the most pollen laden breeze tolerable. Mine eyes and nose do thank thee.    
    
    
    Grr, Parcelforce man, I saw your van this morning, and I saw you not deliver my parcel that you had in your hand. Not pleased.    
    
    
    Seems my home broadband has recently and inexplicably doubled in bandwidth from 0.8Mbps to 1.6Mbps. 1990's, here I come!    
    
    
    Unreserved apologies ParcelForce man, seems my delivery was coming via TNT, you just happened to be bringing something from the same company    
    
    
    Being forced to revert nicely formatted HFS+ drives to FAT32 for compatibility with linux based NAS. Seems ext3 is not a good option for OSX    
    
    
    @linjones Have a great, well-earned break :-)    
    
    
    If Punxsutawney Phil has been correct 39% of the time, swap the interpretation, he's then 11% better than random! http://tinyurl.com/2tffex    
    
    
    Happy Day to gays and lesbians in #Iceland! - http://bit.ly/9J2Zzf #gayrights #marriage #equality #glbt (via @aldakalda)    
    
    
    Today feels like a day that will involve making and looking at lots of graphs. Pretty graphs admittedly, but graphs none the less.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I'm sure the unions will of course see the wisdom in this request and help the Mayor enact this efficiency measure forthwith    
    
    
    Ministers of religion will not be included in the immigration cap. Why the hell not? (via @threedaymonk)    
    
    
    London's twitter traffic plotted as a contour map.... http://bit.ly/95qwJI - rather fascinating (via @stephenfry)    
    
    
    My widget! It works! But I need to make it an order of magnitude quicker for it to be useful. Blast.    
    
    
    Some (and I stress some) Police officers need to actually read the law they are supposed to be upholding: http://tinyurl.com/28bpad7    
    
    
    Thanks  to @jasonbstanding for showing me Paul Gardner-Stephen's wallet-sized Enigma wheel? http://is.gd/d8Xks (via @SLSingh)    
    
    
    @puntofisso Reading that list I had such high hopes for www.magic.gov.uk expecting something Susanna Clarke-esque. At least it was mappy.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I recommend her! "Jonathan Strange & Mr Norrell" http://tinyurl.com/3xpnbxe    
    
    
    Just harassing the Flickr Pandas via their API. Not a sentence I thought I'd be tweeting today. http://www.flickr.com/explore/panda    
    
    
    Not a good time to be a Computer Science graduate it seems: http://tinyurl.com/3a77y3d    
    
    
    @gridinoc I can recommend the Netgear ReadyNAS Duo, they're currently giving away a second HD for free in a promo    
    
    
    @a__rebours Probably a bit of both, but mostly the former I think    
    
    
    @puntofisso Well, as long as companies keep wanting PhDs when I come to job hunting, I'm happy :-) After that...    
    
    
    @barnstormed Flying spitfires through a sky filled with pteradons with Superman as a co-pilot?    
    
    
    Naughty Flickr Panda, I certainly can't use *that* picture in a public demonstration of my system.    
    
    
    Must. Resist. Countering. Other people's. Passive-aggressiveness. With. More. Passive-aggressiveness.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Railtrack comedy gold: via b3ta and @alexlomas, hosted on fitlads, oddly http://dlvr.it/2F9LL (via @bengoldacre)    
    
    
    Off to Pride! Let's wave something colourful...    
    
    
    Beers in Soho Square after the Pride Parade rock. That is all.    
    
    
    @barnstormed I assume that's an 'unlimited' plan that now appears to have limits?    
    
    
    I feel like a prune that's been dehydrated by the symptoms of my hayfever. I blame 2-(1H-imidazol-4-yl)ethanamine - (histamine). Damn you!    
    
    
    @gridinoc The danger of restrictive cartography (including relying on it in non-geo systems) http://tinyurl.com/2ep6f6o    
    
    
    @ch_koula Καλή τύχη!    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Whatcha reading at the moment Dave?    
    
    
    "Clearly a mistake has been made." Politicians should be banned from using the passive voice  http://tinyurl.com/2wbkauj    
    
    
    @demsoc Difference being, in the West, national political leaders have to earn that respect through democratic elections, unlike in China...    
    
    
    I'm loving the ChronoZoom HTML5-based project, great way to explore data at scale(s) http://www.chronozoomproject.org     
    
    
    Just discovered that spectral representation of Aphex Twin's track 'Mathematical Equation' has a face in it! http://tinyurl.com/7mj4j    
    
    
    Continually checking websites to see if my flight is still on, otherwise Xmas in Spain, or possibly a British airport. Do McD's do roasts?    
    
    
    @puntofisso Cheers, and I'm glad to hear you got back OK, even if it was a bit of a nightmare! Buon Natale :-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso I appreciate that, thanks! We'll make you a subject of her Majesty yet ;-)    
    
    
    The theme from The Exorcist is floating around the office from somewhere outside (I'm on the 8th floor), thoroughly bizarre...    
    
    
    @FlyingBinary My pleasure, a worthy cause :-)    
    
    
    I think I've been looking at maps and satellite images too much today, just described the British Isles as "those small islands over there"    
    
    
    Currently reading @doctorow 's "FTW" and investigating www.bitcoin.org - digital economy/labour markets -alicious.    
    
    
    Yep. Think I've just got into the festive spirit. Not a moment too soon. Let's see if British Rail can spoil that on my final journey leg...    
    
    
    OMG Chester is freezing,  having to jog along platform to keep warm while dodging drunk Santas    
    
    
    @puntofisso Of course you can, although integration will mean giving up coffee and good food in favour of tea and chips.    
    
    
    @puntofisso You're in! Welcome to the realm    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I couldn't fit 'Arriva Trains Wales' in! Promise!    
    
    
    @lmontrieux By the time you read this, it will all be over, and you'll be relieved and happy :-) This, I predict.    
    
    
    Chatted to Andrew Trotman from U. of Otago about search indexes over lunch, wondering whether to romanize or not to romanize...    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Woo! I'm almost as good at predicting as that German octopus! I wonder if I can monetize this new ability...    
    
    
    Adobe based DRM on British Library document keeps hanging, crashing and generally failing. Useless.    
    
    
    @Retrophile Have you seen the HTML5 implementation of Conway's GoL? http://sixfoottallrabbit.co.uk/gameoflife/    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Next time we go to Pink Punters, that's *exactly* what I'm going to wear...    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Could well be - I think you should bring the Smurf outfit along again if I'm going as a psychic octopus...    
    
    
    @Retrophile The Curse of the Curious Geek - it's an affliction we all share...    
    
    
    @gridinoc "#Evil", but only as in "#Evil Genius". Noroc pe eforturile dvs. de viitor :-)    
    
    
    Welcome to the British Summer. Warm and dry to monsoon in about 24 hours. Batten down the hatches!    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort All the best things are in places called Walnut Tree :-)    
    
    
    Wondering how much image processing would be needed to retrieve censored text: http://tinyurl.com/34phrbb I guess redaction method dependant    
    
    
    @gregorybradley @bengoldacre needs some kind of symbol we can shine on to stormy clouds above Gotham whenever scientific BS hits the news    
    
    
    Submitted my first patch to a Sourceforge project (FlickrJ) - how come I've not done this before? Really kinda fun in a very geeky way    
    
    
    Christmas Doctor Who rocked. Sky sharks!    
    
    
    I kinda suspected Zac Goldsmith was a prat, but his interview behaviour here just confirms it: http://tinyurl.com/3ayymch    
    
    
    Home made mini touch table for less than £20. Sweet. Mk II will rock even more.  Need some IR LEDs.  http://twitpic.com/26lqzg    
    
    
    I can heartily recommend Touché for those interested in DIY Mac connected touch tables: http://gkaindl.com/software/touche    
    
    
    I'm trying to not be cynical about the #bigsociety stuff, but it feels like .gov jettisoning off work and hoping ppl will do it for free    
    
    
    @threedaymonk If the government can't ring fence vital services properly, you think the BBC would survive if funded from general taxation?    
    
    
    @threedaymonk Perhaps then it'd be a trade-off between value-for-money and effective independence, and I think I'd prioritise the latter    
    
    
    @threedaymonk The Charter is by no means perfect but any governments 'strict rule' of today becomes the 'aspirational guideline' of tomorrow    
    
    
    Also just made a crude gesture driven interface with my laptop webcam, some paper thimbles and some simple image processing. Fun :-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso I think in my case it's a general disillusionment with British government, nothing particularly coalition specific :-)    
    
    
    Just discovered the really amazing query-by-example tool Detexify for looking up LaTeX symbols http://detexify.kirelabs.org/classify.html  Massive timesaver!    
    
    
    @oliward I've not decided yet, either could be fun, though only one could get published :-)    
    
    
    iTunes 9.2.1 update, a few minor fixes = over 120MB?!    
    
    
    @mqtran It's the muggy heat, KMi is like a cheap sauna at the moment.    
    
    
    #SeientolegTwp. Just because it sounds better in Welsh, #stupidscientology    
    
    
    Received my 'free' extra 1TB drive for my Netgear ReadyNAS, took about 30s to install, automatic set up for RAID. Very impressed.    
    
    
    @mattsta Are you this fine Tweeter's neighbo(u)r and have you been to Home Depot recently? ;-)    
    
    
    . @marcdonnchadh Have just been given €250,000 in used notes in a brown paper bag. Coincidently, #NominateScully2012 !    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Congratulations!    
    
    
    No BT, I'm 'in debit' with you, I just haven't paid you for the service you haven't provided me with yet! Scary worded letters do not endear    
    
    
    @mattsta Bon voyage :-)    
    
    
    So, politicisation of the Police; fancy a BNP police authority? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-10757014    
    
    
    @puntofisso @markiliffe @lampone I am indeed, our plan to rent a canal boat fell through :-( I get in about 21:30    
    
    
    My #whereCampEU 2011 laptop sticker is looking lonely. It could do with a 2012 companion...    
    
    
    I can't tell tell difference between Terence Stamp http://tinyurl.com/8sxnot and Patrick Bauchau http://tinyurl.com/3mcnt - can you?    
    
    
    @mqtran That's a coincidence, cos I thought they both looked like detectives from horror stories...    
    
    
    #wherecampeu off to a great start in Amsterdam -feel like I'm missing out on the parallel sessions tho. Done my prez, time to enjoy the geo!    
    
    
    @Skinner_M it was on some recent research on geo spatial data analysis that makes it easier to understand big geo data sets thru regions    
    
    
    @Skinner_M I can show you the demo when you come and visit, there are pretty maps :-)    
    
    
    @Skinner_M Marvellous, we must chat...    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Congratulations!    
    
    
    Woot! My paper with @vanessa_murdock , Hugues Bouchard and Adrian Popescu on POI detection got accepted at #SIGIR2012!    
    
    
    Passing through Casnewydd/Newport, now train announcements in both Welsh and English, can here southen grammar forms. Me = language geek.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Hey, WhereCamp was great thanks, you really must come along to the next one, I think you'd like it :-)    
    
    
    I want the new UK Kindle. It's almost got to to my mental threshold price point, but would eat into my iPad fund http://tinyurl.com/33h4b75    
    
    
    @threedaymonk I can recommend http://www.postcardteas.com/ if you enjoy your tea. Cool shop, immensely knowledgeable proprietor, in London.    
    
    
    FOIed map of BT fibre optic roll-out in Milton Keynes: http://depositfiles.com/files/y3v9oe2hd I appear to be on a cusp. Darn.    
    
    
    Way too much stuff to do, nowhere near enough time, today requires hard-core heavy-duty dance music on quite loud.    
    
    
    @osbornec @puntofisso @stevenfeldman @markiliffe I completely don't have the hair to be Rebeccah. Nor the equine inclinations...    
    
    
    Currently desmutifying my Flickr image data set - there's a lot of random things on Flickr...    
    
    
    And when I say *my* Flickr data set, I mean one I'm creating for an experiment, not my own images. They're far less interesting.    
    
    
    @Retrophile Lol, I should have been clearer, not *my* uploaded images, just ones from others I'm using for work :-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso That's freaky, I was thinking similar things about night sky photography myself a few days ago! Great minds...    
    
    
    @puntofisso "Crazy" academics? We like to think of ourselves as "special". Or possibly, on occasion, eccentric.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Good point. I should embrace my positive craziness ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso @louisebrown We should suggest a new chapter for Debrett's - "How to Introduce Oneself to a Fellow Tweeter in Real Life"    
    
    
    Just used the word "sciuricide" in a sentence. Geekishly proud.    
    
    
    @ChristianHambly 'Squirrel murder' - it's a long story...    
    
    
    @mattsta Eek, who's that in reference to?    
    
    
    Colleague just shown me colour evaluation task: http://tinyurl.com/lcdhy7 A bit my like current experiment, made my eyes go funny.    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Not as good as you, though Suzanne also got 3. I think I rushed mine. And everything went psychedelic after staring too long    
    
    
    Remind me why I need to restart Firefox and Chrome to update MS Office?! What are you doing to my browsers Microsoft?    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase @seo01 Some people have *way* too much free time...    
    
    
    @Suw You will, however, only be able to check in to LOCOG sanctioned venues special rules for Olympics, in order to protect brands    
    
    
    @markiliffe *groan*    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Did you wake up this morning? Are you sure?    
    
    
    Just had a Relentless energy drink - 52g sugar, 160mg caffeine - my head feels like a beehive. With a disco in it. On a Saturday night.    
    
    
    Just been chatting with colleague and introduced to her 3D motion tracking system - proper Hollywood. Was too big for me to 'borrow'.    
    
    
    Rwy'n falch cyrraedd y Torch Olympaidd y Gogarth heddiw! Nice to see Llandudno  and Parc Eirias in the news http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-18235115 …    
    
    
    Die Welle and Good Bye Lenin! in the same week. German cinema FTW.    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj I hear Hebrew has been used when Latin and Greek aren't enough. Personally, I go for Georgian...    
    
    
    On a very cosy train from Dorset to London where New Year festivities await!    
    
    
    @borkurdotnet If @World were a username use that, otherwise, think of hashtags as simple Twitter tags for Tweets. You're good with those :-)    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock If I'm going to continue to follow you Dr M you're gonna have to be witty, erudite and interesting - just your normal self    
    
    
    @ChristianHambly What character do you play? That game has sucked so much time from my life, but I keep going back...    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Congratulations! :-)    
    
    
    Just been out watching the Perseids - some nice big ones tonight. And saw some satellites. And a bat. Might have been a duck. Was dark.    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Now I've checked the website, I want one too...    
    
    
    @ChristianHambly Night elf Moonkin mostly - just been checking out EVE Online this weekend, also very cool :-)    
    
    
    The WHSmiths in London City Airport just seems to sell books on finance, business and how to beat depression. Make of that what you will.    
    
    
    Just watching the Gaelic programme 'Blasad' which mostly consist of someone trying to understand what a vegetarian is. Rare up North?    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Have you been watching Sliding Doors again?    
    
    
    @mermhart Independent Women! Classic track    
    
    
    @nick_searle Hey, nice to meet you too, looking forward to the Tweet deluge :-)    
    
    
    Filling in the gaps of GPS with medium wave radio: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-18633917 …    
    
    
    Trying to track down an open source / free electronic lab book for Mac that can digitally sign entries for auditing. Any ideas Twitterverse?    
    
    
    Motorola really are a bit crap - FroYo for Milestone *at the end of the year*? It's not like you're having to write a new mobile OS    
    
    
    UK Visual Analytics Summer School 2010: keynotes/lectures/tutorials http://bit.ly/enfWGS #sensemaking #visualization #kmi (via @sbskmi)    
    
    
    Grappling with Amazon's Mechanical Turk. Need this experiment running and out the way - I have a thesis to write!    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Dear Dave, you just don't get my snooty cellular attitude and formulaic demeanour, regards, Excel    
    
    
    Dear academic publishers, if you're going to charge me stupid money for access, I'm not going to cite your publications. Simples.    
    
    
    @Documentally Love the Leica - some day one will be mine...    
    
    
    @StevenFeldman @stu_lester @markiliffe @archaeogeek NMA's data are to geography what dictionaries are to literature; functional, but no soul    
    
    
    @StevenFeldman @stu_lester @markiliffe @archaeogeek Vernacular geo differs from person to person, over time & use-cases. Lots of challenges!    
    
    
    @AlanTuringYear EDM should request the pardon for all convicted of homosexuality, not just our heroes. Pardon implies validity of 'crime'?    
    
    
    Using BBC Micros to teach A-Level students @TNMOC http://tinyurl.com/3xdyczn BBC BASIC - ah, the good ol' days.    
    
    
    @computid Congrats on the grades! Well done :-)    
    
    
    Submitted my experiment to Mechanical Turk - now the waiting game begins...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Will do - just waiting for it to all crash around me and spend a week fixing stuff. Fingers crossed it's robust enough!    
    
    
    Right, write thesis Adam, words into document, go!    
    
    
    @Dr_Black Congratulations on the UCL and CGA positions!    
    
    
    @puntofisso Or, of course, the correct way: http://www.addedbytes.com/blog/if-php-were-british/ …    
    
    
    Comment on ancient unsolved Eclipse bug ticket: "Seems like they just look at it and discuss it, like some rare, valuable piece of artwork."    
    
    
    @seo01 How are the crenellations on the wardrobe coming?    
    
    
    I want almost every watch from this place, gorgeous and geeky! http://www.tokyoflash.com/ Must resist. Or convince someone to buy for me.    
    
    
    @nick_searle I sincerely hope so! Otherwise that was my last three years down the drain...    
    
    
    @computid Hey Adam, did you see this model Cray? http://chrisfenton.com/homebrew-cray-1a/    
    
    
    @puntofisso @benterrett I might, if I knew what a 'pivotal tracker' was in English... something financial, or mechanical? Intrigued!    
    
    
    @fdans Brick through the window, or something more subtle...?    
    
    
    @fdans Ah, the Spiderman Technique, good choice :-) Glad you got in OK in the end    
    
    
    Hmm, results from my experiment not exactly as I wanted them. Now to spend ages trying to work out what went wrong...    
    
    
    @PaulDJohnston Turn off hardware acceleration in the Flash right click menu, worked for me    
    
    
    Surely the BBC non-News story "Archbishop backs papal visit cost" is as surprising as "Pope = Catholic"    
    
    
    @SLSingh Bletchley Park would be perfect for these! http://www.bletchleypark.org.uk/     
    
    
    @seo01 Do you now have to permanently adopt the pose of one of the meerkats in Neighbourhood Watch posters everywhere?    
    
    
    Line up at this afternoon's #sigir2012 discussion panel, should be good! pic.twitter.com/WCfkbHa7    
    
    
    @danielequercia I don't think Hindus go to Synagogue :-)    
    
    
    @danielequercia I'm currently at Yahoo! Research in Barcelona, you're at Cambridge right?    
    
    
    @danielequercia Until recently Geographic Context and Experience under Vanessa Murdock, now Semantic Search under Peter Mika    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Surely you meant: "who's with me‽" :-)    
    
    
    Slides from my talk on POI Mining from the Web given at SIGIR 2012 are up on my website: http://www.adamrae.com/?p=17     
    
    
    Reading about fascinating alternative to atomic clock based global navigation satellite system: Japanese QZSS http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/QZSS     
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Bit like Frogger but with train doors...    
    
    
    @tim_waters I seem to get some "Map Tile Not Ready" and broken tiles when I try and view that Geocommons page, is it just me?    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock "Other"?! I'll have to change that.    
    
    
    I need to build myself one of these: http://tinyurl.com/be58fd Pico projector, sense cam and a Beagle Board? Helmet not so fetching    
    
    
    Kind of thrilling seeing photos I've taken being shared and enjoyed around the Interwebs. Flickr Account Stats FTW! http://www.flickr.com/help/stats/     
    
    
    Just bought the new Terry Pratchett book,  woo!    
    
    
    @tomcoates I went to Marrakech for 1st time last year, was really beautiful, though expensive if you look like a tourist ;-) Have fun!    
    
    
    @nick_searle It's September still!    
    
    
    Making diagrams and deriving graphs for my thesis. On a Sunday night. When will this all end!? I'm sure I have a life to get back to...    
    
    
    @Skinner_M Reclaiming it from kids or for kids?    
    
    
    BBC article on Google mapping projects and some insight into how they curate it: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-19536269 …    
    
    
    @mattsta Only tiny if you count the comments… I think they had a "Meet the GMaps" press event and everyone got pretty much the same content    
    
    
    The Daily Mash - QUEEN TO HAVE LUNCH WITH INSANE CRIMINAL http://bit.ly/cXPbeW    
    
    
    I love this thing - mini quadrotor flying with precision: http://www.engadget.com/2010/09/16/quadrocopters-can-now-fly-through-thrown-hoops-the-end-really-i/ … via @engadget    
    
    
    My friend and colleague is in her PhD viva as I type - I'm on tenterhooks! Sending supportive vibes her way.    
    
    
    And the lovely Ainhoa Llorente Coto is now a Doctor! I'm so pleased for her :-D Seems there is light at the end of the tunnel    
    
    
    @bletchleypark I'm in the wrong country this month for #stationx at #bpark meetup I'm afraid. Hopefully will be able to make one soon tho    
    
    
    The Emissaries of China make an ursine Gift unto the Scots, unaware that Pictish Hordes may well deep-fry the poor Panda (@DrSamuelJohnson)    
    
    
    Cool use of computer vision coupled with problem solving and mobile apps: Google Goggles does sudoku  http://aol.it/gk7tQq    
    
    
    Like some aspects of the new iOS6 maps, but coverage is poor, and it seems many nations that had full features with GMaps have now lost them    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Skinner_M @puntofisso @tractiveeffort @rewiredstate Emergency office-based hammocks FTW!    
    
    
    @puntofisso @tractiveeffort @skinner_m @rewiredstate I would love to, tho I fear I'll be in the wrong country *yet again*. Need to fix this.    
    
    
    Biggest frustration for me so far with iOS6 maps is the lack of Barcelona metro stops…    
    
    
    @Skinner_M @tractiveeffort @puntofisso Shall I give you guys a ring tonight maybe, see what's abrewin' in the brain pots?    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort @skinner_m @puntofisso  Sounds, just let me know when is good for you guys    
    
    
    Bored? Boring! http://www.crossrail.co.uk/near-you#.UGHVK6Si-jk …    
    
    
    Piropos and the art of dirty/creepy Spanish compliments... http://choquecultural.posterous.com/piropos  via @LaWaneza    
    
    
    @mqtran I've banned myself from StarCraft II for the duration of my thesis. I'd never get it done otherwise.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I wondered why you walked right passed me without saying hello... ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso Completely :-)    
    
    
    Cool visualisations of text analysis from various sources: http://bit.ly/MZe5o I think it uses Processing, not sure http://bit.ly/FUmVf    
    
    
    Actually, all this guy's research is cool! http://bit.ly/9xnXDy    
    
    
    US President didn't have to wait and get agreement before ending Army racial segregation, why is DADT different? http://tinyurl.com/2wln547    
    
    
    Woo, and it seems I have FroYo (Android 2.2) on my Milestone. Zippy and pretty. This is what it should have been like on release.    
    
    
    @barnstormed Nice, thanks for the heads up!    
    
    
    We've seen Video Placing, Social Event Detection, a BBC Research keynote and now Violent Scene Detection, #mediaeval 2012 keep it coming!    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Ah, The Case of the Smoking Gnu.    
    
    
    Another #mediaeval comes to an end, award won, coveted MediaEval Rubrik's Cube received - job done :-)    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Are things now all signed and arranged for the new place?    
    
    
    haha RT @mjrobbins: RT @vbloke Did you know that the "B" in Benoit B. Mandelbrot stands for 'Benoit B. Mandelbrot'? (via @bengoldacre)    
    
    
    Just posted my #mediaeval '12 slides on my blog, including "Code of Conduct: Science Kills!" on supporting code sharing http://www.adamrae.com/?p=20     
    
    
    A whistle-stop trip to North Wales for my Gran's 90th and I'm reminded that it was the women in my family that got the longevity genes. Eek.    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Massive congratulations Alice!    
    
    
    OH: Welsh Fusilier on colleague's imminent stationing to the Falkland Islands: "You'll get bored. It's just a load of penguins"    
    
    
    Argh, my lust for a Leica M9 is growing. As is my inability to pay for one. Life is so unfair.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I think "øl" will probably be sufficient as well as well received.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/2tdgu0 One of these "The Americas" stories is not like the others. UK truly the 51st State in the eyes of Fox News.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort "Small (or some) beer" indeed - five minutes and you're already picking up the lingo :-)    
    
    
    Just been at a seminar of Shyamala Doraisamy on real-time heart beat categorisation. Reminds me of when I used to be able to do DSP.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Dave, you're on holiday, enough with the work related train news. 

Hope you're having fun i Norge.    
    
    
    Woo, my Internet is about 6x faster than it was this morning! Seems it might be finally fixed. Fingers crossed it stays this speedy.    
    
    
    @40_thieves Are you using LaTeX? Not exactly fun to enter but they do come out pretty.    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock They have been looking at me smugly recently. Maybe my encryption-foo finally beat theirs...    
    
    
    Gist I'm getting from #acmmm12 panel discussion is that multimedia community needs new ways to evaluate its own value/direction    
    
    
    Dear @acmmm12, why can't I tweet a question to the panel at #acmmm12 ? We have the technology!    
    
    
    @ngrams Thanks :-) I may have left it a little for now I think...    
    
    
    All geo meetings should take place in Japanese tea houses next to temples full of curious, sacred deer... #ACMMM12    
    
    
    @mattsta Eek, even more menacing after a day (partially) spent petting the creatures...    
    
    
    @mattsta Anyway I think they're abusing their 'sacredness' by nosing around in my lunch box, then looking all doe-eyed when I catch 'em @ it    
    
    
    I have just cast vote number 78 for Bradwell Abbey on The Race to Infinity website http://www.racetoinfinity.bt.com     
    
    
    @mattsta Of course, and even video! Will try an upload in batches rather than a big splurge at the end of my trip    
    
    
    @mattroweshow Fingers crossed the numbers jump a bit. I'm just concerned they'll use low numbers as justification for delays.    
    
    
    Can I haz iPad? It appears I can! Woo. Wonder if I can finish my thesis on it. Tappity tap.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Yup, saw a great deal on the uni noticeboard, snapped it up! It's swipalicious :-)    
    
    
    Back in Dorset, have 100 things to do and the entire village loses power. Hour in dark so far, can't pack by candle light & allergic to cat    
    
    
    EU project proposal overload. Email overload. Thesis overload. Danger, Will Robinson!    
    
    
    The ever excellent XKCD is geo-related today… http://xkcd.org/1138/     
    
    
    Previous wiki excerpt all about the biscuits made near my home village. Yay for slightly funnily named traditional foodstuffs!    
    
    
    @mattsta I never knew you were fluent in Mandarin!    
    
    
    Off to #bpark for some geekistory. Always something I've not seen before    
    
    
    A morning ahead of formalising abstract system models. How did I end up doing this again?    
    
    
    @Skinner_M "Praying on the vulnerable" Are they a religious organisation as well?! Biscuit well and truly taken...    
    
    
    Watching the sunrise over Gatwick as I head off to Florence for my first trip to Italy. Tired like a zombie tho.    
    
    
    @mattsta A current preoccupation? ;-)    
    
    
    @mattsta Evidently a man in demand...!    
    
    
    Visualising world geo data on a big wall at work - Making Data Analysis Fun™    
    
    
    I haz Raspberry Pi. That's my Sunday sorted then. pic.twitter.com/ZCu6Ah6l    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Hey Greg, Happy New Year :-) Yes, still here in BCN, change of job, but otherwise same as before, how're things with you?    
    
    
    @CharlotteHase I'm still working on that myself. Some cool inspiration online though. I may try a Media Centre and move on from there…    
    
    
    @seo01 Probably set up a media centre of some kind first, but I want to play with the GPIO pins, maybe control a few household appliances...    
    
    
    Great read from Wired on Mandelbrot, his maths as art: http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/01/mandelbrot-images …    
    
    
    13,000 black and white TVs, all watching digital TV… http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-20957218 …    
    
    
    Publishing a Paper without the Code is Not Enough http://zite.to/SglOWr  via @zite    
    
    
    Colour extraction from film trailers, a preponderance for orange and teal: http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/01/orange-teal-infographics/ …    
    
    
    Maptastic! Transport usage choraplethed across the UK: http://www.guardian.co.uk/news/datablog/interactive/2013/feb/01/cycle-drive-work-map-census-2011 …    
    
    
    Wishing I was @StationX at #BPark - work and geography got in the way...    
    
    
    Map Of The Day - Equal sized US states according to population http://zite.to/12SJdSu  via @zite    
    
    
    @Skinner_M @curiousc @loncreativelabs Keep me posted on the #opendata, currently working on interesting projects that need community data    
    
    
    Mapped: Twitter Languages in New York http://zite.to/WduKcL  via @zite    
    
    
    A guide to the writing systems of the world: http://www.buzzfeed.com/awesomer/maps-you-never-knew-you-needed?sub=2043479_914968 …    
    
    
    @barnstormed Oh, they reel you in all nice and lovely, then when anything goes even slightly wrong, the CS is unspeakably useless    
    
    
    @barnstormed Ah, in which case, best of luck, hopefully you'll have a better experience than I did. Enjoy the fibressness!    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Hell hath no fury like a French railway worker made redundant by a computer.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Crap! Robin Hood airport is closed. You've got a week to get your shit together, otherwise I'm blowing the airport sky high!! #IAmSpartacus    
    
    
    Mission: Take photos of nocturnal Barcelona glistening in the rain. Result: Severe dampness.    
    
    
    For the colour nerds out there: using Blender to model colour spaces
http://www.photo-mark.com/notes/2013/mar/13/color-theory-blender/ …    
    
    
    To celebrate UK LGBT History Month: one of the many #LGBTHeroes I'd like to highlight: Alan Turing, mathematician who worked @bletchleypark    
    
    
    why I’m quitting Mendeley (and why my employer has nothing to do with it) http://zite.to/1103dzi  via @zite    
    
    
    England’s two nations, and the value of equal-area mapping http://zite.to/11imf4G  via @zite    
    
    
    Why is Science Behind a Paywall? http://zite.to/11r35gE  via @zite    
    
    
    'You don't even know what you're voting for': MP paints damning portrait of life in Westminster http://zite.to/159i6yW  via @zite    
    
    
    The Unelected Banker Sitting in our Parliament to Make Life Easier for Banks http://zite.to/14wXhhO  via @zite    
    
    
    That last tweet might be of particular interest to @puntofisso and his love of the arcane    
    
    
    .@BillEllson The Remembrancer has access, rights and privileges in Parliament that no other local government representative has    
    
    
    @puntofisso The only area of the UK that allows businesses to vote, yeesh...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Then, good sir, we have work to do!    
    
    
    @puntofisso Oh, I've always been political ;-) 
¡Viva la revolución! 
(In a safe and orderly fashion, of course)    
    
    
    Introduced to Netflix project Lipstick by @hearlamb - great tool for visualising and analysing PIG scripts. http://techblog.netflix.com/2013/06/introducing-lipstick-on-apache-pig.html …    
    
    
    @mattsta Was the architecture the sole reason for that photo? ;-)    
    
    
    @mattsta I knew it! You heart Power Rangers...    
    
    
    @mattsta you mean to say that not all possible confectionary are available in the US?!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Joy: Films as maps… http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/07/movie-maps-gallery/?pid=7162&viewall=true …    
    
    
    @mrowebot Yeah same here, it was only afterwards that I saw the zombies...    
    
    
    Mapping Millions of Dots http://zite.to/1605XjM  via @zite    
    
    
    Mapping Millions of Dots: http://mapbox.com/blog/mapping-millions-of-dots … via @MapBox    
    
    
    @mpguerra @njyx I'll check with my fellow Brandcrumbers, see what they think :-)    
    
    
    @mpguerra Had you seen this at all? Computational Craft :-) http://www.k2g2.org/blog:bit.craft:computational_model_of_knitting …    
    
    
    @mattsta That stack of region codes DVDs still hurts...    
    
    
    Already missing the silence and pristine air of the Pyreneean mountains I was up last week. Work email inbox size upon return: Himalayan.    
    
    
    via @threedaymonk: http://fuckyeahfreeinterns.tumblr.com/ 
Exploitation by any other name...    
    
    
    Barcelona full of the besuited and befuddled for the Mobile World Congress. The pickpockets are gonna have a field day...    
    
    
    @Suw I can recommend this http://everytimezone.com/  , gives me a spatial sense of the differences    
    
    
    @Suw My pleasure - it's come in handy when I've got paranoid about cross-zone travel/meeting arrangements :-)    
    
    
    The closer to #mediaeval13 I get the more excited I am - it should be a great workshop. Hope my filmmaking of the event comes out OK…    
    
    
    @mattroweshow He got charged and was fined £1000, I was just playing Spartacus along with load of other Tweeps to show how absurd it is    
    
    
    British universities shouldn't condone this kind of gender segregation http://zite.to/1emFBv1     
    
    
    Particularly enjoyed the #nosql13 talk on Neo4J, much development since my early foray into the field of graph DBs a few years ago    
    
    
    Been converting geo boundaries in SHP format to SVG - building the world one outline at a time...    
    
    
    Woo! Congratulations #bpark ! http://www.theregister.co.uk/2011/02/25/turing_papers_saved/ …    
    
    
    I haz Wherecamp.eu ticket! http://wherecampeu2011.eventbrite.com/  Register while they're hot (and free).    
    
    
    Not sure re: the Portuguese-Irish connection, but interesting graph of lexical distance between languages nonetheless http://elms.wordpress.com/2008/03/04/lexical-distance-among-languages-of-europe/ …    
    
    
    Making maps from Foursquare and Twitter data - really interesting usage behaviour    
    
    
    @mattroweshow That looks interesting, although I think the submission deadline is a little close!    
    
    
    @mattroweshow Nice one, I'll keep an eye out!    
    
    
    @seo01 Nice - I agree! How did you do the infograms/skewed maps?    
    
    
    @seo01 Just what I was after - cheers!    
    
    
    @andycodling I sure hope the people you're meeting with aren't on Twitter ;-)    
    
    
    Data, meet maps: http://www.targetmap.com/     
    
    
    @puntofisso I have absolutely no idea to what you are referring ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso (I need to have a gentle sarcasm emoticon) Your initial guess was right :-)    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Remember the Golden Rule of cat names: Pick something you won't be embarrassed calling out of your front door at 4am in PJs    
    
    
    #moreGettingOn please. Understated comedy at its best.    
    
    
    @hockeyshooter The student bars there are great, one for each faculty (many) and in each a beer menu as long as your arm. If not longer.    
    
    
    Very robust sub-image tracking from Zdenek Kalal: http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2011/04/predator-smart-camera-locks-on-tracks-anything-mercilessly/ …    
    
    
    Spent most of the day trying to compile OpenCV on Snow Leopard. Still not happening. Darn you invisible incompatibilities!    
    
    
    Almost 24 hours of me fiddling with stuff to get OpenCV to compile and run on Snow Leopard. But I can now do things to pictures!    
    
    
    Discovering the joys of the oh-so-humourously-named content versioning system "Git"    
    
    
    Ozwald Boeteng has a depressingly bad website for such a cool designer: http://tinyurl.com/yeggvy5 Asking whether I have Flash installed?!    
    
    
    I do find it funny that Mandy thinks The Sun's new support for the Tories is sinister, but wasn't when it supported Labour...    
    
    
    While I'm considering replacing my nicked iPhone, should I only consider another Apple device? Those Android phones are tempting too...    
    
    
    @vicchi Coincidence! Same with me today. I've logged in again, is that it for re-enabling?    
    
    
    How do I use a possessive apostrophe with brand name Yahoo! ? How about a question mark with it for that matter? Looking ugly all mashed up    
    
    
    Open Science meets Open Source: http://marciovm.com/i-want-a-github-of-science …    
    
    
    RT: @NunoCardoso Evolution of the British, French, Spanish and Portuguese empires in bubble diagrams. Nice. http://is.gd/4XNqH (via @seo01)    
    
    
    I also knew pigeons were dangerous: http://tinyurl.com/y8ps3yz    
    
    
    @andywasley I think Sir Humphrey might even have used the word "courageous"    
    
    
    Now booked for flight back to Blighty. Still need to work out where I'm spending Christmas...    
    
    
    Come on Red Bull, work your chemical, mind-altering magic    
    
    
    I so adore those fire alarms that go on just long enough for me to start taking the 8 floors of stairs, then stop after the fire door shuts    
    
    
    Why do I have a button on my British Mac keyboard with ± and § on it? Until just then, I have *never* typed those characters...    
    
    
    Ah Wolfram Alpha, finally you have a use: http://tinyurl.com/yd25uwp    
    
    
    Sorting out travel plans for Christmas holidays involving London, Milton Keynes(!), North Wales and Dorset. Where's my rail discount card...    
    
    
    @Carter_AndrewJ Just a small undertaking then...?! :-D Are you feeling better btw?    
    
    
    @threedaymonk This is held up as a flaw by pro-FPTPers, ignoring that this occurs way more frequently under FPTP    
    
    
    Ah, morning 'xocolata calenta' (- xurros) and musings over unfortunate possibility cat seizures. Pretty average start to the day.    
    
    
    Ah ha! (Formerly) secret office chocolate stash comes to the rescue... And no, I'm not revealing its location. So ner.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Perhaps a cattle prod would be more effective.    
    
    
    @andywasley Hear, hear!    
    
    
    @HRBeaman Cool! Which language are you learning at the moment? Has Twitter been useful?    
    
    
    @HRBeaman Good stuff - let me know how it goes :-)    
    
    
    Just removed four(!) recently blown light bulbs in apartment. With Spanish wiring, this is a life threatening exercise. H&S is for sissies!    
    
    
    Playing with Nokia Ovi Maps in 3D, very cool, though a pity it requires its own plugin http://maps.ovi.com/3d/     
    
    
    @puntofisso Oh, trust me, whole other world! ;-)    
    
    
    OK, that's two buttons that have come off my jumper in as many days. I suspect foul play.    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Not another TFL nude calendar Dave?! I thought you promised not to do any more of those...    
    
    
    I seem to have been bitten in my sleep last night. I now have 2 thumbs, 7 fingers and 1 one swollen sausage attached to my hands. Eek.    
    
    
    Swollen finger beginning to interfere with typing. It's like mashing buttons with a pogo stick.    
    
    
    @puntofisso X-ratedness is in the dirty mind of the beholder... ;-)    
    
    
    I just generated my #TweetCloud out of a year of my tweets. Top three words: barcelona, time, getting - http://w33.us/11tr    
    
    
    Gosh, Mondays really should be outlawed. I suggest we skip over and go straight to Tuesday. Agreed?    
    
    
    @puntofisso Let's hope you don't need a press pass to get anything bigger than a point&shoot! Sponsor Kodak may not want the competition ;-)    
    
    
    Just lost two days worth of effort due to bad documentation of the UNIX 'join' command. Peeved.    
    
    
    @threedaymonk http://sourceforge.net/projects/supersensetag/ … SuperSenseTagger shared under Apache License V2.0, can use included WSJ data for POS tagging    
    
    
    Have just bought Twix from the vending machine upstairs but now need to wait for it to defrost before eating. Think machine is a bit faulty    
    
    
    @seo01 Careful with the punctuation in that Tweet! Or am I being dense...?    
    
    
    @curiousc I can recommend Zotero, integrates well and can output into a variety of systems and formats http://www.zotero.org/     
    
    
    Confirmation that Dave Cameron is indeed undead and doesn't need to breathe - 116 word run-on sentence! http://www.number10.gov.uk/news/speeches-and-transcripts/2011/04/statement-between-the-pm-and-australian-prime-minister-63369 …    
    
    
    Just spent a whizzy few hours on a bed in a bar here in Barna drinking cocktails. This is the life.    
    
    
    Just saw Alan Bennett's Talking Heads with Dame Thora Hird. Masterpiece, and never fails to make me well up.    
    
    
    Joy - the massive electric blue floodlights lighting my building shine directly into my cubicle. That's my colour vision screwed for Xmas.    
    
    
    Just weighed (empty!) luggage on bathroom scales pre-return to UK. Pitifully underestimated allowance I'd need. Can I add more easyJet?    
    
    
    Seems the answer is yes. If you are an actual millionaire. Which if I were, I wouldn't be flying easyJet.    
    
    
    I can hear Spanish kids singing "London Bridge is falling down..." through my wall at home. Cute, but also slightly menacing.    
    
    
    Thanks to over-ordering of the catering for a meeting in the office I am now having lunch Mk II. Perhaps that should be iLunch 2.0. Nom.    
    
    
    Gosh, the new Chrome on Mac really does feel snappy.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @puntofisso Kind of like this idea :http://www.vmware.com/products/mobile/ ?    
    
    
    In a minor panic over leaving party tomorrow. How much wine? How much beer? Should nibbles have been pre-arranged? The pressure!    
    
    
    The ArchB of Canterbury accused the gov't of treating religious faith as "eccentricity" practised by "oddities". Says the man in the dress?!    
    
    
    Getting carried away looking at online party food recipes for tonight. This could either turn out really well, or major culinary disaster!    
    
    
    Britons! Go forth and vote, preferably "Yes!" Make a difference.    
    
    
    Party was a success! Up til 7am setting world to rights. 4hrs sleep, then someone else's leaving lunch. Thoroughly lovely. Exhausted.    
    
    
    Just went out for dinner with visiting friends of my flatmate. Was offered pig's trotters. How could I refuse? Mmm, cartilage...    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I'm working up to introducing cockles as party food. But give me time, and they'll be the talk of every social gathering...    
    
    
    Astonishing and also quite funny octopus larks: http://tinyurl.com/ydn6ssf Feels like it needs the Benny Hill music in the background    
    
    
    Darn, seeing #uksnow tweets and just know it'll all be gone by the time I get back on Friday.    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Congrats on the new home! I hope the move was stress-free, I usually end up losing a box somewhere along the way...    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Very pleased for you both! Say hi from me :-)    
    
    
    MediaEval 2011: Placing Task CfP - get the details on taking part in this GeoTagging challenge at http://www.multimediaeval.org/mediaeval2011/placing2011/index.html …    
    
    
    Gone for the Droid - should arrive in MK before I do :-)    
    
    
    @craig_macdonald Also encountered this recently when trying to work out why load ing \n separated Tweet records kept randomly going wrong!    
    
    
    @aldakalda You may want to break it to her gently that some loony countries (mine included) still have them :-(    
    
    
    After epic journeyage I'm now back in the UK. (s/es/co.uk/g) And I have my new Droid to fiddle with on the train to Wales tomorrow!    
    
    
    Flickr photos taken during my recent trip to Madrid http://flic.kr/s/aHsjuKYBCj    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Yeah. Sure. :-)    
    
    
    Now in North Wales and have just been to the local carvery - mmm, pleasingly full    
    
    
    Seems the crunchy bits in gran's Xmas pud were the molten remains of the packaging it came in...    
    
    
    Navigating Xmas evening TV schedule with Gran's sensibilities to bad language in mind - surprisingly tricky    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Thank you and the same to you mate :-)    
    
    
    DPM Clegg's white paper on Lords' Reform: options for mostly or completely elected Lords, except CoE Bishops still get in?! FAIL. Big time.    
    
    
    @cabinetofficeuk What possible justification is there for unelected Bishops of a single religious group to have seats in a Reformed Lords?    
    
    
    Temporarily back in the land of 3G (London) before inevitably losing the connection when the train gets to the Dorset border...    
    
    
    @seo01 I imagine this may have already popped up on your radar? http://www.kmjn.org/notes/geographically_dense_wikipedia.html …    
    
    
    @vicchi There'll be a 3 person Y! contingent at #wherecampeu :-)    
    
    
    @vicchi Me, Vanessa and Hugues coming from Barcelona, not sure if there'll be more    
    
    
    Seems my allergies to my sisters cats hasn't lessened in the last year. Breathing shouldn't be an optional extra when visiting home...    
    
    
    Day spent visiting Dorset family. Reaffirmed my belief that they're all slightly bonkers but utterly wonderful too.    
    
    
    Trying to get my Motorola Milestone (Droid) to sync properly with my Mac. No more iPhone-like iTunes plug-in-and-sync for me...    
    
    
    Had a great night out meeting old friends then came home to my brother fainting for his first time. I thought he had a stroke. No such luck.    
    
    
    Suffice it to say, he's fine, but the carpet in my sister's bedroom will not be the same after meeting the ketchup from my bro's flung chips    
    
    
    Finally back in MK after a relaxing Christmas and a great New Year's Eve. Thanks to all involved. You're all lovely.    
    
    
    Just caught up with #doctorwho , was sad seeing DT go. Was that the Doctor's mum helping out there I wonder?!    
    
    
    @Siouxsinner Interesting idea - but do you think they'd bring her back when most modern new fans wouldn't know who she is?    
    
    
    Just found myself converting from sterling into euros to get a better sense of a price. This can't be good.    
    
    
    @Siouxsinner Even more interesting! Now the wait for the next series is going to be even harder :-)    
    
    
    Have now picked and paid admin fee for new flat in Milton Keynes! Now to see how long it takes to actually move in...    
    
    
    From static maps with high human overhead to giving people the geo data they actually need, from @vicchi #wceu    
    
    
    Note to self: remind people Yahoo do maps too... #wceu    
    
    
    Finally T-Mobile have transferred my old number to my Milestone. Only 8 days late. Not a great start to our new contractual relationship...    
    
    
    Can a new geo ontology help connect data? @vicchi I wonder whether yetanotherstandard will actually help, will it be flexible enough?    
    
    
    @puntofisso #wceu Surely the concept of place/poi is too subjective and dependant on use-case to proscribe so specifically    
    
    
        
    
    
    Loved the visualisations from @oobr at #wceu - pretty data, telling stories.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley I am indeed! Still sorting out a flat, but that's work-in-progress. Now to get back into work mode after the holidays...    
    
    
    @davethackwell Hey! I'm fine thanks. MK's very snowy, a couple of inches or snow, looking great :-) All good with u guys?    
    
    
    @vtri We'll be publishing all our experimental results soon, stay tuned :-)    
    
    
    . @vanessa_murdock up at #wceu talking about Yahoo! Geo experience research, specifically modelling locations with UGC    
    
    
    Hugues Bouchard currently showing off Y! Geo Intent demos at #wceu    
    
    
    "Kinda cool" data visualisations from @osbornec = contender for understatement of the meet up at #wceu    
    
    
    Seems my tiny home village in Dorset can get twice as high broadband speeds than my new estate in the city of Milton Keynes. FTTP please.    
    
    
    @davethackwell Possibly this coming summer, thru a BT Experimental scheme: http://tinyurl.com/y96sy94 I'm too impatient though!    
    
    
    @nanubrown Not tried DoubleTwist, have been playing with MissingSync and Salling Media Sync, neither quite live up to expectations yet    
    
    
    Why hello C, it's been a while. Memory management you ask? Method overloading? Let me explain...    
    
    
    @StationX Where can I find out more about the event on 20th Jan?    
    
    
    Mr Weatherman insisted I'd experience both heavy snow and drifts over night and today. Not a flake of it. Thoroughly disappointed.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ah. Great. Only after leaving Spain does Santander let me get cash out for free from my UK Abbey (i.e. Santander) account in Spain. Grr.    
    
    
    @andywasley Something more like this maybe? http://img.listal.com/image/77025/936full-attack-of-the-killer-tomatoes!-poster.jpg …    
    
    
    I keep running into the people who have joined the KMi lab since I left before going to Spain - each and everyone of them lovely.    
    
    
    Doing a face detection/recognition experiment. I have faces whizzing past on my screen à la Spooks/CSI/any film with a police database in it    
    
    
    @gridinoc Let me know if anything interests you, I joined up a little while ago, potential for interesting stuff, but data still a bit flaky    
    
    
    My recently purchased rubber cover for my phone makes my Milestone look like a device of the Borg. I expect assimilation shortly.    
    
    
    Just tried to donate via UK Red Cross website for Haiti, but no go. Went to DEC instead: http://tinyurl.com/4b8cu    
    
    
    @puntofisso Thanks :-) Although put like that it sounds like I'm going to Mordor or something...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Surprisingly close, but instead of a big glowing eye hovering over an army of orcs, we have Xscape and hordes of chavs :-)    
    
    
    Now have the keys to my new flat and a house load of IKEA boxes sitting in the living room. Now, where's my screwdriver...    
    
    
    I now have table, chairs, sofa bed, lamp and bookcase constructed - on an IKEA assembly roll!    
    
    
    @tim_waters "Going home"?    
    
    
    Just saw 'The Road'. Bleak, yes. Moving, to a degree. But ultimately unsatisfying    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I sympathise! But hey, tell us anyway...    
    
    
    @oliward Ah, I haven't read the book yet. I felt a bit disappointed by the 'happy' end after all the bleakness, different in the original?    
    
    
    Arggh, head full of cold-induced cotton wool. Nose uncooperative, general feeling of grottiness. And my Must Do Today list is still long...    
    
    
    @clarkalastair Congratulations! 白头偕老 :-)    
    
    
    @gt_p @mrshb2b pointed me in your direction about the BP Social Media Tweet-Up tomorrow. If I can make it, what are the arrangements? Cheers    
    
    
    Tea and social media at #stationx . I hear there's also a bus ride ride involved?!    
    
    
    Excellent (if occasionally surreal!) day @bletchleypark today for #stationx. I approve of Tweet-Ups. More please.    
    
    
    Dear T-Mobile, please don't keep selling USB broadband dongles that break Snow Leopard. Also, acknowledge there is a problem. That is all.    
    
    
    PHD Comics: The PHD Movie! http://www.phdcomics.com/movie  via @phdcomics    
    
    
    There are no services in my area that can provide any more than potential 1Mbps internet access. IN URBAN MILTON KEYNES! Flipped off.    
    
    
    Darn, yet another paper rejected. Seriously wondering whether I'm just bad or reviewers the world over hold a very specific grudge    
    
    
    Changes to Yahoo! Geo APIs: http://developer.yahoo.com/blogs/ydn/posts/2011/06/yahoo-maps-apis-service-closure-announcement-new-maps-offerings-coming-soon/ …    
    
    
    @threedaymonk Funny, I doubt Raffarin would be complaining if French were the dominate language for press spokespeople...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @andywasley Contact our apparently mutual friend @puntofisso - he's the expert in online detection...    
    
    
    Just spent amazing morning at Postcrd Teas near Bon Street at a green tea tasting session with immensely knowledgeable Timothy. Gyokuro!    
    
    
    Fine tea, books, gadgets, pub lunch and the Imperial War Museum for my first time. Excellent Saturday, and it's not even over yet...    
    
    
    Next door's cat just helped me take a water meter reading. Surprisingly knowledge about water meters, but paws not so handy for lid removal    
    
    
    Much as I love my new sofa, it really isn't the best place to work with laptop+external hard drives+other connections. Need a proper desk    
    
    
    @vicchi Was there proper quaffing involved? Surely the only way to drink Viking beer...    
    
    
    X-Ray scanner + Metallic ink + t-shirt = Body Scanner #fail: http://bit.ly/gudqNP (via @puntofisso)    
    
    
    Just been hooked up to an EKG, skin resistance and facial muscle monitors while playing Little Big Planet. And all in the name of science!    
    
    
    Not the best time of year to experiment with my storage heaters. My boost dial doesn't go high enough for tonight's temps...    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort Praps the pigeon was unmovable and the car was unstoppable and hence a philosophical conundrum has been inadvertently solved    
    
    
    @9600 Perhaps it could be your personal super power - you can *hear* the code passing through the machine...    
    
    
    @andywasley Have you played the Broken Sword games on the iPad? It was like reliving my early teens :-)    
    
    
    As undoubtedly pretty as the #iPad is, I feel somewhat let down. Nothing exactly revolutionary about it. Just a scaled-up iPod Touch really    
    
    
    Back from my first Catalan IKEA experience. Shockingly similar to the [insert country] one. They must get it all in a catalogue or something    
    
    
    Just been delving into Visual Basic. It has {GoTo}s. I haven't seen one of them since programming in actual BASIC over a decade ago    
    
    
    @HRBeaman Massive congratulations!    
    
    
    Dear research computer, in order to meet my fast approaching deadline I shall hammer you mercilessly until you process my data. Understood?    
    
    
    Who's idea was it to encourage young children to let off firecrackers in the street for a week before St Joan? Like WW3 outside my place.    
    
    
    The more I stare at this page of LaTeX typeset prose, the more I feel an æsthetic stirring. Beautiful in a frequently overlooked way.    
    
    
    @xan1112 Did it, after doing your coursework, become a 5 core desktop? :)    
    
    
    @xan1112 Deus in machina!    
    
    
    My Motorola Milestone now connects to an update server, but alas, no Android 2.1 for me yet. Still, promising sign    
    
    
    @xan1112 Yahoo! wouldn't let - no, I'm kidding, I got mine *just* before the GooglePhone came out. Still love it though :-)    
    
    
    “…the code is just part of the science, and not usually a goal in its own right” http://bit.ly/bbcTyl /via @yokofakun (via @gridinoc)    
    
    
    Just had phone call from new letting agent. Showing surprising initiative and intelligence. I'm not used to this. Slightly worrying.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I approve of the purchases and disagree with the craziness. That is all.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Or I should say that this is a thing that I think is good. Just to maintain that form of writing that P*r*c was so fond of.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @xan1112 Strangely, Mosterton can get higher speeds than this bit of urban Milton Keynes. Crappy MK.    
    
    
    Just had unexpectedly positive and productive meeting, inordinately relieved! Now to celebrate with special tea. I'm so rock and roll, me.    
    
    
    @puntofisso I would if I were in the right country, darn...    
    
    
    "The Guild" rules. And so do their music videos:  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=urNyg1ftMIU    
    
    
    @gridinoc I'm surprised they didn't arrest you for wantonly provoking a criminal...    
    
    
    @9600 It's so you can tell whether the beam is narrow enough to make it suitable for DIY home laser eye surgery...    
    
    
    According to Mac Office 2008 Excel, 2+1 is still 2 in my spreadsheet. I think I've just found the root of the banking crisis.    
    
    
    @9600 Well I sincerely hope they learnt their lesson there...    
    
    
    @nanubrown Yep, and seemingly in this still-live session it's repeatable. Maybe I turned off the 'do maths' Excel feature by mistake.    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh I've been using my iPad recently for article reading. With software like Mendeley syncing everything, it's a one-stop shop    
    
    
    Just been at fascinating talk on stereo photography courtesy of the Open University Camera Club. Next project: Avatar Comes to MK.    
    
    
    @gridinoc Surely now that you're in the country it doesn't matter? ;-)    
    
    
    Weird though this will sound, I'm missing the British weather today. I likes me a good roof shaker storm.    
    
    
    Have just been wired up again to monitors, sensors and been videoed whilst playing Halo 3 for friend. Why aren't I do my PhD on this again?    
    
    
    @xan1112 I had to stop myself from swearing profusely when I remembered every utterance was being recorded. Halo brings out the gamer in me    
    
    
    @xan1112 You've seen the tapes?!    
    
    
    Petition not to publicly fund Pope's visit now over 8,000. http://bit.ly/dhjDey Let this 'head of state' pay for his own party.    
    
    
    A friend just announced that he was worried his hard drive didn't have enough trilobites. I sympathised. Mine doesn't either.    
    
    
    @andywasley (@puntofisso) What was the name of that blog you used to maintain? You little rascal... ;-)    
    
    
    @tractiveeffort I'm confused. That flies in the face of my scant understanding of electricity. But glad you got a workable solution    
    
    
    @andywasley Looking very dapper, wish I was there to cheer you guys and gals on!    
    
    
    Missed out on London Pride, looks like another cracking parade, hope you had fun London tweeps!    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Yeesh, time flies... If only I were there to take another one today :-)    
    
    
    @cmjones85 Was there trampleage?    
    
    
    @cmjones85 In which case, ha det gøy! As gøy as possible in fact ;-)    
    
    
    @cmjones85 Ditto ;-)    
    
    
    I doubt Google just randomly crawls the web, they use good parallel texts like EU/UN docs and other curated collections http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2011/06/an-economic-burden-google-can-no-longer-bear/240283/ …    
    
    
    @clarkalastair Hey, going well thanks, Spain is great - how are things with you? Are you back in the UK again now? You were in China right?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Skinner_M Ning is handy for setting up an online community, if that's the kind of thing you're after    
    
    
    Always awkward for Britons to congratulate Americans on their Independence Day - feels somewhat treasonous...    
    
    
    @vanessa_murdock I thought you were British? ;-)    
    
    
    Aperture 3 is being released! I'm stupidly excited. Have been waiting so long. Faces! Places! Calm down Adam, calm down...    
    
    
    @puntofisso You seem to be going through the same list of mental questions I did shortly after I got my Droid...    
    
    
    @threedaymonk When I first heard those ads I was expecting something from Star Trek, or at least Buck Rogers. But nope, box on wheels it is.    
    
    
    Woo, Android 2.0.1 on my UK Milestone at last! Let's hope it fixes my current bug bears.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Well, there're apps for killing tasks (I know, not exactly a solution), but no, it's a case of working around these 'features'    
    
    
        
    
    
    @hockeyshooter s/hate/love/g - actually, that sounds quite aspirational    
    
    
    Aperture is quietly chugging away at finding faces in almost a decade of personal photos. Bringing back memories...    
    
    
    @nanubrown It costs £169/$199, gives me more metadata and fine tuning than sticks can be shaken at, face recognition is not bad at all :-)    
    
    
    Heard, then saw a pair of courting woodpeckers on my way to work this morning. Sign of spring to come? *fingers crossed*    
    
    
    @Dr_Black I find it mostly fills the world with more kitten videos...    
    
    
    Today is a day of lists. Lists that will get shorter, not longer. Vain hope?    
    
    
    Wondering how many FireEagle, Google Latitutude, 4sqr etc. accounts will have been cancelled today due to  http://pleaserobme.com    
    
    
    The UNIX 'join' command is devil spawn in inconsistency form...    
    
    
    Classic. "The first rule of Tautology Club is the first rule of Tautology Club" http://xkcd.com/703/    
    
    
    @threedaymonk Nope, they must be mercilessly mocked publicly.    
    
    
    Erm, I close my curtains for five minutes and suddenly MK has gone all winter wonderland on me again? It's like Ninja snow...    
    
    
    @Documentally Isn't it normally law? :-)    
    
    
    Just volunteered my services to Bletchley Park - have you? #BPark    
    
    
    @pjbryant That'll teach me to keep my Twitter profile up-to-date! Actually far closer to BP now.    
    
    
    @gt_p Not sure yet, will be going to my interview soon to find out where I'll be most useful. Excited!    
    
    
    A day minor achievements - if I had written them down they'd be mostly crossed off by now. And I'm not done yet. Rar!    
    
    
    @sleicester I've wanted to play around with Arduino stuff for ages, let me know how it goes    
    
    
    It's ridiculous o'clock in the morning and I'm watching QI in Dutch. My body clock is screwed. http://tinyurl.com/yzek9ad    
    
    
    Ah, IKEA. Land of curiously named soft furnishings and a whole load of stuff I don't really need and yet seem to end up buying.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Scrummy balls.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley How on earth could a Tweet about tasty Swedish meat balls be euphemistic? I just don't see it...    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Thérémine, perhaps? http://tinyurl.com/knp4c    
    
    
    @raemond Please could you RT 2show @nationaltrust the support they would get for helping 2save Bletchley Park #NTsaveBPark (via @Kailua09)    
    
    
    @lmontrieux Yes Lionel, yes you will :-)    
    
    
    Arg, drowning in data...    
    
    
    And will journalists be encouraged to become science literate before stoking baseless controversy? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-14314501 …    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey You whippersnapper you... :-)    
    
    
    Missing being @StationX at #bpark again this month, going to have to sort out some kind of virtual presence arrangement...    
    
    
    Ah Time Machine, on the rare occasions when I've needed you, you have been there. Thank you for saving my spreadsheet in such a wooshy way    
    
    
    @barnstormed "My most secret source" Sir Winston Churchill. Sounds more like Colonel Saunders :-)    
    
    
    Attempting to navigate MK buses on way to #BPark in the rain...    
    
    
    @john_goss Congrats on the #LGBT History month talks at #BPark earlier, all went splendidly! Thanks    
    
    
    Dydd Gwyl Dewi Da pawb :-)    
    
    
    Why do I have a job that means I don't see the outside world for most of the day? I have to visit the one window to see the sunshine :-(    
    
    
    @barnstormed I have given up on @motorola after fiasco with Milestone, useless communication and terrible upgrade strategy    
    
    
    @oobr Excellent news! My mate @tractiveeffort named 'Pudding Mill'. I seem to move in very geo circles...    
    
    
    Surprised myself at how saddened I am at the news that Kristian Digby has died: http://tinyurl.com/yf4fgfb    
    
    
    @gt_p Do your night time cloud shots go up anywhere online at all?    
    
    
    @gt_p Cool, I'll keep an eye out for them    
    
    
    Is there a clearer example of cultural cowardice than culling off the exceptional so that the average feel less threatened? (via @MitchBenn)    
    
    
    @john_goss Better public exposure of party manifestos is one thing, the 'personalisation' of politics is another, e.g. Kennedy-Nixon debates    
    
    
    Seems my bank (Santander) now charges me £1.25 on top of the €0.99 for a Android Marketplace app, making price £2.15 instead of £0.90. Grr.    
    
    
    Arduino Explorer kit on its way! Now to hover around for the postman on a daily basis until it arrives...    
    
    
    @mrshb2b I'm sorry to hear that, keep positive :-)    
    
    
    @gregorybradley http://www.newrailalphabet.co.uk/ But pricey though...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @gregorybradley Ah! Best of luck hunting it down...    
    
    
    Just saw a contemplative man smoking a pipe on campus. If people feel they have to smoke, pipes are the way to go.    
    
    
    Libel law used to suppress 'bad' academic book review http://bit.ly/aKqlWA -- shocking! (via @richardh)    
    
    
    @9600 http://tinyurl.com/y8amp5m Go for the one front and centre. The bigger the pipe, the better the contemplation...    
    
    
    Best. Online. Game. Eva. http://games.adultswim.com/robot-unicorn-attack-twitchy-online-game.html    
    
    
    Finally retrieved all my books from a friends's loft. Ah books. Oh! how I have missed you all... Now, do I have shelf space?    
    
    
    @mrshb2b With the OU! They do different levels and you can fit it around other commitments. Of course, I'm biased...    
    
    
    Arduino has arrived! Right, that's my weekend sorted...    
    
    
    @puntofisso An Italian who can't do la erre moscia? Shocked! ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso D'oh, you're quiet correct and I should've spotted that. I shall now beat myself with a copy of "Italian Phonology for Dummies"    
    
    
    @puntofisso It's the only way I'll learn...    
    
    
    More open travel data, woot! Go TfL, shame on you Network Rail... http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2011-08/05/tfl-api …    
    
    
    My first Arduino circuit... http://twitpic.com/16xqqn    
    
    
    Woo! Speakers I thought I broke two years ago now magically work. And yes, I horde broken gadgetry *just in case*. Now smug.    
    
    
    Word(s) of the Day: Riot Wombles! https://twitter.com/#!/search/%23riotwombles …    
    
    
    David Cameron wanting to shut down 'social media' during unrest just shows his utterly lack of understanding of what it is + what it can do    
    
    
    @AliceMorrissey Hear, hear!    
    
    
    Quietly ripping apart a paper I'm reviewing. I feel bad for the authors - but if you're going to do *that* to data, you can blame yourself    
    
    
    @puntofisso Damn.    
    
    
    @AlrightTit District 9 - Aliens and South African accents, what more could you want? :-)    
    
    
    Waiting for yet another delayed MK bus on the way to @StationX at #bpark . Need a car. This is getting silly.    
    
    
    Cipher book used for secret WW2 communication at #bpark http://twitgoo.com/k6o0l    
    
    
    @Documentally Thanks for the welcome, and good to meet you earlier! See you at the next @StationX at #BPark    
    
    
    @sleicester @StationX is the social media Tweet-Up that happens once a month at Bletchley Park #BPark - come along!    
    
    
    @Retrophile Nope, just forgot to remove it :-) Currently hunting down LCD/LED arrays and wireless connectivity options on eBay - any advice?    
    
    
    @Dr_Black #BPark never fails to intrigue, educate and generally make me feel proud to be geeky :-)    
    
    
    Getting freaked out at how much of my house I can see in Dorset. I can see in in the back window! Into the kitchen! Why Google, why?!    
    
    
    Have I started my first Twitter trend with #Proud2bGeeky after my day at #BPark ?! Not yet you say? Well, we've got work to do then...    
    
    
    "the plural of anecdote is not data" ... @bengoldacre's Bad Science gets quoted at #wherecampeu (via @vicchi)    
    
    
    @marcdonnchadh Nah, proper research has to have number and graphs, otherwise how do you get a computer to do it for you? ;-)    
    
    
    Maplins has everything it seems (except the components I went in for of course) http://twitgoo.com/kbygx    
    
    
    Just had first wet shave in about a decade - injury-free too. Could get used to this smoothness...    
    
    
    Ahh, I can almost hear the Hadoop cluster chugging away on the other side of the Atlantic, processing my data...    
    
    
    Just realised the date. Beware the eyes of Mars!    
    
    
    Beginning to really dislike the personalised Ask-an-animated-avatar services some companies put on their sites. Usually useless.    
    
    
    UK citizens to be disconnected from the net without any due process. ORG explains what you can do: http://bit.ly/9t4aTO RT! via @tomcoates    
    
    
    Same day response from my MP (Mark Lancaster) re: #DeBill. Pleasantly surprised. Let's hope he can turn his supportive words into actions.    
    
    
    @9600 It's like Hello World in optoelectrical form    
    
    
    Just had the plumbers in to fix immersion. Much breathing-in-between-clenched-teeth and general tutting. I see expense on the horizon.    
    
    
    @40_thieves This was the machine I inexpertly waxed lyrical about during the #BPark tour the other day: http://is.gd/aNkkH (link via @9600)    
    
    
    @mqtran Congrats on the paper acceptance!    
    
    
    @mqtran That'll teach me to read Tweets more carefully!    
    
    
    @ChristianHambly Impressive! Bon appétit...    
    
    
    @puntofisso Whenever I try putting usernames in it reports the same period (23-07) always calculated on exactly 0 tweets (at bottom of page)    
    
    
    @puntofisso OK, it 'works' if I use refresh link at bottom of page. You sleep between 1pm and 9pm?!    
    
    
    Alice in 3D was good, but not stellar. Would probably have been easier on the eyes in 2D, didn't take full advantage of that 3rd dimension    
    
    
    About to make the mistake of going to supermarket on an empty stomach. Will attempt to resist cake.    
    
    
    Best Glee quote ever: http://tinyurl.com/yfkex73 Sue Sylvester Rules.    
    
    
    If I were a terrorist, the last place I'd want to try and attack would be this one: http://tinyurl.com/yl2dr38    
    
    
    Finding this frequency monitor weirdly hypnotic http://tinyurl.com/ykez43f Is it wrong I keep wanting it to edge past either legal level?    
    
    
    Just received a 419 purportedly from the UK House of Lords offering FIVE HUNDRED THOUSANDS UK STERLING. Well, I *assume* it's a 419...    
    
    
    I may never go on a motorway again: http://tinyurl.com/yk72ycx    
    
    
    @barnstormed I was trying to guess what the moniker would be before your second Tweet, and it seems I guessed right. I see nappies...    
    
    
    @gridinoc Want to borrow mine? I got my kit a fortnight ago...    
    
    
    Much of my daily work is just fiddling with massive text files, formatting, reformatting, processing. Surely a machine should be doing this!    
    
    
    Today I shall strictly enforce my To Do lists. Things 'Will Get Done (tm)' and I shall feel achievement. That or curl up in a ball and cry.    
    
    
    @puntofisso Interesting!    
    
    
    @puntofisso I merely added it to my 'toRead:toDO' sublist and assigned it an appropriate priority level ;-)    
    
    
    At #mediaeval2011 in, appropriately, a mediaeval convent in Pisa. Placing Task overview presented, now enjoying other tasks...    
    
    
    Hard-Fi. Suburban Knights. Office escapism.    
    
    
    I do not recognise this version of Milton Keynes. Nuns? Woolworths? http://tinyurl.com/yh4e7vh    
    
    
    Sue Sylvester on 'Sneaky Gays'. Brilliant. http://bit.ly/dpvgqf (via @ahj)    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj Or it says that the International Conference on Science Essay deadline is April the 6th ;-)    
    
    
    @puntofisso Garage Band is very handy for such projects    
    
    
    Using maps to visualise where stuff comes from and how much carbon it costs: http://www.sourcemap.com/     
    
    
    Note re: Yahoo! Maps Web Services, shut down is on the 13th September http://developer.yahoo.com/maps  Check out http://api.maps.ovi.com  The King is dead etc    
    
    
    @Carter_AndrewJ I'd recommend a +4 Mace of Biting Satire.    
    
    
    Eek, just gave a presentation to the Vice-Chancellor of The Open University. Heart was pounding. Fortunately a friendly, knowledgeable guy    
    
    
    @andycodling Keep going, you can do it :-)    
    
    
    @bletchleypark Can #bpark get one of these and let me play with it pls?:-)Wonderful demo of a real Turing Machine http://tinyurl.com/ygd4mhz    
    
    
    @qikipedia Surely that should be "More than 90% of computers hackers *who get caught / brag* are male." :-D    
    
    
    Lunchtime at #ECIR after an interesting morning on machine learning in information retrieval    
    
    
    Completely pooped after long day at #ecir2010. Great keynote by Barry Smyth, social search is officially hot stuff. Phew. That's reassuring.    
    
    
    Multimedia and interaction analysis personal highlights for me today at #ecir . Looking forward to conference banquet tonight at #bpark !    
    
    
    I know I shouldn't be so shocked, but easyJet charge €16 for using a Visa card?! On what planet is that fair trading?    
    
    
    #bpark was perfect conference venue for #ecir banquet last night. Thanks to the guides who gave tours, and organisation staff, great job!    
    
    
    @vicchi Will there be @w3gconf stickers à la WhereCampEU to adorn my rather plain looking laptop? :-)    
    
    
    @vicchi Excellent - just found out some of the stickerage will be Y! stickerage. I shall be geo branded to the hilt...    
    
    
    Looks like #w3g is shaping up to be a great (un)conference, only a few days to go!    
    
    
    Attempting to cope with post conference deluge of stuff that has been on hold this last week. So. Many. Emails.    
    
    
    @barnstormed I evidently work on the wrong floor.    
    
    
    "Bow ties are cool" #opendata from @madprof and the battle to release data at #w3g    
    
    
    Geo apps development, the potential and challenges at #w3g , many of which couldn't have been made without #opendata    
    
    
    @rollohome one word: Harsh ;-)    
    
    
    @rollohome I'm seeing a healthy market for t-shirts with "I'm a flippant geographer" on them... #w3g    
    
    
    @rollohome @vanessa_murdock All in the name of geo science, naturally ;-) Great to meet you Rollo, until the next time!    
    
    
    The Inbetweeners marathon via 4od. Good stuff.    
    
    
    @puntofisso UK/EU having financial problems too, have UK/EU developers/orgs made better job of showing value of open data perhaps?    
    
    
    @puntofisso That's a key point, governments and their auditors aren't great at quantifying social benefit and indirect financial benefits    
    
    
    My 3 year old Macbook Pro is beginning to feel the strain. Time to find a pre-end-of-tax-year budget I can plunder for upgrades.    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Echoing a comment on there, gov.uk seems to have forgotten there's more to the UK than just GB. Horrific kerning too!    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Exactly! Tired, unimaginative old themes with nothing to differentiate it from almost everything that has gone before...    
    
    
    @andywasley @sosogay Well done guys!    
    
    
    Either I've stumbled onto the set of Shaun of the Dead 2 or I'm watching commuters heading into Milton Keynes rail station before 8am on a d    
    
    
    Well Barcelona, I'm not impressed with this so-called weather you seem to have at the moment. I expected an actual change from the UK!    
    
    
    To use "themself" or not to use "themself", that is my current grammatical dilemma.    
    
    
    @joshspero How about in the phrase "This is the first step in helping someone to help themself"? If one is trying to be non-gender specific?    
    
    
    Have got to the stage of pre-deadline-experiment-running when I wiggle my fingers at the monitor hoping for H. Potteresque magic to happen    
    
    
    One paper submitted on Sunday, another due on Wednesday. I'm sentence forging like some crazy wordsmith.    
    
    
    Getting confusing signals as to exactly which constituency I'm in after recent boundary changes. Can't find authoritative source #ge2010    
    
    
    Just realising very few of my clothes actually fit properly. I appear to be unfortunately clownish today. Must remedy.    
    
    
    I like my typographical ligatures, but can I get away with "æsthetics" in a science paper?    
    
    
    Seems my local MP said one thing to me in email regard #debill but instead of voting against, merely didn't turn up to vote at all.    
    
    
    Excellent news for Bletchley Park! http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-england-beds-bucks-herts-15171726 …    
    
    
    @gregorybradley Sounds like wise advice to me, and as it's serif, I'm gonna risk it...    
    
    
    Wait- THAT'S Justin Bieber?! THAT'S what all the tweens are swooning over? In my day we'd have wedgied him clean in half. (via @MitchBenn)    
    
    
    Dear Icelandic Volcano, could you ensure you don't belch forth too much ash mid next week as I'd like to get home in one piece, kbaithnx    
    
    
    Slightly Bond villain-esque approach there Iceland. Using a volcano to hold the UK to ransom over a few little banking issues...?    
    
    
    Bad Science Alert: You can't fairly compare between ranks with different members, changes between 2000/9 r meaningless http://bbc.in/h5yevW    
    
    
    Hmm, current phone giving up the ghost, so, iPhone 4[s], Galaxy S II or maybe the Nexus Prime?    
    
    
    Recognising inspirational women in science, maths, tech and engineering - it's Ada Lovelace Day, who are your geek heroines?    
    
    
    It seems gov.uk thinks that "homeoffice.gov.uk/agencies-public-bodies/ips/" is more 'accessible' than "ips.gov.uk" http://www.cabinetoffice.gov.uk/news/hundreds-government-websites-closed …    
    
    
    UK gov saves £1.7m by moving content from multiple domains to one? How much were they paying for domains?! They control .gov.uk anyway no?    
    
    
    @oobr Do you happen to know of open access data set for Barcelona Bicing network? I'm prepared to scrape, would rather reuse...    
    
    
    @oobr Cool, thanks!    
    
    
    @RealBillBailey May I join you? Am stuck here also. Have my own spade and extra baggy trousers with string around ankles.    
    
    
    Seems my magical ability to fix set of speakers by not using them for a few months strikes again. I'm good. Very good. The power is scary.    
    
    
    Getting back into the local swing of things with a siesta. Feel rejuvenated!    
    
    
    Weird, I'm a bit ambivalent about the idea of getting an iPad, yet last night I dreamt I had one, although it appeared to be running WinCE    
    
    
    @gregorybradley I went with the aesc/ash as, ultimately, on balance, taking all things into account, I liked the look of it in this paper:-)    
    
    
    @vicchi My attempt after consultation with an Icelander sounded more like Ear-Full-Of-Yoghurt and so shall it hence be known    
    
    
    Arg. Likelihood of me getting back to the UK tomorrow look increasingly slim. If I don't make it tomorrow, unlikely to return before weekend    
    
    
    Borrowing an Apple Magic Mouse for a bit. I want one of my own now. I really want one. It loves my fingers. If only it were cheaper!    
    
    
    I have, thru prayer to the mighty Ear-Full-Of-Yoghurt, managed to get back to the UK! Plane v. late and half empty, but got me home. Phew.    
    
    
    Everyone vote #LibDem and @Nick_Clegg to make Murdoch Lose Britain (please RT to help boost TT)! (via @carter_andrewj)    
    
    
    @carter_andrewj @marcdonnchadh That tweet was so cringeworthy it's given me a heart murMur, Doctor! 

Yep. Bad, very bad. I'm sorry.    
    
    
    Having to use MS Word for writing a scientific document - utter miserable pain...    
    
    
    Hearing Nick Clegg referring to the "old parties" was telling and subtle enough not to seem too rehearsed. #leadersdebate    
    
    
    