Sundays in #Cork. Oldies and Irish and a roast. #Daycent pic.twitter.com/hddljPDeRJ    
    
    
    It's the same every day at my parents house Judge Judy and Steve Wilkos double bills. Exhausting stuff.    
    
    
    Something to remember for my move to Dublin pic.twitter.com/sKRhrhLRI3    
    
    
    "There are four lights" I'm in #The1701    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I still tend toward the late 50s myself. I'm a Mad Man at heart you're a hippy commie.    
    
    
    It's being a suit to college day #interviews pic.twitter.com/mHYTVd8jCs    
    
    
    Enjoyed the mock interview today for class. Of all the subjects I've ever performed a presentation on, myself was probably the strangest.    
    
    
    There's a guy standing in front of me on the bus "bus surfing" apparently I'm not the only person in the world that does that.    
    
    
    Well done Jason Collins. http://sportsillustrated.cnn.com/magazine/news/20130429/jason-collins-gay-nba-player/#ixzz2RrjYUqUM …    
    
    
    Google Now on iOS is good fun isn't it? Will probably be a massive drain on battery though on my old iPhone 4    
    
    
    Testing out self deleting tweets from efemr this goes away in sixty seconds apparently #1m    
    
    
    needless to say it's still a bit buggy    
    
    
    Last night my poor teammate broke our project for submission and presentation today, he's absolutely distraught. #DontWorry    
    
    
    @Adlers1 to not so subtly tell people you like them "in that way" no?    
    
    
    Interesting idea http://www.tweetbookz.com  create a physical book of your twitter feed.    
    
    
    30 needles in my leg today at the physio. I'm Hellraiser. #NoPainNoGain    
    
    
    My Countdown project is gaining momentum "RT @FullSpectrum13 30 Days to Full Spectrum Degree Show #fullspectrum #30 pic.twitter.com/T57Voqm3Kb"    
    
    
    @Adlers1 anyone that has ever poked me has at least wanted to... Well I won't finish that sentence.    
    
    
    18 days until a new life in Dublin. #BleedinDeadly    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I'll be hanging out all the time, you'll both be bugged from me, it's been far too long.    
    
    
    Hellz yeah “@CROSSYFM104: SO TOMORROW pic.twitter.com/W8olnVIIHI”    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Work and Love. I'm finishing CIT so I'm my field Diblin is the best place and janis is moving there he has a job secured though    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell score, thanks. I'll need all the eyes and ears I can get to find a job ASAP.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell looked up that job, nice place to start out fresh outta college. I'll be applying tonight.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I noticed that but the earlier you're in the better chance of getting a base English speaking role plus my German isn't bad.    
    
    
    I started the day with one gaol project housing and ended the day with a completely different one. #Yikes    
    
    
    It's my hope that I can have one more module finished in it's entirety by the end of the day. #2toGo    
    
    
    My picture and my house number. @FullSpectrum13 @CIT_ie degree show at Wandsford Quay gallery in 28 days #cork pic.twitter.com/jhZ0SzvXCP    
    
    
    @CorkBuzz1 My picture & my house too @FullSpectrum13 @CIT_ie degree show at Wandsford Quay gallery in 28 days #cork pic.twitter.com/uYLyW1ih6j    
    
    
    @IFTN Multimedia and Visual Comms @CIT_ie degree show @FullSpectrum13 at Wandsford Quay gallery #cork is in 28 days pic.twitter.com/Nq4okLtSlg    
    
    
    Going for lunch with @RichDsy. Actually  does he actively use the twitter anymore or is he just a lurker.    
    
    
    @RichDsy the perverted man in the corner watching people use the "new technology" We'll all be there someday.    
    
    
    I wonder how many people will get number 26. It's a very recognisable place but not number. @FullSpectrum13 #TheNumbersProject    
    
    
    Can you figure out where today's @FullSpectrum13 countdown photo comes from? "26 Days! pic.twitter.com/eO12CgzPL8"Clue: it's a student hotspot.    
    
    
    I've had really bad fever dreams today, college featured heavily of course. Glad to wake up in the real world though.    
    
    
    Fundraiser Gig for @FullSpectrum13 in @CyprusAveCork Tues 7/5 9pm - €5 - Waking Up Sunday Tuesday Boots 25 days to go pic.twitter.com/1zclRBDqyv    
    
    
    Hey @whazoncork, how about a retweet out of the goodness of your Cork loving hearts? https://twitter.com/JiveCork/status/331110922783444992 … it would be very appreciated.    
    
    
    @damienmulley Damien, how about a retweet for a very good cause? We need to rasie money for our college exhibition. https://twitter.com/JiveCork/status/331110922783444992 …    
    
    
    @damienmulley You sir are a scholar and a gent.    
    
    
    Kris Kross - Jump: http://youtu.be/010KyIQjkTk  #WiggidaWiggidaWiggidaWack    
    
    
    No rest for the wicked. Off to the physio next.    
    
    
    Star Trek tomorrow night, on my birthday, AGAIN. Can't wait.    
    
    
    Isn't physiotherapy mad. I just paid my friend's girlfriend to feel me up for an hour. Anywhere else that'd be frowned upon.    
    
    
    Full Spectrum gig tonight, Cyprus Avenue! #Cork 9pm €5 entry ! Great bands! DJ and Spot prizes and MY BIRTHDAY DRINKS pic.twitter.com/SBg1gfvJf5    
    
    
    How cute @ryandolanmusic and team Ireland look #eurovision http://fb.me/21xnyPeT0  #InItToWinIt    
    
    
    Good morning Alan. pic.twitter.com/D9UFfCLo5k    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Thanks Wolfgang. 10 days to my Dublin move too.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Very. College finishes on the 17th and I move on the 18th. Scary but brilliant.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime We should definitely catch up. No job but the boyfriend who is moving too is the new Revenue Manager for Travelodge Irl so..    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime we have a place to stay for free until we find an apartment. I'm hoping to break into social media through the C.S. roles    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Yep. WE've been separated by his training in the UK for the last 6 months and definitely feel that it's time #CantWait    
    
    
    Just blew my mind by thinking "The true Deadliest Catch… is the human doing the catching" :P http://dsc.discovery.com/tv-shows/deadliest-catch … …    
    
    
    Wow I'm wrecked from a tough week. One more tough week ahead though.    
    
    
    At the dentist for a check up. #yuck    
    
    
    After this only one more module to go. 4 years of work end in 7 days. pic.twitter.com/JBzMagRnU5    
    
    
    Here we go "RT @FullSpectrum13: 20 Days! pic.twitter.com/Iik74T8eM9"    
    
    
    Ever feel like telling somebody they're not doing it right? http://www.funnyjunk.com/funny_pictures/218106/your …    
    
    
    50 Billion app downloads by tomorrow morning. Amazing. #iTunes pic.twitter.com/h1QOXmlwik    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell chill out. I'll be on my way up there this time next week.    
    
    
    One of my personal favourites. I really have to make a poster of these. RT "@FullSpectrum13: 19 Days! pic.twitter.com/cwTTJ8juq2"    
    
    
    Beyond exhausted, perpetually on the edge of sickness and more stressed than an elastic at breaking point. This is the final week of college    
    
    
    Tired and Emotional “@kjmarsh: Paula White pulled off last BBC show early : Radio Today AUDIO http://bit.ly/13NHsUQ  >> quite some sign off”    
    
    
    SAturday Night Live with Kristen Wiig, I'm starting the day in style.    
    
    
    No bus services operating in Cork, Galway, Limerick, Clare or Kerry and the Greater Dublin Area due to the bus eireann strikes action.    
    
    
    Interesting read “@mathewi: "Back to the future: What if the 'mass media' era was just an accident of history?" http://nie.mn/10iyGh7 ”    
    
    
    @ryandolanmusic congrats, will listen on Monday to get me ready for Tuesday's performance #ComeOnIreland    
    
    
    F1 spoiler from both my mother and my father. After all the years of switching off the news when the soccer results come on. #SchoolboyError    
    
    
    Bus Éireann strike set to continue into tomorrow and beyond http://www.rte.ie/news/2013/0512/391767-bus-eireann-strike/ …    
    
    
    It's always so geeky to hear Patrick Steward introducing each race on #bbcf1 I keep waiting for him to say Engage.    
    
    
    There are some beautiful visuals in the original Star Trek movie but it really is the most boring two hours you'll ever spend.    
    
    
    Affected by the Bus Éireann strike? The #liftfairy can help http://jrnl.to/125adu4     
    
    
    So while @robinscreech4 goes to get glue I do my my physio Sometimes I really think I am #DoingTime 4 days    
    
    
    @OrlaFlynnCCAD Thanks for the follow Orla. I hope you're enjoying my #fullspectrum countdown pics.    
    
    
    It's almost ready for #fullspectrum "The Gaol Project" #DoingTime pic.twitter.com/hRN9JH7Y9n    
    
    
    @OrlaFlynnCCAD hehe, it certainly does stand out. Enjoy, and I hope to see you at the exhibition. Don't forget to say hi.    
    
    
    @greentothebone oooooooooooh well that's what I'm doing after Game of Thrones then.    
    
    
    @LeamCanto @rtenews Bachelor's quay is the city centre though. Anything on the central island is.    
    
    
    I had a dream about construction of #DoingTime last night. I'm a little obsessed.    
    
    
    Rising? It's always been there “@thejournal_ie: Horrific murder fuels fears of rising homophobia in Russia http://jrnl.to/1282prF ”    
    
    
    Daft Punk Random Access Memories really is great music to write final presentations to. #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Giovanni Giorgio sounds so much like Werner Herzog on the new Daft Punk album it's spooky.    
    
    
    It's time for #DoingTime our final year project to move on. Transporting it to @CIT_ie now.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell what's happening with him. I've heard other people talking about him too. Please tell me he's leaving.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Are we all supposed to be racists now? Ah jaysus, I don't have time for racism. 2 1/2 days left.    
    
    
    Heading back up to college. Lets get this thang done.    
    
    
    "Doing Time" is up and running at the @CIT_ie Multimedia symposium tonight on the top floor of the IT building from 6-8pm #DoingTime    
    
    
    Eurovision Running order for Saturday. Amazing Result for Ireland number 26 of 26 http://www.eurovision.tv/page/news?id=running_order_for_the_grand_final_revealed …    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow back @WolfgangDigital I'll be keeping an eye out for any vacancies you advertise in the near future.    
    
    
    Let my phone at home as I was about to get on the bus as I move to Dublin. Cue movie style rush through traffic. My mother had great fun.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Cheers Wolfgang. We must catch up some time soon too. I'll be free a lot as I start the job search.    
    
    
    Giggle “@damienmulley: "Damien Mulley blogger and traffic source" Maybe you should have removed that last bit before contacting me”    
    
    
    "Time" to move on. The story of Doing Time. #DoingTime #FullSpectrum http://aroconnor.tumblr.com/post/50728866658/birth-and-rebirth …    
    
    
    @bbceurovision Alan and Jānis are watching in Dublin and scoring the acts as they go, playing for a bottle of wine.    
    
    
    Waking to my first day in Dublin with a dream about college. C'mon brain, it's time to switch off.    
    
    
    So Dublin what do you have to offer today?    
    
    
    First day as a resident in Dublin and I'm treating myself to something yummy @bobosburgers I'm gonna enjoy this.    
    
    
    I bought a leap card so I'm pretty much a Dub now #BleedinDeadly    
    
    
    Gonna attempt to have a stress free day today. I've been going non stop since.... Well January actually.    
    
    
    The world's top brands: Apple, Google, IBM, McDonalds, Coca Cola, AT&T, Micosoft, Marlboro, Visa, China Mobile. Yikes I've used 8.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Yep I'd need too move to China or take up smoking to complete the set. Two things I'm unprepared to do.    
    
    
    The shiny new argument cleaning up across the net.  http://www.lurkingglass.com/threads/how-do-you-pronounce-gif.103149/ …    
    
    
    No fears here Mr Brogan (whoever you are) I walk around Ballymun alone all the time. pic.twitter.com/5d2D8ZVDa6    
    
    
    @RichDsy Hehe, everything is quite nearby. Only problem I had was being asked "are you gay" on the way home from ikea with Jānis last night.    
    
    
    Someone really should start tweeting under #ApartmentFairy it's impossible to get a place in Dublin.    
    
    
    @RichDsy Nope, with a bit of luck that's the plan for tonight though. We just took the bus back from Finglas and it ends there.    
    
    
    One apartment viewing ahead of us today. Just one. Looking for a place here is a full time job in itself.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell that @AnnCoulter tweet is a weird one. His political leanings and religion are much more important than skin colour.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell oh yeah, I know that after all you know when @piersmorgan calls @AnnCoulter a publicity leech there is a problem. Would...    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell have expected her to focus on the usual hot button topics or religion or politics though. See what @LennoxLewis said?    
    
    
    Looking for a place to live, a job and updating my website at the same time. That's multitasking.    
    
    
    @recruitireland I'll take a peek now. Lets see what you have for someone e in Digital Media in Dublin.    
    
    
    It doesn't happen often but this little guy is the bane of my life. pic.twitter.com/2sIlcOtt4E    
    
    
    @garethoconnor I guarantee you'll love it. Plenty for fans and new viewers alike.... action packed too.    
    
    
    Dear god there is a Penny Pushing daytime TV quiz show called Tipping Point. The wonders I've missed being in college :p    
    
    
    My throat is so sore today. Much to my boyfriends happiness it's gonna be a one day vow of silence for me.    
    
    
    I've just updated my profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me, view my profile and most of all recommend me at http://lnkd.in/KDbamw     
    
    
    Chilling out with @JaLazLV #NowPlaying 7 Seconds (Duet With Neneh Cherry) by Youssou N'Dour on #Spotify http://open.spotify.com/track/76D5nfZbYzZYfUZKGy73jy …    
    
    
    We at #DoingTime get a mention “@CIT_ie: Light shines on Full Spectrum | The #Cork News http://thecorknews.ie/articles/light-shines-full-spectrum-10791 …"    
    
    
    Letting agents in Dublin think you came down with the last shower if you say you're from Cork. Tried to get 200 over the asking price.    
    
    
    Monaco GP highlights on the BBC. Excellent.    
    
    
    Ok cork, I'll see you tomorrow :)    
    
    
    Ok Cork, I'm coming down, what have ya got for me?    
    
    
    @dellers yuck, glad I've brought the raincoat so.    
    
    
    @greentothebone it's about to start in Dublin too. I just escaped it.    
    
    
    @greentothebone Actually, you coming to the exhibition on Thursday Ross?    
    
    
    Thank goodness Jānis would never share if this is the kind of person advertising. #NeedAPlaceInDublin pic.twitter.com/50FNnZM85R    
    
    
    See my creation Doing Time at Full Spectrum, opening 6.30pm Thurs May 3 until June 8 at CIT Wandesford Quay Gallery http://www.citdegreeexhibitions.com     
    
    
    @greentothebone Excellent I look forward to seeing you there. I know you for a while now but we've never actually met.    
    
    
    I've been next on the queue for 30mins already. This is stretching my patience a lil but.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime ah it's alright so far. Getting a place (and a job) is a pain but I'm actually down in cork now for Thursday's exhibition.    
    
    
    12 months later I'm still dealing with an ex manager who didn't give me a p45.    
    
    
    My mother was very impressed my project for @FullSpectrum13 was mentioned in @TheCorkNews    
    
    
    Now officially JiveCork on Snapchat. I'd better see what everyone is talking about.    
    
    
    Right then Star Trek in bed it is. Staying with the parents for a few days is extremely boring.    
    
    
    Oooh I think I'm through to the second round of an Online Specialist job. I say I think because the email was especially cryptic.    
    
    
    Interesting that RTE are honouring the requests of parents not to repeat #PrimeTime PSB at its best. http://www.thejournal.ie/rte-no-repeats-or-online-airing-of-prime-time-creche-investigation-928711-May2013/?utm_source=twitter_self …    
    
    
    Finally :) A new @SminkyAnimation Sminky Short, Elephant. http://youtu.be/2uZQnhvf49o     
    
    
    @robinscreech4 neither did I and I think it's a pity it's not repeated but doing this works for everyone. Watch the #PrimeTime ratings soar.    
    
    
    Aaaah a nice cold can of @CocaCola on ireland's yearly sunny day. #perfection    
    
    
    Is Nelly singing about Portia di Rossi? #NowPlaying Hey Porsche by Nelly who is #BarkingUpTheWrongTree http://open.spotify.com/track/3uuGbRzMsDI5RiKWKOjqWL …    
    
    
    Kicking off tonight at 6:30 until June 8th visit #DoingTime in the Multimedia room @FullSpectrum13 pic.twitter.com/XM6OzEwxw4    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell thanks Kev. We're the white one in the middle pic.twitter.com/7qlkxC1KQe    
    
    
    @greentothebone thanks Ross. Delighted to see so many people turn up and    
    
    
    @greentothebone to meet you for the 1st time too.    
    
    
    Had to run to catch the bus to Dublin there. Back to reality after a fabulous night at @FullSpectrum13. Bye Cork    
    
    
    Traveling to Dublin on an @Aircoach without air conditioning or windows #baked should have went with gobé    
    
    
    It just felt so good to turn down a letting agent who tried to get one over on us. Balance of power restored.    
    
    
    Hoping the guys at @awty2013 are having a great time. The people from @FullSpectrum13 send you all the best. #ortloike    
    
    
    Leaving the folks at Travelodge Ballymun to move into the new place. Seriously in need of unpacking.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Thanks Derek. Say hi if you're gonna be up for #DublinPride    
    
    
    There's a man behind me on the bus that sounds like old Mr Brennan. I really am living in #Dublin    
    
    
    "and nicknamed the Rebel County, since the Senate hearings last week." Not the only factual inaccuracy in this story  http://mobile.bloomberg.com/news/2013-05-31/apple-no-ghost-in-ireland-where-cork-frets-senate-hearing-taxes.html …    
    
    
    Waking up for the first time in the new apartment. Still getting used to the mattress. Place is lookin good though.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Top of Glasnevin bottom of Finglas. Very nice apartment, top floor too so it has a great view.    
    
    
    On http://twitter.com  you can now get tailored trends to Cork and Galway too. Time to get #Langer trending. pic.twitter.com/1Goc0XEVFw    
    
    
    Getting bills and finances sorted today. Who knew there was so much paperwork in moving house?    
    
    
    @beccanoonan I'm at it's counterpart in Finglas now. Great pictures coming from you all in the states I'm crazy jealous.    
    
    
    Ben Dunne gyms. Worth the bus trip from Finglas for the cheaper price or not? #Dublin    
    
    
    So this @irishexaminer Limerick billboard that's gotten everyone up in arms is a bit silly. Bad idea to put it outside Limerick station too.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe I spotted the Finglas leisure centre alright, its a fair walk from me but could be worth it. Are you local too?    
    
    
    @RichDsy    
    
    
    @RichDsy Indeed you could. You're pretty much the reason I'll rent for life.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe Prospect Hill the border between Finglas and Glasnevin. The hunt goes well, I have a Skype interview with a US startup 2mor.    
    
    
    . @bobosburgers It's almost worth the bus into town on this glorious day.    
    
    
    Fire alarm at the apartment block, there's only one thing for it... Go out and enjoy the sun in the shared garden until it stops.    
    
    
    Big day planned today. I have a lot of walking around to do but it's sunny so :D    
    
    
    Broken leap card scanner on the bus. Free trip to town, well that's a good start to the day.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Happy out. The new place is lovely, I have an interview later today the only trial is getting stuff up from Cork. I need a van.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 and how are you keeping in Cork?    
    
    
    Going to take a look at the European Space Expo in @tcddublin it certainly is quite an impressive structure. pic.twitter.com/walsuwaowO    
    
    
    Loving the live soapbox talks at @SpaceExpoDublin in association with @ScienceGallery pic.twitter.com/yVjwKjREZK    
    
    
    @blueswannabe it went really well actually, nice chat with lively people, fingers crossed. I just passed the IFIC area there actually.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe Working hard no doubt. Just found out I have another interview with a different company next week too. #ThingsArePickingUp    
    
    
    THAT episode of Game of Thrones will be viewed in the penthouse tonight. #NoSpoilers    
    
    
    Watching Teen Wolf Season 3. #GuiltyPleasure #NightOff    
    
    
    @mushacles Not the greatest episode to be honest a lot of glossing over the 2nd season ending.    
    
    
    Yikes MT “@Kotaku: Microsoft confirms that Xbox One will need to connect to the Internet every 24 hours for gaming: http://bit.ly/17s1J6O ”    
    
    
    Channel 4 certainly have the right idea MT “@siliconrepublic: Channel 4 to launch dedicated second screen app: http://silrep.com/13fNtIr ”    
    
    
    Busy busy busy. Back to #Cork for 24 hours.    
    
    
    No autocorrect I didn't mean mire, the much more likely more would have been a better choice. #SnootyAutocorrect    
    
    
    If there's one thing I've learned in life it's if you ever get lost looking for Abercrombie & Fitch then follow your nose.    
    
    
    About to enjoy a free breakfast thanks to the folks at Denny Ireland and @98FM here at their Grafton Street pop up cafe. YUM.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Who is it you're working with at the moment actually?    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Lemmie know if they're hiring then :D)))) Still shopping around for a job here. Looking to earn myself some €€€.    
    
    
    Re-watching The Name of the Doctor while on the bus to Cork. This episode makes up for all the crappy ones this season. #Trenzelore    
    
    
    The Queen Photobombs The BBC http://www.buzzfeed.com/sirajdatoo/the-queen-photobombs-the-bbc?sub=2305581_1248293 …    
    
    
    There's something very weird about waking up without an alarm at 8am on Sunday. Feels like a missed opportunity.    
    
    
    After over a year of watching F1 on streams I finally get to watch a race live again... and in HD.    
    
    
    We desperately need some rain for Alonso #BBCF1 #f1    
    
    
    ALO battling HAM for second. Come on Ferando. 11 laps remaining. #canadiangp #f1 #bbcf1    
    
    
    Annonces françaises tonight on Channel 4 to celebrate #TheReturned    
    
    
    Can't wait “@TheDailyShow: John Oliver takes his seat behind The #DailyShow desk tomorrow night! 11/10c. pic.twitter.com/9Ltuj8nFWi”    
    
    
    OSX Mavericks? MAVERICKS? So they're naming it after a Mel Gibson movie.    
    
    
    Now that I'm finally going to use the Xbox I'm very happy to hear about the death of Microsoft Points.    
    
    
    It's all lovely that Safari is shiny and new but get to the point guys. I'm switching from #WWDC to #e32013    
    
    
    Ok I must admit App Nap is both a great idea and clever name.    
    
    
    iCloud keychain, given their track record on cloud services I reserve judgement until I hear that it works. #wwdc    
    
    
    Maps App. How about making the maps open source instead? Fanboys would fix this thing together quite easily. #wwdc    
    
    
    iBook text books with high fidelity content on the mac. That's the future folks. #MakeItHappen #wwdc    
    
    
    Here comes the Air. All day battery life FTW #WWDC    
    
    
    Ship date for Xbox One is November. #e32013    
    
    
    Piano black finish and cylindrical display. The new Mac Pro looks weird. It may kick ass but looks cheap #wwdc    
    
    
    Office 365 from Apple then. iWork for iCloud, iSnooze. Where's my ios7? #wwdc    
    
    
    iOS FINALLY. #wwdc    
    
    
    I'd say my iPhone 4 may either just scrape this update or is gonna be left behind. #TearsForIOS7 #WWDC    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa The software on the phones and iPads.    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa Thank gawd. :D)))))    
    
    
    Very flat, very nice though. It's just so...... Different. #wwdc    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa I really like the new look. Dammit, I'm gonna have to get a 5S aren't I?    
    
    
    Transparency on Control Centre, that's excellent. #wwdc    
    
    
    New Siri sounds good but iOS in the car is really the next step. #wwdc    
    
    
    iTunes radio. IT LIVES #wwdc I betcha it's not in Ireland though.    
    
    
    ios7 on iPhone 4 and later YAY. I'm delighted #wwdc    
    
    
    Between the excitement of WWDC and Game Of Thrones tonight I'm in nerd heaven.    
    
    
    So, how long before iTunes Radio comes to Ireland? I'm predicting one year. It could never be available from launch, could it?    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I wouldn't mind paying for iTunes Match in that case. A cheap one off payment and replace my DRM songs too. #WhyNot    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I love Spotify and must admit it has some thing iTunes Radio hasn't but I could live without them to save 100ish quid.    
    
    
    This makes me so happy RT “@JoannaStern: Confirmed: You can put Newsstand into a folder in iOS 7!!”    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I passed your offices a few mind ago, had been at the shopping centre and was passing. Nice place.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Definitely next time I'm up here interested in the couples memberships at Dunne's Gym.    
    
    
    Watching Star Trek the Original Series on CBS Action. I must be very bored.    
    
    
    Yikes, I'm currently watching a CNN correspondent Arwa Damon getting hit by tear gas in Istanbul. #turkey    
    
    
    Ad for Ibiza club Matinée is an 80s/90s dream. These guys have to work with Daft Punk. http://youtu.be/ED5azV-xrHM     
    
    
    That's UCC on How I Met Your Mother again. Always so weird.    
    
    
    Could someone at @RTENewsNow take a look at the tabs on the right of the screen they need to be re-aligned as they're going over the picture    
    
    
    Lovely shop assistant in Jack & Jones wants to help me pick out my boxers. The prude in me blushes at the thought. #SoIrish    
    
    
    @spiller2 I did get that feeling but she was a lady and I'm a happily married man. #Shudder    
    
    
    #ManOfSteel #CantWait pic.twitter.com/qs1xNzMEi7    
    
    
    Dear makers of "Man of Steel", tonight you have made me a very angry man. #ManOfSteel #Rant    
    
    
    Looks like Dublin Zoo is on the agenda today. Young Mr. Jānis is very excited.    
    
    
    It's been a funny old day. Aches and pains from an awkward sleep but I had good fun in town. #Dublin    
    
    
    I'm hooked on Big Brother already, I'm loing Michael the fake Cork contestant. #BB #SecretsAndLies    
    
    
    Listening to @stephenfry on @Herring1967 Leicester Square podcast speaking about his bi-polar disorder. Such an interesting subject matter.    
    
    
    Just pushed through a few updates to http://www.aroconnor.com  time flies content gets old and twitter changes their API. All solved now though    
    
    
    Nominations live. I'm loving #BBUK so much right now.    
    
    
    @brianclayton probably HMV again. They're reopening in Dublin and Limerick too.    
    
    
    Beautiful day for @MichelleObama to visit Glendalough. #IrishSummer    
    
    
    @brianclayton That's quite a coup I haven't bought a physical CD or DVD in years but its good to see a small company expanding these days.    
    
    
    WHA? “@GMA: Neil Patrick Harris to star as Hedwig in "Hedwig and the Angry Inch" on Broadway” #IJustDied    
    
    
    It's always weird when you see someone you've followed on twitter in real life. I think I've just seen @darraghdoyle    
    
    
    @darraghdoyle *wipes the tears (of laughter) away.    
    
    
    Where's my Mickey? Coming Thursday #Facepalm http://thenextweb.com/apps/2013/06/18/disney-builds-on-hit-water-puzzler-franchise-with-wheres-my-mickey-game/?utm_medium=Spreadus&awesm=tnw.to_a0ZBG&utm_campaign=social%20media&utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    Blurring the lines pic.twitter.com/LuAiC3XEPj    
    
    
    The poor bored Obama kids. http://abcnews.go.com/GMA/video/malia-sasha-obama-vacation-obama-girls-impressed-summer-19426194 …    
    
    
    So, I have a degree now (Very happy).    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Cheers. There will be celebrations :D    
    
    
    I should really celebrate the end of college tonight. But how?    
    
    
    @blueswannabe oh yes, but very rarely and I'm at a wedding tomorrow and it'll be expected there. Would much prefer good food or a movie.    
    
    
    Xbox One is a market player. Not only have they Uturned on stuff they've also canceled regional restrictions http://news.xbox.com/2013/06/update     
    
    
    And we are awake, Cork, I'm heading your way.    
    
    
    At a wedding in Blarney, quite tired and hungry. Food will perk me up though.    
    
    
    Oh my god, how did nobody tell me sorbet could be THIS good.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell yep I'm at a wedding in Blarney. Never had it before (not in the least bit posh) its GORGEOUS.    
    
    
    I'm stuffed. One day I think I'll turn into a potato. Then I'll probably cannibalistically eat myself because I smell sooo good.    
    
    
    Being at this wedding the sudden realisation has hit me I'm definitely a city boy. Farming was mentioned in the speeches.    
    
    
    This is one hell of a groom's speech. #LovelyGuy    
    
    
    Maybe it's all the sugar from the cake but I'd love a bit of Crystal Swing now.    
    
    
    Mad traffic on the way into Dublin and its moving extremely slowly.    
    
    
    Such a mistake to take Michael the people's puppet out tonight. I'd vote for him to win if I could. #BBUK #PeoplesPuppet    
    
    
    Folks looking for work, good luck. “@ConorCulkin: Mahon Point cinema and Suas bar both looking for for staff. #jobfairy”    
    
    
    Refreshing my typing skills by typing song lyrics. "You don't need money, 
Don't take fame, Don't need no credit card to ride this train."    
    
    
    I'm usually not a sucker fro advert songs but "Michelle Gayle - Sweetness" is a classic http://youtu.be/xvK26tC9UNY     
    
    
    I really enjoy seeing @iainlee on #bbots he should be on the show more often though, he's great fun. @bbuk sort it out.    
    
    
    I just realised I haven't played all of Tomb Raider, Guardian of Light. Lets get this done. #TripBackInTime    
    
    
    Catching up on my film review podcasts trying to figure out weather to go see #WorldWarZ or not.    
    
    
    The @KermodeMovie review of #ManOfSteel is so on the button it's scary.    
    
    
    @Adlers1 Is that in Ballymun?    
    
    
    Big afternoon tomorrow #FingersCrossed    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Indeed. A little nervous but it'll (hopefully) be fine. Meet up this week?    
    
    
    Three mobile phone network down across the country (Thank goodness I thought it was just me) http://jrnl.ie/964056     
    
    
    And we're back. The last few hours without internet were dark times. Dark, dark times :P @threecare    
    
    
    Interviews are always a bit exhausting but now I can relax for the evening.    
    
    
    @Adlers1 Weird, it looked so familiar (though I could know it from Killarney too).    
    
    
    Oh Silvio Berlusconi you're never gonna go to jail but at least you're banned from public office.    
    
    
    My 10,000th tweet I dedicate to my @JaLazLV    
    
    
    10,001 thanks to @kevinjpurcell @robinscreech4 @greentothebone @shiteandonions @thejackanory @damienmulley @dmndnn pic.twitter.com/YVyPknJvuC    
    
    
    @JaLazLV http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ViwtNLUqkMY …    
    
    
    @dmndnn I finally broke 10,000 so I looked to see who I contacted most in that time and the words I used most (you're on the list)    
    
    
    @dmndnn Downloaded my entire archive from the settings section on twitter and let http://Wordle.com  do the rest.    
    
    
    As in life “@bbuk: "Be tactful" is a good rule. #BBUK”    
    
    
    @ippily You're zooming through them. :)    
    
    
    "No, I'm not going to the world cup". A video to make to think. http://youtu.be/ZApBgNQgKPU     
    
    
    Trading #BBUK for #PrimeTime. Unfortunately things couldn't be more REALITY on the latter.    
    
    
    Not a great job on covering the situation tonight on #rtept too much navel gazing. Put on @MiriamOCal, mammy will sort it out.    
    
    
    "Gym?" "Eh I suppose so." That's my inner monologue people. #nopainnogain    
    
    
    Good first day back at the gym, I'm gonna get that dodgy knee fixed by hook or by crook.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 I'm waiting on an email today with fingers crossed.    
    
    
    @robinscreech4 Mostly businesses    
    
    
    According to twitter's stats I'm tweeting less now than at any other point in my history. Maybe it doesn't have the same attraction?    
    
    
    GOT THAT JOB :D    
    
    
    Forced myself to the gym today because I had work celebrations last night. So so difficult, I wouldn't recommend it.    
    
    
    This would be nice in my apartment ;) pic.twitter.com/N16nPW9kzX    
    
    
    Passing by Rte News nonchalantly as they film a piece to camera. This is the real reason I moved to Dublin.    
    
    
    @garethoconnor Were you not miffed by him not living up to his ideals in the ending (trying to not give spoilers to others)?    
    
    
    @garethoconnor Fair point I guess, I was happy with most of the movie but (fittingly) that was the straw that broke the camel's back for me.    
    
    
    @CROSSYFM104 Enjoyed your DJing last night at the party and you played Kiki for me. Cheers.    
    
    
    Louis should stay out. There's no way he can win and theres no reason to wreck the car. #f1 #BritishGP    
    
    
    I know I shouldn't, especially after the gym, but I wanted that hot chicken roll so bad.    
    
    
    Visited Google Reader for the last time, such a shame to see it go. Underused and under appreciated. #MarkAsRead    
    
    
    A new addition to the collection today my hard drives Space and Time have a new brother... Beyond. #Nerdgasam    
    
    
    Mummy, aka Jackie Travers is angry. #bbuk    
    
    
    Who changed or tried to change their nomination? #bbuk #bbnoms    
    
    
    Taking a trip to the office to see what Barrow Street has to offer.    
    
    
    New Ben and Jerry's Ireland flavours Áras an uachtar reoite is the best. http://thedailyedge.thejournal.ie/irish-ice-cream-flavours-ben-and-jerrys-975421-Jul2013/?utm_source=facebook_short …    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Did indeed, thanks.    
    
    
    #NowPlaying Be My Baby by The Ronettes on #Spotify #ThisIsMyJam http://open.spotify.com/track/3BdC6ZHg7g8MhKr96gbJ2u …    
    
    
    Two young men on the bus with bow ties, bowler hats and umbrellas (even though its not raining). You don't get that in Cork.    
    
    
    Oh wait, they're tourists who probably think this is genuinely Irish clothing. At least it's not a flat cap I guess.    
    
    
    The "Time Travel" bill would see us on a different timezone to our neighbours across the border http://www3.todayfm.com/reader/421.435/243/0/ …    
    
    
    Second day in a row going to the gym. There's nothing g better to motivate me like paying in advance.    
    
    
    I now have Star Trek style pointy sideburns. Best barber ever.    
    
    
    One thing I hate about gyms is the people who take two machines at the same time. #SharingIsCaring    
    
    
    My list of ten things to do today is down to three. Now that's a productive day.    
    
    
    Resisted the temptation of a post gym hot chicken roll. #Success    
    
    
    Why games of today are easier and how  today's gamers couldn't play the 1st level of Super Mario. http://www.p4rgaming.com/majority-of-gamers-today-cant-finish-level-1-in-super-mario-bros/ …    
    
    
    Goodnight all.    
    
    
    @NyleLennon would be right. Jaysus the death section in the paper will be huge. #DyaSeeWhoDied    
    
    
    I'd like to change this T-Shirt so it ends with... = Good Times. (From the Rally for Life people) http://fb.me/25WIyhKoU     
    
    
    And is Dan getting a warning for breaking the rules while pushing Dexter? Ah come on #TeamDexter #bbuk @bbbots    
    
    
    @Adlers1 Fair dues to her :) it's always great to hear the good stories when there are so many bad ones out there.    
    
    
    It's boiling in Dublin today. How can I go to the gym on a day like today. Topless in the park anyone?    
    
    
    Tesco wifi fluctuating between 37 and 64 kbps. I could send a carrier pigeon to Cork with the pictures faster.    
    
    
    War'um day at the Ha'penny Bridge. #IrishSummer2 pic.twitter.com/8PIgkq2t8D    
    
    
    Gay discount at the tailors. #PinkMafia    
    
    
    Dublin's free wifi is infuriating, 4 different services to choose from but an "unable to connect" message on all of them.    
    
    
    Cooking the yummiest Shepherds Pie in history.    
    
    
    Everybody should read the hacked http://www.youthdefence.ie  statement today. It's time to see who and what's behind those disgusting posters.    
    
    
    I'm wearing shorts and I'm not even in the gym #IrishSummer    
    
    
    So I'm scalded as they would say back home. A bright shade of red now but hoping to brown a bit.    
    
    
    Hayfever and Asthma suffers in Dublin beware. The pollen count us ridiculously high today. I'm choked.    
    
    
    @dmndnn will be chained to my inhailer for the day I'd say.    
    
    
    @dmndnn Hayfever wise I've had a better than average year. Been on generic stuff from the UK chemist superdrug, £1.50 for 14.    
    
    
    @dmndnn I remember you saying ya were very badly effected last year too. It must be tough. The doctor can't do anything on prescription, no?    
    
    
    @UlsterBank_Help A queue of 10 people and a cashier having a personal conversation at the desk. O'Connell st Dublin has gone very downhill.    
    
    
    Such fun RT“@gavreilly: Now looking distinctly like we're going to be here until 2am. At least. #abortion #dail”    
    
    
    Better late than never, a new episode of #TrueBlood    
    
    
    "Sorry but did you see a horse running with nobody on it this way?" "Yes, Yes I did" #OnlyinFinglas    
    
    
    “@rtenews: Lucinda Creighton has said she has given her letter of resignation to Taoiseach Enda Kenny” #WinWin    
    
    
    I hope all the Orange men marching today have their sunblock on or they'll go Red.    
    
    
    Chuck Foley, the inventor of Twister, has died. It's only now I realise I've never actually played the game. That needs to be rectified.    
    
    
    Phone just got a MASSIVE smash against the pavement but didn't fall on the screen and everything seems fine. Perhaps I should do the lotto.    
    
    
    Last opportunity to take a trip to the beach for a while I'm gonna take it. Sandymount #IrishSummer    
    
    
    Really enjoyed a dip in the sea at Sandymount and Booterstown. #Dublin is a great place to be in sunny weather.    
    
    
    Why would any grown man choose to speak into his speakerphone on the bus for no good reason? #GrindsMyGears #GrumpyOldMan    
    
    
    WHAT THE HELL. Ad bread mid eviction? This is ridiculous @bbuk #bbuk    
    
    
    Beach? Shur why not. #Sandymount    
    
    
    Sitting next to a child on the bus with two dads who asked them "Are you gay or what?" #Awkward    
    
    
    Finn :(  http://m.hollywoodreporter.com/news/glee-star-cory-monteith-dies-584965 …    
    
    
    At Pacific Rim last night I kept expecting Megazord to show up. #PacificRim #Megazord #GoGoPowerRangers http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W7pHy2MB6HM …    
    
    
    Justice League: The Flashpoint Paradox. Well thats my weekend sorted anyway. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xe0JiobQ98o …    
    
    
    A sleepy start to the day. Time to make the shower a little colder and jolt me awake.    
    
    
    Listening to Margret Cho on the bus to work. Thank goodness nobody hears what's going on in my ears.    
    
    
    Delighted to start helping people today at Squarespace an excellent day's work done. #Squarespace    
    
    
    The Dublin accent still confuses me, often I don't know if people are speaking English of not.    
    
    
    Pity I missed Bruce Springsteen in Cork last night. Sure there was trouble with the bar but who needs a drink to enjoy such a great artist.    
    
    
    Street performance world championships hit Cork for round two #spwc http://instagram.com/p/b_E0FvyzaP/     
    
    
    There's water falling from the sky. In Ireland, cloudless Ireland. #WhatTheFluich    
    
    
    #NowPlaying Islands In The Stream by Dolly Parton on #Spotify yet I'm still cool. http://open.spotify.com/track/3982VGQZth3ehB8adPPvg3 …    
    
    
    The moment where your phone unexpectedly stops working and starts again is a lot like death and resurrection.    
    
    
    @RichDsy Well I was cheeky in putting ios7 beta 3 on. It looks great but is a little iffy on the iPhone 4 for now.    
    
    
    Clocking off. #Hometime    
    
    
    @GrabOneIE 8am to 4pm shift. It's a blessing on a sunny evening so much it offsets the crappyness of getting outta bed at 6:30.    
    
    
    @GrabOneIE That's one hell of a commute, counting myself lucky I live in Finglas now. You have a good evening too. Big fan of what you do.    
    
    
    PUSH...... PUSH. #RoyalBaby    
    
    
    And relax. A good day's work done. pic.twitter.com/Xku2EZUb3K    
    
    
    Banging your head on the bedside table really is a crappy way to wake up. #Ouch    
    
    
    Yussss, @Rubberbandits on @Spotify "Can't Wait".    
    
    
    Yikes, that's fast “@rtenews: The referendum on the abolition of the Seanad will take place on Friday 4 October”    
    
    
    The local homeless man has a phone with a hands free headset. Where does he charge it? #ImNotBeingFunnyBut    
    
    
    How did I forget that HBO's The Newsroom was back on tv? Double episode bonanza for me then.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Nice. I've got it on now actually.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell You do get that it's just a baby like any other right? :p    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell That's what they said about his dad, we'll probably never see this guy ascend to the throne.    
    
    
    I'm awake, I'm awake, I'm awake. Lets do this thing #Work    
    
    
    Email filters, a genius invention.    
    
    
    .@owensdamien I neeedz spelcheque for twitr.    
    
    
    Working 8 to 4 doesn't quite have the same "Dolly Parton" ring to it    
    
    
    Work to home in 45mins. A new record.    
    
    
    Always miss you Cork City. RT:“@diarmuidhistory: River Lee, from North Mall, Cork; evening sun after rain pic.twitter.com/2v7LtdIofr”    
    
    
    @diarmuidhistory Indeed. Work and love brought me here but Cork will always have a place in my heart.    
    
    
    A very misunderstood breed of dog “@OMGFacts: Pit bulls were used as babysitters! Read more here ----> http://omgf.ac/ts/kfX ”    
    
    
    Almost work time... Just around the corner. http://instagram.com/p/cL4zttyzbk/     
    
    
    This rain storm is freakin crazy.    
    
    
    Yup its Ireland again. http://instagram.com/p/cO697dyzVl/     
    
    
    @GrabOneIE Lol, we've gotten so used to sunny days the rain terrifies us.    
    
    
    Nearly there. T minus two hours to the weekend    
    
    
    Started using Jānis' old iPhone with it's better quality camera, Yus. There'll be many many more pictures uploaded now.    
    
    
    Ok, work emails read. I'm certainly a company man these days reading mails on Saturday night.    
    
    
    @FromFirstToLast I'm in Finglas now sin May too (which at this stage makes my twitter name a relic).    
    
    
    I wonder whats going on in the world today. Time to stick one earphone in and listen to the headlines on @Newstalkfm    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Are you reporting and not on the desk today? Will tune in at 12. Pick a station for me. Sorry @Newstalkfm friends first :P    
    
    
    Four desktops, One Laptop. I am the king of space management.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell No you've dragged me away from poor @Newstalkfm now I'm gonna critique everything I hear ;P Q102 at 12 it is #JudgementDay    
    
    
    @UlsterBank_Help Is there a problem logging in on the iPhone app? I've been trying all morning and get a service unavailable message.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Listened to Q102. Horsemeat? Slow news day :P It's better when you read it pal.    
    
    
    Monsoon. http://instagram.com/p/cWt56zyzTl/     
    
    
    Somehow every morning the bus comes around the corner just far enough away that I have to jog 200m. #MorningRun    
    
    
    "We expect to answer your call in about 13 minutes" damn you Revenue.    
    
    
    Lazy evening planned. I probably should have gone to the gym but its just so (temporally) nice out.    
    
    
    Step off one bus directly on to another. #FullOfWin.    
    
    
    Doesn't have a weird accent it's just not a Dublin one. #CorkBoyInTheOffice    
    
    
    Ah yeah. That's Dooblin. http://instagram.com/p/ccE6e6yzWy/     
    
    
    #NowPlaying Wake Me Up - Radio Edit by Avicii on #Spotify A good going to work song. http://open.spotify.com/track/294vBlXfZYspeI29SXZaON …    
    
    
    Tea break at work with my new misleading mug. http://instagram.com/p/cecAOlyzfc/     
    
    
    Ran for a 140 bus home and caught it, LIKE A BOSS.    
    
    
    Am I going mad or does @IanDempsey not know #GoCar have been sucessuflly operating in #Cork for years now it's only new to Dublin guys #iand    
    
    
    GoCar CLAMPED! via @broadsheet_ie #GoFigure http://www.broadsheet.ie/2013/08/02/gocar-clamped/ …    
    
    
    Dublin man on bus to son "See that flag dare, dats Cork" I felt like saying no sir that's Galway we're red and white which you'll soon learn    
    
    
    Cork flags, Cork flags everywhere in Dublin :D    
    
    
    Mind Blown “@secboffin: Why did I _only now_ realise that vimeo is an anagram of movie?”    
    
    
    Just a couple of hours to go. New Doctor Who promo trailer teases the arrival of the 12th Doctor http://www.blastr.com/2013-8-2/new-doctor-who-promo-trailer-teases-arrival-12th-doctor …    
    
    
    Geek overload #DoctorWho #GuessWho #WhoIsTwelve    
    
    
    "Tie me kangaroo down sport". Strewth, Rolf's second arrest.    
    
    
    Remembering sunnier days than these in Ireland. http://vimeo.com/christierney/blackrock-thirty …    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Again. I'll believe it when he's actually gone and stays away for 2 years. He just wants a triumphant return I'd say.    
    
    
    @newschambers @jonathanhealy Maybe honest mistake in the shop? The number of people I met who were ridiculously uninformed was mind boggling    
    
    
    Square meals, yum. #foodporn #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/ctZ8R1yzag/     
    
    
    The local trains in Dublin and its suburbs aren't great. The usual story, a poorly planned old fashioned service that needs investment.    
    
    
    In desperate need of a cup of tea.    
    
    
    @GrabOneIE it's a snip at €195.    
    
    
    @despod that's quite good, I might get one for my mother. Any chance of a link?    
    
    
    @despod ah great company Carrefour.    
    
    
    @damienmulley how strange, me too.    
    
    
    Watching Glee and said something my mother would say, "He's dead now". I'm truly an old man now.    
    
    
    @boucherhayes it's not like we'd stop that just because ye won a match.    
    
    
    Well that working day could only be classed as Excellent.    
    
    
    Gym gym gym. I've gotta pay for yesterday's pizza... In sweat.    
    
    
    Remember when the trends on twitter were actual news events and pretty interesting, now it's just One Direction fans making up nonsense.    
    
    
    @GrabOneIE Pitfalls of a popular service. I've noticed I tweet much less these days and it's mostly because good content is so hard to find.    
    
    
    I know this is a bit late but I just can't wait for "iPhone Media Event All But Confirmed for September 10" http://www.macrumors.com/2013/08/12/iphone-media-event-all-but-confirmed-for-september-10/ …    
    
    
    @RichDsy I'm interested though in rumours that the camera will only be 8 MP not the expected 10 or 12. Thats a big selling point for me.    
    
    
    @RichDsy Extremely but apple are already pushing the boundaries of what's possible on compression. We'll see.    
    
    
    Is @LanaDelRey trying to tell us something with her new single Summertime Sadness. Cheer up love, sing a nice happy song for a change.    
    
    
    The video for the new Bebo is genius, now that Facebook isn't what it used to be its time to #TakeBackBebo http://bebo.com/     
    
    
    The Tardis street view is pretty much the best thing the Internet has ever done. We can switch it off now. http://maps.gstatic.com/m/streetview/?hl=en&ll=51.492159,-0.19092&spn=0.005291,0.013937&sll=51.492140,-0.193028&layer=c&cid=12502927659667388442&panoid=c9UMhWP_MWm9U0L48xEjYw&cbp=13,291.8,,0,18.86&gl=US&t=m&cbll=51.492132,-0.192862&z=17 …    
    
    
    If you don't get the points you wanted today it's not the end. Only a small % of people know what they want to do at 18 anyway #LeavingCert    
    
    
    Not a jury in the world... Who am I kidding? "Women held in Peru claim they were forced to carry drugs" http://simply.pylba.com/a/hAO1A?tw     
    
    
    Having a little fun in the office today with Moustache day. pic.twitter.com/ZL2cm3ZE1I    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Yep great fun and enjoying every min of it.    
    
    
    PC WC via @broadsheet_ie http://www.broadsheet.ie/2013/08/14/pc-wc/ …    
    
    
    Perhaps tonight I'll finally write my Tesco based Erotic movie "Unexpected item in bagging area".    
    
    
    Floor plans released for the infamous Area 51 base reveal it's a much more mundane place than expected http://www.cnn.com/2013/08/15/us/area-51-documents/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Good man. Most of your problems lie on your computer's end though.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell You're only getting that far? Gimme a call if it doesn't work for you. I'll take a look. They still have no service in mine.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Fingers Crossed I'm hoping we'll have it in by next month. In other news off to the UK for a few days  next month @THORPEPARK    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Yep, roller coasters we were there in March but it had to close because of freezing. Comp tickets though. Just a lil break.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Yup. Any plans for the next while, going back home or to Cork?    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell This Sat yeah I'd say we'll be out. Should meet those other friends of yours so we'll stop by. Cork next sat for me too.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell just googled that. Not entirely sure it's Jānis' music but i'll run it by him. Can always pop by somewhere and say hi anyway.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Yup. I spotted that. He's a funny one music wise. I can't turn on any of the Alternative music channels.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Sounds class. I was listening to my 50's do-wop this morning.    
    
    
    Phew, what a day! So glad it's home time. #TheWeekendHasLanded    
    
    
    The countdown to #Riddick in Ireland has begun. Spotted in Cineworld Dublin @kateesackhoff pic.twitter.com/ClTtt9mDFS    
    
    
    Red 2 is quite good fun and I really enjoyed the homage to Bourne.    
    
    
    Woah, sleepy morning. Gonna have a coffee and become a hyperactive loon.    
    
    
    Everyone makes mistakes but #SlaneGirl lives in the Internet age. The #SlaneBoys deserve just as much blame though.    
    
    
    It's not every day someone gets to say this but I just met the nicest bus driver. Really helpful guy.    
    
    
    @obrienbarry Nope. Turkish I think. I live up here in Dublin now I'd have been very impressed to meet a driver so nice in Cork    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Limerick person on the twitter, has a chip on his shoulder about living in Cork's shadow. ;)    
    
    
    Super healthy chicken curry and a trip straight to the gym. Nice way to finish off a work day.    
    
    
    There's a woman parading around in front of me at the gym disappointed she's receiving no attention #StillGotTheCharm #ImGayLove    
    
    
    I've seen 3 people in the same Batman T Shirt today (2 Girls 1 Guy) is Batman having a concert in town or something?    
    
    
    The brownies at work... so much NOM, they're my only weakness. Well off to the gym to pay for that now :)    
    
    
    @JaLazLV lol, it's on Facebook too. I just had 1 on the way out the door. #ImStillGood.    
    
    
    @JaLazLV actually two days ago. Your verbal abuse is forever on twitter for the world to see now ;)    
    
    
    “@madeupstats: You will spend a total of 10 MONTHS of your life watching content buffering.” So worth it to do it all in one go though.    
    
    
    It sounds like the pond was too small #BigFishGames are departing Cork. Pity, to have a games dev in town was a boost to Cork Media Industry    
    
    
    Gorgeous jacket in the Cleary's flood sale store and I forgot my wallet at home. #FirstWorldProblems    
    
    
    Drunk lady on the bus singing "Wake me up when it's all over". You should have stated in the womb love #MeanTweets    
    
    
    Holy shiz, Ben Affleck Is the New Batman http://variety.com/2013/film/news/ben-affleck-is-the-new-batman-1200586881/ …    
    
    
    Cue jokes about Manure MT @siliconrepublic "BBC 5Live to operate only on renewables on Energy Day: http://bit.ly/16mTToJ "    
    
    
    Back to Cork, the rebel city for 24 hours tomorrow. Flying visit to top up the accent back to 100%    
    
    
    Soothers, Dummies, Pacifiers whatever you want to call them. This child on the bus could really really use one. #ImNeverHavingKids    
    
    
    My home by the Lee #Corked    
    
    
    Chilling reading. Russia's hate laws propagating fear http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/3804490 …    
    
    
    21 hours in Cork. No visit is long enough but this was quicker than most.    
    
    
    I know you want it, I know you want it #BlueLines    
    
    
    Conditioner bottle exploded in my bag. I put my hand in the bag and it came out covered in white goo. I looked very "suspect".    
    
    
    Crazy diversions around Dublin today for the Lockout commemorations. I've gotta get Mr Laz to the airport so we're leaving super early.    
    
    
    Quick #selfie before @JaLazLV heads back to #Latvia pic.twitter.com/9LgGSzCvtz    
    
    
    Mind Blown RT“@TheNextWeb: What if Apple’s iWatch is… a TV? http://tnw.to/g0hmZ  by @thepixel_lounge”    
    
    
    Good morning and happy Labour Day America. Go easy on us today please.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell it's too close, I say recount the votes.    
    
    
    Did someone say there's a new episode of #Homeland #HellYeah    
    
    
    Charlie Hunnam will always be young Nathan from Queer as Folk to me.    
    
    
    Pink "True Love" #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I found some change down the back if the sofa. Sadly it seems like I missed my opportunity to buy Nokia with it.    
    
    
    Glad to be using @stripe from @collision @patrickc as part of my work with Squarespace here in Ireland. Delighted it's launching here today.    
    
    
    @kctodayfm The big smoke doesn't change a guy, all those years in Cork still count :D    
    
    
    #ThatAwkwardMomentWhen You sit next to somebody because there are no other seats left then suddenly you're the only 2 people there.    
    
    
    @Daphne and the super cool dress with skulls makes it's first appearance too. She must be delighted.    
    
    
    Beautiful sky over Finglas this morning. Worth taking a moment with before heading to work.    
    
    
    Oh Thursday, you're never going to be as good as Friday so you might as well just stop trying. #PoorMansFriday    
    
    
    The guy shouting while walking behind me crazy or just using a hands free? I don't know and I'm not gonna look.    
    
    
    A very productive day in work today. Looking forward to a visit from my NYC colleagues on Monday. #TheWeekendHasLanded    
    
    
    Between the Sweden and Clare matches love nor money can buy Blue and Yellow balloons in #Dublin    
    
    
    When you see a @CorksRedFM bus around the corner from your home in Dublin you realise the move from Cork to Dublin has been a small one.    
    
    
    I'm not watching the #XFactor who said I was? Oh god I admit it I am and I'm so ashamed.    
    
    
    A big welcome to my colleagues from NYC. Wrap up folks, it's cold out there in #Dublin today.    
    
    
    Now that I know the crew in work so well I'm really getting to know some of the other @dogpatchlabs companies. Great work being done there.    
    
    
    Checking out Snapchat at JiveCork let's see what all the fuss is about.    
    
    
    Ok, let's do this thing. #iphone5s    
    
    
    Major excitement #WWDC    
    
    
    Guy to Guy on bus v sincerely "there'll be 500 girls there if ya don't find 1 that'll go home with ya you're definitely gay" #Maevesdropping    
    
    
    Alan hyperventilates a little. http://www.me-me-me.tv/images/2013/09/Dr-Who.png …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Rainy night in London this #FridayThe13th hoping it drys up before taking a trip to Heaven.    
    
    
    Morning all, time to wake up here. I need a post holiday holiday. #SoTired    
    
    
    A panorama of the Airbus as it passes over the Liffey during Flightfest yesterday  http://www.broadsheet.ie/2013/09/16/airbus-lane/ …    
    
    
    17:01 #TrekNerd    
    
    
    @NyleLennon Goodness. We had a twins day in work recently. I didn't participate :)    
    
    
    Gridlock at protest central here in Dublin. Hoping to bypass it all by going to the gym until it all blows over.    
    
    
    Still major bus delays from the protests on O'Connell st. in #Dublin #AhHaor    
    
    
    If you're in Dublin this evening don't expect to go anywhere. Protests on O'Connell bridge. pic.twitter.com/nfU1dlxz7l    
    
    
    @RichDsy Austerity, silly ol fools. There are some good pictures on @thejournal_ie    
    
    
    Will be the proud owner of an iPhone 5s tomorrow? #FingersCrossed    
    
    
    Gardaí warn fans to beware of all Ireland ticket scams. Very convincing forgeries within... http://jrnl.ie/1094046     
    
    
    Saw About Time on Date Night last night :D Memories of much of this great soundtrack from growing up. http://spoti.fi/15ISAaB  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Advice needed. To buy a iPhone 5s from the states or not? I know someone going over that could get one. Please RT.    
    
    
    @jaybrannan I back up to iPhoto on my computer regularly but that's mostly for display purposes.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime yikes that was a ton of detail and all I needed thanks. Let I wouldn't be bothered about for the moment anyway but...    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I've read that the Worldwide warranty from the US isn't. People bring a phone to apple EU told they need to bring back to US    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime It might still be worth it for me anyway. I work for a US company now with people back and forth regularly that could do it.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime You've been a massive help there, wow.  Are you buying one via the same route or happy with the phone you have?    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime the guys are going to NYC really soon so chances are slim that I'll get one with current stock levels but fingers crossed :)    
    
    
    It's Friday and it's sunny here in Dublin. Perfect start to the day.. Let's do this thing.    
    
    
    The weekend is almost here.. rejoice ♫ Friday I'm In Love – The Cure http://spoti.fi/19rwRR1  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    @RichDsy go to sleep you're up to early, it's Saturday :p    
    
    
    @greentothebone Wow, what pastures new are you off to now?    
    
    
    @RichDsy wow..... http://youtu.be/6jzWRYr-b_Y  the place will be done in no time.    
    
    
    @greentothebone ah...... well :)    
    
    
    Smell like pre pubescent hormone induced hysteria. #1Direction pic.twitter.com/1I8UvRSOqO    
    
    
    Now that I have seen it, I'm saying.... I watched the last 5 mins of Strictly for that :O #SaveTheDay    
    
    
    Haven't been home in time to watch the @rtenews at Sixone in ages. Impressed.    
    
    
    I have this attitude to work that if you don't learn something in work every day then you're doing it wrong. Today was a big learning day.    
    
    
    Delighted to hear my colleagues at @squarespace are sponsoring the @jarlath An Irishman Abroad podcast. Work life and leisure time merge.    
    
    
    It's been so so cool to watch @neiltyson from my desk at @SquarespaceDUB today. I've never laughed and learned so much at the same time.    
    
    
    Chugger for @Concern on College Green just said to a passing lady to get her attention "Hello, ya look a bit depressed" #Facepalm    
    
    
    The Seannad refferendum... pic.twitter.com/qyMgfXxn5f    
    
    
    Some people never turn off the clicks on their smartphone. Sitting next to one of these in a quiet doctors office I ask why?    
    
    
    I just entered the new competition from @GrabOneIE fingers crossed    
    
    
    Well @GrabOneIE http://youtu.be/5NV6Rdv1a3I     
    
    
    @thebenlandis thanks for the follow Ben    
    
    
    @ChrisRGuitarist Thanks for the follow :)    
    
    
    Here comes the weekend guys. Time to let those batteries recharge. It's been a long week.    
    
    
    Siri getting beefed up? “@mashable: Apple Acquires Personal Assistant App Cue http://on.mash.to/18V9i3l ”    
    
    
    @alispagnola Thanks for your follow Ali    
    
    
    http://telly.com/1B0AKYF  - Can't we just all be friends. Wrecking Sinead - Miley Curus.    
    
    
    Can't we just all be friends? @MileyCyrus and @Sinead_OConnor Wrecking Sinead http://telly.com/1B0AKYF  at #Pantibar #ireland    
    
    
    @darraghdoyle Can't we just all be friends? https://twitter.com/JiveCork/status/389196176500985857 …    
    
    
    If I could only be as productive in the gym now as I have been at work today I'll be sporting a 6 pack by 6pm.    
    
    
    @OwensDamien Jinkies! Maybe Velma and Scully were one and the same.    
    
    
    Protests hit Westmorland St as the Budget looms. #budget2014 pic.twitter.com/DydviV0fHE    
    
    
    Here we go. #GraduationDay    
    
    
    'Doctor Who 50th Anniversary: The Day of The Doctor' in Cineworld Dublin. I'm going http://www.cineworld.ie/whatson/6843     
    
    
    @dublinbusnews 1, 47, 56a, 77a all bringing you up the side of it via Pearse street.    
    
    
    I'm sitting in a doctor's office where the clock hasn't been put back yet. They went back 10 days ago! My faith in this doc is dwindling.    
    
    
    In bed at 10pm because of a chest infection... Seriously dude, you used to be cool.    
    
    
    Sorry @nerdist it took the Genie App 60 questions to guess it was you. pic.twitter.com/UFi4Z8mmEl    
    
    
    Super excited about the next few weeks at work. A new adventure is about to begin.    
    
    
    Phew, it's finally the weekend again. Time to sleep like there's no tomorrow. Though I'm kinda hoping there is... I have plans.    
    
    
    @danpgomez DPG follows me :D yay. Consider yourself followed back sir.    
    
    
    @danpgomez Lol, now if I had those I'd definitely have fantastic workflow.    
    
    
    What? Why? ... What? MT:“@MacRumors: Apple Maps Significantly More Popular Than All Other iOS Map Apps, Inc Google http://www.macrumors.com/2013/11/11/apple-maps-significantly-more-popular-than-all-other-ios-mapping-apps-including-google/ …”    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime yep, never underestimate the power of laziness.    
    
    
    @robinscreech4 oh god no, it's still awful.    
    
    
    Ok time put away the wok emails etc for the evening Alan. Time to watch Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.    
    
    
    @danpgomez Tahiti is a magical place ;)    
    
    
    Nice "The original copy (by @teekenng)" https://vine.co/v/hi5LzAXaPM9     
    
    
    Finally have my iPhone 5s in Kardashian Gold. #DollarBills    
    
    
    Great song to get you through the workday. I love Spotify in the office :D ♫ Shiny Happy People – R.E.M. http://spoti.fi/IFqhxw  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I totally did art :p #ARTPOP #ArtHaus http://gifs.techha.us/Dj0lVVDUQhmi_DEiQBZElw.gif …    
    
    
    Last day of Squarespace Irl. at @dogpatchlabs you've been a kind home to us but, as with all companies eventually, we've outgrown the kennel    
    
    
    Passed this bookshop getting in the #Movember spirit on the way home pic.twitter.com/JYpl1T0T13    
    
    
    Don’t Boldly Go There via @broadsheet_ie I have one of these somewhere at my parents, should dig it out. http://www.broadsheet.ie/2013/11/15/make-your-own-star-trek-episode/ …    
    
    
    @RichDsy your twitter profile pic, the Rich concentration face. I'd bet that you were concentrating on your next move in chess. Am I right?    
    
    
    Foggy night at the Aviva Stadium for #IREvAUS #IrelandsCall    
    
    
    Watching the last episode of The B in Apartment 23. I love this show so much how could it have been cancelled?    
    
    
    Tonight on the projector, Un film de Pedro Almodóvar #ImSoExcited pic.twitter.com/U3ap09AXxq    
    
    
    Lesson 23: Why punctuation is important.  “@wossy: Woah, speak for yourself mate.  https://vine.co/v/htVTha5gt2a ”    
    
    
    Good morning twittles.    
    
    
    I honestly had a really fun day today at work. Not everybody can say that about their job. I'm a very lucky man to work at Squarespace.    
    
    
    @danpgomez Nice :D you buy it?    
    
    
    @danpgomez Pretty good. Great day at work and settling down for a Dr Who tv movie all about the creation of the show. #Nergasam And you sir?    
    
    
    @danpgomez It's very very good. You're missing out. What tv are you in to? Probably seeing everything on DVR what with working late nights.    
    
    
    @danpgomez All good shows, don't watch em all but I love twist. I loved Desperate Housewives back in the day. Tonight American horror story.    
    
    
    What, it's Friday? Where did that come from? It's Thursday -> Saturday right? #HibernateForWinter    
    
    
    Some good theory's here. “@MichaelAusiello: FAMILY GUY Mystery: Will a Christmas Miracle Resurrect Brian? http://tvline.com/2013/11/26/family-guy-brian-alive-resurrected-not-dead-spoilers/ …”    
    
    
    Beverly Hills Cop? Don't mind if I do. #BackTotThe80s    
    
    
    @danpgomez Have a great thanksgiving tomorrow. I wanna see plenty of updates here :p Fingers crossed we at the Irish team have a good day 2.    
    
    
    Home office ready for tomorrow. Dual screen bliss. #ThanksgivingTakeover    
    
    
    I'm famous :p thanks to @HelenAndOlly at Answer Me This for the mention on episode 279 https://soundcloud.com/aroconnor/the-people-at-answer-me-this?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=share&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Off to Amsterdam for the weekend, will be missing #latelate #toyshow thankfully  have @RTEplayer to compensate.    
    
    
    Thanks for the #ff @danpgomez :)    
    
    
    Staying in the house of a friend who has young kids and woke to hear "Mamma" shouted repeatedly. Reminded of http://m.imdb.com/title/tt2023587/ …    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Now if it was Catchphrase's Roy Walker... Then you would.    
    
    
    After two days with friends on the outskirts Amsterdam City Centre now calls. Bright lights and late nights await. pic.twitter.com/KmxDcM8ibR    
    
    
    Esprit in Amsterdam. The ceiling was so cool I almost didn't look at the clothes. pic.twitter.com/IxwGUhZPeS    
    
    
    @danpgomez not the greatest jump on point as it was still a bit kiddie at that point but stick with it until the end of the season #ItRocks    
    
    
    So when do #Dominos start using the #AmazonDrone technology? That's what I want to hear.    
    
    
    I'll be one of millions doing this today but I'd like to offer my sincere congratulations to @TomDaley1994    
    
    
    Most people come to Amsterdam for a different type of Coffee Shop. I however am enjoying another Earl Grey tea at Starbucks. #FeelSoAlive    
    
    
    Home from the holidays. #NotSpeakingMurican    
    
    
    Had one of those "What, it can't be 6:30am? That's not my alarm" mornings. Need a post holiday holiday.    
    
    
    Looking forward to visiting Cork this weekend. Much planning to do. #DeckTheHalls    
    
    
    My video of birds in Dam Square Amsterdam yesterday in (Slow Motion) http://youtu.be/prmbgYdPnDA     
    
    
    Five-year-old's confesses to John Lewis: 'I broke bauble' My Faith in humanity restored... http://www.itv.com/news/update/2013-12-05/five-years-old-confession-to-john-lewis-i-broke-bauble/ …    
    
    
    I remember the day he was freed very very well, today is a sad one. A true world statesman, Goodbye Nelson. http://youtu.be/AgcTvoWjZJU     
    
    
    Thurs was a day of encounters with weird people. The drunk man in the cinema who thought he was Carrie being the strangest. Bring on Friday.    
    
    
    I always think if I lived near work I'd probably never leave. It's probably a good thing I have a one hour travel each way then.    
    
    
    The last RT was because I love sleep THAT much. #EarlyNightsEarlyMornings    
    
    
    Running for buses. Every day.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell HA. Lightweight. Try Latvian, I actually got quite a taste for it but pacing yourself is the key with that stuff.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I can't do it before a work or travel day anymore. Lil Jameson and Coke though tonight n' going to Cork 2mor #BreakinTheRules    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Whiskey FTW. Owl fellas of the world unite.    
    
    
    Junkyard robot figure I spotted while waiting for the bus back to Cork. #ChristmasIdeas #NoFilter pic.twitter.com/bmWR6YYKh5    
    
    
    Downloading apps on my new iPad while on the bus back to Dublin. Yay.    
    
    
    Back home in Dublin. I'm calling it, it's official... I'm a Dublin jackeen.    
    
    
    Empty Dublin Bus with the door open, this is how GTA 6 begins. pic.twitter.com/2JYEpePY3b    
    
    
    @davidmcg that was at Benson St near the Facebook (and our) offices too.    
    
    
    Forgot how nice it is to start work when it's bright outside.    
    
    
    Snapchat, I'm JiveCork over there but to be honest don't get it. Does it only make sense to use if you're Down For Whatever? #dfw #snapchat    
    
    
    Clever RT “@RichLeighPR Naughty/nice celebrities according to @socialsantaco based on how much they swear on Twitter http://socialsanta.co/celebrity ”    
    
    
    The Christmas mood has definitely been set in our living room. http://seene.co/s/2m4BgH     
    
    
    Sign language interpreter at Nelson Mandela service called out as fake.  http://www.upi.com/Odd_News/Blog/2013/12/10/Sign-language-interpreter-at-Nelson-Mandela-service-called-out-as-fake-on-Twitter/1791386710346/ …    
    
    
    Purple morning sky from the quays of central Dublin. #NoFilter #panorama pic.twitter.com/LBJVg3gHJV    
    
    
    Just sayin RT“@OMGFacts: The King of Cambodia is unmarried, has no children, and is a dance instructor! Details ---> http://omgf.ac/ts/9o9 ”    
    
    
    Have you cleared your cache? #fivewordtechhorrors    
    
    
    It's working on my end! #fivewordtechhorrors    
    
    
    @jonathanhealy Oh they're always sued in Glasnevin. Elsewhere though, like yourself, I've never seen one in use.    
    
    
    Yay, I'm a middle aged woman “the_overtones: Ireland we're coming! Playing the @RTELateLateShow this Friday at 9.30pm on RTE 1 - tune in x”    
    
    
    @danpgomez Nice presentation earlier Mr. I'm looking forward to using the site. Cool that we were both featured in today's meeting.    
    
    
    On a scarily empty bus after a long day in work. I do love being the tech guy at work though.    
    
    
    The Mandela sign language interpreter now has his own parody Twitter account @MemorialSigner    
    
    
    It's Friday, the day of work's Christmas party and I've got a massage today. 3 reasons to be very happy.    
    
    
    Mind blown “@OMGFacts: The animal in Firefox is not actually a fox! Learn more ---> http://omgf.ac/ts/x04 ”    
    
    
    Having a massage from a woman was quite strange, though in retrospect I' v glad it was a woman. It's a very intimate experience.    
    
    
    Red wine vending machines at the Dublin Wine Rooms. #Snazzy http://instagram.com/p/h4CGKgyzWs/     
    
    
    Christmas crackers, we hear from our colleague Noah they haven't invaded America yet. How? http://instagram.com/p/h4E0y2SzaL/     
    
    
    THE DOCTOR: “Not forever. I can change 12 times. 13 versions of me. 13 silly Doctors.” #DoctorWho http://www.blastr.com/2013-12-13/time-doctor-teaser-tidbits-xmas-dinner-fair-bit-nudity?utm_source=dlvr.it&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Introducing the other half to Milk tonight, not the drink the movie.    
    
    
    @greentothebone Seen it a few times myself already. Tis pretty good.    
    
    
    Christmas has officially begun now that I've watched Love Actually. #ChristmasIsAllAround    
    
    
    Ron Burgundy on Taoiseach Enda Kenny's Address to the Nation. #BiggerThanXFactor http://youtu.be/M44h0PBmo10     
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell G'way outta that, tonight your mind is only on #XFactorFinal    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell We have the telly set to automatically flick. I'm sure he's watching himself so will delay starting.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Perhaps the Troika have will have gone into deadlock and they'll have to keep us in the programme for a while longer.    
    
    
    Congratulations Enda on winning #xfactor tonight and our Taoiseach Sam for exiting the bailout programme #irlexit    
    
    
    Mid wrapping frenzy I wrapped Jānis' phone then rang it, I may be going insane. #WrapStar pic.twitter.com/zA9HguqSCY    
    
    
    Gym done. Now I can safely feel good about myself tonight as sit in front of a computer doing a little extra work.    
    
    
    Huge improvement in customer service at @UlsterBank_Help O'Connell St in Dublin. Tell Mick I really appreciate his help.    
    
    
    A truly touching story RT “@thescore_ie: This is great. Ajax ‘sign’ terminally-ill 8-year-old boy http://tsc.re/1cyncIX ”    
    
    
    @huss Do they feature a picture of you with the taoiseach?    
    
    
    Walking dead mid season finale was just wow. So glad I gave it a 2nd go after a slow few episodes.    
    
    
    Last night while going to sleep I created the funniest tweet ever. It's morning now and all I have is this. #NoSleepTillBrooklin #DreamLies    
    
    
    Christmas present from Squarespace a Patagonia jacket. #ImLoved pic.twitter.com/AzVFfDnfIY    
    
    
    @RichDsy The make version of one of these chaps http://www.evo.com/outlet/mid-layer-tops/patagonia-piton-1/4-zip-jacket-womens.aspx#image=60226/301348/patagonia-piton-1-4-zip-jacket-women-s-black-front.jpg … Small sqsp logo on the side.    
    
    
    Scrooged is on... Perfect. Might follow it up with Home Alone.    
    
    
    Just spoke to someone at @Postvox customer service who wanted a "responsible adult" to be there to accept my re-delivery I'm 32 and annoyed.    
    
    
    Now the counter agent Noel @ Cardiff Lane D2 wouldn't take my word that I was there I'd like to be contacted to officially complain @Postvox    
    
    
    @Postvox They were the original source of the issue. Really disappointed in the service I paid for. I'll be contacting the postal address.    
    
    
    Explaining to @JaLazLV what a bottle neck is via text. Sometimes I'm shocked he's lived in Ireland almost 10 years and not heard these words    
    
    
    @RichDsy That's nice. About time too.    
    
    
    Fought the insane Dublin traffic and caught the @Aircoach just in time... Driving home for Christmas.    
    
    
    Much like @KCTodayfm I'm heading back to Cork for Christmas. Barely made my bus due to the traffic but glad to be on the motorway now.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Will do and the same to you too Derek. Happy Christmas.    
    
    
    Seriously the people who reported this need to unfollow RT “@kathygriffin: Really people??? pic.twitter.com/ecAEk3zUPj”    
    
    
    @endac That's absolutely fantastic news and I hope you have a great Christmas too.    
    
    
    Merry Christmas twitters. I hope you all got exactly what you wanted from Santa.    
    
    
    Not since Tiny Tim walked in a Christmas Carol has a Miracle given so much hope "@justinbieber My beloved beliebers I'm officially retiring"    
    
    
    Christmas in Cobh. http://instagram.com/p/iWSMTjyzT1/     
    
    
    One of the usual ;) http://instagram.com/p/iWd6czSzeh/     
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Ah now. It's like being at home in Dublin. We're watching too.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell #AhHaor    
    
    
    I'm so glad I left retail before St. Stephen's Day became the consumerist mess it now is.    
    
    
    Just bought my first game on iTunes. I enjoyed Back to the Future The Game that much I wanted more. #bttf    
    
    
    My parents have the tv on so loud. I wonder could I convince them they're actually deaf if I hit mute?    
    
    
    @FacesPics RT “@GeorgeTakei: Does anyone else see this and think, "COOOOOOOKIE!!!!" pic.twitter.com/PpQNCiNiee”    
    
    
    Ronan O’Gara documentary #ROG looks like it will be some quality new year TV. http://thescore.thejournal.ie/rog-documentary-teaser-ireland-1241234-Dec2013/ …    
    
    
    So so true RT “@twisteddoodles: Adverts before and after Christmas. http://twitpic.com/dqa9q5 ”    
    
    
    Weird man on the bus back to Dublin just asked the driver to stop for a Smoke Break... on a motorway.    
    
    
    Keeping the candle lit by watching the #TOTP Christmas special. I've apparently watched it every year since I was born.    
    
    
    My last retweet shows just how far Ireland has come in such a short time.    
    
    
    I just realised... We'll never be Royals. Well, that's a disappointment.    
    
    
    How did we ever live without a Coffee Machine. #Tassimo #CafeCrema http://instagram.com/p/ilQ3_Eyzep/     
    
    
    The poor girl behind me on the bus must not be able to afford headphones. Her phone's speakers are working overtime.    
    
    
    Just passed Pat Kenny on Grafton St. I had a moment where I thought... I know that man, is he a friend of my mother's? In a way I was right.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Ah Jesus. You really didn't know?    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Watching Alan Carr on +1 here.    
    
    
    @Haganator @kevinjpurcell Bubbles, ah he's never been the same since Michael Jackson died. #AwfulSad    
    
    
        
    
    
    Interesting but who though MT “@leedalyire: Irish minister says ‘we have had enough of this s**t’ on equal marriage http://pocket.co/s28Qr ”    
    
    
    Today is Broadband day. The day we finally after 6 months wait get UPC. #FingersCrossed    
    
    
    Nom *tears, Nom *tears, Nom, why am I doing this :p pic.twitter.com/d1kmqld0qO    
    
    
    My home by (or in this case in) the Lee tonight. #Floods #Cork #WhatTheFliuch http://www.broadsheet.ie/2014/01/02/rebel-well/ …    
    
    
    Morning high tide again in Cork as water reclaims the city MT “@jonathanhealy: pic.twitter.com/fAngwLfRvg”    
    
    
    @RichDsy South Terrence was badly hit I'm glad it was never that bad while I lived there. Dublin was pretty calm last night actually.    
    
    
    Poor Girl. We were all young once, best to stay off the twitter. How a teen's Twitter joke sparked vicious abuse http://jrnl.ie/1247263     
    
    
    The banks of the river Liffey almost breaking outside work today. http://instagram.com/p/iuRnMyyzW4/     
    
    
    This friends reunion business is likely to be a fake as we've see this type of thing before. That said 2014 would be a great time to do it.    
    
    
    Congrats my old @dogpatchlabs office mates @BalconyTV who hit 10,000 videos on @Youtube today. Keep up the good work.    
    
    
    Sundays in #Cork. Oldies and Irish and a roast. #Daycent pic.twitter.com/hddljPDeRJ    
    
    
    It's the same every day at my parents house Judge Judy and Steve Wilkos double bills. Exhausting stuff.    
    
    
    Something to remember for my move to Dublin pic.twitter.com/sKRhrhLRI3    
    
    
    "There are four lights" I'm in #The1701    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I still tend toward the late 50s myself. I'm a Mad Man at heart you're a hippy commie.    
    
    
    It's being a suit to college day #interviews pic.twitter.com/mHYTVd8jCs    
    
    
    Enjoyed the mock interview today for class. Of all the subjects I've ever performed a presentation on, myself was probably the strangest.    
    
    
    There's a guy standing in front of me on the bus "bus surfing" apparently I'm not the only person in the world that does that.    
    
    
    Well done Jason Collins. http://sportsillustrated.cnn.com/magazine/news/20130429/jason-collins-gay-nba-player/#ixzz2RrjYUqUM …    
    
    
    Google Now on iOS is good fun isn't it? Will probably be a massive drain on battery though on my old iPhone 4    
    
    
    Testing out self deleting tweets from efemr this goes away in sixty seconds apparently #1m    
    
    
    needless to say it's still a bit buggy    
    
    
    Last night my poor teammate broke our project for submission and presentation today, he's absolutely distraught. #DontWorry    
    
    
    @Adlers1 to not so subtly tell people you like them "in that way" no?    
    
    
    Interesting idea http://www.tweetbookz.com  create a physical book of your twitter feed.    
    
    
    30 needles in my leg today at the physio. I'm Hellraiser. #NoPainNoGain    
    
    
    My Countdown project is gaining momentum "RT @FullSpectrum13 30 Days to Full Spectrum Degree Show #fullspectrum #30 pic.twitter.com/T57Voqm3Kb"    
    
    
    @Adlers1 anyone that has ever poked me has at least wanted to... Well I won't finish that sentence.    
    
    
    18 days until a new life in Dublin. #BleedinDeadly    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I'll be hanging out all the time, you'll both be bugged from me, it's been far too long.    
    
    
    Hellz yeah “@CROSSYFM104: SO TOMORROW pic.twitter.com/W8olnVIIHI”    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Work and Love. I'm finishing CIT so I'm my field Diblin is the best place and janis is moving there he has a job secured though    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell score, thanks. I'll need all the eyes and ears I can get to find a job ASAP.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell looked up that job, nice place to start out fresh outta college. I'll be applying tonight.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell I noticed that but the earlier you're in the better chance of getting a base English speaking role plus my German isn't bad.    
    
    
    I started the day with one gaol project housing and ended the day with a completely different one. #Yikes    
    
    
    It's my hope that I can have one more module finished in it's entirety by the end of the day. #2toGo    
    
    
    My picture and my house number. @FullSpectrum13 @CIT_ie degree show at Wandsford Quay gallery in 28 days #cork pic.twitter.com/jhZ0SzvXCP    
    
    
    @CorkBuzz1 My picture & my house too @FullSpectrum13 @CIT_ie degree show at Wandsford Quay gallery in 28 days #cork pic.twitter.com/uYLyW1ih6j    
    
    
    @IFTN Multimedia and Visual Comms @CIT_ie degree show @FullSpectrum13 at Wandsford Quay gallery #cork is in 28 days pic.twitter.com/Nq4okLtSlg    
    
    
    Going for lunch with @RichDsy. Actually  does he actively use the twitter anymore or is he just a lurker.    
    
    
    @RichDsy the perverted man in the corner watching people use the "new technology" We'll all be there someday.    
    
    
    I wonder how many people will get number 26. It's a very recognisable place but not number. @FullSpectrum13 #TheNumbersProject    
    
    
    Can you figure out where today's @FullSpectrum13 countdown photo comes from? "26 Days! pic.twitter.com/eO12CgzPL8"Clue: it's a student hotspot.    
    
    
    I've had really bad fever dreams today, college featured heavily of course. Glad to wake up in the real world though.    
    
    
    Fundraiser Gig for @FullSpectrum13 in @CyprusAveCork Tues 7/5 9pm - €5 - Waking Up Sunday Tuesday Boots 25 days to go pic.twitter.com/1zclRBDqyv    
    
    
    Hey @whazoncork, how about a retweet out of the goodness of your Cork loving hearts? https://twitter.com/JiveCork/status/331110922783444992 … it would be very appreciated.    
    
    
    @damienmulley Damien, how about a retweet for a very good cause? We need to rasie money for our college exhibition. https://twitter.com/JiveCork/status/331110922783444992 …    
    
    
    @damienmulley You sir are a scholar and a gent.    
    
    
    Kris Kross - Jump: http://youtu.be/010KyIQjkTk  #WiggidaWiggidaWiggidaWack    
    
    
    No rest for the wicked. Off to the physio next.    
    
    
    Star Trek tomorrow night, on my birthday, AGAIN. Can't wait.    
    
    
    Isn't physiotherapy mad. I just paid my friend's girlfriend to feel me up for an hour. Anywhere else that'd be frowned upon.    
    
    
    Full Spectrum gig tonight, Cyprus Avenue! #Cork 9pm €5 entry ! Great bands! DJ and Spot prizes and MY BIRTHDAY DRINKS pic.twitter.com/SBg1gfvJf5    
    
    
    How cute @ryandolanmusic and team Ireland look #eurovision http://fb.me/21xnyPeT0  #InItToWinIt    
    
    
    Good morning Alan. pic.twitter.com/D9UFfCLo5k    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Thanks Wolfgang. 10 days to my Dublin move too.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Very. College finishes on the 17th and I move on the 18th. Scary but brilliant.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime We should definitely catch up. No job but the boyfriend who is moving too is the new Revenue Manager for Travelodge Irl so..    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime we have a place to stay for free until we find an apartment. I'm hoping to break into social media through the C.S. roles    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Yep. WE've been separated by his training in the UK for the last 6 months and definitely feel that it's time #CantWait    
    
    
    Just blew my mind by thinking "The true Deadliest Catch… is the human doing the catching" :P http://dsc.discovery.com/tv-shows/deadliest-catch … …    
    
    
    Wow I'm wrecked from a tough week. One more tough week ahead though.    
    
    
    At the dentist for a check up. #yuck    
    
    
    After this only one more module to go. 4 years of work end in 7 days. pic.twitter.com/JBzMagRnU5    
    
    
    Here we go "RT @FullSpectrum13: 20 Days! pic.twitter.com/Iik74T8eM9"    
    
    
    Ever feel like telling somebody they're not doing it right? http://www.funnyjunk.com/funny_pictures/218106/your …    
    
    
    50 Billion app downloads by tomorrow morning. Amazing. #iTunes pic.twitter.com/h1QOXmlwik    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell chill out. I'll be on my way up there this time next week.    
    
    
    One of my personal favourites. I really have to make a poster of these. RT "@FullSpectrum13: 19 Days! pic.twitter.com/cwTTJ8juq2"    
    
    
    Beyond exhausted, perpetually on the edge of sickness and more stressed than an elastic at breaking point. This is the final week of college    
    
    
    Tired and Emotional “@kjmarsh: Paula White pulled off last BBC show early : Radio Today AUDIO http://bit.ly/13NHsUQ  >> quite some sign off”    
    
    
    SAturday Night Live with Kristen Wiig, I'm starting the day in style.    
    
    
    No bus services operating in Cork, Galway, Limerick, Clare or Kerry and the Greater Dublin Area due to the bus eireann strikes action.    
    
    
    Interesting read “@mathewi: "Back to the future: What if the 'mass media' era was just an accident of history?" http://nie.mn/10iyGh7 ”    
    
    
    @ryandolanmusic congrats, will listen on Monday to get me ready for Tuesday's performance #ComeOnIreland    
    
    
    F1 spoiler from both my mother and my father. After all the years of switching off the news when the soccer results come on. #SchoolboyError    
    
    
    Bus Éireann strike set to continue into tomorrow and beyond http://www.rte.ie/news/2013/0512/391767-bus-eireann-strike/ …    
    
    
    It's always so geeky to hear Patrick Steward introducing each race on #bbcf1 I keep waiting for him to say Engage.    
    
    
    There are some beautiful visuals in the original Star Trek movie but it really is the most boring two hours you'll ever spend.    
    
    
    Affected by the Bus Éireann strike? The #liftfairy can help http://jrnl.to/125adu4     
    
    
    So while @robinscreech4 goes to get glue I do my my physio Sometimes I really think I am #DoingTime 4 days    
    
    
    @OrlaFlynnCCAD Thanks for the follow Orla. I hope you're enjoying my #fullspectrum countdown pics.    
    
    
    It's almost ready for #fullspectrum "The Gaol Project" #DoingTime pic.twitter.com/hRN9JH7Y9n    
    
    
    @OrlaFlynnCCAD hehe, it certainly does stand out. Enjoy, and I hope to see you at the exhibition. Don't forget to say hi.    
    
    
    @greentothebone oooooooooooh well that's what I'm doing after Game of Thrones then.    
    
    
    @LeamCanto @rtenews Bachelor's quay is the city centre though. Anything on the central island is.    
    
    
    I had a dream about construction of #DoingTime last night. I'm a little obsessed.    
    
    
    Rising? It's always been there “@thejournal_ie: Horrific murder fuels fears of rising homophobia in Russia http://jrnl.to/1282prF ”    
    
    
    Daft Punk Random Access Memories really is great music to write final presentations to. #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Giovanni Giorgio sounds so much like Werner Herzog on the new Daft Punk album it's spooky.    
    
    
    It's time for #DoingTime our final year project to move on. Transporting it to @CIT_ie now.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell what's happening with him. I've heard other people talking about him too. Please tell me he's leaving.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Are we all supposed to be racists now? Ah jaysus, I don't have time for racism. 2 1/2 days left.    
    
    
    Heading back up to college. Lets get this thang done.    
    
    
    "Doing Time" is up and running at the @CIT_ie Multimedia symposium tonight on the top floor of the IT building from 6-8pm #DoingTime    
    
    
    Eurovision Running order for Saturday. Amazing Result for Ireland number 26 of 26 http://www.eurovision.tv/page/news?id=running_order_for_the_grand_final_revealed …    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow back @WolfgangDigital I'll be keeping an eye out for any vacancies you advertise in the near future.    
    
    
    Let my phone at home as I was about to get on the bus as I move to Dublin. Cue movie style rush through traffic. My mother had great fun.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Cheers Wolfgang. We must catch up some time soon too. I'll be free a lot as I start the job search.    
    
    
    Giggle “@damienmulley: "Damien Mulley blogger and traffic source" Maybe you should have removed that last bit before contacting me”    
    
    
    "Time" to move on. The story of Doing Time. #DoingTime #FullSpectrum http://aroconnor.tumblr.com/post/50728866658/birth-and-rebirth …    
    
    
    @bbceurovision Alan and Jānis are watching in Dublin and scoring the acts as they go, playing for a bottle of wine.    
    
    
    Waking to my first day in Dublin with a dream about college. C'mon brain, it's time to switch off.    
    
    
    So Dublin what do you have to offer today?    
    
    
    First day as a resident in Dublin and I'm treating myself to something yummy @bobosburgers I'm gonna enjoy this.    
    
    
    I bought a leap card so I'm pretty much a Dub now #BleedinDeadly    
    
    
    Gonna attempt to have a stress free day today. I've been going non stop since.... Well January actually.    
    
    
    The world's top brands: Apple, Google, IBM, McDonalds, Coca Cola, AT&T, Micosoft, Marlboro, Visa, China Mobile. Yikes I've used 8.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Yep I'd need too move to China or take up smoking to complete the set. Two things I'm unprepared to do.    
    
    
    The shiny new argument cleaning up across the net.  http://www.lurkingglass.com/threads/how-do-you-pronounce-gif.103149/ …    
    
    
    No fears here Mr Brogan (whoever you are) I walk around Ballymun alone all the time. pic.twitter.com/5d2D8ZVDa6    
    
    
    @RichDsy Hehe, everything is quite nearby. Only problem I had was being asked "are you gay" on the way home from ikea with Jānis last night.    
    
    
    Someone really should start tweeting under #ApartmentFairy it's impossible to get a place in Dublin.    
    
    
    @RichDsy Nope, with a bit of luck that's the plan for tonight though. We just took the bus back from Finglas and it ends there.    
    
    
    One apartment viewing ahead of us today. Just one. Looking for a place here is a full time job in itself.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell that @AnnCoulter tweet is a weird one. His political leanings and religion are much more important than skin colour.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell oh yeah, I know that after all you know when @piersmorgan calls @AnnCoulter a publicity leech there is a problem. Would...    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell have expected her to focus on the usual hot button topics or religion or politics though. See what @LennoxLewis said?    
    
    
    Looking for a place to live, a job and updating my website at the same time. That's multitasking.    
    
    
    @recruitireland I'll take a peek now. Lets see what you have for someone e in Digital Media in Dublin.    
    
    
    It doesn't happen often but this little guy is the bane of my life. pic.twitter.com/2sIlcOtt4E    
    
    
    @garethoconnor I guarantee you'll love it. Plenty for fans and new viewers alike.... action packed too.    
    
    
    Dear god there is a Penny Pushing daytime TV quiz show called Tipping Point. The wonders I've missed being in college :p    
    
    
    My throat is so sore today. Much to my boyfriends happiness it's gonna be a one day vow of silence for me.    
    
    
    I've just updated my profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me, view my profile and most of all recommend me at http://lnkd.in/KDbamw     
    
    
    Chilling out with @JaLazLV #NowPlaying 7 Seconds (Duet With Neneh Cherry) by Youssou N'Dour on #Spotify http://open.spotify.com/track/76D5nfZbYzZYfUZKGy73jy …    
    
    
    We at #DoingTime get a mention “@CIT_ie: Light shines on Full Spectrum | The #Cork News http://thecorknews.ie/articles/light-shines-full-spectrum-10791 …"    
    
    
    Letting agents in Dublin think you came down with the last shower if you say you're from Cork. Tried to get 200 over the asking price.    
    
    
    Monaco GP highlights on the BBC. Excellent.    
    
    
    Ok cork, I'll see you tomorrow :)    
    
    
    Ok Cork, I'm coming down, what have ya got for me?    
    
    
    @dellers yuck, glad I've brought the raincoat so.    
    
    
    @greentothebone it's about to start in Dublin too. I just escaped it.    
    
    
    @greentothebone Actually, you coming to the exhibition on Thursday Ross?    
    
    
    Thank goodness Jānis would never share if this is the kind of person advertising. #NeedAPlaceInDublin pic.twitter.com/50FNnZM85R    
    
    
    See my creation Doing Time at Full Spectrum, opening 6.30pm Thurs May 3 until June 8 at CIT Wandesford Quay Gallery http://www.citdegreeexhibitions.com     
    
    
    @greentothebone Excellent I look forward to seeing you there. I know you for a while now but we've never actually met.    
    
    
    I've been next on the queue for 30mins already. This is stretching my patience a lil but.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime ah it's alright so far. Getting a place (and a job) is a pain but I'm actually down in cork now for Thursday's exhibition.    
    
    
    12 months later I'm still dealing with an ex manager who didn't give me a p45.    
    
    
    My mother was very impressed my project for @FullSpectrum13 was mentioned in @TheCorkNews    
    
    
    Now officially JiveCork on Snapchat. I'd better see what everyone is talking about.    
    
    
    Right then Star Trek in bed it is. Staying with the parents for a few days is extremely boring.    
    
    
    Oooh I think I'm through to the second round of an Online Specialist job. I say I think because the email was especially cryptic.    
    
    
    Interesting that RTE are honouring the requests of parents not to repeat #PrimeTime PSB at its best. http://www.thejournal.ie/rte-no-repeats-or-online-airing-of-prime-time-creche-investigation-928711-May2013/?utm_source=twitter_self …    
    
    
    Finally :) A new @SminkyAnimation Sminky Short, Elephant. http://youtu.be/2uZQnhvf49o     
    
    
    @robinscreech4 neither did I and I think it's a pity it's not repeated but doing this works for everyone. Watch the #PrimeTime ratings soar.    
    
    
    Aaaah a nice cold can of @CocaCola on ireland's yearly sunny day. #perfection    
    
    
    Is Nelly singing about Portia di Rossi? #NowPlaying Hey Porsche by Nelly who is #BarkingUpTheWrongTree http://open.spotify.com/track/3uuGbRzMsDI5RiKWKOjqWL …    
    
    
    Kicking off tonight at 6:30 until June 8th visit #DoingTime in the Multimedia room @FullSpectrum13 pic.twitter.com/XM6OzEwxw4    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell thanks Kev. We're the white one in the middle pic.twitter.com/7qlkxC1KQe    
    
    
    @greentothebone thanks Ross. Delighted to see so many people turn up and    
    
    
    @greentothebone to meet you for the 1st time too.    
    
    
    Had to run to catch the bus to Dublin there. Back to reality after a fabulous night at @FullSpectrum13. Bye Cork    
    
    
    Traveling to Dublin on an @Aircoach without air conditioning or windows #baked should have went with gobé    
    
    
    It just felt so good to turn down a letting agent who tried to get one over on us. Balance of power restored.    
    
    
    Hoping the guys at @awty2013 are having a great time. The people from @FullSpectrum13 send you all the best. #ortloike    
    
    
    Leaving the folks at Travelodge Ballymun to move into the new place. Seriously in need of unpacking.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Thanks Derek. Say hi if you're gonna be up for #DublinPride    
    
    
    There's a man behind me on the bus that sounds like old Mr Brennan. I really am living in #Dublin    
    
    
    "and nicknamed the Rebel County, since the Senate hearings last week." Not the only factual inaccuracy in this story  http://mobile.bloomberg.com/news/2013-05-31/apple-no-ghost-in-ireland-where-cork-frets-senate-hearing-taxes.html …    
    
    
    Waking up for the first time in the new apartment. Still getting used to the mattress. Place is lookin good though.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Top of Glasnevin bottom of Finglas. Very nice apartment, top floor too so it has a great view.    
    
    
    On http://twitter.com  you can now get tailored trends to Cork and Galway too. Time to get #Langer trending. pic.twitter.com/1Goc0XEVFw    
    
    
    Getting bills and finances sorted today. Who knew there was so much paperwork in moving house?    
    
    
    @beccanoonan I'm at it's counterpart in Finglas now. Great pictures coming from you all in the states I'm crazy jealous.    
    
    
    Ben Dunne gyms. Worth the bus trip from Finglas for the cheaper price or not? #Dublin    
    
    
    So this @irishexaminer Limerick billboard that's gotten everyone up in arms is a bit silly. Bad idea to put it outside Limerick station too.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe I spotted the Finglas leisure centre alright, its a fair walk from me but could be worth it. Are you local too?    
    
    
    @RichDsy    
    
    
    @RichDsy Indeed you could. You're pretty much the reason I'll rent for life.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe Prospect Hill the border between Finglas and Glasnevin. The hunt goes well, I have a Skype interview with a US startup 2mor.    
    
    
    . @bobosburgers It's almost worth the bus into town on this glorious day.    
    
    
    Fire alarm at the apartment block, there's only one thing for it... Go out and enjoy the sun in the shared garden until it stops.    
    
    
    Big day planned today. I have a lot of walking around to do but it's sunny so :D    
    
    
    Broken leap card scanner on the bus. Free trip to town, well that's a good start to the day.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 Happy out. The new place is lovely, I have an interview later today the only trial is getting stuff up from Cork. I need a van.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 and how are you keeping in Cork?    
    
    
    Going to take a look at the European Space Expo in @tcddublin it certainly is quite an impressive structure. pic.twitter.com/walsuwaowO    
    
    
    Loving the live soapbox talks at @SpaceExpoDublin in association with @ScienceGallery pic.twitter.com/yVjwKjREZK    
    
    
    @blueswannabe it went really well actually, nice chat with lively people, fingers crossed. I just passed the IFIC area there actually.    
    
    
    @blueswannabe Working hard no doubt. Just found out I have another interview with a different company next week too. #ThingsArePickingUp    
    
    
    THAT episode of Game of Thrones will be viewed in the penthouse tonight. #NoSpoilers    
    
    
    Watching Teen Wolf Season 3. #GuiltyPleasure #NightOff    
    
    
    @mushacles Not the greatest episode to be honest a lot of glossing over the 2nd season ending.    
    
    
    Yikes MT “@Kotaku: Microsoft confirms that Xbox One will need to connect to the Internet every 24 hours for gaming: http://bit.ly/17s1J6O ”    
    
    
    Channel 4 certainly have the right idea MT “@siliconrepublic: Channel 4 to launch dedicated second screen app: http://silrep.com/13fNtIr ”    
    
    
    Busy busy busy. Back to #Cork for 24 hours.    
    
    
    No autocorrect I didn't mean mire, the much more likely more would have been a better choice. #SnootyAutocorrect    
    
    
    If there's one thing I've learned in life it's if you ever get lost looking for Abercrombie & Fitch then follow your nose.    
    
    
    About to enjoy a free breakfast thanks to the folks at Denny Ireland and @98FM here at their Grafton Street pop up cafe. YUM.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Who is it you're working with at the moment actually?    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Lemmie know if they're hiring then :D)))) Still shopping around for a job here. Looking to earn myself some €€€.    
    
    
    Re-watching The Name of the Doctor while on the bus to Cork. This episode makes up for all the crappy ones this season. #Trenzelore    
    
    
    The Queen Photobombs The BBC http://www.buzzfeed.com/sirajdatoo/the-queen-photobombs-the-bbc?sub=2305581_1248293 …    
    
    
    There's something very weird about waking up without an alarm at 8am on Sunday. Feels like a missed opportunity.    
    
    
    After over a year of watching F1 on streams I finally get to watch a race live again... and in HD.    
    
    
    We desperately need some rain for Alonso #BBCF1 #f1    
    
    
    ALO battling HAM for second. Come on Ferando. 11 laps remaining. #canadiangp #f1 #bbcf1    
    
    
    Annonces françaises tonight on Channel 4 to celebrate #TheReturned    
    
    
    Can't wait “@TheDailyShow: John Oliver takes his seat behind The #DailyShow desk tomorrow night! 11/10c. pic.twitter.com/9Ltuj8nFWi”    
    
    
    OSX Mavericks? MAVERICKS? So they're naming it after a Mel Gibson movie.    
    
    
    Now that I'm finally going to use the Xbox I'm very happy to hear about the death of Microsoft Points.    
    
    
    It's all lovely that Safari is shiny and new but get to the point guys. I'm switching from #WWDC to #e32013    
    
    
    Ok I must admit App Nap is both a great idea and clever name.    
    
    
    iCloud keychain, given their track record on cloud services I reserve judgement until I hear that it works. #wwdc    
    
    
    Maps App. How about making the maps open source instead? Fanboys would fix this thing together quite easily. #wwdc    
    
    
    iBook text books with high fidelity content on the mac. That's the future folks. #MakeItHappen #wwdc    
    
    
    Here comes the Air. All day battery life FTW #WWDC    
    
    
    Ship date for Xbox One is November. #e32013    
    
    
    Piano black finish and cylindrical display. The new Mac Pro looks weird. It may kick ass but looks cheap #wwdc    
    
    
    Office 365 from Apple then. iWork for iCloud, iSnooze. Where's my ios7? #wwdc    
    
    
    iOS FINALLY. #wwdc    
    
    
    I'd say my iPhone 4 may either just scrape this update or is gonna be left behind. #TearsForIOS7 #WWDC    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa The software on the phones and iPads.    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa Thank gawd. :D)))))    
    
    
    Very flat, very nice though. It's just so...... Different. #wwdc    
    
    
    @aoifemeefa I really like the new look. Dammit, I'm gonna have to get a 5S aren't I?    
    
    
    Transparency on Control Centre, that's excellent. #wwdc    
    
    
    New Siri sounds good but iOS in the car is really the next step. #wwdc    
    
    
    iTunes radio. IT LIVES #wwdc I betcha it's not in Ireland though.    
    
    
    ios7 on iPhone 4 and later YAY. I'm delighted #wwdc    
    
    
    Between the excitement of WWDC and Game Of Thrones tonight I'm in nerd heaven.    
    
    
    So, how long before iTunes Radio comes to Ireland? I'm predicting one year. It could never be available from launch, could it?    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I wouldn't mind paying for iTunes Match in that case. A cheap one off payment and replace my DRM songs too. #WhyNot    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I love Spotify and must admit it has some thing iTunes Radio hasn't but I could live without them to save 100ish quid.    
    
    
    This makes me so happy RT “@JoannaStern: Confirmed: You can put Newsstand into a folder in iOS 7!!”    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime I passed your offices a few mind ago, had been at the shopping centre and was passing. Nice place.    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Definitely next time I'm up here interested in the couples memberships at Dunne's Gym.    
    
    
    Watching Star Trek the Original Series on CBS Action. I must be very bored.    
    
    
    Yikes, I'm currently watching a CNN correspondent Arwa Damon getting hit by tear gas in Istanbul. #turkey    
    
    
    Ad for Ibiza club Matinée is an 80s/90s dream. These guys have to work with Daft Punk. http://youtu.be/ED5azV-xrHM     
    
    
    That's UCC on How I Met Your Mother again. Always so weird.    
    
    
    Could someone at @RTENewsNow take a look at the tabs on the right of the screen they need to be re-aligned as they're going over the picture    
    
    
    Lovely shop assistant in Jack & Jones wants to help me pick out my boxers. The prude in me blushes at the thought. #SoIrish    
    
    
    @spiller2 I did get that feeling but she was a lady and I'm a happily married man. #Shudder    
    
    
    #ManOfSteel #CantWait pic.twitter.com/qs1xNzMEi7    
    
    
    Dear makers of "Man of Steel", tonight you have made me a very angry man. #ManOfSteel #Rant    
    
    
    Looks like Dublin Zoo is on the agenda today. Young Mr. Jānis is very excited.    
    
    
    It's been a funny old day. Aches and pains from an awkward sleep but I had good fun in town. #Dublin    
    
    
    I'm hooked on Big Brother already, I'm loing Michael the fake Cork contestant. #BB #SecretsAndLies    
    
    
    Listening to @stephenfry on @Herring1967 Leicester Square podcast speaking about his bi-polar disorder. Such an interesting subject matter.    
    
    
    Just pushed through a few updates to http://www.aroconnor.com  time flies content gets old and twitter changes their API. All solved now though    
    
    
    Nominations live. I'm loving #BBUK so much right now.    
    
    
    @brianclayton probably HMV again. They're reopening in Dublin and Limerick too.    
    
    
    Beautiful day for @MichelleObama to visit Glendalough. #IrishSummer    
    
    
    @brianclayton That's quite a coup I haven't bought a physical CD or DVD in years but its good to see a small company expanding these days.    
    
    
    WHA? “@GMA: Neil Patrick Harris to star as Hedwig in "Hedwig and the Angry Inch" on Broadway” #IJustDied    
    
    
    It's always weird when you see someone you've followed on twitter in real life. I think I've just seen @darraghdoyle    
    
    
    @darraghdoyle *wipes the tears (of laughter) away.    
    
    
    Where's my Mickey? Coming Thursday #Facepalm http://thenextweb.com/apps/2013/06/18/disney-builds-on-hit-water-puzzler-franchise-with-wheres-my-mickey-game/?utm_medium=Spreadus&awesm=tnw.to_a0ZBG&utm_campaign=social%20media&utm_source=Twitter …    
    
    
    Blurring the lines pic.twitter.com/LuAiC3XEPj    
    
    
    The poor bored Obama kids. http://abcnews.go.com/GMA/video/malia-sasha-obama-vacation-obama-girls-impressed-summer-19426194 …    
    
    
    So, I have a degree now (Very happy).    
    
    
    @Golden_Gaytime Cheers. There will be celebrations :D    
    
    
    I should really celebrate the end of college tonight. But how?    
    
    
    @blueswannabe oh yes, but very rarely and I'm at a wedding tomorrow and it'll be expected there. Would much prefer good food or a movie.    
    
    
    Xbox One is a market player. Not only have they Uturned on stuff they've also canceled regional restrictions http://news.xbox.com/2013/06/update     
    
    
    And we are awake, Cork, I'm heading your way.    
    
    
    At a wedding in Blarney, quite tired and hungry. Food will perk me up though.    
    
    
    Oh my god, how did nobody tell me sorbet could be THIS good.    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell yep I'm at a wedding in Blarney. Never had it before (not in the least bit posh) its GORGEOUS.    
    
    
    I'm stuffed. One day I think I'll turn into a potato. Then I'll probably cannibalistically eat myself because I smell sooo good.    
    
    
    Being at this wedding the sudden realisation has hit me I'm definitely a city boy. Farming was mentioned in the speeches.    
    
    
    This is one hell of a groom's speech. #LovelyGuy    
    
    
    Maybe it's all the sugar from the cake but I'd love a bit of Crystal Swing now.    
    
    
    Mad traffic on the way into Dublin and its moving extremely slowly.    
    
    
    Such a mistake to take Michael the people's puppet out tonight. I'd vote for him to win if I could. #BBUK #PeoplesPuppet    
    
    
    Folks looking for work, good luck. “@ConorCulkin: Mahon Point cinema and Suas bar both looking for for staff. #jobfairy”    
    
    
    Refreshing my typing skills by typing song lyrics. "You don't need money, 
Don't take fame, Don't need no credit card to ride this train."    
    
    
    I'm usually not a sucker fro advert songs but "Michelle Gayle - Sweetness" is a classic http://youtu.be/xvK26tC9UNY     
    
    
    I really enjoy seeing @iainlee on #bbots he should be on the show more often though, he's great fun. @bbuk sort it out.    
    
    
    I just realised I haven't played all of Tomb Raider, Guardian of Light. Lets get this done. #TripBackInTime    
    
    
    Catching up on my film review podcasts trying to figure out weather to go see #WorldWarZ or not.    
    
    
    The @KermodeMovie review of #ManOfSteel is so on the button it's scary.    
    
    
    @Adlers1 Is that in Ballymun?    
    
    
    Big afternoon tomorrow #FingersCrossed    
    
    
    @kevinjpurcell Indeed. A little nervous but it'll (hopefully) be fine. Meet up this week?    
    
    
    Three mobile phone network down across the country (Thank goodness I thought it was just me) http://jrnl.ie/964056     
    
    
    And we're back. The last few hours without internet were dark times. Dark, dark times :P @threecare    
    
    
    Interviews are always a bit exhausting but now I can relax for the evening.    
    
    
    @Adlers1 Weird, it looked so familiar (though I could know it from Killarney too).    
    
    
    Oh Silvio Berlusconi you're never gonna go to jail but at least you're banned from public office.    
    
    
    My 10,000th tweet I dedicate to my @JaLazLV    
    
    
    10,001 thanks to @kevinjpurcell @robinscreech4 @greentothebone @shiteandonions @thejackanory @damienmulley @dmndnn pic.twitter.com/YVyPknJvuC    
    
    
    @JaLazLV http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ViwtNLUqkMY …    
    
    
    @dmndnn I finally broke 10,000 so I looked to see who I contacted most in that time and the words I used most (you're on the list)    
    
    
    @dmndnn Downloaded my entire archive from the settings section on twitter and let http://Wordle.com  do the rest.    
    
    
    As in life “@bbuk: "Be tactful" is a good rule. #BBUK”    
    
    
    @ippily You're zooming through them. :)    
    
    
    "No, I'm not going to the world cup". A video to make to think. http://youtu.be/ZApBgNQgKPU     
    
    
    Trading #BBUK for #PrimeTime. Unfortunately things couldn't be more REALITY on the latter.    
    
    
    Not a great job on covering the situation tonight on #rtept too much navel gazing. Put on @MiriamOCal, mammy will sort it out.    
    
    
    "Gym?" "Eh I suppose so." That's my inner monologue people. #nopainnogain    
    
    
    Good first day back at the gym, I'm gonna get that dodgy knee fixed by hook or by crook.    
    
    
    @Newberry52 I'm waiting on an email today with fingers crossed.    
    
    
    @robinscreech4 Mostly businesses    
    
    
    According to twitter's stats I'm tweeting less now than at any other point in my history. Maybe it doesn't have the same attraction?    
    
    
    GOT THAT JOB :D    
    
    
    Forced myself to the gym today because I had work celebrations last night. So so difficult, I wouldn't recommend it.    
    
    
    This would be nice in my apartment ;) pic.twitter.com/N16nPW9kzX    
    
    
    Passing by Rte News nonchalantly as they film a piece to camera. This is the real reason I moved to Dublin.    
    
    
    @garethoconnor Were you not miffed by him not living up to his ideals in the ending (trying to not give spoilers to others)?    
    
    
    @garethoconnor Fair point I guess, I was happy with most of the movie but (fittingly) that was the straw that broke the camel's back for me.    
    
    
    @CROSSYFM104 Enjoyed your DJing last night at the party and you played Kiki for me. Cheers.    
    
    
    Louis should stay out. There's no way he can win and theres no reason to wreck the car. #f1 #BritishGP    
    
    
    I know I shouldn't, especially after the gym, but I wanted that hot chicken roll so bad.    
    
    
    Visited Google Reader for the last time, such a shame to see it go. Underused and under appreciated. #MarkAsRead    
    
    
    