I know people here don't know how to handle rain...but really? pic.twitter.com/8Z53IITJKZ    
    
    
    I just want to know who was on the phone in that presser    
    
    
    #AZCardinals DE: 'We're not going to beat anybody' without improved pass rush --  http://shar.es/ivSxl  via @AZSports620    
    
    
    BUT NO MAJOR VIOLATIONS MT @ChuckCarltonDMN: OkSt series will report paying players, academic misconduct, drugs & sex w/ recruit hostesses    
    
    
    #AZCardinals LT Levi Brown: Cause of struggles is correctable -- http://bit.ly/1dWzLmF     
    
    
    Because who doesn't like UA coverage on Phoenix sites? #ArizonaWildcats' Neal ruled ineligible by #NCAA: http://bit.ly/1dWAcx9     
    
    
    10 from $. Guy at my table shoved every hand for 10 minutes. Doubled up with
 63o and Q6s. I shove A10s. GUESS WHO ACTUALLY HAS A HAND.    
    
    
    @BrianCarr20 and I wish my Friday night wasn't going to be spent working until 11    
    
    
    Just heard the phrase "consistently averages." Is there a way to inconsistently average?    
    
    
    Only basketball players, obvi. RT @azdesertswarm: I wonder if anyone who doesn't play football smokes pot.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats. 59 watch. Turn on Golf Channel. RT @DanHicksNBC Furyk makes birdy at #5 now -11 thru 13!!!    
    
    
    Late-night Tucson bound.    
    
    
    It doesn't say good things about your program when a tight end makes a catch, shakes a corner and outruns the rest of your secondary.    
    
    
    Running left and pitching with the wrong hand right in front of a defender might be the most Taylor Martinez thing ever.    
    
    
    Playing chickenshit football on the road won't win you many games. Looking at you, Akron.    
    
    
    Akron is so bad. Bad players, bad coaching, and somehow should have won despite missing two field goals and throwing a pick at the 2.    
    
    
    Akron hasn't won a road game since I went to school there. Wow.    
    
    
    Can we talk about how @AlexHWilliams will handle the rest of the day opposed to how he would have if Akron had won?    
    
    
    What a god-awful decision by Johnny Manziel.    
    
    
    Oregon's QB just threw for twice as mamy yards in one half as Arizona's has in two games.    
    
    
    The punter and QB wear the same number? Seems legit.    
    
    
    #KEGBEER #BEARDOWN (@ Dirtbag's w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/1edD219     
    
    
    UTSA might be the dirtiest football team I've ever watched.    
    
    
    Get absolutely screwed, Wisconsin.    
    
    
    I hope ASU feels great about that one.    
    
    
    I wonder if there's been talk about changing Cameron Johnston's number to 13 or 5 in order to try and confuse the defense like Cal did.    
    
    
    WALT WITH THE DAGGER    
    
    
    Owning a #Seahawks #12 jersey is pathetic and embarrassing.    
    
    
    Ah. Good point. MT @bill_slane: @territorialcup do they only where the game will be aired on ESPN? because that game is going to be on Fox    
    
    
    I will never understand a professional athlete being as mentally weak as Trevor Cahill is.    
    
    
    How do you think #ASU fans would react if someone on the defense just laid on the ball every time the Devils wanted to go fast?    
    
    
    Flop a straight and guy calls down with third pair. Great except the part where board runs out to a straight and he has the high end.    
    
    
    Accidentally registered for a FL Stud H/L tournament. Anyone have tips?    
    
    
    Random Stud Hi/Lo tourney update: 20/305. No idea what I'm doing.    
    
    
    Apparently 6th Ave. is now a two-way street. That's a game-changer.    
    
    
    It's been real, baseball. See you in March.    
    
    
    It's been real, baseball. See you in March.    
    
    
    It's been real, baseball. See you in March.    
    
    
    It's been real, baseball. See you in March.    
    
    
    Oh wow. That's not going to make the #Dbacks very happy.    
    
    
    That's the kind of thing that leads to something like drug dogs searching team buses. Or "extra security" in the clubhouse area.    
    
    
    "This free service that I use should change because I said so." MT @statepress An open letter on 'Twitter jail' http://bit.ly/1eUNHPu     
    
    
    Fans, players and media react to the #Dodgers celebration at Chase Field: http://arizonasports.com/42/1663905/Arizona-reacts-to-Dodgers-NL-West-celebration …    
    
    
    Bad football teams somehow stand out so much more when they're in a close game against good teams.    
    
    
    Arizona basketball's Sean Miller is not Arizona football's Rich Rodriguez http://sbn.to/1b03XNk     
    
    
    Sign I'm the worst poker play ever: Get to 5-handed as 2-1 chip leader. 4 get paid. I bubble.    
    
    
    That bust courtesy of someone calling a shove with Q8s and flopping top two.    
    
    
    Arizona basketball's Sean Miller is not Arizona football's Rich Rodriguez http://sbn.to/1b03XNk     
    
    
    I should just insta-fold every time I flop two pair because a flush or straight is coming somewhere around a billion percent of the time.    
    
    
    .@KirkHerbstreit is on a mission today to make sure people know that Arozona and Arizona State are different. I like it.    
    
    
    Calling a personal foul with no elaboration and no number is the shadiest call a ref can make.    
    
    
    Off to Washinrgton vs Idaho state. Huskies are 49.5 pt favorites. Should be fun    
    
    
    So Ohio State gets jumped when it wins 42-7 and criticized for winning 76-0. Makes sense.    
    
    
    But at least ASU had that big program-defining win last week.    
    
    
    ASU is somewhere between above average and good. Somehow its fans got the idea it's better than that.    
    
    
    I'm just amazed that after Ohio State dropped in the polls after a 42-7 win, Urban Meyer is getting criticized for running up the score.    
    
    
    Let's change that to what in the world are these refs in the Utah-BYU game looking at?    
    
    
    That was a BS reverse on the PI call. If BYU wins... Ehhhh    
    
    
    Good god this crew is terrible.    
    
    
    It's almost weird seeing the Cardinals line up under center and run in 3rd-and-short after Whisenhunt's "tough, disciplined football" era.    
    
    
    The only thing worse than accuweather updates are accuweather updates that expired a half hour ago.    
    
    
    I hate the rules about when coaches can/can't throw challenge flags. Just tell them to pick the flag up and move on.    
    
    
    @NickRillo @BrianCarr20 the worst part    
    
    
    Call from UA alumni person, asked what I did for work. "Sportswriter." More chit chat, then "can you donate $?" Umm, I said sportswriter...    
    
    
    #AZCardinals linebacker Lorenzo Alexander says he won't turn into an "IR ghost" after suffering a Lisfranc injury http://arizonasports.com/40/1664746/Cards-Alexander-not-discouraged-by-seasonending-injury …    
    
    
    So the Houston #Astros drew a 0.0 Nielsen rating in Houston on Sunday. http://arizonasports.com/164/1664759/Houston-Astros-draw-00-Nielsen-rating-in-Houston …    
    
    
    The #ArizonaWildcats will face their toughest competition of 2013 at UW, and it's a team that's similar to the UA: http://arizonasports.com/45/1664780/Rodriguez-UW-game-will-be-great-challenge-for-Wildcats …    
    
    
    It's incredible to me that Terrelle Pryor is playing quarterback in the same game as Peyton Manning.    
    
    
    Discussion in the sports dept: What is the worst personnel move (player, GM, manager) #Dbacks have made in their history? #JustWondering    
    
    
    #Dbacks Kirk Gibson on the #Dodgers peeing in the pool: "Not cool. That's bad pool etiquette."    
    
    
    More #Dbacks' Gibson: Protecting teammates 'Something we need to do better' -- http://bit.ly/1bavImz     
    
    
    Something #Dbacks fans are familiar with: Shortstop will be an open competition during spring training -- http://bit.ly/14EWjD7     
    
    
    Michael Wacha against the #ArizonaWildcats in  the 2011 College Station Regional: 7 ip, 5 hits, 0 runs, 4 strikeouts in a no-decision.    
    
    
    Kurt Heyer threw 7.2 innings, giving up 5 hits, two runs and striking out six in that game. Took the L in the regional championship game.    
    
    
    It's sure a good thing #ASU has "No pity for the kitty," otherwise the UA might have won more than EVERY TERRITORIAL CUP SERIES EVER HELD.    
    
    
    Between that and "Fear the Fork," ASU has come up with some gems.    
    
    
    Oh man, this takes me back to the Sun Devil Laws. Like No. 39: Diamonds are a Girl's best friend. Note the random capitalization of "Girl's"    
    
    
    If anyone wants to enjoy some more, like No. 169: "Wells Fargo is our Home Court. I am the advantage." Here you go - http://www.sundevillaws.com/categories.html#football …    
    
    
    It's sure a good thing #ASU has "No pity for the kitty," otherwise the UA might have won more than EVERY TERRITORIAL CUP SERIES EVER HELD.    
    
    
    It's like everything's lining up for a brisk little two-hour, 1-0 game, then #Dbacks baseball happens.    
    
    
    It's awkward that Randall Delgado's Twitter account just tweeted.    
    
    
    Behind a pregnant woman in line at Bevmo. This is awk.    
    
    
    There's no kegbeer like airport kegbeer! (@ Phoenix Sky Harbor International Airport (PHX) - @phxskyharbor) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1asIFDL     
    
    
    Oh hey, Seattle. (@ Seattle-Tacoma International Airport (SEA) w/ 83 others) http://4sq.com/175WDvF     
    
    
    It's weird being somewhere with a season between hot and cold.    
    
    
    Hands down the most relevant game in baseball tonight. (@ Safeco Field - @mariners for Athletics vs Mariners) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16xQGKu     
    
    
    Safeco Field just got louder for a dancing grounds crew than Chase Field has been in two years.    
    
    
    To Rainier! (at @SamsTavern w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1bONV8s     
    
    
    Seattle is really living up to that 100 percent chance of rain today.    
    
    
    Get a clue. Is it really that hard? RT @SportsCenter: Washington will wear these metallic gold helmets Saturday against Arizona #ASUvsUW    
    
    
    Let's go 'Cats! (@ Husky Stadium for Arizona Wildcats vs Washington Huskies w/ @wildcatphotog) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1hbw6yG     
    
    
    Lets go 'Cats! http://instagram.com/p/e0izv7HgaH/     
    
    
    To be a little fair, Denker isn't seeing anything down the field. WRs need to help him out.    
    
    
    Arizona has no chance in this game with BJ Denker at quarterback.    
    
    
    Who's having a worse game...Denker or Riggleman?    
    
    
    Nothing says "We trust you BJ" like a quarterback power on 3rd-and-long. And he's not even the #ArizonaWildcats' worst player today.    
    
    
    Solid decision-making from Denker there. He really looks like he belongs on this field tonight.    
    
    
    I hated on BJ Denker a lot tonight but it's not his fault the #ArizonaWildcats don't have anyone better.    
    
    
    Dueces, Seattle. Looking forward to seeing the sun for the first time in four days. http://instagram.com/p/e2x0pOHgcL/     
    
    
    Somehow I managed to record both the pre- and post-game shows without recording the actual #ArizonaWildcats game. That's impressive.    
    
    
    #AZCardinals HC Arians: Cards 'not that far off' from offensive success -- http://arizonasports.com/40/1666414/Arians-Cards-not-that-far-off-from-offensive-success …    
    
    
    CBS Sports NFL Insider: #AZCardinals should look "very hard" at taking QB early in 2014 draft -- http://arizonasports.com/40/1666458/CBS-Insider-Cards-should-think-very-hard-about-drafting-QB-early …    
    
    
    #ASU is off to as good a start as it could have hoped, but the Sun Devils' run defense has Todd Graham concerned -- http://arizonasports.com/44/1666477/ASUs-Graham-Big-runs-have-been-our-nemesis …    
    
    
    Just read someone saying that the weather cleared up in the second half of the #ArizonaWildcats game Saturday. Good one, internet commenter.    
    
    
    Hey, look at MLB umpires being right where they should be in a one-game playoff. The center of attention. Oh, wait ...    
    
    
    Bought GTA on the way home from work to prepare for this whole government shutdown thing. #SunsOutGunsOut    
    
    
    Switching things up a little bit today... pic.twitter.com/W5HkEtR6YJ    
    
    
    Hahahahaha. Oh wow. #Dbacks RT @JonHeymanCBS ex-dbacks manager A.J. Hinch is a candidate for the cubs. http://cbsprt.co/17pWWBF     
    
    
    Cleveland really, really deserves this. I went to a lot of games there back in my day. Good to see the Jake packed again.    
    
    
    I am BEYOND thrilled to announce that I am joining the @ESPNTUCSON team! Catch me 3 - 6 p.m. in the near future. Dreams do come true, folks.    
    
    
    It'd be cool if TBS could fix this whole double-sounds thing.    
    
    
    Oh Cleveland. Someday.    
    
    
    Did this TBS guy really just say he'd rather not have a 3-0 lead?    
    
    
    I'm still wondering why baseball - a sport that prides itself on longevity - decided one game is the best way to see who moves on.    
    
    
    It's just unreal how much better hockey is live compared to on TV.    
    
    
    First thought when I walked outside: "Man, it's a little chilly out." It was 85. I love Arizona.    
    
    
    Driving to Fort McDowell to run kings into aces on the first hand of the tournament was a good time.    
    
    
    I think a puppy dies every time a goal-line play in the middle of the field is reviewed.    
    
    
    It's always sunny when you're cool, Brady Hoke.    
    
    
    The #Dbacks want to add a power corner-outfield bat, but @DHallDbacks says they still don't regret trading @JUP_8TL: http://bit.ly/1a1S6Id     
    
    
    Butch Jones is the man!    
    
    
    Solid stuff from the photog on the field taking off his hat and screaming at the ref after that PI in the end zone.    
    
    
    Ohio State's defense is absolutely terrible.    
    
    
    Ohio State is putting on a clinic on how to lose games on the road when you're the significantly better team.    
    
    
    It's amazing that Northwestern played 30 minutes against the No. 4 team in the country without committing a single penalty.    
    
    
    Taylor Kelly said Wednesday that the #ASU offense was firing on all cylinders. So much for that.    
    
    
    Braxton Miller has cost Ohio State at least 21 points in this game.    
    
    
    I  REALLY thought #ASU was going to win that game something like 42-20. Oops.    
    
    
    Ohio State has to snap that ball instantly.    
    
    
    I can't wait to listen to people rip Ohio State for beating the No. 16 team on the road.    
    
    
    I'm so confused about why Ohio State didn't give that ball to Carlos Hyde.    
    
    
    Yeah, give it to the guy who's the reason you're in a close game, not the guy who's the reason you're winning it.    
    
    
    FOR THE LOVE OF BACKDOOR COVERS!    
    
    
    @AlexHWilliams Hello Alex. Can you follow for a DM?    
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: #Coyotes trail wire-to-wire in loss to San Jose #Sharks - http://bit.ly/16qHCVl     
    
    
    Oh my god Mark May just said something rational about Ohio State.    
    
    
    God forbid Karlos Dansby touches the 6-6, 250 pound quarterback.    
    
    
    Can someone explain to me how Larry Fitzgerald wasn't out of bounds?    
    
    
    USC opened -7 against the #ArizonaWildcats. It's down to -6. That confuses me.    
    
    
    USC opened -7 against the #ArizonaWildcats. It's down to -6. That confuses me.    
    
    
    If you're gonna tailgate me when I'm going faster than the speed limit in the right lane, you better be prepared to go 20 for a while.    
    
    
    They're showing the World Series of Poker on ESPN, while game 2 of the WNBA Finals is on ESPN2. There's something wrong with that.    
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: #Coyotes fall in early hole, suffer second straight road blowout - http://bit.ly/1akJkqn     
    
    
    I feel like I should know better than to open snapchats from @JackBridge45 when I'm at work.    
    
    
    Every main headline I write is a hammer. @LukeMMoney would be in heaven.    
    
    
    I'm surprised that #AZCardinals fans already want to get rid of Carson Palmer after spending three years watching the alternative.    
    
    
    I'm surprised that #AZCardinals fans already want to get rid of Carson Palmer after spending three years watching the alternative.    
    
    
    I feel like I should know better than to open snapchats from @JackBridge45 when I'm at work.    
    
    
    I'm surprised that #AZCardinals fans already want to get rid of Carson Palmer after spending three years watching the alternative.    
    
    
    @BrianCarr20 who are you    
    
    
    Thats got to be one of the flukiest runs in baseball history    
    
    
    I remember when the best part about getting SI was reading Rick Reilly.    
    
    
    Little disappointed it's not glasses ref tonight    
    
    
    I feel like I've seen Shaq Richardson and Jon McKnight running 10 yards behind a USC receiver before.    
    
    
    This drive is all Arizona needs from Denker.    
    
    
    Lol Arizona kickers    
    
    
    Most of Denker's threat as a passer depends on run game. Don't get empty set on third and short.    
    
    
    It says a lot about Pac-12 refs that the third down play even had to be reviewed.    
    
    
    People calling for Denker to be benched - fumbles like that are the only way it happens.    
    
    
    You've gotta be shitting me with that pizza hut ad. Who thought that was a good idea?    
    
    
    I hate the decision to not run on third then go for fourth, especially with a kicker who just missed a 38-yarder by 20 yards.    
    
    
    It looks like BJ Denker has been to the Denard Robinson school of deep balls.    
    
    
    @kcoharah how is that place?    
    
    
    @kcoharah how is that place?    
    
    
    The video's what starting at 2:35? MT @APlayersProgram Doors open at 1pm with video's starting at 2:35pm! #APlayersProgram    
    
    
    I really think Arizona's two worst players are its kicker and punter.    
    
    
    Context is not this stat's friend. RT @WildcatSports: BJ Denker now has 262 yards passing. Cody Kessler 231 #AZvsUSC #arizonawildcats    
    
    
    I really think Arizona's two worst players are its kicker and punter.    
    
    
    @AlexHWilliams miss you boo    
    
    
    RichRod was so on-point when he said Ka'Deem Carey runs hungry. Best way to describe it. Guy always wants the extra yard.    
    
    
    I think the most concerning thing about Denker is that when he sees pressure, his first reaction is to run straight backward.    
    
    
    Coaches can learn to work around the inaccuracy and get Denker in situations where he's comfortable. But I don't think panic is fixable.    
    
    
    Oh wow Arizona. Best throw of Denker's life.    
    
    
    Everyone should know by now that SHIT GETS WEIRD ON THURSDAY NIGHTS IN THE PAC-12.    
    
    
    Dropping that in between four defenders. Wow.    
    
    
    Second straight game this has been clear - #ArizonaWildcats aren't far from competing in the Pac. RichRod has them going right direction.    
    
    
    A little more defensive depth … a little more consistency at QB all it takes. No reason at all to be discouraged by the #ArizonaWildcats.    
    
    
    So...um, did anyone ever ask why the clock kept running when Redd ran outta bounds?    
    
    
    Second straight game this has been clear - #ArizonaWildcats aren't far from competing in the Pac. RichRod has them going right direction.    
    
    
    So...um, did anyone ever ask why the clock kept running when Redd ran outta bounds?    
    
    
    Maybe I have a drinking problem, but I don't get the point of having A beer.Like "hey, let's get a beer." No thanks. I'll have several.    
    
    
    This really might be the funniest thing I've ever seen. http://bit.ly/19FsxvT     
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: #Coyotes top #Flyers 2-1, win second straight behind Greiss' stellar debut in net - http://bit.ly/16W9RxD     
    
    
    Former #Dbacks Triple-A manager Brett Butler will join the Miami #Marlins' coaching staff, the Reno Aces announced - http://bit.ly/17ldXtE     
    
    
    Former #Dbacks Triple-A manager Brett Butler will join the Miami #Marlins' coaching staff, the Reno Aces announced - http://bit.ly/17ldXtE     
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    The good news is that we're pretty much guaranteed weird baseball. #weirdbaseball    
    
    
    Sometimes you've just gotta spend Friday night sitting in bed, eating ice cream and watching New Girl.    
    
    
    But judging by split on TL, a tag/no tag debate not much different than a double play with the fielder a foot away off 2nd base.    
    
    
    Todd Blackledge is really taking the spirit of the targeting rule into consideration when he says the OU kid should get the boot. [/sarcasm]    
    
    
    I missed a FAT GUY TOUCHDOWN because of Jehovah's witnesses at my door. I am NOT happy about that.    
    
    
    Washington's stadium was pretty loud when it was half-full against Arizona in the worst weather ever. I bet that'll be fun for Oregon today.    
    
    
    I really hope someone makes a GIF of the face-painted Texas fan screaming "Fuck you, Sooners, fuck you!"    
    
    
    I really like watching Washington play football.    
    
    
    I think he's down but don't think it can get overturned. Two huge Oregon mistakes so far.    
    
    
    No matter what they called on the field it was standing. Not a conspiracy theorist but it sure seemed like someone wanted Oregon to score.    
    
    
    Awesome. FS1 is doing the commercial - kickoff - commercial that has ruined America.    
    
    
    What's that big bright thing in the sky in Seattle? I spent four days there and didn't see it once.    
    
    
    It's impossible for a quarterback to be successful or taken seriously when he's wearing No. 98.    
    
    
    I like having Pac-12 Network but Cox's abysmal service means I might not have it long.    
    
    
    I'm curious to see how many votes Clemson is going to gain on Ohio State this week.    
    
    
    I'm confused about why @WildcatHoops' cover picture (or whatever you wanna call it) is a non-UA player.    
    
    
    I'm confused about why @WildcatHoops' cover picture (or whatever you wanna call it) is a non-UA player.    
    
    
    After that playcalling, there's about a 0 percent chance the Michigan kid makes this field goal.    
    
    
    BRADY HOKE FOR PRESIDENT    
    
    
    How in the world does a 1-0 baseball game with 10 combined hits take almost four hours? That's not helping the sport's popularity.    
    
    
    There you go Ole Miss, take 10 seconds off the clock and let the Heisman Trophy winner win the game. Brilliant.    
    
    
    Not sure why but I just don't buy UCLA as an elite team. Think there are three Pac-12 North teams better than them.    
    
    
    Run on the first two downs to get to 3rd-and-1, then go empty and throw an incompletion. Is Ken Whisenhunt back with the Cardinals?    
    
    
    OK, the Carson Palmer experience is over. That's four inexcusable throws in three possessions.    
    
    
    Wow. I was wrong. Carson Palmer isn't an upgrade over the dumpster fire they had at QB last year.    
    
    
    At least the Cardinals' quarterbacks last year just hurt the offense. Now Palmer's putting the defense in terrible spots too.    
    
    
    Carson Palmer might be playing one of the worst games in NFL history    
    
    
    Two picks, a delay of game and standing in the end zone for five seconds before getting sacked for a safety. Quality stuff.    
    
    
    That's not interference. Corners don't get to slow down and make receivers slow down right behind them.    
    
    
    I'm glad the Cardinals feel the need to run sweep/reverse/passes to a cornerback to pick up two freaking yards.    
    
    
    Also way too early to go for two. Almost a guarantee that will bite the Cardinals at some point.    
    
    
    So the 49ers get two personal fouls to the Cardinals' one, and they all offset?    
    
    
    Sure is a good thing the Cardinals went for two early in the third quarter.    
    
    
    It never seemed smart at any point. MT @danbickley: Arians' decision to go for 2 in the third quarter doesn't seem so smart right about now    
    
    
    Cardinals should be 5-1 and tied for first. Instead 3-3 and tied for last. It all comes down to little things.    
    
    
    Just had the same woman cut me off for a parking spot then not hold the door twice. Good morning to you, too.    
    
    
    @Forbes: #AZCardinals receiver Larry Fitzgerald (@LarryFitzgerald) is the NFL's most-liked player - http://bit.ly/19NgxhK     
    
    
    Oregon's three toughest games: UCLA, Washington, Stanford. UCLA and UW play Stanford week before playing Ducks. #helpfulscheduling    
    
    
    Was wondering why I hadn't heard anything about Jordin Mayes after the Red/Blue game. Just looked at the box score. Now it makes sense.    
    
    
    A pair of #ArizonaWildcats freshmen stood out in Saturday's Red-Blue Game - http://bit.ly/19HZMmk     
    
    
    Nuts. MT @GregDillard: Zbynek and Milan Michalek will play each other tomorrow night for the 36th time. They're 17-17-1 #Coyotes    
    
    
    #AZCardinals lineman Calais Campbell (@Campbell93) is "hopeful" for Thursday's game after a scary injury Sunday - http://bit.ly/GVz7bi     
    
    
    Bj Denker on stage 'we obviously made a lot of progress' against USC... Do you buy it, or was it just cosmetic in 2nd half    
    
    
    Just found out that my two mentors at the Courier, where i interned last summer, were laid off. So sad to hear, and so undeserving.    
    
    
    The #AZCardinals' short week forces them to use a different method of preparation for the Seattle #Seahawks - http://bit.ly/GVBDhI     
    
    
    I wonder what the thought process is behind pimping your first hit of a seven game series when you're down 0-2.    
    
    
    I'm amazed that ASU fans are ripping the punt flag when their coach wears that headset and wristband.    
    
    
    Writers can use racism to argue idiotic points or use anti-racism to look too deeply into something. Sometimes it's just about SPORTS    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats RichRod on weekly PHX radio appearance: "We don't even try to win the day like Oregon ... we talk about winning the play."    
    
    
    More #ArizonaWildcats RichRod on @AZSports620: Denker anticipated coverage windows at USC, threw guys open. Gave BJ/staff more confidence.    
    
    
    UA's RichRod: Utah's size and experience present a major challenge for the #ArizonaWildcats Saturday - http://bit.ly/1fAOpkb     
    
    
    #ASU's Will Sutton -- averaging 3 tackles per game with 2.5 total tackles for loss, 1 sack -- is on USA Today's midseason All-American team.    
    
    
    Here's a fun exercise: Go to the Pac-12 football stats page, Ctrl+F "Sutton," and see how many hits you get. (Hint: it's 0)    
    
    
    Ugh. That was a great pitching plan from Tazawa. God that was ugly.    
    
    
    #ASU's Todd Graham today: "We were ready for that schedule. Should have been 4-1." I think there's a strong argument for 2-3, too.    
    
    
    So the Cardinals paid the Steelers $2.8 million to take Levi Brown, and they're not even getting something in return.    
    
    
    It's like Robin Sparkles. RT @KTAR923: The newest viral video is like Rebecca Black's "Friday," but worse (VIDEO) - http://bit.ly/1cqG3Im     
    
    
    @nicoledimtsios Are they the Arizona Coyotes yet?    
    
    
    The first two episodes of the Walking Dead are really making me wonder why it's so popular.    
    
    
    Isn't that the point? MT @dailywildcat: voter ID laws just constrict accessibility, easiness for individuals to vote. http://ow.ly/pTIpe     
    
    
    Part of the reason I didn't go tonight was I didn't want to deal with Seattle's weird-ass fans. Please don't show them after every play.    
    
    
    Carson Palmer made two bad plays, an opponent's tight end made a big gain and the Cardinals missed tackles. All is right in the world.    
    
    
    The Cardinals failed to convert on third down and Javier Arenas made another god-awful decision on a kickoff. It's like why do I even watch?    
    
    
    O-line issues and a Carson Palmer interception. Couldn't we have just saved everyone the trouble of playing a stupid Thursday game?    
    
    
    Hey, look at the Cardinala getting embarrassed in a national TV game. That never happens    
    
    
    The Cardinals bouncing back after an embarrassing start is ACTUALLY something new. Good to see.    
    
    
    The Cardinals even get screwed when they get a holding call.    
    
    
    That punt where Peterson got hurt has got to be a penalty. How is blocking someone into a returner any less dangerous than hitting him?    
    
    
    That's 10 points the Seahawks have gotten through luck    
    
    
    The Cardinals have a bunch of good pieces on defense. The problem is that they'll all be past their prime once the offense is anywhere close    
    
    
    I don't want to put this game on Palmer, but then he goes and misses a throw like that.    
    
    
    #AZCardinals coach Bruce Arians says (again) that the interceptions aren't Carson Palmer's fault: http://bit.ly/177dPnd     
    
    
    #AZCardinals RB Andre Ellington had a couple gems today. 
Q: How did Seattle slow down Cards' O
A: They did some stuff to slow us down.    
    
    
    More #AZCardinals Ellington: 

Q: Surprised you only got 3 carries?
A: Just kept giving it to Mendenhall (Avg. 1.6 YPC). He had the hot hand    
    
    
    Slightly obsessed with black nail polish.    
    
    
    The Cardinals are so good. So experienced. I don't see anybody beating them.    
    
    
    ESPN's Brock Huard says #ASU's game against Washington tomorrow is "huge for both programs." - http://bit.ly/16lOQGF     
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: Coyotes lose 2nd straight late lead, fall to Ducks in shootout - http://bit.ly/1aYjpVu     
    
    
    Whenever I can't find something to watch on Netflix I just watch Scrubs and I never regret it.    
    
    
    I would say this is another banner day for the SEC, but Tennessee and Vandy will just jump to 11 and 15 if they win.    
    
    
    The two people who I'm in line behind at Subway are getting a combined 12 sandwiches. So much for thinking this would be fast.    
    
    
    That catch was unreal.    
    
    
    Ohio State clearly had a lot of respect for Iowa's passing attack coming into this game.    
    
    
    And Bradley Roby has cost himself so much money this year    
    
    
    I can't wait to hear Ohio State get ripped for Northwestern's loss while no one says anything about Georgia's affecting Clemson.    
    
    
    Yeah, don't let a corner hit a tight end in the chest. This fucking targeting rule has got to go.    
    
    
    Its fantastic that Ohio State can't stop an offense that's stuck in 1960.    
    
    
    Ohio State is playing like a very bad football team and it's going to lose because of that.    
    
    
    Yahoo! writes a story about Roby tweeting during the game, and commenters call him a thug and gangster. Keep it real, internet people.    
    
    
    Ohio State responded after halftime in a way I didn't think it was capable of doing. Great to see.    
    
    
    So, what do you think? Are the #ArizonaWildcats in a must-win 3-game stretch playing Utah, Colorado and Cal the next 3 weeks?    
    
    
    Bradley Roby gets ejected and this Auburn guy doesn't even get a flag. Way to be consistent, NCAA refs.    
    
    
    I was eigher WAY too high on Washington or they completely packed it in after the Oregon and Stanford losses.    
    
    
    It says a lot about the #ArizonaWildcats that the thing their fans bitch about most is the ZonaZoo. Talk about small-time.    
    
    
    The #ArizonaWildcats are tied at 7 with Utah in the first quarter in Tucson. Keep up with the action here - http://bit.ly/1gu67r6     
    
    
    *Drops mic* RT @TheCoolSub: That was a gift to Flowers. Which is weird cuz Flowers usually ARE the gift!    
    
    
    @nicoledimtsios If they do that twice and convert 1-for-2 then they get 1 more point #math    
    
    
    @ZachEClark Didn't Tennessee win that game?    
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: #Coyotes score five unanswered, including Smith's empty-netter, to top Red Wings 5-2 - http://bit.ly/19UK9Ge     
    
    
    Why do refs explain why grounding was NOT called? Seems akin to something like "there's no penalty for holding because no one was held."    
    
    
    I can't remember the last time Arizona had a kicker or punt returner. I don't get how a program can consistently lack the same thing.    
    
    
    Big-time downfield throw from BJ Denker. Imagine an Arizona offense with Austin Hill if that throw is consistently there.    
    
    
    I hate everything about going for 2 here.    
    
    
    I said this earlier today, but I'm really starting to think the #ArizonaWildcats win the next 3 games then at least compete with UCLA.    
    
    
    Looked like a bad call. Somebody on TV confirm?    
    
    
    #Pac12 refs gonna be Pac-12 refs.    
    
    
    Also, Trevor Ermisch is playing the game of his life on STs. Two big hits and a fumble recovery.    
    
    
    I remember when he was like 5-foot-2, 110 pounds as a high school sophomore. Talk about a growth spurt.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats Ka'Deem Carey breaks a 44-yard run on 3rd-and-5 to put Arizona ahead of Utah, 35-24, with 1:30 to play in Tucson.    
    
    
    40 CARRIES FOR 236 YARDS. It's like Ka'Deem Carey thinks he's Javon Ringer or something.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats top Utah, 35-24, behind Ka'Deem Carey's 236 rushing yards and school-record 40 carries - http://bit.ly/1gu67r7     
    
    
    Cat Tracks: Carey leads #ArizonaWildcats to much-needed #Pac12 win - http://bit.ly/1gumHag     
    
    
    #ASU quarterback Taylor Kelly: "It's pick your poison with us." Sun Devils display versatility in Washington rout - http://bit.ly/1c7IH94     
    
    
    Since Arizona took their first timeout, they are on a 9-4 run. Lead USC 21-18 in the second set. Snuka assist count: 34. (Season-high is 48)    
    
    
    Wow. Can't even punt without shooting themselves in the foot this quarter.    
    
    
    Mike Riley ordered victory In-n-Out before Oregon State actually won. That's awesome. http://bit.ly/19XksVJ     
    
    
    Day after #ASU holds Sankey to 22 yards and forces <50% completion rate, guy says "defense needs work." Never change, Internet commenters.    
    
    
    When players in the sports say they added weight and didn't lose quickness/agility, do they actually have evidence of the latter?    
    
    
    When players in the sports say they added weight and didn't lose quickness/agility, do they actually have evidence of the latter?    
    
    
    When players in the sports say they added weight and didn't lose quickness/agility, do they actually have evidence of the latter?    
    
    
    When players in the sports say they added weight and didn't lose quickness/agility, do they actually have evidence of the latter?    
    
    
    I think it is apparent by the first BCS standings that Ohio State doesn't control its own destiny. Needs a lot of help, even if unbeaten.    
    
    
    I think it is apparent by the first BCS standings that Ohio State doesn't control its own destiny. Needs a lot of help, even if unbeaten.    
    
    
    I'm confused by hockey fans' insistence to give players nicknames that are longer than their actual names.    
    
    
    A good way to avoid that penalty? Don't chest-bump the quarterback four seconds after the ball is out.    
    
    
    Chip leader at the Fort on break. Five from the money #lfg pic.twitter.com/i0z6zhaaIt    
    
    
    Knocked out the second chip leader on the first hand back. Building heaps! pic.twitter.com/pNWHg8bCQg    
    
    
    I love playing for six hours, going out fourth, and making $60 fucking dollars. Totally worth it.    
    
    
    Especially after having more than a quarter of the chips in play 11-handed. I'm mad. HULK SMASH.    
    
    
    @dailywildcat wrong link?    
    
    
    I think the Cardinals should trade Fitz. But from an org. standpoint, do long-term positives outweigh short-term negatives?    
    
    
    I wish the Diamondbacks scouted wherever the Cardinals found five guys throwing 100 that know when to go in.    
    
    
    Almost every day, Cox. pic.twitter.com/HaVB2Lm6eR    
    
    
    6-5 starters and relievers throwing 100. If anybody has pitching figured out, it's the Cardinals.    
    
    
    How could Deacalso take that, asks Tim McCarver. IT WAS A FOOT INSIDE, TIM, THAT'S HOW.    
    
    
    Anytime I see Staples Center, I remember how awesome the last Pac-12 Tourney trip there was w/ @offensivelyfoul @Mike_Schmitz #gbabybates    
    
    
    There's no easier way for a bar to win me over than for its website to say "breakfast during football season only."    
    
    
    AP photogs know that you're allowed to take horizontal pictures during an NBA game, right?    
    
    
    Horizon fakes a punt on 4th and 15. Run the ball, don't get back to line of scrimmage. Pinnacle ball with eight seconds left.    
    
    
    Horizon fakes a punt on 4th and 15. Run the ball, don't get back to line of scrimmage. Pinnacle ball with eight seconds left.    
    
    
    Tonight's internet commenter special: Pedroia is a clown. I know because my brother was at ASU at the same time but didn't know him.    
    
    
    It's only 8:30 and I've already seen someone say the D-backs should trade Skaggs and Gregorius for Kole Calhoun.    
    
    
    Oregon's duck is awesome. And obvious sign is obvious and funny. - http://bit.ly/1amWKCi     
    
    
    @GregDillard What's up with the 'Yotes start time today? Just trying to find a way to compete with CFB and World Series?    
    
    
    Don't touch my phone for an hour and it drops 20 percent battery. Keep it real, Samsung.    
    
    
    The #Suns announced today that they've exercised their options on the Morris twins and Miles Plumlee - http://bit.ly/1c7AUEg     
    
    
    Opponents a combined 15-28. MT @SportsCenter: Since beating Texas A&M 49-42 Sept. 6, Alabama has outscored  opponents 236-16    
    
    
    Channing Frye: Tanking "is bullshit." #Suns    
    
    
    'Cats! (at @ArcadiaTavern) http://4sq.com/1bqxjjw     
    
    
    This game is all Arizona ever needs from BJ Denker.    
    
    
    Just be a threat to get the ball outside and Arizona will be fine offensively    
    
    
    Sometimes you spend $50 on nachos and Miller Light #oops    
    
    
    I'm legitimately excited to see the Twitter reaction from people in Arizona when this Cowboys game gets switched to the Cardinals.    
    
    
    I LOVE WAITING TWO HOURS FOR OUR FOOD TO BE DELIVERED    
    
    
    #Dbacks first baseman Paul Goldschmidt has won the 2013 Hank Aaron Award, @MLB announced Sunday - http://bit.ly/1aiIGO7     
    
    
    The #AZCardinals defense solved its tight end woes in Sunday's 27-13 win over Atlanta - http://bit.ly/1g5LjVM     
    
    
    #AZCardinals running back Andre Ellington had a breakout game in his 1st NFL start  - http://bit.ly/1g5NF79     
    
    
    Wasn't it at like 10 a.m. last year? RT @ryan_finley: :) RT @DSBerk: Nothing says homecoming like an 8 p.m. kick time.    
    
    
    How often do you see a guy make a great play in one inning, then fly out to the wall in the next?    
    
    
    Then how do you know? MT @WildcatHoops: 30 minutes till opening tip-off. But you wouldn't know that if you were at McKale.    
    
    
    Played at the Fort tonight. More than doubled up on the first hand of the tournament. I'm the second person out. #rungood    
    
    
    Just started the #ArizonaWildcats exhibition...a lot of Pac-12 fan bases are going to REALLY dislike TJ McConnell in a couple months.    
    
    
    Sometimes I really love Arizona. pic.twitter.com/QZkklnahHw    
    
    
    Super slow greens at Aguila for the #AZHS D2 golf championships. Girls hits a chip and yells at it to slow down. It does...15 feet short.    
    
    
    Tucson Salpointe entered the final day 8 strokes behind Scottsdale Notre Dame. Took the Lancers just 4 holes to grab a 4-stroke lead. #azhs    
    
    
    Barring some kind of implosion,  Sahuaro is going to win its first girls golf state title. Started the day in third, 9 shots back.    
    
    
    In the snack shop writing and an older guy comes in and closes a tab that's been running for three days. Someone's living the dream.    
    
    
    Yotes! (@ http://Jobing.com  Arena - @jobingarena for @LAKings vs @phoenixcoyotes w/ 53 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/HrlukS     
    
    
    What makes people think they get to stop traffic just because they don't know which lane they should be in?    
    
    
    Stephen Drew is hitting home runs and making errors WHAT IS HAPPENING    
    
    
    Need an #NBA refresher course? Arizona Sports' 2012-13 predictions have you covered - http://bit.ly/19TTL5i     
    
    
    The #Suns' revamped frontcourt impressed in Phoenix's season opening win - http://bit.ly/17YH5XV     
    
    
    If there is no foul for running into the kicker, WHY THE HELL DID SOMEONE ON YOUR CREW THROW A FLAG FOR RUNNING INTO THE KICKER?!    
    
    
    The Coyotes are what the #Dbacks wanted to be with the whole "grit" mantra.    
    
    
    I'm amazed that Grant Jerrett got drafted and traded without ever actually signing a contract. How is that possible?    
    
    
    Something I learned today: A lot of people don't understand what restricted free agent means.    
    
    
    I'm surprised Glen Mason made it this far in life without someone telling him that it's Ohio State, not Hia State.    
    
    
    I miss Ralphie.    
    
    
    Jake Plummer says Ka'Deem Carey will get more yards this week because he was suspended against NAU. Because that makes sense.    
    
    
    Now he says that Arizona's offense will eat up clock to keep Cal's offense off the field. Does he watch football?    
    
    
    Now @Pac12Networks PBP guy says #ArizonaWildcats have 3 straight road wins. Try one. Amateur hour every hour.    
    
    
    If I'm Arizona, I'm all for 3rd and 10 over 2nd and 20.    
    
    
    Or maybe I'm just underestimating how terrible Cal is.    
    
    
    Great awareness, interfering on an 8-yard pass on 3rd and 20.    
    
    
    People like to point to speed & explosiveness to measure athleticism. Ka'Deem Carey is an unreal athlete. Great balance and body control.    
    
    
    How is unnecessary contact above the shoulders not targeting?    
    
    
    How is unnecessary contact above the shoulders not targeting?    
    
    
    BJ Denker is trying to get a receiver killed today.    
    
    
    What a god awful holding call.    
    
    
    Haha Pac-12 refs.    
    
    
    Oh my God did that really just happen?    
    
    
    Arizona's return game has actually been very good today. That's rare.    
    
    
    Arizona didn't really just run a reverse on 3rd-and-3, did it?    
    
    
    19-7 is such a playing-at-Cal score.    
    
    
    Does anyone know why Arizona seems to get away from the read-option near the goal line?    
    
    
    My god, Pac-12 Networks must really be struggling to sell ads. Seems like they have the same house ads on repeat    
    
    
        
    
    
    Arizona's defense does some really dumbass things sometimes.    
    
    
    Three Cal touchdowns, and two of them were on drives aided by a really, really stupid penalty by the #ArizonaWildcats defense.    
    
    
    Devin Gardner just made one of the biggest chicken-shit plays I've ever seen in football.    
    
    
    I guess blatant pick plays don't get called in the Pac-12 now.    
    
    
    Devin Gardner just made one of the biggest chicken-shit plays I've ever seen in football.    
    
    
    Watching Ohio State's offense against Michigan State will be fun. Watching it against Michigan will be fun too, but for different reasons.    
    
    
        
    
    
    If the #ArizonaWildcats can hold on, they can't ask for any more momentum heading into a big showdown against No. 17 #UCLA next week.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats need a first down or we're looking at Cal ball with about 50 seconds and a chance to win.    
    
    
    I think not kicking it deep was a mistake. Now even if Cal gets the stop, a touchdown almost impossible with field position.    
    
    
    Glen Parker is wrong. Winning league games on the road is tough, especially with a big game looming next week. No reason for concern.    
    
    
    What the hell team did this guy research that has won three straight road games? Because that's the second time he's said it.    
    
    
    If you replace "beach" with "betch" in Corona commercials, they make so much more sense.    
    
    
    This game is as much about Miami not being very good as it is Florida State being good. About the equilavent of MSU beating Michigan today.    
    
    
    If you want to sell UO and Bama as a level above everyone else, fine. But I don't buy for a second that FSU is discernably better than OSU.    
    
    
    Beating a Clemson team that's going full Clemson and a vastly overrated Miami team just doesn't do it for me.    
    
    
    ASU has blown out CU, a drained UW team and WSU, but say #ArizonaWildcats fans are too confident from beating bad teams. Right right right.    
    
    
    ASU is ranked one spot ahead of Notre Dame in both polls, because that makes sense.    
    
    
    Is it just me or does the #Suns broadcast have really bad timing with the whole returning-from-commercials thing?    
    
    
    #Suns Strokes: Phoenix runs out of gas in bid for third-straight win to open season - http://bit.ly/1706P5T     
    
    
    I will someday make a final table and not run like absolute shit there, right?    
    
    
    It's borderline hilarious that ASU fans are worried about Todd Graham -- he of the 14-7 record at ASU and 63-36 overall -- going to Texas.    
    
    
    Ohhhhhhhh!!!! Straight!!! Let's keep it going!    
    
    
    Finally getting around to watching WSOP heads-up. Can't believe crowds aren't kept under better control.    
    
    
    Just got it in on a J56 flop with JJ against 55. Care to guess who won that one?    
    
    
    Guy floats a flop with four high and goes runner-runner flush. I must have missed that day of poker school.    
    
    
    The #DBacks added to their collection of defensive awards today - http://bit.ly/1aIaU4X     
    
    
    #ASU hoops coach Herb Sendek: "Who are we?" - http://bit.ly/1iQwUd9     
    
    
    So Terrelle Pryor & Co. get suspended for 42% of season, while Artis & Carter get 27% for same thing. You go, NCAA.    
    
    
    On that 3rd-and-short, almost every Stanford offensive lineman snapped his head back at some point pre-snap. How is that legal?    
    
    
    A pair of #AZCardinals cracked ESPN's rookie rankings this week - http://bit.ly/1dR6MhK     
    
    
    Ha, that should be fun for the Alma mater. RT @ctownrivals: Hamilton will face Sandra Day O'Connor on Saturday, Horizon will play Xavier.    
    
    
    I can't wait to hear people say that a team that lost to Utah and struggled with Army should jump Ohio State.    
    
    
    Tomorrow I will reach the age where I could have a kid & it wouldn't be weird anymore....fug.    
    
    
    @JackBridge45 They're rewarding me in the Oregon game!!    
    
    
    @JackBridge45 They're rewarding me in the Oregon game!!    
    
    
    @JackBridge45 They're rewarding me in the Oregon game!!    
    
    
    Oh no, Stanford.    
    
    
    Haha at the Oregon guy who walked away clapping after that tackle on second down. Way to know the situation.    
    
    
    Wooooo homecoming 13 woooo (@ Gentle Ben's Brewing Co.) http://4sq.com/1erFf9r     
    
    
    Baxter, you don't speak spanish!    
    
    
    Let's go Cats! http://instagram.com/p/gezcmHHgc_/     
    
    
    My people! (@ The Hut) http://4sq.com/1hUJKJq     
    
    
    The best game on TV is a 14-point Minnesota-Penn State game. It's November, THIS SHOULDN'T BE HAPPENING!    
    
    
    Utah and ASU might be 1-2. RT @ZackBlatt: Utah's got to be the most schizophrenic team in the Pac-12, right?    
    
    
    Tyler Wilson is absolutely terrible. How in the world is someone that bad voted a captain?    
    
    
    Line at Bags two hours before kick where am I?    
    
    
    Bearing the fuck down. http://instagram.com/p/ghL8X_ngZI/     
    
    
    B.J. Denkernick now gets the ball back with 6:15 left and a chance to put Arizona ahead. Having a sneaky good game.    
    
    
    There are certain things in sports that should be a penalty/foul on principal. That third down play was one of them.    
    
    
    Wooooo homecoming '13! (@ No Anchovies) http://4sq.com/1ez2bni     
    
    
    Why in the world would anybody not go to U of A?    
    
    
    It's fucking November and I'm sitting outside in shorts drinking beer. I love this place.    
    
    
    So homecoming went pretty well. pic.twitter.com/HyX9aHVTRX    
    
    
    Good to know that whistles are meaningless in football now.    
    
    
    Tonight in things my neighbors are listening to: an instrumental version of Celine Dion's "My Heart Will Go On."    
    
    
    It's like Ted doesn't know who he's talking to when Walter White says he'll make his life miserable.    
    
    
    Outside of being 7 feet tall, what does Tarczewski bring to the table as a basketball player?    
    
    
    "But that doesn’t count. What counts is when you play a team in their own arena."    
    
    
    I'm far from a hockey expert, but it seems like the #Coyotes are worse than pretty much everyone the play yet keep finding ways to win.    
    
    
    I'm far from a hockey expert, but it seems like the #Coyotes are worse than pretty much everyone the play yet keep finding ways to win.    
    
    
    I'm far from a hockey expert, but it seems like the #Coyotes are worse than pretty much everyone the play yet keep finding ways to win.    
    
    
    I'm far from a hockey expert, but it seems like the #Coyotes are worse than pretty much everyone the play yet keep finding ways to win.    
    
    
    Not a single 1st-place vote. MT @AZSports620: #Dbacks 1B Goldschmidt finishes 2nd to McCutchen in NL MVP voting. http://bit.ly/1gPkLsc     
    
    
    Safe to say that McCutchen winning was a foregone conclusion. But people voting Craig Kimbrel and Matt Carpenter ahead of Goldy...really?    
    
    
    Rick Hummel, who writes for the STL Post-Dispatch, had three Cardinals on his ballot. Voted Goldschmidt 6, Russell Martin 10.    
    
    
    Does anyone know of a cost-free, internet-based way to watch the #ArizonaWildcats tonight?    
    
    
    Does anyone know of a cost-free, internet-based way to watch the #ArizonaWildcats tonight?    
    
    
    Does anyone know of a cost-free, internet-based way to watch the #ArizonaWildcats tonight?    
    
    
    Character Counts: #Marlins give star rookie the best surprise of his career - http://bit.ly/1cudxnU     
    
    
    In the history of organized basketball, has driving baseline ever ended well for the offensive team?    
    
    
    'Yotes Notes: #Coyotes fall to Blackhawks in shootout - http://bit.ly/1brWPnd     
    
    
    This game is just like the #ASU football game last year for me, which ended up with the UA at the 10-yard line about to go up 3 scores in 4Q    
    
    
    And by that I mean I'm just going to block out all the bad.    
    
    
    If this isn't a mirror image of the Florida game last year, I don't know what is.    
    
    
    If anyone's still trying to figure out the whole Twitter thing, look at @LaMetABC15's timeline and never do that.    
    
    
    'Cat Tracks: #ArizonaWildcats pass first road test of the season against San Diego State - http://bit.ly/1dwzEuW     
    
    
    The first photo in this gallery isn't nasty at all...#ArizonaWildcats - http://bit.ly/1dwBdsJ     
    
    
    I know the sports night has taken a turn for the worst when I look up and Boise State-New Mexico State women's hoops is on the TV.    
    
    
    The first photo in this gallery isn't nasty at all...#ArizonaWildcats - http://bit.ly/1dwBdsJ     
    
    
    Haboob: Cincinnati's dressing room was dirty, so the Bearcats' coaches ran some gassers - http://bit.ly/1dwFk8g     
    
    
    I feel like going into an office building on Friday between 4 and 5 is close to what firefighters experience going into a burning building.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats fans ... would you rather have Aaron Gordon right now, or a sophomore Derrick Williams?    
    
    
    Michigan State losing to Columbia with 11 minutes left ... could we be watching the No. 2 #ArizonaWildcats the next time they play?    
    
    
    Paul Pierce: "How do you not fucking call that?"    
    
    
    Paul Pierce: "How do you not fucking call that?"    
    
    
    Character Counts: #SFGiants mascot Lou Seal saved by Batkid - http://bit.ly/1fIlCYy     
    
    
    I swear, whenever I write on deadline I get an intense craving for fast food.    
    
    
    Just had a staredown with a coyote in the @AZSports620 parking lot. That was unexpected.    
    
    
    U of A, not ASU. It's really not difficult. MT @chadfordinsider Don’t forget about another super-freshman: ASU’s Aaron Gordon.    
    
    
    Why in the world is Ron Burgandy not Gameday's guest picker?    
    
    
    Washington State just ran the most blatant pick play I've ever seen and it didn't get called.    
    
    
    I don't know who this P12N color guy is, but he couldn't sound more bored and unenthusiastic. Can make out about 1/3 of what he says.    
    
    
    What exactly is surprising about a small crowd for a team that's 3-3 in conference playing the Pac-12's worst program at noon?    
    
    
    As fun to watch as Good Braxton Miller is, Bad Braxton Miller is equally as infuriating.    
    
    
    Shaq didn't make any more contact before the ball got there than WSU's blocking receivers make on almost every play.    
    
    
    Nothing good has ever come from Ohio State playing at Illinois.    
    
    
    I bet House Hunters is really hitting its target demographic by advertising on @Pac12Networks.    
    
    
    "I know OSU is playing without its starting safety, 2 starting linebackers and best D-lineman, but I have concerns on D." Great insight.    
    
    
    Maybe Terrence Miller wants a better throw next time.    
    
    
    "Arizona State will have to kick..." Seriously @Pac12Networks? Your PBP guy doesn't know what game he's calling?    
    
    
    The combination of D-level announcers and D-level football is making this #ArizonaWildcats game almost unwatchable.    
    
    
    Dodge, duck, dip, dive, Denker.    
    
    
    .@theAdamGreen remember the other day when you were saying college kickers seem better?    
    
    
    Who is going to win the #ArizonaWildcats game? Everyone, because it will be over.    
    
    
    That's one of the worst sequences I've ever seen a quarterback have.    
    
    
    I wonder what it would look like if your typical college student's biggest mistake was broadcast to thousands of people on the internet.    
    
    
    Ohio State just won a road game by four scores and scored 60 points, and I'm getting phone notifications asking if that will hurt it. WHAT?    
    
    
    Aaron Murray might be down but there should be riots in Athens if this gets overturned.    
    
    
    hahahaha!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    If Georgia doesn't take the lead here I'll feel wronged by how this game ends.    
    
    
    I really hope USC goes to the Rose Bowl. That would be so awesome.    
    
    
    WSU fans who think @MeganCoghlan reflects poorly on the UA should look at her @ mentions and think about how those people reflect on WSU.    
    
    
    When's the last time the #ArizonaWildcats played well on offense? Colorado? The #ASU game looks like it's going to be miserable.    
    
    
    I guess this answers the question of "how can a great team lose to Utah?" Cardinal good, but not great.    
    
    
    College football is a better place when Lane Kiffin isn't in charge of one of its marquee programs.    
    
    
    Is it just me, or does #ASU -- at least to some degree -- have the ability to flip a switch mid-game and get points/a stop when it needs it?    
    
    
    ASU at UCLA next week. How long has it been since the Devils played this meaningful a game this late in the season? (Not a rhetorical Q)    
    
    
    Updated: #AmberAlert issued for two missing Buckeye girls - http://bit.ly/1aycTGl     
    
    
    I live for driving with the windows down and heat on.    
    
    
    That was a pretty cool magic trick by Patrick Peterson to end up with the football.    
    
    
    This is one of my favorites from @ghansen711, and he couldn't be more spot-on. #ArizonaWildcats http://azstarnet.com/sports/columnists/hansen/greg-hansen-soft-cats-regress-as-spirit-fans-disappear/article_f72f36d9-5322-5895-a45e-0fe9a7e8259c.html …    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat sports editor who wrote the controversial WSU column responds. RT @MeganCoghlan http://bit.ly/1bxArc7  #enoughisenough    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    The @dailywildcat says they have no plans to remove the sports editor responsible for dragging the DW's name through the mud. #Yikes    
    
    
    With 5-star hair. RT @territorialcup: A lot of folks forget Jacob Hazard was a three-star recruit.    
    
    
    Mark May just picked Michigan State over Ohio State. I'm absolutely shocked.    
    
    
    It's disgusting that someone using this logic can play a huge role in the CFB championship race - http://on.nfl.com/186KNEW     
    
    
    Bowl Watch: Where do national prognosticators have #ASU and the #ArizonaWildcats ending up this postseason? - http://bit.ly/IfnWKt     
    
    
    Kevin Durant walks into the building in Stillwater. Guy can't get enough basketball.    
    
    
    Kevin Durant walks into the building in Stillwater. Guy can't get enough basketball.    
    
    
    It's like NY or LA? Can't go wrong. RT @offensivelyfoul: @AlexHWilliams @Mike_Schmitz so the question is: las cruces or stillwater?    
    
    
    Kevin Durant walks into the building in Stillwater. Guy can't get enough basketball.    
    
    
    #UCLA's backfield will present a unique challenge for the #ASU defense on Saturday - http://bit.ly/1ffhgL9     
    
    
    Obviously still super early, but could the #Suns be a playoff team this year?    
    
    
    Desperation cries from #ASU fans watching this basketball game might be my favorite thing about tonight.    
    
    
    Sure, Carson is going off, but two #ASU starters haven't scored on a combined 12 FGA. That's not very good.    
    
    
    #ASU fan complains about how bad Bachynski is defensively then gets mad at Carson for not taking a shot quick enough. High Expectations.    
    
    
    What a game for Carson, but #ASU needed 40 from him to squeak by a UNLV team that lost to Cal-Santa Barbara by 21 at home. Not a good sign.    
    
    
    Now ASU fan is amazed that 13 NBA scouts were at that game. This basketball thing must be like a brave new world.    
    
    
    I take back what I asked earlier about the Suns and the playoffs.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats top Rhode Island 87-59 behind Johnson's double-double, advance to NIT semifinals in New York - http://bit.ly/17L951s     
    
    
    #Suns Strokes: Phoenix squanders chances down stretch, fall 107-104 at Kings - http://bit.ly/1bCdhSb     
    
    
    .@GottliebShow on #ArizonaWildcats AG: "If you're going to be a 6-foot-8 3, it's OK to post. I just wish he would work on his post game."    
    
    
    When traffic gets in the way of me picking up my Mama's Hawaiian BBQ takeout, I get very angry.    
    
    
    Got heeem RT @ZackBlatt: Uh oh, I might've just become the face of the fans storming the field against Oregon fiasco, thanks to @ZachEClark.    
    
    
    The #Coyotes are becoming a "model of how to run a franchise," according to ESPN's @NHLBarryMelrose - http://bit.ly/Ij7JUC     
    
    
    Also don't=find in that 2nd tweet. Wishful thinking that I could get through a rant w/o any typos... 😑    
    
    
    #FYeahNature http://bit.ly/Ij9AZC     
    
    
    Sit down at a 2-3 table and lose two pots with aces in five minutes. That was fun.    
    
    
    If any of you have called a 3bet shove getting worse than 3:1 with KJo, can you please explain why?    
    
    
    If any of you have called a 3bet shove getting worse than 3:1 with KJo, can you please explain why?    
    
    
    So how ironic is it that I put a case back on my phone today and then the screen shattered later?    
    
    
    So 'A' Mountain has been attacked from the South AND the West this week...    
    
    
    Cortez Johnson just got absolutely dismissed on a double move...so he clearly would have fit in well with the #ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    Zona Zoo, hour until game time. If people show, probably won't be until right at kickoff. Big "if", though. pic.twitter.com/38Pgm5iYrR    
    
    
    Something worth watching today: B.J. Denker's grip on the football. Not very big hands + rain = bad combo.    
    
    
    Arizona has played three games in downpours this year...that's gotta be rare.    
    
    
    Ka'Deem Carey, meet America. America, Ka'Deem.    
    
    
    Looks like RT Mickey Baucus shaken up on the TD. Trainers looking at him.    
    
    
    Wow, BJ Denker. I didn't think he had any of these throws in him.    
    
    
    That Mariota lateral was thrown at the Oregon 49 and caught at the 50...would have been overturned if reviewed.  #ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    Taylor Denker with the pooch kick out of Todd Graham's playbook.    
    
    
    Oregon is starting to get real chippy...#ArizonaWildcats need to handle that well in a close game.    
    
    
    DODGE, DUCK, DIP, DIVE, DENKER.#ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    How does Oregon get away with a false start on like 95 percent of its offensive plays?    
    
    
    The #ArizonaWildcats are going to win this game and it's absolutely unbelievable.    
    
    
    BJ Denker: 19/21 for 177 yards and two touchdowns. Good way to beat a top-5 team. #ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    UA has a chance to win this game.    
    
    
    Every play here that Oregon doesn't score is a huge win for the #ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    45,000 #ArizonaWildcats fans on the field right now couldn't change the outcome. This one's over. Wow.    
    
    
    In terms of this game's location in the "rebuilding process", it feels like Derrick Williams just dunked on Duke.    
    
    
    Oregon has had like 3 or 4 of the most blatant holds I've ever seen and somehow that last one didn't get called.    
    
    
    Oregon is just getting physically abused right now and it's awesome.    
    
    
    "What a performance by Arizona State's D." Well, we knew that was coming eventually.    
    
    
    I was feeling good about Ohio State -33.5 when the Buckeyes were up 42-0. Not so much right now.    
    
    
    I wonder what the clown I sat in front of during the UCLA game who was bashing the 3-3-5 for three straight hours has to say right now.    
    
    
    Good god UCLA act like you've at least practiced a late game situation before.    
    
    
    Imagine how different the Territorial Cup could be if Ka'Deem doesn't fumble at the goal line against UCLA.    
    
    
    RT @AlexHWilliams: Imagine how different the Territorial Cup could be if Ka'Deem doesn't fumble at the goal line against UCLA.    
    
    
    It entertains me when people who dont know anything about football argue loudly about football.    
    
    
    It entertains me when people who dont know anything about football argue loudly about football.    
    
    
    ASU loves using the #ArizonaWildcats logo on signs and shirts MT @SunDevilEquip: We don't celebrate long. #beatuofa pic.twitter.com/03SNkbWl3V    
    
    
    Guy in a BWW uniform is talking shit about U of A because he clearly made a good college choice. Claims to be an Oregon fan.    
    
    
    Did I really just see Mendenhall hit a hole hard and run through contact?    
    
    
    Hey, three incompletions by Palmer and all three should have been picked off.    
    
    
    What a clown...you're losing 24-3, haven't gotten a stop, and you do that when you get a sack?    
    
    
    The Cardinals need to take the playcalling from that drive and bury it in a place it will never be found again.    
    
    
    I feel like four-way stop signs and turn signal usage are pretty solid measures of intelligence.    
    
    
    Stalking Jack and finding many sexual/lovey pictures with @ericbbrady.. Should I be worried?    
    
    
    The best part about the picture of the two Florida guys blocking each other is the Georgia Southern guy face-down at the goal line.    
    
    
    I hope USC takes a page out of 2007 ASU's book and sells Pac-12 South Champions gear if it beats UCLA Saturday.    
    
    
    Solid day for ASU...spray painting statues and throwing stuff on the court.    
    
    
    Solid day for ASU...spray painting statues and throwing stuff on the court.    
    
    
    Decent resume win for #ASU, but again it was a game it should win. 7-point home favorite against marginal top-25 team.    
    
    
    But #ASU is obviously better and isn't a Pac-12 doormat anymore.    
    
    
    What is with people's inability to watch a football game in an office without yelling, pounding a desk and dropping 15 F-bombs?    
    
    
    I don't think I've seen a single person spell Bachynski right on my timeline tonight.    
    
    
    As good as the HBO documentary is on Ohio State-Michigan, I'll never understand why they put some of these clowns on camera.    
    
    
    Final table at Talking Stick. Second in chips $3100 up top lets gooo pic.twitter.com/S2ShA0Osue    
    
    
    Busto 8th. Had to 3-bet fold JJ in a big spot then TT> KK> QQ. Good game.    
    
    
    Adversity is good for college basketball teams, especially when you still win the game.  #ArizonaWildcats    
    
    
    I can't wait until Sat. so I can hear people not old enough to have watched ASU in the Rose Bowl tell me Arizona has never been to one.    
    
    
    "How to confuse UA fan: Ask him what Pasadena is like in January." Also a good way to confuse any ASU fan younger than 24.    
    
    
    @WildcatSports @WildcatHoops Broken link.    
    
    
    Internet #ASU fan says JR Redmond and Marion Grice are better than Ka'Deem. That's beautiful.    
    
    
    Ohio State is a 17-point road favorite against Michigan. For history's sake, OSU opened -17 at home against a BAD 2010 UM team.    
    
    
    I think the AP had a high school sophomore who's never shot basketball before shoot the ASU hoops game tonight.    
    
    
    Win or lose tonight, this tourney couldn't have gone better for #ArizonaWildcats. Huge deficit against Drexel plus weird wait-time tonight.    
    
    
    You want young, possibly championship-caliber teams to deal with as much weird stuff as possible early in the season.#ArizonaWildcats have.    
    
    
    Tarczewski watch: One touch, one turnover.    
    
    
    #ArizonaWildcats are doing exactly nothing well right now.    
    
    
    I'm glad there's only one sport where refs can influence the game at any point they feel like it. God this is frustrating.    
    
    
    Is that really not a travel?    
    
    
    How much more awesome would these Oregon uniforms be with a yellow helmet that had bright green feathers?    
    
    
    Gameday talking #ArizonaWildcats. Herbie, Desmond take ASU.    
    
    
    Good start to a big day. Let's go Bucks! pic.twitter.com/f2Aj7zmNUI    
    
    
    There's something about drinking beer in sweatpants and slippers that just feels right.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Now Dontre Wilson is gone. Fan fucking tastic, Ohio State.    
    
    
    But the refs let it get there. You HAVE to stop it when five UM guys surround Wilson when he's trying to get up.    
    
    
    That is absolutely, 100 percent on the refs. Terrible officiating.    
    
    
    The good news is that Michigan will be out of gimmicks soon.    
    
    
    I get the heat-of-the-moment argument to an extent, but what seriously provokes someone to want to throw a punch in a football game? Really.    
    
    
    How do you stop brawls? Flag UM for talking shit after every tackle. But maybe too little too late.    
    
    
    It's going to be the most ACC thing ever when Duke beats Florida State next weekend.    
    
    
    Love that decision by Hoke, but can't believe he'd do that without a better play lined up.    
    
    
    Well one down two to go. WAR EAGLE!    
    
    
    Wonder if Graham or RichRod will make the same decision Brady Hoke did if they're faced with it tonight.    
    
    
    Never change, ASU. pic.twitter.com/cRcjFRDutF    
    
    
    What does Sparky have in common with mermaids and unicorns?    
    
    
    Sign here says "Wilbur licks himself." Of course he does. He's a cat. How else would he get clean?    
    
    
    WAR WAGLE!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Two down, one to go. Let's go Cats!    
    
    
    Let's go Cats!!!! (@ Sun Devil Stadium - @sparkyarizonast for Arizona Wildcats vs Arizona State Sun Devils) http://4sq.com/1fUy9ez     
    
    
    Is it just me, or is there some Phoenix media that's extremely homer-ish compared to other places? Check out @abc15's last RT. At least try.    
    
    
    Guy from the Detroit Free Press has OSU No. 8, behind Auburn, Mizzou, Bama, Oklahoma State, South Carolina and Stanford. Wow.    
    
    
    "I look at the entirety of the season, not a single high or low moment." Ohio State HASN'T HAD A LOW MOMENT. My mind is blown right now.    
    
    
    Ha, call holding on Mathieu to negate a pick then don't throw a flag on that last play to Floyd. That's terrible, NFL refs.    
    
    
    #AZCardinals didn't play well but they were robbed of a chance to win this game by the officiating.    
    
    
    @KylePayne_28 If Ohio State falls after beating a top-10 team at a neutral site there should be riots.    
    
    
    Down to 13/517. Top three stack. 910 > AK aipf rivers a 3-outer. Next hand K10>KJ aipf rivers a 10. That was fun.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ohio State was really lackluster when it was up 31-14 in the 4th quarter against Wisc. I wonder how much of this these guys really believe?    
    
    
    The idea that RichRod isn't a very good coach and doesn't care about beating ASU is probably one of the silliest things I've ever heard.    
    
    
    The idea that RichRod isn't a very good coach and doesn't care about beating ASU is probably one of the silliest things I've ever heard.    
    
    
    @Yostmeister @MGoJen RichRod never had a team that was near the level of OSU. Should have beat ASU last year, but overmatched this year.    
    
    
    How do you know it's winter in Scottsdale? People at a sports bar are actively watching hockey.    
    
    
    Did you guys know that it's loud in Seattle?    
    
    
    @ZonaZooOfficial filling up before game time. Follow us for updates from McKale #ArizonaWildcats pic.twitter.com/fs9vfrkNfD    
    
    
    "This is where Arizona State has been so strong on the offensive boards." Really, @Pac12Networks? What a joke.    
    
    
    I've done broadcasting. I know it isn't easy. But I always knew what schools I was covering.    
    
    
    There's a guy who always tweets @AZSports620 who appears to be an #ASU football fan and #ArizonaWildcats basketball fan. Not kidding.    
    
    
    So Tarczewski gets fouled twice, Texas Tech goaltends, and the #ArizonaWildcats get no points. Solid.    
    
    
    I think a puppy dies every time someone comments "must be a slow news day" on an article.    
    
    
    Wrecking ball is a song that guys at 1st r too embarrassed to say we like but once we find out every guy likes it we play it more than girls    
    
    
    The two least-talented #ArizonaWildcats teams I've ever seen just combined to win 15 games and people are mad at the coach. Unbelievable.    
    
    
    Waiting for my timeline to blow up RE: that ASU Deadspin video...    
    
    
    Waiting for my timeline to blow up RE: that ASU Deadspin video...    
    
    
    Just hit the bad beat jackpot on Merge and it got counterfeited on the river. That was fun.    
    
    
    So the No. 1 #ArizonaWildcats sounds pretty cool.    
    
    
    When is the last time Arizona was #1? #ALittleHelp    
    
    
    Digging up SDS photos for something ... caption from last Cards game there: "After 18 seasons at the University of Arizona's stadium..."    
    
    
    That's an AP caption, so hey, it's not just ESPN and the Pac-12 Networks.    
    
    
    It's nice to be at the top, but what's @APlayersProgram's ultimate goal: to be ranked No. 1 in December, or to win a national championship?    
    
    
    The Twitter machine is on fire today.    
    
    
    The Twitter machine is on fire today.    
    
    
    Someone asked Dustin Pedroia if he's underpaid. "Are you kidding? I'm rich as fuck." Awesome answer.    
    
    
    I should start tweeting my stories in third person. MT @sportsiren: Holly Rowe takes a look at Arizona St WR D.J Foster.    
    
    
    I can't believe it's been three years and no one has convinced Spencer Dinwiddie his mustache is ugly.    
    
    
    Like every college football fan outside of Austin & Waco, I'm settling for Baylor-Texas for the next 10 mins 'til Auburn-Missouri begins.    
    
    
    I feel like Tad Boyle's goal every year is to put together the ugliest team in America and he always does a fantastic job.    
    
    
    Basketball refs do know that you don't have to call anything when there's contact, right?    
    
    
    There were no fouls in the first half and about 50 in the second half, so I'm assuming it's Pac-12 refs on the KU-Colorado game.    
    
    
    Tarczewski just got chop blocked going for a rebound and it wasn't a foul somehow.    
    
    
    The hack on his wrist didn’t help either. ’t @azdesertswarm: Brandon Ashley a little strong on that one    
    
    
    The idea that Ohio State is the third-best basketball team in the country is hilarious to me.    
    
    
    The idea that Ohio State is the third-best basketball team in the country is hilarious to me.    
    
    
    The good news is that UNLV can’t keep shooting 65 percent.    
    
    
    Brandon Ashley has four fouls and I'm not sure he's actually committed one yet.    
    
    
    Oh hey, look at the air raid siren making an appearance at McKale.    
    
    
    And tickets were about $20 cheaper. RT @territorialcup: ASU sells out the UA game but not this one. Huh.    
    
    
    Hooray, football! pic.twitter.com/psRg9dbTCS    
    
    
    Hooray, football! pic.twitter.com/psRg9dbTCS    
    
    
    Wait, so punching Shazier in the head is not only not an ejection, but not even a penalty?    
    
    
    Well this Ohio State season sure was fun while it lasted.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    So, #ASU, can we talk about basketball yet? Do we have your permission?    
    
    
    Um...if the #Dbacks are really considering trading Skaggs and Eaton for Trumbo, well, that just seems dumb.    
    
    
    Um...if the #Dbacks are really considering trading Skaggs and Eaton for Trumbo, well, that just seems dumb.    
    
    
    Um...if the #Dbacks are really considering trading Skaggs and Eaton for Trumbo, well, that just seems dumb.    
    
    
    Have you had a chance to check out the new http://dailywildcat.com  yet? What do you think?    
    
    
    Not a good trade for the #dbacks. Think Adam Dunn.    
    
    
    Not a good trade for the #dbacks. Think Adam Dunn.    
    
    
    People keep saying Trumbo is Reynolds 2.0...does anyone have a problem with .240, 40 bombs and 100 RBIs? I know I don't. #Dbacks    
    
    
    Just your casual 29-3 run for Florida. It's a no big deal.    
    
    
    Newly acquired #Dbacks OF Mark Trumbo: "I'm not cool with strikeouts." - http://bit.ly/1d8AZHA     
    
    
    #Suns GM Ryan McDonough is one of the few people not surprised by Phoenix's start - http://bit.ly/18VmzOi     
    
    
        
    
    
    Pretty sure that was a "Dammit Kaleb catch the ball!" from McConnell.    
    
    
    How in the hell does someone who's played basketball his whole life take two free throws without hitting the rim?    
    
    
    UA must not be as athletic or well-coached as who it plays b/c how else would the other team be in dbl-bonus before UA's in 1-1 every game?    
    
    
    I'm about to make me some hot chocolate... Yeaaa    
    
    
    Just realized this is the first dead day in, like, 3 years where I'm not playing in the KAMP-Daily Wildcat basketball game.    
    
    
    Hammered kid next to me at the poker table: "What time is it?" Me: "3:30." Him: "In the afternoon?" Solid.    
    
    
    Headed to Hoop Hall West today to check out Stanley Johnson, Stephen Zimmerman, Chase Jeter, Rex Pflueger, and a handful of other prospects.    
    
    
    What would be a good season for Trumbo? Internet commenter: .275 with 50 bombs. Hahahahaha    
    
    
    Headed to Hoop Hall West today to check out Stanley Johnson, Stephen Zimmerman, Chase Jeter, Rex Pflueger, and a handful of other prospects.    
    
    
    @ericbbrady Which wine pairs best with the breakfast nachos?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is there a team in America with a worse shooting percentage within four feet than the #ArizonaWildcats?    
    
    
    Josiah McConnell isn't having his best game so far.    
    
    
    12 PPG, 2.8:2 assist-to-turnover in four games. RT @azdesertswarm: Don't do that to Josiah. Was killing it in D-League last I checked    
    
    
    Oh, the wonderful time of year when we get to remind basketball refs that whether the ball goes in or not has no bearing on it being a foul.    
    
    
    What did Brandon Ashley do to college basketball refs?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yeah, that last shot's a pretty good synopsis of the first half. Not sure that could have gone much worse for UA and it's still in it.    
    
    
    Do they really let the other team set up offense when a guy is down? Thought they stop it unless it's a fast break.    
    
    
    Do they really let the other team set up offense when a guy is down? Thought they stop it unless it's a fast break.    
    
    
        
    
    
    One of the refs in this game worked Iowa-Iowa State last night, which ended at 11:30 p.m. Because that makes sense, right?    
    
    
    Lol at no And-1 on that Tarczewski dunk after some of the ticky-tack crap that's been called at the other end.    
    
    
    So no we're at at least two free points and a free possession for Michigan thanks to horrible calls.    
    
    
    Not that I'm saying the refs are any worse in this game than they typically are, because they're not. But it's still an issue.    
    
    
    At least Arizona seems to be learning that if you initiate contact offensively you're probably getting a call.    
    
    
    "You can't win a game like this if you don't play it." Classic SMiller.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'll take the blame for that one. RT @Vincemarotta: So much for a fast-moving first half.    
    
    
    After reading the fantastic MMQB story on an officiating crew, I'm curious what this review's going to be like.    
    
    
    Just a general though: How is a hit in the endzone in a 3-point game in Week 15 of a team in a playoff race unnecessary roughness?    
    
    
    I'm not sure there's a more difficult feat in sports than winning on the road in the NFL.    
    
    
    Things playoff teams don't do: Blow 17-point leads in less than three minutes.    
    
    
    Cards have been stupid, but they have 3x as many penalties as the Titans for 4x as many yards.    
    
    
    How in God's green earth is that not a 15-yard personal foul at the end of the play? That's terrible.    
    
    
    Seriously, Powers got lit up in the end zone without the ball. That's a joke.    
    
    
    Bird Bits: #AZCardinals top Titans despite blowing late three-score lead - http://bit.ly/1fwMGdr     
    
    
        
    
    
    #AZCardinals guard Daryn Colledge: Offense took it personally when QB Palmer was injured on illegal hit - http://bit.ly/19rMew8     
    
    
        
    
    
    #Analysis MT @offensivelyfoul: Probably would've been a different game had GS not passed it to the Suns half the time.    
    
    
    New look McKale #arizonawildcats pic.twitter.com/Jv5TfAqAmv    
    
    
    I wonder how long it would take for Jose Valverde and Miguel Montero to come to blows.    
    
    
    Guy calls a raise with Q3s, rivers a flush, bets 7x pot and I pay him off. God that's special.    
    
    
    Yeah, I just lost this hand in an 80BB pot after getting it in on the flop. pic.twitter.com/0ud32wl5Eg    
    
    
    In the money at TS. Shove ATs from the button and BB tank calls KK then tries to fist bump me when he won. Wanted to fist bump his face.    
    
    
        
    
    
    FB friend: "This weather is too warm for it to be December. Yuck!" Congrats on being the first person to ever complain about sunny and 70.    
    
    
    Beer pong 101. MT @GottliebShow: Not really,more arch,more likely to make it-wider target area    
    
    
        
    
    
    Maybe Korchek shouldn't touch the ball any more.    
    
    
    @nicoledimtsios Wins at UM and SDSU, neutral over Duke. Up 20 playing bad without its 7-foot center. What's there to be worried about?    
    
    
    Kurt Warner: The #AZCardinals' chances in Seattle hinge on creating big plays - http://bit.ly/1juvE4O     
    
    
        
    
    
    I have yet to watch an extended amount of an Ohio State basketball game this year and not think "Man, this is painfully boring."    
    
    
    #ASU isn't selling single-game tickets to the #ArizonaWildcats game Feb. 14. Interesting tactic.    
    
    
    What the hell did the Saints just do?    
    
    
    Remember an interview I did with @Greg_Byrne a couple years ago. "If you haven't noticed, I like video boards." That's proving pretty true.    
    
    
    #ASU isn't selling single-game tickets to the #ArizonaWildcats game Feb. 14. Interesting tactic.    
    
    
    Sometimes things just aren't meant to be...like the Cardinals making the playoffs this year.    
    
    
    Lesson learned: Don't hit Rob Housler in the face because he won't catch it.    
    
    
    Wilson throws late, over the middle, across his body and it's incomplete. Palmer hits his TE in the face in the endzone and it's an INT.    
    
    
    Patrick Peterson is a bad decision machine lately    
    
    
    The Cardinals must have really pissed off whoever is in charge of luck this season.    
    
    
    Seahawk fans are so great that they're booing their team that'll be the No. 1 seed and has won 14 straight at home.    
    
    
    At least Patrick Peterson was too busy bitching about something to go after that ball.    
    
    
    Is there a team in recent memory that's been more screwed by its league than the Cardinals have been by the NFL this season?    
    
    
    Payback for that Foles foot interception in Seattle?    
    
    
    Is there a team in recent memory that's been more screwed by its league than the Cardinals have been by the NFL this season?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Someone help me out. If the Niners lose tonight, are the Cards in?    
    
    
    Someone help me out. If the Niners lose tonight, are the Cards in?    
    
    
    I wonder if Atlanta's coaches think that net 30-yard gain was worth it.    
    
    
    In a season where nothing went right for the #AZCardinals, NOTHING CONTINUES TO GO RIGHT.    
    
    
    There's about 15 plays this season where if a single one goes the other way, the #AZCardinals control their own playoff destiny.    
    
    
    In a season where nothing went right for the #AZCardinals, NOTHING CONTINUES TO GO RIGHT.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Also it's going to be awesome when three NFC West teams are 11-5 and one of them doesn't make the playoffs.    
    
    
    So Falcons, 10-point underdogs, trail by 10 and line up for a FG. SF calls timeout and ATL doesn't kick it. Why?    
    
    
    So losing two games they should have won aside, the Cardinals have been hurt by SEA, SF, NO and that terrible non-PI on Gronk in Carolina.    
    
    
    So losing two games they should have won aside, the Cardinals have been hurt by SEA, SF, NO and that terrible non-PI on Gronk in Carolina.    
    
    
    Solid night for Arizona sports fans. #Coyotes lose on a puck in the goalie's pants. Falcons throw a pick inside the 10 with 1:30 left down 3    
    
    
    The #Coyotes lost tonight on one of the flukiest plays in recent memory - http://bit.ly/1gTvDp7     
    
    
    ASU is 10-1, Arizona is 3-7.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Jeff Garcia to back up Foles. RT @ZackBlatt: Jon Kitna signs back up with Dallas. What's next….Jeff George to Oakland?    
    
    
    Watching '97 UA-Kentucky. I'm nervous and I know who wins. What a game.    
    
    
    I bet Russell Westbrook is the only player pumped about these jerseys because they are "trendy"    
    
    
    A package stolen from my house and 8 hours of work. Really feeling the Christmas spirit today.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm on a different computer and using a different browser but getting FB ads for something I looked at earlier today. Stay creepy, adtech.    
    
    
    Dude just played Hang On Sloopy and We Don't Give a Damn in a bar full of Michigan fans. I'm down with that. http://4sq.com/JjG6fn     
    
    
        
    
    
    That the FOX announcer would even suggest that the #AZCardinals punt this pall is so funny.    
    
    
    Like how is someone so stuck in the stone age of football that they would suggest punting on 4th and inches on the plus side of the 50?    
    
    
    Not that I have any bias against kickers from years of torment, but I don't think many people realize how devastating a missed short FG is.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Didn't Palmer learn his lesson about throwing to Housler in the end zone last week?    
    
    
    49ers guy rips off Ellington's shoe and sock, drops it, kicks it, and no penalty?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Remember when Boldin had 6 catches for 106 yards in the first quarter? One catch for 8 yards since then.    
    
    
    That's not going to stand.    
    
    
    I take that back. Thought his elbow came down OOB before the second foot but I'm wrong.    
    
    
    By the Numbers: The #AZCardinals' 23-20 loss to the San Francisco #49ers - http://bit.ly/1eP38ZH     
    
    
    #AZCardinals NT Dan Williams: "We gave them a lot ... in the end, it came back and bit us." - http://bit.ly/1jYj1iR     
    
    
    #AZCardinals QB Palmer becomes first in NFL history to reach 4,000 yards with three different teams - http://bit.ly/1djgpq7     
    
    
    That's only 20 INT less than Carson Palmer. MT @ZachEClark: Nick Foles ... 27 TD, 2 INT and now a NFC East championship. #Incredible    
    
    
    Lolwut? MT @FitzBeatSr: AZ qualifies for the playoffs! Nick Coles QB incredible year for Eagles No.1 QB based on QBR- http://bit.ly/1geXtti     
    
    
    Texas Tech clearly watched film of BJ Denker and is trying to emulate the #ArizonaWildcats offense against ASU.    
    
    
    ASU couldn't be getting any luckier and is still getting ran. That's a shocker.    
    
    
    Valiant effort by Will Sutton trying to get himself into the box score.    
    
    
    And LOL at fans on either side acting like bowl games mean anything about a team or coaching staff.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Arizona's special teams are extra special today.    
    
    
    After seeing Williams, what would Ka'Deem run for in the ACC? 3,000 yards? 4,000? Totally unimpressed.    
    
    
    Good for BJ Denker going out with a game like this.    
    
    
    Unfortunately for ESPN announcer's gambling reference, Arizona was -7, not -24. At least have a clue if you're gonna go there.    
    
    
    First New Years Eve, first time on Mill Ave. Pray for me, y'all.    
    
    
    Rage rage rage (@ Downtown Tempe / Mill Avenue District for Circle K New Year's Eve Block Party w/ 23 others) http://4sq.com/Jtor4T     
    
    
    Last-second pick to beat Duke 52-48...must be time for the SEC chant.    
    
    
    You are Wisconsin. It's third and inches in field goal range and your backup quarterback is in the game. What do you do?    
    
    
    In what world is 80 yards on 13 carries "bottled up?"    
    
    
    The idea that the #ArizonaWildcats went head-to-head with Bama in something to do with football and won is mind boggling.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I think this is the first non-UA ASU hoops game I’ve been to. What an odd environment.    
    
    
    McKissic hits a 3 to put #ASU up 14-8. Pimps it down the court. Blackwell gets a dunk for UW with no one within 10 feet.    
    
    
    #ASU up 16-12 at the under-16 timeout. McKissic has 7, Carson has 5. Only 3 points for Devils haven’t been in paint or at FT line.    
    
    
    Washington’s 8-0 run puts the Huskies up 18-16 at the 11:59 mark. UW getting a lot of easy baskets. Doesn’t look good when it can’t run.    
    
    
    Now that UW run is extended to 18-4. Huskies lead #ASU 30-20 with 6:46 left in the first.    
    
    
    #ASU trails Washington 40-23 at half. Carson has 10. Bachynski 4 and 4. UW ended the half on a 28-7 run.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Looking big picture, #ASU has to win games like this if it wants a tournament look. Especially when its one of few national TV games.    
    
    
    #ASU shot 10 percent over the last 12 minutes or so of the half.    
    
    
    The sound people here somehow missed the memo that there are about 6,000 people here.    
    
    
    #ASU went zone to close the first half. Now going full-court to open the second. Devils still down 15.    
    
    
    #ASU’s 9-0 run gets the Washington lead to 10. Timeout Huskies. Sun Devils shooting 66 percent in the 2nd after closing the 1st 2-of-20.    
    
    
    That didn’t last long. UW’s 8-0 run gets the lead back up to 18. Not 6 minutes into the second half and we’ve had a 9-0 and 8-0 run.    
    
    
    #ASU’s bench finally gets on the board…at the 11:46 mark of the second half. Washington leads 56-41 with 11:22 to play.    
    
    
    Nigel Williams-Goss comes up with a steal and layup and UW (8-5) leads by 23 with 7:57 to go. Shaping up to be a bad loss for #ASU.    
    
    
    Weirdest part about this game is UW isn’t playing out of its mind or anything. Neither team looks like anything special.    
    
    
    This one’s all but over. Washington leads #ASU 74-52 with 3:41 to go. Brutal loss for the Sun Devils.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Final from Wells Fargo Arena: Washington 76, #ASU 65. Sun Devils’ first home loss of the season and it wasn’t as close as the score.    
    
    
        
    
    
    FAT GUY TOUCHDOWN THIS IS AWESOME    
    
    
    