Made the front page again. Thanks to everyone who has provided help and strength along the way.… http://instagram.com/p/gV6Y-XP0PA/     
    
    
    Have to say @JACKSONVILLE_FC logo and crest is top notch. Random, I know.    
    
    
    @frankiedevai Thanks Frankie!    
    
    
    @SocratesMTL I just love that blue/gold mix.    
    
    
    My contribution to 2013 election and voting coverage: 'Voters approve casinos, marijuana tax in ballot measures' http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865589976/Voters-approve-casinos-marijuana-tax-in-ballot-measures.html …    
    
    
    Every day gets infinitely better when you realize MLS playoffs are on later, especially second legs. PUMPED. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    But then you realize #NYvHOU is on Univision and #SKCvNE is on MLS Live and not NBC or ESPN. Shame. #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    @GlennDavisSoc Could see NY going with the counter-attacking style. But maybe they'll just attack since everything's on the line. Fun game.    
    
    
    My story on the Supreme Court and how its case about public prayer in a NY suburb could affect the nation: http://bit.ly/19DDJxj  #scotus    
    
    
    @GlennDavisSoc Agreed. But RBNY could also get caught badly on the counter-attack, too. His send-off changed the series for them.    
    
    
    Some of these playoff games are a good way to sell people on the idea of MLS Live. Problem is it won't bring in newbies. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    November 19. Orlando City. MLS. Allegedly. http://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/local/breakingnews/os-mls-awards-orlando-franchise-20131106,0,4972653.story?utm_content=bufferb6600&utm_source=buffer&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Buffer …    
    
    
    @rhalloran11 Good question. Range of options for them in USL PRO. Might want to avoid teams with potential to be a MLS club.    
    
    
    Cheesy Garlic Bread flavored Lays chips. So...weird....    
    
    
    Most likely will be attending tomorrow's playoff clash between RSL and LA Galaxy. First ever live MLS playoff match for me. #mls    
    
    
    Messi has this way of silencing critics in a timely fashion. #messi    
    
    
    Petke gets a contract extension. Definitely must have confidence rather than worry for tonight's game with that move. #rbny #mls    
    
    
    Unfortunate result for RBNY. Deserved more than an ugly loss to Houston. But Dynamo are always dangerous in these playoffs. #mls    
    
    
    SKC and Revs is so open and back-and-forth. Both teams want this so bad. #NEvSKC    
    
    
    Really sucks these games aren't on a national broadcast. Both would have been attractive to new fans. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Revs are filled with impressive young players. Only thing the franchise really has going for it. #NERevs #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Been enjoying SKC and Revs. Wonder if first leg was this good, but couldn't tell cause of those football lines. #NEvSKC    
    
    
    To Houston and Revs credit, both were consistently in the mix for playoff spots all season. Rarely did they drop too far away. #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Hold on to your butts. #nerevs #skc #nevskc #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Drama and excitement in the 2 East matches. Wonder how tomorrow's West clashes will go. RSL/LA and PDX/SEA should deliver. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    My Boston-based friend: "Fagundez has to go on a maradona run." Something beautiful about that. #nerevs #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Watching Revs from Utah and I have same commentators as my Mass friends. Wish it was nationally broadcasted. #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    This has been going on for awhile, but sad to see Blockbuster putting the nail in the coffin: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-24844350 …    
    
    
    Western Conference semifinals tonight. Last night's drama was great. Expecting another round of it. #mlsplayoffs #mls    
    
    
    One of the best nights in college history. Plus, I'm wearing a RSL hat and they have a playoff match… http://instagram.com/p/ga6VCkv0J2/     
    
    
    Can't say I'm surprised with Adu not being resigned. Rarely dressed or made matchday 18. Wonder where he's onto next.    
    
    
    Adu had a lot of promise but is proving to be uncoachable. Next step down would be a move to Chivas. #mls    
    
    
    This morning I wondered when the next Killers album would be. Come to find they're releasing a compilation album this month. #thekillers    
    
    
    @halpal8 Just started following you again. You're still my 2nd favorite person from Charlotte.    
    
    
    Star Wars Episode VII. December 18, 2015. Excited.    
    
    
    @MrSeanMSweeney Considering Walt Disney just tweeted it out from their official account, I'd say pretty likely.    
    
    
    @MrSeanMSweeney I think the initial release date was for summer 2015, so they probably pushed it to December to accommodate delays.    
    
    
    Really interested to see where Adu ends up. Going to Liga MX has proved valuable for USMNT revivals. Maybe he'll find success there. #usmnt    
    
    
    Must be said that Freddy Adu is, without a doubt. the most overrated player in FIFA video games. #fifa14 #adu    
    
    
    @SoccerByIves Definitely think Porter is the right coach for Adu. Probably could make him work well in the Timbers system.    
    
    
    So Massachusetts is having a killer sunset apparently...    
    
    
    Time dor some MLS playoffs. #mls #rsl #realsaltlake #rslvla http://instagram.com/p/gb4IpkP0EZ/     
    
    
    Portland and Salt Lake. Great Western Conference final on tap. Unfortunately, playoff schedule doesn't make it easy to follow. #mls    
    
    
    Drinking Dunkin! They just opened one here in Salt Lake. Fantastic. http://instagram.com/p/gdSO2wv0L-/     
    
    
    FC Kansas City, one of the top teams of the NWSL this year, has picked up Amy Rodriguez, a top #USWNT star, from Seattle. Watch out. #NWSL    
    
    
    Rio Tinto Stadium's atmosphere was enjoyable last night. Everyone was pumped and ready, which is surprising given the wicked wind. #RSL    
    
    
    Got my office talking about Real Salt Lake this morning. Victory. #rsl #mls #soccer    
    
    
    @fuegote Part of me thinks you're still upset by that loss and avoiding the team like a bad ex-girlfriend.    
    
    
    If Dynamo make it to the MLS Cup, it'd be impressive. Barely any turnaround for them between play-in and East semifinals. #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Wonder what effects playoffs will have on MVP, Rookie of the Year races. Is Magee still top choice despite no playoffs? #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    And.... #FF to the @SoccerNewsday crew: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    RSL winning MLS Cup 2009. #flashbackfriday #ff #rsl #realsaltlake http://instagram.com/p/gd18s4v0ON/     
    
    
    Houston will be lucky to get out with a good result with all the turnaround. They'll cherish the break. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Congrats to the NY Cosmos. Strong return. Had an advantage with half season, but very nice to see them take Soccer Bowl. #nasl #nycomos    
    
    
    Next season will be true test for Cosmos, to see of they can succeed through both halves. Good moment for NYC fans, though. #nycosmos #nasl    
    
    
    MLS Western Conference Final first leg. Portland vs. Salt Lake. #rsl #realsaltlake #mls #mlsplayoffs… http://instagram.com/p/gjkjnqv0Px/     
    
    
    First time seeing the Timbers play live tonight. Should be am absolute cracker between RSL and PDX. #mls #mlsplayoffs #rslvpor    
    
    
    @LeKurosawa Only a solid 50. Nothing for a Northeasterner.    
    
    
    Watched an abundance of RSL games this season in person and on TV. Still don't get the point of Robbie Findley or Devon Sandoval. #rslvpor    
    
    
    Wow. What a great half of entertaining soccer. #mls #mlsplayoffs #rslvpor    
    
    
    And Sandoval and Findley just proved me wrong. #mlsplayoffs #mls #rslvpor    
    
    
    Jurgen Klinsmann has called in his 23-man squad for upcoming #USMNT friendlies: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/mens-national-team/2013/11/131111-roster-rel-scot-aust.aspx …    
    
    
    GK: Bill Hamid, Tim Howard, Sean Johnson #usmnt    
    
    
    DEF: DaMarcus Beasley, John Brooks, Geoff Cameron, Brad Evans, Omar Gonzalez, Eric Lichaj, Michael Orozco #usmnt    
    
    
    MID: Alejandro Bedoya, Michael Bradley, Mix Diskerud, Fabian Johnson, Jermaine Jones, Sacha Kljestan, Brek Shea #usmnt    
    
    
    FWD: Jozy Altidore, Terrence Boyd, Clint Dempsey, Aron Johannsson, Eddie Johnson, Chris Wondolowski #usmnt    
    
    
    Unfortunate Mike Magee couldn't get a call up. No Donovan or Beckerman, but given their MLS scenarios it makes sense. #usmnt    
    
    
    Klinsmann definitely testing the waters and making his final decisions on some. Mix, Johannsson, Kljestan, Shea all on the bubble. #usmnt    
    
    
    Dempsey certainly a player to watch for these upcoming friendlies. Have to wonder if slump is just at SSFC or if it will flow to #USMNT    
    
    
    Whether or not Portland advances after last night's 4-2 loss to RSL, the things Porter has done in his 1st pro season are unreal. #timbers    
    
    
    Nice to see Eric Lichaj getting another call-up. Heard he's been doing great in England. Wonder how of him we'll see. #usmnt    
    
    
    USL OKC franchise potential logos/colors/team names: http://newsok.com/prodigal-soccer-submits-possible-team-names-logos-for-usl-franchise/article/3902074# …!    
    
    
    Can't say I'm impressed any of the options for #OKC team. Names are lame and colors are typical. Spirit is my favorite design. #uslpro    
    
    
    Looks like Philadelphia's looking for an attacking DP on Valeri's level. Well worth it if they can find that type of player. #mls #doop    
    
    
    TFC's looking to become the best team from 2004 with Eto'o and Defoe interest. #tfc    
    
    
    Newest @thekillers album out. It's a compilation album, but has some new stuff. Great work. Favorite band.    
    
    
    @Rlevine62 YES. Just Another Girl gives me chills. OK, not really. But still. Two great songs.    
    
    
    Big issue with Magee ever getting a USMNT call-up is that he could fail in the system and it'd be another Jack McInerney situation. #usmnt    
    
    
    @holdenb75 Good question. Though his slump started a game or two before the call-up. Still stopped his momentum. Hasn't been the same.    
    
    
    Saw "The Damned United" on Sat. One of the best soccer movies I've seen. Funny, engaging and a good 100 mins of film. #leeds #derbycounty    
    
    
    Orlando had more than 20,000 in town to see the USWNT play Brazil. Big numbers as they gear up for MLS expansion.    
    
    
    WNBA averaged more viewers than MLS this year, one site says: http://www.sportsbusinessdaily.com/Journal/Issues/2013/11/11/Media/By-The-Numbers.aspx … #mls    
    
    
    MLS games were weekend-based, where as WNBA games were primetime, according to @SBJSBD. #mls #wbna    
    
    
    USMNT manager Jurgen Klinsmann discusses team in Q&A: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/mens-national-team/2013/11/131112-qa-jk-on-sct-aust-friendlies.aspx … #usmnt    
    
    
    Great quote by Klinsmann: "It’s not about ... what you did in the past, it’s always about the moment, the present and the future." #usmnt    
    
    
    My thoughts on the recent #USMNT callups: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1405/usmnt-report-little-magic-in-euro-friendly-callups …    
    
    
    Oldest friends transform. #tt #transformationtuesday #transformtuesday #friends #oldestfriends #bros… http://instagram.com/p/gn_tCiv0BN/     
    
    
    USMNT Report: Little Magic in Euro Friendly Callups http://bit.ly/1i5ogK9  #usmnt #usa #USAvSCO #usavaut #scotland #austria #USMNTReport    
    
    
    @BrianStraus Would certainly free up some space for the top-heavy Sounders, too, and give them the chance for a defender or midfielder.    
    
    
    @BrianStraus True. It'd be good to see how they work from the beginning of a season and after WC prep. But might hurt Neagle's growth.    
    
    
    @SteveDavis90 Enjoyed this and agree with most of it. British/Scottish coach won't help MLS' game grow, either. Style is boring and brutish.    
    
    
    Expecting Mexico to breeze past New Zealand, but you never know with the #AllWhites. Always remember that 2010 WC match with Italy. #eltri    
    
    
    Believers unite to combat religious jokes and jabs http://bit.ly/1eGBtcs  #faith #religion    
    
    
    My picks for the #WorldCup play-offs starting today: Mexico, Uruguay, Greece, Sweden, France and Iceland.  #uefa #eltri    
    
    
    I'm choosing Iceland to eventually qualify because I'm Irish. #iceland #uefa    
    
    
    Very true. RT @GrantWahl: Whether you like him or dislike him, the World Cup is more interesting with Luis Suárez involved.    
    
    
    USMNT fans: It's OK to root for Mexico . Helps CONCACAF and the USA's national team grow overall. #usmnt #eltri    
    
    
    Really wonder what Mexico would have been like had FMF hadn't kept Chepo as long as they did. Likely a much different story. #eltri    
    
    
    ICYMI: My thoughts on Klinsmann's latest USMNT selections: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1405/usmnt-report-little-magic-in-euro-friendly-callups … #usmnt    
    
    
    How fun that would be! RT @goaleric: Just found out it's Chepo's birthday today. Cosmos, do your thing.    
    
    
    Orlando City confirmed that they'll be announced as an MLS expansion franchise on Nov. 19 at the Cheyenne Sallon, according to @BrianStraus    
    
    
    If reports are to be believed and Orlando is being announced on Nov. 19, I have to say it's about damn time MLS gets a purple team. #ocsc    
    
    
    For more on Orlando's expansion: RT @wvhooligan: A couple more details on @OrlandoCitySC’s announcement next week: http://wvhooligan.com/2013/11/13/17682/orlando-city-confirms-will-next-mls-franchise/ …    
    
    
    @AdrianHealey That's a great way to put it.    
    
    
    Mexico and New Zealand going on. Lots of money, hopes, dreams and tequila riding on this. #MEXvNZL    
    
    
    Mexico dominating with its own dos a cero right now.    
    
    
    @Rlevine62 It's their language ... ;)    
    
    
    @rogbennett Maybe by then Australia will get to host a World Cup ... ;)    
    
    
    Imagine if Egypt and New Zealand came back from this WC play-off deficits to qualify... #wc2014 #mexvnzl #egypt    
    
    
    USMNT tends to renew contracts, but still a cool fact. RT @SoccerInsider: Mexico 4 coaches in 3 months. USA 4 coaches in 18 years.  #eltri    
    
    
    European soccer clubs spark discussion on religious tolerance http://bit.ly/HYZHjz  #ajax #celtic #ucl #championsleague #religion #thfc    
    
    
    Seattle's smart to try and move EJ. Invested a lot in Martins and Dempsey, and Neagle's on the up-climb. EJ might find money elsewhere. #mls    
    
    
    If TFC has trouble signing Gilardino or Eto'o, which is likely, maybe they should make a move for EJ. #tfc #mls    
    
    
    Plus Seattle is incredibly top-heavy. Move Johnson, find cap room and restructure the back and midfield. Good move for them. #ssfc #mls    
    
    
    Cool to see. RT @pauldalglish: Here you go. Each team in @mls is ranked based on final league position vs spending. pic.twitter.com/tGO2AUKpjL    
    
    
    I think I might have a late go at this #NaNoWriMo thing. I won't ever say that hashtag out-loud, though.    
    
    
    @halpal8 Well done.    
    
    
    Nice piece about how the EPL is losing creative play: http://www.soccernewsday.com/world/a/1411/creativity-disappearing-in-the-epl … #epl #bpl #premierleague    
    
    
    Is Australian soccer and the Socceroos heading into a new era? http://bit.ly/19mT8xU  #socceroos #australia    
    
    
    Looks like we've got a new @USLPRO team named. Oklahoma decides on @EnergyFC for its team name. Mix of Sounders/Dynamo. #uslpro #energyfc    
    
    
    OKC Energy is without better than OKC Wind. Wind, really?    
    
    
    So far the #LAGalaxy have been the most active offseason team. Signing players left and right. #mls    
    
    
    Tomorrow a very important game for the USMNT on multiple levels. Lots on the line for bubble players. #usmnt    
    
    
    First Naughty Mrs. Clause (eggnog latte) of the season. Courtesy of lordricci. http://instagram.com/p/gvbqHZP0MJ/     
    
    
    Canada down 1-0 to Czech Republic currently. Team has some established MLS players, but can't seem to ever get things going. #canMNT    
    
    
    It'd be nice to see a world where Canada, Mexico and the USA are the three top CONCACAF sides. Can it be done?    
    
    
    My thoughts ahead of #USMNT's match against Scotland later today: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1419/usmnt-report-building-a-blueprint-begins-in-glasgow … #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Exciting day of international matches. Doesn't get any bigger than USA/SCO and POR/SWE. Two fun clashes for fans. #usmnt #usavsco #porvswe    
    
    
    #USMNT lineup for #USAvSCO: GK - Howard. DEF - Evans, Gonzalez, Cameron, Beasley. MID - Bradley, Jones, Bedoya, Kljestan, EJ. FWD - Altidore    
    
    
    I'd expect EJ to move forward if US can't score. But looks like Klinsmann sticking with the 4-2-3-1 lineup. #USMNT    
    
    
    @davisjsn Diskerud tends to show himself more than Bedoya in USA games. Definitely would have liked to see him start today.    
    
    
    @davisjsn True. Kljestan disappears at points, too, so Mix would have fit in well there, like you said. We'll probably see him later.    
    
    
    @davisjsn Good point. I think both are on the bubble for World Cup so Klinsmann likely wants minutes for them both to measure value.    
    
    
    Cool graphic to see the visuals for today's #USMNT lineup, courtesy @ussoccer: pic.twitter.com/iTnytGn7eN    
    
    
    Altidore was successful in Holland for months without anything coming in a USA jersey. Same may be true for Johannsson. #USMNT    
    
    
    Speaking of Johannsson, kind of, here's a good piece by @JoshRobinson23 on Iceland and its success http://on.wsj.com/1aalFvb     
    
    
    Is it just me or does Hampden Park look empty? #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Have to say @AlexiLalas has a perfect 1970's mustache. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Don't get why USA makes these long crossing balls so early. Building up play might be the best method. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Maybe it's the cold Scotland weather, but Klinsmann is sporting his attire in recent months. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    So far, Scotland's been owning the ball in their half and the US is controlling the ball in their half. Back and forth. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    And a good #FF out to the @SoccerNewsday Team: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    Got off work and heard about 0-0 USA score. What a shame. #usmnt    
    
    
    US just got somewhat of a reality check. Can't succeed at the World Cup when you draw Scotland 0-0. #usmnt #usavsco    
    
    
    US was mostly reserves, but there's a certainly a level difference between the two sides. US, based on this year, should be above. #usmnt    
    
    
    @adifranco77 still think there's a huge difference between US and Scotland. American reserves should beat this Scotland team.    
    
    
    Spent the morning playing 7-on-7 in the midst of a light snow storm. Love the game in unfavorable conditions. #soccer #utah    
    
    
    @capasso10 Probably has to do with timing and the way specific stadiums work.    
    
    
    Good for Japan to draw Holland this weekend. Honda is a fantastic player for Japan. Definitely a player who needs to get into Europe.    
    
    
    About to settle down and watch/analyze #USMNT in #USAvSCO. Heard/read it's an average game with nothing exciting. We'll see.    
    
    
    Last night, FS1 had a commercial touting Germany vs. England as a match between two of world's best soccer teams. Seems a little much. #fifa    
    
    
    Nigeria and Ivory Coast have qualified for the World Cup. Both are strong African nations in recent years. #brazil #wc2014    
    
    
    Love how #OCSC is promoting this. RT @OrlandoCitySC: Two Days.  Be there--->http://on.fb.me/1j5yxna  #OrlandoIsReady pic.twitter.com/7Efu2LrCgx    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC I won't be there, unfortunately, but I'll be following along for sure. Are you live streaming the announcements?    
    
    
    @EvanReam @rosshard Should have been more clear. Meant into one of Europe's bigger leagues. UCL is fine, but needs better league to play in.    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC Great. Excited to hear what you guys got coming. ;)    
    
    
    @EvanReam @rosshard Poor mistake on my part not to clarify that. Thanks for catching!    
    
    
    Just finished USA/Scotland. No entertainment, slow, sleepy. 2nd half was better with Shea/Johannsson, but otherwise a weak showing. #usmnt    
    
    
    Had to watch the UFC ppv last night. Paint me a someone who prefers WWE/pro wrestling over MMA. #ufc #mma #wwe    
    
    
    What might this be that I'm working on? #novel #nanowrimo http://instagram.com/p/g1CGBiv0Cn/     
    
    
    Excited to see whether or not Orlando City changes their logo if/when they move to MLS. I'd expect a slight change. #ocsc    
    
    
    @GunnarBerndt I just like logo changes. And there's a lot of potential with the purple/red/gold and Lions, so it'd be fun to see.    
    
    
    Still believe Messi is the best player in the world (likely ever). But due to injuries this year, can't see him getting Ballon d'Or. #fifa    
    
    
    Used to cover UM. RT @BleacherReport: VIDEO: UMass' Raphiael Putney throws down a massive dunk vs. Youngstown State http://bit.ly/1b3JGpv     
    
    
    Underreported/talked about story: Chivas USA fell 1-0 to FC Tucson, a #uslpro side.    
    
    
    My thoughts on the USA's 0-0 draw with Scotland: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1422/usmnt-report-throwaway-game-in-glasgow … #USMNT    
    
    
    Miami Kings SC. Thoughts?    
    
    
    Orlando Health and Orlando City SC Announce Historic Agreement http://orlandocitysoccer.com/news/?article_id=1653 … #ocsc    
    
    
    Qatar World Cup is just becoming a bigger problem by the day: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-24980013# …!    
    
    
    The NYCFC fan movement ad is really well done, but it probably turned off all Manchester United fans. Give/take for the team. #nycfc #mcfc    
    
    
    USMNT Report: Throwaway Game in Glasgow http://bit.ly/17DJyqE  #usmnt #usa #usasoccer #usavsco #scotland #fifa #concacaf #USMNTReport    
    
    
    That USA/Mexico combo jersey is the greatest ugly Christmas sweater I've seen. #usmnt #eltri    
    
    
    Anyone know what Orlando City SC's big announcement for tomorrow is? #ocsc #gocity #mls #uslpro    
    
    
    Big day of soccer ahead. USA takes on Austria and Orlando City makes a "major" announcement. Keep eyes peeled to Twitter. #usmnt #ocsc #mls    
    
    
    Thoughts ahead of today's #USMNT contest with Austria: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1426/usmnt-report-a-second-chance-in-austria … #usavaut    
    
    
    Whether or not LeBron joins Beckham for Miami franchise, recent discussions have brought MLS and the future team publicity. #mls    
    
    
    Sydney Leroux joining Reign FC. Sad to see her leave my home state, but Seattle can surely use her talents after last season. #nwsl    
    
    
    Egypt playing Ghana right now in WCQ play-off. Egypt up 1-0, making it 2-6 aggregate. #EgyptVsGhana    
    
    
    The #USMNT starting team: Howard; Cameron, Gonzalez, Brooks, Beasley; Bradley, Jones; Bedoya, Johannsson, Shea; Altidore #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Smart move to include Shea and Johannsson, who can make plays at times and brought energy in last match. Still not sure about Bedoya. #USMNT    
    
    
    NBC Sports broadcasts are top notch. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Nice play from Austria so far. USA seems in control, but Austria looks one or two breaks away from getting past the Americans. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    I really think there's a difference in skill when the USA plays with the Waldo jerseys and when they play in plain white. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Wow. What skill from Austria right now. Dumbing the USA. If someone was at that far post, it would have been a sure goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Nice shot from Jozy there. A little too far out for him, but still a nice chance at goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Great one-touch play from the US there, capped with an excellent shot from Johannsson. This is a better-moving US side. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Replays showing that was as close to a goal as you'll get without it being a goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Alaba a good player, surprised he couldn't get that off. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Gonzalez with two great plays. Well done. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    And it's 1-0 Austria. Janko scores. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Not impressed with Brooks so far. He's young and far from fully developed, but more of a problem for USA's starting lineup. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    You realize how poor the USA plays without Donovan, Dempsey with a game like this. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    HT: Austria 1 - 0 USA. Tough half for the USA. No one playing with that extra step. Backline -- Omar decent, but Brooks poor. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    USA needs to work on finishing and creating play. Should move Johannsson to striker with Altidore and put Diskerud in the middle. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Diskerud on for Johannsson and EJ for Shea. Decent dubs, but would have liked to see Jones taken off. Hot-headed. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Boyd with a good attempt there. Nice shot. Would have liked to score there. EJ and Diskerud adding a bit of flavor to this lineup. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Bradley whiffs that volley. USA searching for a goal. Altidore with a decent shot, but not powerful or high enough. Low. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Kljestan comes in for Bedoya. Still not sure what Klinsmann seems him in a USA jersey. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Crazy things going on in Sweden/Portugal. Ibra with two goals, Ronaldo with two goals. Insane.    
    
    
    USA had something good going there for awhile with attacking play, but seems to have dropped off in the last 10 minutes. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    And that's it: USA falls to Austria 1-0 in Vienna. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    USA's year went from low to high to higher to low. Fair. #USAvAUT #USMNT    
    
    
    So with Alonso being signed to a DP contract, likely EJ will be shopped around and moved. He probably wanted DP money. #ssfc #usmnt    
    
    
    Great image. RT @ESPNFC: Only two WC2014 spots left up for grabs. Here's how they will line up in Brazil next summer. pic.twitter.com/lT3pp0Z2Sj    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan The draw this year seems mighty tough for all teams, really. Exciting stuff!    
    
    
    Would be kind of funny if @OrlandoCitySC pulled one from under the rug and said they were joining the #NASL. #mls21 #ocsc    
    
    
    @AndrewDasNYT LOL. An intern must have pasted the wrong logo for all the banners, so they decided to run with it.    
    
    
    Young journos: Make sure to check out the USA TODAY collegiate correspondent program. Helps immensely! http://www.usatodayeducate.com/staging/index.php/collegiate-correspondent-program … #journalism    
    
    
    If #OCSC joins MLS (still if, technically), i can't wait to see a sea of purple in the stands. Such a cool color for a soccer club.    
    
    
    I'm not in Orlando. I'm only following this through Twitter. But #OCSC's jump to MLS has got me feeling like a giddy boy on XMas. Awesome.    
    
    
    @djonesjax Thanks, I saw that. I'm trying night to get too distracted ;)    
    
    
    Watching live now. Orlando City about to be announced as #MLS21. Exciting stuff. #OCSC    
    
    
    "The Beautiful Game to the City Beautiful." #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    Add Orlando? Check. #MLS21 #mls    
    
    
    "We Want Kaka" chants. Kaka would be cool for Orlando, but he's injury-prone. But good for marketing/promotion. #OCSC    
    
    
    Confirmed: Chivas USA, NE Revs and SJ Quakes have the worst logos in #MLS.    
    
    
    Garber making his way to the stage on Orlando. #MLS21    
    
    
    Garber's added the scarf. #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    "The when is now" - Garber #OCSC #MLS21    
    
    
    "It was about all you purple people." - Don Garber. #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    11th expansion team in 10 years, says Garber. Can't expect them to slow down. #mls21 #mls #OCSC    
    
    
    "With #OCSC we will show the rest of the world that our country is leading the game." #mls21 #mls    
    
    
    And it's official. @OrlandoCitySC has been announced as MLS's 21st team.  Congrats to Orlando and its fans. #ocsc #orlandoisready #mls21    
    
    
    Exciting thought: We now get two new teams for FIFA16. #ocsc #mls21 #fifa    
    
    
    @greypaul such a shame!    
    
    
    @jrstlouis That's certainly a concern, given how some MLS teams play now. Hopefully players are found abroad and within the US with talent.    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC Major.    
    
    
    MLS can only grow with more teams. More teams means more markets, more TV deals, more supporters, more cash. Excited to see the growth. #mls    
    
    
    @jrstlouis I think European players are being overpaid in Europe, too ;) Either way, just exciting to have pro soccer in a new city.    
    
    
    @jrstlouis Agreed. We'll see how it turns out!    
    
    
    No matter if OCSC, NYCFC, Beckham's potential Miami - there's going to be divide about expansion. Fun to see new teams if done right. #mls    
    
    
    Brad Evans: A Gold Cup midfielder, not a World Cup defender. #USMNT    
    
    
    Thinking about #USMNT and just realizing that Klinsmann moves so many players around it's impossible to know where everyone will play.    
    
    
    Jones, Bedoya didn't do much for USA. Par for the course. Replace with Beckerman and Zusi for WC. Klinsmann will probably keep Jones. #usmnt    
    
    
    @BuckiNick7 I believe that's where he plays club so could work.    
    
    
    @chisokrkid77 I'd put Beckerman ahead of Jones.    
    
    
    @ZacWassink starts at 1 a.m. EST, right? Hmmm... 1:01.    
    
    
    @ZacWassink @DohertySoccer I'm an optimist.    
    
    
    So what happens when Orlando City SC comes to Salt Lake City, and the Lions have to contend with Leo the Lion? #rsl #ocsc #mls    
    
    
    Final thoughts: Great day for soccer. #USMNT game, #ocsc officially joining #MLS, Ibra/Ronaldo go punch-for-punch, Houston/#NWSL? Love it.    
    
    
    Totally went hashtag overload in that last tweet. Pardon the #s.    
    
    
    Orlando has been awarded an MLS franchise to begin playing in 2015. Expected to bring in designated player. #mls #ocsc    
    
    
    Mexico qualified for the World Cup last night with a 4-2 (9-3) win over New Zealand. #eltri    
    
    
    RBNY/Sky Blue potential MLS/NWSL deal is a no-go, according to reports. #nwsl #rbny #sbfc    
    
    
    USMNT fell to Austria, 1-0, yesterday in Vienna to end the USA's 2013 calendar year schedule. #usmnt #usavaut    
    
    
    Speaking of the NWSL, Houston may be adding its own franchise, according to reports. #nwsl    
    
    
    My thoughts on the #USMNT loss yesterday: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1429/usmnt-report-year-ends-with-a-whimper …    
    
    
    Interesting article about how valuable #MLS teams are: http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrissmith/2013/11/20/major-league-soccers-most-valuable-teams/ …    
    
    
    Great article on what MLS can do to fix the playoffs: http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/soccer-insider/wp/2013/11/20/mlss-disappearing-act/# …! #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Idea: MLS could keep two conferences, but just change the names. Make them general (American/National or A/B, 1/2). #mls    
    
    
    Respect Steve Nicol. But the style of play he promoted at NE Revs was nowhere near as fun to see as Timbers/RSL. Can't agree with him. #MLS    
    
    
    @JeffreyCarlisle @WilliamMathis1 @VoxFossili True. Jones capable of good ball in attack. But he's too inconsistent for me. Just my 2 cents!    
    
    
    Jones over Cameron in the defensive midfielder role, and will likely start come WC time. Think Beckerman would be better there. #usmnt    
    
    
    Get amped. RT @PCarrESPN: FIFA hasn't announced the full draw format, but here are the projected pots for Dec. 6: pic.twitter.com/CPaSala35k    
    
    
    What might really hurt the USMNT at the World Cup is the group. Team is shaky, but these groups are going to be tough. #usmnt #wc2014    
    
    
    If you're Bob Bradley, do you come back to MLS or try and make it as a manager in Europe? #mls #bobbradley    
    
    
    Why retailers open or close their doors on Sunday http://bit.ly/1fmJeEP  #business #amazon #verizon #hobbylobby #smallbusiness #sunday    
    
    
    Getting ready to leave my first ever #USMNT game more than 8 years ago. Wow. #usa #ussoccer http://instagram.com/p/g-8dSWv0Lg/     
    
    
    Getting ready to leave my first ever #USMNT game more than 8 years ago. Wow. #usa #ussoccer #tbt… http://instagram.com/p/g-8dSWv0Lg/     
    
    
    So Native Americans originated from Europe? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-25020958 …    
    
    
    @wvhooligan @BrianStraus Agree. 2014 is loaded with talented teams, and the draw looks to create difficult groups. Excited for the piece.    
    
    
    If you can't beat them, cut 10 of your players and figure out a way to rebuild, I guess. #chivasusa #mls    
    
    
    Figured it out: TFC has signed Hulk Hogan! #tfc #mls    
    
    
    I get Ricketts has won a Goalkeeper of the Year and is up for it again this year, but he's never overwhelmingly impressed me. #rctid #mls    
    
    
    @theaxepdx This year he's been great without a doubt. Just never taken interest in him over the past couple of the years.    
    
    
    Love what Houston is doing in regards to possible #NWSL expansion. Refundable deposits. Gauges interest and cash. Cool stuff.    
    
    
    And you really can't go wrong with a $25 season ticket. Such a steal. #houstondynamo #NWSL    
    
    
    Can't help a little bit of holiday joy with each sip of a Nighty Mrs. Clause (Eggnog Latte).    
    
    
    Check out the @SoccerNewsday staff's choices for 2013 MLS Year End Awards: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1439/sn-picks-2013-mls-year-end-awards … #mls #mlsawards #mlsmvp #mlsroy    
    
    
    Missed this ESPN FC story situation. Can someone fill me in?    
    
    
    @ETNMcCracken Thanks Sean. Unfortunate stuff from ESPN.    
    
    
    SN Picks!: 2013 MLS Year End Awards http://bit.ly/1bIIQK6  #mls #mlsawards #mlsmvp #mlsroy #usa #ussoccer #SNPicks    
    
    
    Have to give a #FF to the excellent @SoccerNewsday staff. Check them out here: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    Debating whether to get into the Hunger Games madness and see the movies/read the books. I probably won't. #hungergames #catchingfire    
    
    
    And @PhilSchoen gets it right in his latest article on the #USMNT. Good read: http://bit.ly/1i2qg8h     
    
    
    Agreed. RT @ETNMcCracken: It's this sort of myopic, self-serving work that unfairly makes all sports reporting (and journalism) look bad.    
    
    
    Remind all your friends, family, co-workers, Tweeps, FB buds, Snapchat friends, Instagramers that the MLS playoffs return this weekend!    
    
    
    On Saturday, Herb is proud to run on Dunkin. #dunkin #dd #breakfast http://instagram.com/p/hELY2rP0Gc/     
    
    
    Woke up to all these Messi transfer rumors. Never count it out, but can't see #Barca getting rid of him. Would be fun to see where he goes.    
    
    
    Wait a tick ... is Toronto FC signing Messi?  #messi #tfc #yeahright    
    
    
    Been asked a few times to predict Sporting KC vs. Houston. Tough call to make. SKC is at home, but Houston's home is the playoffs. #mls    
    
    
    Settling in for #SKCvHOU. Exciting game. Not sure if Houston will do as Well given no Bruin/Clark.    
    
    
    SKC atmosphere is very impressive. Fans look excited, thrilled. Nice tifo, fireworks. Great image of the league. #mlsplayoffs #mls #SKCvHOU    
    
    
    Wow. 22 degrees in Kansas City. Get the gloves out boys. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Would you expect anything else from Houston? Complete spoilers. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Houston Dynamo is like that guy that ruined the ending of Harry Potter for you. #SKCvHOU #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    We've got ourselves a game here fellers. Excellent and exciting game so far. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    First leg of Houston and SKC was dreadful,  boring and lackluster. This one has that extra punch and style. Love it. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Sporting KC would host one hell of an MLS Cup. #skcvhou #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Sporting KC in the Dwyers seat. Right? Right? #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    SKC fans want this so bad. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Congratulations to Sporting KC - MLS Eastern Conference Champions. #mls #mlsplayoffs #SKCvHOU    
    
    
    2013 - The Year of Sporting KC #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Woke up the sweet sounds of Manchester United and Cardiff. Nice kick-off to the day. #epl #BPLonNBC    
    
    
    Wonder what SKC/HOU would have been like with Clark and Bruin. Dynamo had chances, so with that fire, maybe a different result. #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    That awkward moment when Messi and Ronaldo are BOTH injured.    
    
    
    Hear my thoughts on #RSLvPOR around the 10-minute mark here: http://sportsathome.webs.com/apps/videos/vi … #rsl #rctid #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    @readmyfunny Thanks for clicking! It's not my website, I spoke on the radio show. Definitely give the podcasts a listen. They're good stuff.    
    
    
    In honor of RSL's playoff game tonight,  here's a photo I took at a game a couple of years back. #rsl… http://instagram.com/p/hHepI7P0DC/     
    
    
    What are your pre-game thoughts about #RSLvPOR?    
    
    
    RSL has the advantage, but it's not unrealistic for Portland to snag two goals. Three, tough. Extra time wouldn't surprise me. #RSLvPOR    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan What temp we got there in Portlandia?    
    
    
    Last game before the final game. Like a good TV show, penultimate is always straight fire. Time to enjoy. #rslvpor    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan @MichaelOrrFtbl @dan_itel As a former northeastern resident - keep your hands, ears and head warm buddies. Enjoy the game!    
    
    
    Man. Portland game looks amazing. Raucous fans, great play. Just a great image of MLS. #mlsplayoffs #mls #rslvpor    
    
    
    Portland really needs a goal to make this interesting. #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs #mls    
    
    
    Findley doesn't give up. Salt Lake up 5-2 on aggregate. #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    And there you have it. Real Salt Lake - 2013 Western Conference Champions #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Whoever Toronto FC signs this week, not sure it'll be enough to fix the franchise. #tfc #torontofc #mls    
    
    
    My alma mater. RT @steve_hewitt: UMass basketball is ranked No. 24 in this week's AP Top 25 poll, its first ranking in the poll since 1998.    
    
    
    Anyone else having "Defying Gravity" by Wicked stuck in their heads? Anyone? No? Just me? OK.    
    
    
    Major League Soccer reveals 2014 regular season schedule, with two-week break for World Cup: http://www.mlssoccer.com/news/article/2013/11/25/major-league-soccer-reveals-2014-regular-season-schedule-two-week-break-worl?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=news&utm_campaign=paid … #mls    
    
    
    Feel like more was expected out of Maximiliano Rodríguez. But Waiver Draft list is weak. Not sure who the sleepers are. #mls    
    
    
    Michael Bradley at rightback? Don't count on it. #USMNT    
    
    
    And Dillion Powers was voted as Rookie of the Year. Deserved. #mlsroy #rapids    
    
    
    MLS's rookie class of 2013 was stellar. All solid players in the league now. #mls    
    
    
    'Death of the Family' is grim, dark and full of twists http://bit.ly/1cLK5d3  #batman #joker #deathofthefamily #dccomics #dc #comics    
    
    
    Just discovered the book "Amish Vampires in Space."    
    
    
    Never thought I would see gas in the $2 range again. http://instagram.com/p/hL3Yv2P0Hk/     
    
    
    Revs, Union, Fire, DC and Dallas all vying for Eddie Johnson it seems. Looks like he's likely heading east: http://www.goal.com/en-us/news/1110/major-league-soccer/2013/11/25/4433158/mls-wrap-eddie-johnson-sweepstakes-underway?ICID=OP … #mls    
    
    
    Thinking about 2013 MLS season, and SKC/RSL makes a lot of sense for a final. #MLSCup #mls    
    
    
    Can't believe I'm saying this, but the race for the EPL title is wide-open. Top 9 spots have legitimate shot. #epl    
    
    
    TFC signing Defoe (and another striker) will make another top-heavy MLS side. Teams in 2013 showed strong midfield is key to winning. #mls    
    
    
    Seattle, LA Galaxy both top heavy teams. Appealing to fans, owners, TV stations, but does little to succeed. Example is this season. #MLS    
    
    
    That said, I can't say I'm not excited to see Defoe in a TFC uniform. A recognizable, proven EPL player in MLS. Exciting. #mls    
    
    
    True, but they had a certain world class midfielder ... RT @TheMikeDonovan: @hscribner LA Galaxy did win last 2 titles though    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan LOL. Make that two world class midfielders ;)    
    
    
    RBNY also sort of top heavy with Cahill/Henry, but this year they had a lot of working parts, including Olave in the back. #rbny #mls    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan He also brings intangibles that others certainly don't. Leadership, presence, etc., that helped LA surely.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan Oh, no. I meant like forwards/strikers/attackers.    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp I clicked the link, but I'm not going to read the article out of fear that I may like PB more than I should.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan Oh, definitely. Impact, too, to an extent. Difference is LA/Seattle spent big money on its forwards/attackers.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan No doubt. They just really stick out due to lack of production from Demps/Martins.    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp I recently agreed wholeheartedly with this one: http://www.buzzfeed.com/jeremybender/struggles-of-being-23 …    
    
    
    EJ definitely a striker worth grabbing if club has money/resources to please Seattle. He scores, knows the league.  Attitude a problem. #mls    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp Not sure whether to be weirded out or impressed. Probably the latter because I'm from this place: http://www.buzzfeed.com/adamdavis/foods-that-new-england-does-better-than-anywhere-else …    
    
    
    @Ben_Jata Good point. Lot of the current criticism is about the pay me stuff. So once paid that should disappear.    
    
    
    @Jonny_Soccerly It's very good. Usually a 4-5 horse race. Wide-open this year. Has a lot to do with Moyes taking over for ManU.    
    
    
    Situation sucks, but the #MLSTicketGate hashtag is hilarious.    
    
    
    Stadium collapse in Brazil. Reportedly 3 killed. Stadium is supposed to host 2014 World Cup opener. #wc2014    
    
    
    Anybody else feel like today is eerily similar to a half day of school? I'm not in school, but it has that vibe. #thanksgiving    
    
    
    And one other thought: I really want to see "Frozen" now that I know Idina Menzel voices a character. She's awesome in so many ways. #Frozen    
    
    
    Black Friday - The Day When Singing Christmas Songs Becomes Socially Acceptable    
    
    
    Well #ThanksToSoccer I've made some incredible friends and found a job I love doing. Thank you.    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving everyone!    
    
    
    Unreal that TicketGate extended past just the Ticketmaster situation and has spiraled out of control. Unfortunate for buyers/fans. #rsl #mls    
    
    
    @halpal8 Your Thanksgiving tweets have been hilarious.    
    
    
    Fun stuff here. Give it a read! RT @jrstlouis: Hey!  It's 'Drunken Thanksgiving WC Draw 2014'.  RT appreciated!!  http://bit.ly/1il7xoQ     
    
    
    And cue the mountain of ice cream. #icecream #sundae #foodporn http://instagram.com/p/hUzEvEP0Np/     
    
    
    Would be fun to see Donovan and Dempsey play together for Everton in January. #usmnt    
    
    
    December.    
    
    
    Stoked for the Christmas season and all the festivities this time of year brings. Let's finish out the year with love, passion and lights.    
    
    
    Holiday Heisenberg. #breakingbad #bb #heisenberg #walterwhite #holidays #christmas http://instagram.com/p/hZYI3rv0KS/     
    
    
    Introducing your MLS Coach of the Year -- Caleb Porter. Deserved. Finishes ahead of Petke, Kreis and Pareja in that order. #mls    
    
    
    Road to the World Cup begins on Feb. 1 when the USA takes on South Korea at the StubHub Center in Carson, Calif.: http://www.ussoccer.com/News/Mens-National-Team/2013/12/131202-MNT-v-Korea-Republic.aspx …    
    
    
    Solid warm-up match for the #USMNT. Should be a good indicator of where the US stands among other teams.    
    
    
    Nature of modern day journalism calls for things like Kreis/NYCFC report today. 24/7 news cycle asks for constant information. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    It's also important to remember nothing has been confirmed about Kreis going to NYCFC. Things change in an instant. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    Kreis possibly moving is a part of the story. Means it may be his final MLS Cup with RSL, and means he may not coach in 2014. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    World Cup pots as expected. Dangerous draw possibilities for the USA. In most cases, they're battling for 2nd/3rd spot in groups. #WC2014    
    
    
    Don't forget MLS State of the League address is today. Garber likely to talk expansion (MIA/ORL), MLS Cup and 2014 season. #mls    
    
    
    People forget how big of a country Brazil is. Nearly as big as USA and China. Distances traveled for upcoming WC will be large. #WC2014    
    
    
    @EvanReam @robertjonas @SacRepublicFC Really love those kits. Hope they're the real deal.    
    
    
    MLS State of the League is live here: http://www.mlssoccer.com/mlscup/2013/state-of-the-league?utm_source=Twitter&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=News&utm_campaign=Paid … #mls    
    
    
    Garber praising RSL ahead of MLS Cup. Talking history and how the team has done in recent years since it  came into MLS in 2005. #mls    
    
    
    Garber proud of Sporting KC's turnaround since the darker days of the Wizards. Encourages everyone to see Sporting Park. #mls    
    
    
    Garber says he wants MLS to be one of the top soccer leagues in the world by 2022. #mls    
    
    
    Don't cross the line - unless you're Steven Lenhart. #mls    
    
    
    Garber talking stadium development. #mls    
    
    
    Garber - 10 teams in 2004, 21 by 2015, 24 by 2020. What a growth. #mls    
    
    
    Garber: MLS currently in talks with owners from Atlanta and Miami. #mls    
    
    
    Garber says there's a lot of work needed for Atlanta and Miami, but MLS is looking to the southeast for expansion teams. #mls    
    
    
    "This country can really love this game." - Don Garber on USA soccer culture. #mls    
    
    
    Garber said USA winning the World Cup would help build league, USSF, college soccer, etc. #mls    
    
    
    Alan Black of SF Chron. asking a fantasy question. Donovan coaches USMNT, WC in India, MLS one of the top 5 leagues in world. Uhh... #mls    
    
    
    Garber talking MIA. Excited to have Beckham as an owner, and thrilled if Miami is MLS 22nd team. "A lot of work that needs to happen." #mls    
    
    
    "We can't go to Miami without the right stadium situation." - Don Garber #mls #mlstomiami    
    
    
    Garber said he wants to work with Beckham and Simon Fuller as quick as possible to get the best deal. #mls    
    
    
    Garber says Tim Leiweke can turn Toronto FC around. #mls #tfc    
    
    
    Garber explaining a winter schedule is in consideration. But playing in February in TOR/VAN/, as well as an extended break, are issues. #mls    
    
    
    Agenda item 13.5 is big for FIFA this week. Puts FIFA members under legal status:  http://keirradnedge.com/2013/12/03/point-13-5-the-agenda-item-putting-fifa-exco-members-on-their-best-behaviour/# …!    
    
    
    USA barely got out of the group stage in 2010 World Cup with an easy draw. Horizon looks bleak for this year's squad. #usmnt    
    
    
    MLS Best XI is a 3-4-3? You mean it's not a 4-2-3-1? You mean attacking/aggressive midfielders were highlighted? Awesome. #mls    
    
    
    @cargold21 Turn it off?    
    
    
    New World Cup ball looks like it belongs in 2010. #fifa #wc2014    
    
    
    Rimando definitely deserved Goalkeeper of the Year for 2013. Ricketts was solid, but was shaky more often than Nick. #mls    
    
    
    Should be in Kansas City this weekend for MLS Cup. Let me know if you'll be around. #mls #mlscup    
    
    
    What a sweet goal. RT @BrianStraus: Get it while it's hot. Jozy Altidore's goal against Chelsea: http://youtu.be/ZEkECTkCFQU     
    
    
    Luis Suarez just set the standard for hat tricks today. Three beautiful goals. Fantastic player. #suarez #epl    
    
    
    Everton.    
    
    
    Everton up 1-0 on Manchester United. ManUtd's manager David Moyer previously coached for Everton. #efc #mufc    
    
    
    Oh, Moyes. Poor Moyes.    
    
    
    Cant imagine how good a Aguero/Messi combo would be at Barca. Phew. #barca    
    
    
    Solid 9. #winter #slc #saltlakecity #utah http://instagram.com/p/hi0H-jv0NS/     
    
    
    Mike Magge has won the MLS MVP Award. Deserved for regular season performance. Didn't make playoffs, but transformed Chicago. #cf97 #mls    
    
    
    Why the MLS Cup Final matchup between SKC and RSL makes sense: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1469/this-mls-cup-matchup-makes-sense … #mlscup #mls    
    
    
    Excited for my journey to Kansas City this weekend. Going there for the first time ever. Soccer, family and fun atmosphere. #MLSCup    
    
    
    @RedStaplerGuy I hear the steak is outrageous. Excited to try authentic KC BBQ sauce/food. By the way, love your Twitter handle name.    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp Thanks! I'm excited to get a glimpse at Sporting Park. That's if my scarf and hat combo doesn't cover my whole face.    
    
    
    Appears TFC has A-level and B-level DPs in mind. Might make sense to spring for a couple B players than 1 or 2 As for success in MLS. #mls    
    
    
    This MLS Cup Matchup Makes Sense http://bit.ly/IKiAHL  #skc #sportingkc #realsaltlake #rsl #rslvskc #mlscup #mlscup2013 #mlsplayoffs #mls    
    
    
    So @SacRepublicFC kit released today. Love the color arrangements seen here: http://shop.sacrepublicfc.com/collections/kits … #uslpro    
    
    
    RIP Nelson Mandela. What a difference you made for South Africa, and the world.    
    
    
    2022 World Cup host Qatar under fire for labor 'abuses' http://bit.ly/1cdxsGj  #qatar #fifa #wc2022 #qatar2022    
    
    
    Just told a good Canadian pal of mine that I'm headed to MLS Cup this weekend. Her response?: "Why is it so late?" Perfectly put. #MLSCup    
    
    
    Here's the NY Times' obituary of Nelson Mandela. Excellent as always: http://www.nytimes.com/2013/12/06/world/africa/nelson-mandela_obit.html?smid=tw-share …    
    
    
    Hard for USA to advance past group stage. Pots 1/4 are STACKED except for England/Bosnia/Croatia (who are all on US' level, if not higher).    
    
    
    Kind words from a MVP candidate. RT @divaio9: Magic Mike Magee #MVP well deserved! And now we all get ready for next #mls  season kick off!    
    
    
    Seems people are split between watching Nelson Mandela coverage, football and Sound of Music live broadcast.    
    
    
    It's been said before, but one of the most inspiring things about Mandela is that he gave up his power willingly. Amazing man. #RIPMandela    
    
    
    World Cup Draw today. Who else is excited?! #wc2014 #worldcupdraw    
    
    
    At Salt Lake International about to head out towards Kansas City dor MLS Cup 2013. #mls #mlscup #rsl… http://instagram.com/p/hlMrJeP0MB/     
    
    
    Got a good amount of RSL fans here at SLC airport heading to Denver (and eventually KC). #mls #mlscup #rsl    
    
    
    World Cup Draw about to kick off. Who ya got? #WorldCupDraw    
    
    
    Germany and Ghana. You can't make this stuff up. #usmnt    
    
    
    Holland/Chile/Spain another hard group. Uruguay/Italy/England will be fun. Exciting World Cup ahead. #worldcupdraw    
    
    
    First stop - Omaha. Outside Creighton University's soccer stadium. #omaha #creigton #ontheroad #mlscup http://instagram.com/p/hl3LAnP0Jw/     
    
    
    Take a look at the World Cup Draw: RT @ESPNFC: Here is the World Cup Draw in full, all 8 Groups.

#WCDraw pic.twitter.com/C6JVcbHsoS"    
    
    
    What are your thoughts on the USA's draw? #usmnt    
    
    
    8,886 WC miles. 8,886 moments to play. 8,886 WC miles. 8,886 for the USA. Cuz of the draw (x2). Cuz of the draw. (Sang to Rent song) #USMNT    
    
    
    It's #MLSCup Day. Grab your scarves, hats, gloves, mittens, handwarmers, long johns, ski masks, snow pants and love for soccer! #skc #rsl    
    
    
    Left Omaha and now en route to Kansas City for the #MLSCup. Smelling BBQ sauce already. #skc #rsl    
    
    
    Kansas City is ready. #mlscup #mls #skcvrsl #skc #rsl http://instagram.com/p/hoEPeZv0KK/     
    
    
    Hello, Kansas City. #kc #kansascity #mlscup #mls http://instagram.com/p/hoK5QDv0GQ/     
    
    
    At Oklahoma Joe's in Kansas City. Place is popping with RSL fans. #mlscup #rsl #skc #rslvskc    
    
    
    Let the MLS Cup begin. #mlscup #mls http://instagram.com/p/homRoZP0Kx/     
    
    
    What a half. Can't feel my fingers. Sporting Park is the real deal. Let's see what happens here. #mlscup #mls #skcvrsl    
    
    
    RSL struggled to find offense last night. Fun game, too physical at points. But KC controlled a lot. Deserved the win. #MLSCup #rsl #skc    
    
    
    Lots of interesting stuff out of KC. Environment and atmosphere was top notch. Fun banter between RSL and SKC fans. Good stuff. #mls #mlscup    
    
    
    Something definitely learned last night at the MLS Cup: The USA needs to bring Zusi and Beckerman to Brazil. #mls #usmnt    
    
    
    Penalties are a tough way to decide a champion. But this was definitely The Year of #SKC from beginning to end without a doubt. #mls #mlscup    
    
    
    Weird to think the MLS season is over. What now? #mls    
    
    
    @JessMarkland No. :)    
    
    
    We decided to build a RSL volcano last night. Metaphor. #rsl #realsaltlake #mls #mlscup http://instagram.com/p/htNiZjP0Gl/     
    
    
    Imagine if #MLSCup was played on Saturday in Sandy, Utah. It was snowing like crazy all day. Would have been much worse a final.    
    
    
    Just goes to show #MLS can't host the Cup Final in December. Need to change that.    
    
    
    Columbus Crew re-sign Oduro. Great move. Necessary player for the club's development. #Crew96    
    
    
    The Red Sox just won the World Series. Why is everyone leaving? Baseball fans, explain this. #redsox #mlb    
    
    
    Space and religion: How believers view latest space developments http://bit.ly/1fdVVzb  #space #religion #galaxy #faith #universe #earth    
    
    
    FC Dallas trades Jackson to Toronto FC for an unknown amount of cash. Good move for TFC. Jackson can be solid for them. #fcd #tfc #mls    
    
    
    Jackson's only 25, which is a step up from some of the older players Toronto has been in talks with. Could work well. #tfc #mls    
    
    
    Kenny Cooper also gone from FC Dallas. Deal couldn't be reached. Will be eligible for the MLS Re-Entry Draft. Big move. #mls #fcdallas    
    
    
    Boy, that escalated quickly. Michael Gspurning's contract option was declined by Seattle. Somebody should snatch him up. Top keeper. #mls    
    
    
    MLS unveiled the 68 eligible player for the Re-Entry draft: http://www.mlssoccer.com/news/article/2013/12/09/major-league-soccer-unveils-list-eligible-players-december-re-entry-draft …    
    
    
    Solid group of players in the Re-Entry draft. You could build a pretty decent squad out of that pot. #mls    
    
    
    Christmas Party on the top floor of the Zions Bank building in downtown Salt Lake. #slc #saltlakecity… http://instagram.com/p/huYUwTP0GJ/     
    
    
    It's sad when you actually want 40 degree weather. This single digit stuff is just not cool, Mother Nature. #utah #slc #saltlakecity    
    
    
    Garber says no chance of Chivas being contracted or moved. Attendance is down, likely will only get worse. Black eye for the league. #mls    
    
    
    If Eto'o does come to MLS, hope it's to a lesser team that could benefit from exposure - like Fire, DCU, Chivas even. #mls    
    
    
    World Cup 2014 in Brazil: "All in One Rhythm." .... except for the rioters outside the stadiums. NBD. #brazil #wc2014    
    
    
    Jason Kreis will leave RSL for NYCFC. Big moment in the history of MLS and RSL. #mls #rsl #nycfc    
    
    
    Kreis certainly the coach NYCFC wants. Has a style, winning coach in the league, etc. Great move for them. Will hurt RSL tremendously. #mls    
    
    
    Wonder if Kreis knew about the move during MLS Cup. Kind of hard to make that decision in 1-2 days. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    @AlexiLalas @ESPNFC Glad you went with the diamond midfield instead of a 4-2-3-1. Nice moves.    
    
    
    Have to imagine tremendous pressure will be on Kreis to succeed at NYCFC. A lot more than SLC. I'd say instant results are expected. #mls    
    
    
    Also important to remember that RSL's assistant head coach, C.J. Brown, is headed to the Chicago Fire.  Another piece leaving. #RSL #mls    
    
    
    Miami Beckham United ... what a name that would be. Definitely the RBNY of the southeast. #mls #mlstomiami    
    
    
    Kreis' introduction to Man City culture shows direction NYCFC will take. Heavy MCFC influence. #nycfc    
    
    
    Rosales leaving Sounders FC is unreal. He's such a good player with leadership capabilities. Any team that grabs him is lucky. #mls    
    
    
    SKC's missing a good striker. If EJ made it back, KC would be on a whole new level. EJ/Zusi combo would work wonders. #mls #usmnt    
    
    
    Just saw the Barca highlights. Oofa. That third goal was pure beauty. Well done. #barca #ucl    
    
    
    Is it really about the small teams? NYCFC might break that mold. http://www.ussoccerplayers.com/2013/12/the-wait-for-nycfc.html# …!    
    
    
    @edencreamer Thanks for the follow. My followers list just got an injection of swagger.    
    
    
    Chivas USA trades for Rosales for Bowen and No. 2 Allocation pick. Might have been able to scoop him up in the Re-Entry draft. #chivasusa    
    
    
    Mauro Rosales is an Argentine, for the record. #chivasusa    
    
    
    TFC and Chivas usa both make solid trades this week. Looks like they're heading in the right direction. Slowly. Very slowly. #tfc #cusa #mls    
    
    
    Probably not a good idea to charge journalists (who don't make a lot of money as it is) for exclusive interviews. #mls #nufc    
    
    
    #USMNT manager Jurgen Klinsmann will remain as USA coach through 2018.    
    
    
    These trades are coming out like wildfire. #mls    
    
    
    The best thing about Steve Zakuani moving to Portland is we'll get a new Windows ad before MLS highlight videos. Hopefully. #mls    
    
    
    They say deaths come in threes. I say the same for major soccer news. #nwsl #mls #usmnt    
    
    
    Love that Houston has a NWSL side. League will grow with more teams. Support has been great, too. Can't wait to it. #nwsl #nwslinhouston    
    
    
    Anyone have an update on TFC's biggest signing in MLS history? #tfc #falsehopes    
    
    
    Arena, Bradley and Klinsmann -- 3 #USMNT coaches in a row that got the extension. Hopefully for 2022 we see Kreis/Porter vying for the role.    
    
    
    Nice article by @LeanderOnFOX on Klinsmann extension, especially how previous USA coaches have done in 2nd terms: http://msn.foxsports.com/foxsoccer/usa/story/jurgen-klinsmann-contract-extension-promotion-makes-sense-on-all-levels-121213 …    
    
    
    Going on MySpace is like walking through a graveyard.    
    
    
    Leon's got a 2-0 lead in the Liga MX playoffs. American could easily comeback in 2nd leg, but will be tough one for sure. #ligamx    
    
    
    TFC has sold the rights of Bobby Convey to Red Bull New York. #mls    
    
    
    My thoughts on Klinsmann's extension, the World Cup Draw and how the #USMNT will fare in Brazil: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1492/usmnt-report-daunting-wc-draw-for-yanks …    
    
    
    Reading up on this Beyonce album drop. Interesting move to let the music stand on its own without pre-promotion/marketing. #beyonce    
    
    
    Porter unleashed: Portland Timbers trade Sal Zizzo to SKC for alllocation money. #skc #rctid    
    
    
    Defender Lovel Palmer will head to #CF97 from RSL for allocation money.    
    
    
    Gilberto - Young and dynamic, but unproven in a lot of ways. TFC fortunate to have him. Let's see if he succeeds. #tfc #torontofc    
    
    
    Dallas get Moffat and Seattle gets Kenny Cooper's rights? That's a really big trade. Why does Seattle want another forward, though? #mls    
    
    
    @theaxepdx But with Dempsey/Martins/Neagle and then add in Cooper, still pretty top heavy.    
    
    
    @theaxepdx Makes sense if Martins moves for sure.    
    
    
    Sad to hear about Arapahoe High School. Thoughts are with everyone affected.    
    
    
    Looks like Portland Timbers will ahead to the CCL ahead of RSL. Bad day for Salt Lakers. #rsl #rctid    
    
    
    Knowing RSL, they'll comeback next year and complete the North American 'treble.' #rsl    
    
    
    Hearing and reading that Carl Robinson is going to be the new head coach of Vancouver Whitecaps. #vwfc #whitecaps    
    
    
    #PTFC gets #CCL spot for winning the conference in the season, but #RSL won the conference overall through playoffs. Hmm. Interesting. #mls    
    
    
    Alright so I think we have to give Toronto a chance this season with Defoe and Gilberto. #MLS #tfc    
    
    
    Suarez with 2 goals in Liverpool's 5-goal rout over Tottenham. Yikes. There's no stopping this guy. #lfc    
    
    
    Out of DC/LA/Chivas for Eddie, DCU might be the best rout. It'd be his team to lead and might guarantee him a DP slot. #mls    
    
    
    Here's a look at the UCL draw: http://msn.foxsports.com/foxsoccer/championsleague/story/premier-league-clubs-face-tough-knockout-stage-round-of-16-preview-121613?cmpid=tsmfb:fscom:foxsoccer …    
    
    
    Arsenal/Bayern and ManCity/Barca are going to be two cracking sets. Excited for those. #ucl    
    
    
    @SonjaMissio @SerieAFFC Me too.    
    
    
    @LeanderOnFOX The double-dash -- one of the least appreciated punctuation marks out there.    
    
    
    If Chivas USA snags Eddie Johnson, on paper they'd be a playoff contender with Rosales, Jean-Baptiste, Bocanegra. #mls    
    
    
    Seattle is playing musical chairs ... but with goalkeepers. #ssfc #mls #sounders    
    
    
    @LeanderOnFOX I believe it was Vonnegut who said that the semi-colon just proves you went to college. Em dash all the way.    
    
    
    Looks like Eddie Johnson might head to DC. If he's hot and hungry, then DC will surely be lifted. They've made a lot of good moves. #mls    
    
    
    @Frances_Locke Thanks for reading and letting me know. I didn't see any author bio or info on the page. I'll fix it for you.    
    
    
    Beckham's search for a Miami #MLS takes a step forward as Miami-Dade County agrees to negotiate with Becks in search for stadium site    
    
    
    DC United has landed Eddie Johnson. Now time to see if EJ will be hungry and hot, or tamed and unsuccessful now that he's paid. #mls    
    
    
    Anytime a profile player joins a team in MLS (EJ to DC, Dempsey to Sounders, Henry to RBNY), I always want their new jersey. Odd. #mls    
    
    
    DC grabs Espindola today and traded for EJ yesterday. Yowza. #dcu #mls    
    
    
    Wow. Ronaldinho with a sweet golazo. Completely fools everyone watching. Jaws dropped.    
    
    
    See the golazo by Ronaldinho here: https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=662927267099525 …    
    
    
    RSL and Impact announce their head coaches. RSL's is Jeff Cassar and IMFC's is Frank Klopas. #imfc #rsl #mls    
    
    
    Cassar's been with RSL since 2007, so he should be familiar with Kreis' style and attitude. RSL keeps it in the family. #rsl    
    
    
    Nice to see Raja Casablanca reach the Club World Cup final. No matter end result in the final, it's still a cool accomplishment. #cwc    
    
    
    #TBT to when I fought the Grinch...and won. #tbt #throwbackthursday #grinch #year2006 #xmas #christmas http://instagram.com/p/iG0fWZP0J7/     
    
    
    Bob Bradley trying to get into the EPL. Tottenham sacks AVB. Anyone else think this is too coincidental? #thfc #avb #halfkidding    
    
    
    The idea of Google/Facebook/Apple buying the MLS TV rights is fascinating. League would be a pioneer of sports league for doing that. #mls    
    
    
    Great article about the divides between media, fans, leagues and organizations in North American soccer: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1507/north-american-soccer-needs-unifying-blueprint-not-division …    
    
    
    Smart move by SKC to add @EnergyFC to its USLPRO affiliation with ORL. Once OCSC comes to MLS, SKC will still have OKC team. #uslpro #mls    
    
    
    For all soccer news, commentary and analysis, follow the @SoccerNewsday staff. You can find their accounts here: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following … #FF    
    
    
    For baseball updates, jokes and commentary, give my good friend @ShoresOnSports a follow, too! #FF    
    
    
    #2013TaughtMe that Drake has a tremendous replay value. His songs don't really get old. Fine wine kind of thing.    
    
    
    Given Clint Dempsey's recent run of luck, I wouldn't be surprised if he failed his physical ahead of his move to Fulham. #ffc #dempsey #mls    
    
    
    This version of the Lakers is like a really good TV show that did good for two seasons, but went on way too long and hasn't been cancelled.    
    
    
    Harry Potter prequel about his family life before Hogwarts is coming to the stage http://bit.ly/1bVJ4Ag  #harrypotter #jkrowling #hogwarts    
    
    
    @halpal8 You still have like 11 days dude...    
    
    
    @halpal8 Well, there's always next year.    
    
    
    @halpal8 I can't read emojis on Twitter :(    
    
    
    @halpal8 Gotchya.    
    
    
    Beckham coming back? Unlikely, but this is interesting nonetheless: http://futnsoccer.com/2013/12/20/retired-david-beckham-transfer-target-bolivar/ …    
    
    
    Want to play with NASL teams in FIFA 14? Well, now you can. Sort of: http://mnunitedfc.com/2013/12/nasl-comes-fifa14/ …    
    
    
    Winter begins.    
    
    
    Nielsen announced as OKC Energy coach. Boy, that escalated quickly. #okc #uslpro    
    
    
    Channeling my inner drawer....that doesn't exist. http://instagram.com/p/iPb9ehv0NJ/     
    
    
    @SonjaMissio Stay safe.    
    
    
    Scotland might not know how to form its domestic league, but it can sure hell make a fine breakfast tea. #spfl    
    
    
    Even though Ribery said he'd consider playing in MLS (or in UAE), he also says he "would not count that as part of my real career." #mls    
    
    
    Just took the @nytimes dialect quiz. It says I'm from Massachusetts. Accurate. Check it out: http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2013/12/20/sunday-review/dialect-quiz-map.html …    
    
    
    Sometimes I wonder if Mourinho has lost his step, or he's just trolling the EPL. #cfc #bplonnbc #bpl    
    
    
    Top 5 of the EPL is incredibly open. Definitely a tight race to the finish. #epl #bpl    
    
    
    Missing my Massachusetts team right now. Hope you all have a wonderful holiday. #SpotlightBoys #TheCrew #massachusetts    
    
    
    Of course it's Christmas Eve when I finally get some Christmas Cheer. Well. Here we go.    
    
    
    Wonder what Santa's bringing Qatar for Christmas. Maybe that yet-to-be-invented technology they've been talking about? #santa #qatar #wc2022    
    
    
    Dempsey now officially heading back to Fulham on loan. Many will look for him to regain form ahead of MLS season and World Cup. #ffc #mls    
    
    
    And let the #AChristmaStory marathon begin. Best Christmas movie ever.    
    
    
    Would be great for MLS/USA to have a #BoxingDay type of situation. Only not in December when the country is iced. Maybe in the summer. #mls    
    
    
    Around the 4th seems to be the popular choice. July 5 or 6 would do well -- might give families another activity to do for holiday. #mls    
    
    
    The "PT-FC" chant just got stuck in my head. Ah. #mlsoffseason #mls    
    
    
    Manchester City really are a talented side. Wouldn't be surprised to see them to dominate EPL in 2014 and grab the title. #epl #mcfc #bpl    
    
    
    ManUtd in 7th in the EPL standings. Certainly still in it. Unlikely they'll capture the EPL crown, but top 4 isn't out of the question. #epl    
    
    
    Great article by @ussoccerplayers on #MUFC and whether the club can really be mediocre or not: http://www.ussoccerplayers.com/2013/12/can-manchester-united-be-mediocre.html …    
    
    
    Seems like an open and shut case. RT @AP_Sports: Celtic beats St Johnstone to stay 11 points clear in Scottish league http://apne.ws/1edRNxE     
    
    
    Would really like to see Pittsburgh grab an MLS team. Good sports market. I see it as another KC type. #mls #riverhounds    
    
    
    @PNaegelyRS They average about 3,000 now in the USL. With time, and the general push MLS gives, it might works. A few years away, though.    
    
    
    @Southern_Legion MLS can definitely hold 40 teams eventually. Lots of cities can/will take to soccer and help out the growth.    
    
    
    #FBF to those summer days in Erie. #flashbackfriday #erie #pa http://instagram.com/p/ibevhBP0Gy/     
    
    
    Ted Lasso is back, kind of: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SStxsyXxZKM&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Make sure to follow @SoccerNewsday and its staff for soccer news, analysis and commentary: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following … #ff    
    
    
    Great look at the Sounder academy. Seems to be on the rise for sure: http://www.soundersfc.com/news/articles/2013/12-december/sounders-academy-growth.aspx … #ssfc    
    
    
    Wonder what the reaction would be if a USA sports team's owner fired their coach, who just got them to the playoffs. #VincentTan #ccfc #epl    
    
    
    ...and didn't have any knowledge of the sport either...    
    
    
    Can't really get into this UFC thing. Heard Dana White isn't a soccer fan, either, which doesn't help matters.    
    
    
    Should Steven Lenhart consider a UFC career? #AskAlexi    
    
    
    Imagine a world where you could binge-watch the entire MLS season on Netflix... #MLS    
    
    
    @druryfire if I'm not mistaken, they're still building tech. for outdoor A/C to make their area viable for a summer WC.    
    
    
    @druryfire I think building it for a large scale stadium and the city itself is still yet to be built. Either way, we'll see how it goes.    
    
    
    France's 75% tax rate gets approval. Has implications for #Ligue1. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/business-25541739 …    
    
    
    LOL. Hilarious. RT @TanFacts: Vincent Tan has requested that EA Sports place him on the cover of FIFA 15 pic.twitter.com/iBahek3slv    
    
    
    2013 - One of the best years of my life. Thank you.    
    
    
    Beckham, LeBron, Jay-Z, Beyonce, Tom Cruise, Will Smith, Jack Nicholson, Kobe, Pau Gasol, Eva Longoria. Call it Celebrity FC. #mls #miami    
    
    
    Have to imagine that if PSG found a way to sign Messi, it would elevate the French club to new levels in marketing. #psg #messi    
    
    
    @IanDarke They're steaming right now, but hard to break through to that top five.    
    
    
    Defoe announcement imminent, according to several reports. TFC will likely add a top striker. With the right service, could be deadly. #tfc    
    
    
    Don't forget to read the @SoccerNewsday staff's awards for the 2013 MLS season: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1439/sn-picks-2013-mls-year-end-awards … #mls #awards2013 #year2013    
    
    
    @_EnricoS @Tiny0ne Have to imagine their form will change, given Gilberto isn't tall either (5-foot-10). Wonder how #TFC will do in 2014.    
    
    
    @Tiny0ne @_EnricoS It's probably better than being the "We're seriously concerned for your well being" Chivas USA. ;)    
    
    
    Niche interests, like soccer, proving crucial in magazine industry http://bit.ly/1hd1YYo  #soccer #journalism #magazines    
    
    
    Qatar is about an hour away from being 8 years away from its World Cup instead of 9... #wc2022 #worldcup #qatar #nye    
    
    
    Now that Fox Soccer Daily is off the air for repairs, have to wonder if they'll even bring it back.    
    
    
    Barnsley move would give Shea playing time. Likely a good fit seeing as he hasn't played often recently. And he's inconsistent. #usmnt    
    
    
    @jonahfreedman "Promoting Toronto ... one way or another."    
    
    
    No. 50 is perfect. List of what @USATODAY wants from 2014 in sports: http://ftw.usatoday.com/2013/12/50-changes-wed-like-to-see-in-sports-in-2014/ …    
    
    
    Good list. RT @the11ca: Breaking Bad sportswriting habits: How I see PLASTIC PITCH going against the grain: http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/146256602/plastic-pitch-a-thought-provoking-canadian-soccer/posts/708416 …    
    
    
    #USMNT moment of the year for me was the #SnowClasico. Meant a lot mentally/psychologically for the team at the time. Crazy game.    
    
    
    #USMNT had a successful 2013. But if the right players aren't chosen, 2014 might be a disappointing year: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1429/usmnt-report-year-ends-with-a-whimper …    
    
    
    Friends: I'm now on Mountain Time. Try not to send me any New Years spoilers! #NYE #NewYearsEve #NewYearsSpoilers    
    
    
    Last year I wrote a blog post about my 13 #NewYearsResolution. 10 of 13 were met: http://herbscribner.wordpress.com/2013/01/02/13-resolutions-for-2013/ …    
    
    
    Allegri potentially leaving #ACMilan shows another loss of a quality soccer mind from Serie A. #seriea    
    
    
    Looks like JELD-WEN Field might expand the width of the field to 75 yards. #rctid #ptfc    
    
    
    I really wonder how I'd perceive Dwayne Johnson as an actor had I not known him as The Rock first. Probably on same level as Vin Diesel.    
    
    
    Appears Camilo may have been sold to Queretaro. Not confirmed completely it seems. #vwfc    
    
    
    Funny and nice read by @GrantWahl on predictions for 2014: http://soccer.si.com/2014/01/01/world-cup-winner-epl-race-mls-shakeups-and-more-14-predictions-for-2014/ …    
    
    
    Several Twitter sources: Bob Bradley has been hired by Stabaek, a Norwegian club. Has played in Europa League and UCL in the past.    
    
    
    Move sends Bradley, an American coach, to a European club that has played in international competitions. Will be interesting to watch.    
    
    
    What are your thoughts on Bob Bradley's likely move to Stabaek?    
    
    
    SJ changing logo and jerseys and will show off the changes later this month. Exciting and refreshing for one of the stale teams in #MLS    
    
    
    Would also like to see NE Revs and Crew switch up their images, too. Still stuck in the older days of #MLS. Always a fan of growth/change.    
    
    
    @smackz_413 By far the worst news of the day...    
    
    
    @UtahMortReport Congrats dude!    
    
    
    #USMNT Jan. roster camp announcement set for tomorrow: http://prosoccertalk.nbcsports.com/2014/01/02/u-s-national-team-camp-roster-to-be-announced-friday/ …    
    
    
    We've got the #USMNT training camp roster here: http://www.ussoccer.com/teams/us-men/latest-roster/140103-jan-training-camp.aspx … (thanks to @twelfthyank and @JoshDeaver)    
    
    
    GK: Tally Hall, Bill Hamid, Sean Johnson, Nick Rimando. #usmnt    
    
    
    DEF: Besler, Gonzalez, Clarence Goodson, Michael Harrington, Chris Klute, Chance Myers, Shane O'Neill, Seth Sinovic, DeAndre Yedlin. #USMNT    
    
    
    MID: Eric Alexander, Beckerman, Brad Davis, Mix Diskerud, Brad Evans, Feilhaber, Luis Gil, Mike Magee, Dax, Graham Zusi #USMNT    
    
    
    FWD: Agudelo, Donovan, EJ, Wondo. #USMNT    
    
    
    Good mix of MLSers, U-20 members and veterans. Magee, Sinovic, Klute, O'Neill, Feilhaber all strong choices. #usmnt    
    
    
    Top guys (Jozy, Dempsey, Bradley, Howard) all working in Europe, so certainly makes sense to bring in some new blood. #usmnt    
    
    
    Should be exciting to see Yedlin, Magee. Both deserved a call-up after this #MLS season. Now it's time for them to prove their worth. #usmnt    
    
    
    Davis has another chance to show his ability, too. Best left midfielder USA has. Needs to impress to take that spot for Brazil. #usmnt    
    
    
    Mix Diskerud (Rosenborg) and Juan Agudelo (out of contract) are the only non-MLS members of this Jan. roster. #usmnt    
    
    
    @AndrewDasNYT I believe his contract with the Revs expired on Jan. 1.    
    
    
    @AndrewDasNYT Oh, you meant #USMNT roster. Odd. Now he's not there. Hmm.    
    
    
    Odd that Agudelo no longer on the #USMNT Jan. camp roster. Full list here: http://www.ussoccer.com/teams/us-men/latest-roster/140103-jan-training-camp.aspx …    
    
    
    Yedlin, a true rightback, called up by Klinsmann. Building depth for sure. #usmnt    
    
    
    @GreatPain 3 members from the current roster will be cut before going to Brazil for this camp. So likely neither.    
    
    
    More than 1,000 people selected for potential move to Mars http://bit.ly/1cqYD3e  #mars #marsone #space #spacetravel #galaxy #stars #planets    
    
    
    @jrstlouis You could have been Mars' first soccer commentator. #WorthIt    
    
    
    NWSL announces 2014 allocation players: http://www.nwslsoccer.com/home/778387.html# …!    
    
    
    Another solid article by @ussoccerplayers on the hook of MLS: http://www.ussoccerplayers.com/2014/01/finding-a-hook-for-major-league-soccers-regular-season.html# …! #mls    
    
    
    @ESPNFC @TaylorTwellman Kioyo    
    
    
    Please give a follow to some of the @SoccerNewsday staff if you're looking for soccer news!: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following … #FF    
    
    
    And the #USWNT also announced its roster today: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/womens-national-team/2014/01/140102-jan-ntc-training-camp.aspx …    
    
    
    So what did Klinsmann say about the latest call-ups? Find out here: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/mens-national-team/2014/01/140103-jk-jan-camp-qa.aspx … #usmnt    
    
    
    @halpal8 Enjoy it for the both of us!    
    
    
    @JeffreyCarlisle @Ben_Jata Dawkins is every SJ fan's 'One that got away.'    
    
    
    @Bdkma95 I like to think so.    
    
    
    @Rlevine62 solid choices. Lots of MLS guys, which is typical for Jan. camp. There's probably a couple that could squeak to WC squad.    
    
    
    Spurs and Arsenal playing is putting so many American soccer fans against each other. Derby continues.    
    
    
    Made the front page again. Thanks to everyone who has provided help and strength along the way.… http://instagram.com/p/gV6Y-XP0PA/     
    
    
    Have to say @JACKSONVILLE_FC logo and crest is top notch. Random, I know.    
    
    
    @frankiedevai Thanks Frankie!    
    
    
    @SocratesMTL I just love that blue/gold mix.    
    
    
    My contribution to 2013 election and voting coverage: 'Voters approve casinos, marijuana tax in ballot measures' http://www.deseretnews.com/article/865589976/Voters-approve-casinos-marijuana-tax-in-ballot-measures.html …    
    
    
    Every day gets infinitely better when you realize MLS playoffs are on later, especially second legs. PUMPED. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    But then you realize #NYvHOU is on Univision and #SKCvNE is on MLS Live and not NBC or ESPN. Shame. #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    @GlennDavisSoc Could see NY going with the counter-attacking style. But maybe they'll just attack since everything's on the line. Fun game.    
    
    
    My story on the Supreme Court and how its case about public prayer in a NY suburb could affect the nation: http://bit.ly/19DDJxj  #scotus    
    
    
    @GlennDavisSoc Agreed. But RBNY could also get caught badly on the counter-attack, too. His send-off changed the series for them.    
    
    
    Some of these playoff games are a good way to sell people on the idea of MLS Live. Problem is it won't bring in newbies. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    November 19. Orlando City. MLS. Allegedly. http://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/local/breakingnews/os-mls-awards-orlando-franchise-20131106,0,4972653.story?utm_content=bufferb6600&utm_source=buffer&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Buffer …    
    
    
    @rhalloran11 Good question. Range of options for them in USL PRO. Might want to avoid teams with potential to be a MLS club.    
    
    
    Cheesy Garlic Bread flavored Lays chips. So...weird....    
    
    
    Most likely will be attending tomorrow's playoff clash between RSL and LA Galaxy. First ever live MLS playoff match for me. #mls    
    
    
    Messi has this way of silencing critics in a timely fashion. #messi    
    
    
    Petke gets a contract extension. Definitely must have confidence rather than worry for tonight's game with that move. #rbny #mls    
    
    
    Unfortunate result for RBNY. Deserved more than an ugly loss to Houston. But Dynamo are always dangerous in these playoffs. #mls    
    
    
    SKC and Revs is so open and back-and-forth. Both teams want this so bad. #NEvSKC    
    
    
    Really sucks these games aren't on a national broadcast. Both would have been attractive to new fans. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Revs are filled with impressive young players. Only thing the franchise really has going for it. #NERevs #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Been enjoying SKC and Revs. Wonder if first leg was this good, but couldn't tell cause of those football lines. #NEvSKC    
    
    
    To Houston and Revs credit, both were consistently in the mix for playoff spots all season. Rarely did they drop too far away. #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Hold on to your butts. #nerevs #skc #nevskc #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Drama and excitement in the 2 East matches. Wonder how tomorrow's West clashes will go. RSL/LA and PDX/SEA should deliver. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    My Boston-based friend: "Fagundez has to go on a maradona run." Something beautiful about that. #nerevs #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Watching Revs from Utah and I have same commentators as my Mass friends. Wish it was nationally broadcasted. #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    This has been going on for awhile, but sad to see Blockbuster putting the nail in the coffin: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-24844350 …    
    
    
    Western Conference semifinals tonight. Last night's drama was great. Expecting another round of it. #mlsplayoffs #mls    
    
    
    One of the best nights in college history. Plus, I'm wearing a RSL hat and they have a playoff match… http://instagram.com/p/ga6VCkv0J2/     
    
    
    Can't say I'm surprised with Adu not being resigned. Rarely dressed or made matchday 18. Wonder where he's onto next.    
    
    
    Adu had a lot of promise but is proving to be uncoachable. Next step down would be a move to Chivas. #mls    
    
    
    This morning I wondered when the next Killers album would be. Come to find they're releasing a compilation album this month. #thekillers    
    
    
    @halpal8 Just started following you again. You're still my 2nd favorite person from Charlotte.    
    
    
    Star Wars Episode VII. December 18, 2015. Excited.    
    
    
    @MrSeanMSweeney Considering Walt Disney just tweeted it out from their official account, I'd say pretty likely.    
    
    
    @MrSeanMSweeney I think the initial release date was for summer 2015, so they probably pushed it to December to accommodate delays.    
    
    
    Really interested to see where Adu ends up. Going to Liga MX has proved valuable for USMNT revivals. Maybe he'll find success there. #usmnt    
    
    
    Must be said that Freddy Adu is, without a doubt. the most overrated player in FIFA video games. #fifa14 #adu    
    
    
    @SoccerByIves Definitely think Porter is the right coach for Adu. Probably could make him work well in the Timbers system.    
    
    
    So Massachusetts is having a killer sunset apparently...    
    
    
    Time dor some MLS playoffs. #mls #rsl #realsaltlake #rslvla http://instagram.com/p/gb4IpkP0EZ/     
    
    
    Portland and Salt Lake. Great Western Conference final on tap. Unfortunately, playoff schedule doesn't make it easy to follow. #mls    
    
    
    Drinking Dunkin! They just opened one here in Salt Lake. Fantastic. http://instagram.com/p/gdSO2wv0L-/     
    
    
    FC Kansas City, one of the top teams of the NWSL this year, has picked up Amy Rodriguez, a top #USWNT star, from Seattle. Watch out. #NWSL    
    
    
    Rio Tinto Stadium's atmosphere was enjoyable last night. Everyone was pumped and ready, which is surprising given the wicked wind. #RSL    
    
    
    Got my office talking about Real Salt Lake this morning. Victory. #rsl #mls #soccer    
    
    
    @fuegote Part of me thinks you're still upset by that loss and avoiding the team like a bad ex-girlfriend.    
    
    
    If Dynamo make it to the MLS Cup, it'd be impressive. Barely any turnaround for them between play-in and East semifinals. #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Wonder what effects playoffs will have on MVP, Rookie of the Year races. Is Magee still top choice despite no playoffs? #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    And.... #FF to the @SoccerNewsday crew: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    RSL winning MLS Cup 2009. #flashbackfriday #ff #rsl #realsaltlake http://instagram.com/p/gd18s4v0ON/     
    
    
    Houston will be lucky to get out with a good result with all the turnaround. They'll cherish the break. #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Congrats to the NY Cosmos. Strong return. Had an advantage with half season, but very nice to see them take Soccer Bowl. #nasl #nycomos    
    
    
    Next season will be true test for Cosmos, to see of they can succeed through both halves. Good moment for NYC fans, though. #nycosmos #nasl    
    
    
    MLS Western Conference Final first leg. Portland vs. Salt Lake. #rsl #realsaltlake #mls #mlsplayoffs… http://instagram.com/p/gjkjnqv0Px/     
    
    
    First time seeing the Timbers play live tonight. Should be am absolute cracker between RSL and PDX. #mls #mlsplayoffs #rslvpor    
    
    
    @LeKurosawa Only a solid 50. Nothing for a Northeasterner.    
    
    
    Watched an abundance of RSL games this season in person and on TV. Still don't get the point of Robbie Findley or Devon Sandoval. #rslvpor    
    
    
    Wow. What a great half of entertaining soccer. #mls #mlsplayoffs #rslvpor    
    
    
    And Sandoval and Findley just proved me wrong. #mlsplayoffs #mls #rslvpor    
    
    
    Jurgen Klinsmann has called in his 23-man squad for upcoming #USMNT friendlies: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/mens-national-team/2013/11/131111-roster-rel-scot-aust.aspx …    
    
    
    GK: Bill Hamid, Tim Howard, Sean Johnson #usmnt    
    
    
    DEF: DaMarcus Beasley, John Brooks, Geoff Cameron, Brad Evans, Omar Gonzalez, Eric Lichaj, Michael Orozco #usmnt    
    
    
    MID: Alejandro Bedoya, Michael Bradley, Mix Diskerud, Fabian Johnson, Jermaine Jones, Sacha Kljestan, Brek Shea #usmnt    
    
    
    FWD: Jozy Altidore, Terrence Boyd, Clint Dempsey, Aron Johannsson, Eddie Johnson, Chris Wondolowski #usmnt    
    
    
    Unfortunate Mike Magee couldn't get a call up. No Donovan or Beckerman, but given their MLS scenarios it makes sense. #usmnt    
    
    
    Klinsmann definitely testing the waters and making his final decisions on some. Mix, Johannsson, Kljestan, Shea all on the bubble. #usmnt    
    
    
    Dempsey certainly a player to watch for these upcoming friendlies. Have to wonder if slump is just at SSFC or if it will flow to #USMNT    
    
    
    Whether or not Portland advances after last night's 4-2 loss to RSL, the things Porter has done in his 1st pro season are unreal. #timbers    
    
    
    Nice to see Eric Lichaj getting another call-up. Heard he's been doing great in England. Wonder how of him we'll see. #usmnt    
    
    
    USL OKC franchise potential logos/colors/team names: http://newsok.com/prodigal-soccer-submits-possible-team-names-logos-for-usl-franchise/article/3902074# …!    
    
    
    Can't say I'm impressed any of the options for #OKC team. Names are lame and colors are typical. Spirit is my favorite design. #uslpro    
    
    
    Looks like Philadelphia's looking for an attacking DP on Valeri's level. Well worth it if they can find that type of player. #mls #doop    
    
    
    TFC's looking to become the best team from 2004 with Eto'o and Defoe interest. #tfc    
    
    
    Newest @thekillers album out. It's a compilation album, but has some new stuff. Great work. Favorite band.    
    
    
    @Rlevine62 YES. Just Another Girl gives me chills. OK, not really. But still. Two great songs.    
    
    
    Big issue with Magee ever getting a USMNT call-up is that he could fail in the system and it'd be another Jack McInerney situation. #usmnt    
    
    
    @holdenb75 Good question. Though his slump started a game or two before the call-up. Still stopped his momentum. Hasn't been the same.    
    
    
    Saw "The Damned United" on Sat. One of the best soccer movies I've seen. Funny, engaging and a good 100 mins of film. #leeds #derbycounty    
    
    
    Orlando had more than 20,000 in town to see the USWNT play Brazil. Big numbers as they gear up for MLS expansion.    
    
    
    WNBA averaged more viewers than MLS this year, one site says: http://www.sportsbusinessdaily.com/Journal/Issues/2013/11/11/Media/By-The-Numbers.aspx … #mls    
    
    
    MLS games were weekend-based, where as WNBA games were primetime, according to @SBJSBD. #mls #wbna    
    
    
    USMNT manager Jurgen Klinsmann discusses team in Q&A: http://www.ussoccer.com/news/mens-national-team/2013/11/131112-qa-jk-on-sct-aust-friendlies.aspx … #usmnt    
    
    
    Great quote by Klinsmann: "It’s not about ... what you did in the past, it’s always about the moment, the present and the future." #usmnt    
    
    
    My thoughts on the recent #USMNT callups: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1405/usmnt-report-little-magic-in-euro-friendly-callups …    
    
    
    Oldest friends transform. #tt #transformationtuesday #transformtuesday #friends #oldestfriends #bros… http://instagram.com/p/gn_tCiv0BN/     
    
    
    USMNT Report: Little Magic in Euro Friendly Callups http://bit.ly/1i5ogK9  #usmnt #usa #USAvSCO #usavaut #scotland #austria #USMNTReport    
    
    
    @BrianStraus Would certainly free up some space for the top-heavy Sounders, too, and give them the chance for a defender or midfielder.    
    
    
    @BrianStraus True. It'd be good to see how they work from the beginning of a season and after WC prep. But might hurt Neagle's growth.    
    
    
    @SteveDavis90 Enjoyed this and agree with most of it. British/Scottish coach won't help MLS' game grow, either. Style is boring and brutish.    
    
    
    Expecting Mexico to breeze past New Zealand, but you never know with the #AllWhites. Always remember that 2010 WC match with Italy. #eltri    
    
    
    Believers unite to combat religious jokes and jabs http://bit.ly/1eGBtcs  #faith #religion    
    
    
    My picks for the #WorldCup play-offs starting today: Mexico, Uruguay, Greece, Sweden, France and Iceland.  #uefa #eltri    
    
    
    I'm choosing Iceland to eventually qualify because I'm Irish. #iceland #uefa    
    
    
    Very true. RT @GrantWahl: Whether you like him or dislike him, the World Cup is more interesting with Luis Suárez involved.    
    
    
    USMNT fans: It's OK to root for Mexico . Helps CONCACAF and the USA's national team grow overall. #usmnt #eltri    
    
    
    Really wonder what Mexico would have been like had FMF hadn't kept Chepo as long as they did. Likely a much different story. #eltri    
    
    
    ICYMI: My thoughts on Klinsmann's latest USMNT selections: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1405/usmnt-report-little-magic-in-euro-friendly-callups … #usmnt    
    
    
    How fun that would be! RT @goaleric: Just found out it's Chepo's birthday today. Cosmos, do your thing.    
    
    
    Orlando City confirmed that they'll be announced as an MLS expansion franchise on Nov. 19 at the Cheyenne Sallon, according to @BrianStraus    
    
    
    If reports are to be believed and Orlando is being announced on Nov. 19, I have to say it's about damn time MLS gets a purple team. #ocsc    
    
    
    For more on Orlando's expansion: RT @wvhooligan: A couple more details on @OrlandoCitySC’s announcement next week: http://wvhooligan.com/2013/11/13/17682/orlando-city-confirms-will-next-mls-franchise/ …    
    
    
    @AdrianHealey That's a great way to put it.    
    
    
    Mexico and New Zealand going on. Lots of money, hopes, dreams and tequila riding on this. #MEXvNZL    
    
    
    Mexico dominating with its own dos a cero right now.    
    
    
    @Rlevine62 It's their language ... ;)    
    
    
    @rogbennett Maybe by then Australia will get to host a World Cup ... ;)    
    
    
    Imagine if Egypt and New Zealand came back from this WC play-off deficits to qualify... #wc2014 #mexvnzl #egypt    
    
    
    USMNT tends to renew contracts, but still a cool fact. RT @SoccerInsider: Mexico 4 coaches in 3 months. USA 4 coaches in 18 years.  #eltri    
    
    
    European soccer clubs spark discussion on religious tolerance http://bit.ly/HYZHjz  #ajax #celtic #ucl #championsleague #religion #thfc    
    
    
    Seattle's smart to try and move EJ. Invested a lot in Martins and Dempsey, and Neagle's on the up-climb. EJ might find money elsewhere. #mls    
    
    
    If TFC has trouble signing Gilardino or Eto'o, which is likely, maybe they should make a move for EJ. #tfc #mls    
    
    
    Plus Seattle is incredibly top-heavy. Move Johnson, find cap room and restructure the back and midfield. Good move for them. #ssfc #mls    
    
    
    Cool to see. RT @pauldalglish: Here you go. Each team in @mls is ranked based on final league position vs spending. pic.twitter.com/tGO2AUKpjL    
    
    
    I think I might have a late go at this #NaNoWriMo thing. I won't ever say that hashtag out-loud, though.    
    
    
    @halpal8 Well done.    
    
    
    Nice piece about how the EPL is losing creative play: http://www.soccernewsday.com/world/a/1411/creativity-disappearing-in-the-epl … #epl #bpl #premierleague    
    
    
    Is Australian soccer and the Socceroos heading into a new era? http://bit.ly/19mT8xU  #socceroos #australia    
    
    
    Looks like we've got a new @USLPRO team named. Oklahoma decides on @EnergyFC for its team name. Mix of Sounders/Dynamo. #uslpro #energyfc    
    
    
    OKC Energy is without better than OKC Wind. Wind, really?    
    
    
    So far the #LAGalaxy have been the most active offseason team. Signing players left and right. #mls    
    
    
    Tomorrow a very important game for the USMNT on multiple levels. Lots on the line for bubble players. #usmnt    
    
    
    First Naughty Mrs. Clause (eggnog latte) of the season. Courtesy of lordricci. http://instagram.com/p/gvbqHZP0MJ/     
    
    
    Canada down 1-0 to Czech Republic currently. Team has some established MLS players, but can't seem to ever get things going. #canMNT    
    
    
    It'd be nice to see a world where Canada, Mexico and the USA are the three top CONCACAF sides. Can it be done?    
    
    
    My thoughts ahead of #USMNT's match against Scotland later today: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1419/usmnt-report-building-a-blueprint-begins-in-glasgow … #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Exciting day of international matches. Doesn't get any bigger than USA/SCO and POR/SWE. Two fun clashes for fans. #usmnt #usavsco #porvswe    
    
    
    #USMNT lineup for #USAvSCO: GK - Howard. DEF - Evans, Gonzalez, Cameron, Beasley. MID - Bradley, Jones, Bedoya, Kljestan, EJ. FWD - Altidore    
    
    
    I'd expect EJ to move forward if US can't score. But looks like Klinsmann sticking with the 4-2-3-1 lineup. #USMNT    
    
    
    @davisjsn Diskerud tends to show himself more than Bedoya in USA games. Definitely would have liked to see him start today.    
    
    
    @davisjsn True. Kljestan disappears at points, too, so Mix would have fit in well there, like you said. We'll probably see him later.    
    
    
    @davisjsn Good point. I think both are on the bubble for World Cup so Klinsmann likely wants minutes for them both to measure value.    
    
    
    Cool graphic to see the visuals for today's #USMNT lineup, courtesy @ussoccer: pic.twitter.com/iTnytGn7eN    
    
    
    Altidore was successful in Holland for months without anything coming in a USA jersey. Same may be true for Johannsson. #USMNT    
    
    
    Speaking of Johannsson, kind of, here's a good piece by @JoshRobinson23 on Iceland and its success http://on.wsj.com/1aalFvb     
    
    
    Is it just me or does Hampden Park look empty? #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Have to say @AlexiLalas has a perfect 1970's mustache. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Don't get why USA makes these long crossing balls so early. Building up play might be the best method. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    Maybe it's the cold Scotland weather, but Klinsmann is sporting his attire in recent months. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    So far, Scotland's been owning the ball in their half and the US is controlling the ball in their half. Back and forth. #USAvSCO    
    
    
    And a good #FF out to the @SoccerNewsday Team: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    Got off work and heard about 0-0 USA score. What a shame. #usmnt    
    
    
    US just got somewhat of a reality check. Can't succeed at the World Cup when you draw Scotland 0-0. #usmnt #usavsco    
    
    
    US was mostly reserves, but there's a certainly a level difference between the two sides. US, based on this year, should be above. #usmnt    
    
    
    @adifranco77 still think there's a huge difference between US and Scotland. American reserves should beat this Scotland team.    
    
    
    Spent the morning playing 7-on-7 in the midst of a light snow storm. Love the game in unfavorable conditions. #soccer #utah    
    
    
    @capasso10 Probably has to do with timing and the way specific stadiums work.    
    
    
    Good for Japan to draw Holland this weekend. Honda is a fantastic player for Japan. Definitely a player who needs to get into Europe.    
    
    
    About to settle down and watch/analyze #USMNT in #USAvSCO. Heard/read it's an average game with nothing exciting. We'll see.    
    
    
    Last night, FS1 had a commercial touting Germany vs. England as a match between two of world's best soccer teams. Seems a little much. #fifa    
    
    
    Nigeria and Ivory Coast have qualified for the World Cup. Both are strong African nations in recent years. #brazil #wc2014    
    
    
    Love how #OCSC is promoting this. RT @OrlandoCitySC: Two Days.  Be there--->http://on.fb.me/1j5yxna  #OrlandoIsReady pic.twitter.com/7Efu2LrCgx    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC I won't be there, unfortunately, but I'll be following along for sure. Are you live streaming the announcements?    
    
    
    @EvanReam @rosshard Should have been more clear. Meant into one of Europe's bigger leagues. UCL is fine, but needs better league to play in.    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC Great. Excited to hear what you guys got coming. ;)    
    
    
    @EvanReam @rosshard Poor mistake on my part not to clarify that. Thanks for catching!    
    
    
    Just finished USA/Scotland. No entertainment, slow, sleepy. 2nd half was better with Shea/Johannsson, but otherwise a weak showing. #usmnt    
    
    
    Had to watch the UFC ppv last night. Paint me a someone who prefers WWE/pro wrestling over MMA. #ufc #mma #wwe    
    
    
    What might this be that I'm working on? #novel #nanowrimo http://instagram.com/p/g1CGBiv0Cn/     
    
    
    Excited to see whether or not Orlando City changes their logo if/when they move to MLS. I'd expect a slight change. #ocsc    
    
    
    @GunnarBerndt I just like logo changes. And there's a lot of potential with the purple/red/gold and Lions, so it'd be fun to see.    
    
    
    Still believe Messi is the best player in the world (likely ever). But due to injuries this year, can't see him getting Ballon d'Or. #fifa    
    
    
    Used to cover UM. RT @BleacherReport: VIDEO: UMass' Raphiael Putney throws down a massive dunk vs. Youngstown State http://bit.ly/1b3JGpv     
    
    
    Underreported/talked about story: Chivas USA fell 1-0 to FC Tucson, a #uslpro side.    
    
    
    My thoughts on the USA's 0-0 draw with Scotland: http://www.soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1422/usmnt-report-throwaway-game-in-glasgow … #USMNT    
    
    
    Miami Kings SC. Thoughts?    
    
    
    Orlando Health and Orlando City SC Announce Historic Agreement http://orlandocitysoccer.com/news/?article_id=1653 … #ocsc    
    
    
    Qatar World Cup is just becoming a bigger problem by the day: http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-middle-east-24980013# …!    
    
    
    The NYCFC fan movement ad is really well done, but it probably turned off all Manchester United fans. Give/take for the team. #nycfc #mcfc    
    
    
    USMNT Report: Throwaway Game in Glasgow http://bit.ly/17DJyqE  #usmnt #usa #usasoccer #usavsco #scotland #fifa #concacaf #USMNTReport    
    
    
    That USA/Mexico combo jersey is the greatest ugly Christmas sweater I've seen. #usmnt #eltri    
    
    
    Anyone know what Orlando City SC's big announcement for tomorrow is? #ocsc #gocity #mls #uslpro    
    
    
    Big day of soccer ahead. USA takes on Austria and Orlando City makes a "major" announcement. Keep eyes peeled to Twitter. #usmnt #ocsc #mls    
    
    
    Thoughts ahead of today's #USMNT contest with Austria: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1426/usmnt-report-a-second-chance-in-austria … #usavaut    
    
    
    Whether or not LeBron joins Beckham for Miami franchise, recent discussions have brought MLS and the future team publicity. #mls    
    
    
    Sydney Leroux joining Reign FC. Sad to see her leave my home state, but Seattle can surely use her talents after last season. #nwsl    
    
    
    Egypt playing Ghana right now in WCQ play-off. Egypt up 1-0, making it 2-6 aggregate. #EgyptVsGhana    
    
    
    The #USMNT starting team: Howard; Cameron, Gonzalez, Brooks, Beasley; Bradley, Jones; Bedoya, Johannsson, Shea; Altidore #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Smart move to include Shea and Johannsson, who can make plays at times and brought energy in last match. Still not sure about Bedoya. #USMNT    
    
    
    NBC Sports broadcasts are top notch. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Nice play from Austria so far. USA seems in control, but Austria looks one or two breaks away from getting past the Americans. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    I really think there's a difference in skill when the USA plays with the Waldo jerseys and when they play in plain white. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Wow. What skill from Austria right now. Dumbing the USA. If someone was at that far post, it would have been a sure goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Nice shot from Jozy there. A little too far out for him, but still a nice chance at goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Great one-touch play from the US there, capped with an excellent shot from Johannsson. This is a better-moving US side. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Replays showing that was as close to a goal as you'll get without it being a goal. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Alaba a good player, surprised he couldn't get that off. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Gonzalez with two great plays. Well done. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    And it's 1-0 Austria. Janko scores. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Not impressed with Brooks so far. He's young and far from fully developed, but more of a problem for USA's starting lineup. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    You realize how poor the USA plays without Donovan, Dempsey with a game like this. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    HT: Austria 1 - 0 USA. Tough half for the USA. No one playing with that extra step. Backline -- Omar decent, but Brooks poor. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    USA needs to work on finishing and creating play. Should move Johannsson to striker with Altidore and put Diskerud in the middle. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Diskerud on for Johannsson and EJ for Shea. Decent dubs, but would have liked to see Jones taken off. Hot-headed. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Boyd with a good attempt there. Nice shot. Would have liked to score there. EJ and Diskerud adding a bit of flavor to this lineup. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Bradley whiffs that volley. USA searching for a goal. Altidore with a decent shot, but not powerful or high enough. Low. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Kljestan comes in for Bedoya. Still not sure what Klinsmann seems him in a USA jersey. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    Crazy things going on in Sweden/Portugal. Ibra with two goals, Ronaldo with two goals. Insane.    
    
    
    USA had something good going there for awhile with attacking play, but seems to have dropped off in the last 10 minutes. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    And that's it: USA falls to Austria 1-0 in Vienna. #USAvAUT    
    
    
    USA's year went from low to high to higher to low. Fair. #USAvAUT #USMNT    
    
    
    So with Alonso being signed to a DP contract, likely EJ will be shopped around and moved. He probably wanted DP money. #ssfc #usmnt    
    
    
    Great image. RT @ESPNFC: Only two WC2014 spots left up for grabs. Here's how they will line up in Brazil next summer. pic.twitter.com/lT3pp0Z2Sj    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan The draw this year seems mighty tough for all teams, really. Exciting stuff!    
    
    
    Would be kind of funny if @OrlandoCitySC pulled one from under the rug and said they were joining the #NASL. #mls21 #ocsc    
    
    
    @AndrewDasNYT LOL. An intern must have pasted the wrong logo for all the banners, so they decided to run with it.    
    
    
    Young journos: Make sure to check out the USA TODAY collegiate correspondent program. Helps immensely! http://www.usatodayeducate.com/staging/index.php/collegiate-correspondent-program … #journalism    
    
    
    If #OCSC joins MLS (still if, technically), i can't wait to see a sea of purple in the stands. Such a cool color for a soccer club.    
    
    
    I'm not in Orlando. I'm only following this through Twitter. But #OCSC's jump to MLS has got me feeling like a giddy boy on XMas. Awesome.    
    
    
    @djonesjax Thanks, I saw that. I'm trying night to get too distracted ;)    
    
    
    Watching live now. Orlando City about to be announced as #MLS21. Exciting stuff. #OCSC    
    
    
    "The Beautiful Game to the City Beautiful." #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    Add Orlando? Check. #MLS21 #mls    
    
    
    "We Want Kaka" chants. Kaka would be cool for Orlando, but he's injury-prone. But good for marketing/promotion. #OCSC    
    
    
    Confirmed: Chivas USA, NE Revs and SJ Quakes have the worst logos in #MLS.    
    
    
    Garber making his way to the stage on Orlando. #MLS21    
    
    
    Garber's added the scarf. #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    "The when is now" - Garber #OCSC #MLS21    
    
    
    "It was about all you purple people." - Don Garber. #ocsc #MLS21    
    
    
    11th expansion team in 10 years, says Garber. Can't expect them to slow down. #mls21 #mls #OCSC    
    
    
    "With #OCSC we will show the rest of the world that our country is leading the game." #mls21 #mls    
    
    
    And it's official. @OrlandoCitySC has been announced as MLS's 21st team.  Congrats to Orlando and its fans. #ocsc #orlandoisready #mls21    
    
    
    Exciting thought: We now get two new teams for FIFA16. #ocsc #mls21 #fifa    
    
    
    @greypaul such a shame!    
    
    
    @jrstlouis That's certainly a concern, given how some MLS teams play now. Hopefully players are found abroad and within the US with talent.    
    
    
    @OrlandoCitySC Major.    
    
    
    MLS can only grow with more teams. More teams means more markets, more TV deals, more supporters, more cash. Excited to see the growth. #mls    
    
    
    @jrstlouis I think European players are being overpaid in Europe, too ;) Either way, just exciting to have pro soccer in a new city.    
    
    
    @jrstlouis Agreed. We'll see how it turns out!    
    
    
    No matter if OCSC, NYCFC, Beckham's potential Miami - there's going to be divide about expansion. Fun to see new teams if done right. #mls    
    
    
    Brad Evans: A Gold Cup midfielder, not a World Cup defender. #USMNT    
    
    
    Thinking about #USMNT and just realizing that Klinsmann moves so many players around it's impossible to know where everyone will play.    
    
    
    Jones, Bedoya didn't do much for USA. Par for the course. Replace with Beckerman and Zusi for WC. Klinsmann will probably keep Jones. #usmnt    
    
    
    @BuckiNick7 I believe that's where he plays club so could work.    
    
    
    @chisokrkid77 I'd put Beckerman ahead of Jones.    
    
    
    @ZacWassink starts at 1 a.m. EST, right? Hmmm... 1:01.    
    
    
    @ZacWassink @DohertySoccer I'm an optimist.    
    
    
    So what happens when Orlando City SC comes to Salt Lake City, and the Lions have to contend with Leo the Lion? #rsl #ocsc #mls    
    
    
    Final thoughts: Great day for soccer. #USMNT game, #ocsc officially joining #MLS, Ibra/Ronaldo go punch-for-punch, Houston/#NWSL? Love it.    
    
    
    Totally went hashtag overload in that last tweet. Pardon the #s.    
    
    
    Orlando has been awarded an MLS franchise to begin playing in 2015. Expected to bring in designated player. #mls #ocsc    
    
    
    Mexico qualified for the World Cup last night with a 4-2 (9-3) win over New Zealand. #eltri    
    
    
    RBNY/Sky Blue potential MLS/NWSL deal is a no-go, according to reports. #nwsl #rbny #sbfc    
    
    
    USMNT fell to Austria, 1-0, yesterday in Vienna to end the USA's 2013 calendar year schedule. #usmnt #usavaut    
    
    
    Speaking of the NWSL, Houston may be adding its own franchise, according to reports. #nwsl    
    
    
    My thoughts on the #USMNT loss yesterday: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1429/usmnt-report-year-ends-with-a-whimper …    
    
    
    Interesting article about how valuable #MLS teams are: http://www.forbes.com/sites/chrissmith/2013/11/20/major-league-soccers-most-valuable-teams/ …    
    
    
    Great article on what MLS can do to fix the playoffs: http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/soccer-insider/wp/2013/11/20/mlss-disappearing-act/# …! #mls #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    Idea: MLS could keep two conferences, but just change the names. Make them general (American/National or A/B, 1/2). #mls    
    
    
    Respect Steve Nicol. But the style of play he promoted at NE Revs was nowhere near as fun to see as Timbers/RSL. Can't agree with him. #MLS    
    
    
    @JeffreyCarlisle @WilliamMathis1 @VoxFossili True. Jones capable of good ball in attack. But he's too inconsistent for me. Just my 2 cents!    
    
    
    Jones over Cameron in the defensive midfielder role, and will likely start come WC time. Think Beckerman would be better there. #usmnt    
    
    
    Get amped. RT @PCarrESPN: FIFA hasn't announced the full draw format, but here are the projected pots for Dec. 6: pic.twitter.com/CPaSala35k    
    
    
    What might really hurt the USMNT at the World Cup is the group. Team is shaky, but these groups are going to be tough. #usmnt #wc2014    
    
    
    If you're Bob Bradley, do you come back to MLS or try and make it as a manager in Europe? #mls #bobbradley    
    
    
    Why retailers open or close their doors on Sunday http://bit.ly/1fmJeEP  #business #amazon #verizon #hobbylobby #smallbusiness #sunday    
    
    
    Getting ready to leave my first ever #USMNT game more than 8 years ago. Wow. #usa #ussoccer http://instagram.com/p/g-8dSWv0Lg/     
    
    
    Getting ready to leave my first ever #USMNT game more than 8 years ago. Wow. #usa #ussoccer #tbt… http://instagram.com/p/g-8dSWv0Lg/     
    
    
    So Native Americans originated from Europe? http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/science-environment-25020958 …    
    
    
    @wvhooligan @BrianStraus Agree. 2014 is loaded with talented teams, and the draw looks to create difficult groups. Excited for the piece.    
    
    
    If you can't beat them, cut 10 of your players and figure out a way to rebuild, I guess. #chivasusa #mls    
    
    
    Figured it out: TFC has signed Hulk Hogan! #tfc #mls    
    
    
    I get Ricketts has won a Goalkeeper of the Year and is up for it again this year, but he's never overwhelmingly impressed me. #rctid #mls    
    
    
    @theaxepdx This year he's been great without a doubt. Just never taken interest in him over the past couple of the years.    
    
    
    Love what Houston is doing in regards to possible #NWSL expansion. Refundable deposits. Gauges interest and cash. Cool stuff.    
    
    
    And you really can't go wrong with a $25 season ticket. Such a steal. #houstondynamo #NWSL    
    
    
    Can't help a little bit of holiday joy with each sip of a Nighty Mrs. Clause (Eggnog Latte).    
    
    
    Check out the @SoccerNewsday staff's choices for 2013 MLS Year End Awards: http://soccernewsday.com/usa/a/1439/sn-picks-2013-mls-year-end-awards … #mls #mlsawards #mlsmvp #mlsroy    
    
    
    Missed this ESPN FC story situation. Can someone fill me in?    
    
    
    @ETNMcCracken Thanks Sean. Unfortunate stuff from ESPN.    
    
    
    SN Picks!: 2013 MLS Year End Awards http://bit.ly/1bIIQK6  #mls #mlsawards #mlsmvp #mlsroy #usa #ussoccer #SNPicks    
    
    
    Have to give a #FF to the excellent @SoccerNewsday staff. Check them out here: https://twitter.com/SoccerNewsday/following …    
    
    
    Debating whether to get into the Hunger Games madness and see the movies/read the books. I probably won't. #hungergames #catchingfire    
    
    
    And @PhilSchoen gets it right in his latest article on the #USMNT. Good read: http://bit.ly/1i2qg8h     
    
    
    Agreed. RT @ETNMcCracken: It's this sort of myopic, self-serving work that unfairly makes all sports reporting (and journalism) look bad.    
    
    
    Remind all your friends, family, co-workers, Tweeps, FB buds, Snapchat friends, Instagramers that the MLS playoffs return this weekend!    
    
    
    On Saturday, Herb is proud to run on Dunkin. #dunkin #dd #breakfast http://instagram.com/p/hELY2rP0Gc/     
    
    
    Woke up to all these Messi transfer rumors. Never count it out, but can't see #Barca getting rid of him. Would be fun to see where he goes.    
    
    
    Wait a tick ... is Toronto FC signing Messi?  #messi #tfc #yeahright    
    
    
    Been asked a few times to predict Sporting KC vs. Houston. Tough call to make. SKC is at home, but Houston's home is the playoffs. #mls    
    
    
    Settling in for #SKCvHOU. Exciting game. Not sure if Houston will do as Well given no Bruin/Clark.    
    
    
    SKC atmosphere is very impressive. Fans look excited, thrilled. Nice tifo, fireworks. Great image of the league. #mlsplayoffs #mls #SKCvHOU    
    
    
    Wow. 22 degrees in Kansas City. Get the gloves out boys. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Would you expect anything else from Houston? Complete spoilers. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Houston Dynamo is like that guy that ruined the ending of Harry Potter for you. #SKCvHOU #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    We've got ourselves a game here fellers. Excellent and exciting game so far. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    First leg of Houston and SKC was dreadful,  boring and lackluster. This one has that extra punch and style. Love it. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Sporting KC would host one hell of an MLS Cup. #skcvhou #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Sporting KC in the Dwyers seat. Right? Right? #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    SKC fans want this so bad. #SKCvHOU #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Congratulations to Sporting KC - MLS Eastern Conference Champions. #mls #mlsplayoffs #SKCvHOU    
    
    
    2013 - The Year of Sporting KC #mls #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Woke up the sweet sounds of Manchester United and Cardiff. Nice kick-off to the day. #epl #BPLonNBC    
    
    
    Wonder what SKC/HOU would have been like with Clark and Bruin. Dynamo had chances, so with that fire, maybe a different result. #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    That awkward moment when Messi and Ronaldo are BOTH injured.    
    
    
    Hear my thoughts on #RSLvPOR around the 10-minute mark here: http://sportsathome.webs.com/apps/videos/vi … #rsl #rctid #MLSPlayoffs    
    
    
    @readmyfunny Thanks for clicking! It's not my website, I spoke on the radio show. Definitely give the podcasts a listen. They're good stuff.    
    
    
    In honor of RSL's playoff game tonight,  here's a photo I took at a game a couple of years back. #rsl… http://instagram.com/p/hHepI7P0DC/     
    
    
    What are your pre-game thoughts about #RSLvPOR?    
    
    
    RSL has the advantage, but it's not unrealistic for Portland to snag two goals. Three, tough. Extra time wouldn't surprise me. #RSLvPOR    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan What temp we got there in Portlandia?    
    
    
    Last game before the final game. Like a good TV show, penultimate is always straight fire. Time to enjoy. #rslvpor    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan @MichaelOrrFtbl @dan_itel As a former northeastern resident - keep your hands, ears and head warm buddies. Enjoy the game!    
    
    
    Man. Portland game looks amazing. Raucous fans, great play. Just a great image of MLS. #mlsplayoffs #mls #rslvpor    
    
    
    Portland really needs a goal to make this interesting. #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs #mls    
    
    
    Findley doesn't give up. Salt Lake up 5-2 on aggregate. #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    And there you have it. Real Salt Lake - 2013 Western Conference Champions #rslvpor #mlsplayoffs    
    
    
    Whoever Toronto FC signs this week, not sure it'll be enough to fix the franchise. #tfc #torontofc #mls    
    
    
    My alma mater. RT @steve_hewitt: UMass basketball is ranked No. 24 in this week's AP Top 25 poll, its first ranking in the poll since 1998.    
    
    
    Anyone else having "Defying Gravity" by Wicked stuck in their heads? Anyone? No? Just me? OK.    
    
    
    Major League Soccer reveals 2014 regular season schedule, with two-week break for World Cup: http://www.mlssoccer.com/news/article/2013/11/25/major-league-soccer-reveals-2014-regular-season-schedule-two-week-break-worl?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=news&utm_campaign=paid … #mls    
    
    
    Feel like more was expected out of Maximiliano Rodríguez. But Waiver Draft list is weak. Not sure who the sleepers are. #mls    
    
    
    Michael Bradley at rightback? Don't count on it. #USMNT    
    
    
    And Dillion Powers was voted as Rookie of the Year. Deserved. #mlsroy #rapids    
    
    
    MLS's rookie class of 2013 was stellar. All solid players in the league now. #mls    
    
    
    'Death of the Family' is grim, dark and full of twists http://bit.ly/1cLK5d3  #batman #joker #deathofthefamily #dccomics #dc #comics    
    
    
    Just discovered the book "Amish Vampires in Space."    
    
    
    Never thought I would see gas in the $2 range again. http://instagram.com/p/hL3Yv2P0Hk/     
    
    
    Revs, Union, Fire, DC and Dallas all vying for Eddie Johnson it seems. Looks like he's likely heading east: http://www.goal.com/en-us/news/1110/major-league-soccer/2013/11/25/4433158/mls-wrap-eddie-johnson-sweepstakes-underway?ICID=OP … #mls    
    
    
    Thinking about 2013 MLS season, and SKC/RSL makes a lot of sense for a final. #MLSCup #mls    
    
    
    Can't believe I'm saying this, but the race for the EPL title is wide-open. Top 9 spots have legitimate shot. #epl    
    
    
    TFC signing Defoe (and another striker) will make another top-heavy MLS side. Teams in 2013 showed strong midfield is key to winning. #mls    
    
    
    Seattle, LA Galaxy both top heavy teams. Appealing to fans, owners, TV stations, but does little to succeed. Example is this season. #MLS    
    
    
    That said, I can't say I'm not excited to see Defoe in a TFC uniform. A recognizable, proven EPL player in MLS. Exciting. #mls    
    
    
    True, but they had a certain world class midfielder ... RT @TheMikeDonovan: @hscribner LA Galaxy did win last 2 titles though    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan LOL. Make that two world class midfielders ;)    
    
    
    RBNY also sort of top heavy with Cahill/Henry, but this year they had a lot of working parts, including Olave in the back. #rbny #mls    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan He also brings intangibles that others certainly don't. Leadership, presence, etc., that helped LA surely.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan Oh, no. I meant like forwards/strikers/attackers.    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp I clicked the link, but I'm not going to read the article out of fear that I may like PB more than I should.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan Oh, definitely. Impact, too, to an extent. Difference is LA/Seattle spent big money on its forwards/attackers.    
    
    
    @TheMikeDonovan No doubt. They just really stick out due to lack of production from Demps/Martins.    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp I recently agreed wholeheartedly with this one: http://www.buzzfeed.com/jeremybender/struggles-of-being-23 …    
    
    
    EJ definitely a striker worth grabbing if club has money/resources to please Seattle. He scores, knows the league.  Attitude a problem. #mls    
    
    
    @KatherineRupp Not sure whether to be weirded out or impressed. Probably the latter because I'm from this place: http://www.buzzfeed.com/adamdavis/foods-that-new-england-does-better-than-anywhere-else …    
    
    
    @Ben_Jata Good point. Lot of the current criticism is about the pay me stuff. So once paid that should disappear.    
    
    
    @Jonny_Soccerly It's very good. Usually a 4-5 horse race. Wide-open this year. Has a lot to do with Moyes taking over for ManU.    
    
    
    Situation sucks, but the #MLSTicketGate hashtag is hilarious.    
    
    
    Stadium collapse in Brazil. Reportedly 3 killed. Stadium is supposed to host 2014 World Cup opener. #wc2014    
    
    
    Anybody else feel like today is eerily similar to a half day of school? I'm not in school, but it has that vibe. #thanksgiving    
    
    
    And one other thought: I really want to see "Frozen" now that I know Idina Menzel voices a character. She's awesome in so many ways. #Frozen    
    
    
    Black Friday - The Day When Singing Christmas Songs Becomes Socially Acceptable    
    
    
    Well #ThanksToSoccer I've made some incredible friends and found a job I love doing. Thank you.    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving everyone!    
    
    
    Unreal that TicketGate extended past just the Ticketmaster situation and has spiraled out of control. Unfortunate for buyers/fans. #rsl #mls    
    
    
    @halpal8 Your Thanksgiving tweets have been hilarious.    
    
    
    Fun stuff here. Give it a read! RT @jrstlouis: Hey!  It's 'Drunken Thanksgiving WC Draw 2014'.  RT appreciated!!  http://bit.ly/1il7xoQ     
    
    
    And cue the mountain of ice cream. #icecream #sundae #foodporn http://instagram.com/p/hUzEvEP0Np/     
    
    
    Would be fun to see Donovan and Dempsey play together for Everton in January. #usmnt    
    
    
    December.    
    
    
    Stoked for the Christmas season and all the festivities this time of year brings. Let's finish out the year with love, passion and lights.    
    
    
    Holiday Heisenberg. #breakingbad #bb #heisenberg #walterwhite #holidays #christmas http://instagram.com/p/hZYI3rv0KS/     
    
    
    Introducing your MLS Coach of the Year -- Caleb Porter. Deserved. Finishes ahead of Petke, Kreis and Pareja in that order. #mls    
    
    
    Road to the World Cup begins on Feb. 1 when the USA takes on South Korea at the StubHub Center in Carson, Calif.: http://www.ussoccer.com/News/Mens-National-Team/2013/12/131202-MNT-v-Korea-Republic.aspx …    
    
    
    Solid warm-up match for the #USMNT. Should be a good indicator of where the US stands among other teams.    
    
    
    Nature of modern day journalism calls for things like Kreis/NYCFC report today. 24/7 news cycle asks for constant information. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    It's also important to remember nothing has been confirmed about Kreis going to NYCFC. Things change in an instant. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    Kreis possibly moving is a part of the story. Means it may be his final MLS Cup with RSL, and means he may not coach in 2014. #nycfc #rsl    
    
    
    World Cup pots as expected. Dangerous draw possibilities for the USA. In most cases, they're battling for 2nd/3rd spot in groups. #WC2014    
    
    
    Don't forget MLS State of the League address is today. Garber likely to talk expansion (MIA/ORL), MLS Cup and 2014 season. #mls    
    
    
    People forget how big of a country Brazil is. Nearly as big as USA and China. Distances traveled for upcoming WC will be large. #WC2014    
    
    
    @EvanReam @robertjonas @SacRepublicFC Really love those kits. Hope they're the real deal.    
    
    
    MLS State of the League is live here: http://www.mlssoccer.com/mlscup/2013/state-of-the-league?utm_source=Twitter&utm_medium=referral&utm_content=News&utm_campaign=Paid … #mls    
    
    
    Garber praising RSL ahead of MLS Cup. Talking history and how the team has done in recent years since it  came into MLS in 2005. #mls    
    
    
    Garber proud of Sporting KC's turnaround since the darker days of the Wizards. Encourages everyone to see Sporting Park. #mls    
    
    
    Garber says he wants MLS to be one of the top soccer leagues in the world by 2022. #mls    
    
    
    Don't cross the line - unless you're Steven Lenhart. #mls    
    
    
    Garber talking stadium development. #mls    
    
    
    Garber - 10 teams in 2004, 21 by 2015, 24 by 2020. What a growth. #mls    
    
    
    Garber: MLS currently in talks with owners from Atlanta and Miami. #mls    
    
    
    Garber says there's a lot of work needed for Atlanta and Miami, but MLS is looking to the southeast for expansion teams. #mls    
    
    
    "This country can really love this game." - Don Garber on USA soccer culture. #mls    
    
    
    Garber said USA winning the World Cup would help build league, USSF, college soccer, etc. #mls    
    
    
    