    
    
    
        
    
    
    Checking out "Compassionate Listening Basic Intensive:  Healing Our World from" on Compassionate Action Network: http://ning.it/q2XYq2     
    
    
        
    
    
    What a great organization - and what a great opportunity:  they are look for a new Executive Director.  They deserve t…http://lnkd.in/2sxDmm     
    
    
    @UW how could first day of classes be set for Rosh Hashanah when it's been on the calendar for over 3000 years?!    
    
    
    Sign this, I did http://movetoamend.org/motion-to-amend     
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Action Network http://ning.it/u5LkIi     
    
    
        
    
    
    gnawing my fingernails to knuckles wAiting to hear more from CLP in Pakistan!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @clp_mag  you made it! yeah!    
    
    
    glad i don't know the real story of peshawar adventures and blessing the protective angels    
    
    
    Brighten your day! Check this video out -- Life Vest Inside - Kindness Boomerang - "One Day" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nwAYpLVyeFU&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    celebrating end of tax season with jim:  free at last!    
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Action Network http://ning.it/AbUZ0B     
    
    
    LinkedIn Events: Compassionate Listening: 2 day Basic Intensive - Healing Our World From the Inside Out http://linkd.in/xJ80gB  in Seattle    
    
    
    LinkedIn Events: Compassionate Listening:  1 day Basic  - NYC:  Healing Our World From the Inside Out http://linkd.in/x8VjJa     
    
    
    Seattle Transpartisan Alliance Salon on "Media & Society"  Wed, Jan 18 (St Thomas Church -Phinney Ridge, 6 to 9) http://meetu.ps/6hYcF     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Worried about getting older? @PatcohenNYT says middle-aged brains actually work better in some ways http://ideas.time.com/2012/01/10/the-advantages-of-the-middle-age-brain/ … via @TIMEIdeas    
    
    
    Say NO ▓▓▓▓ to Internet ▓▓▓▓▓▓▓▓ censorship. http://pol.moveon.org/nointernetcensorship/?rc=tw … #StopSOPA #StopPIPA via @MoveOn    
    
    
        
    
    
    I was Born This Way. Join @ladygaga’s @BTWFoundation, and help us empower youth & inspire bravery: http://bit.ly/sNhivO  via @BTWFoundation    
    
    
    feeling relieved in seattle cause i just heard all is well from jessica and clp gang in karachi    
    
    
    My 1st phone tweet.  R u fleeing or hurrying    
    
    
    End Monsanto's campaign of fear and intimidation against America's farmers http://bit.ly/Ack1Wa  @food_democracy Pls RT #stopMonsanto    
    
    
    Buffett Rule Will Raise $50 Billion Per Year, Affect Just 0.08 Percent of Taxpayers | NationofChange: http://www.nationofchange.org/analysis-buffett-rule-will-raise-50-billion-year-affect-just-008-percent-taxpayers-1327766301#comments … via @AddThis    
    
    
        
    
    
    Inside Apple's Hidden Factories. Finally. http://motherjones.com/blue-marble/2012/01/apple-factories-ipad-iphone-labor … via @motherjones    
    
    
    Susan Partnow & The Power of Restorative Circles and Compassionate Listening | Feb. 2nd http://malirowanpresents.com/index.php?option=com_content&view=article&id=69:susan-partnow-a-compassionate-listening-feb-2nd&catid=16:upcoming-events&Itemid=145 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tell Obama to Cease FDA Ties to Monsanto http://signon.org/s/hhw_zX  #signon    
    
    
    Tell @komenforthecure "maybe" isn't enough. They need to commit to funding breast health care via Planned Parenthood. http://pol.moveon.org/komen/     
    
    
    Help Save Heirloom Seeds and Keep Monsanto Out of Your Garden: http://gaia-health.com/articles501/000524-save-heirloom-seeds.shtml#.Ty9PerNKg5u.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tell Obama to Cease FDA Ties to Monsanto http://signon.org/s/hhw_zX  #signon    
    
    
        
    
    
    Transform Conflict through building Conflict Evolution systems and Restorative Circles (Seattle, Feb 18): http://lnkd.in/7w4b3D     
    
    
        
    
    
    Seattle Transpartisan Alliance Salon - Art  & Creativity - serious fun! http://meetu.ps/7Fkrs     
    
    
    Please come  Wed March 21 - Salon on how  Arts & Creativity can help bridge  divides: Seattle Transpartisan Alliance http://meetu.ps/7Fkrs     
    
    
        
    
    
    for Congressional Action to Label GMOs in Food http://signon.org/s/iNCisA  #signon    
    
    
    Don't let Republicans block the Violence Against Women Act! http://bit.ly/HfqIum  @CREDOmobile #fem2 #p2    
    
    
    Checking out "Compassionate Listening Basic Intensive:  Healing Our World from" on Compassionate Action Network: http://ning.it/IgCA0X     
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm attending a Meetup with Seattle Transpartisan Alliance http://meetu.ps/8qYHj     
    
    
    My life has been deeply transformed by this powerful practice; I'd love to share the skills and practices with you! http://lnkd.in/qHB7Ki     
    
    
        
    
    
    Join me at the next Seattle Transpartisan Alliance Salon http://meetu.ps/8x2yF     
    
    
    Support the Student Loan Forgiveness Act of 2012 http://signon.org/s/r4gOiA  #signon    
    
    
    How Did We Get Here: A Brief History  of Monsanto and the US Government  http://www.occupymonsanto360.org/2012/02/23/how-did-we-get-here-a-brief-history-of-monsanto-and-the-us-government/#.T5Ir9bRhwtE.twitter …    
    
    
    Checking out "Restorative Circles - Deepening in your Practice workshop" on Compassionate Action Network: http://ning.it/I8bYkM     
    
    
    Compassionate Seattle: Creating Collective Impact TED Award Overview: http://youtu.be/VdWq9RZeW2s  via @youtube    
    
    
    The bees are dying. Tell @Bayer_sd @Tweet2Harvest to vote against their deadly pesticides! Only 24 hrs left to sign http://www.avaaz.org/en/bayer_save_the_bees/?weQrbdb …    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm here and it's a blast #ImAglobalist    
    
    
    Come and join the fun #ImAglobalist    
    
    
    Just posted a photo http://instagr.am/p/J_HYidNrg_/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/J_HYidNrg_/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/J_HYidNrg_/  fun time fandangoing #ImAglobalist    
    
    
    Sign the letter of support to Christiane Amanpour to end gender segration in Israel http://bit.ly/IrBBZ6     
    
    
        
    
    
    San Franciso/Bay Area friends:  Compassionate Listening one day June 30!  Please come & spread the word! http://sfjune30oneday.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/LdQdlj     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/xx-6wM  San Francisco area colleagues:  June 30 one day introduction...    
    
    
    This'll get your blood moving on a cool spring morning! Robert Reich: "The REAL Public Nuisance": http://youtu.be/ltxMtS1Frpk  via @youtube    
    
    
        
    
    
    Join Seattle Sun 6/10 noontime Moment of Silence  http://www.compassionateseattle.org/events/sunday-june-10-12-00-noon-city-wide-moment-of-silence …    
    
    
        
    
    
    City wide vigil: "Community Wid… http://www.compassionateseattle.org/video/video/show?id=2386694%3AVideo%3A97918&xgs=1&xg_source=msg_share_video …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/LXH2CN     
    
    
    July 15 in Rainier Beach..join us@ "Compassion and Service  to End Violence" on Compassionate Seattle: http://ning.it/O1Yo5u     
    
    
    Just added a new blog post on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/Ob2J6G     
    
    
        
    
    
    Come downtown Monday to show your support: "Social Justice for South Seattle" on Compassionate Seattle: http://ning.it/PsHnSY     
    
    
    Just added a new blog post on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/N9jH1y     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/MrqLoR     
    
    
    Want yours? Click to get an invite to build your graphical bio on Vizify. https://www.vizify.com?t=xovtraxvizify.com/?t=xovtrax  via @vizify    
    
    
        
    
    
    Why King County doesn't need a new juvenile hall http://www.seattleglobalist.com/2012/08/03/why-king-county-doesnt-need-a-new-juvenile-hall/5715 … via @SeaGlobalist    
    
    
    Have fun and great weather    
    
    
        
    
    
    Too depressing to imagine a Romney win. Get engaged voters! http://front.moveon.org/this-video-might-stop-romney-from-becoming-president/?rc=emailac …    
    
    
    Everyone around you needs to see this video @RBReich dropped everything for: http://bit.ly/PGTvLU  via @moveon @PaulRyanVP @MittRomney    
    
    
    Rock on! https://m.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=486524998024911&set=vxywtia.1346350747.1346350748.449228458421232&type=1&src=email_notif#!/home.php?__user=659683957 …    
    
    
    Seattle area friends:  Please come to Seattle Center for a  Conversation Cafe on Creating Compassion in our Community - http://tinyurl.com/9u8zzeo     
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/ONvkQb     
    
    
        
    
    
    Aurora theater shooting survivor demands a plan from Obama and Romney to end gun violence: http://www.demandaplan.org/aurora-share     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Tell @BarackObama thank you for trying to achieve a ceasefire in Gaza, and ask him to keep it up with @jstreetdotorg http://bit.ly/XSF7aD     
    
    
        
    
    
    Compassionate Listening: Seattle 2 day Basic Intensive - Healing Our World From the Inside Out http://lnkd.in/qHB7Ki     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/k45eXr  I have been teaching deep listening at Swedish healthcare system and Providence as well including large groups......    
    
    
    UNO Roboto -- The Grandma: FUN!!  especially since it's my sister Elaine!   http://youtu.be/4zjP1g3jttQ  via @youtube    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tell Senate: Don't let the Obama Administration's "Assassination Czar" run the CIA! http://act.demandprogress.org/act/brennan/?referring_akid=.1818061.6R_pvV&source=typ-tw … via @demandprogress    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tell the Senate: Support a ban on assault weapons. http://bit.ly/TZZbXW  #p2 #standdownNRA via @CREDOMobile    
    
    
    Include a talking filibuster in any package of Senate rules reforms http://signon.org/s/m1FuTf  @signon    
    
    
        
    
    
    Clock is ticking on  final comment period to urge @BarackObama to reject Keystone XL.Take action now: http://bit.ly/11dTS8k  @CREDOMobile    
    
    
    Just added a new event on Compassionate Seattle http://ning.it/10JWPjI     
    
    
    I participated in #GiveBIG today to support local nonprofits and stretched my donation. You can too! http://www.seattlefoundation.org/GiveBIG     
    
    
    I just signed a petition to name extreme storms after policy makers who deny climate change. http://climatenamechange.org  #ClimateNameChange    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Seattle meets Sister Lucy & Maher's Healing Use of the Arts" Sept 26 in Seattle -Kirtan + Bollywood dance lessons http://ning.it/14uzm7Q     
    
    
    Seattle meets Sister Lucy & Maher's Healing Use of the Arts ... plus Bollywood dancing! http://www.seattleglobalist.com/event/seattle-meets-sister-lucy-mahers-healing-use-of-the-arts-plus-bollywood-dancing … via @SeaGlobalist    
    
    
    Restorative Circles workshop 9.18.13 at Center for Spiritual Living. http://ning.it/15Q2BNf     
    
    
    @petersessum i was at @KING5Seattle in the @KING5NewDayNW audience too! Great segment on #compassiongames    
    
    
    @petersessum @susan4ps @petersessum @KING5Seattle @KING5NewDayNW    
    
    
        
    
    
    Bollywood fun! Sr Lucy inspiration! TH 9/25 seattle https://www.facebook.com/events/567479959985031/ …    
    
    
    http://bpt.me/472123  - Sign up now to Meet Sister Lucy in Seattle: Maher&#39;s Model of Hope for Oppressed Women & Children !    
    
    
    Redmond siblings a dynamic duo fighting for immigration reform http://www.seattleglobalist.com/2013/09/20/redmond-siblings-a-dynamic-duo-fighting-for-immigration-reform/16193 … via @SeaGlobalist    
    
    
    Indian Nun brings fresh approach to domestic violence to Seattle http://www.seattleglobalist.com/2013/09/23/indian-nun-domestic-violence-seattle/16634 … via @SeaGlobalist    
    
    
        
    
    
    Only 1 in 10 engineers are women. We should probably fix that. @goldieblox has 1 idea how. (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/if-3-little-girls-did-this-to-my-house-id-do-everything-i-could-to-get-them-full-rides-to-harvard-am2-8a?g=2 …    
    
    
    My life is enhanced as yours will be:"Compassionate Listening -Healing the World from Inside Out" http://december2013intensive.eventbrite.com/?aff=estw  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Meet my hero Sister Lucy who  Saves Thousands  from Domestic Violence in India http://www.yesmagazine.org/peace-justice/after-this-indian-nun-witnessed-a-womans-murder-she-saved-thousands-more-from-domestic-violence?ica=Tweet&icl=ShareBar_Art_UR …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Team Members: volunteer coordinator, outreach, communications http://www.volunteermatch.org/search/opp262124.jsp?sms_ss=twitter&at_xt=4db9fb40484706e4,0 … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Check out this Meetup with Seattle Transpartisan Alliance http://meetu.ps/2B6RX    
    
    
    Checking out "Compassionate Listening Basic Intensive:  Healing Our World from" on Compassionate Action Network: http://ning.it/q2XYq2    
    
    
    This will be an awesome training in compassionate listening:  http://sept2011intensive.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw     
    
    
    