Abraham Lincoln "Things may come to those who wait, but only things left by those who hustle."    
    
    
    Innovating a Socially Conscious Business | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20121025155322-25745675-innovating-a-socially-conscious-business …    
    
    
    Great Architect and Artist Oscar Niemeyer dies at 104. His principle was "Life imitates Art far more than Art imitates Life"    
    
    
    Maria Blanchard mi foto de su bello retrato por Tora Vega Holmström (1921) http://cultura.elpais.com/cultura/2012/11/02/actualidad/1351858874_278987.html … http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=x2KzuXL6qiM … pic.twitter.com/zQByR5WX    
    
    
    “@indy_johar: RT @DisruptSummit: How algorithms secretly shape the way we behave - Guardian http://vsb.li/BTpkeb  #algorithm” to think about    
    
    
    Naughton parafraseando a Keines "men who believe to be exempt from any intellectual influences, are usually the slaves of some algorithm"    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/gmsnSYcp    
    
    
    @Yoriento @eraser  Gracias Alfonso Good night    
    
    
    Great video @realjohngreen Ownership of @ideas4all is not important parallel creativity and building over others is http://johngreenbooks.com/on-the-ownership-of-ideas/ … #fb    
    
    
    Why Aaron Swartz’s Ideas Matter by @WillKnight MIT, http://xurl.es/swartzMIT     
    
    
    Swartz testament the power of an #idea, technology should exist to make the world a better place" which I share  http://xurl.es/hacktivisthero  WP #fb    
    
    
    Coworking at The HUB, Where #Ideas Come to Meet, Not a trend a reality
  http://xurl.es/4kn4q   Quien se sabe las cifras españolas ?    
    
    
    One Europe One Driving Licence. One more step on harmonization. A quick win for #Europe to start 2013 . http://xurl.es/5usgp  @ideas4all #fb    
    
    
    Does Davos have a gender problem?@Reuters' Emma Thomasson looks at a perennial concern for the WEF:7 Yes it does http://xurl.es/xhisn  #women    
    
    
    @Davos hoy UK no debe salir de Europa ni siquiera consultarlo M Sorrell UK referendum is grey swan threat  H Davies:Referendum won't help UK    
    
    
    Via @PinarAkal1: Nothing ever goes away until it has taught us what we need to know. ~Pema Chödrön”    
    
    
    Letter me slowly 2. Printing Museum Madrid @ Printing Museum Madrid http://instagr.am/p/VRGQ8CH6Cg/     
    
    
    “@indy_johar @commutiny: Privileged access vs. public scrutiny - why lobbying transparency matters http://shrd.by/hOqmd1  via @OpenDemocracy”    
    
    
    My followers live in Spain (77.9%), Venezuela (5%), the U.S. (5%) & more. Create your map at http://twocation.com/     
    
    
    Recomiendo video @McKinsey #womenmatter Making the Breakthrough 2012 y estudio http://www.mckinsey.com/features/women_matter … #mujeres pic.twitter.com/jEMyD2E81g    
    
    
    “we resist to act on the idea of the future being different from the present,
 its so repugnant to our conventional modes of thought" Keynes    
    
    
    @esadecreapolis @ideas4all @ContuNegocio_es @MICProductivity @QuimeraRR @ESADE @totsantcugat @MarketMoving2 @KenPMorse  Thnak you    
    
    
    @greggfraley Why Mashups are so powerful in #Innovation @ideas4all http://tinyurl.com/d5rsjwb  Could not agree more,I call them #Hybridations    
    
    
    @ideas4all buenos pronostico expertos innovación 2013 “@IXchat: Twenty Innovators on What We’ll Be Doing in 2013 - http://su.pr/2qki13     
    
    
    Great post @smashingmag Communicating complex @ideas with comics 3innovation http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/03/15/communicating-complex-ideas-with-comics/ …    
    
    
    Own languages, twitter misspellings. The Justin Bieber fans have a habit of ending words in 'ee', as in 'pleasee'. http://www.guardian.co.uk/news/datablog/2013/mar/15/twitter-users-tribes-language-analysis-tweets#.UUQ9aRjgzY4.twitter …    
    
    
    @peterdiamandis XPrize communicates brilliantly i need of risk for progress, crazy ideas for disruptive innovation http://xurl.es/wqpuy     
    
    
    Seing the Samsung Smartwatch project I remembered idea in @ideas4all  form 2008 @SamsungMobile Parallel creativity http://ideas4all.com/ideas/1314-create-mobile-bracelets-brazaletes-brazamob-which-combines-a-bracelet-and-mobile-phone-add-a-fashion-series-suggested-tiffankia …    
    
    
    Via @RogerFrancis1 What can Biology teach us about adapting our organisations? http://ow.ly/iuqqa  Fascinating HBR Blog/ Be an octapus    
    
    
    Games that help you screen job applicants and #innovators #idea http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/812e6856-8b18-11e2-8fcf-00144feabdc0.html … #FT    
    
    
    ...sacrifice for ur art and u will be repaid but ask of art to sacrifice herself for u and a bitter disappointment may come to u Oscar Wilde    
    
    
    @knowdler Si si pensar es googlear en el cerebro    
    
    
    Cursos online que me han interesado Gamification Pensilvania, Making sense of Data Toronto, Crush course creativity Stamford, Genes Maryland    
    
    
    @amaiaATICOmpany ya te dire algo si al final tomo alguno    
    
    
    I'm using @simplymeasured to analyze my Twitter followers in Excel. http://bit.ly/owpX5r     
    
    
    Gracias @arrobero @pinobethencourt @blogypan sí un privilegio a room with a view justamente ayer 28, 72 años de la muerte de Virginia Woolf    
    
    
    @jmgrande @pinobethencourt @blogypan Gracias Jesus por hoy y muchos viernes    
    
    
    Para emprendedores @loic toca teclas clave con ejemplos inspirador @loic 10 ways to start your business doing nothing http://buff.ly/YIFP9T     
    
    
    Corrigiendo error en tweet    
    
    
    @HappenCoworking gracias    
    
    
    I find Bookclub video enlightening of why all angles are necessary for life and specially for #ideas and #innovation http://xurl.es/y3awg     
    
    
    @cthoen Chris thank you for the recent references like your daily http://paper.ly/cthoen 
great #innovation reading source source    
    
    
    Sesión de noche  Bookclub video enlightening, all angles are necessary specially for #ideas and #innovation http://xurl.es/y3awg     
    
    
    I P. McCarthy ‏@Toffeemen68 Should #entrepreneurship be mandatory for professors? http://soa.li/0ayZX6V  ,Yo Creo que si via @elenapisonero    
    
    
    Swiss top innovators due to international public-private co-publications strong linkages between industry and science http://xurl.es/8b8j7     
    
    
    Innovative students should dropout of school or have university education a hybrid educational system is what matters http://xurl.es/kghz4     
    
    
    GEM Entrepreneurship monitor Ghana Nigeria Thayland top Brazil Equador,Uganda Switzerland next #Women  equalization http://xurl.es/io5rz  -    
    
    
    Finland most innovative economies, only country where students leave high school ‘innovation-ready. http://xurl.es/aani6  Invent your job    
    
    
    #womenquotes "Silent gratitude isn't very much use to anyone"Gertrude Stein La Gratitud silenciosa no le sirve a nadie via @marta_dominguez    
    
    
    @jorgesegado @juanmanfredi @vicentelozano @jtoufi gracias Jorge    
    
    
    @loogic @ideasvodafone si si Javier muy cierto un abrazo    
    
    
    @EL_Bijani gracias    
    
    
    @Virginiapalonso @_anapastor_ gracias Virginia    
    
    
    My own version of an optimist.If I can't make it through one door, I'll go through another door - or I'll make a  door. Rabindranath Tagore    
    
    
    The butterfly counts not months but moments, and has time enough.
Rabindranath Tagore. Time management    
    
    
    The Economist World’s next great leap forward: Towards the end of poverty. Avances en reducción de pobreza extrema  http://www.economist.com/news/leaders/21578665-nearly-1-billion-people-have-been-taken-out-extreme-poverty-20-years-world-should-aim?frsc=dg%7Ca …    
    
    
    Irene Natividad Global Summit #women are the third billion in Business y seguimos siendo y somos clave en las economias mundiales    
    
    
    Presidenta Kosovo Global Summit #women Ambition crossing borders of rigid politics/regulation is our strength & raising children as equals    
    
    
    Kosovo Prime Minister she says #women are 40% of entrepreneurship 
and new smes of the emergent  markets Global Summit    
    
    
    #women caregivers and decision 
makers but in part of the world have no freedom:rights. tbe one big voice and together we can make changes    
    
    
    #inspirationday Emma Fernandez Magic ones with a price, todo tiene un precio    
    
    
    Lo siento Corrijo me cuesta en el iphone  #inspirationday Magic comes with a price, Todo tiene un precio    
    
    
    #inspirationday @ricardo_lop  al cliente lo minimo pidele lo imprescindible no le hagas darte datos q no vas a usar la navegabilidad clave    
    
    
    A good manager innovates all things correctly, a good leader only innovates a few, the correct and trenscendent ones #innovation    
    
    
    Its said leaders know and show the way to others, I believe a good leader always doubts of all paths and teaches us to question them,    
    
    
    Steve Jobs "Innovation distinguises a leader and a follower".  I believe leaders' innovations are more disruptive and improve the world    
    
    
    Leaders make people dream, learn, grow, improve and be happy. El líder hace que la gente sueñe, aprenda, crezca, mejore y sea feliz    
    
    
    Leaders are a step ahead in their vision, at the same height, closer in the day to day, and a step behind, leaving space, when delegating    
    
    
    Una idea/historia para una pelicula #Ideas wanted: Amazon Studios baits aspiring screenwriters with Storyteller  http://xurl.es/etuk0     
    
    
    You sharpen your #ideas by reducing yourself to the level of the people you are with and a sense of humour and a complete relaxation Mandela    
    
    
    I tell them, I was also a terrorist yesterday, but, today, I am admired by the very people who said I was one. Mandela Los tiempos cambian    
    
    
    “@TOLMOS: En el Hotel Palace /cc @anamariallopis pic.twitter.com/yYhmt0lP3v” great words future of internet    
    
    
    “After climbing a great hill, one only finds that there are many more hills to climb.” Mandela/ It applies to #innovation, it's a continum    
    
    
    I have cherished the ideal of a democratic and free society with equal opportunities it is an ideal for which I am prepared to die. Mandela    
    
    
    “Nelson Mandela has lived every word of his teaching, whatever the cost. His abiding lesson is about forgiveness" Deepak Chopra,    
    
    
    "I realized they could take everything form me except my mind and heart and I decided not to give them away". Mandela Long walk to freedom    
    
    
    I went through the gate if I still hated them, they would still have me.I wanted to be free. And so I let it go.Mandela Long walk to freedom    
    
    
    Cerf @vgcerf en Madrid habló de Internet of things y los implantes, ahora the internet of you via @carlosdomingo http://xurl.es/lusu7     
    
    
    @topideas4alleng Picasso on creativity/innovation, "Its another thing, you turn your head and its another thing" Innovators, another thing    
    
    
    @Rakelmarkos @Emprendedores gracias    
    
    
    @Juanatalavera buenos dias para ti también Juana    
    
    
    @anamariallopis    
    
    
    Thanks @mediaczar for sharing Why everyone is more popular than you? Great network maths. http://mczar.me/128LFTK  .Siempre+ populares que tú    
    
    
    Just finished preparing in-company  conference which I have named The Digital Transformation Tornado. Enjoyed  learning via papers/videos    
    
    
    "It is better to have useless knowledge than to know nothing" Seneca. I think useless knowledge to most is knowledge to some    
    
    
    "All art is an imitation of nature" Seneca. I believe Nature is all, is everywhere is part of all we see feel and create    
    
    
    BigData useless knowledge until analysis/hypothesis validation and conclusions to act innovatively occur. BD intrinsically useful knowledge    
    
    
    "Be silent as to services you have rendered, but speak of favours you have received" Seneca    
    
    
    "I shall never be ashamed of citing a bad author if the line is good"Seneca. Lo mismo hacía Casals con los intérpretes encontrar el instante    
    
    
    "If one does not know to which port one is sailing, no wind is favorable" Seneca. Consejo a emprendedores, saber puerto dónde quieres llegar    
    
    
    Dear @BernieHernie Me gustaria hablar contigo but I dont have your new email left message KRs    
    
    
    Discovering Science communicator Neil deGrasse Tyson "One should not be too distracted by definitions. Ideas often transcend definitions.”    
    
    
    Neil deGrasse Tyson When I tweet I carve the words and whats left is the most important concept to communicate in a simple & most direct way    
    
    
    Neil deGrasse Tyson "When I tweet I feel like Michael Angelo I cut away everything that is not... a tweet  is like a soundbite"    
    
    
    @neiltyson "We're entering a new era where science and space in particular are artists muses, taking a new relationship with your culture"    
    
    
    Braque, La realidad sólo se revela iluminada por un rayo de #poesía. Reality only reveals itself when it is illuminated by a ray of poetry.    
    
    
    American biggest firms: Back on top | @TheEconomist http://econ.st/1ervBU9 . Últimos 4 años emergentes bajan USA sube pic.twitter.com/reEC2yGeOu    
    
    
    Georges Braque "La verdad existe , sólo las mentiras se inventan" . Truth exists only lies are invented pic.twitter.com/aBlkfvql92    
    
    
    Good morning , interesting article; Economic history: When did globalisation start? | @TheEconomist http://econ.st/17TWquV     
    
    
    Quote O´Leary @EFNI "Brussels is the Empire Base, Berlaymont bdg the Death Star where every shred of innovation is left outside the door"    
    
    
    @EFNI Innovation Euro strategy failed, it was treated as an official religion leading to disbursement of tax revenues on admin objectives    
    
    
    @EFNI Euro Innovation Strategy failed, Many countries policies of R&D based mainly on grants thus making #innovation dependent on EU funds    
    
    
    @EFNI National policies treated ideas and projects in a protectionist manner preventing the emergence of a European common #innovation space    
    
    
    @EFNI Innovation by regions in Europe, Spain lets do better and start working to lead in some sectors pic.twitter.com/5SBjBYNPEH    
    
    
    @BernieHernie trying to contact you good #ideas please call    
    
    
    If an elderly scientist states something is possible, he is almost certainly right. if impossible, he is very probably wrong. Clarke's Law    
    
    
    Artgur Clark's 2nd Law "The only way of discovering the limits of the possible is to venture a little way past them into the impossible"    
    
    
    Arthur Clarke's 3rd Law"Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic" that is why it suffers resistance #innovation    
    
    
    @monicadeza @ernestociorra at #innova13 @ideas4all pic.twitter.com/eVT84ba1FL    
    
    
    @ernestociorra  ask a brazilian what is change he gives you ideas and welcomes opportunities #innova13    
    
    
    @ernestociorra  you ask an Italuan qhat is change he does not give you ideas hecis afraid of cost savings  and losin his job    
    
    
    #innova13 @ernestociorra la #innovacion debe medirse e incentivarse con KPIs    
    
    
    @anamariallopis: Can you have a square wheel we dont want a round wheel the type of reaction to inovation great sgort film #innova13    
    
    
    @Inma_Eiroa Muchas gracias Inma    
    
    
    #TUOPORTUNIDAD1, EL INNOVADOR DISRUPTIVO Y EL MAVERIK, …http://quatremots-anamariallopis.blogspot.com.es/2013/10/tu-oportunidad-el-innovador-disruptivo.html … @CHRISTIANRF @jperezdolset lecciones pic.twitter.com/78w4lcfKrF    
    
    
    The best time to plant an #idea was ten years ago, the second time is today, plant your ideas, you wont regret it    
    
    
    “@anapiccola: Good #infography "@IndiaToday #RIPNelsonMandela pic.twitter.com/sY3aVj5ga9"” Me ha gustado    
    
    
    "Part of being optimistic is keeping one's head pointed toward the sun, one's feet moving forward" Mandela    
    
    
    As promised, we still don't have many answers. So far the avg. is 6,8 ideas/day. We would love to know how many #ideas /day you have    
    
    
    There are no big vs. small ideas. Just ones you believe in. Don't waste time guessing their size.Just do them.Hiroshi Ishii MIT @NovaXestion    
    
    
        
    
    
    "@SteveCase As Software Eats The World,Non-Tech Corp Are Eating Startups http://tcrn.ch/JnQPF  "Behind software/Startups are ideas/ideators    
    
    
    Martin Luther King "I was not afraid of the words of the violent, but of the silence of the honest"    
    
    
    "@SteveCase As Software Eats The World,Non-Tech Corp Are Eating Startups http://tcrn.ch/JnQPF  "Behind Software/Startups are #ideas/talent    
    
    
    Ensalada plus se Vanesa pic.twitter.com/NAeVEJilnK    
    
    
    Noche Centro Niemeyer pic.twitter.com/vuTy1UEfVQ    
    
    
    They did it again "WE ARE LIGHT" El Chorrillo Panamá, Graffiti @Boamistura Social #innovation WOW the Watson dance http://vimeo.com/m/82264239     
    
    
    @BOAMISTURA lo que hacéis es Social #innovation. You do real Social #innovation an injection of optimism in Brazil, South Africa, Panamá    
    
    
    Seasons Greetings, ideas4all Team Eng https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yo-Hl8qzY2E#t=6 …. Wake up the kid in you. Share  #ideas    
    
    
    @isgavi @EPEconomia Gracias    
    
    
    Alan Turing "We can only see a short distance ahead, but we can see plenty there that needs to be done" Lets do things, make #ideas happen    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Mathematical reasoning...is the combination of two facilities, which we may call intuition and ingenuity"#ideation uses both    
    
    
    Alan Turing "A computer would deserve to be called intelligent if it could deceive a human into believing that it was human" Its hapenning    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Science is a differential equation. Religion is a boundary condition" Para pensar    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Machines take me by surprise with great frequency" I could not agree more specially today #ideas, design, technology combined    
    
    
    Alan Turing One of the greatest innovators, the imagination to decipher codes and other mathematical challenges #innovation #ideas    
    
    
    One of my favorites "The Cambridge Quintet" by Casti. A dinner of Scientists discussing the human possibilities of Turings' like machines    
    
    
    2014 new hope to knees recovery,ligament discovered. Anatomy #innovation #discovery http://reut.rs/1gys7Op  Esperanza para nuestras rodillas.    
    
    
    T EDISON “Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time” Play it again Sam    
    
    
    Thomas Edison “If we all did the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves” Always try your best, people will notice    
    
    
    "We live in new times -the age of the hero is past- now is the time of the non-virtuous man". Gogol 1842, He could have written this in 2008    
    
    
    Great @Google is celebrating Simone de Beauvoirs 106 birthday, Thanks from me, Spain, and many other #women as well pic.twitter.com/YsiAi2X3TO    
    
    
    "Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay." Simone de Beauvoir .Great advise #entrepreneurs #women    
    
    
    Simone de Beauvoir "I tore myself away from the safe comfort of certainties through my love for truth - and truth rewarded me".    
    
    
    Via @brainpicker: H C Andersen's little-known sketches & beautiful travel notes on Europe http://j.mp/1hDWnKH ” sensitive travel sketches    
    
    
    Inequality by the click. Technology and new jobs not enough Adair Turner and Pope Francis @INETeconomics @ProSyn http://bit.ly/1kuomPb     
    
    
    @jguereta hecho    
    
    
    Abraham Lincoln "Things may come to those who wait, but only things left by those who hustle."    
    
    
    Innovating a Socially Conscious Business | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20121025155322-25745675-innovating-a-socially-conscious-business …    
    
    
    Great Architect and Artist Oscar Niemeyer dies at 104. His principle was "Life imitates Art far more than Art imitates Life"    
    
    
    Maria Blanchard mi foto de su bello retrato por Tora Vega Holmström (1921) http://cultura.elpais.com/cultura/2012/11/02/actualidad/1351858874_278987.html … http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=x2KzuXL6qiM … pic.twitter.com/zQByR5WX    
    
    
    “@indy_johar: RT @DisruptSummit: How algorithms secretly shape the way we behave - Guardian http://vsb.li/BTpkeb  #algorithm” to think about    
    
    
    Naughton parafraseando a Keines "men who believe to be exempt from any intellectual influences, are usually the slaves of some algorithm"    
    
    
    pic.twitter.com/gmsnSYcp    
    
    
    @Yoriento @eraser  Gracias Alfonso Good night    
    
    
    Great video @realjohngreen Ownership of @ideas4all is not important parallel creativity and building over others is http://johngreenbooks.com/on-the-ownership-of-ideas/ … #fb    
    
    
    Why Aaron Swartz’s Ideas Matter by @WillKnight MIT, http://xurl.es/swartzMIT     
    
    
    Swartz testament the power of an #idea, technology should exist to make the world a better place" which I share  http://xurl.es/hacktivisthero  WP #fb    
    
    
    Coworking at The HUB, Where #Ideas Come to Meet, Not a trend a reality
  http://xurl.es/4kn4q   Quien se sabe las cifras españolas ?    
    
    
    One Europe One Driving Licence. One more step on harmonization. A quick win for #Europe to start 2013 . http://xurl.es/5usgp  @ideas4all #fb    
    
    
    Does Davos have a gender problem?@Reuters' Emma Thomasson looks at a perennial concern for the WEF:7 Yes it does http://xurl.es/xhisn  #women    
    
    
    @Davos hoy UK no debe salir de Europa ni siquiera consultarlo M Sorrell UK referendum is grey swan threat  H Davies:Referendum won't help UK    
    
    
    Via @PinarAkal1: Nothing ever goes away until it has taught us what we need to know. ~Pema Chödrön”    
    
    
    Letter me slowly 2. Printing Museum Madrid @ Printing Museum Madrid http://instagr.am/p/VRGQ8CH6Cg/     
    
    
    “@indy_johar @commutiny: Privileged access vs. public scrutiny - why lobbying transparency matters http://shrd.by/hOqmd1  via @OpenDemocracy”    
    
    
    My followers live in Spain (77.9%), Venezuela (5%), the U.S. (5%) & more. Create your map at http://twocation.com/     
    
    
    Recomiendo video @McKinsey #womenmatter Making the Breakthrough 2012 y estudio http://www.mckinsey.com/features/women_matter … #mujeres pic.twitter.com/jEMyD2E81g    
    
    
    “we resist to act on the idea of the future being different from the present,
 its so repugnant to our conventional modes of thought" Keynes    
    
    
    @esadecreapolis @ideas4all @ContuNegocio_es @MICProductivity @QuimeraRR @ESADE @totsantcugat @MarketMoving2 @KenPMorse  Thnak you    
    
    
    @greggfraley Why Mashups are so powerful in #Innovation @ideas4all http://tinyurl.com/d5rsjwb  Could not agree more,I call them #Hybridations    
    
    
    @ideas4all buenos pronostico expertos innovación 2013 “@IXchat: Twenty Innovators on What We’ll Be Doing in 2013 - http://su.pr/2qki13     
    
    
    Great post @smashingmag Communicating complex @ideas with comics 3innovation http://www.smashingmagazine.com/2013/03/15/communicating-complex-ideas-with-comics/ …    
    
    
    Own languages, twitter misspellings. The Justin Bieber fans have a habit of ending words in 'ee', as in 'pleasee'. http://www.guardian.co.uk/news/datablog/2013/mar/15/twitter-users-tribes-language-analysis-tweets#.UUQ9aRjgzY4.twitter …    
    
    
    @peterdiamandis XPrize communicates brilliantly i need of risk for progress, crazy ideas for disruptive innovation http://xurl.es/wqpuy     
    
    
    Seing the Samsung Smartwatch project I remembered idea in @ideas4all  form 2008 @SamsungMobile Parallel creativity http://ideas4all.com/ideas/1314-create-mobile-bracelets-brazaletes-brazamob-which-combines-a-bracelet-and-mobile-phone-add-a-fashion-series-suggested-tiffankia …    
    
    
    Via @RogerFrancis1 What can Biology teach us about adapting our organisations? http://ow.ly/iuqqa  Fascinating HBR Blog/ Be an octapus    
    
    
    Games that help you screen job applicants and #innovators #idea http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/812e6856-8b18-11e2-8fcf-00144feabdc0.html … #FT    
    
    
    ...sacrifice for ur art and u will be repaid but ask of art to sacrifice herself for u and a bitter disappointment may come to u Oscar Wilde    
    
    
    @knowdler Si si pensar es googlear en el cerebro    
    
    
    Cursos online que me han interesado Gamification Pensilvania, Making sense of Data Toronto, Crush course creativity Stamford, Genes Maryland    
    
    
    @amaiaATICOmpany ya te dire algo si al final tomo alguno    
    
    
    I'm using @simplymeasured to analyze my Twitter followers in Excel. http://bit.ly/owpX5r     
    
    
    Gracias @arrobero @pinobethencourt @blogypan sí un privilegio a room with a view justamente ayer 28, 72 años de la muerte de Virginia Woolf    
    
    
    @jmgrande @pinobethencourt @blogypan Gracias Jesus por hoy y muchos viernes    
    
    
    Para emprendedores @loic toca teclas clave con ejemplos inspirador @loic 10 ways to start your business doing nothing http://buff.ly/YIFP9T     
    
    
    Corrigiendo error en tweet    
    
    
    @HappenCoworking gracias    
    
    
    I find Bookclub video enlightening of why all angles are necessary for life and specially for #ideas and #innovation http://xurl.es/y3awg     
    
    
    @cthoen Chris thank you for the recent references like your daily http://paper.ly/cthoen 
great #innovation reading source source    
    
    
    Sesión de noche  Bookclub video enlightening, all angles are necessary specially for #ideas and #innovation http://xurl.es/y3awg     
    
    
    I P. McCarthy ‏@Toffeemen68 Should #entrepreneurship be mandatory for professors? http://soa.li/0ayZX6V  ,Yo Creo que si via @elenapisonero    
    
    
    Swiss top innovators due to international public-private co-publications strong linkages between industry and science http://xurl.es/8b8j7     
    
    
    Innovative students should dropout of school or have university education a hybrid educational system is what matters http://xurl.es/kghz4     
    
    
    GEM Entrepreneurship monitor Ghana Nigeria Thayland top Brazil Equador,Uganda Switzerland next #Women  equalization http://xurl.es/io5rz  -    
    
    
    Finland most innovative economies, only country where students leave high school ‘innovation-ready. http://xurl.es/aani6  Invent your job    
    
    
    #womenquotes "Silent gratitude isn't very much use to anyone"Gertrude Stein La Gratitud silenciosa no le sirve a nadie via @marta_dominguez    
    
    
    @jorgesegado @juanmanfredi @vicentelozano @jtoufi gracias Jorge    
    
    
    @loogic @ideasvodafone si si Javier muy cierto un abrazo    
    
    
    @EL_Bijani gracias    
    
    
    @Virginiapalonso @_anapastor_ gracias Virginia    
    
    
    My own version of an optimist.If I can't make it through one door, I'll go through another door - or I'll make a  door. Rabindranath Tagore    
    
    
    The butterfly counts not months but moments, and has time enough.
Rabindranath Tagore. Time management    
    
    
    The Economist World’s next great leap forward: Towards the end of poverty. Avances en reducción de pobreza extrema  http://www.economist.com/news/leaders/21578665-nearly-1-billion-people-have-been-taken-out-extreme-poverty-20-years-world-should-aim?frsc=dg%7Ca …    
    
    
    Irene Natividad Global Summit #women are the third billion in Business y seguimos siendo y somos clave en las economias mundiales    
    
    
    Presidenta Kosovo Global Summit #women Ambition crossing borders of rigid politics/regulation is our strength & raising children as equals    
    
    
    Kosovo Prime Minister she says #women are 40% of entrepreneurship 
and new smes of the emergent  markets Global Summit    
    
    
    #women caregivers and decision 
makers but in part of the world have no freedom:rights. tbe one big voice and together we can make changes    
    
    
    #inspirationday Emma Fernandez Magic ones with a price, todo tiene un precio    
    
    
    Lo siento Corrijo me cuesta en el iphone  #inspirationday Magic comes with a price, Todo tiene un precio    
    
    
    #inspirationday @ricardo_lop  al cliente lo minimo pidele lo imprescindible no le hagas darte datos q no vas a usar la navegabilidad clave    
    
    
    A good manager innovates all things correctly, a good leader only innovates a few, the correct and trenscendent ones #innovation    
    
    
    Its said leaders know and show the way to others, I believe a good leader always doubts of all paths and teaches us to question them,    
    
    
    Steve Jobs "Innovation distinguises a leader and a follower".  I believe leaders' innovations are more disruptive and improve the world    
    
    
    Leaders make people dream, learn, grow, improve and be happy. El líder hace que la gente sueñe, aprenda, crezca, mejore y sea feliz    
    
    
    Leaders are a step ahead in their vision, at the same height, closer in the day to day, and a step behind, leaving space, when delegating    
    
    
    Una idea/historia para una pelicula #Ideas wanted: Amazon Studios baits aspiring screenwriters with Storyteller  http://xurl.es/etuk0     
    
    
    You sharpen your #ideas by reducing yourself to the level of the people you are with and a sense of humour and a complete relaxation Mandela    
    
    
    I tell them, I was also a terrorist yesterday, but, today, I am admired by the very people who said I was one. Mandela Los tiempos cambian    
    
    
    “@TOLMOS: En el Hotel Palace /cc @anamariallopis pic.twitter.com/yYhmt0lP3v” great words future of internet    
    
    
    “After climbing a great hill, one only finds that there are many more hills to climb.” Mandela/ It applies to #innovation, it's a continum    
    
    
    I have cherished the ideal of a democratic and free society with equal opportunities it is an ideal for which I am prepared to die. Mandela    
    
    
    “Nelson Mandela has lived every word of his teaching, whatever the cost. His abiding lesson is about forgiveness" Deepak Chopra,    
    
    
    "I realized they could take everything form me except my mind and heart and I decided not to give them away". Mandela Long walk to freedom    
    
    
    I went through the gate if I still hated them, they would still have me.I wanted to be free. And so I let it go.Mandela Long walk to freedom    
    
    
    Cerf @vgcerf en Madrid habló de Internet of things y los implantes, ahora the internet of you via @carlosdomingo http://xurl.es/lusu7     
    
    
    @topideas4alleng Picasso on creativity/innovation, "Its another thing, you turn your head and its another thing" Innovators, another thing    
    
    
    @Rakelmarkos @Emprendedores gracias    
    
    
    @Juanatalavera buenos dias para ti también Juana    
    
    
    @anamariallopis    
    
    
    Thanks @mediaczar for sharing Why everyone is more popular than you? Great network maths. http://mczar.me/128LFTK  .Siempre+ populares que tú    
    
    
    Just finished preparing in-company  conference which I have named The Digital Transformation Tornado. Enjoyed  learning via papers/videos    
    
    
    "It is better to have useless knowledge than to know nothing" Seneca. I think useless knowledge to most is knowledge to some    
    
    
    "All art is an imitation of nature" Seneca. I believe Nature is all, is everywhere is part of all we see feel and create    
    
    
    BigData useless knowledge until analysis/hypothesis validation and conclusions to act innovatively occur. BD intrinsically useful knowledge    
    
    
    "Be silent as to services you have rendered, but speak of favours you have received" Seneca    
    
    
    "I shall never be ashamed of citing a bad author if the line is good"Seneca. Lo mismo hacía Casals con los intérpretes encontrar el instante    
    
    
    "If one does not know to which port one is sailing, no wind is favorable" Seneca. Consejo a emprendedores, saber puerto dónde quieres llegar    
    
    
    Dear @BernieHernie Me gustaria hablar contigo but I dont have your new email left message KRs    
    
    
    Discovering Science communicator Neil deGrasse Tyson "One should not be too distracted by definitions. Ideas often transcend definitions.”    
    
    
    Neil deGrasse Tyson When I tweet I carve the words and whats left is the most important concept to communicate in a simple & most direct way    
    
    
    Neil deGrasse Tyson "When I tweet I feel like Michael Angelo I cut away everything that is not... a tweet  is like a soundbite"    
    
    
    @neiltyson "We're entering a new era where science and space in particular are artists muses, taking a new relationship with your culture"    
    
    
    Braque, La realidad sólo se revela iluminada por un rayo de #poesía. Reality only reveals itself when it is illuminated by a ray of poetry.    
    
    
    American biggest firms: Back on top | @TheEconomist http://econ.st/1ervBU9 . Últimos 4 años emergentes bajan USA sube pic.twitter.com/reEC2yGeOu    
    
    
    Georges Braque "La verdad existe , sólo las mentiras se inventan" . Truth exists only lies are invented pic.twitter.com/aBlkfvql92    
    
    
    Good morning , interesting article; Economic history: When did globalisation start? | @TheEconomist http://econ.st/17TWquV     
    
    
    Quote O´Leary @EFNI "Brussels is the Empire Base, Berlaymont bdg the Death Star where every shred of innovation is left outside the door"    
    
    
    @EFNI Innovation Euro strategy failed, it was treated as an official religion leading to disbursement of tax revenues on admin objectives    
    
    
    @EFNI Euro Innovation Strategy failed, Many countries policies of R&D based mainly on grants thus making #innovation dependent on EU funds    
    
    
    @EFNI National policies treated ideas and projects in a protectionist manner preventing the emergence of a European common #innovation space    
    
    
    @EFNI Innovation by regions in Europe, Spain lets do better and start working to lead in some sectors pic.twitter.com/5SBjBYNPEH    
    
    
    @BernieHernie trying to contact you good #ideas please call    
    
    
    If an elderly scientist states something is possible, he is almost certainly right. if impossible, he is very probably wrong. Clarke's Law    
    
    
    Artgur Clark's 2nd Law "The only way of discovering the limits of the possible is to venture a little way past them into the impossible"    
    
    
    Arthur Clarke's 3rd Law"Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from magic" that is why it suffers resistance #innovation    
    
    
    @monicadeza @ernestociorra at #innova13 @ideas4all pic.twitter.com/eVT84ba1FL    
    
    
    @ernestociorra  ask a brazilian what is change he gives you ideas and welcomes opportunities #innova13    
    
    
    @ernestociorra  you ask an Italuan qhat is change he does not give you ideas hecis afraid of cost savings  and losin his job    
    
    
    #innova13 @ernestociorra la #innovacion debe medirse e incentivarse con KPIs    
    
    
    @anamariallopis: Can you have a square wheel we dont want a round wheel the type of reaction to inovation great sgort film #innova13    
    
    
    @Inma_Eiroa Muchas gracias Inma    
    
    
    #TUOPORTUNIDAD1, EL INNOVADOR DISRUPTIVO Y EL MAVERIK, …http://quatremots-anamariallopis.blogspot.com.es/2013/10/tu-oportunidad-el-innovador-disruptivo.html … @CHRISTIANRF @jperezdolset lecciones pic.twitter.com/78w4lcfKrF    
    
    
    The best time to plant an #idea was ten years ago, the second time is today, plant your ideas, you wont regret it    
    
    
    “@anapiccola: Good #infography "@IndiaToday #RIPNelsonMandela pic.twitter.com/sY3aVj5ga9"” Me ha gustado    
    
    
    "Part of being optimistic is keeping one's head pointed toward the sun, one's feet moving forward" Mandela    
    
    
    As promised, we still don't have many answers. So far the avg. is 6,8 ideas/day. We would love to know how many #ideas /day you have    
    
    
    There are no big vs. small ideas. Just ones you believe in. Don't waste time guessing their size.Just do them.Hiroshi Ishii MIT @NovaXestion    
    
    
        
    
    
    "@SteveCase As Software Eats The World,Non-Tech Corp Are Eating Startups http://tcrn.ch/JnQPF  "Behind software/Startups are ideas/ideators    
    
    
    Martin Luther King "I was not afraid of the words of the violent, but of the silence of the honest"    
    
    
    "@SteveCase As Software Eats The World,Non-Tech Corp Are Eating Startups http://tcrn.ch/JnQPF  "Behind Software/Startups are #ideas/talent    
    
    
    Ensalada plus se Vanesa pic.twitter.com/NAeVEJilnK    
    
    
    Noche Centro Niemeyer pic.twitter.com/vuTy1UEfVQ    
    
    
    They did it again "WE ARE LIGHT" El Chorrillo Panamá, Graffiti @Boamistura Social #innovation WOW the Watson dance http://vimeo.com/m/82264239     
    
    
    @BOAMISTURA lo que hacéis es Social #innovation. You do real Social #innovation an injection of optimism in Brazil, South Africa, Panamá    
    
    
    Seasons Greetings, ideas4all Team Eng https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yo-Hl8qzY2E#t=6 …. Wake up the kid in you. Share  #ideas    
    
    
    @isgavi @EPEconomia Gracias    
    
    
    Alan Turing "We can only see a short distance ahead, but we can see plenty there that needs to be done" Lets do things, make #ideas happen    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Mathematical reasoning...is the combination of two facilities, which we may call intuition and ingenuity"#ideation uses both    
    
    
    Alan Turing "A computer would deserve to be called intelligent if it could deceive a human into believing that it was human" Its hapenning    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Science is a differential equation. Religion is a boundary condition" Para pensar    
    
    
    Alan Turing "Machines take me by surprise with great frequency" I could not agree more specially today #ideas, design, technology combined    
    
    
    Alan Turing One of the greatest innovators, the imagination to decipher codes and other mathematical challenges #innovation #ideas    
    
    
    One of my favorites "The Cambridge Quintet" by Casti. A dinner of Scientists discussing the human possibilities of Turings' like machines    
    
    
    2014 new hope to knees recovery,ligament discovered. Anatomy #innovation #discovery http://reut.rs/1gys7Op  Esperanza para nuestras rodillas.    
    
    
    T EDISON “Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time” Play it again Sam    
    
    
    Thomas Edison “If we all did the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves” Always try your best, people will notice    
    
    
    "We live in new times -the age of the hero is past- now is the time of the non-virtuous man". Gogol 1842, He could have written this in 2008    
    
    
    Great @Google is celebrating Simone de Beauvoirs 106 birthday, Thanks from me, Spain, and many other #women as well pic.twitter.com/YsiAi2X3TO    
    
    
    "Change your life today. Don't gamble on the future, act now, without delay." Simone de Beauvoir .Great advise #entrepreneurs #women    
    
    
    Simone de Beauvoir "I tore myself away from the safe comfort of certainties through my love for truth - and truth rewarded me".    
    
    
    Via @brainpicker: H C Andersen's little-known sketches & beautiful travel notes on Europe http://j.mp/1hDWnKH ” sensitive travel sketches    
    
    
    Inequality by the click. Technology and new jobs not enough Adair Turner and Pope Francis @INETeconomics @ProSyn http://bit.ly/1kuomPb     
    
    
    @jguereta hecho    
    
    
    