En dan verneem je plots dat je vermeld wordt - Journalists detained, attacked amid unrest in Egypt - http://cpj.org/x/56a1     
    
    
    @yaseralzayat @AltenaB Dunkiville, beautiful!    
    
    
    Johan Heldenberg en @JensFranssen over een interventie in Syrië. Wel of niet ingrijpen?  Bij @JanHautekiet    
    
    
    Het is nog lang niet voorbij! @AP: BREAKING: #Egyptian officials say Interior Minister has survived car bomb explosion targeting his convoy.    
    
    
    @janeikelboom het is toch al een verdubbeling!    
    
    
    Schrijft aan een stuk over radicalisering bij #MB voor @nrcnext en dan dit:Bomb explodes near Eg. intr. min.'s convoy http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/80840.aspx     
    
    
    #AntiCoup Alliance Calls "People Protect Revolution" Friday #Sep6 http://www.ikhwanweb.com/article.php?id=31297 … … #egyanticoup    
    
    
    @tarekshalaby how can I reach you today?    
    
    
    Read this article http://shar.es/isAdH   and support the @DailyNewsEgypt ! @MaherHamoud1    
    
    
    Wat met Egypte? Morgen te horen in #deochtend op @radio1be iets na 8h00.  @JoostScheffers    
    
    
    @JoostScheffers @JacoStoop Zie het nu pas, ging hopelijk goed! @JacoStoop tot wanneer ben je in Nederland?    
    
    
    @AltenaB @JoostScheffers Dat hoor je morgen!  (En Joost, ik doe mijn best he in de zelfverkoop/propaganda!)    
    
    
    @JoostScheffers @AltenaB Oh wat fijn! Dan zien we elkaar binnenkort weer!    
    
    
    @JoostScheffers Ik ga dat toch niet meer doen... ik vind het maar niets. Maar goed, ik moest het een keer proberen he!    
    
    
    HRW report on CW in #syria via @bouckap http://www.hrw.org/node/118725/     
    
    
    @Misslernhkr Njah, I do not really need that... but thanks anyway...    
    
    
    Military targets attacked in Sinai, 6 dead | Mada Masr http://www.madamasr.com/content/military-targets-attacked-sinai-6-dead … via @madamasr    
    
    
    BY IWPR - Syria: How It All Began: http://youtu.be/GvV4RSJSWH4     
    
    
    #egypt Adly Mansour (of was het Sisi?) verlengt de noodtoestand en #curfew. Einde was gepland op vrijdag de 13de... http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/81455.aspx     
    
    
    Jihadi group Bayt al-Maqdis threatens further attacks in Cairo, Alexandria: (Al-Watan via @erictrager18) http://bit.ly/1g5sjSR     
    
    
    Egypt extends state of emergency 2 months: For ref. 12 Sept. 2013 http://reut.rs/13RHv3A   - tot midden november dus erg gezellig daar!    
    
    
    @HaraldDoornbos Ik vreesde al een triest verhaal...    
    
    
    Meer geweld weer in #Egypt - BBC News - Egypt hit by pro and anti-Mohammed Morsi protests http://bbc.in/1eMzYrr     
    
    
    Hoppa, een week de tijd voor #Assad om een inventaris van #CW op te stellen en onder internationaal toezicht te plaatsen. #Syria @radio1be    
    
    
    De Ensors, met die voor beste debuut voor de straffe Charlotte De Bruyne! http://www.standaard.be/cnt/dmf20130914_00741562?utm_source=facebook&utm_medium=social&utm_term=dso&utm_content=article&utm_campaign=seeding …    
    
    
    Foto's van @JeffRuig van ons laatste bezoek aan Syrië: Syrisch militair trainingskamp voor jonge Koerden http://cult.thepostonline.nl/2013/09/04/beeld-syrisch-militair-trainingskamp-voor-jonge-koerdische-marxisten/ … via @TPOnl    
    
    
    @DemuynckDi @JeffRuig @TPOnl Het gaat over de foto's he. Niettegenstaande is YPG filosofie daar wel echt op gebaseerd, zo zeggen ze zelf.    
    
    
    School textbook calls 30 June a coup, Education Minister halts its printing | Egypt Independent http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/school-textbook-calls-30-june-coup-education-minister-halts-its-printing … via @egyindependent    
    
    
    Onze collega @JensFranssen leest tussen de lijnen van het VN rapport – #Syria #CW http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/1.1731787 …    
    
    
    @jonamorem I have it on my computer, in case you want it!    
    
    
    Nog drie keer slapen #D66 Day of the Middle East in #Utrecht met @petra_stienen en @koertdebeuf !! https://www.facebook.com/events/483038761774176/?fref=ts …    
    
    
    M'n stuk over seksueel geweld in #Egypt nu ook in Vlaanderen te lezen via @Knack http://www.knack.be/nieuws/wereld/egypte-president-afzetten-is-gemakkelijker-dan-vrouwen-beschermen-tegen-seksueel-geweld/article-opinion-106441.html …    
    
    
    Vote for our amazing initiative 'Syrious Mission' http://voordewereldvanmorgen.nl/Kom_in_actie/ASN_Bank_Wereldprijs/Projecten/Syrious_Mission … & share @koertdebeuf @radio1be @JeffRuig @janeikelboom @RenaNetjes    
    
    
    On the return of the security state. The story of a foreign journalist. #Egypt The deep return | @MadaMasr http://www.madamasr.com/content/deep-return …    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes When I asked them why they are so expensive, they told me it's because it is #belgianchocolate Ya rab! #sisi #egypt    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes @MLMeulenbroek Helemaal van chocolade! Zelf de kaders van de chocoladefotokaders zijn puur Belgische chocolade!    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes Egyptian made with Belgian chocolate maybe? Or do they have a cheaper version nowadays?    
    
    
    Vandaag in @DeGroene m'n stuk vanuit Zaatari vluchtelingenkamp - Driehonderd dollar voor Syrische bruid http://www.groene.nl/2013/38/driehonderd-dollar-voor-syrische-bruid …    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter @DeGroene Ben jij in Nederland? Niet in NY? Ik ben dit weekend in Utrecht/Amsterdam!    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter @DeGroene DM!    
    
    
    "Pottenrevolutie" in Egypte - Annabell Van den Berghe http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/1.1733049 … wat is er van de revolutionairen geworden? - op @vrtderedactie    
    
    
    @AltenaB @janeikelboom Men zegt dat wijsheid met de jaren komt... Ik kan nu echt niet anders dan dat te geloven. #ervaringsdeskundigen    
    
    
    Belgisch koppel wist uit winkelcentrum te ontsnappen - De Standaard http://www.standaard.be/cnt/dmf20130921_00752973?utm_source=facebook&utm_medium=social&utm_term=dso&utm_content=article&utm_campaign=seeding … via @destandaard    
    
    
    Na #D66MiddleEast met @koertdebeuf, @petra_stienen en @AltenaB op weg naar A'dam op bezoek bij @JeffRuig en @DeGroene. #delagelandenzijnin    
    
    
    Door @rechterhans - Waar zijn de vrouwelijke journalisten in Syrië? Overal! http://debuitenlandredactie.nl/2013/09/waar-zijn-de-vrouwelijke-journalisten-in-syrie-overal/ … @debuitenlandred    
    
    
    @petra_stienen @rechterhans Wauw, samen met @Raniaab. Vast en zeker de moeite waard! Afstemmen op #buitenhof dus!    
    
    
    @AltenaB nu nog bij @DeGroene zien hoe de Nederlandse brandweer net als in #egypte de brand niet helpt te blussen. pic.twitter.com/be7tlx9tT3    
    
    
    @Bassem_Sabry my question exactly!    
    
    
    "Geen brand"? Waar rook is, is vuur. Ook in het transformatorhuisje. #meteigenogengezien http://www.nu.nl/algemeen/3582802/stroomstoring-in-deel-centrum-amsterdam.html … via @NUnl    
    
    
    @KajaVerbeke Dankje!    
    
    
    What to do in #Cairo? An overwiew... http://www.cuipcairo.org/     
    
    
    @joostbastmeijer Verdorie toch...    
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 My thoughts exactly, tomorrow in @nrcnext.    
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 Egypte keert terug naar de militaire almacht - @DeMorgen - http://s.demorgen.be/1710929?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=web#.UkLg7tpvNIg.twitter … …    
    
    
    Why you should all visit Ghent!  http://www.standaard.be/cnt/blrto_20130925_001?utm_source=facebook&utm_medium=social&utm_term=dso&utm_content=article&utm_campaign=seeding … @destandaard    
    
    
    Christian Louboutin turns heel on anti-Islamist ad http://ara.tv/yuhyr  via @AlArabiya_Eng #VlaamsBelang maakt zich weer populair.    
    
    
    The Islamic Rebel Alliance (not) to restore the Syrian Republic - Your Middle East http://www.yourmiddleeast.com/features/the-islamic-rebel-alliance-not-to-restore-the-syrian-republic_18284 …    
    
    
    @RelHajoui Het teken dat alles goed gaat... Pas als ze de verkeersruzies staken, gaat het echt mis. #Egypt in dat geval.    
    
    
    Zo, tegen de lente heeft #Egypt nieuwe president! @reuters: Egypt's foreign minister says trans. gov. end by spring http://reut.rs/1ePHWS6     
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 @RenaNetjes And yet, you can't live without any of both sides... I know, we know...    
    
    
    Nog maar net opnieuw gewend geraakt aan #Cairo en het volgende #protest staat al gepland. Zondag #6Oct #Egypt    
    
    
    @operationlibyia @koertdebeuf @SaikoSomaTick Oh yeah, that nun...    
    
    
    @p_vanostaeyen Gezien! Ik ben benieuwd wat dat nu weer gaat geven...    
    
    
    Lovely to see the amazing @NihalSaad today. Inspiring as always! #Egypt #cairo is not totally depressed yet! #optimism #strongpersonality    
    
    
    #Egypt's curfew gives you plenty of time to finish all the projects you could never finish... #alwayslookatthebrightside #Cairo    
    
    
    Explosions in #Dokki and #Downtown being heard. Also in #GardenCity our apartment is suffering from tear gas. #Cairo #Egypt    
    
    
    Thousands of Muslim Brotherhood protesters march in Cairo http://reut.rs/1gafU2M  via @reuters    
    
    
    @Aaron_T_Rose @cliffcheney Same here...    
    
    
    Few thousands protesters fled into Mounira after clashes and gunfire on qasrelaini. Quieter now.    
    
    
    Rabaa zou groter zijn. Voorlopig rustiger in Mounira en Downtown.    
    
    
    One muslimbrother killed during the clashes near Tahrir, a medical says to @Reuters    
    
    
    Allez hop... Sexual harassed door de politieagenten die net een MB neerschoten. Ik zal maar zwijgen zeker?!    
    
    
    @liamstack from qasr al Aini and manual    
    
    
    @liamstack but things calmed down here    
    
    
    @liamstack yes. Heading towards manial    
    
    
    @liamstack traffic is back here.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @masmou3 still banging pots?    
    
    
    Listening now #documentarymaking in #Egypt RT @ganzeer Want to calm down in the midst of this mess, Aya Metwally: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nJP_pHDjLAI&feature=c4-overview&list=UUqY2DW1AZtVTdHbysHgNx0A … …    
    
    
    @amtwll    
    
    
    Comparing #MB to #Israel : Tamarod calls for celebrations in Tahrir Square, Ettehadiya http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/tamarod-calls-celebrations-tahrir-square-ettehadiya … via @egyindependent #egypt    
    
    
    Remembering the good old days! On my way to #CairoJazz to listen to #WustElBalad and the amazing #Mezo!    
    
    
    Streets in Cairo are empty. No traffic. Meanwhile #Tahrir is getting big. A lot of people, national flags and tanks of course.    
    
    
    Lichtpuntje? Egypt releases two Canadians, acclaimed director John Greyson and Dr. Tarek Loubani, held without charge http://gu.com/p/3jaq8/tw     
    
    
    Verschillende anti-coup betogingen gaan nu richting Tahrir, waar de coup supporters zich verzamelen om #6Oct te vieren. #Egypt    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AltenaB Ik denk dat ze mij in Nederland net beter kennen... Maar jullie zijn met meer natuurlijk. #Tahrir is al enorm, en #MB zijn onderweg    
    
    
    Any news on the time of curfew tonight? #Egypt #Cairo    
    
    
    MOH tells AJE 1 Muslim Brotherhood protester has been killed during clashes with security forces in village of Delga, in Menya. #Egypt    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter Zo snel mogelijk?    
    
    
    @evaludemann yes    
    
    
    Tahrir and Maspero are fully packed. So far only pro army and pro morsi chants.    
    
    
    @EduardCousin you could say so indeed    
    
    
    Hmm steeds meer sirenes van ziekenwagens op de corniche. Ik zie voorlopig nog geen clashes of gevechten op het plein.    
    
    
    Was just stopped at kempinsky next to 4seasons. No entrance possible due to clashes with police and Anticoup alliance. Tear gas fired.    
    
    
    Traffic is coming back to corniche, mostly ambulances.... #Tahrir #6oct    
    
    
    Heavy security in gardencity. Tahrir had the athmosphere of celebrations for an hour or so, now clashes. Also elsewhere in #Egypt    
    
    
    At this side of Tahrir there was only teargas, at the other side also gunfire reported #Egypt #oct6    
    
    
    @evaludemann was quiet for à while, now the streets around the square arent too safe... Ambulances, teargas, gunfire and it only started    
    
    
    Horns in support of alSisi in one ear, anti Sisi chants in the other one. GardenCity #oct6    
    
    
    Tahrir seems an island of illusions. Ppl celebrating '73 while in its surroundings police and army are pushing #MB back with gas and guns.    
    
    
    @WestonBurma you seriously believe i am looking for a job at this time? #oct6    
    
    
    Again heavy fights in front of four seasons.    
    
    
    @jonamorem @ianjameslee Inventive I must say...    
    
    
    Hearing gunfire near Tahrir, on the corniche. #oct6 #Egypt    
    
    
    Helikopters vliegen heeeeeeeeel laag boven mijn hoofd... #Egypt #Oct6    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf Perfect moment...    
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 Don't be too optimistic ya 'albi!    
    
    
    So far I couldn't confirm. RT @EgyAntiCoup Breaking || Martyr in Doki. #AntiCoup #Oct6 pic.twitter.com/rA8lw706QA    
    
    
    @Ateyya Few #MB members tried to reach #Tahrir through a small boat to the Nile shores from Maspero side. #oct6 #egypt    
    
    
    A couple of very young (underaged) guys heading with sticks towards Tahrir...  Not sure which side they are on. #Oct6    
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 its ironic. How would i think you being optimistic these days? Hatta ana mish mutafa'ila!    
    
    
    @evaludemann lots of women in Tahrir. In the march towards it coming from the corniche not.    
    
    
    Ppl in #Tahrir asking to sign petition to have Sisi for president. 'The one who listens to the ppls voice'    
    
    
    On their way to #tahrir lets celebrate!! pic.twitter.com/RmiJKsYb7e    
    
    
    @evaludemann a part of it, but thats not representing the different groups    
    
    
    Gunfire around Tahrir and fireworks above it. This is unbelievable. Meanwhile heli's giving a show.    
    
    
    Gigantische rookwolk boven #tahrir    
    
    
    @evaludemann trying to find this out. This is called the revolutionairy front but havent heard of demo's by them today.    
    
    
    En nu de minder vrolijke. #elkombeurt pic.twitter.com/QzNyxwlKiM    
    
    
    @weskandar there has to be a bit of variation of course...    
    
    
    @weskandar four,going back and forth all the time...    
    
    
    Gunfire again!    
    
    
    @weskandar make it eight    
    
    
    @yaseralzayat da'iman    
    
    
    Flying lower and lower...    
    
    
    Surroundings of #Tahrir are nasty.  some thugs came after me but a semiramisguard helped escaping. Fled trough back entrance, heading home    
    
    
    @DLachine @Zeinobia @bothainakamel1 @koertdebeuf    
    
    
    And then you pause your conversation since the jets are flying too close. Can't hear each other, windows are almost exploding...    
    
    
    3 dead in Menya and 2 in Cairo, anyone can confirm?    
    
    
    “@MaiE_89: .@ONtvLIVE is reporting at least 15 dead in today's clashes. #Egypt”    
    
    
    @JacoStoop yes just saw it on ONtv!    
    
    
    @islamudinsajid thanks!    
    
    
    In Belgium it is the train I am hearing every 5 min. In Egypt I change that for a F16 every single minute.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @islamudinsajid Today wasn't (isn't) a good day indeed.    
    
    
    @islamudinsajid They believe we are biased    
    
    
    Weer 15 doden bij protesten in Egypte http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/1.1747585 …    
    
    
    Doors and windows trembling while F16's flying over #GardenCity    
    
    
    @islamudinsajid Reports of StateTV    
    
    
    Dodental in #Egypt intussen op 28 en nog vier uur tot het uitgaansverbod weer ingaat. #oct6    
    
    
    Health Ministry: 28 killed in #Egypt clashes, 26 of them in #Cairo. #oct6  94 injured nationwide.    
    
    
    So now there is a party in #Tahrir, pro-Sisi. But what happens around Tahrir? How are #Dokki and #Manial and #Ramses, anyone?    
    
    
    Dodental blijft oplopen. MOH tells AJE 34 people killed today across Egypt and 209 injured. #Oct6 #Egypt    
    
    
    @Alastair_Beach @MariamKirollos MOH tells AJE 34 people killed today across Egypt and 209 injured. #Oct6    
    
    
    @JanoCharbel 34 and 209 injured - MOH    
    
    
    @AnubisIIVII At this moment? Are they still there because things seem to have calmed down.    
    
    
    @BBishay1 Still at this point? And were exactly because at this side (corniche) it is calm now.    
    
    
    Numbers so far: 28 death, 209 injured and 423 arrested in #Egypt today #Oct6    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KetyDC @bencnn @Reuters Were do you get the number 44? I know about 38.    
    
    
    @moftasa @KetyDC Were do you get the number 44 from? I can't find this at MOH, I only find 38.    
    
    
    @moftasa @KetyDC (great profile picture 3ala fikra!)    
    
    
    @moftasa @KetyDC Thanks!    
    
    
    @PatrickKingsley Amazing how #Egypt communicates isn't it! Sad story, definitely, but the honking is an art at least. All about #traffic    
    
    
    @PatrickKingsley 44 killed, 229 injured and 423 arrested. Still counting.    
    
    
    @leloveluck cheesecake would also do.    
    
    
    De twee canadese journalisten die gisteren werken vrijgelaten mogen #egypt niet verlaten. #stoplist aan de luchthaven! #pressfreedom    
    
    
    De balans van gisteren, 53 doden en bijna 300 gewonden. Meer dan Mohamed Mahmoud vorig jaar over vijf dagen tijd.    
    
    
    Oog om oog, tand on tand. Weer 5 soldaten gedood vandaag in #egypt    
    
    
    En aan bomauto in de Sinai. #Egypt    
    
    
    @DGNeree geen probleem. Dank!    
    
    
    @evaludemann I did, thanks. Working on this still, they decided not to mingle in politics since politics aren't really working...    
    
    
    It's not getting any better soon in #Egypt: Anti-Coup Alliance: We will protest in Tahrir Square next Friday, no matter what sacrifices are.    
    
    
    Chants against the army at Zeinhom. Mothers crying for their sons who died in yesterday's clashes. #egypt #oct6    
    
    
    Something happening at #Sharm at this time? Ppl talking about another attack but can't confirm. #Egypt    
    
    
    So far nothing more on #Sharm, have the feeling this is either a miscommunication or someone stirring ill-feeling. #Egypt    
    
    
    @SimaDiab @Nader_G_Attar heading there tomorrow, leaving Cairo in the morning I case someone has blankets but no time to head there    
    
    
    On Sunday 39 ppl died from live ammunition. #oct6. #egypt #cairo    
    
    
    Egypt’s Military Is Burning, Looting, and Destroying Its Way Across the Sinai Peninsula http://www.slate.com/articles/news_and_politics/foreigners/2013/10/abdel_fattah_al_sisi_s_sinai_campaign_egypt_s_military_is_targeting_civilians.html … via @slate    
    
    
    Heading to Montaza station. Syrian refugees still being held there. #Egypt #alexandria    
    
    
    Clashes between pro-Sisi and pro-Morsi supporters today in Zagazig, Morsi's hometown. #egypt    
    
    
    Furqan claimed verantwoordelijkheid voor de aanslagen gisteren in #egypt MB blijft het geweld officieel afkeuren, Furqan steunt wel Morsi    
    
    
    #maspero twee jaar geleden, 28 doden door toedoen van militairen. Sommigen herinneren het zich nog, maar het blijft opvallend stil. #egypy    
    
    
    #pt kopten waren slachtoffer van sectarisch geweld door leger, vandaag steunen ze Sisi massaal... Angst voor MB w steeds groter.    
    
    
    Vandaag in @DeGroene m'n stukje over patrouilles tegen seksueel geweld in de metro van #cairo #egypt. Privé initiatief en politievrouwen!    
    
    
    De Groene Amsterdammer - Veilig in de Egyptische vrouwenwagon http://www.groene.nl/2013/41/veilig-in-de-egyptische-vrouwenwagon …    
    
    
        
    
    
    A lot of tea and a lot of friendly female smiling can get you far in #egypt #alexandria #montaza    
    
    
    Another 30 Syrian refugees this morning send back to Syria. They fear the Syrian government will arrest them once they arrive in Syria.    
    
    
    Morsy to be brought to trial on Ettihadiya incidents 4 November | Egypt Independent http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/morsy-be-brought-trial-ettihadiya-incidents-4-november … via @egyindependent    
    
    
    @vrancki is reporting from Za'atari refugee camp for Belgian radio and television, follow her for interestig updates! #Syria1212 #Zaatari    
    
    
    Libya's prime minister was kidnapped and released again apparently. Things can go fast.    
    
    
    Dan denk je, in Nederland is het net zo erg als in België. Blijkt het over een Belg in Nederland te gaan... #zedenfeiten    
    
    
    Almost zero journalists in #Libya. Seems everybody wants to be based in #Egypt #Lebanon or #Jordan. @JoostScheffers it's time to run!    
    
    
    @hugohooijkaas Cuijk is Tongeren? Van mij mag je hem hebben! #zedenfeiten    
    
    
    Opnieuw een aanslag in #Egypt: Suicide bombing kills 3 troops, 1 policeman http://shar.es/EromX     
    
    
    US cuts militairy aid to #Egypt, Israel fears more attacks near Gaza border. Today already a suicide bomb in El-Arish, near border. #Sinai    
    
    
    Having a chat with Malala Yousafzai tomorrow. #nobleprice    
    
    
    Please RT: Love to hear your thoughts! How are Middle East Governments Addressing Gaps? Link to discussion & event:  http://www.maarefah.net/open-government/resource/video-justice-sector …    
    
    
    Vandaag op radio1 muziek v Edith Piaf en interessant nieuws vanuit Zaatari @Vrancki http://www.radio1.be/programmas/vandaag/conflict-syrië-drijft-inwoners-naar-buurlanden …    
    
    
    Back from #Montaza's Syrian refugees. Pro-Sisi marches planned tomorrow in #Cairo mainly. Then off to #Sinai. Always something in #Egypt    
    
    
    Good overview on #Egypt RT @reuters: Special Report - The real force behind Egypt's 'revolution of the state'  http://reut.rs/1fleBzk     
    
    
    Breaking News: Nobel Peace Prize Awarded to Organization for the Prohibition of Chemical Weapons http://nyti.ms/Zf40cq     
    
    
    @Bassem_Sabry You're attending live?    
    
    
    Follow Worldbank's session online! http://live.worldbank.org/transition-open-government-arab-world … 'on Social media outreach used by WB'    
    
    
    @Bassem_Sabry And please, to share your ideas during and also after the session, go to: http://www.maarefah.net/open-government/resource/video-justice-sector …    
    
    
    Minister Nahas (Lebanon): #wblive democracy is not something you can buy - you must practice it    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter Ben je in Cairo?    
    
    
    Nine injured in Kafr El-Sheikh clashes http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/83795.aspx  #Lukaku is vandaag dus groter nieuws!    
    
    
    @adamakary Do we know more on this?    
    
    
    @adamakary @Cairo67Unedited @Rassd_News and do we know who it is?    
    
    
    @leloveluck @cliffcheney @erinmcunningham @basildabh Please, include me in this... Starving as well. #GarcenCity    
    
    
    Her last days #eid #cairo http://instagram.com/p/fXbkKRl1Eo/     
    
    
    49 mensen omgekomen in #Peru. Altijd dichter dan je denkt. #Kenia #Egypt #Peru    
    
    
    De Groene Amsterdammer - Veilig in de Egyptische vrouwenwagon http://www.groene.nl/commentaar/2013-10-11/veilig-in-de-egyptische-vrouwenwagon?fb_action_ids=10151629253032000&fb_action_types=og.likes&fb_source=other_multiline&action_object_map=%257B%252210151629253032000%2522%253A606385786085851%257D&action_type_map=%257B%252210151629253032000%2522%253A%2522og.likes%2522%257D&action_ref_map=%255B%255D …    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf Zijde gij daar niet een beetje te oud voor?    
    
    
    Russian photographer abducted by Syrian rebels          http://ara.tv/zscas  via @AlArabiya_Eng    
    
    
    Hmm how much lower can these jets actually fly? #gardencity #cairo #sisi    
    
    
    State TV confirms one died and one injured in plane crash in Luxor. #egypt    
    
    
    Vandaag voorlopig rustig in Caïro. In Luxor en Sinaï zijn minder rustig...    
    
    
    RT Syrie:apparemment l'attaque contre la télé et radio du régime est une opération suicide d'un combattant de #JAN https://twitter.com/al_khansaa2/status/389465851931279360 … …    
    
    
    Love it! “@AliTahmizian: Yeeee check out our route to Sokna @Annabellvdb! http://instagram.com/p/faSnnEGD-t/  thanks @shadihamid”    
    
    
    19 injured in Ultras Ahly Cairo Airport clashes, including 1 policeman and 2 conscripts. | @AlMasryAlYoum http://www.almasryalyoum.com/node/2205116  #Egypt    
    
    
    Tear gas and birdshot fired in Cairo airport clashes | News , Middle East | THE DAILY STAR http://www.dailystar.com.lb/News/Middle-East/2013/Oct-13/234585-tear-gas-and-birdshot-fired-in-cairo-airport-clashes.ashx …    
    
    
    @jensfranssen for televions: Herman Nackaerts is positief over toekomst Iraans kernprogramma http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/2.30449?video=1.1754456 …    
    
    
    U.S. citizen found dead in Egyptian prison http://reut.rs/17zWgpo  via @reuters    
    
    
    @Nader_G_Attar would like to call you concerning my trip to Montaza last week. Could you DM your number?    
    
    
    @SimaDiab Would like to call you about my trip to #Montaza last week. Could you DM your number?    
    
    
    RT  @seldeeb Goal   #Egypt #Eid    
    
    
    19 out of 23, does that make me an introvert?  http://huff.to/1d2j6xt     
    
    
    The first day of our #SafeEid action has ended! We prevented 26 cases of harassment. We'll see you tmrw in #TalaatHarb!    
    
    
    Als we dan de Nobelprijs aan een kind moeten geven, dan kies ik voor #Nada! http://www.yourmiddleeast.com/videos/video-yemeni-girl-who-fled-marriage-joins-tv-show-with-egyptian-cleric_18728 … #ChildMarriage    
    
    
    Went to patrol with @Imprint_Mov, an amazing initiative in #Egypt, despite all instabilities in the country. Thumps up for @NihalSaad #Cairo    
    
    
    Pro-Morsi rally in front of al haram hospital. #Cairo RT @Zeinobia    
    
    
    @yaseralzayat Mabrouk! wi hashufak 'urayyib isA 3alashan matinseesh el3arabi!    
    
    
    BREAKING: Car bomb explodes near Egypt army intelligence building- sources http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/84252.aspx  via @ahramonline    
    
    
    Masked men fire on Coptic wedding group in Cairo, killing man, woman and 8-year-old child: http://apne.ws/16p2eKe   -SS    
    
    
    Gunmen open fire on a church wedding in Imbaba. Reports of three dead, including an eight year old child. #Egypt #Cairo    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter What?!  Welke liberalen zijn dat dan precies?    
    
    
    Authorities never made it this difficult in #Egypt. A month to get all permits, and even then you're hold for over 6 hours @ Min. of Defense    
    
    
    Our crew has been released after six hours of custody for not shooting anything. #Egypt isn't very welcoming these days. #Mukhabarat #Cairo    
    
    
    They didn't believe I could have studied Arabic at University, because Arabic isn't a job... Yet another 2 hours being held for that. #Cairo    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter  Oef!    
    
    
    And as if it isn't enough, heading home after shooting at a friends place and being stopped again by officers at this moment. #cairo    
    
    
    Managed to get away after overhearing phone call of the bawab with the police. The boys still being held in the building. #pressfreedom    
    
    
    So even when you're working day is over and you decide to have the first proper meal of the day, #mukhabarat are watching & arresting #cairo    
    
    
    Boys are free as well.    
    
    
    Curious what today will bring. Filming on several places in the city #cairo #pressfreedom    
    
    
    Our crew at Muqattam. http://instagram.com/p/f5c6M9F1C3/     
    
    
    Bert en Leslie vastgehouden bij het ministerie van defensie. http://instagram.com/p/f5c7Mvl1C7/     
    
    
    @JensFranssen RT @vvanwilgenburg YPG claims to have taken control of SyrianIraqi border gate. Significant development if true via @Rojekazad    
    
    
    Two months ago we could still film the #army (with @ramaekers_robin & @JoVerstichel) but these times seem to be over in suspicious #Cairo.    
    
    
    @KajaVerbeke In Egypte gaat het ook die kant uit...    
    
    
    @JensFranssen    
    
    
    Public prosecutor just received a claim accusing @DrBassemYoussef of threatening national security & defamation of Sisi #Egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    A WorldBank event worth attending! On access to information in MENA region! http://www.maarefah.net/portal/event/access-information-maarefah-event …    
    
    
    RT Bel: bizarre report: Jailed and ousted president Morsi says "the military coup is ending soon" in message to son http://www.middleeastmonitor.com/news/africa/7955-morsis-son-conveys-message-to-supporters …”    
    
    
    Another evening at the police station. #cairo #egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    @KajaVerbeke een algemeen gespannen sfeer, en houding tov journalisten...    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes net vrijgelaten!    
    
    
    Back home. Fortunately you can order sushi at any time of the day in Cairo. #curfew #cairo #pressfreedom    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf @RenaNetjes Helaas echt waar. Ze maken het er niet makkelijker op. Maar (voorlopig) dus weer vrij.    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes hij stond inderdaad even uit. Vorige keer gingen ze door al mijn gegevens en dat wilde ik niet nog een keer...    
    
    
    More protests expected tomorrow, asking for independent judiciary. Anti-Coup Alliance to protest on Tuesday http://shar.es/I7SCE     
    
    
    Morsi rejects authority of Egypt court due to try him - Your Middle East http://www.yourmiddleeast.com/news/morsi-rejects-authority-of-egypt-court-due-to-try-him_19020 …    
    
    
    On our way to Tahrir. With permit. But let's wait and see what this will bring. #egypt #cairo #pressfreedom    
    
    
    Small pro Sisi demo in front of Shoura Assembly. #cairo #egypt    
    
    
    @AltenaB vandaag geen bezoek aan het politiekantoor. Wel twee agressieve burgers. #egypt en #paranoia    
    
    
    @Annabellvdb Jammer van die storende dt-fout alweer    
    
    
    #MuslimBrotherhood leader, Esam el-Erian arrested in early morning. He was @FjpartyOrg deputy chief & on run since July army takeover    
    
    
    Yesterday in @VillaVPRO & it's only getting worse. 3 judges have stepped down from MB trial. Morsi keeps rejecting court's authority. #Cairo    
    
    
    Besides one bruise and some ass grabbing, we also got tea. So depends what you consider 'a good treat'.  #Egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    @AltenaB We nemen gewoon de minibus jong.    
    
    
    @tabulagaza Yes.    
    
    
    My story now for @SyriaDeeply today ‘I Sold my Sister to Save the Family’ – Syria News: http://beta.syriadeeply.org/2013/10/i-sold-sister-save-family/#.UnKuG7aIm3J.twitter …    
    
    
    @MattheaVrij @SyriaDeeply @Refugees Thanks!    
    
    
    @uygaraktas Thanks!    
    
    
    Police prevent clashes between al-Sisi and Bassem Youssef supporters outside studio | Egypt Independent http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/police-prevent-clashes-between-al-sisi-and-bassem-youssef-supporters-outside-studio …    
    
    
    Supporters of ousted president Mohamed Morsi to rally outside Police Officers' Academy during his trial on Monday: http://www.google.com/hostednews/afp/article/ALeqM5jbyWcz2T3GpNAI98VCbi1nedGiyA?docId=5129b461-b1a6-4fb1-a658-0e8dda2eec01&hl=en … …    
    
    
    Again only one side of the story. 'Egypt army arrests head of Sinai radical militant group, dozens others' http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/85319.aspx  #Egypt    
    
    
    “Electronic gates will be installed on the road leading to Tora” "MB called for protests in the three days before" http://www.aawsat.net/2013/11/article55321029 …    
    
    
    Sterk! @RGjournalist over hoe de stroom van Syrische vluchtelingen Libanon ontwricht http://www.rtlnieuws.nl/nieuws/laatste-videos-nieuws/oneindige-stroom-syrische-vluchtelingen-gaat-door … … RT @janeikelboom    
    
    
    Egypt detains 22 female Islamist supporters in run up to Morsi trial: http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/egypt-detains-22-women-islamists-morsy-trial … … lawyer says detainees between 15 and 25.    
    
    
    #pressfreedom in #egypt is even getting worse. @DrBassemYoussef is banned...    
    
    
    @lucypawle @TheBigPharaoh My thoughts and experiences exactly! #cairo #egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    After speaking about @pressfreedom in #egypt, I could listen to the amazing @akildasan with #cantaloop #US3 on radio1.be    
    
    
    @DailyNewsEgypt After 3 months, which is the maximum period... Not really a surprise. And still, things can always change quick in #Egypt.    
    
    
    Back-to-back opposing demonstrations held in front of High Court http://shar.es/Ik62t  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @MaherHamoud1 I had one with me, that I am not using... But took it back two days ago. How long can you wait?    
    
    
    @forsoothsayer @Ssirgany fen bizzabt?    
    
    
    Benieuwd wat dat gaat geven! Supreme Council for Journalism praises draft constitution articles on press freedoms http://ow.ly/2BfETV     
    
    
    No recorders, phones, laptops allowed in #Morsi trial tomo. RT @PatrickKingsley    
    
    
    The (on purpose) leaked video of #Morsi from within the quarters where he is being detained http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xw53Xuo44GE …    
    
    
    Robert Fisk : As #Morsi goes to trial, General #Sisi should remember: Egypt is a dangerous place to rule! http://www.independent.co.uk/voices/comment/as-morsi-goes-to-trial-general-sisi-should-remember-egypt-is-a-dangerous-place-to-rule-8919862.html … …    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf @GalalAmrG ?    
    
    
    Can someone confirm? #Egypt Gov announces #Morsi will not attend trial, raising fears about his health & treatment http://www.miamiherald.com/2013/11/03/3729552/morsi-wont-attend-opening-of-his.html … …    
    
    
    Apparently only few foreign journalists got their accreditation to follow #MorsiTrial tomorrow. About 250 in total. #Cairo #Egypt    
    
    
    #MorsiTrial started state TV says, so far no major protests in #Cairo or at the Police Academy in #Tagamu, #Egypt    
    
    
    The dynamic has changed at the barricade. Now protesters r younger men w Guy Fawkes masks and gas masks. Ready to start a fight #MorsiTrial    
    
    
    First session of #MorsiTrial adjourned... #Egypt #cairo    
    
    
    Crowds of #Morsi supporters getting bigger and their chants louder... Security forces on high alert so far no clashes pic.twitter.com/ux88LklpIM    
    
    
    RT Police assaulted photojournalist @3araab in Alex and took camera. Police and pro-Morsi are 2 sides of the same dirty coin. #pressfreedom    
    
    
    BREAKING: judge at #MorsiTrial adjourns court for the day; case will resume on January 8th. #cbc    
    
    
    It was utter chaos inside, the 14 co-defendnts & their lawyers chanting against the army, some anti-#Morsi journos calling for death penalty    
    
    
    #Egypt is no place for journalists at this time. #PressFreedom #Cairo #MorsiTrial Both sides; anti- and pro-Morsi are against journos.    
    
    
    #BREAKING: #Egypt state TV: #Morsi to be transferred to Borg Al Arab Prison in #Alexandria.    
    
    
    Good piece on what happened this morning: #MorsiTrial adjourned as chaos breaks out in Egy court http://gu.com/p/3k4nj/tw  by @PatrickKingsley    
    
    
    A week later I still remember that police officer. Getting ready for bed when I find the bruise still… http://instagram.com/p/gWUZpGl1B7/     
    
    
    A week later, I still remember that police guy. Getting ready for bed & I notice the bruise on my leg is still growing. #Egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf In België voor een paar dagen. Maar de blauwe plekken heb ik meegenomen zo blijkt! Jij nog daar?    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf Volgende week!    
    
    
    The 1st Syrian province that was totally free from Assad is now ruled by ISIS #syria http://www.cnn.com/2013/11/05/world/meast/syria-al-qaeda-town-walsh/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Rustige vrijdag in #Cairo: Ministry of Health: 2 killed during clashes in #Egypt today. 12y old boy in Giza & a man in shot in head in Suez.    
    
    
    Deze week een kort stukje van me in @DeGroene over ongelijkheid in Egypte: http://www.groene.nl/artikel/gelijkheid-blijft-ver-weg-in-egypte …    
    
    
    .@JensFranssen Journalists covering Syria's civil war face a growing risk of kidnapping, murder | Fox News http://fxn.ws/1bm7tgS     
    
    
    Egypt to hold parliamentary vote by March - http://Aljazeera.com  http://dlvr.it/4HvhpK     
    
    
    @vincent_v_p Dank!    
    
    
    19/11 wordt Mohamed Mahmoud herdacht, protest tgn het leger. Leger riep intussen op om die dag massaal op straat te komen 'tegen terrorisme'    
    
    
    Na één dag alweer hetzelfde gedoe in #egypt. Een ware politiestaat...    
    
    
    My latest story for IPS – Cairo Women Bring Men Back on the Rails | http://www.ipsnews.net/2013/11/cairo-women-bring-men-back-on-the-rails/ …    
    
    
    @AliTahmizian 'alf shukr!    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@AFP: #BREAKING: Egypt's Brotherhood offers talks to "exit" post-Morsi crisis”    
    
    
    Good read! How did a movie producer get what Egyptian liberal politicians are missing? - Your Middle East http://www.yourmiddleeast.com/opinion/how-did-a-movie-producer-get-what-egyptian-liberal-politicians-are-missing_19271# ….    
    
    
    “@AlArabiya_Eng: Alicia Keys sets Dubai ‘on fire’ http://ara.tv/5mms2  via @AlArabiya_Eng” @koertdebeuf    
    
    
        
    
    
    And then comes chaos in #Cairo, real chaos. Because it's raining for exactly two minutes. And then everything turns back to normal. #Egypt    
    
    
    People are getting nervous again in #Cairo. Nobody knows what Tuesday (anniversary of Mohamed Mahmoud) will bring. #Egypt    
    
    
    Waar was de tijd dat je in #egypt om 23u zei dat de avond nog jong was? #avondmens #cairo @theendofcurfewtimes (at least for the time being)    
    
    
    Twelve students have been sentenced to 17 years for causing riots #Egypt #NewLaw    
    
    
    Tahrir is already closed. Marches will start this afternoon, together with the inauguration of the memorial of massacres. #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    Inauguration of a memorial, for their pen massacres. Schizophrenia in #egypt #MohamedMahmoud #cairo    
    
    
    "@Aaron_T_Rose: Protestors march in Abdeen in remembrance of #Jika. (3/5) #Egypt pic.twitter.com/bvWpLNumkY"    
    
    
    World Bank predicts the refugee population in #Lebanon will reach 1.6 million, or 37% of the overall population by the end of 2014 #4Corners    
    
    
    The Ultras are now marching from Abdeen to the ministry of interior. #cairo #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    Families of #MohamedMahmoud martyrs gather at Abdeen earlier today in commemoration. Peaceful. Not sure what the Ultras plan at the MOI.    
    
    
    A few thousands just arrived at #MohamedMahmoud, chants against Morsi & Sisi, these are the revolutionaries of #25jan #cairo #egypt    
    
    
    As security forces kept Tahrir open, protesters enter the square. Crowd is growing. But no traffic #cairo has its heart in her mouth.    
    
    
    The commemoration monument was just unveiled, curious how long it will survive. Nummers in Tahrir increasing. Angry #egypt    
    
    
    As expected, the first stones of the monument are now thrown at the monument itself... #tahrir #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    The memorial is already sticked with 6 april posters. #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    #egypt wants to ban graffiti, meanwhile the first graffiti appears on the freshly built monument on #tahrir #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    So how long will #egypt stand without the emergency law. Army seems to be playing a dangerous game here.    
    
    
    So why having Tahrir open today? And why ending curfew and the emergency law only days before?! #egypt #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    Less people already in #tahrir    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @henkjanvanvliet Ik vind #bekladden nochtans een schoon woord!    
    
    
    New paintings in progress on #MohamedMahmoud walls. #Tahrir    
    
    
    Strange feeling at #tahrir. Anti-military protesters gather at one side, pro-military gather at the other side of the square #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    Teargas in #tahrir    
    
    
    First confrontations between anti-Sisi and pro-Sisi are a fact. Police firing teargas #MohamedMahmoud #tahrir #egypt    
    
    
    After a few canisters of teargas, police seem to have stopped firing. #tahrir still in chaos. Pro and anti SCAF are seperated. #Cairo    
    
    
    Tamarod cancelled their march, Ultras kept marching toward #Mohamed_Mahmoud    
    
    
    #tahrir is getting closed. Pro Sisi have left it seems.    
    
    
    Pro army has left, anti army (also anti morsi) still on #tahrir, while its getting closed. Morsi supporters will start marching at 5pm.    
    
    
    A symbolic coffin for Mohamed Mahmoud victims is put over the monument in Tahrir after being destroyed. pic.twitter.com/0qhDVvnKb5    
    
    
    Sounds like a goal... #Egypt #Ghana    
    
    
    How footbal is more important than politics. #Egypt - Ghana now on #Tahrir. Few still chanting against the regime and army. #MohamedMahmoud    
    
    
    Gisteren tal van arrestaties op het Tahrirplein #opgezetspel? Vandaag opnieuw 10 agenten gedood in de #sinai    
    
    
    @HaraldDoornbos Ah daarom! Ik zou alvast geen goede jihadist zijn...    
    
    
    Hardhandig leger in Egypte - Annabell Van den Berghe http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/1.1783137 …    
    
    
    2 people have died in Cairo #MohamedMahmoud #egypt    
    
    
    Trying to get my flag jacket back... means asking a favor of the people that took it from me #Egypt #policestate and wastas #goodolddays    
    
    
    Syrian in #egypt are now on hunger strike...    
    
    
    @AltenaB ?    
    
    
    Anti protest law in #Egypt is a fact. When gathering with ten or more, one should now ask permission of the #policestate    
    
    
    "Have we forgotten 12,000 civilians incl. children who are still in jail?" #Egypt approves military trials http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/87113.aspx     
    
    
    @AnnemarieKlok @p_vanostaeyen @MCTSamuel @docnl @HansJMelissen @HaraldDoornbos Wow.    
    
    
    @AltenaB Vanaf een balkon in Irak kan je alles zien wat er in Syrië gebeurt... Volgens mij weet @janeikelboom er alles van!    
    
    
    @MLMeulenbroek @janeikelboom @estermeerman Als journalist moeten vooral je stukken kwaliteit hebben...    
    
    
    @LoveLiberty @liamstack But it usually takes them about 6 hours to ask only these 3 questions... #sigh #egypt    
    
    
    Got invited to attend the @RiscTraining, and will therefore be in NYC next February. Excited! Thanks @frontlineclub & @ejbeals    
    
    
    Security bolstered near Giza pyramids ahead of #Morsi demo aimed at defying oppressive new protest law http://gate.ahram.org.eg/News/422966.aspx … …    
    
    
    New Constitution allows military trials for civilians, today there will be protest against it. #NOMiliTrials #Egypt #Cairo    
    
    
    Not sure yet about #Sisi (and #Morsi), but Nasserist Hamdeen Sabbahi plans to run for president! #Egypt    
    
    
    Meme being circulated on Facebook depicting #Egypt's protest law as... a suppository  http://twitpic.com/dmjjw1     
    
    
    Also protests will be held against the Protest law and the Graffiti law. #Egypt #Cairo    
    
    
    U.S. says concerned with Egyptian law that restricts protests http://reut.rs/IeeCXS  via @reuters    
    
    
    In less than an hour, protest will start against the anti-protest law, against the anti-graffiti law and against the military trials. #Cairo    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sad! RT @Sophie_MJones Police officer:"If we want harsher antisexual harassment law, we need law dictating what women should wear"@NihalSaad    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Nazret_Amal @Beltrew And who is killing who again?  Not sure that law could make a difference... At least not for the safety of civilians.    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter Indeed, it's still a proposal. They will vote for it 'soon'.    
    
    
    RT 'Police will use water cannons and tear gas to disperse protesters protesting new protest law' http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/87513.aspx  ”    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter It will...    
    
    
    Interesting note: Police dispersed protest against anti protest law. Next step after fighting terrorism, bc protesters were not MB! #Cairo    
    
    
    Police already arrested more than 30pp who were protesting illegally under the new law, people still gathering... #cairo Shoura Council    
    
    
    Protest dispersed near Shura Council, protesters now heading to Talaat Harb. #NoMilTrials #egypt #cairo    
    
    
    @Zeinobia @nazlyhussein considering they already harassed me -being foreign not in a march- badly, we can imagine what they do these girls!    
    
    
    Reports say activists @salmasaid @AidaElkashef and @Monasosh are arrested #egypt    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter ben je ook bij het protest?    
    
    
    So now the police is setting fire on TalaatHarb, but most people have left already (or got arrested). Are they burning themselves?    
    
    
    Nearly 100 protestors got arrested today, while protesting against military trials and anti-protest law. #Egypt    
    
    
    5 released including Ahmed Heshmat. @alaa says @Monasosh called and said the girls were beaten    
    
    
    @liamstack @salmasaid @Monasosh AFTE has the latest list!    
    
    
    The girls who got arrested yday under the new antiprotest law were left in the desert around midnight, after being sexual assaulted #egypt    
    
    
    Women in Alexandria get sentenced to 11 years of jail, for being #MB    
    
    
    As expected, most are talking about new protest today in TalaatHarb, almost no news on the 14 MB girls that got sentenced for 11 years.    
    
    
    Oh, and these girls got arrested before the anti protest law was issued... #Egypt    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf @MarietjeSchaake @GuyVerhofstadt Morsi was niet goed vr corrupte elite, klopt, mr ook niet vr groot deel v bevolking.    
    
    
    @koertdebeuf @MarietjeSchaake @GuyVerhofstadt #pt dus coup of niet, veel vd betogers gisteren waren alleszins pro 30 juni.    
    
    
    @RenaNetjes @janeikelboom @BrendaStoter Morsi was niet goed vr corrupte elite, klopt, mr ook niet vr groot deel v bevolking.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @janeikelboom daar ben in het niet mee eens, velen zijn er later op teruggekomen. Maar getuigden toen wel dat ze helemaal met Tamarod waren    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AliTahmizian indeed... For distributing flyers and blocking the road... Ya salaam!    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @RenaNetjes @BrendaStoter er was genoeg weerstand v corrupte elite & volk om aan te nemen dat hij als machthebber niet deugde    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @RenaNetjes @BrendaStoter #pt en daarbij komen ook gewoon de ondemocratische feiten. Lijkt me geen waardeoordeel.    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter Helemaal juist, velen hebben zich ook bedacht na het optreden van de veiligheidsdiensten.    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @RenaNetjes @BrendaStoter ik ben niet verbaasd, maar het gaat niet over mij. Desalniettemin is term #waardeoordeel incorrect    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @RenaNetjes @BrendaStoter says who? ;-)  In het geval van mijn tweet, vertelden ze (demonstranten v gisteren oa) me zelf...    
    
    
        
    
    
    Veiligheidsdiensten beweren gearresteerde meisjes nr thuis te hebben gebracht. Hier ware locatie, waar ze hen dumpten pic.twitter.com/EwfkmQZYLO    
    
    
    Student killed by police today at Cairo Uni, Mohamed Reda was killed with 2 live bullets according to lawyer @ahmed3zat at morgue now    
    
    
    Sentencing MB, harassing activists and dumping them in the desert, and killing students. #Egypt    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter @MLMeulenbroek @janeikelboom @RGjournalist Het blijft toch gewoon razend interessant, look on the bright side jongens!    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter @Meisju Je stukken zijn fijn, ook zonder de taal. Die taal, dat komt wel met de tijd!    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @BrendaStoter @Meisju The bright side Jan, the bright side!    
    
    
    @janeikelboom @BrendaStoter @Meisju Brenda heeft nog zoveel tijd. #jongzijn    
    
    
    En hoppa. @alaa liet weten dat hij zichzelf zaterdag zou aangeven, en werd vandaag in zijn woning gearresteerd. Politie sloeg z'n vrouw.    
    
    
    Just filed an article about the most recent #arrests in #Cairo, and yet even before @alaa could hand himself over, he got arrested at home.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Another detention order was filed against founder of 6th April, Ahmed Maher. Most probably will get arrested soon as well #Cairo #NoMilTrail    
    
    
    #UN calls for amending #Egypt protest law http://owl.li/rgS04     
    
    
    Small clashes between security forces and anti-coup protesters reported in Mohendiseen, Suez, Mahalla & Qena http://m.dailystar.com.lb/News/Middle-East/2013/Nov-29/239359-egypt-islamists-rally-despite-protest-law.ashx … … #Egypt    
    
    
    Report cites "gunshot wounds" as cause of death, while MOI denies anything other than tear gas used during Thursday campus clashes    
    
    
    vertaling van opschrift bij foto PT 'Dit is de vrijheid die we willen' een pamflet van ISIS, #Syria in #Raqqa    
    
    
    @BrendaStoter Waar sta je?    
    
    
    world bank to finance new projects in egypt, says finance minister: http://is.gd/jw2pJG  #egyecon #mena #development #WB    
    
    
    World Bank to finance new projects in Egypt: Minister http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/87808.aspx  via @ahramonline    
    
    
    @yaseralzayat we are having diner (or Egyptian lunch) around six in Amsterdam. Call @AltenaB !    
    
    
    @Ghoneimalex "I left Abdeen court. Please, move away, everyone it's a setup, thugs are turning people in." #Egypt @Meedana    
    
    
    RT Protesters are dividing themselves to 2 lines (men&women) holding their IDs to show they r not afraid of detention pic.twitter.com/Mv6YGSeh1y    
    
    
    Oh dear! “@oritperlov: @TheBigPharaoh After the lingerie and the new chocolates here comes the #Sisi pajamas :D pic.twitter.com/AQCNtnxxT1”    
    
    
    @SimaDiab Facebook is working again since being back in Holland, but yes, faced the same problems yday in #Cairo    
    
    
    @hebamorayef on targeting activists in #Egypt http://www.hrw.org/news/2013/11/29/dispatches-egyptian-police-target-leading-activists …    
    
    
    Dank! “@janeikelboom: #terugluistertip @AltenaB: @Annabellvdb over de situatie in #Egypte @TROSNieuwsshow @radio1nl http://www.tros.nl/tros-radio-tips/nieuwsshow/nieuwsshow-uitzendingen/item/?tx_trosradio[itemid]=168602&cHash=fff9e5da372dd01ddd5552a7ad91de9b …”    
    
    
    “@AFP: Egypt panel begins voting on new constitution http://bit.ly/18u8siy ”    
    
    
    Ahmed Maher is released, but no news about Alaa so far... #egypt    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Gsquare86 So what about other signs, such as a cross for example. Isn't that the same problem?    
    
    
    Constitutional committee just voted on article 204, allowing military trials for civilians. 41 voted yes, 6 no, 1 abstention.    
    
    
    In #Egypt there is now an app to use when you get arrested https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=info.staturtweets.arrested …    
    
    
    @JonathanRashad @glcarlstrom Unfortunately this is indeed what we all expected. #NoMilTrials    
    
    
    Khaled Said trial today again causes violence outside the court room already. #Alexndria #Egypt    
    
    
    Hmm... a bit bizarre. Head of lawyers defending Alex female protesters disappears http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/88052.aspx     
    
    
    Next week expected in Amsterdam, but the great poet Ahmed Fouad Negm died this morning... #egypt    
    
    
    @PatrickKingsley @david_conn @GuardianWitness @RobinMcKie Congrats!    
    
    
    Report on human trafficking in #Sinai, incl. locations where migrants get tortured to obtain money from friends/family. Eritreans/Sudanese    
    
    
    A year ago the clashes at the Presidential Palace started. #Morsi is now on trial for that. #Egypt    
    
    
    #pt Vreemd genoeg worden ze zelf door die grondwet een verboden partij...  #egypt    
    
    
    Vrouwelijke betogers Egypte vrijgelaten - BNR Nieuwsradio http://www.bnr.nl/feeds/anp/BUI/223917-1312/vrouwelijke-betogers-egypte-vrijgelaten … #BNR    
    
    
    Egyptian Christian journalist detained for inciting sectarian strife http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/88449.aspx     
    
    
    How Egypt's Gen. el-Sisi won @TIME's Person of the Year poll  http://ti.me/18dztGH     
    
    
    Vrouwen moeten uit de buurt blijven van bananen en komkommers.#Egypt http://www.radio1.be/programmas/nieuwe-feiten/zee-zwemmen-buitenechtelijke-seks …    
    
    
    According to a statement signed by 13 NGOs including HRW and Amnesty Inernational, at least 2329 were killed in #Egypt since #25Jan 2011    
    
    
    #pt and almost half of them in August of this year only...    
    
    
    UN to launch first airlift of aid within Syria. Up to 12 flights from Thursday to Sunday aiming to reach 60,000 people in remote regions    
    
    
    Business tycoon Naguib Sawiris: Armed Forces chief Sisi must run for president to improve conditions in #Egypt http://shorouknews.com/news/view.aspx?cdate=09122013&id=2608aaa6-8a67-4a4e-93a0-a20fddd22b75 … …    
    
    
    Overleven in de vrieskou, met enkel een plastic zeil http://www.deredactie.be/permalink/1.1802435 … #Syria    
    
    
    #pt luister via #pt naar @Tinekeceelen over de vreselijke situatie voor Syrische vluchtelingen na 1000 dagen burgeroorlog. @vrtderedactie    
    
    
    RT Alleged leaked recording of General #Sisi describing a bonkers premonition in which he was president of #Egypt: http://www.karmamole.com/septic/english-translation-of-el-sisis-new-leak/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Het sneeuwt!  En dan nog wel in #Cairo en niet in #Gent, voor het eerst in 112 jaar. #omgekeerdewereld!    
    
    
    While Egyptians are happy to get some snow, Syrian refugees are trying to survive it... #Zaatari #Lebanon #Jordan #Turkey #Syria    
    
    
    Good read on how to conduct profound research... Redefining my role as a researcher http://wp.me/p45q9s-2p  @MiaElFeky    
    
    
    Most Female Journalists Have Been Threatened, Assaulted, or Harassed at Work. Why We Don't Talk About It. http://www.slate.com/blogs/xx_factor/2013/12/03/sexual_harassment_in_journalism_a_new_study_shows_that_the_majority_of_female.html … @slate    
    
    
    @liamstack How long are you staying for?    
    
    
    @liamstack thought you lived in Egypt as well... Sorry for that!    
    
    
    #Egypt President, PM endorse new draft #constitution, LE500 fine announced for non-participation in #referendum http://madamasr.com/content/president-prime-minister-endorse-constitution … …    
    
    
    "@TheCairoPost: 200k policemen and 150 security units to secure referendum: security source #Politics http://thecairopost.youm7.com/news/55884/politics/200k-policemen-150-security-units-secure-referendum-security-source … …"    
    
    
    Egypt's constitution 2013 vs. 2012: A comparison http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/88644.aspx   via @ahramonline    
    
    
    "The Brotherhood are planning to disrupt the constitutional referendum & to derail #Egypt's roadmap" Nader Bakkar http://www.shorouknews.com/news/view.aspx?cdate=12122013&id=659e489a-37e9-48eb-94f3-545bd7abec6b … …    
    
    
    Russia will provide Egypt with $2billion military hardware, so Egypt does survive without US...  http://www.egyptindependent.com/news/russia-provide-egypt-military-hardware-says-putin-s-envoy … …    
    
    
    Working on a new project with @NihalSaad @hendelbalouty. #Egypt #Cairo pic.twitter.com/4YysI2uGVv    
    
    
    @muiz @ORHamilton It says 'video is not available in your region'.    
    
    
    @ORHamilton @muiz ok great! Assabr gameel mish keda? Thanks!    
    
    
    @abdallahelshamy transferred, along with 300 others, from Abu Zaabal to Torra prison this morning.    
    
    
    Like all foreigners, #Morsi is a spy. #Egypt Ousted president Morsi to stand trial for espionage http://english.ahram.org.eg/News/89445.aspx  @ahramonline    
    
    
    Naar goede traditie! Groot Dictee 2013 - http://s.vk.nl/3564573?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=web#.UrJNCq2Mdj4.twitter … @volkskrant    
    
    
    At work with Nihal. http://instagram.com/p/iKNprPl1Ej/     
    
    
    @Annabellvdb @NihalSaad    
    
    
    The bombing of Mansoura police station is already seem as one of the biggest terrorist attacks in #egypt    
    
    
    Nu al acht doden geteld bij de aanval op het politiekantoor in Mansoura, meer dan 100 gewonden. #Egypt    
    
    
    Het Mansoura theater moest er ook aan geloven. Grotendeels verwoest door de aanslag op politiekantoor vlakbij. #egypt    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    3 explosions already today in #Egypt: #Alexandria #AlArish #cairo    
    
    
    #MB wordt beschuldigd van de aanslagen in #egypte, #MB zelf ontkennen elke betrokkenheid.    
    
    
    @JasminaOnline Dank!    
    
    
    Volgens AP al 11 doden. “@AP: Explosion at police headquarters north of Cairo kills at least 11; scores injured: http://apne.ws/1c2g21Z ”    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    The #mansoura attack fits the schedule of Egypt's government & the legitimation of the war on terror.    
    
    
    While enjoying Christmas, there is a mass funeral in #Mansoura, and more casualties in #Aleppo.    
    
    
    In #Mansoura worden moslimbroeders niet enkel geviseerd door de overheid, maar ook door medeburgers. #MB worden bedreigd en aangevallen.    
    
    
    Although #MB claims having nothing to do with #Mansoura bomb attack, they are officially declared a terrorist group by interim gov. #Egypt    
    
    
    Bomb explodes near Cairo public bus, kills one | Egypt Independent http://www.egyptindependent.com//news/bomb-explodes-near-cairo-public-bus-kills-one … via @egyindependent    
    
    
    Opnieuw een bomaanslag in #Egypt vlakbij de Azhar universiteit waar lange tijd pro-Morsi betogingen plaatsvonden. #Cairo #MB    
    
    
    Opnieuw een student doodgeschoten door politie in #Egypt. Gebeurde bij de Azhar universiteit, waar eerder pro-Morsi betogingen doorgingen.    
    
    
    #Beirut #Aleppo #Cairo, het ziet er niet goed uit.    
    
    
    Dit weekend lees je in @trouw het stuk over de Downtown graffiti artiesten van #Cairo, en het nakende verbod. Met o.a. Ahmed Naguib.    
    
    
    Shorouk: "We want Sisi President Of Egypt" group files a lawsuit to "force" Sisi to run for President http://www.shorouknews.com/news/view.aspx?cdate=29122013&id=4f919450-23bf-4311-9604-1ac7afaa0624 … … #Egypt    
    
    
    @EricTrager18 Would like to send you an email, could you give me your address?    
    
    
    Statement from #Egypt's interior ministry on today's arrest of AJE staff from the Marriott https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=650348248342175&set=a.181676241876047.36036.181662475210757&type=1&theater … …    
    
    
    @adamakary Want to send you a DM, could you follow me for a sec. ?    
    
    
    #Egypt.ische overheid heeft vrij spel. Wie tegen staat is, is met #MB, #MB zijn terroristen, dus zowat iedereen kan nu opgesloten worden.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Talked to a colleague of the arrested Al Jazeera journos. Stories are frightening. "Army wants to kill and MB is ready to die for Morsi"    
    
    
    If you're not with the army, you're with MB. And thus a terrorist. #Egypt    
    
    
    Another journalist, photographer, arrested in #Egypt. 140 new arrests, for illegal protest this summer (anti protest law is a month old)    
    
    
    Again none activists sentenced to two years jail in #alexandria #egypt    
    
    
    AJE journaliste @repent11 and @PeterGreste  are still detained #egypt #pressfreedom    
    
    
    New clashes today between #MB and #securityforces in #Egypt. Death toll rising.    
    
    
    .@Mosireen: Ahmed Maher, Ahmed Douma & Mohamed Adel resume hunger strike to protest prison conditions https://m.facebook.com/mosireen/posts/589615094442203 … …    
    
    
    AJE Journos detained because the had no accreditation… is the newest story in #Egypt. Before it was detention bc they had #MB contact info.    
    
    
    4 killed in clashes with security forces #Egypt while 5 killed in #Beirut Libanon by a bomb. In North of #Syria 5 NGO workers of AZG missing    
    
    
    