Duty calls tomorrow night, @hwatterworth. Will have to press pause on the christmas crafting this week.    
    
    
    Imagining an alternate reality version of #glee starring Zooey and Mr. Ward. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W18_OO8TD78    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hey girl! Try to remember your book tomorrow. I'm dying to see it!    
    
    
    Wonders if the Draper not-so-dreamy house can be far behind. RT @LesaHannah Mad Men Barbie dolls! http://nyti.ms/c15ijc    
    
    
    Today marks the 1 year anniversary of loosing/accidentally throwing out half my wardrobe. I still miss you Prada pants & camel hair skirt.    
    
    
    got a link-back from NYMAG.COM! http://bit.ly/d2sxUG And is a tad excited about that.    
    
    
    Psst @jen_thompson! Did you see the #mimicoforever love on @designsponge? The neighb' is totally legit now! http://ow.ly/6btdl    
    
    
    DH reminds me #Christmas is only four months away. Does he know me, or does he know me?!? @hwatterworth, start your glue gun. #geturcrafton    
    
    
    @LMMichaels Pretty beet treats for you! :) http://instagr.am/p/LadXV/     
    
    
    Fantastic night in the 'hood with @hwatterworth. Dinner? Delicious. The conversation? Even better. Wonder what the DHs had ;) #mimicoforever    
    
    
    @jen_thompson @hwatterworth thanks for the recommendation.    
    
    
    With sweater vest + toque his cute quotient is off the charts! RT @shessnaphappy A reason to smile today: http://flic.kr/p/8XYsMP    
    
    
    How long do beets last before peeled? @hwatterworth. Another night with no time to cook! Do I have a few more days?!    
    
    
    YES. RT @ellistuhler Today's song courtesy of @hwatterworth. Magnifique cover of Serge's Bonnie and Clyde. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tXeCLVsA5PQ …    
    
    
    Looky, looky! It's #TIFF guru @boomboomtunes in @nowlifestyle! She's *that* awesome. http://ow.ly/6iUDz    
    
    
    I. love. rock and roll. too, karaoke bar across the street, but it's time for effing bed. #somebodypulltheplug #mimicoforever    
    
    
    @ThatEricAlper Dean & Britta?    
    
    
    Monday night's a-calling, @hwatterworth : http://twitpic.com/3d94px    
    
    
    The catalyst for my annual holiday weight gain: shortbread meltaways (cc @thehomeslice) http://wp.me/p1fmo-ix    
    
    
    @thary_c Still thinking (and laughing about) our amazing simultaneous InDesign breakthroughs today. Virtual high five!    
    
    
    I need need need new running shoes and I'm open to suggestions. Huge fan of the Saucony shoes I currently wear.    
    
    
    LOVE 'EM. RT @MakeupJunkieJDT: has anyone tried that Goody corkscrew pin?? I keep seeing commercials for it! any good?? http://bit.ly/dGwwxz    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Really??? We'll have to have a tutorial sesh! They take a teensy bit of practice, but not much.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1hd9b6 - Springtime in yorkville - these flowers are too exotic looking for TO! #btje    
    
    
    Just saw a woman wearing a tube sock as a scrunchie. There are no words.    
    
    
    Essential reading for PRs. RT @rockitpromo Media, Darling: @lesahannah http://goo.gl/fb/svMcJ    
    
    
    @justingodard Oh no! She got the fries! RT @ninagodard Festive special wins! http://yfrog.com/gywvij    
    
    
    It's @LesaHannah in-the-media day! More pitch tips, plus her POV on print vs. online. http://tinyurl.com/23xcmco    
    
    
    @gregory_goose Do share your findings! Mmm Schweppes...    
    
    
    Yay to my nerdy co-worker who HAD to change the type to Helvetica. Ha.    
    
    
    Just realized the new season of Mad Men starts July 25th. Calendar marked.    
    
    
    Great way to start a beautiful Saturday - 9 am kickboxing class & then breakfast with my girl @hwatterworth !    
    
    
    Yes please! RT this message if you'd like tickets to @theclothingshow from #urbanebloc - 6 pairs to give away!    
    
    
    @urbanebloc hi! I can't respond to your DM because you're not following me. Please send me your email and I'll get in touch!    
    
    
    Warning to my coworkers: tomorrow I will adjust the thermostat accordingly and wear my scarf. #gohabsgo    
    
    
    Headline du jour: "Mullet family held over Amish haircut attacks" http://bit.ly/ukSbSy  (via @TorontoStar)    
    
    
    He's nothing without the greasy hair. RT @lesahannah: Confirmed: Taylor Kitsch is not hot unless he's Riggins. http://bit.ly/w3CPfs     
    
    
    @hwatterworth And therefore, a nobody...PS Riggins greeting cards would be AMAAAZZING though.    
    
    
    My pretty little sister snapped by my super-talented friend. RT @shessnaphappy Bride, Sugarbush & Shiny Red Fire Engine http://ow.ly/7LhKU     
    
    
    Do Onion Rings count as a vegetable serving?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth does short bread count as a dairy?    
    
    
    Hey @Vaboolous! RT @shedoesthecity Guide to Toronto's holiday craft fairs including 4 this weekend: http://tinyurl.com/72x72cz     
    
    
    Mad Men is so awesome.    
    
    
    Really? Comic Sans has fans? RT @dailycandy: For all you Comic Sans fans: http://dly.me/6018RlaA     
    
    
    Most nauseating day. Ever.    
    
    
    3 day vegan juice cleanse complete! On to #powerball    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Happy New Years!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Happy New Years Heather!!!!  xoxo    
    
    
    Sooo, it's official. I'm the beauty expert on the @MarilynDenisCTV show!!! First show is on jan 11th 2011, ppl!!    
    
    
    I am all booked for my trip for @IDSToronto.    
    
    
    @TonicLiving you rock my socks! Ordered swatches yesterday and they're already in my mailbox! Thanks so much!    
    
    
    Hey @jen_thompson, these were WAY easier than the poinsettias and pinecones: http://yfrog.com/h0k7gij    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for the recommendation!  Very kind!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Just make sure that you saw my reply email - I think that I sent it at your new address    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/h2cf4sj
 http://yfrog.com/gyeccbj
 http://yfrog.com/gyc1tgj
X 10! Don't you wish you joined my cookie exchange?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Gorgeous! And LOVE the cushion fabric. Making "mantle" magic. Wrong to hang 4 stockings if we're only 2 b/c it looks better?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for the follow. I am following back and love ur blog too!    
    
    
    So, SO happy to be back. RT @kimvallee: @hwatterworth is back. Cool Tools: Olioboard Helps You Decorate Your Home http://ow.ly/8ny2p     
    
    
    For new pinners who've been asking how to find people... Pinterest: 13 Tips for Cutting Edge Users http://ow.ly/8obJG  via @mashable    
    
    
    Want! RT @kimvallee Breathe Easy: the sexy Middle Colors Humidifier http://ow.ly/8ofyP     
    
    
    All those registered for "Blogs & Media" please check your inbox for a very important e-mail on how to complete registration. - Lindsay    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Shoot us an e-mail at info@blogpodium.com with your Name & E-mail, so we can see why you didn't get the registration e-mail    
    
    
    Is it 'peaked' or 'piqued' my interest that is correct? #burningquestions    
    
    
    Working from old stomping grounds @uofg today. I've missed the smell of this library.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth all libraries really do have their own particular smell, don't they? #booklove    
    
    
    Congrats! Very well-deserved! RT @covetgarden: We are super happy to be featured today on Design Sponge http://fb.me/1rlMXXre9     
    
    
    @chrissychrzan Try Kama Design on Carden St.: http://www.kamadesign.com/kamadesign/home/    
    
    
    Seeing @sheandhim with @ablahut - our first concert as marrieds. Appropriate since we chose one of their songs for our first dance.    
    
    
    Breakfast for dinner = rainy day antidote. http://instagr.am/p/kEKhs/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth 'Pancake' really is the happiest word in the English language, isn't it?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth today I said "how do you like your coffee?" And I said, "crisp" and... crickets... Dammit!    
    
    
    A little eye candy for you this morning @deannemoser: http://reveriemag.com/     
    
    
    I can't decide if I want to play with my new flat iron or my new nail polish.    
    
    
    @BlogPodium is here!  looking forward to a morning with blogger friends old and new #blogpodium    
    
    
    @KatMooreMedia wants to see personality, passions and photos of the bloggers behind the blog to consider for promo. #blogpodium    
    
    
    Which blogs should you follow? @kimberleyseldon: curation is okay as long as you have an original voice and offer opinion. #blogpodium    
    
    
    Editing/appreciation has as much value as creation if the goal of the blog is to share beauty. @margotaustin #blogpodium    
    
    
    Photography is an important skill to develop of you want to achieve success with your blog. @ramblingreno #blogpodium    
    
    
    Re: online vs. print: "There are only two kinds of press: press and no press" @kimberleyseldon #blogpodium    
    
    
    SM influence is a major factor for media considering bloggers to feature - it's a symbiotic relationship. @KatMooreMedia #blogpodium    
    
    
    Don't overlook the words. It's about the story. @margotaustin #blogpodium    
    
    
    Quite literally jewellery for your home - a chandelier created from necklace chain. #ids12 http://ow.ly/i/qRCT     
    
    
    @hwatterworth #blogpodium THX for the post ... So pleased you joined us this morning!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth yes! It has been ages! Will be nice to say hi in person!    
    
    
    @justingodard It has a point. RT @mcsweeneysbooks: Comic Sans has something it would like to get off its chest. http://bit.ly/9YriiT    
    
    
    Corduroy capris: just say no.    
    
    
    Getting a sneak peek inside the March issue of @HouseandHome @cdn_designblgrs meetup.    
    
    
    So motivated by @casslavalle's talk @cdn_designblgrs meetup. Thanks for sharing your challenges + tips!    
    
    
    Original content + don't procrastinate on your post idea + collaborate = blogs in 2012. @casslavalle #cdb2012    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @houseandhome @cdn_designblgrs hi Heather    
    
    
    Ya know @cdn_designblgrs, @casslavalle + @cameronmacneil + new blog friends would've been enough! TY for the super fun night + prize! :)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Enjoyed catching up with you this weekend! Congrats on all the exciting news in your world & your win tonight!    
    
    
    @shanatweet @CdnFoodieGirl i'm pretty sure tweetdeck is available for iOS too. that's what i use for multiple twitter accounts on android!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Great win Heather! It was nice seeing you again, next time we will chat longer!    
    
    
    @ramblingreno Yes! Ditto. :)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @shanatweet do you use hootsuite free/paid? looks like a good solution for bringing together all social media accts in 1 app    
    
    
    For a second there, I thought I was living next to cousin Matthew. http://ow.ly/i/r5jx  #thingsmimicoisnt #downtonabbey    
    
    
    Testing/creating a possible new flavor of another "Only Two" cupcake recipe... first batch is in the oven!    
    
    
    Okay font geeks, a little help identifying this one please? (cc @justingodard @cherithbrooke @thary_c @dreizle) http://ow.ly/i/rgL0     
    
    
    Read it and drool, people. RT @_jasonhudson: BLOGGED: Night Cheese | http://jasonhudson.com     
    
    
    Deals on shoes make me VERY happy!!! Under $55 regular $260 WOOT!!!    
    
    
    Excited to officially announce that I will be teaching @ Conestoga College starting in April! Interior decorating & floral design classes.    
    
    
    @cdn_designblgrs @blogpodium Know anyone? RT @jen_thompson WANTED: #Edmonton-based interior designer... I've got something in mind.    
    
    
    I miss you, @hwatterworth.    
    
    
    Filing under staycation sewing projects. RT Our new Summer Beach Hat has vintage appeal with a high-fashion flair! http://ow.ly/21qPm    
    
    
    Anyone have a great example of a Toronto city map broken down by neighbourhood?    
    
    
    Dance Mix 93 up here in the hizzouse. No more caffeine after 9pm for PeeJ. Go to "bread"  #oldskool #beats #fail    
    
    
    This Movie is Broken opens in theatres in Toronto and Vancouver on June 25th. RT for your chance to win passes (via @bssmusic)    
    
    
    Some dude on this bus is sitting on an office chair. Waiting for the bus driver to slam on the brakes and him to go wheeling down the aisle.    
    
    
    @karenlimusic And from here, he looks like Dwight K. Schrute. http://yfrog.com/5p66487178j    
    
    
    If I ever have a home with a spare room, this quilt will cover the bed. #grandmamadeit http://instagr.am/p/HCWIU8sWeK/     
    
    
    @justingodard Thanks again for last year's Christmas gift. I think it sounds even better this year. #wintermusic    
    
    
    Just me on my birthday at the beach! http://instagr.am/p/HPfoLrrbFM/     
    
    
    Check it @cupcakeride – you will love these! RT @designsponge elastic portable planters for your bike! http://bit.ly/AF4hb2     
    
    
    "What's for dinner?" "Breakfast." http://ow.ly/9cNxy  #recipe #pancaketuesday    
    
    
    Attn: @justingodard RT @siofan Wes Anderson American Express commercial http://youtu.be/rbO3BS0Uzm0     
    
    
    The view:
 http://img.ly/eFaAf 
http://img.ly/eFaK     
    
    
    @shessnaphappy Ideas for T's b-day? MT @HWTM_Jenn A creative "The Lorax" Inspired Dessert Table http://fb.me/Ty7JxxlA     
    
    
    Stepping out of my regular creative shoes to spend my afternoon writing new content for the Living Fresh website. Can we say big challenge.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Great idea Heather! Thanks for the offer. How is Guelph treating you? We should plan a coffee date.    
    
    
    Um, HANDS DOWN the best Xmas gift thus far is from @hwatterworth: Jon Hamm greeting cards!!  http://plixi.com/p/64660381    
    
    
    @blogpodium Did you the big news from last night? #Blogpodium "The Business of Blogging" announced! http://www.blogpodium.com     
    
    
    @hwatterworth do you have power this evening?    
    
    
    @gappelbergk @craig_a_carter yup Dallas tweeps, that sign says 99 F. http://yfrog.com/50cltpj    
    
    
    @justingodard Just saw a handwritten sign you would've loved. New shop called "Global Cheese" - "o" was a cheese wheel with wedge missing.    
    
    
    Wish List: Holly Farrell's retro Barbie & Ken paintings, at Katharine Mulherin gallery. http://hollyfarrell.com/Available/index.html    
    
    
    @janinefalcon Great segment on BT! I want your necklace in my stocking!    
    
    
    @JustinKase3 Well done on the filamentous biomaterial piece. :)    
    
    
    Our Dig-in Downtown fliers for @downtownguelph are everywhere! http://instagr.am/p/IICz15HyPQ/     
    
    
    Definitely need the twitterladies to weigh in on this purchase...good thing I took pictures. (@ Winners) http://4sq.com/8uqlxr    
    
    
    Morning Road Trip http://instagr.am/p/IJ2zcALbLK/     
    
    
    @ReCreativeWorks Can't you craft some up in your studio? ;)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth It was really nice to spend some time with you today, great chat! 3 hours flew by! Have a great afternoon!    
    
    
    Friend of mine just had lunch w/ @hwatterworth & forgot to mention that I miss seeing her stylish shoes.    
    
    
    @annaandkristina major cute factor on this basket, but if you need to haul stuff try a back rack basket. http://tinyurl.com/2dtz5pw    
    
    
    @_biancs_ we have to suggest to Leigha! RT @amandabella: Cardio at #bootycamp w/ water balloons during heat wave is the best thing ever    
    
    
    @justingodard You are so cut for not even dropping a HINT about my Christmas gift from @ablahut. #giddy!    
    
    
    @ablahut just told me he used foot scrub on his face in the shower this a.m. "It didn't say you couldn't use it on your face!" #boysareweird    
    
    
    Cool! Just found out you can go tubing in the Elora Gorge - anyone ever done it?  http://bit.ly/db1BkZ    
    
    
    Feist & M. Ward - Sometimes Always (Live @ Royal Albert Hall, London, 25/03/12) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qIosDX9_4-A&sns=tw … via @youtube    
    
    
    I have so much Mad Men to watch tonight.    
    
    
    Ah-mazing: Pairing Up the Heroes of #DowntonAbbey with their #MadMen Soul Mates http://ow.ly/9UKDY  via @slate    
    
    
    "I was your teacher... Bugsy. Brown." http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wqWxGMqI_SE … #oldschool (cc @hwatterworth cuz only you would appreciate)    
    
    
    Obsessed with this note posted in 4th floor kitchen  http://tweetphoto.com/32676828    
    
    
    I have #madmen to watch tonight, but I really feel like renting this: http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1462768/    
    
    
    @jen_thompson Is it just me or was that pretty much the best first ice cream date ever? Thanks lady!    
    
    
    @jen_thompson ha! "Plotting neighbourhood improvement, one cone at a time."    
    
    
    Dude, if you're gonna share the bus bar with me, please wear deodorant. #peeewww    
    
    
    OMG! @hwatterworth @justingodard Walking out of the office, dandelion fluff coming at me!!!  Do not open your mouth!  #allergies    
    
    
    A packed bus on a hot day is a human experience I can live without #yourpitsaredisgusting    
    
    
    Need new spring makeup and styling aids? Products you feel you don't need anymore we will donate to our building self esteem event.    
    
    
    Copy editors/grammar nazis/journo students : Well-made OR well made ???    
    
    
    @hwatterworth yes, four hearts for grammar    
    
    
    Any recommendations for a good wedding cake baker in Guelph?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @JACHAminerals @WellingtonCakes HAHAHA.. i said the same thing!    
    
    
    inspiration for our latest project on the blog today!!! http://wp.me/pVjJc-1bE     
    
    
    attention crafters!  do you know where to purchase these colourful reinforcement rings used on these tags? http://www.etsy.com/listing/81490612/kraft-paper-tags-with-bakers-twine-x-10 …    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for following!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Sorry I missed you today! Thank you for your generation, it was an amazing contribution.  I will forward you an invite tom.    
    
    
    I'm thinking this up your alley @healthandswellness RT @craft How-To: Maple Bacon Ice Cream: http://bit.ly/dsKwLt    
    
    
    Hey new friends!!! @WeddingWire @shopPIGMENT @hwatterworth @ahabbershaw @helloterumi @kmcamera @brightonkeller    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Thanks for the follow, and the order! :) Your print is on route!    
    
    
    Seriously. It's been a year with CS4 and my Export Movie shortcut still doesn't work in Flash.    
    
    
    @ablahut Are you reading this? RT @DT666 I have posted a new blog: http://dischord.inmusic.ca/    
    
    
    @jen_thompson Hi neighbour! Hope you're having a lovely week!    
    
    
    Dam Beavers = best name for a nature documentary ever.    
    
    
    @jen_thompson Fun! Thumbs up on another ice cream date. Wednesday eve? Yes to bringing the boys (more flavour options to try that way!)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth It's a double date! See you around 8ish next Wednesday night?    
    
    
    @living_fresh Have you seen the latest issue of Styled mag? So much flower-y goodness – thought of you! http://ow.ly/avGPt     
    
    
    Dad is giving me the LOLs. And he's now signing off texts with "-30-".  #toofunny #lovehim pic.twitter.com/bX8iJN6e    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Now, that would be quite something. In other news, #Mimico & me miss you. How are the new digs?    
    
    
    Psst @justingodard RT @ThatEricAlper Hear Ghostly International's We'll Never Stop Living This Way comp for free at NPR - http://dld.bz/DbFd    
    
    
    Fresh ingredients from my garden! Mmmm yummy pasta primavera! http://yfrog.com/i3u3jmj    
    
    
    @ChickAdvisor My pleasure - loved checking out the cool C.A. digs + the cupcake! (Maybe I could be a Starbucks girl after all...)    
    
    
    Hey, Montreal! Thanks for being so good to me today!    
    
    
    @jen_thompson @hwatterworth WAIT do you ladies know each other?!    
    
    
    I feel your pain RT @AlideBold Dear IPhone. Please stop guessing what I'm typing and then doing auto complete. You're almost always wrong.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth This belly shot inspires me! What aisle would you pick? cc @amelialyon http://www.amelialyon.net/     
    
    
    Anyone know what these are called? Love them. #gardening http://instagr.am/p/K8BOllMWVU/     
    
    
    @shessnaphappy For your "formal" shoots, perhaps? http://www.bloomtheorystraps.com/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth @freshimages http://jachamineralsblog.blogspot.ca/2012/05/girls-day.html … Thanks to all who contributed to our girls day, make sure to read the blog.    
    
    
    So lucky my hubs makes my lunch daily. Today: roast chicken sammie w/his homemade bbq sauce on fresh Ace Bakery multi-grain.    
    
    
    Thanks @shedoesthecity for tickets to tomorrow's This Movie Is Broken screening!    
    
    
    Breaking in my cute red Enzo Angilioni pumps. Am in pain but worth it? http://yfrog.com/1aefxj    
    
    
    Any recos for a baby photographer in Toronto?    
    
    
    Kinda wish I was under 14 for this http://www.onf-nfb.gc.ca/eng/mediatheque/schedule.php?id=2047 #animation #nfb    
    
    
    Planning a wine and bike tour in Niagara-on-the-Lake. Any suggestions for the best wineries to visit? #niagara #wine    
    
    
    @hwatterworth That sounds awesome! Pls tell me it comes complete with a piggy for your basket (as per the website's photo!)    
    
    
    Looking for a pattern/how-to for a cute pin cushion to use with my fab new craft box... If you'll share, I just might make one for you, too!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth You read my mind :) Love the can bottom (with a citrus stripey ribbon in mind!). Same date/time next week, Chez Thompson?    
    
    
    Kind of really excited to find @judyblume here. Also, perhaps the most spectacular Twitter bio I've read.    
    
    
    Missing our Sweet Olenka dates lately @jen_thompson.    
    
    
    Our two favourite *ICE CREAM* places in #Toronto so far: http://bit.ly/bUzcbJ and http://bit.ly/auAtns So what's yours?    
    
    
    @living_fresh Thanks for your sweet note yesterday! And congrats on the new space (officially!). Can not wait to come check it out!    
    
    
    Today I shot what will likely be my favourite newborn photo. Think baby and bicycle. Omg.    
    
    
    Pyjama days I hardly knew ye: http://tinyurl.com/2vspdhb    
    
    
    @pinterest @8en thanks for the mention - I'm really enjoying Pinterest!    
    
    
    Dude beside me on the bus this morning had a "Note Tote" binder. Now I'm all nostalgic for grade 5.    
    
    
    And a stylist (cuter outfit, per Carrie Bradshaw). RT @writemonkey Squirrel: A tree rat with a good PR agent.    
    
    
    Anyone want to join me in a soup swap? RT @kimvallee National soup swap scheduled for Jan 22. http://kim.tl/hxAvHl    
    
    
    Uh-mazing. RT @mynameisguygal: incredible video by John St, spoofing a typical case study for an ad campaign http://is.gd/kg453    
    
    
    @hwatterworth knows few things are better than a handwritten thank-you note. Pretty penmanship, too! #timeless    
    
    
    So many ideas on the brain! Thanks to the awesome @hwatterworth for a great night at @thebeetcafe last night.    
    
    
    @OptimuscrimeTO You should meet Karyn @makesomething (re: quilters).    
    
    
    @justingodard @ninagodard Likewise, I want to start collecting photos of Peggy's priss face: http://tinyurl.com/2d9z73q    
    
    
    Love this peek inside @dougcoupland's second home (via @poppytalk): http://tinyurl.com/q3vzlq    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Missing our weeknight jaunts to Sweet Olenkas! Nephews visiting this Saturday afternoon. I assume kids like ice cream. You in?    
    
    
    @jen_thompson 4 of course! Though we did a 22 km ride last weekend. I just DM'ed you too...    
    
    
    Tour de Greenbelt rider's blog... http://post.ly/xkx5    
    
    
    Congrats @thekit on a gorgeous first issue! The anticipation was intense today, but so worth it!    
    
    
    Drinking my dinner through a straw and drooling all over the place. #dentalwork #icantfeelmylips    
    
    
    @kflemming Happy Birthday (officially)! Hope your day is lovely.    
    
    
    More Blog love! Thanks Heart Heather http://heartheather.com/2010/09/13/covet-garden/ http://fb.me/A1UqHq3k    
    
    
    @CovetGarden Awesome! Looking forward to it and the blog updates.    
    
    
    AHmazing! RT @chantelsimmons The Babysitter's Club: Where Are They Now? http://huff.to/bnG8n3 (via @huffingtonpost)    
    
    
    Thank you sweet friend! RT @shessnaphappy The people with these feet... http://ow.ly/dXLFi     
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hey Momma! How are you and your little family doing?    
    
    
    Envious of long-haired landscaper dudes have mastered the top knot.    
    
    
    So true! I attempted today. May have been #fail. RT @hwatterworth: Envious of long-haired landscaper dudes have mastered the top knot.    
    
    
    Looking forward to Baskin Robbins BRight Choices deskside tastings tomorrow!    
    
    
    @covetgarden thanks for the #FF! Happy weekend!    
    
    
    @MyDailyRndmness Have you seen the mushroom-y goodness in @sweetpaul? Thought you would appreciate! ;) http://www.sweetpaulmag-digital.com/sweetpaulmag/fall2012#pg68 …    
    
    
    On husbands who bake, plus a secret for keeping cookies soft: http://tiny.cc/vc05a    
    
    
    Mine is making dbl choc ones from @babycakesnyc's book right now! RT @hwatterworth: On husbands who bake http://tiny.cc/vc05a    
    
    
    @KFlemming He exfoliates AND bakes - talk about a catch! (And the bread thing really does work!)    
    
    
    Just pulled some of mr@hwatterworth's cookies out if oven, just in time for tonight's premiere marathon.    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy Thanks for following Michelle! I love your photos - gorgeous!    
    
    
    No, I'm not with child. That's just my lunch and all the chocolate bark I consumed over the holidays, thanks.    
    
    
    @justingodard My last RT was directed at you, nerd.    
    
    
    This is terrifying and amazing. http://crapatmyparentshouse.com/ @crapatmyparents    
    
    
    Browsering for shoes: http://tinyurl.com/2aymajy    
    
    
    Even better than the first! RT @covetgarden Our October issue is now online! www.covetgarden.com    
    
    
    Super excited to have lunch today with the talented @hwatterworth. #colleaguesturnedfriends    
    
    
    @jcasensio @hwatterworth Ha, not likely to happen ;)    
    
    
    This is what it looks like when a proper photographer takes your picture. Thanks @shessnaphappy http://instagr.am/p/RQOR4GMstz/     
    
    
    Ladies & gents of #Guelph: if you're not an @ExperienceThree client you're missing out! TY Veronica, Jason & Angie for a relaxing morning!    
    
    
    Mason jars + cheesecloth + googly eyes = #Halloween crafting. http://instagr.am/p/RWezruEJe1/     
    
    
    Is it bad that I feed the neighborhood stray kitten? http://yfrog.com/bhm6qtj    
    
    
    Foodie friday, on a Monday. http://ow.ly/2OrBg    
    
    
    Up early for 30 minute free run before work. Now planning to bookend my day with this. Doubling up on exercise. Weight loss continues. -13.7    
    
    
    I'm talking to you, @hwatterworth!  @craft Flickr Pool Weekly Roundup: http://flpbd.it/nFWmR     
    
    
    @hwatterworth 6am - it's a free run on my Wii... Once I don't look so pathetic and awkward I'll venture outdoors. You run?    
    
    
    Hey! That's me! RT @greenbeltca Tour de Greenbelt photo contest honourable mention to a tour blogger: http://fb.me/Iw9WzZaE    
    
    
    @hwatterworth It means a hiatus from good ol' Sweet Olenkas for a while. How about a weeknight walk sometime?!?!    
    
    
    Congrats, beauties, on the P&G nominations! @JanineFalcon @Beauty_Editor @AlideBold @AErmter @taniakwong @Carlenetweets    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/2vrdbp    
    
    
    Canned cranberry sauce is not an option people. http://tinyurl.com/2ecdz4z    
    
    
    @justingodard @bittermadrid Try to contain yourselves, boys. http://tinyurl.com/38uut2b    
    
    
    If you're giving books for the holidays, @vangerwen shows you how wrap them pretty!
http://www.chapters.indigo.ca/inspiration/its-a-wrap/video1/ …”    
    
    
    If you're giving books for the holidays, @vangerwen shows you how wrap them pretty!
http://www.chapters.indigo.ca/inspiration/its-a-wrap/video1/ …”    
    
    
    En route to Thanksgiving dinner, smell of warm apple crisp is overwhelming the car. Lucky for family, I didn't bring a spoon.    
    
    
    Excited! RT @shessnaphappy Just landed tix to Belle & Sebastien @ Massey Hall next week thx to @hwatterworth. Yay for a #girlsnightout    
    
    
    @hwatterworth who made crisp--you or husband?    
    
    
    You rule, @LesaHannah. Congrats! #pgawards    
    
    
    So great to see you this morning @alidebold! Did you shop more for yourself or the boy? #ooak12    
    
    
    @E_M_I Glad we crossed paths today Emilija! Your wee Stella is gorgeous. xo    
    
    
    @boomboomtunes Moment of silence for J.R. this morning. http://www.thestar.com/news/world/article/1292569---dallas-star-larry-hagman-dies … PS: AMAZING "best of J.R." montage at the end of link.    
    
    
    @JenifferBissett Best babysitter ever! Thanks so much lady!    
    
    
    3:30am wake-up call... Hubbs delivers cup of coffee in bed. #husbandoftheyear    
    
    
    @KFlemming @LesaHannah Dream = reality: http://tinyurl.com/2c73hs4  (the rocks are Canyon-esque, right?)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @KFlemming Heather, you're amazing.    
    
    
    Been looking at this miserable face all day. Teething? Growth spurt? #saveme http://instagr.am/p/S09AETGtZE/     
    
    
    Glitter tape is the new love of my crafting life. http://instagr.am/p/S13pVXEJRe/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth I think of you when I wear this shirt. #bicycle http://instagr.am/p/S_FNHpMWbM/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth Congrats on the new gig! Assuming you're still at MK?    
    
    
    Ooh, sparkly. http://instagr.am/p/TB-itkEJV5/     
    
    
    @lesahannah Happy happy birthday! I owe you a b-day cupcake in NYC!    
    
    
    Love the pinecones! RT @kimvallee Felt and Stich Holiday Workshop with Betz White, the author of Sewing Green http://kim.tl/9XMUqi    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Me too! Do I sense a Mimico Christmas Crafter in the works? @kimvallee Felt and Stich Holiday Workshop: http://kim.tl/9XMUqi    
    
    
    Wow, thank you for the lovely flowers @marykaycanada (via @hwatterworth) and P&G Beauty&Grooming Team. Very unexpected and appreciated!    
    
    
    There is naked dancing to LCD Soundsystem happening in my kitchen. http://plixi.com/p/51877734    
    
    
    Looking for suggestions on how to create fake boobs for my Joan from #madmen hallowe'en costume.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth, these laundry decals belong above my brand new washer/dryer: http://kim.tl/cXANJ1    
    
    
    Filler fruit. As in melon. #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    #FF friends, old and new: @_BIANCS_ @shessnaphappy @justingodard @jen_thompson @KimVallee @JeromeParadis    
    
    
    @justingodard you will love: RT @Pinterest A little color for your friday afternoon: http://color.aurlien.net/    
    
    
    LOVE! (Almost as much as The Hamm's cameo.) RT @LesaHannah Blown away by @s_dsquared's lace tips http://plixi.com/p/71455989    
    
    
    Reason 492 why I love #Guelph: city doesn't pick up Xmas trees; volunteers do in support of kid's grants. http://tinyurl.com/a4nr9py  #treesfortots    
    
    
    Reason 492 why I love #Guelph: city doesn't pick up Xmas trees; volunteers do in support of kid's grants. http://tinyurl.com/a4nr9py  #treesfortots    
    
    
    Reason 492 why I love #Guelph: city doesn't pick up Xmas trees; volunteers do in support of kid's grants. http://tinyurl.com/a4nr9py  #treesfortots    
    
    
    @LDepante Hi stranger! Been thinking about you lately. Hope you've had fantastic holidays! :)    
    
    
    @_BIANCS_ Voila: the answer to your poulet prayers. http://tinyurl.com/2v54p6p    
    
    
    Why hasn't someone made a hat with a pillow built into it? It would make so many hours of my life more comfortable.    
    
    
    Check out @kimvallee's first free Halloween Printable Tags and Stickers - designed by me! http://kim.tl/c3myYS    
    
    
    Pretty morning sky in the Royal City. #guelphonography #guelph http://instagr.am/p/UHMlxAkJYs/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth I love you. That is all.    
    
    
    needs to buy craft supplies (wool felt, for example) and doesn't want to go to Michael's. Suggestions, anyone? (many thanks in advance!)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth STUNNING! We need to find a retailer pronto b/c I really dont want to spend my $ at Michaels. Discuss @birdsandbeans this Sat?    
    
    
    My tea/hand towel for @blarkness ! Time to stitch it up!!!! http://plixi.com/p/53276448    
    
    
    Alright  ̶g̶h̶o̶u̶l̶s̶  girls, who's ready to party? RT @kimvallee http://kim.tl/dy5wiV    
    
    
    Sometimes I'm still scared of my shadow. #holyshitihaveakid http://instagr.am/p/UULqzJEJek/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for following! i too am a connoisseur of ice creams but in no way do i compare to @SpicyMouseShop's dearth of knowledge    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for following! i too am a connoisseur of ice creams but in no way do i compare to @SpicyMouseShop's dearth of knowledge    
    
    
    @LesaHannah @AErmter Congrats ladies!    
    
    
    @pinnpann Hi Annika! I found you on Twitter! Are you back from Estonia?    
    
    
    @pinnpann Hi Annika! I found you on Twitter! Are you back from Estonia?    
    
    
    Happening now: my mom is about one hour into a corneal transplant. #organdonation    
    
    
    We on for tomorrow at 10am @hwatterworth ?    
    
    
    Was lamenting the return of hockey, until this cuteness happened in the living room. http://instagr.am/p/UsGGJkEJTD/     
    
    
    Thanks to @hwatterworth for introducing me to @covetgarden. Plan to dive into the November issue tonight: http://fb.me/GTqGzv3C    
    
    
    Stop the presses. RT @guelphmercury: Report from field: Goose frozen into pond west of #Guelph may be hunter's decoy that has fooled people.    
    
    
    For you @cherithbrooke @justingodard @thary_c RT @Omiyage_ca:Graphic designers illustrate (bad) client feedback http://sharpsuits.net     
    
    
    I could go for a stack of these pancakes right now. RT @KimVallee Apple Recipe picks for a brunch or to serve with tea http://kim.tl/dkiTDX    
    
    
    Another project for my holiday DIY list! RT @KimVallee @hwatterworth shares a DIY Advent Calendar from Julie Ree http://kim.tl/ce8SjF    
    
    
    For the ribbon-obsessed! RT @kimvallee Ribbon organizing solution - a gr8 find by our writer @hwatterworth http://kim.tl/gJGZ70    
    
    
    What are some fun/cheap things to do with a baby in Calgary in February? (Besides stay inside and snuggle.) #yyc    
    
    
    Hey Twitter-world. My daughter Elinor is going to be a big sister :)    
    
    
    Hey Twitter-world. My daughter Elinor is going to be a big sister :)    
    
    
    730. All's well that ends well: http://foursentencestories.blogspot.com/2013/02/730-alls-well-that-ends-well.html …    
    
    
    Crafting. Not just for Christmas anymore, @hwatterworth. OMG Adorable Stuffed Fabric Hearts: http://flip.it/mOWKS     
    
    
    Crafting. Not just for Christmas anymore, @hwatterworth. OMG Adorable Stuffed Fabric Hearts: http://flip.it/mOWKS     
    
    
    Nine years ago tonight I was dancing the night away in a white gown. Happy anniversary Johnny @humbybros. (PS: best DJ ever @hnicradio :)    
    
    
    Hey, that's me! :) RT @uofg: Technology Specialist Loves Teaching, Writing, Baking Bread http://fb.me/1SwxK7pn2     
    
    
    Hi @hwatterworth! I'm sorry you can't make it. There has been a lot of interest, however, so maybe me & @mingaskills will host another!    
    
    
    Thought of you @shessnaphappy MT @brainpicker Flickr yanked up from the sea by its collar at the last possible moment http://j.mp/XtqG7B     
    
    
    Crafting. Not just for Christmas anymore, @hwatterworth. OMG Adorable Stuffed Fabric Hearts: http://flip.it/mOWKS     
    
    
    Crafting. Not just for Christmas anymore, @hwatterworth. OMG Adorable Stuffed Fabric Hearts: http://flip.it/mOWKS     
    
    
    If snickering at another patron's check out receipts isn't the best reason to use the library, I don't… http://instagr.am/p/Vt15MCkJYh/     
    
    
    Hey Twitter-world. My daughter Elinor is going to be a big sister :)    
    
    
    Paris has been there for thousands of years and isn't going anywhere. You will see it and it will be worth the wait. #tweetyour16yearoldself    
    
    
    Beautiful day for cross country skiing. Or napping. Whatever. #yyc #instagraham http://instagr.am/p/V79ZvqkJaN/     
    
    
    @_BIANCS_ Can you believe this? http://www.sucks-rocks.com/    
    
    
    Have a friend doing bridal shopping in TO. Beckers, Ritchie, where else should she go?    
    
    
    C'mon y'all, it's Connie Britton. http://nyti.ms/VUs2J5     
    
    
    When the repair guy discovers a nursing pad is the reason your washing machine won't drain. #awkward    
    
    
    When the repair guy discovers a nursing pad is the reason your washing machine won't drain. #awkward    
    
    
    @jcasensio Ha.    
    
    
    Future goalie. #instagraham http://instagr.am/p/Wrsrt7kJRA/     
    
    
    Parade's End > Downton Abbey (S1).    
    
    
    For you, @littlehouseblog! Spotted at HomeSense in #Guelph. http://instagr.am/p/W5AMrIkJYy/     
    
    
    Signs of spring. @ooak_toronto #madehere http://instagr.am/p/XC1IIOkJcn/     
    
    
    Such a treat to finally meet @kimvallee and @jeromeparadis in person tonight! Can't wait to check out #IDS tomorrow.    
    
    
    @living_fresh You got this. RT @instagram This weekend's Hashtag Project: #WHPflowerpower http://blog.instagram.com/post/46621166586/whp-67 … …    
    
    
    Think I just might get crafty today. Wonder what @hwatterworth is up to?    
    
    
    Check out this post by @hwatterworth about the Kazoo! Print Expo. Featuring us and All Sorts Press! http://heartheather.com/2013/04/09/my-city-kazoofest-print-expo/#more-3383 …    
    
    
    @thechicstorm So happy to finally see yours in person today! RT Hair Trend: Let's Talk (Again) About The Top Knot. http://www.glamour.com/beauty/blogs/girls-in-the-beauty-department/2011/02/hair-trend-have-you-been-weari.html?mbid=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    @TheGlitterGeek so glad you made it out  :) Dont worry doll... @hwatterworth will be happy to send you some iluminators! @marykaycanada    
    
    
    Hellooooooo, United States of Tara. Where have you been all my life?    
    
    
    @lizaherz You look nothing like your Twitter pic. (I've been following all along!)    
    
    
    Wondering who @hwatterworth and @kflemming would rather be stranded on a desert island with: T, Alice or Buck? #usoftara    
    
    
    Snow days call for stoup (yup, stoup). http://tinyurl.com/68l4prd #recipe    
    
    
    @Bookshelfnews Do you stock @uppercasemag and/or @puregreenmag?    
    
    
    Probably chatting about lawns and BBQs. #guytalk #spring http://instagram.com/p/Yv5r5ZEJUo/     
    
    
    May flowers. #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/YyAOWhEJZs/     
    
    
    Sweet rides for miles. Thought of you @cupcakeride! http://instagram.com/p/Y1QKkwEJaG/  #guelphonography    
    
    
    Hello, old friend. http://instagram.com/p/ZETj5FEJVa/     
    
    
    And her family! RT @oldscollege College alum Susan Hoy from Land & Water Program an inspiration to faculty, staff, students & donors.    
    
    
    The sharpest pencil skirt in your closet comes from @iva_jean. #biking http://ow.ly/lmjN3     
    
    
    Bike-riding ladies of #Guelph: please join me for a Sweet Ride on June 15! http://ow.ly/lxCMX     
    
    
    Hey @downtownguelph! I'm organizing a women's group bike ride in June - care to share? https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Did you ever wind up braving the line to buy that IKEA apron?    
    
    
    Hey @downtownguelph! I'm organizing a women's group bike ride in June - care to share? https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    Hey @downtownguelph! I'm organizing a women's group bike ride in June - care to share? https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    Hey @downtownguelph! I'm organizing a women's group bike ride in June - care to share? https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    LADIES! @hwatterworth is starting Guelph's very own Sweet Ride to get more ladies to ride bicycles. Spread the word: http://ow.ly/lxNAH     
    
    
    Bike-riding ladies of #Guelph: please join me for a Sweet Ride on June 15! http://ow.ly/lxCMX     
    
    
    LADIES! @hwatterworth is starting Guelph's very own Sweet Ride to get more ladies to ride bicycles. Spread the word: http://ow.ly/lxNAH     
    
    
    The only thing that's going to make this day better is the giant cupcake I'm going to eat after this... #surgery pic.twitter.com/bwA6tn6B7H    
    
    
    @jen_thompson I'll drink to that! (Tasted like Quik, no?). Hope you get your pre-party nap. xo    
    
    
    @pinnpann Hey mama! Thanks for spreading the word about #sweetrideguelph. Do you ride? (And if so, do you ride with a baby belly?)    
    
    
    @pinnpann PS, congrats on girl #2! :)    
    
    
    Hey @lizaherz! How are you celebrating World Nutella Day? (A suggestion: http://tinyurl.com/695z8yp)    
    
    
    #Guelph girls: if you like riding your bike and have a sweet tooth, you should probably join me for this. https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    #Guelph girls: if you like riding your bike and have a sweet tooth, you should probably join me for this. https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    Last day of #mayhealth but it won't be the last day of this new partnership. http://instagram.com/p/Z-mKrZJhZ8/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth I smell an apron-making business in the brewing. I'll be your in-house copywriter.    
    
    
    #Guelph girls: if you like riding your bike and have a sweet tooth, you should probably join me for this. https://www.facebook.com/events/528823993820511/ …    
    
    
    Last day of #mayhealth but it won't be the last day of this new partnership. http://instagram.com/p/Z-mKrZJhZ8/     
    
    
    Come ride a bike + eat ice cream with me. No spandex required. http://ow.ly/lF2iT  #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    Really excited about tomorrows #potluck - 100 people have RSVP'd!    
    
    
    #Guelph friends: where can I rent or borrow a button maker?    
    
    
    #Guelph friends: where can I rent or borrow a button maker?    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy Nice! Congrats!    
    
    
    It feels so wrong to spend a June afternoon making soup. But come dinner time it's going to taste so right.    
    
    
    If you were turning 4 years old and your birthday party was today, what would you want for a present? @vccarin and I could use this info.    
    
    
    Saturday morning perfection. #guelphonography @ Exhibition Park http://instagram.com/p/aTe_LEEJas/     
    
    
    Saturday morning perfection. #guelphonography @ Exhibition Park http://instagram.com/p/aTe_LEEJas/     
    
    
    5 p.m. and NOW it rains?!    
    
    
    I know as a blogger my work isn't important but receiving an email saying I helped save a shop with one post makes me incredibly happy.    
    
    
    Rainy Monday = cookies. http://instagram.com/p/aZl4-FEJUx/     
    
    
    Rainy Monday = cookies. http://instagram.com/p/aZl4-FEJUx/     
    
    
    Rainy Monday = cookies. http://instagram.com/p/aZl4-FEJUx/     
    
    
    Rainy Monday = cookies. http://instagram.com/p/aZl4-FEJUx/     
    
    
    Hey @BraunsBicycles! I'm organizing a women's group ride this Saturday in Guelph. Can you help spread the word? http://ow.ly/lUYBg     
    
    
    Hey @BraunsBicycles! I'm organizing a women's group ride this Saturday in Guelph. Can you help spread the word? http://ow.ly/lUYBg     
    
    
    Hey @BraunsBicycles! I'm organizing a women's group ride this Saturday in Guelph. Can you help spread the word? http://ow.ly/lUYBg     
    
    
    #Guelph girls: if you like riding your bike and have a sweet tooth, you should probably join me for this. http://ow.ly/lUZaQ     
    
    
    @downtownguelph @EXPERIENCETHREE  Thanks for RTs about #sweetrideguelph! :)    
    
    
    Bike ride with my boys to listen to bagpipes, followed by baby's first ice cream cone. Stellar Tuesday… http://instagram.com/p/acUXzzkJc8/     
    
    
    Hey @2RiversFestival! #SweetRideGuelph is this Saturday and we'll be riding along the rivers! http://ow.ly/m0PQS     
    
    
    Saturday forecast looks perfect for biking and ice cream! Please join me for #sweetrideguelph: http://ow.ly/m0Puo     
    
    
    Can't wait Terri! MT @tlrowanrmt Happy Friday! Please join me Saturday cycling for icecream! http://bit.ly/12oxJrr  #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    Cute! Sweet Ride #Guelph #bike ride June 15 - Leisurely ride for ladies with sweet stops along the way http://bit.ly/12oxJrr  @hwatterworth    
    
    
    Cute! Sweet Ride #Guelph #bike ride June 15 - Leisurely ride for ladies with sweet stops along the way http://bit.ly/12oxJrr  @hwatterworth    
    
    
    Cute! Sweet Ride #Guelph #bike ride June 15 - Leisurely ride for ladies with sweet stops along the way http://bit.ly/12oxJrr  @hwatterworth    
    
    
    Cute! Sweet Ride #Guelph #bike ride June 15 - Leisurely ride for ladies with sweet stops along the way http://bit.ly/12oxJrr  @hwatterworth    
    
    
    Sweet Riders: please check the FB event page for details on meetup location + time. See you tomorrow! #guelph http://ow.ly/m2YUy     
    
    
    Today, we ride! #sweetrideguelph meets up at noon at the farmer's market location at Exhibition Arena. http://ow.ly/m3TQN     
    
    
    Today, we ride! #sweetrideguelph meets up at noon at the farmer's market location at Exhibition Arena. http://ow.ly/m3TQN     
    
    
    @DrJulieGill @tlrowanrmt @Shecrochets2 Thanks for the RTs ladies! See you soon! :) #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    Perfect weather, cool company + mega-sized ice cream cones... I'm declaring the inaugural #sweetrideguelph a delicious success!    
    
    
    Thanks for riding with me today @shecrochets2 @tlrowanrmt @minitee @gypsylinguist! #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    Just home from #sweetrideguelph! From door to door just under 14km!!! Awesome day for ice cream and a bike ride :)    
    
    
    @gypsylinguist Hey Lisa! Thanks for joining the ride today! Would love to see any photos you took - can you email them to me?    
    
    
    @gypsylinguist Hey Lisa! Thanks for joining the ride today! Would love to see any photos you took - can you email them to me?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi Heather.  Too bad I missed your sweet ride yesterday.  It would have been fun.  :)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth BTW... GORBA has ladies rides every Thursday night.  http://gorba.ca/     
    
    
    Wishes all Mondays came with flowers! Thanks for the sweet gesture @radhabs! http://yfrog.com/h7y1dusje    
    
    
    A few thoughts on the first #sweetrideguelph. (Not gonna lie, I'm a bit emotional about the whole thing.) http://ow.ly/m7soR     
    
    
    Anybody know how long The Boathouse ice cream section is open for? Google only has the tea room hours.    
    
    
    Last week to get earlybird rates to @BlogPodium & hear me & Sarah Richardson speak. (Not together, & yes I'm giving myself top billing :P)    
    
    
    Last week to get earlybird rates to @BlogPodium & hear me & Sarah Richardson speak. (Not together, & yes I'm giving myself top billing :P)    
    
    
    Just took a call from CBC National News! They're interviewing us for this Thurs's evening news! #OMG    
    
    
    YES. RT @margotaustin: Wish I could carry a seam ripper to free a million forgotten stitched-down vents and slits. #wardrobefail    
    
    
    Thanks @Shecrochets2 @tlrowanrmt @MINITee @gypsylinguist + 4 non-Twitterers: you made #sweetrideguelph awesome. http://ow.ly/mbdIW     
    
    
    Thanks @Shecrochets2 @tlrowanrmt @MINITee @gypsylinguist + 4 non-Twitterers: you made #sweetrideguelph awesome. http://ow.ly/mbdIW     
    
    
    Thanks @Shecrochets2 @tlrowanrmt @MINITee @gypsylinguist + 4 non-Twitterers: you made #sweetrideguelph awesome. http://ow.ly/mbdIW     
    
    
    Ahh! Uh! Ah! Uh! #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#0     
    
    
    HUUUUUHHH uhh HUHH #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#0     
    
    
    Ah-ah-aahhhh! #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#0     
    
    
    Ahh! Uh! Ah! Uh! #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#1     
    
    
    Mother fucking bitch #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#0     
    
    
    HUUUUUHHH uhh HUHH #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#1     
    
    
    Ah-ah-aahhhh! #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#1     
    
    
    Mother fucking bitch #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#1     
    
    
    Mother fucking bitch #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#1     
    
    
    Ah-ah-aahhhh! #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#2     
    
    
    HUUUUUHHH uhh HUHH #SurrenderYourSay http://bit.ly/11ZXSvX#2     
    
    
    Help choose the date for July's #sweetrideguelph! http://ow.ly/mh2Iv     
    
    
    Pretty rose and prettier evening light. #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/a1xdsWkJT1/     
    
    
    @shessnaphappy You need to try this for your throat! RT @kimvallee Cold and Cough Tea Tins at DavidsTea http://kim.tl/ewNwbX    
    
    
    Are you between 20-35? Just curious to know if you flip through the Real Estate Paper that comes to your home? Just a Y or N please :) thx!    
    
    
    At the temporary farmer's market and it's fab! So much room to move around! pic.twitter.com/XoUFI3rx3d    
    
    
    At the temporary farmer's market and it's fab! So much room to move around! pic.twitter.com/XoUFI3rx3d    
    
    
    At the temporary farmer's market and it's fab! So much room to move around! pic.twitter.com/XoUFI3rx3d    
    
    
    @hwatterworth : http://curbside.on.ca/blogs/curbside-cycle/8170297-nighttime-moon-ride …    
    
    
    Last chance to choose the date for the next #Guelph Sweet Ride! Ride details coming later this week. http://ow.ly/mkSHH     
    
    
    Last chance to choose the date for the next #Guelph Sweet Ride! Ride details coming later this week. http://ow.ly/mkSHH     
    
    
    Last chance to choose the date for the next #Guelph Sweet Ride! Ride details coming later this week. http://ow.ly/mkSHH     
    
    
    The Decline and Fall of the English Major http://nyti.ms/16YWed4  (we aren't all meant to be teachers!)    
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph rides again July 13 - and we're visiting @WellingtonCakes and @WithTheGrain! Details: http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph rides again July 13 - and we're visiting @WellingtonCakes and @WithTheGrain! Details: http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    Saddle up ladies! #sweetrideguelph rides again July 13! More info on the route and sweet stops here: http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    Settling in for Mad Men. Perfect end to a great weekend.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth I noticed you like ice cream. Sapphire has in-house ice cream! #guelph #homemade    
    
    
    The hygenists at my dental office are grooving to some seriously heavy reggae.    
    
    
    More fun on bikes: the @bicycleopera project makes a stop in #Guelph on July 13. http://ow.ly/mD8ni     
    
    
    Coincidently, #sweetrideguelph is also July 13 with stops @WellingtonCakes + @WithTheGrain! RSVP here: http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    I wait all year for these. http://instagram.com/p/bUaddqkJYD/     
    
    
    Love living in a neighborhood where people ring the door bell to tell you your car windows are down in a thunderstorm.    
    
    
    @make_something, my boyf is a tech - and he'll work for fabric! :) DM me if you'd like his contact info.    
    
    
    I wait all year for these. http://instagram.com/p/bUaddqkJYD/     
    
    
    DIY sunscreen from diaper cream? @mingaskills this is for you! http://ow.ly/mEVUM  (via @janinefalcon @beautygeeks)    
    
    
    DIY sunscreen from diaper cream? @mingaskills this is for you! http://ow.ly/mEVUM  (via @janinefalcon @beautygeeks)    
    
    
    Let the goodtimes roll. Art in the Shops today. Art on the Street Sat. We also have a Farmers' Market Wednesday and Street Sale Thurs-Sun.    
    
    
    Let the goodtimes roll. Art in the Shops today. Art on the Street Sat. We also have a Farmers' Market Wednesday and Street Sale Thurs-Sun.    
    
    
    Let the DIY wedding crafts begin! Covered in glue gun wounds but worth it!! @freshimages pic.twitter.com/A0urMGu35Q    
    
    
    Thunder + Lighting = Ctrl+S  #Designing #Work    
    
    
    Thunder + Lighting = Ctrl+S  #Designing #Work    
    
    
    We have Tomato Basil Soup as our feature at the Café for the next few days!    
    
    
    White on white on white. http://instagram.com/p/bhxHQpkJTT/     
    
    
    So much happening in @downtownguelph this weekend, including #sweetrideguelph on Sat.! http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    So much happening in @downtownguelph this weekend, including #sweetrideguelph on Sat.! http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    So much happening in @downtownguelph this weekend, including #sweetrideguelph on Sat.! http://ow.ly/mpUCB     
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph re-scheduled to Sat. July 20! So much happening in Guelph this weekend - sometimes enough is enough! http://ow.ly/mRw8K     
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph re-scheduled to July 20! So much going on in #Guelph this Sat. Sometimes enough is enough! :) http://ow.ly/mRw8K     
    
    
    Best feeling ever! Seeing your work in print, thanks so much @WeddingbellsMag! pic.twitter.com/1qgaw9R6NZ    
    
    
    Never thought about my husband's monogram in quite this light. #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/buXHXCkJRh/     
    
    
    Best feeling ever! Seeing your work in print, thanks so much @WeddingbellsMag! pic.twitter.com/1qgaw9R6NZ    
    
    
    Longest run yet - 4.2 kms!    
    
    
    Saddle up ladies! #sweetrideguelph rides again this Sat. (rescheduled from July 13)! More info: http://ow.ly/n15aD     
    
    
    Amazing what you can learn to do when it's too hot to play outside. http://instagram.com/p/b3jNe0kJbW/     
    
    
    @HillsideFest Are strollers permitted on the free shuttle bus?    
    
    
    My sister's amazing cupcakes! "@MissKRobs #hawaiianthemed cupcakes!!! Happy birthday! http://instagram.com/p/b88V1MSSTY/  "    
    
    
    Might this heat wave break in time for #sweetrideguelph tomorrow? Here I was hoping we'd need to add an ice cream stop en route... :)    
    
    
    Might this heat wave break in time for #sweetrideguelph tomorrow? Here I was hoping we'd need to add an ice cream stop en route... :)    
    
    
    Might this heat wave break in time for #sweetrideguelph tomorrow? Here I was hoping we'd need to add an ice cream stop en route... :)    
    
    
    Today, we ride! #sweetrideguelph meets up @WellingtonCakes at noon! Cooling down @wtgbakerycafe later this aft. http://ow.ly/m3TQN     
    
    
    @wtgbakerycafe Thanks for the RT! Please save me a beehive square! :) #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    @DirtyGirlReview Lovely to meet and sweet-ride with you today! I'll let you know when I can make it out for a GORBA ladies ride. :)    
    
    
    Couldn't have asked for a nicer day, tastier treats or fun co-riders for #sweetrideguelph! Thanks for riding with me @DirtyGirlReview!    
    
    
    Today, we ride! #sweetrideguelph meets up @WellingtonCakes at noon! Cooling down @wtgbakerycafe later this aft. http://ow.ly/m3TQN     
    
    
    Giant skies, corn fields and gravel roads. Think I might be a country girl after all. #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/cKxkUjEJUy/     
    
    
    Giant skies, corn fields and gravel roads. Think I might be a country girl after all. #nofilter http://instagram.com/p/cKxkUjEJUy/     
    
    
    Probably prouder than I should be about this lettuce. #growyourownfood http://instagram.com/p/cMl3FGkJTk/     
    
    
    Probably prouder than I should be about this lettuce. #growyourownfood http://instagram.com/p/cMl3FGkJTk/     
    
    
    Probably prouder than I should be about this lettuce. #growyourownfood http://instagram.com/p/cMl3FGkJTk/     
    
    
    Going to Hillside this weekend? Grab everything you need for a picnic! Salads, breads, cheeses & charcuterie...so good!    
    
    
    guelph is the best place on earth on hillside weekend    
    
    
    Today was kind of awesome. #squishykissycakeface http://instagram.com/p/cSuyoNEJR6/     
    
    
    Just heard this great quote -- "You can go forward or backward but you can't stand still"...I couldn't AGREE more!! :)    
    
    
    Evidently, the best way to spend your first birthday is in a room with 1,600 balloons. #nofilter @… http://instagram.com/p/cX74rNkJSb/     
    
    
    NEW Metallic Coloured Edges on 22pt Cotton cards. 3 sets to GIVEAWAY, reply to enter: Which one is your favourite? pic.twitter.com/2B3h8Hue9D    
    
    
    I don't know who's manning the Loblaws Muzak, but Sonic Youth circa '94? Yes!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth I thought you might be interested in my inspire! event in Guelph: http://wp.me/P2ze7x-OS   Please share.#13inspire    
    
    
    Primary colours. #ironingisforsuckers http://instagram.com/p/cwdyu_kJaY/     
    
    
    Whatcha doin' this Saturday afternoon? Join the #sweetrideguelph crew for Milkshakes + pie + beer! http://ow.ly/o46RI     
    
    
    Harvest time. #yum http://instagram.com/p/dNcw20EJWr/     
    
    
    @jenipherreads @friendsmycloset Thanks for the RTs! :)    
    
    
    Milkshakes, and pie, and beer, oh my! This Sat. #SweetRideGuelph stops @biteoncorkst @mosboroughfarm @thealbionhotel! http://ow.ly/o87ca     
    
    
    Milkshakes, and pie, and beer, oh my! This Sat. #SweetRideGuelph stops @biteoncorkst @mosboroughfarm @thealbionhotel! http://ow.ly/o87ca     
    
    
    Before you visit @Guelph_Rotaract ribfest Sat., how about an appetizer of milkshakes + pie + beer? http://ow.ly/o46RI  #sweetrideguelph    
    
    
    Whatcha doin' this afternoon? Join the #sweetrideguelph crew for milkshakes + pie + beer! http://ow.ly/o46RI     
    
    
    Smaller chance of getting lost on today's #SweetRideGuelph with these in my pocket. http://instagram.com/p/dZobp3EJcm/     
    
    
    @jenipherreads Good luck today! :)    
    
    
    I love a good Oxford comma.    
    
    
    FEATURED BLOG: Looking for rides w/treats in Guelph. Ontario? Read @hwatterworth for that along w/crafts. http://ow.ly/oFbck     
    
    
    Gwenivere Teele Gofton was born 6.22 today. 9 pound 6 ounces. 22 inces long. We are all doing great :)    
    
    
    And by internet, you mean Internet, right? ;) RT @kattancock: Sometimes I can't help it and I want to copy edit the whole internet.    
    
    
    Ok world I am back! Weddings done and my life has returned to business as usual! pic.twitter.com/6K58V9boTJ    
    
    
    @hwatterworth will you be at #blogpodium this weeken?    
    
    
    Someone talk me out of wearing motorcycle boots on Sat. #blogpodium    
    
    
    RT @lisa_ttro: Woman stabs her ex-boyfriend for refusing to stop listen to the Eagles. We've all been there. http://bit.ly/1aTq3kF     
    
    
    Excited to be part of #Guelphonography's top 20! More excited to see winning shots on something other than a screen. http://ow.ly/oZls1     
    
    
    Excited to be part of #Guelphonography's top 20! More excited to see winning shots on something other than a screen. http://ow.ly/oZls1     
    
    
    +1 RT @JuliaPJMcEwen God, I'm so jealous of your life. RT@LesaHannah: Oh look it's those cute Proenza boys! http://plixi.com/p/77925566    
    
    
    Excited to be part of #Guelphonography's top 20! More excited to see winning shots on something other than a screen. http://ow.ly/oZls1     
    
    
    Have you ever received a happy birthday letter from your car dealership? http://yfrog.com/h0rmilwj #hyundai    
    
    
    @hwatterworth hilarious. I wonder if @iainforsyth knew that!    
    
    
    @DrMarkKubert Thanks for seeing the husband on short notice yesterday! Next time I'll send some sort of baked good with him.    
    
    
    We're in business. (More at http://heatherwatterworth.com ). http://instagram.com/p/efJBNkEJV1/     
    
    
    @DrMarkKubert Thanks for seeing the husband on short notice yesterday! Next time I'll send some sort of baked good with him.    
    
    
    #FF RT @hwatterworth: We're in business. (More at http://heatherwatterworth.com/ ). http://instagram.com/p/efJBNkEJV1     
    
    
    <3 it! Awesome-sauce & good for you, lady! RT @hwatterworth We're in business. (More at http://heatherwatterworth.com  ). http://instagram.com/p/efJBNkEJV1/     
    
    
    We're in business. (More at http://heatherwatterworth.com ). http://instagram.com/p/efJBNkEJV1/     
    
    
    We're in business. (More at http://heatherwatterworth.com ). http://instagram.com/p/efJBNkEJV1/     
    
    
    I want a meal plan. MT @visitguelph @HospitalityUofG 100 MileGrille | Farm Gate to Campus Plate at Creelman Hall http://ow.ly/p4pyW     
    
    
    @jen_thompson You're at #blogpodium! Need to find you! #mimicoforever    
    
    
    My room at #blogpodium, all set up. I'm presenting at 11:30. Eeek! http://instagram.com/p/ehonf_K8Oc/     
    
    
    @jen_thompson You're at #blogpodium! Need to find you! #mimicoforever    
    
    
    Just caught my 6yo checking out a girl at swimming lessons.    
    
    
    Lunch is served! #BlogPodium pic.twitter.com/Os6XEvXamQ    
    
    
    True friends share their dessert. @jen_thompson #2forks1plate #blogpodium http://instagram.com/p/eiBWbQEJb1/     
    
    
    Just caught my 6yo checking out a girl at swimming lessons.    
    
    
    True friends share their dessert. @jen_thompson #2forks1plate #blogpodium http://instagram.com/p/eiBWbQEJb1/     
    
    
    "Traditional advertisers don't necessarily understand non-traditional revenue streams of new media". @CovetGarden's Rhonda Riche #blogpodium    
    
    
    True friends share their dessert. @jen_thompson #2forks1plate #blogpodium http://instagram.com/p/eiBWbQEJb1/     
    
    
    True friends share their dessert. @jen_thompson #2forks1plate #blogpodium http://instagram.com/p/eiBWbQEJb1/     
    
    
    @kekad Just 10 minutes into your pres and I'm hooked. So much valuable info. (And thanks for standing up so we can see you!) #blogpodium    
    
    
    "Are you a broadcast medium or an engagement engine?" - @kekad #blogpodium    
    
    
    "Are you networking or need-working?" Think about what you can offer to brand partnerships, not what you need. -@kekad #blogpodium    
    
    
    Aaaaaand hand cramp. Wow @kekad - you need your own #blogpodium! So much value and insight in your session. Thank you!    
    
    
    You know you're a word nerd when... http://instagram.com/p/eiN6EJkJT7/  @chaptersindigo #blogpodium #indigohome    
    
    
    The gardiner being closed sucks:(    
    
    
    Started a FB group for Canadian Home, Design & Lifestyle bloggers to support & network with each other. Come join: http://on.fb.me/1ezWbKK     
    
    
    The gardiner being closed sucks:(    
    
    
    If you missed @theartofdoingstuff's talk at @BlogPodium, read her lesson in the business of blogging: http://ow.ly/p9cG9     
    
    
    September's #SweetRideGuelph is taking a savoury turn at the corner of meat and cheese. Join me this Saturday! http://ow.ly/p9fbu     
    
    
    Just did a quick interview with @CBCKW891 about the @guelphonography event coming up this Friday. Who's coming out?    
    
    
    @HeatherNHeels Just wanted to let you know #SweetRideGuelph is this Saturday! Would love it if you can join us! http://ow.ly/pdpA9     
    
    
    @HeatherNHeels Just wanted to let you know #SweetRideGuelph is this Saturday! Would love it if you can join us! http://ow.ly/pdpA9     
    
    
    @HeatherNHeels Just wanted to let you know #SweetRideGuelph is this Saturday! Would love it if you can join us! http://ow.ly/pdpA9     
    
    
    @HeatherNHeels Just wanted to let you know #SweetRideGuelph is this Saturday! Would love it if you can join us! http://ow.ly/pdpA9     
    
    
    @missamybarnes I know you're excited to get this tweet. You too @staceylaughlin. :)    
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph starts @wtgbakerycafe and stops @oxguelph this Saturday!  Please don't make me indulge alone. http://ow.ly/p9fbu     
    
    
    Whoa, just realized that tomorrow will be the beginning of Year Three for #lunchupguelph!    
    
    
    @justingodard Welcome to married life.    
    
    
    Nice work @missamybarnes! MT @HRCHeritage Great podcast on London Life building; #ldnont #doorsopen site this weekend http://ow.ly/phiZh     
    
    
    Instagram of my giant 3rd place #guelphonography Instagram. I love this city. http://instagram.com/p/eyRBrFkJY3/     
    
    
    @DrJulieGill Ah! How come both my boys met you and I didn't?! Sorry to have missed you tonight - let's fix that soon!    
    
    
    Third place: Sweet Ride For Miles by Heather Watterworth #Guelphonography pic.twitter.com/qehEKykrOG    
    
    
    Brilliant photos at @guelphphonography thanks to everyone involved for showcasing our city so beautifully    
    
    
    @ChrisOfGuelph Congrats Chris!    
    
    
    @DrJulieGill Ah! How come both my boys met you and I didn't?! Sorry to have missed you tonight - let's fix that soon!    
    
    
    Third place: Sweet Ride For Miles by Heather Watterworth #Guelphonography pic.twitter.com/qehEKykrOG    
    
    
    Stuff-a-Bus Food Drive, Sept 29, 8-6 p.m., Zehrs on Eramosa. Stop by and help Stuff-a-Bus with donations for the #Guelph Food Bank.    
    
    
    Third place: Sweet Ride For Miles by Heather Watterworth #Guelphonography pic.twitter.com/qehEKykrOG    
    
    
    The @guelphonography crew. Cheers to my partners in photo crime. pic.twitter.com/N6bGq0NgJr    
    
    
    It's a busy weekend in #Guelph, but there's a @wtgbakerycafe grilled cheese sandwiches with your name on it. #sweetrideguelph rides at noon!    
    
    
    Brilliant photos at @guelphphonography thanks to everyone involved for showcasing our city so beautifully    
    
    
    Congrats @ChrisOfGuelph, Jen Thorne and @hwatterworth! ... The @guelphonography top 3!    
    
    
    It's a busy weekend in #Guelph, but there's a @wtgbakerycafe grilled cheese sandwiches with your name on it. #sweetrideguelph rides at noon!    
    
    
    Grilled cheese for one. #sweetrideguelph @ With the Grain http://instagram.com/p/ez6VPlkJT8/     
    
    
    Grilled cheese for one. #sweetrideguelph @ With the Grain http://instagram.com/p/ez6VPlkJT8/     
    
    
    Mid-point stop on #sweetrideguelph. Bring on the cannolis. http://ow.ly/i/3h8Yr     
    
    
    #sweetrideguelph pit stop. http://instagram.com/p/e0Dz7-kJV6/     
    
    
    mmm... went apple picking and can't wait to try some of these APPLE recipes http://bit.ly/18X6VL6  #apple #recipes #fall    
    
    
    mmm... went apple picking and can't wait to try some of these APPLE recipes http://bit.ly/18X6VL6  #apple #recipes #fall    
    
    
    Hey @RusticRetrieval! Inherited this barrister's bookcase. To paint or not to paint? http://ow.ly/i/3he4B     
    
    
    @RusticRetrieval I really like it too! I'd show you the living room if it wasn't covered in toys (it's nothing special anyway). :)    
    
    
    Hey @RusticRetrieval! Inherited this barrister's bookcase. To paint or not to paint? http://ow.ly/i/3he4B     
    
    
    Hey @RusticRetrieval! Inherited this barrister's bookcase. To paint or not to paint? http://ow.ly/i/3he4B     
    
    
    Hey @DrJulieGill, remember that time, seven years ago today when we got married? To each other? That was awesome.    
    
    
    The Guelph Farmers' Market needs more work - https://sweettemptations.ca/why-the-guelph-farmers-market-is-a-work-in-progress/ … Read our perspective as an 'islander' vendor    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    This loud-mouthed woman was eager to get online and make sure that Commander Hadfield would still be tweeting. Don't worry, he is.    
    
    
    @LynnBeSocial Here's my @guelphonography post with your photo of the wonderful organizing committee. Thanks again! :) http://ow.ly/po0Yk     
    
    
    Great post! RT @hwatterworth: Here's my @guelphonography post with your photo of the wonderful organizing committee. http://ow.ly/po0Yk     
    
    
    @blushshop Hi Michele! Thanks for the follow! Did @RusticRetrieval fill you in on the #Guelph blogger brunch we're planning?    
    
    
    Expresso    
    
    
    Expresso    
    
    
    In which I win 3rd place @guelphonography and gush about #Guelph. http://ow.ly/po9WY     
    
    
    Great post! And congrats! RT @hwatterworth: In which I win 3rd place @guelphonography and gush about #Guelph. http://ow.ly/po9WY     
    
    
    In which I win 3rd place @guelphonography and gush about #Guelph. http://ow.ly/po9WY     
    
    
        
    
    
    Which do you prefer? We value your input. pic.twitter.com/KLLkAB4tW2    
    
    
    Which do you prefer? We value your input. pic.twitter.com/KLLkAB4tW2    
    
    
    Linked #guelph #guelphonography http://instagram.com/p/fA4wW4rpS1/     
    
    
    Bill Watterson's advice is a perfect Monday morning read for freelancers and passion pursuers. http://bit.ly/1fcBogC  via @zenpencils    
    
    
    Check it out!  Thanks Heather! http://heartheather.com/2013/10/01/my-city-guelphonography-2013-exhibit/ … @guelphonography #guelphonography #guelph    
    
    
    @greyrockco Better stock up on those awesome @WearPact tights – I think a few new customers are heading your way. :) http://ow.ly/pC87c     
    
    
    @greyrockco Better stock up on those awesome @WearPact tights – I think a few new customers are heading your way. :) http://ow.ly/pC87c     
    
    
    What it rains it pours, and I usually forget my umbrella.    
    
    
    Happy birthday @hwatterworth !!!  Have a great day!    
    
    
    Special Birthday wishes going out to @hwatterworth !!!
See you soon!    
    
    
    @Tiny_Pants you are the WINNER for the #tonicfabricfun contest! #blogpodium #tonicliving  more deets here  http://www.tonicliving.com/News.aspx     
    
    
    So flattered to be included! Thanks Jen! RT @ramblingreno: On the blog: Top 10 Blogger Business Cards http://bit.ly/1e8kMDI     
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi Heather! I love your website! Who did it?!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi Heather! I love your website! Who did it?!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi Heather! I love your website! Who did it?!    
    
    
    Friday night lights, Canadian style. #fnl #rinkrat http://instagram.com/p/fokLPekJZz/     
    
    
    Really looking forward to our local blogging gals brunch this weekend!    
    
    
    #guelphblogbrunch is coming your way @39CardenStreet. See you soon @rusticretrieval @HeatherNHeels @bearandlionmama @blushshop @itsdilovely!    
    
    
    #guelphblogbrunch is coming your way @39CardenStreet. See you soon @rusticretrieval @HeatherNHeels @bearandlionmama @blushshop @itsdilovely!    
    
    
    Delicious #guelphblogbrunch @39CardenStreet! Thanks for indulging our snap happy group! :)    
    
    
    #guelphblogbrunch is coming your way @39CardenStreet. See you soon @rusticretrieval @HeatherNHeels @bearandlionmama @blushshop @itsdilovely!    
    
    
    #guelphblogbrunch is coming your way @39CardenStreet. See you soon @rusticretrieval @HeatherNHeels @bearandlionmama @blushshop @itsdilovely!    
    
    
    #guelphblogbrunch is coming your way @39CardenStreet. See you soon @rusticretrieval @HeatherNHeels @bearandlionmama @blushshop @itsdilovely!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth No words to describe the WOW of this post! Work It. http://heartheather.com/2013/09/16/work-it/ …    
    
    
    should my blog have self responsive web design??? #helpme #bloggingquestion    
    
    
    should my blog have self responsive web design??? #helpme #bloggingquestion    
    
    
    Today @DrJulieGill and I heard the number of heart beats in our family jump from two to three.    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] How I made 5 new friends over brunch. #guelphblogbrunch http://ow.ly/q4ha2     
    
    
    Today @DrJulieGill and I heard the number of heart beats in our family jump from two to three.    
    
    
    @tlrowanrmt Happy birthday lady! May you day include cupcakes, and pie, and ice cream, and all the sweet things ever.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for such a lovely blog post! #newfriends http://heartheather.com/2013/10/22/how-i-made-5-new-friends-over-brunch/ …    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] How I made 5 new friends over brunch. #guelphblogbrunch http://ow.ly/q4ha2     
    
    
    Great post about the #GuelphBlogBrunch and our little bistro by @hwatterworth! Awesome pics too! http://buff.ly/18K9EM7     
    
    
    Great post about the #GuelphBlogBrunch and our little bistro by @hwatterworth! Awesome pics too! http://buff.ly/18K9EM7     
    
    
    Coming out to @atmoscafeetc tomorrow night for @guelphonography Meet and Greet? I think you should.    
    
    
    filing under "awesome" #guelphblogbrunch http://heatherinheels.com/2013/10/file-under-awesome-guelphblogbrunch/ … @hwatterworth @RusticRetrieval @bearandlionmama @blushshop @39CardenStreet    
    
    
    Tonight! RT @downtownguelph: .@guelphonography Meet and Greet at @atmoscafeetc. Not too late to be a joiner. http://ow.ly/q7bYI     
    
    
    I both met and greeted at #guelphonography exhibit @atmoscafeetc with @PhotoMediaDecor ... And I forgot to take a picture.  #next_year    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] Butternut squash soup with a hit of acid. http://ow.ly/qatDm     
    
    
    Nice work @missamybarnes! RT @hrcheritage: The 3rd @Bldg_Stories Podcast on Keefer Mansion in Thorold released Mon. http://ow.ly/qbxtX     
    
    
    @hwatterworth see you tonight if you're still going! Yay! @igniteguelph    
    
    
    So excited to hear about #igniteyouth - the "offspring" of @igniteguelph developed by local high school students. April 25, 2014.    
    
    
    “There's a bit of magic in everything, and some loss to even things out.”  – Lou Reed    
    
    
    Avocados, a @TipsNailBar manicure, and time to catch up with @janinefalcon... Is it Monday yet? #LuvMexAvocado    
    
    
    Avocados, a @TipsNailBar manicure, and time to catch up with @janinefalcon... Is it Monday yet? #LuvMexAvocado    
    
    
    Shiny, soft and beet-tastic thanks to @MissAvaCado and @TipsNailBar. #LuvMexAvocado http://instagram.com/p/gB3_tNEJUr/     
    
    
    Beautifying from the inside out. #nomnomnom #luvmexavocado http://instagram.com/p/gB4Y0tkJVH/     
    
    
    Shiny, soft and beet-tastic thanks to @MissAvaCado and @TipsNailBar. #LuvMexAvocado http://instagram.com/p/gB3_tNEJUr/     
    
    
    Every time @JanineFalcon tells me I have great skin I squeal. She's giving us avocado beauty hacks #luvmexavocado pic.twitter.com/50wkeoac2b    
    
    
    In love with this moody purple grey! Nars, NY Dolls. Pretty hand model is Victoria of @_thebeautyteam. http://ow.ly/i/3yAy7  #LuvMexAvocado    
    
    
    In love with this moody purple grey! Nars, NY Dolls. Pretty hand model is Victoria of @_thebeautyteam. http://ow.ly/i/3yAy7  #LuvMexAvocado    
    
    
    In love with this moody purple grey! Nars, NY Dolls. Pretty hand model is Victoria of @_thebeautyteam. http://ow.ly/i/3yAy7  #LuvMexAvocado    
    
    
    @LeeanneColley So thrilled to have finally met you and have your ridiculously-talented self work on my nails. xo    
    
    
    @LeeanneColley So thrilled to have finally met you and have your ridiculously-talented self work on my nails. xo    
    
    
    Help shape economic dev in #Guelph – free to attend! MT @ONEGuelph: 2 weeks until Community Builders Event http://ow.ly/qhqX0     
    
    
    on pins and needles waiting to hear if I am one of the lucky 5 chosen for the #ParaBlogCrew @PARAPaints #fingerscrossed #dreamBIG    
    
    
    @momwhoruns Great meeting you last night - wish we'd had more time to chat!    
    
    
    Nice to see @linerglttrgloss @makeupjunkie19 @hwatterworth @lelotheartist @beautygeeks @_thebeautyteam on #Monday! http://beautyphd.blogspot.com/2013/10/nails-philosophy-avocados-from-mexico.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Okay #Guelph, time to toss that pumpkin. Ready to re-decorate? Order your festive greenery to support a local school http://greening-committee.blogspot.ca/2013/10/holiday-wreath-fundraiser.html …    
    
    
    Pour vous, @justingodard. RT @sparkcbc: A visual history of beautiful Braun design ^ny http://www.core77.com/blog/braun/     
    
    
    [BLOGGED] November, you've got your work cut out for you. http://ow.ly/qnQSs     
    
    
    [BLOGGED] Butternut squash soup with a hit of acid. http://ow.ly/qatDm     
    
    
    Worst. Keep your eyes peeled people. RT @Brydon: the end of an era...brown betty (my loyal bike) stolen from downtown #Guelph.    
    
    
    @GracieCarroll did you give Vinylux another go? My mani is still perfect and I think it will make it through this week too. I'm amazed    
    
    
    @GracieCarroll did you give Vinylux another go? My mani is still perfect and I think it will make it through this week too. I'm amazed    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] Breakfast, or beauty treatment? Getting hands on with #LuvMexAvocados. http://ow.ly/qwaQH  @MissAvaCado @savvari @JanineFalcon    
    
    
    #Guelph lifestyle/design/[insert your niche here] bloggers: join me for brunch @TheJointCafe on November 24! http://ow.ly/qwbuP     
    
    
    @localkelly Hi Kelly! Just wanted to make sure you got my note about the next #Guelph blog brunch. :)    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] If you don't ask, the answer is always no. http://ow.ly/qAu4f     
    
    
    Thanks for the RTs @shessnaphappy @DrMarkKubert! What are you going to ask for today? ;)    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] If you don't ask, the answer is always no. http://ow.ly/qAu4f     
    
    
    Is this you? It's totally me! Now, go read! RT @hwatterworth: [BLOGGED] If you don't ask, the answer is always no. http://ow.ly/qAu4f     
    
    
    LIFE CHANGING. RT @vangerwen: What to Do When You Run Out of Wrapping Paper: http://bit.ly/1bbA7mS     
    
    
    Do you have a crush on your manicurist? Time to visit @LeeanneColley @TipsNailBar. Here's why: http://ow.ly/qDdY2     
    
    
    Do you have a crush on your manicurist? Time to visit @LeeanneColley @TipsNailBar. Here's why: http://ow.ly/qDdY2     
    
    
    #Guelph lifestyle/design/[insert your niche here] bloggers: join me for brunch @TheJointCafe on November 24! http://ow.ly/qwbuP     
    
    
    Gwenivere Teele Gofton was born 6.22 today. 9 pound 6 ounces. 22 inces long. We are all doing great :)    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] I'm a sentimental hoarder. (And I'm encouraging you to be too with a $50 @minted giveaway.) http://ow.ly/qIRqA     
    
    
    Refreshing perspective on children/digital identity/privacy. RT @KimVallee: Why we gave our baby a digital identity http://ow.ly/qJSBT     
    
    
    Cross off find/buy/address/mail Christmas cards from your list in one go. Enter to win a $50 @minted gift card! http://ow.ly/qITjY     
    
    
    [BLOGGED] Here's how to make sure no one shreds your Christmas card this year. http://ow.ly/qITpE  @minted #giveaway    
    
    
    Cross off find/buy/address/mail Christmas cards from your list in one go. Enter to win a $50 @minted gift card! http://ow.ly/qITjY     
    
    
    Last day to enter to win a $50 @Minted gift card! http://ow.ly/qITjY     
    
    
    New job boots. #fromwhereistand #firstday #guelph #excited #youcantellbecauseineverusethismanyhashtags http://instagram.com/p/g26xYskJWL/     
    
    
    Excited to officially join @ONEGuelph team today! Amazing organization enabling growth and community wellbeing in the city I love. #Guelph    
    
    
    Excited to officially join @ONEGuelph team today! Amazing organization enabling growth and community wellbeing in the city I love. #Guelph    
    
    
    Hey @lucidcreative! Christmas has come early – you won the $50 @Minted giveaway on my blog. Check your e-mail! Happy shopping! :)    
    
    
    Just won a $50 @minted giveaway from @hwatterworth!  Now comes the big dilemma.  Should I spend it on xmas cards or wedding stuff???    
    
    
    @sustaininguelph Great meeting you today. Looking forward to col.lab.o.rating soon.    
    
    
    A post by @hwatterworth about having a support system - if you don't ask, the answer is always no http://heartheather.com/2013/11/07/if-you-dont-ask-the-answer-is-always-no-a-free-printable/ …    
    
    
    Excited to officially join @ONEGuelph team today! Amazing organization enabling growth and community wellbeing in the city I love. #Guelph    
    
    
    Dear @justingodard, Almost every day I am grateful that you took time to teach me about bezier curves.    
    
    
    Dear @justingodard, Almost every day I am grateful that you took time to teach me about bezier curves.    
    
    
    Steam is down. #steam http://issteamdown.com     
    
    
    Steam is down. #steam http://issteamdown.com     
    
    
    Congrats Michele! :) RT @blushshop: Excited to share this article from LUXE life!
http://www.theluxelife.com/article/blush-rural-boutique-big-city-style/ … http://fb.me/17ywe09EU     
    
    
    Great shopping in Guelph (yeah, you read that right): http://www.theluxelife.com/article/blush-rural-boutique-big-city-style/ … cc @blushshop @ontheballhall    
    
    
    Last call for any #Guelph bloggers who want to meet for brunch @TheJointCafe on Sunday. Details and RSVP: https://www.facebook.com/events/248509728634914/ …    
    
    
    @hwatterworth cool website! Thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    Help make #Guelph a little yummier by supporting @Sweet_T_Cakes flagship storefront campaign! http://ow.ly/r6NZl     
    
    
    Help make #Guelph a little yummier by supporting @Sweet_T_Cakes flagship storefront campaign! http://ow.ly/r6NZl     
    
    
    There are only 4 Saturdays until Christmas, and 3 of them have #Guelph handmade craft shows happening. A round-up: http://ow.ly/r78t0     
    
    
    Looking 4ward to #guelph #blogbrunch @TheJointCafe @hwatterworth @blushshop @lynneknowlton @RusticRetrieval @itsdilovely @heatherinheels    
    
    
    Loved my first time being a member of the Grizzly Bear Coffee coffee share. Looking forward to the winter share! http://ow.ly/r834q     
    
    
    Thanks for a fun #guelphblogbrunch @blushshop @lynneknowlton @RusticRetrieval @itsdilovely @LocalKelly @friendsmycloset @bearandlionmama!    
    
    
    The best @indiegogo campaigns have cupcakes as perks. Help @Sweet_T_Cakes build more space to bake more cupcakes! http://ow.ly/r6O1k     
    
    
    Oh @LesaHannah, never change. RT @shop_pretty: "French manicures are obscene, vile, tacky beyond reason…” http://www.shoppretty.ca/2013/11/the-editor-hates-it-fashion-beauty.html …    
    
    
    Just found a toy truck in my purse. I'm really, officially, a mom. #instagrahamwashere http://instagram.com/p/hMAwsRkJen/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth cool website! Thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    Is it really this close to Christmas?? Thanks @hwatterworth handmade holiday // guelph craft show listings http://heartheather.com/2013/11/23/guelph-craft-show-listings/ …    
    
    
    I can't wait... Had to share! Can you guess what our holiday window is going to be? #numbers #red… http://instagram.com/p/hOrNzCw4sb/     
    
    
    Some bridal hair fascinators I created for trial runs with my brides. Thoughts?!  http://twitpic.com/431wju     
    
    
    @E_M_I Hi lady! Will I be seeing you got breakfast tomorrow?    
    
    
    @E_M_I Hi lady! Will I be seeing you got breakfast tomorrow?    
    
    
    @blushshop @APaperBuffet @MPezzanoart @GreyRockCo @EXPERIENCETHREE @hwatterworth are just some of my fav #entrepreneurs #local    
    
    
    [BLOGGED] A gift guide for cyclists featuring @CanGift @RYBDenim and @MomentumMag. Plus, you could win a Bike Cap! http://ow.ly/rwffX     
    
    
    "A study in blue-collar beauty": @lesahannah interviews hair & makeup leads on The Fighter http://bit.ly/ijjqWf    
    
    
    If you brave the cold on your bike, you deserve to win a bike cap. Enter to win one on my blog: http://ow.ly/rIgPT     
    
    
    Just saw a little girl hug the crossing guard near her school. Morning made. #Guelph    
    
    
    Orange you glad you let me paint the office orange? @InnovateGuelph pic.twitter.com/sUa1FlsZIi    
    
    
    My wee elf. #laterGraham http://instagram.com/p/iMpFcFkJYK/     
    
    
    And the game hadn't even started yet. #rinkrats #twoofakind http://instagram.com/p/iPBk_UkJT-/     
    
    
    PJ Harvey's voice makes me want to weep. So beautiful. See: the River. Also Black Hearted Love for baby making.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/irn6c Last date as an unmarried couple!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi Heather I am en route from Hawaii.  Wishing you a beautiful and blessed day for your nuptials.  Love Lynda    
    
    
    has retired her pink pom poms. (So long, and thanks for all the lip gloss.)    
    
    
    Awesome – congrats @kimvallee! RT At Home with Kim Vallee one of best blogs for foodies in 1st issue of @Zeste_tv http://yfrog.com/h7ap9itj    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy @hwatterworth looks great!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth how do you feel about the canteen at the bell lightbox?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Five sound good?    
    
    
    @dreizle Thanks for the follow! Looking forward to meeting you next week!    
    
    
    Adieu Toronto. Honeymoon in Paris here we come!    
    
    
    @ninagodard I love the idea of purchasing additional typefaces. Obvi I just need Helvetica. Maybe a little Didot won't hurt.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth looking forward to meeting you tomorrow! :)    
    
    
    @mikebaronowski My new hair elicited mock wolf howls from husband. Well done Edward Scissorhands!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Just creeping your profile! I hope you don't mind! :)    
    
    
    Dress for tonight. You can't tell burt it is bright yellow. http://yfrog.com/h7ui0unj    
    
    
    Even though I am so tired, I'm excited be in a room full of talented and successful people.  Can their awesomeness rub off on me?  #cmw    
    
    
    But you already knew this, right @LesaHannah @kflemming? RT @natomaton J. Crew coming to Toronto in 2011: http://tinyurl.com/3782ftt    
    
    
    Yes mom that is me -- part of a feature in Allure mag Korea on worldwide beauty bloggers! Super cool I think!  http://yfrog.com/gznfofcj     
    
    
    Smartie Pants! @KimVallee Our writer @hwatterworth shared a story by @marthastewart on how to protect cookbook pages http://kim.tl/fTqu1K     
    
    
    You know what that is? That is my stuff shoved into my kitchen so they can fix my bloody floors. http://yfrog.com/h3qp0vij    
    
    
    Was photographed by Gabor Jurina this morning for @Dove skincare launch event. Model material, I am not!    
    
    
    @baharniramwalla So fun to see your pretty face! Let's do that more often please.    
    
    
    @_biancs_ Break out the diorama! RT @artofdoingstuff Marshmallow Easter Peep place cards! http://wp.me/pPpVJ-3Gn    
    
    
    @_BIANCS_ I've been following this regiment the past few weeks – good motivation to purge! http://cure.apartmenttherapy.com/2009/fall/    
    
    
    @janinefalcon, congrats on your very, very well deserved win last night!    
    
    
    Hey Internet, where can I find iPhone friendly gloves?? #stupidwinter    
    
    
    Happy Friday @KFlemming! Pour vous: http://tinyurl.com/2b6o523    
    
    
    Ha! RT @DT666 PS: Shark Flu. It's only a matter of time.    
    
    
    My son is home, at last!!! He sleeps peaceful in his mamaRoo (thanks 4moms) while listening to a playlist http://twitpic.com/4f41sh     
    
    
    @jcasensio You *might* want to strike that little detail from your resume. What stage are you in these days, anyway?    
    
    
    Virtual high fives! RT @lmmichaels @Fila_100 microsite is LIVE! Hard work pays off :) (cc @aimskeane @Dreizle @emsaso)    
    
    
    Check out me & @Styledwithin in the @FashionCanada LGFW street style snaps! http://bit.ly/gzOcyz    
    
    
    @boomboomtunes Watching Jamie Oliver's Food Revolution and he just referenced J.R. Ewing. Thought you should know. #eventhebritsknowwhoheis    
    
    
    @SaraACooper do tell! (If it's the 82, there's not a hope in the evenings...)    
    
    
    @SaraACooper yup, it's rush hour only. I've been riding that route for 5+ years. Mornings are generally painless; evenings... not so much.    
    
    
    @boomboomtunes We're not alone! RT @ShannonBoudjema you know you're gen x when s/o in office has no clue about JR or Dallas / "Who shot JR!"    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy Pssst! RT @wordaddict914 Looking for a Mommy in Toronto who is in a Mommy-and-me group for a nat'l feature- DM ME!! :)    
    
    
    @justingodard Dude. Brain cell. Seriously. We can't even blame it on osmosis anymore.    
    
    
    Hooray for a quick drink w/ @hwatterworth.    
    
    
    Jealous!! RT @justingodard Hooray for a quick drink w/ @hwatterworth.    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy Love seeing the result of this! :) "RT Yellow Makes Me Happy" http://flic.kr/p/9yDq9e    
    
    
    @ablahut You will lose your mind over this - no more picks in the laundry! :) http://tinyurl.com/3ks5uza    
    
    
    I love Steve Buscemi, but this is terrifying. RT @rlangdon The Chicks With Steve Buscemeyes Tumblr http://bit.ly/felNzZ    
    
    
    Perfect rainy day lupper (lunch + supper) and girl talk with @_biancs_ @thegrilledcheez.    
    
    
    The brows! The brows! RT @LesaHannah I love PJ Harvey, but hair on the cover of today's TO Star is unforgivable. http://plixi.com/p/93614791    
    
    
    That. is. AWESOME. RT @shessnaphappy Bacon Skaters. #ilovemysonsmind http://instagr.am/p/DVQHV/    
    
    
    @justingodard For Viv: http://enroute.aircanada.com/en/film-festival    
    
    
    @hwatterworth sweet - merci!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for following. judging by your bio, we will get along well!    
    
    
    +1 RT @makesomething @MarthaStewart i'm in Toronto, Canada and we don't have Hallmark here! i miss watching you, Martha!    
    
    
    @SarahFlink Which Twitter app are you using?    
    
    
    Husband making Easter egg bread. http://instagr.am/p/DbbPc/    
    
    
    @ablahut Date night June 22. And, let's face it, probably May 14 too. RT @Outside_Music Sloan NA Tour News: http://tinyurl.com/3ju8g9l    
    
    
    @boomboomtunes @kristin_new Spotted! (in photo #3) http://tinyurl.com/6e4mny4 (cc @lchoee)    
    
    
    Smart. RT @davefleet QR Code Resume Makes Your Embossed Paper Look Lame: http://on.mash.to/fdbqW9    
    
    
    @jen_thompson How much are you loving those gratuitous ice cream shots? ;) "RT Cool it, Ladies!: http://tinyurl.com/447pw7r"    
    
    
    So much fun @cdn_designblgrs meetup last night! Loved meeting @the_HomeSlice @SogniESorrisi @YYZdesign @littlehouseblog @lisamurphyTO + ...    
    
    
    More lovely bloggers from @cdn_designblgrs meetup: @alifemorefab @eatliveshop @pink_peacock @cherishtoronto @inlifeinfashion    
    
    
    You can thank @ablahut for that. :) RT @Dreizle Learned a new term today. PEBKAC = Problem exists between keyboard and chair.    
    
    
    @ramblingreno So lovely to finally meet you! Thanks for chatting with me. :) #CBMisstweetup    
    
    
    @decormentor Great chatting with you tonight! Can't wait to see your new site and learn more about Decor Mentor. #CBMisstweetup    
    
    
    @hdstylestudio @living_fresh Thanks for spreading some luck my way ladies! Definitely rubbing shoulders with you next time. :)    
    
    
    Thanks @cdn_designblgrs @verdigrisvie @CBSquareOne for organizing a fun tweet up last night!    
    
    
    Great to meet all you gals last night! @JennBrouwer @hwatterworth @hdstylestudio @LisaMackay @living_fresh @lovelaughshop #FF xo    
    
    
    @ablahut ha! A Romance Flowchart: When Is It Inappropriate to Use Your iPhone? http://gizmodo.com/5419435/ (via @sarahroger)    
    
    
    Anyone know CP style for the abbreviation of Nunavut? My book is outdated...    
    
    
    @frozengrapes thanks!    
    
    
    @make_something I'm sure your holiday to-do list is long enough, but RT @design_sponge terrarium ornaments how-to http://bit.ly/6uox9A    
    
    
    Magnolias! RT @laurenonizzle: Are these cherry blossoms? I don't even care. They're beautiful. http://twitpic.com/4sgs16    
    
    
    Feet finally regain feeling after 45 min. bus wait and it's time to head into the cold again.    
    
    
    So many terrified children. http://www.sketchysantas.com/    
    
    
    @hwatterworth that's weird- I swear I was already following you hah but I wasn't- don't know how that happened. Happy Tuesday!    
    
    
    @yahoocanadalife These are really well-designed - you may need to embrace hat head though! http://www.wildhagenwear.com/    
    
    
    So much for penmanship awards. http://ow.ly/4MCct    
    
    
    So excited about @ChatelaineMag's month of May salads! Such a great idea.    
    
    
    The beautiful @kimvallee! RT @fashioncanada: Our beauty at every age series continues: Top tips at 42 http://bit.ly/j26yq3    
    
    
    Crazy cat ladies achieve a new level of craziness. RT @beautygeeks: Cat Manicure: Nail Tips for Kitty. Seriously. http://nblo.gs/hsaIf    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Thanks for the RT, Heather!    
    
    
    49 tabs X 3 browser windows RT @ohjoystudio: just realized i have 49 tabs open on my browser #tabaholicsanonymous    
    
    
    Garage-saleing for find vintage muffin tins this weekend. So cute! http://ow.ly/4OCvj (cc @_biancs_)    
    
    
    Amazing. RT @stephnairn: Dads are the Original Hipsters http://ow.ly/4OE8G    
    
    
    Really miss Friday afternoon commutes with @hwatterworth.    
    
    
    Sat afternoon beauty MVPs: @getSUPER SPF, @korresusa concealer & @tartecosmetics lip stain in "Amused".    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Bc I am oily I don't need creamy moisture! Love @getSUPER's packaging too!    
    
    
    @cisionsupport how can I specify a contact for an outlet already in a list? When I specify a contact it duplicates the outlet in the list.    
    
    
    Thanks @cisionsupport! Figured it out.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Inspiration for a certain Sept wedding? Thx to @justinleephoto http://ow.ly/4S7UU (via @grnweddingshoes)    
    
    
    Signed up for Pinterest last night but battery died before I could really play with it. Have some invites if anyone else is curious    
    
    
    Went to Winners at lunch to look for shoes that can make my swelling feet feel better.  Ended up with throw pillows and chocolate. Oops.    
    
    
    @KimVallee @hwatterworth Thank you!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @BaharNiramwalla! Have a beauty day. :)    
    
    
    In need of some font-spiration right now. Nothing seems quite right.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth I've settled on Avant Garde.    
    
    
    That's it!  I'm officially a blackberry hater. Freezing, corrupt address book, and useless browser!  Anyone want to buy a cheap Bold! :P    
    
    
    @hwatterworth not the 'iLight'...if that's what you mean. ;)    
    
    
    Yay! The Crate & Barrel gift certificate I won at the tweet up arrived! Thank you so much @CBSquareOne for the prize & hosting a fun event!    
    
    
    @beautyparler Happy blogiversary lady! Here's to many more beauty-full posts to come.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth oops, actually I think its this one: http://trunc.it/gj90r.  Same computer, but front-mount sensor.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Had to go on a bit of a recon mission but look what I found! (cc @justingodard) http://instagr.am/p/EMLr9/    
    
    
    Is 5 calendars too many for one home? RT @kimvallee Our 2011 Calendar Round-Up prepared by @hwatterworth http://kim.tl/gQuDO2    
    
    
    @lesahannah @siofan PLEASE tell me you just say the Hammer as half of the Ambiguously Gay Duo on SNL!!!    
    
    
    Totally captivated by @HairRomance's 30 Days of Twist & Pin Hairstyles. Beauty gals: you will love! http://ow.ly/4VWc0    
    
    
    You're so on it, right @justingodard? RT @toromagazine: Daily TORO: Hear a New Track From Bon Iver http://ow.ly/1cHkmU    
    
    
    Waiting for an invite from Pintrest is like waiting in a long line at a club & hoping to be allowed in- What the heck, I wanna join / party    
    
    
    @hwatterworth yes!! Thank you Heather! Now I'm vip ;)    
    
    
    Is there a way to gage how many followers are gained from a set date to another date? Besides doing it manually?    
    
    
    So excited for new PJ Harvey,"Let England Shake", out Feb 14. The woman is a force to be reckoned with.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth I haven't quite figured it out yet but I love all the beautiful photos! Any tips?    
    
    
    @boomboomtunes If we had known each other in the 80s, we would have used this to talk about JR: http://pinterest.com/pin/24736514/    
    
    
    Dear Rain, ENOUGH ALREADY!!    
    
    
    Paris: Need neighbourhood suggestions to stay.    
    
    
    @ablahut Memories! RT @jtriangle: Review of the Crossways Mall (Dundas and Bloor) @blogTO: http://goo.gl/2vey8    
    
    
    I would appreciate if the birds didn't poop on my clean diapers. mkaythanks.    
    
    
    Wish I was staying put but it's back to NYC this weekend. Wedding in Brooklyn and work on Tues. Can't wait to finally meet @hwatterworth!    
    
    
    Thank You @hwatterworth for the beautiful inclusion in your blog http://tinyurl.com/3ow9zze. I am most thrilled that you loved your products    
    
    
    @josh_assad Happy (first) birthday (wishes on Twitter!). Hope you're having a great day! :)    
    
    
    @khregs @josh_assad At least you were on time? :)    
    
    
    Too much dust in the air = furnace fail. What about our lungs?! #homerenos    
    
    
    Church sign in the neighb':  "Prayer is the original wireless connection." #mimicoforever (cc @Jen_Thompson)    
    
    
    Could be worse. Could be Dodge. RT @bondean: They use a Jesus and Mary Chain song in a Volkswagon ad. Is nothing sacred?    
    
    
    Okay @justingodard, so you were right about Bon Iver afterall. (Phil Spector Xmas wasn't bad either). Now what else you got?    
    
    
    Fun! Tomorrow I'm starting a 30-day photography challenge. Check it out! http://whitepeachphoto.com/2011/05/25/photography_challenge/    
    
    
    There's nothing sweeter than a @cupcakeride! http://ow.ly/57eWi    
    
    
    Thank you for the lovely write up! Can I share on FB? RT @hwatterworth There's nothing sweeter than a @cupcakeride! http://ow.ly/57eWi    
    
    
    @hwatterworth goats cheese smashed potatoes = good call  http://yfrog.com/h0mr0urj     
    
    
    @jordan23_craig Now now, no need to rub it in!    
    
    
    @lizaherz @janinefalcon Psst, your beauty math debunking skills are needed. RT @poppytalk If you put on 15 spf + 30 spf , do you get 45 spf?    
    
    
    Thanks @rebeccaemma for planning my Saturday! RT @toronto_life: Etsy pop-up shop to happen this weekend: http://ow.ly/59CLH    
    
    
    Rock and roll! RT @hitRECordJoe I FEEL HAPPY OF MYSELF! http://tumblr.com/x6d2tuhtmk #LittleKidsGivingPepTalks    
    
    
        
    
    
    *smile*  @KimVallee well @hwatterworth had me with her bio! Brilliance. :)    
    
    
    Hey @ss_cupcakes! Whatcha baking for Dad's day? A suggestion: http://pinterest.com/pin/30736067/    
    
    
    @khregs Double date with @pyamaguti and @ablahut this Friday? http://tinyurl.com/6hukw6v    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @ablahut Psst: RT @outside_music: Want to meet @Sloanmusic at their show on June 22? http://ow.ly/5eNlm    
    
    
    i cannot decide! do we like designlovefest or design love fest. spaces or no spaces? it's time i choose for realz. help please.    
    
    
    Ankle strap! RT @rebeccaemma: Shoemergency! At barneys and can't make a decision. What do you think?! http://yfrog.com/gy3abwnj    
    
    
    @kat_peterson and we love your visits! Thanks for a fun chat this morning!    
    
    
    @justingodard food for thought: http://www.creativepro.com/article/abcs-hj    
    
    
    @jen_thompson @shessnaphappy @AlideBold Thanks for the RTs chicks! So thrilled to be contributing to @ChickAdvisor! :)    
    
    
    Yay Heather (@hwatterworth)! http://j.mp/jK25eK    
    
    
    @FourLeafClover Thank you for your sweet comment on my blog! Made my day! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ladies: do you like your guy waxed or hairy & scary? How much is too much for dudes to take off?    
    
    
    Pssst @AndyLouCooper... RT @rockitpromo: Feist will be joining us @ #Powerplant for Powerball 13 tonight. Gonna be a rockin' night!    
    
    
    #FF Girl Crush Edition: @JanineFalcon @LesaHannah @KFlemming @KimVallee @jen_thompson @shessnaphappy @make_something    
    
    
        
    
    
    June Girl's Ride is Sat.! RT @cupcakeride: Sweet Ride ride report! @BobbetteBelle, La Boheme & the Distillery: http://www.cupcakeride.com/blog/?p=131  #bikeTO    
    
    
    On June 23, starting at 12 for 160 mins, @KiehlsCa will donate 100% of in-store & online sales to children's oncology camps!    
    
    
    @justingodard by colour?    
    
    
    Today is #KIEHLSSHOPFORTHECAUSE! At 12, for 160 mins, @KiehlsCa will donate 100% of sales instore & online to kids cancer camps! Please RT!    
    
    
    Something off about this Kate Moss cover, non?? http://bit.ly/d2nX1d    
    
    
    Really wish there was a place to get ice cream around Spadina/Adelaide.    
    
    
    @justingodard weren't you yammering about him? RT @ThatEricAlper NPR has posted a World Cafe session with James Blake: http://dld.bz/aeNCx     
    
    
    Nice Jason! Well deserved! RT @theserovingeyes: Check me out on @FLAREfashion! bit.ly/mhXY4K. So exciting! Thanks @RyanMCheung!    
    
    
    @shessnaphappy nice on both accounts? What colour did you choose for the pan?    
    
    
        
    
    
    June @CupcakeRide Recap: nearly 2 weeks late but no less sweet. http://heartheather.com/2011/07/04/cupcake-ride-june-2011/ …    
    
    
    @justingodard RT Brian Jonestown Massacre playing the Phoenix in June! Anton with Matt Hollywood (!) but not Joel Gion(via @johnpapa)    
    
    
    Script meeting, inane questions, seminar planning, and no alcohol. Already hating this... @justingodard @hwatterworth    
    
    
    more about the workroom's new online shop! http://bit.ly/p3EWNu     
    
    
    This morning some graphic designers intro'd me to virtual tearsheet/pinboard site Pinterest.com & O.M.G. Should I fall down the rabbit hole?    
    
    
    At my house with the girls from nkpr! @LMMichaels @amskeane @SarahFlink...we love @dominos pizza! :) http://yfrog.com/klctgzkj    
    
    
    Ooooh birthday loot! http://yfrog.com/1ecoyrj    
    
    
    Mmm birthday chocolate shell filled with chocolatey goodness... http://yfrog.com/32tlqj    
    
    
    Need zzz's but must stay awake for @PChiddy #Patrick Chan    
    
    
    This little gal was too cute for words - had to have her for our tree (she looked familiar, too!): http://twitpic.com/3bhsx6    
    
    
    @justingodard losing it over this: just heard about this Chat Roullette thing. F'n CRAZY !! (via @aquadrunkard)    
    
    
    @mahlitz I'm not home yet and I left at 5! Brutal!    
    
    
    @LMMichaels Pour vous: Summer quinoa salad recipe with three dressing options: http://www.canadianliving.com/blogs/food/2011/07/22/summer-quinoa-salad-recipe-with-three-dressing-options/ …    
    
    
    Didn't get the memo to wear all black today. In orange and polka dots instead. #HolidayinJuly #PRFail    
    
    
    @hwatterworth, you were right; I'm on what's to be the first of many tubes of Sugar Rosé. Why didn't I try this earlier?! #lipbalmobsession    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hi! Can you follow me? I want to DM you a question. Thanks!    
    
    
    The companion shoe to every Christmas pageant of my childhood. http://tinyurl.com/2bxkfdm    
    
    
    Congrats Sarah! Have a beautiful first day! FRT @LesaHannah @s_dsquared officially joins me today as Beauty Editor at @FashionCanada.    
    
    
    A year older this morning, but none the wiser.    
    
    
    401 is rammed. Bus driver took detour. Passengers look panicked. #notsoscenicroute    
    
    
    Dear Mississauga Transit, Perhaps consider hiring drivers who actually know the city. #route82    
    
    
    Duty calls tomorrow night, @hwatterworth. Will have to press pause on the christmas crafting this week.    
    
    
    Imagining an alternate reality version of #glee starring Zooey and Mr. Ward. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=W18_OO8TD78    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Hey girl! Try to remember your book tomorrow. I'm dying to see it!    
    
    
    Wonders if the Draper not-so-dreamy house can be far behind. RT @LesaHannah Mad Men Barbie dolls! http://nyti.ms/c15ijc    
    
    
    Today marks the 1 year anniversary of loosing/accidentally throwing out half my wardrobe. I still miss you Prada pants & camel hair skirt.    
    
    
    got a link-back from NYMAG.COM! http://bit.ly/d2sxUG And is a tad excited about that.    
    
    
    Psst @jen_thompson! Did you see the #mimicoforever love on @designsponge? The neighb' is totally legit now! http://ow.ly/6btdl    
    
    
    DH reminds me #Christmas is only four months away. Does he know me, or does he know me?!? @hwatterworth, start your glue gun. #geturcrafton    
    
    
    @LMMichaels Pretty beet treats for you! :) http://instagr.am/p/LadXV/     
    
    
    Fantastic night in the 'hood with @hwatterworth. Dinner? Delicious. The conversation? Even better. Wonder what the DHs had ;) #mimicoforever    
    
    
    @jen_thompson @hwatterworth thanks for the recommendation.    
    
    
    With sweater vest + toque his cute quotient is off the charts! RT @shessnaphappy A reason to smile today: http://flic.kr/p/8XYsMP    
    
    
    How long do beets last before peeled? @hwatterworth. Another night with no time to cook! Do I have a few more days?!    
    
    
    YES. RT @ellistuhler Today's song courtesy of @hwatterworth. Magnifique cover of Serge's Bonnie and Clyde. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tXeCLVsA5PQ …    
    
    
    Looky, looky! It's #TIFF guru @boomboomtunes in @nowlifestyle! She's *that* awesome. http://ow.ly/6iUDz    
    
    
    I. love. rock and roll. too, karaoke bar across the street, but it's time for effing bed. #somebodypulltheplug #mimicoforever    
    
    
    @ThatEricAlper Dean & Britta?    
    
    
    Monday night's a-calling, @hwatterworth : http://twitpic.com/3d94px    
    
    
    The catalyst for my annual holiday weight gain: shortbread meltaways (cc @thehomeslice) http://wp.me/p1fmo-ix    
    
    
    @thary_c Still thinking (and laughing about) our amazing simultaneous InDesign breakthroughs today. Virtual high five!    
    
    
    I need need need new running shoes and I'm open to suggestions. Huge fan of the Saucony shoes I currently wear.    
    
    
    LOVE 'EM. RT @MakeupJunkieJDT: has anyone tried that Goody corkscrew pin?? I keep seeing commercials for it! any good?? http://bit.ly/dGwwxz    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Really??? We'll have to have a tutorial sesh! They take a teensy bit of practice, but not much.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/1hd9b6 - Springtime in yorkville - these flowers are too exotic looking for TO! #btje    
    
    
    Just saw a woman wearing a tube sock as a scrunchie. There are no words.    
    
    
    Essential reading for PRs. RT @rockitpromo Media, Darling: @lesahannah http://goo.gl/fb/svMcJ    
    
    
    @justingodard Oh no! She got the fries! RT @ninagodard Festive special wins! http://yfrog.com/gywvij    
    
    
    It's @LesaHannah in-the-media day! More pitch tips, plus her POV on print vs. online. http://tinyurl.com/23xcmco    
    
    
    @gregory_goose Do share your findings! Mmm Schweppes...    
    
    
    Yay to my nerdy co-worker who HAD to change the type to Helvetica. Ha.    
    
    
    Just realized the new season of Mad Men starts July 25th. Calendar marked.    
    
    
    Great way to start a beautiful Saturday - 9 am kickboxing class & then breakfast with my girl @hwatterworth !    
    
    
    Yes please! RT this message if you'd like tickets to @theclothingshow from #urbanebloc - 6 pairs to give away!    
    
    
    @urbanebloc hi! I can't respond to your DM because you're not following me. Please send me your email and I'll get in touch!    
    
    
    Warning to my coworkers: tomorrow I will adjust the thermostat accordingly and wear my scarf. #gohabsgo    
    
    
    Headline du jour: "Mullet family held over Amish haircut attacks" http://bit.ly/ukSbSy  (via @TorontoStar)    
    
    
    He's nothing without the greasy hair. RT @lesahannah: Confirmed: Taylor Kitsch is not hot unless he's Riggins. http://bit.ly/w3CPfs     
    
    
    @hwatterworth And therefore, a nobody...PS Riggins greeting cards would be AMAAAZZING though.    
    
    
    My pretty little sister snapped by my super-talented friend. RT @shessnaphappy Bride, Sugarbush & Shiny Red Fire Engine http://ow.ly/7LhKU     
    
    
    Do Onion Rings count as a vegetable serving?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth does short bread count as a dairy?    
    
    
    Hey @Vaboolous! RT @shedoesthecity Guide to Toronto's holiday craft fairs including 4 this weekend: http://tinyurl.com/72x72cz     
    
    
    Mad Men is so awesome.    
    
    
    Really? Comic Sans has fans? RT @dailycandy: For all you Comic Sans fans: http://dly.me/6018RlaA     
    
    
    Most nauseating day. Ever.    
    
    
    3 day vegan juice cleanse complete! On to #powerball    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Happy New Years!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Happy New Years Heather!!!!  xoxo    
    
    
    Sooo, it's official. I'm the beauty expert on the @MarilynDenisCTV show!!! First show is on jan 11th 2011, ppl!!    
    
    
    I am all booked for my trip for @IDSToronto.    
    
    
    @TonicLiving you rock my socks! Ordered swatches yesterday and they're already in my mailbox! Thanks so much!    
    
    
    Hey @jen_thompson, these were WAY easier than the poinsettias and pinecones: http://yfrog.com/h0k7gij    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for the recommendation!  Very kind!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Just make sure that you saw my reply email - I think that I sent it at your new address    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/h2cf4sj
 http://yfrog.com/gyeccbj
 http://yfrog.com/gyc1tgj
X 10! Don't you wish you joined my cookie exchange?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Gorgeous! And LOVE the cushion fabric. Making "mantle" magic. Wrong to hang 4 stockings if we're only 2 b/c it looks better?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth thanks for the follow. I am following back and love ur blog too!    
    
    
    So, SO happy to be back. RT @kimvallee: @hwatterworth is back. Cool Tools: Olioboard Helps You Decorate Your Home http://ow.ly/8ny2p     
    
    
    For new pinners who've been asking how to find people... Pinterest: 13 Tips for Cutting Edge Users http://ow.ly/8obJG  via @mashable    
    
    
    Want! RT @kimvallee Breathe Easy: the sexy Middle Colors Humidifier http://ow.ly/8ofyP     
    
    
    All those registered for "Blogs & Media" please check your inbox for a very important e-mail on how to complete registration. - Lindsay    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Shoot us an e-mail at info@blogpodium.com with your Name & E-mail, so we can see why you didn't get the registration e-mail    
    
    
    Is it 'peaked' or 'piqued' my interest that is correct? #burningquestions    
    
    
    Working from old stomping grounds @uofg today. I've missed the smell of this library.    
    
    
    @hwatterworth all libraries really do have their own particular smell, don't they? #booklove    
    
    
    Congrats! Very well-deserved! RT @covetgarden: We are super happy to be featured today on Design Sponge http://fb.me/1rlMXXre9     
    
    
    @chrissychrzan Try Kama Design on Carden St.: http://www.kamadesign.com/kamadesign/home/    
    
    
    Seeing @sheandhim with @ablahut - our first concert as marrieds. Appropriate since we chose one of their songs for our first dance.    
    
    
    Breakfast for dinner = rainy day antidote. http://instagr.am/p/kEKhs/     
    
    
    @hwatterworth 'Pancake' really is the happiest word in the English language, isn't it?    
    
    
    @hwatterworth today I said "how do you like your coffee?" And I said, "crisp" and... crickets... Dammit!    
    
    
    A little eye candy for you this morning @deannemoser: http://reveriemag.com/     
    
    
    I can't decide if I want to play with my new flat iron or my new nail polish.    
    
    
    @BlogPodium is here!  looking forward to a morning with blogger friends old and new #blogpodium    
    
    
    @KatMooreMedia wants to see personality, passions and photos of the bloggers behind the blog to consider for promo. #blogpodium    
    
    
    Which blogs should you follow? @kimberleyseldon: curation is okay as long as you have an original voice and offer opinion. #blogpodium    
    
    
    Editing/appreciation has as much value as creation if the goal of the blog is to share beauty. @margotaustin #blogpodium    
    
    
    Photography is an important skill to develop of you want to achieve success with your blog. @ramblingreno #blogpodium    
    
    
    Re: online vs. print: "There are only two kinds of press: press and no press" @kimberleyseldon #blogpodium    
    
    
    SM influence is a major factor for media considering bloggers to feature - it's a symbiotic relationship. @KatMooreMedia #blogpodium    
    
    
    Don't overlook the words. It's about the story. @margotaustin #blogpodium    
    
    
    Quite literally jewellery for your home - a chandelier created from necklace chain. #ids12 http://ow.ly/i/qRCT     
    
    
    @hwatterworth #blogpodium THX for the post ... So pleased you joined us this morning!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth yes! It has been ages! Will be nice to say hi in person!    
    
    
    @justingodard It has a point. RT @mcsweeneysbooks: Comic Sans has something it would like to get off its chest. http://bit.ly/9YriiT    
    
    
    Corduroy capris: just say no.    
    
    
    Getting a sneak peek inside the March issue of @HouseandHome @cdn_designblgrs meetup.    
    
    
    So motivated by @casslavalle's talk @cdn_designblgrs meetup. Thanks for sharing your challenges + tips!    
    
    
    Original content + don't procrastinate on your post idea + collaborate = blogs in 2012. @casslavalle #cdb2012    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @houseandhome @cdn_designblgrs hi Heather    
    
    
    Ya know @cdn_designblgrs, @casslavalle + @cameronmacneil + new blog friends would've been enough! TY for the super fun night + prize! :)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Enjoyed catching up with you this weekend! Congrats on all the exciting news in your world & your win tonight!    
    
    
    @shanatweet @CdnFoodieGirl i'm pretty sure tweetdeck is available for iOS too. that's what i use for multiple twitter accounts on android!    
    
    
    @hwatterworth Great win Heather! It was nice seeing you again, next time we will chat longer!    
    
    
    @ramblingreno Yes! Ditto. :)    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @shanatweet do you use hootsuite free/paid? looks like a good solution for bringing together all social media accts in 1 app    
    
    
    For a second there, I thought I was living next to cousin Matthew. http://ow.ly/i/r5jx  #thingsmimicoisnt #downtonabbey    
    
    
    Testing/creating a possible new flavor of another "Only Two" cupcake recipe... first batch is in the oven!    
    
    
    Okay font geeks, a little help identifying this one please? (cc @justingodard @cherithbrooke @thary_c @dreizle) http://ow.ly/i/rgL0     
    
    
    Read it and drool, people. RT @_jasonhudson: BLOGGED: Night Cheese | http://jasonhudson.com     
    
    
    Deals on shoes make me VERY happy!!! Under $55 regular $260 WOOT!!!    
    
    
    Excited to officially announce that I will be teaching @ Conestoga College starting in April! Interior decorating & floral design classes.    
    
    
    @cdn_designblgrs @blogpodium Know anyone? RT @jen_thompson WANTED: #Edmonton-based interior designer... I've got something in mind.    
    
    
    I miss you, @hwatterworth.    
    
    
    