I received a miracle of forgiveness today. A weight I had carried in my heart for 18 years has been lifted.    
    
    
    @pacaunt It was very unexpected,  believe me!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @_sethyoung! http://instagram.com/p/hmblPqAkHJ/     
    
    
    The little one had one of the worst, most emotional days I've experienced with her. Wow. Never felt so heartborken & helpless.    
    
    
    She is so, so sensitive. Can't handle any meanness from other kids or disapproval from her teachers. She is just devastated.    
    
    
    Trying to work with her to help rebalance energetically, but sometimes I think I am too close to it.    
    
    
    @stacyreno She was just a mess today. Beyond anything I have ever seen. It's like having my heart cut open.    
    
    
    @stacyreno I was thinking of you and G. So much easier for me to work with other kids and not my own!    
    
    
    @stacyreno Oh no! Our little girls. :-(    
    
    
    @dagmarebaugh Thanks mama!    
    
    
    @nerdkween That's a great aura color to have!    
    
    
    @DesirreAndrews Wish my uterus was that happy! LOL    
    
    
    @gbkgwyneth @stacyreno Sounds like a good idea!    
    
    
    Give a handwritten note (Advent Day 7) http://wp.me/p1j208-k1     
    
    
    Photo: Give a handwritten note (Advent Day 7) When was the last time you received – or wrote – a... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10WSCK4     
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder Nope. Sometimes codeine is the only thing that will offer relief from a deep, hacking cough. Feel better!    
    
    
    The Carroll  Cloar exhibit at the  Georgia Museum of Art is stunning. http://instagram.com/p/hotZ4yAkBZ/     
    
    
    Can't wait! @TheImperialBar: Still a few more days #monthendsinberdayendsiny pic.twitter.com/SxjaMoaMk2    
    
    
    @woowoo76 I am glad to hear this.    
    
    
    @woowoo76 So important that he can rest comfortably.    
    
    
    @woowoo76 I am sure it has been tough. Is he aware of your presence?    
    
    
    Amazing Carroll Cloar paimting...otherwordly. http://instagram.com/p/ho_gX0gkBI/     
    
    
    Photo: Amazing Carroll Cloar paimting…otherwordly. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10ZoBNb     
    
    
    @stacyreno @suzzzanna Sure you are.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @suzzzanna I just realized my comment could apply to either one of you!!    
    
    
    Bartender wanted to know what name our tab was under. "Free", of course.    
    
    
    Birthday libations with @_sethyoung in Athens, GA. http://instagram.com/p/hpE65PAkK0/     
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Thanks, although it is actually @_SethYoung's bday!    
    
    
    The Branded Butcher in Athens GA is amazing. Farm to table & charcuterie creative goodness.    
    
    
    Pernod butter. Oh. Em. Gee.    
    
    
    White chocolate cheesecake with clementine marmalade and Hungarian dessert wine. http://instagram.com/p/hpMDyggkHi/     
    
    
    Trees lit in lights in Athens, GA. http://instagram.com/p/hpPl_3AkO3/     
    
    
    @abba_ks Their first?! This year marks my 22nd year!    
    
    
    So enjoying spending time with "my love one" @_SethYoung.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kellydouglas We are! Heading back in a little while...    
    
    
    I've forgotten what the sun looks like.    
    
    
    The little one has her 3rd & final hot cocoa fundraiser benefiting @DecPresbyterian's Threshold Ministry today!    
    
    
    She has raised over $200 so far to purchase hats, gloves & scarves for the homeless & poor!    
    
    
    We are going to make a trip to the store this week to purchase them & present the items at our volunteer holiday party.    
    
    
    @woowoo76 That's awesome!    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama There are other ways to encourage improved health in your congregation & beyond w/out selling books.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Caring for our health & wellbeing is a way of honoring God's creation.    
    
    
    My mother-in-law sent a box full of hats, gloves & scarves for little one's fundraiser! http://instagram.com/p/hrE8fGgkKS/     
    
    
    I MUST have one!!! @The7Line: Awesome. RT “@NYMetsFaithful: @The7Line Mini 7 train my gf got me!! pic.twitter.com/4g2C3xxylG”"    
    
    
    @CthatPath You're from the Bronx? #nycinthehouse    
    
    
    @CthatPath Yes - grew up in Flushing on the #7 line!    
    
    
    "I love God. She is special" drawing (with hot cocoa stains.) http://instagram.com/p/hratE_AkER/     
    
    
    Photo: "I love God. She is special" drawing (with hot cocoa stains.) http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10g0Kf4     
    
    
    @francesk My mom got me a #7 shirt from there a few years ago! Have to check out ornaments (and get homesick.)    
    
    
    Sitting thru rehearsal of our church's Xmas play that the little one decided (w/out asking me) she HAD to be in - as an angel.    
    
    
    Today has been a very long, dreary day.    
    
    
    Week 2 of Advent. Lighting the way for the coming of the Lord. http://instagram.com/p/hrgesSgkNG/     
    
    
    Photo: Week 2 of Advent. Lighting the way for the coming of the Lord. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10gEuOL     
    
    
    @francesk @DecaturSquared Oooh yes! I loved those old tokens!    
    
    
    Church play rehearsal is cutting into my dinner time. My kid did look cute in her angel costume & grumpy face, though.    
    
    
    The Christmas pageant that never, ever ends and the parents die of hunger in the pews. The end.    
    
    
    Meanwhile, the children dressed as wise men and shepherds are wrestling in the narthex. #truestory    
    
    
    One child dressed as a wise man says to the other, "Tell him to shut up" about the third, as the angel of the Lord looks on.    
    
    
    The random moments happpening around the Christmas pageant rehearsal are funnier than the play itself.    
    
    
    @CthatPath I'm gnawing on a Sharpie as we speak.    
    
    
    My grumpy angel just ran off the stage to beg me for something to eat."Do you not understand how hungry I am?" she says.    
    
    
    Dinner. Finally!    
    
    
    @stacyreno she got a box of raisins.    
    
    
    @stacyreno I think @_sethyoung would agree, but she likes dried grapes!    
    
    
    Give hugs (Advent Day 8) http://wp.me/p1j208-kc     
    
    
    Photo: Give hugs (Advent Day 8) Words may fail, but a true hugnever does. We are a culture disconnected... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10hQMgj     
    
    
    In case you missed yesterday's #Advent Day 8 post for #24daysofgiving: Give hugs (lots of them!) http://alifeitself.com/2013/12/08/give-hugs-advent-day-8/ …    
    
    
    +2 RT @stacyreno: +1 RT @aReyoUiN: I'm over the rain.    
    
    
    @Pandorasboxheal Thank you for sharing! :-)    
    
    
    Scary! RT @wsbtv: MUST SEE: Ice sheets fall from Texas apartment building. http://twitpic.com/do3yuk  #wsbtv    
    
    
    The lights keep flickering. That's no bueno.    
    
    
    Give blessings (Advent Day 9) http://wp.me/p1j208-ki     
    
    
    Photo: Give blessings (Advent Day 9) Yesterday, we lit the Advent candle of peace. It was a moment to... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10jiehI     
    
    
    @stacyreno WTH?!!!!    
    
    
    @stacyreno Well, this could be the beginning of a better opportunity for you. #beentherebefore    
    
    
    @stacyreno I know. Right there with you. (((hugs))) and lots of fingers crossed!    
    
    
    @stacyreno I'm going to have to look for more permanent work b/c everything I've tried just isn't enough to keep us afloat.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Thanks mama. We will get it together!    
    
    
    @benjamincorey Beautiful post. Thank you for sharing your heart. Wishing you & your wife peace & comfort this Christmas.    
    
    
    Finally - a good use for Viagra! RT @mnt_healthnews: Menstrual cramps relieved by erectile dysfunction drug http://mnt.to/4jrf     
    
    
    @benjamincorey Thanksgiving is always bittersweet for me (lost my grandfather then) so I completely understand.    
    
    
    Day 9 of#Advent. #redbird http://instagram.com/p/htTpNTAkNH/     
    
    
    Photo: Day 9 of#Advent. #redbird http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10k9PTT     
    
    
    Day 9 of #Advent. #redbird http://instagram.com/p/htTzILgkNZ/     
    
    
    Photo: Day 9 of #Advent. #redbird http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10k9eqT     
    
    
    At least it's warm, sunny & tropical in the terrarium. http://instagram.com/p/htUdCngkOM/     
    
    
    Photo: At least it’s warm, sunny & tropical in the terrarium. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10kBHYv     
    
    
    Forget No Child Left Behind. How about No Child Left Hungry or No Child Left Homeless?    
    
    
    Kept wondering what felt different about today. And realized it would have been my grandmother's 91st birthday.    
    
    
    Photo of me and my Grandma, taken on her 88th & last birthday with us in 2010. pic.twitter.com/D7JQ8xmTYV    
    
    
    @francesk Thank you! That was the last pic taken of us. She had a good day, even though she was to the point where she needed a lot of help.    
    
    
    I may end up without health insurance if I can't get this "health assessment" scheduled THIS week.    
    
    
    You'd think getting health insurance from a hospital employer would be better/easier/quicker, but it isn't.    
    
    
    All this talk of Advent, reflection & turning toward God. And what do church people do? Schedule more events & luncheons.    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia I can't opt out of some of it, but trying to do what I can to limit events.    
    
    
    Hoping the little one's choir rehearsal goes better than last night. [Hiding in church library, trying to get blog posts done.]    
    
    
    @stacyreno I could barely make myself leave the house to do ANYTHING, much less run. Today is a #rainday, not #runday.    
    
    
    @stacyreno I hear ya. Haven't exercised in well, a really, really long time. Today ain't the day for me to start!    
    
    
    Today's #Advent post for #24daysofgiving: Give blessings http://bit.ly/1aPM3Xu     
    
    
    Ewwww gross! RT @usnews: Invasion of the 'super roach': asian cockroaches take New York City http://ow.ly/rB1ZV     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Back atcha!    
    
    
    @arbharrisonjr Yes, it certainly can be.    
    
    
    Got a little choked up hearing the little one practice "Silent Night" with the angel choir.    
    
    
    @abba_ks Oh no!    
    
    
    @abba_ks I'm at Green Ginger if you need me to bring you some soup. Just let me know.    
    
    
    My child brings Christmas ornaments with her to dinner.    
    
    
    @PearCat Pssst....your email is showing...    
    
    
    @PearCat Scary stuff.    
    
    
    @PearCat I just wasn't sure if it was yours and didn't want you getting hacked etc.    
    
    
    @abba_ks Mmmm....barium. Er, not. Some Reiki later will help soothe the nasties away.    
    
    
    School's education foundation sends year-end donation card to my house addressed to hubby & ex (who never lived here.) Not getting my $$.    
    
    
    We get along fine. It's just the principle of the thing. That's not MY name!    
    
    
    @Eddi_RonRon Yeah -not what I had expected after all these years!    
    
    
    Need to find time to finish preparing to lead Thursday's PW Bible Study on trusting in God during times of adversity.    
    
    
    Somehow I always end up with the challenging topics - the ones I find myself arguing out loud to myself about!    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Say hi to my hometown for me! #queensgirlforever    
    
    
    Will this rain ever end?    
    
    
    Seriously,  I wrote over 3 pages of notes so far on Scripture passages. Guess that's a clue that seminary is in my near future.    
    
    
    It's just good manners to shake hands with others at social & political functions. Your parents did teach you that, right?    
    
    
    This week, a person w/whom I had a falling out nearly 20 yrs ago (my fault) shook my hand. That was personal & meant a lot.    
    
    
    Me too RT @francesk: @danayoung Leap of Faith parables are what get me through the days most of the time...    
    
    
    Huh? RT @ATLGreg1: Rand Paul says extending UI benefits would be a “disservice” to those Americans (including many veterans) receiving them.    
    
    
    The politicians trying to cut unemployment benefits have never experienced the shame of having to go & apply for them.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 That's bull & we all know it. Jobs are not that easy to come by, even for skilled workers.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 I've been on unemployment twice. The whole process is very demoralizing & a lot of time is spent waiting.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed @ATLGreg1 Oh, right. Duh. Why didn't I think of that? Because I'm lazy. That must be it. ;-)    
    
    
    @JeffHaws @ATLGreg1 $11K & SNAP: livin' the good life. Tell that to the people I see when I volunteer at our church's homeless ministry.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 @JeffHaws Maybe a broken-down used old Caddy.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 It almost makes receiving the benefits not worth the hassle.    
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder @JeffHaws @ATLGreg1 Nope, it sure doesn't. We didn't have health care for a year when hubby was unemployed.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 @JeffHaws Awww man. If only I could have had a few more kids...    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 I never want to go on UI again.    
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder @JeffHaws @ATLGreg1 Not sure it was an option for us either. It was a tough year.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 And sitting through classes I didn't need. No attempt to help people at the level they required.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 I could have taught the resume writing class.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed @CBL1978 @OBoudreaux @ATLGreg1 What about that Jesus guy?    
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder @JeffHaws @ATLGreg1 My goodness, I had no idea. That is definitely not an option for you.    
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder I hope things improve soon for you. Wish there was something I could do.    
    
    
    @LaurelSnyder I understand. I used to have more complex health issues & seeing your own docs is necessary when needed.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Why does that not surprise me?    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 @CBL1978 @rjmedwed @OBoudreaux I think you must be talking about the money changers at the temple. Oops. Wrong poor people.    
    
    
    @abba_ks I have to go for a health assessment on Thurs & have to fast for 8 hrs before. And drive out to who knows where OTP. #grumpy    
    
    
    Oh, right RT @ATLGreg1: @danayoung @CBL1978 @rjmedwed @OBoudreaux “Blessed are the businessmen, for they will inherit huge holiday bonuses."    
    
    
    @abba_ks It was either that or not have health insurance. And I'm a year behind on my mammogram (you can yell at me later.)    
    
    
    The rain is moving out after 6 days so that frigid temps can move in. Why do I not live in the tropics?    
    
    
    @abba_ks They changed the requirements & spouses have to do this yearly health assessment thing. I rarely go to docs....    
    
    
    @abba_ks And I loved my doc just fine BUT she isn't on their plan. Nor are any of the other ones I've used. Sigh.    
    
    
    @stacyreno *groan*    
    
    
    @abba_ks No worries - I had a feeling that might happen. Got time tomorrow or Fri?    
    
    
    @abba_ks 1 pm?    
    
    
    @abba_ks You got it! :-)    
    
    
    Behold! The light has returned!    
    
    
    @standupkid I have been to funerals where friends took pictures posed next to the open casket.    
    
    
    Samuel L. Jackon is filming in the #decaturga area? Think he might want to come by & read my kid a bedtime story?    
    
    
    Wish I'd gotten # of MARTA bus that came within inches of hitting my bumper. Had no intention of slowing down, even though I had blinker on.    
    
    
    I happen to know of another place in #decaturga where another movie will be filming on Thurs.    
    
    
    Actually, I stand corrected. It's a TV series.    
    
    
    @_SethYoung You know where.    
    
    
    @abba_ks #happydance Such awesome news!    
    
    
    Or the DMV RT @pnuts_mama: I'm convinced sitting in banks is preparation for purgatory.    
    
    
    A package from Japan. :-) http://instagram.com/p/hwJPOLgkPG/     
    
    
    @pnuts_mama But I'm a feminist so I need to tell you how to be one! #notfeministenough    
    
    
    ForGIVEness for yourself and others (Advent Day 10) http://wp.me/p1j208-ko     
    
    
    Photo: ForGIVEness for yourself and others (Advent Day 10) A lot has been said about the power of... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10sH-2O     
    
    
    Why must the dog always barf on the rug, when we have plenty of hardwood floor?    
    
    
    @stacyreno I don't even want to think about this Xmas. Gonna be lean unless I get more business soon.    
    
    
    @auntie_jenn Oh man, getting barf outta there is next to impossible.    
    
    
    @auntie_jenn Mine is a wool rug. :-/    
    
    
    On Why I Will Allow (and Encourage) My Kid(s) to Believe in Santa Claus http://wp.me/p1gq9q-bb  via @pastortimbrown    
    
    
    @stacyreno @mamaerika Been there, had that argument.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @mamaerika Santa doesn't always give everything on the list.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @mamaerika In our house, we had "Santa" gifts & some from Mom or Dad. Santa's were usually the few big items on the list.    
    
    
    @hippiejennie Happy (real) labor vibes!    
    
    
    @DecaStan They are just going to reingest it anyway. Easier to do on hardwoods, no?    
    
    
    The teen boy just talked about taking the test for his learner's permit. #lordhavemercy cc: @_SethYoung    
    
    
    @_L1vY_ @stacyreno Amen to that.    
    
    
    It's cold out there. But it's not raining!    
    
    
    @nerdkween Hey, I heard you will be subbing for A's class this week! She will be so excited!    
    
    
    Tempted to just go run and hide until the holidays are over.    
    
    
    SO not happy about this RT @DMetro: School Board Delays Vote on K-3 Rezoning, But Leans Towards Map 7A http://wp.me/p23Vhv-7wU     
    
    
    Worth considering RT @ATLINtownPaper: Ted Turner wants namesake ballpark as green space http://ow.ly/rFgIy  (via @Salon)    
    
    
    @francesk A memorial service should be a celebration of life, right? The pic isn't a big deal; wasn't disrespectful.    
    
    
    @francesk I've been to funerals where friends posed next to open casket of the deceased - this was years ago, before selfies.    
    
    
    A fake sign language interpreter is more offensive at a televised memorial than group pics anyone snapped during the service.    
    
    
    @francesk During my grandmother's viewing, we took group family photos, because it was the only time we were all in the same room.    
    
    
    @francesk Mandela lived a very long, inspired life. It *should* be the cause for much celebration & joy (mixed with sadness, of course.)    
    
    
    Stomach not feeling well this morning. Wish I could crawl back to bed.    
    
    
    @francesk Absolutely. Funerals & memorial services don't need to be grim, somber affairs. Especially not for a life well-lived.    
    
    
    My mom is partially deaf & struggles to hear in crowded places. A fake interpreter at events does everyone a deep disservice.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Thanks - just one of those days (and my many digestive woes.)    
    
    
    I remember my mom working to regain her balance & learning to lip-read after losing her hearing during surgery. It was a hard recovery.    
    
    
    People with hearing impairments live with an invisible disability & are misunderstood by others who don't realize they can't hear.    
    
    
    Many people thought my mom was ignoring them or being a snob, but she couldn't hear them or see that they were addressing her.    
    
    
    Even I forget sometimes to make sure I'm facing her directly when speaking to her & she's been hearing impaired since I was 9.    
    
    
    Living with an invisible disability can be a very alienating. If people can't see why you're struggling, they don't believe it.    
    
    
    There are many types of invisible disabilities - anxiety, depression, addiction, chronic pain - can all fall in this category.    
    
    
    The little one is going to be in her 1st Xmas play tonight, singing in the "Angel Choir." Note to self: don't wear mascara.    
    
    
    @dagmarebaugh @HLNJackie For real?! If so, my kid would have been sent home long ago (as would have I, back in the day.) #chatty    
    
    
    @dagmarebaugh Thanks! Rehearsals were looking rough but the kids singing were sooo sweet.    
    
    
    @HLNJackie @dagmarebaugh Hey, I completely understand. I'm a writer, poet & in social media/communications for my church.    
    
    
    @HLNJackie @dagmarebaugh My parents nicknamed me "Mickey Mouth" as a kid because I talked so much!    
    
    
    Way late to #chsosm chat...our church has an Advent blog w/daily devotionals written by members: http://bit.ly/1gpd6AZ     
    
    
    Looking for flexible freelance/contract work - skills in content mgmt, taxonomy, blogging, social media. http://www.linkedin.com/in/danalisayoung …    
    
    
    When I opened the package, it intoned, "Riiiicola." Seriously. http://instagram.com/p/hyp1bBAkHh/     
    
    
    Thank you to @crispix67 for bringing a donation of adorable kids' hats for the little one's fundraiser!    
    
    
    I've saved every email ever #FiveWordTechHorrors    
    
    
    Post it on the Facebook #FiveWordTechHorrors    
    
    
    Sigh. Advent devotionals don't need to be mini-history lessons. Save it for Bible study.    
    
    
    Buy domain name for $1,000,000! #FiveWordTechHorrors    
    
    
    If your caller ID says "Unavailable", then guess what? I'm unavailable to answer.    
    
    
    I want a Flash homepage. #FiveWordTechHorrors    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Oh I'm glad you enjoyed it! It was the only way to get through that painful rehearsal. :-)    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl I didn't think we were going to be there that long! And this kid either eats nothing or is ravenous.    
    
    
    Tempted to live-tweet the church Christmas play, if I don't get the side-eye from @_sethyoung.    
    
    
    An oldie but goodie for those in web/graphic design #makethelogobigger http://youtu.be/5AxwaszFbDw     
    
    
    Like a choir of angels singing RT @francesk: Some of my favorite words in the English Language: "Our meeting has been cancelled."    
    
    
    @HLNJackie @dagmarebaugh Total awesomeness. :-)    
    
    
    Yes they are! RT @BeMonsterful: .@danayoung The other most beautiful words in the English language: Breakfast served all day.    
    
    
    <3 RT @MichaelPeppard: Lost track of our daughter at the Cloisters museum. Found her here. I have no words. pic.twitter.com/UkjnC4MJQE    
    
    
    No church Christmas play for us. The choir angel has decided she doesn't want to perform. As I'd suspected.    
    
    
    @CthatPath She has very high anxiety around public performances. This is nothing new. They recruited her to be in play w/out asking me.    
    
    
    And the teen boy just showed up with 3 of his friends. Ever hear of texting ahead to let me know? #sigh    
    
    
    Seriously, this day can go suck it.    
    
    
    And you know I have to be in a really lousy mood to say that.    
    
    
    Stupid RT @ReutersBiz: This baby seat comes with an iPad holder and apps to entertain infants http://reut.rs/1cBjO3k  pic.twitter.com/MeUmZpz9tT    
    
    
    @stacyreno Not really. :-/ And my house is full of rambunctious teenagers. #helpme    
    
    
    Ha! YES! RT @PearCat: @danayoung guaranteed smile right here pic.twitter.com/aWDHT7JgHD    
    
    
    @PearCat Slip a Benadryl in his food. He won't notice the difference.    
    
    
    @stacyreno You and I need a do-over of today. And a drink.    
    
    
    @PearCat You could have so much fun with that!    
    
    
    Give yourself permission to say no (Advent Day 11) http://wp.me/p1j208-kC     
    
    
    Photo: Give yourself permission to say no (Advent Day 11) Advent is supposed to be a time for waiting and... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10y8D0K     
    
    
    @PearCat Excellent. :-)    
    
    
    @francesk What's so weird is that she has sung with the children's choir twice now & no problem. Today - forget it.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Hey now. Stop trying to have a worse day than me. ;-)    
    
    
    @stacyreno That's about the only thing I lack - at the moment.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl If I had just told her it was another rehearsal, we'd be there right now.    
    
    
    Targeting me w/email containing the subject line "Men & women over 40, active seniors" isn't going to get me to buy your stuff.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl I generally try not to lie to my children. LOL    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl I can sometimes get her to change her mind, but she's had a very tough past week & hasn't been cooperative.    
    
    
    Phone conversations with your teen #talkward cc: @_SethYoung    
    
    
    @woowoo76 I am so sorry your dad ( and all of you) are suffering through this.    
    
    
    Hiccups, begone!    
    
    
    Lucy the starfish. http://instagram.com/p/hzjG3rAkLN/     
    
    
    Photo: Lucy the starfish. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu10zSMEs     
    
    
    @_L1vY_ I know how to use reflexology to stop hiccups - just hate them.    
    
    
    "Since you're all about non-attachment, let's start with your wallet." The Elf goes rogue... http://instagram.com/p/hzj_JvAkM7/     
    
    
    @_L1vY_ I can do it on myself. When I finally did, the hiccups stopped. #healerhealthyself    
    
    
    @_L1vY_ Scaring people from behind? :-)    
    
    
    @rachelfeit Yes, it did. I press deeply & rotate in a circular motion with thumb on the center of the palm of hand.Reflexes the diaphragm.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Ugh. So sorry to hear all that.    
    
    
        
    
    
    My LDL and triglycerides were not even measurable. You get excited about this stuff in your 40s!    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Me and you both!    
    
    
    Rocked blood pressure/glucose ranges too. BMI was fine but need to head back to @PinnacleAtlanta. I have standards, you know.    
    
    
    And now I want to eat some greasy eggs, bacon and hashbrowns. ;-)    
    
    
    Seriously, I had borderline high cholesterol because my HDL and TC/HDL ranges were so good.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama You're not in Queens anymore, Toto!    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama I was there last month - that's where my parents live! #notkansaseither    
    
    
    @dondrennon Next best thing - egg scramble with bacon and gouda...yum    
    
    
    @francesk Nope. Had mine out in '97 after it got infected.    
    
    
    @Blacktating Don't let your domain go! Start a gofundme campaign to cover domain and hosting costs. Then try to monetize blog.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Your kitchen still looks better than mine.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed The snow looks beautiful there!    
    
    
    @francesk At the church, to be specific. #intheknow    
    
    
    @francesk I have to be at church this afternoon for an event - hoping to get some pics...    
    
    
    @hippiejennie Sounds like you did AMAZING!! Way to go mama!!!    
    
    
    @Blacktating Oh, I see. Totally understand - blogging is a big commmitment.    
    
    
    @francesk I guess you would, since that should create some havoc!    
    
    
    @francesk Getting over there today is gonna be crazeeee...    
    
    
    @francesk I don't know how late they are filming in the area but I thought they said it wasn't going to be all day. Could be wrong.    
    
    
    @francesk Oh ok - good to know.    
    
    
    @PinnacleAtlanta We've been talking about coming back. I need to do some pre-exercise before I do, or it will knock me over! LOL    
    
    
    Making chocolate coconut balls & dancing around my kitchen to @Johnny_Marr's "The Messenger." #lifeisgood    
    
    
    Google Places is missing a lot of necessary categories for businesses. The taxonomist in me is frustrated.    
    
    
    How Millennial Are You? I scored 81 http://pewrsr.ch/T4mr4v  #GenXinageonly    
    
    
    I'm 43 but it still tickles me when my mom gets so proud of my achievements. Especially when she says, "You go girl!"    
    
    
    @rjmedwed There's always been debate about when the millenial age starts. Either way, I'm too old to be an age-specific millenial.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I guess that's what morphed into millenials. Doesn't that capture the Gen Y ages?    
    
    
    @rjmedwed And if you get into the New Age categories, you have Indigo, Crystal and Rainbow children too. :-)    
    
    
    @rjmedwed You could be right about that. I dunno. I'm just a GenXer masquerading as a Millenial. LOL    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I don't watch TV. I think that might have skewed the stats.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I can't handle the noise and electromagnetic energy. :-)    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Although actually my KIDS have the TV on. I do my best to ignore it.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I love silence. Period. End stop.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed And besides, I have kids. This house is never quiet unless they are asleep.    
    
    
    The TV series "The Originals" filming at Decatur Presbyterian Church today. http://instagram.com/p/h1hpvGAkH5/     
    
    
    Photo: The TV series “The Originals” filming at Decatur Presbyterian Church today. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu111LmLd     
    
    
    Getting our Christmas tree! Finally!    
    
    
    Got lots of extra greenery in the hopes of making a giant wreath to go outside the house this year.    
    
    
    I am getting to the point in December where I lose all self-restraint regarding Christmas.    
    
    
    Holy family. #christmas http://instagram.com/p/h2AS72gkGf/     
    
    
    @dondrennon Nice try.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Ummm.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Hang up on him next time.    
    
    
    @_SethYoung @PinnacleAtlanta He ain't heavy. He's my honey(buns).    
    
    
    @stacyreno Tell him you will not tolerate verbal abuse in any form & that you won't respond.    
    
    
    Give yourself space to let the light in (Advent Day 12) http://wp.me/p1j208-kJ     
    
    
    Photo: Give yourself space to let the light in (Advent Day 12) The holidays can be a very hectic time –... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu113Eyj3     
    
    
    @Carl Thank you so much! :-)    
    
    
    @stacyreno Good for you! I know that isn't easy to do, but stick to your guns. Don't be mean back; just firm in your convictions.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Exactly. Proud of you!    
    
    
    Long night of catching up on social media work & then a long (but fun) day of teaching a full Reiki class!    
    
    
    @colombiancoffee Save some for me!    
    
    
    It's right in your Twitter handle! :-) RT @colombiancoffee: @danayoung you know I have the good coffee in my house too :)    
    
    
    Glad to see more people putting up Christmas lights in my neighborhood - brightens up the night!    
    
    
    My first time stamping class certificates with the hanko (seal) given to me by my Reiki teacher. http://instagram.com/p/h4tcbPgkDK/     
    
    
    @stacyreno OMG! That's awful! Hope they are OK too.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Ugh. And more ugh.    
    
    
    @stacyreno They should have been in Oakhurst 15 years ago. THEN it was the 'hood. Not now.    
    
    
    @stacyreno It's become very privileged and snooty, which is a real shame because there is a lot of good diversity.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Yes, you do. Nothing good comes of those listservs.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @_SethYoung It's a bit isolated back in that parking lot as compared to the other retail in the area.    
    
    
    Give a nice greeting (Advent Day 13) http://wp.me/p1j208-kV     
    
    
    Photo: Give a nice greeting (Advent Day 13) During the holidays, I notice that strangers are more likely to... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu118pLpq     
    
    
    @stacyreno @_SethYoung Crowded this time of night?    
    
    
    @dhammagirl Thanks!    
    
    
    @stacyreno @_SethYoung Yikes. Well, I hope they are all OK over there.    
    
    
    I don't ever need to hear another meteorologist talk about how Atlanta could use more rain.    
    
    
    How to embarrass your teenager during Xmas tree decorating: "Daddy likes to play hide the pickle ornament."    
    
    
    Return to India... http://instagram.com/p/h7SZ6LgkLo/     
    
    
    Buddha meditates on my Christmas tree. http://instagram.com/p/h7SkBGgkL3/     
    
    
    My beloved ornament. @_sethyoung http://instagram.com/p/h7SvB3gkML/     
    
    
    One day my frog prince will come... http://instagram.com/p/h7UMAKgkOO/     
    
    
    A red-nosed friend. http://instagram.com/p/h7U4TwgkPa/     
    
    
    I want to do a mashup of Tony Bennett's "Christmasland" and Metallica's "Enter Sandman." #takemyhand    
    
    
    Parents should not be allowed to hold birthday parties for their kids on a Sunday. I need at least ONE day off.    
    
    
    The saddest cat in the entire world. http://instagram.com/p/h8j-FuAkAU/     
    
    
    My favorite duo-color Christmas lights. http://instagram.com/p/h8vgqzAkCp/     
    
    
    One of my cherished ornaments, a dove handmade by my mom. #christmas http://instagram.com/p/h8_NV0gkNy/     
    
    
    Photo: One of my cherished ornaments, a dove handmade by my mom. #christmas http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11IXFJg     
    
    
    How am I spending my Sunday? Working, while my kid attends a birthday party.    
    
    
    I taught class yesterday too, which means I have not had anything resembling a weekend off yet.    
    
    
    Brrrrrrrrr.    
    
    
    @bastardworks MOAR BEARD! #thatshowwediditinlemuria #becausebeards    
    
    
    @stacyreno He's so cute! Love possums (although preferably not in my trash!)    
    
    
    Give yourself a day off (Advent Day 14) http://wp.me/p1j208-l1     
    
    
    Photo: Give yourself a day off (Advent Day 14) The next ten days before Christmas are usually a whirlwind... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11JuUB3     
    
    
    @stacyreno Um, where's your trash can?    
    
    
    @stacyreno How is he getting into the trash can?    
    
    
    @stacyreno You may need to call animal control. They shouldn't kill him - just rezone him elsewhere.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Sounds like he's hungover after having himself a trash party!    
    
    
    Give words of encouragement (Advent Day 15) http://wp.me/p1j208-l5     
    
    
    Photo: Give words of encouragement (Advent Day 15) Do you know someone who is going through a tough time... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11K5pyg     
    
    
    The teen boy just asked me to buy him razors so he can shave his face. #feelingold    
    
    
    Our awesome Christmas bush, thanks to @_sethyoung! http://instagram.com/p/h9fnplAkFp/     
    
    
    Moon and Xmas lights strung across the darkness. http://instagram.com/p/h9iLdSAkJi/     
    
    
    George Rodrigue, painter of the iconic Blue Dog, has died. http://s.nola.com/6F6U6OR  #nola    
    
    
    Divine RT @Golden_Isles: Describe the Golden Isles in one word…    
    
    
    My amazing guy @_SethYoung keeps me sane and loved. #sograteful    
    
    
    All these folks who don't normally do drop off are creating more craziness at school. I need to leave earlier.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl It's elementary school, so I bet it's because the PARENTS don't want to walk in the cold. Too young to let kids walk alone.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Although when I was growing up in NYC, we had no choice but to walk in whatever weather was out there.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Thanks! We need to get over there again for dinner now that y'all are officially open!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to the lovely @mamaerika! Hope you have an AMAZING day! xo    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Although that experience is definitely overrated. Came home once with icicles hanging off my bangs.    
    
    
    @stacyreno You got it mama!    
    
    
    @auntie_jenn But easy to cheat! ;-) LOL    
    
    
    We’re the face of food stamps http://www.salon.com/2012/10/16/were_the_face_of_food_stamps/ … via @Salon    
    
    
    The war on Christmas - then & now - is being waged by Christian fundamentalists http://shar.es/OGKXG  via @benjamincorey    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 I was going to throw a Solstice party (good Buddheo-Christian that I am) but didn't have time for it.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Awww, thank you for the invite! :-)    
    
    
    These dueling leaf blowers are about to drive me crazy.    
    
    
    My mom sent the most awesome boots/stuffed toy set for our Amazing Peace Girl! #christmas http://instagram.com/p/h_bGN_gkE1/     
    
    
    One of 4 different Christmas angels my mom made for me years ago. http://instagram.com/p/h_e9DdAkKA/     
    
    
    Another sweet Christmas angel on my tree, made by my mom. http://instagram.com/p/h_fHyfAkKT/     
    
    
    One more Christmas angel, made by my mom. http://instagram.com/p/h_fWTRgkKm/     
    
    
    My mom is no longer able to sew, and I am really grateful to have these special ornaments on my tree.    
    
    
    The best things in life are handmade with love.    
    
    
    My #24daysofgiving #Advent post: Give words of encouragement http://bit.ly/19NP0bj     
    
    
    @francesk My mom used to make my clothes when I was little. I still have doll she made for me when I was 5 - & clothes too!    
    
    
    @francesk Well, the DOLL clothes I still have - not the clothes she made for me. Wish I did, though!    
    
    
    @francesk My grandmother made my sweaters for me. I miss her - and those sweaters!    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Yup - my mom did that too! She collects special edition Barbies.    
    
    
    @stacyreno I try to remind myself of the things I wanted at that age. And we live in an area of such affluence too.    
    
    
    Me too. RT @d3bbie: I need a clone.  Or an indentured servant.  Just until Christmas is over.    
    
    
    One of my favorite parts of Scripture is the Annunciation & how the event has been depicted in sacred art over the centuries.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Well, yeah, it happens. We all want to fit in and be accepted. It sucks that it has to be about "things", though.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Can't see the moon yet from our house. #downintheditch    
    
    
    Evening sky and Christmas lights in the dogwood tree. http://instagram.com/p/h__6evAkG_/     
    
    
    Photo: Evening sky and Christmas lights in the dogwood tree. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11Q2urD     
    
    
    Full moon in the middle of Christmas lights. http://instagram.com/p/iABbMAgkIy/     
    
    
        
    
    
    What a fantabulous moon!    
    
    
    At @TheImperial with @_sethyoung. Yum awaits us.    
    
    
    @JeffHaws Uh oops. My Twitter doesn't always autofill.    
    
    
    @abba_ks Sounds like when I was pregnant and recovering from jet lag to/from India.    
    
    
    Give in to wonderment (Advent Day 16) http://wp.me/p1j208-lc     
    
    
    Photo: Give in to wonderment (Advent Day 16) One of the best things about Advent and the holiday season is... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11R6014     
    
    
    Teaching the little one about shielding herself in a protective bubble of white light against mean things other kids say.    
    
    
    Wish I could attend a holiday event where I wasn't asked to bring or make something. I am spending so much money lately.    
    
    
    @stacyreno I'm to the point of saying, "No, I can't do it" because the asks get to be so frequent.    
    
    
    Thank you to @mustangmelatl & @abba_ks for donating personal care items for @DecPresbyterian's Threshold Ministry!    
    
    
    My husband @_sethyoung shot & edited this video for WellStar Foundation's Early Lung Cancer Detection Fund: http://youtu.be/CMSAb8Pxl1M     
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Not very Christian of them to steal this woman's business, even though I can sort of support their message of misogyny.    
    
    
    I wish I could get ANY cards sent! RT @pnuts_mama: all of you who send out Christmas cards with great family pictures? I am in awe of you.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @Pontifex! Thank you for living & sharing the TRUE message of love & compassion that Jesus embodies.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 People like her are not the right targets for such a protest. She's just trying to make a living.    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Amen! Preach it, brother! :-)    
    
    
    Check it out! I'm official! @dragonflyreiki Awarded Best of 2013 on Kudzu! http://www.pr.com/press-release/533171 …    
    
    
    Wut?! RT @pnuts_mama: good lord RT @NicoleBoyHouse: Cause you gotta have Phaith. RT @Swistle 10 new U.S. baby girls named Phaith in 2012.    
    
    
    Not for anything, but "Phaith" sounds like a chemical or something cooked up in a hot plate in a trailer.    
    
    
    @MoniseLSeward Yuck! Stay HOME and get well, people!    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Thank you! :-)    
    
    
    Good tips for staying in shape during the holidays! http://www.clickaclass.com/blog/2012/05/15/its-your-vacation-dont-just-sit-there/ … via @ClickAClass    
    
    
    Pope Francis backs public breastfeeding! LOVE this! http://davidgibson.religionnews.com/2013/12/17/pope-francis-backs-public-breastfeeding-makes-traditional/ … via @RNS    
    
    
    I have the best husband ever. Love you @_sethyoung! http://instagram.com/p/iCSh3bAkPd/     
    
    
    So 2000-late! RT @Carl: OH at @BestBuy: "Are you currently with AT&T?"

......
"No, I'm with Cingular."    
    
    
    @stacyreno I'm wearing bird earrings today!    
    
    
    @Carl @timcairl @DecaStan @emkateland Ma Bell's got the ill communication. ;-)    
    
    
    As I sit here working, @_SethYoung is brewing up coffee & washing dishes. He brought me home gorgeous flowers. I'm keeping him.    
    
    
    Repent now. Geographers map America's 7 deadly sins http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/sideshow/geographers-map-seven-deadly-sins-170946186.html …    
    
    
    The little one wants her loose tooth to fall out on Xmas Eve. Tooth Fairy & Santa "can know each other. They can get along."    
    
    
    Santa visit was super successful. NO line & he chatted with the little one for 5 min. He loved the gift she made for him too.    
    
    
    "I think the moon came from outer space."    
    
    
    @mamaerika Ugh.    
    
    
    Yes! RT @RandomOenophile: Having a weird hair day. Perhaps I'll just call it modern & sassy. #curlyhairproblems    
    
    
    Ummm RT @NowWithAlex: huh, so it is. RT @ethanklapper: Here's Mitt Romney ironing clothes that he's already wearing http://twitpic.com/dp4fh6     
    
    
    @JeffHaws @ethanklapper It BUUUUURRRRRNNNNNSSS!!    
    
    
    Comments about the "quality of people" on MARTA are precisely why our public transit fails to be used like it should.    
    
    
    In other cities like NYC, DC or Chicago, using public transit is not a stigma. Which is why ATL is never going to be world-class.    
    
    
    @stacyreno For real?! When did that happen?    
    
    
    @stacyreno I remember seeing a Dekalb police car down toward Ponce on our street last night. Bet that's where it happened.    
    
    
    @mamaerika Good for you! I don't know why it's so hard for employers to treat employees with respect & consideration. I know you work hard.    
    
    
    My heart just breaks for a friend whose son is mentally ill, drug-addicted & homeless. Please pray for her & her son!    
    
    
    Pema Chödrön on learning to be big & small at the same time https://bron.to/ts0i1b1xi2nzpa8s …    
    
    
    Running behind on my blog posts.    
    
    
    And my computer just crashed on me, which means I lost all of my work. Ugh.    
    
    
    @mamaerika @francesk Ultimately, you will benefit because you ARE doing the right, kind & fair thing for your direct reports.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Southpaws FTW!    
    
    
    Give your light to others (Advent Day 17) http://wp.me/p1j208-lh     
    
    
    Photo: Give your light to others (Advent Day 17) So many times in life, we walk in darkness. Advent is the... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11bgFmL     
    
    
    @stacyreno That is so scary! R used to sleepwalk when he was her age but never left the house. Tends to happen during stressful times.    
    
    
    @ndcollier Ouchie. :-(    
    
    
    @ndcollier Has Reiki helped some with the discomfort?    
    
    
    @ndcollier I assume you're trying to avoid the surgical route? I've worked with so many women who deal w/fibroids.    
    
    
    Did anyone really expect enlightened social commentary coming from the Duck Dynasty guys?    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Don't you know? Freedom isn't free, but free speech is!    
    
    
    @ndcollier That could be very helpful! Keeping my fingers crossed for you!    
    
    
    As usual, @JesusOfNaz316 says it way better than I ever could.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed When they're back to making duck calls in obscurity, they may rethink that whole "free speech" thing.    
    
    
    Having trouble keeping up with my #Advent blog posts. My point for writing them was to be an antidote to the ugliness I've been seeing.    
    
    
    In case you missed it...Give your light to others (Advent Day 17) | A life itself http://bit.ly/1fpiD6X     
    
    
    @stacyreno I know. :-( My friend's brother did the same thing as a kid. And this was in Queens, in a busy neighborhood.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Like I said, it is a reaction to stress. Some Reiki maybe?    
    
    
    @stacyreno I used to encounter R walking in circles in the living room. I'd have to lead him back to bed, which he mumbled at me.    
    
    
    @_L1vY_ Ewwwww....    
    
    
    Give someone a meal (Advent Day 18) http://wp.me/p1j208-lo     
    
    
    Photo: Give someone a meal (Advent Day 18) Did you know that over 36 million people – including 13 million... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11fYtZf     
    
    
    Looks like the little one is going to a different school next year. So unhappy about this redistricting process.    
    
    
    And I realize why our neighborhood had NO say. On the border of ATL/Druid Hills & not as connected with rest of Oakhurst community.    
    
    
    Also, at least one person I know who has a kid at Oakhurst hasher grandfathered in b/c she's going into 3rd. So he's not in the fight.    
    
    
    @CubaLibreSez No bad schools but  Westchester is further away & yet another adjustment for her socially, etc.    
    
    
    @dagmarebaugh Well, you know how that goes. There wasn't enough of a fight.    
    
    
    @CubaLibreSez She is going to have to take the bus b/c there is no way I can drive her to W'chester in AM & stepson to DHS. Too crazy.    
    
    
    @CubaLibreSez Thank you. We do the best we can, I guess. :-) I just wish we could keep kids in ONE school for more than a couple of years.    
    
    
    Anyone know of a shoe repair place in/near Decatur that does a good job of cleaning suede boots?    
    
    
    @stacyreno I guess I shouldn't ask you how you came by this knowledge.    
    
    
    When will people learn that just because you're famous doesn't mean you get to say whatever you're thinking in your head?    
    
    
    Someone on my Facebook feed tried to equate New Age "oneness" concepts with the U.S.A. & our right to freedom of speech.    
    
    
    The teen boy just sat here & talked to me about trying to figure out his IB/AP class plans. High school is so complicated now!    
    
    
    RIP & prayers to his family RT @ajc: Sad news. Marietta soldier killed in helicopter crash in Afghanistan. http://bit.ly/1gJ9vOl     
    
    
    It's been challenging coming up with blog posts every day for Advent but I'm so glad that I did this. Writing is such a joy.    
    
    
    Give a kind word (Advent Day 19) http://wp.me/p1j208-lt     
    
    
    Photo: Give a kind word (Advent Day 19) So much of the negativity and tension we experience throughout the... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11hcN-k     
    
    
    Photo: Give a kind word (Advent Day 19) View Post http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11hcPEK     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thank you for the RT! Hugs to you!    
    
    
    The moon, y'all!!    
    
    
    Go you! @SCJoson: With my fellow women colleagues at the NASDAQ opening bell Monday. pic.twitter.com/tjqSFTNvrI    
    
    
    My 'hood! @SCJoson: @pnuts_mama that was a great neighborhood. The Vleigh library, and Benjy's Kosher Pizza, and Kissena Farms.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama @SCJoson Used to go to church w/ my grandma at Queen of Peace
 She worked at Wainright and McCrory's for years. #home    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama @SCJoson My grandma still lives across from Dara Gardens on 71st and 170th.    
    
    
    @SCJoson @pnuts_mama It was Wainright's that was there first. McCrory's was down the block near Valentino's.    
    
    
    Our niece is up for a meritorious promotion to sergeant in the Marine Corps. Proud of her hard work & commitment!    
    
    
    @SCJoson @pnuts_mama Electhester is further away - Parsons Blvd and Jewel Ave. You might be thinking of Pomonok.    
    
    
    Beautiful! @KellyDouglas: Sunrise ATL style http://instagram.com/p/iJP5raK1AP/     
    
    
    @rjmedwed I think we need to see more commentary that demonstrates how the Robertson's pointing to the Constitution has limits.    
    
    
    Yes, there's that too. @rjmedwed: @danayoung I think we need more people to learn how the Constitution works in general.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @rjmedwed The biggest issue I see is that the Robertsons keep saying we're infringing on their freedom of religion (not 1st Amendment btw.)    
    
    
    @rjmedwed They're hiding behind the "sin clause" to make their statements & defend them on religious grounds.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I completely agree with you, but they don't get it & neither do "Sound Bite Americans."    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Although someone must have clued them in, which is why they're saying they may shop for another network.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Those are hilarious!!!! Would look great next to my Holy Family and Wise men ornaments. ;-)    
    
    
    Politicians: please stop with the poverty-shaming. Help your constituents get back on their feet. Don't penalize them.    
    
    
    I have an important call this morning that could lead to more sustainable employment. Wish me luck!    
    
    
    The faces of the people who are struggling to make a living wage aren't always who you think.    
    
    
    @AllisonRentz Awesome boy!    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama @ABC7NY Devastating loss for his family & friends. Praying for them all.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Me neither. Terrible, awful tragedy. :-(    
    
    
    @ATLGreg1 Like A&E didn't know that. They saw a camouflaged cash cow when they saw one.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Aren't their 15 min up already? @AJCBuzz: ICYMI #DuckDynasty star is coming to Atlanta this weekend http://www.accessatlanta.com/weblogs/buzz/2013/dec/20/duck-dynasty-star-coming-atlanta/ … …    
    
    
    Looks like my client isn't going to show. That's why we send appointment reminders - so you can tell me if you can't make it!    
    
    
    Trying really hard to refrain from making a completely inappropriate tweet about Canada.    
    
    
    My pastor just posted a pic on FB he took during one of our church holiday programs. My efforts are paying off! #chsocm    
    
    
    @_L1vY_ I do have to be mindful of my part-time employer (church) but it's almost too funny to resist!    
    
    
    @leoghann To be fair, I'm liking our more liberal, less violent & bigoted neighbors (who clearly know how to party) up North.    
    
    
    @stacyreno You may be in for some rough weather in Memphis this weekend but HAVE FUN!    
    
    
    Me too! > 10 Reasons Why I'm Falling In Love With Pope Francis http://shar.es/Oy2Zo  via @benjamincorey    
    
    
    Whew. Conference call went really well. Now, keep fingers crossed we can get funding!    
    
    
    Writers! You may qualify for a free "writers-in-residence" home...in Detroit! http://huff.to/1cUMgxi  via @HuffPostBooks    
    
    
    My holiday reading: Julian of Norwich. http://instagram.com/p/iJukPAAkHh/     
    
    
    Photo: My holiday reading: Julian of Norwich. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11m0hiV     
    
    
    Off to the little one's holiday party at school. Little kids and sugar galore! The rest of this afternoon should be fuuuunnnnnn...    
    
    
    My ride is here. Yeah right. I wish! http://instagram.com/p/iJxcAFAkLo/     
    
    
    @stacyreno Funny how that happens! Pssst...he might be a stalker!    
    
    
    @AdamsLisa I know you don't know me, but I'm wishing you peace and comfort.    
    
    
    For sale: 'Slightly haunted' home http://shar.es/OznRu     
    
    
    @erinscafe You should cc @BarackObama on all these #obamacare selection tweets. It doesn't sound like the easiest process.    
    
    
    (1 of 2) 1st Amendment protects us from -- laws being made that restrict freedom of religion, the press &/or speech. - LZ Granderson    
    
    
    (2 of 2) "It does not protect us from how society responds to the expression of one's religion, the press or speech. - LZ Granderson    
    
    
    @markalves And probably my bonus too. ;-)    
    
    
    @erinscafe We have insurance thru my husband's employer & NONE of the docs they contract with are the ones I've used for years.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tea time! http://instagram.com/p/iKGo-VAkIM/     
    
    
    @erinscafe You see, #obamacare is really preventative medicine, because now you'll be motivated to NOT get sick. Ever.    
    
    
    @amandagossett Actually, they really don't. But WE do. :-)    
    
    
    You know the little one has had too many candy canes when she walks into the room, holding a hammer, wanting to nail things in.    
    
    
    My theme for today is: #stepawayfromthehammer    
    
    
    The little one wanted me to download all of Tchaikovsky's "The Nutcracker Suite." :-)    
    
    
    @stacyreno You said it, not me! ;-)    
    
    
    Atlanta Botanical Gardens holiday lights. http://instagram.com/p/iKZutogkDC/     
    
    
    Photo: Atlanta Botanical Gardens holiday lights. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11nvNR2     
    
    
    Light spheres set to music. http://instagram.com/p/iKa5ImgkEe/     
    
    
    Photo: Light spheres set to music. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11nyh5u     
    
    
    Dragonflies! http://instagram.com/p/iKdx70gkIb/     
    
    
    Purple cherry blossom lights. http://instagram.com/p/iKfr2lAkKr/     
    
    
    Lady of the fountain. http://instagram.com/p/iKg4jrgkMD/     
    
    
    Photo: Lady of the fountain. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11oD6iO     
    
    
    Luminous lady. http://instagram.com/p/iKiP1TAkN2/     
    
    
    Photo: Luminous lady. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11oGpDh     
    
    
    @DecaturSquared Yes it is amazing!    
    
    
    OH: Woman talking to her children about regifting wine. "It's a cabernet sauvignon!"    
    
    
    @JevanteSampson @SCJoson @pnuts_mama Yup - we all grew up over there! My grandma lived in Pomonok.    
    
    
    The pencil that flew off the balcony in the sanctuary, just missing the elderly couple in the pews below? Yep, that was us.    
    
    
    I suppose we should be grateful it wasn't the pew Bible or hymnal. The best part? It wasn't even the little one's fault.    
    
    
    @abba_ks @HandsomeDash We were in church when a big crack of thunder hit.
 Fortunately @DogNamedJazz left the house intact.    
    
    
    Wonder if they make holiday-themed rain boots.    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Always works for me!    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl @cooljatl Just don't stand OUTSIDE and try to plug in the Xmas lights. :-)    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl @CoolJAtl There's no other way than to light the heck out of the tree!!    
    
    
    My daily advent devotions sort of went by the wayside the past few days b/c of other work. Should I try to finish them?    
    
    
    Sigh. Why are the #DecaturGA cops hanging around on my street? Hoping it wasn't another robbery. :-(    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl Awww, it looks pretty! Get thee more Bailey's stat!    
    
    
    Give yourself a treat (Advent Day 20) http://wp.me/p1j208-ly     
    
    
    Photo: Give yourself a treat (Advent Day 20) Are visions of sugarplums dancing in your head? As I write... http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu11ze59J     
    
    
    @DecaturSquared Officer was checking on homes where people were away for the holidays.  A good thing!    
    
    
    One of my Reiki students is in labor, awaiting her Christmas baby. Please send prayers & good energy for a peaceful arrival!    
    
    
    I've been very emotional these past 24 hrs. Tempted to blame it on hormones but it's really from feeling so much love & joy.    
    
    
    Two beautiful bluebirds, two gorgeous cardinals & one stunning woodpecker in my yard. #happiness    
    
    
    A treat for the birds, hanging on the little dogwood tree. http://instagram.com/p/iRS2zEgkFC/     
    
    
    Custom skateboard design with peace symbols. #amazingpeacegirl http://instagram.com/p/iRWPrXgkJv/     
    
    
    Wow @MikeElk: Banksy's  Christmas Card Shows Mary & Joseph Stopped by The Wall http://mondoweiss.net/2012/12/banksys-christmas-card-shows-joseph-and-mary-stopped-by-the-wall.html …    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Prayers sent your way. _/\_    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Sometimes Twitter accidentally unfollows people. Not sure why that happens. But thanks for refollowing! :-)    
    
    
    @stacyreno I'm still waiting on one. And had to redirect A from the huge box that arrived today containing her stuffed husky dog.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Oh you know what's really crazy? Turns out one of my coworkers at church lived in Flushing near 35th Ave. Small world!    
    
    
    The little one is scootering around the house singing to the Black Keys' "Lonely Boy". And Justin Timberlake.    
    
    
    Don't tell anyone, but I might be making Oreo truffle balls tonight.    
    
    
    @woowoo76 Your friends are here! But I know it is nice to see people *in person* too. Hugs!    
    
    
    @woowoo76 Always here for you - in spirit and with tweet hugs. :-)    
    
    
    @stacyreno Thankfully I was able to deflect that since the hubby receives so many packages. She assumed it was for him.    
    
    
    @stacyreno It will all be fine. Believe in miracles big and small!    
    
    
    "You may call God love, you may call God goodness. But the best name for God is compassion." - Meister Eckhart    
    
    
    @francesk Oh no, really? Sending a prayer up to Archangel Chamuel to help locate your package soon!    
    
    
    @stacyreno Don't stop believin'!    
    
    
    @francesk It was on the Santa list. I don't know if she had seen one previously, but I found one made by Melissa & Doug that was cute.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I grew up in half Catholic/half Jewish house. We celebrated both but I don't see why Jews might think they're missing something.    
    
    
    @francesk She is ALL about her stuffed animals. Meh on dolls & other girly toys. Her room is like a plush farm. LOL    
    
    
    @rjmedwed That's what we did. Although there were a few Jewish-themed ornaments on the tree for my dad. But he liked that.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Hanukkah was celebrated as a distinctly different holiday than Xmas. Same with Easter & Passover. We respected traditions.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed No, not even if they call it a Hanukkah bush. They're not even about the same events.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I understand. These articles tend to be way too flip about things that are very meaningful to people. We need sacred events.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Jesus even would have told you that. ;-)    
    
    
    Precisely. RT @rjmedwed: @danayoung (Jesus would have celebrated Hanukkah.)    
    
    
    @rjmedwed I found that celebrating Jewish holidays gave me context for Jesus's life & ministry. So grateful for that exposure.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed It depends on the denomination. In my case, it was just my life growing up. Also lived next to an Orthodox community.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Is that an alternate name? Never heard of it.    
    
    
    @rjmedwed That would explain it.    
    
    
    My festive little house. http://instagram.com/p/iSFHS6AkOW/     
    
    
    @livyloorose Merry Christmas to you!    
    
    
    For once, nearly ALL of my gifts are wrapped! My back is spasming, however. Wine, please!    
    
    
    @abba_ks There is no good way to wrap gifts without jacking up your spine. After a while, I just throw everything into gift bags.    
    
    
    Merry Christmas Eve to all!    
    
    
    Love my sweet Christmas plates! http://instagram.com/p/iTxSrqgkHD/     
    
    
    "A Charlie Brown Christmas" is always in my house. #christmastimeishere http://instagram.com/p/iUCoDbAkE3/     
    
    
    Photo: "A Charlie Brown Christmas" is always in my house. #christmastimeishere http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu129J2Iq     
    
    
    We got a second Christmas tree on sale. Because more trees! http://instagram.com/p/iUDGc_gkF4/     
    
    
    Getting ready for Santa's arrival! #christmas http://instagram.com/p/iUEOZwAkHu/     
    
    
    @francesk I would be heartbroken if I lost mine!    
    
    
    @rjmedwed Alcohol. It's how we survive the holidays.    
    
    
    @mamaerika @abba_ks @DukeStJournal And Chinese takeout!    
    
    
    @francesk Ah, the "safe" places AKA "good luck finding your stuff again."    
    
    
    Love this story! @nprnews: A Portuguese Tradition Of 'Healing' Dolls For Christmas http://n.pr/K2MlVC     
    
    
    Last gift finally arrived at the house. Getting way down to the wire.    
    
    
    Christmas angel. http://instagram.com/p/iUsIRiAkDO/     
    
    
    I cried my way through our child-led Christmas Eve service. Our sweet girl did so well singing in the choir!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @_sethyoung added more Christmas lights in the front yard! http://instagram.com/p/iUwZN8AkMF/     
    
    
    Beautiful message of love, peace, joy & hope @CNN: Pope at Christmas Eve Mass: 'Do not be afraid.' http://cnn.it/1dBCBcY     
    
    
    @auntie_jenn Bathroom break!!!    
    
    
    Oh no! Prayers to him for healing @patrickherron: Amiri Baraka, former N.J. poet laureate, hospitalized in critical condition    
    
    
    Christmas blessings! My student had her baby boy after two days of labor! Unto us a child is born!    
    
    
    @auntie_jenn I ask myself that same question all the time.    
    
    
    Watched "Elf" with the little one, read "'Twas the Night Before Christmas" & wrote note to her from the other elf. Bring it, Xmas!    
    
    
    @cvarkey Hugs to you.    
    
    
    Our second Christmas tree. ;-) http://instagram.com/p/iVNXmWAkJM/     
    
    
    The first Christmas tree. http://instagram.com/p/iVNmc8AkJk/     
    
    
    @stacyreno Same to you, dear friend! xo    
    
    
    Yes, really. RT @stacyreno: Dear Santa, why didn't you leave a full pot of coffee for me?    
    
    
    Merry Christmas! May peace, hope, love and joy be yours today and always.    
    
    
    Please let us Christians celebrate Christmas without comment. I respect your holidays & traditions too. Thank you.    
    
    
    I'm sorry there are Christians who aren't respectful of other people's traditions. But there are plenty of us that are.    
    
    
    There is so much good to be celebrating this season, regardless of *what* you believe. Allow joy & peace into your heart.    
    
    
    Not trying to be grumpy. Just my daily reminder to ask us all to try to be nicer to one another.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate @stacyreno I actually went back to sleep for an hour after the kid startled me out of bed to open gifts.    
    
    
    Now that Christmas dinner is done, I am done.    
    
    
    @BlissInMe A cloud of delectable delights, no doubt! Merry Christmas to you and Bliss!    
    
    
    I really could go the rest of my life without having to endure another holiday dinner discussion about football.    
    
    
    I have nothing ever to contribute to a discussion about football - pro or college. Let's talk about books or art instead!    
    
    
    @JaMonkey I SO wanted crumb coffee cake this morning!    
    
    
    The little one is scootering around the house singing a song about her brother not having the Christmas spirit.    
    
    
    Yesterday she scootered around singing about Jesus. Today it's Christmas spirit. I think we might have an album in the works.    
    
    
    So heartbreaking @ajc: Sad: Firefighter discovers that dying woman he pulled from crushed SUV was his daughter. http://bit.ly/1kGxeyH     
    
    
    @woowoo76 Oh, Laura. I am so very sorry for your loss. May your dad be at peace. So many hugs & much love to you.    
    
    
    Can't wait to see The Nutcracker tomorrow with @_sethyoung! We scored free tix from his job!    
    
    
    @JaMonkey I have a recipe from a cookbook that belonged to my grandfather. So yummy!    
    
    
    Specially etched & magickally infused candles were a sweet gift from @marlatiara. #angelswatchingover pic.twitter.com/daUnbRtXtZ    
    
    
    Christmas bokeh. http://instagram.com/p/iaHtmhgkKW/     
    
    
    Photo: Christmas bokeh. http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu12NWFEC     
    
    
    "The Nutcracker"! @ The Fox Theatre http://instagram.com/p/ib4_CHAkLo/     
    
    
    So sad to hear that Clark Vreeland of Spanky and the Love Handles has passed away.    
    
    
    Hugs, love and Happy Birthday to sweet @woowoo76.    
    
    
    I did @Darkness2Light: We took the training! Did you? http://ow.ly/i/45BnA     
    
    
    Date night with @_sethyoung!    
    
    
    :-( @CNN: Report: At least 23 dead in train fire in India. http://cnn.it/JjmlVi     
    
    
    Will remind you of that next time he drives u crazy @_SethYoung: Having a teenager has its perks.  “@danayoung Date night with @_SethYoung!”    
    
    
    So grateful for the Healing Touch session I received today. I think I'm still floating a little.    
    
    
    Not sure I can handle a winter of cold and rain.    
    
    
    I don't think there is enough vitamin D to compensate for this weather.    
    
    
    @JuliaMaybell I'm pretty sure I could toss back half my vitamin bottle and it wouldn't make a difference.    
    
    
    Do it! @UlyssesLives: And who is contemplating reading or revisiting #Ulysses in the new year?    
    
    
    This x 1000 @AnnBac9: I am so tired hearing about Duck Dynasty!    
    
    
    @Carl Nope!    
    
    
    That too! @rjmedwed: @danayoung @AnnBac9 Yes! And I'm tired of having folks make money off of hate speech and bigotry!    
    
    
    @Carl @evequickly @MellowMushroom I need to remember that! Always looking for good GF pizza!    
    
    
    “All shall be well, and all shall be well and all manner of thing shall be well.” - Julian of Norwich    
    
    
    @ATLmuse Where are they located?    
    
    
    @ATLmuse I don't have issues with celiac or cross-contamination; I just try to limit/avoid gluten b/c I feel better when I do.    
    
    
    @ATLmuse Awesome - will have to check them out! :-) Hope you are well.    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia "Our commitment to musical excellence as defined by these five pillars upon which we build our brand."    
    
    
    @marlatiara I've been to the one at Edgewood. I liked the GF pizza but the hubby didn't. :-(    
    
    
    Yep, There's A Reason Why You Hate Comic Sans http://www.refinery29.com/science-behind-font … via @refinery29    
    
    
    Lazy Sunday morning, coffee and classic Soul playing. #lifeisgood    
    
    
    @mustangmelatl So are their moms! ;-)    
    
    
    @DeadJournalist I grew up listening to this. It's my happy music.    
    
    
    Yes #halloffame RT @DeadJournalist: Maddux, Thomas, Glavine, Biggio, Trammel, Mussina, Raines, Piazza, Bagwell, Schilling    
    
    
    Someone I know posted a pic of herself on FB holding cookies & roses. Someone commented "at least the roses won't make you gain weight."    
    
    
    Seriously?! What the hell happened to good manners & filters on your thoughts? Think before you post your comments, people!    
    
    
    @GrabMoL Yeah. Totally floored me. And this woman is so sweet - would never say an unkind thing to ANYONE. Made me feel so bad.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama I am STILL picking my jaw up off the floor. I feel so bad for my friend. She is the sweetest person.    
    
    
    @GrabMoL I'm tempted to report her! ;-)    
    
    
    @mamaerika It's such a tough balance. Strict enough so they know you mean what you say but not so much they rebel against you. Hugs mama!    
    
    
    Uh what? RT @DecaturGAPatch: A reader writes Decatur should cease to exist as a city in his Op-Ed. What do you think? http://bit.ly/1fStINX     
    
    
    @mamaerika Oh man. I always hated it when my mom talked to me when I was in trouble. That could be worse than any punishment. LOL    
    
    
    @stacyreno Wait. He said WHAT?!    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate And frankly, I think some people just make thoughtless comments without considering WHAT they are really saying.    
    
    
    @stacyreno You may want to tell him if he doesn't cut the bulldh*t that you'll ask for court-ordered mediation/family therapy.    
    
    
    @stacyreno That was bullsh*t by the way. So pissed I can't even spell straight!    
    
    
    @stacyreno He is holding your girls emotionally hostage, which is wrong, wrong, WRONG.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Same here. But then again, I think we care about what we want to say.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Perhaps explain to him that lying & manipulating his child will only mean she'll resent him later on in life?    
    
    
    @stacyreno Sending you and your sweet girls a BIG hug!    
    
    
    Freezing my butt off.    
    
    
    Making shepherd's pie for dinner. Perfect for a chilly, damp and dreary day.    
    
    
    Another great and yummy choice!    
    
    
    Kind of glad to actually be back on a schedule of sorts. I seem to do better with more of a routine.    
    
    
    The 6 year old is crying because she did her hair & didn't like how it came out. I'm afraid of the teen years already.    
    
    
    @GrabMoL I told her that I have plenty of bad hair days too. And that she is still beautiful,  even if she didn't her hair.    
    
    
    @francesk My daughter has much easier hair than mine (only wavy & not coarse) and yet she still wants it to be stick-straight.    
    
    
    @francesk She uses mousse already! And we condition with shea butter. She has the benefit of my years of suffering with frizz. :-)    
    
    
    @francesk My mom has stick-straight hair. No help to me whatsoever.  :'(    
    
    
    @francesk Nice! Sounds like me in high school! #TheFrizz    
    
    
    #corporatetakeover RT @stacyreno: wtf? An M & M? What happened to the peach? http://instagram.com/p/ije933C_Gc/     
    
    
    Maybe Atlanta should drop a giant baseball on NYE. Oh wait. They already did that a month or so ago.    
    
    
    @ATLmuse But really? A M&M?!    
    
    
    @ATLmuse @rjmedwed "Organizers promise a surprise coming from the hunk of candy" This does not bode well.    
    
    
    @ATLmuse @rjmedwed Best comment: "Come out NYE and see Atlanta's nuts drop!"    
    
    
    @francesk Oh, right. Silly me. #peachdropped    
    
    
    Beautiful RT @CliffBostock: New psychology blog posting: "Broken-hearted, lost in a labyrinth, encountering angels." http://tinyurl.com/monmym2     
    
    
    @stacyreno Amish. Yeah, that's you in a nutshell. F-bombing Amish girl!    
    
    
    My pretty little Oreo truffle balls. http://instagram.com/p/ikU5wlAkN7/     
    
    
    @pacaunt I just finished a batch of them with crushed candy canes on top. :-)    
    
    
    @woowoo76 Thinking of you, dear friend!    
    
    
    Oreo truffle balls with crushed candy cane sprinkles. http://instagram.com/p/ikfK97gkMz/     
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Yes it is! Hope it lifts for you soon. I've been piling on the vitamin D to help counteract mine.    
    
    
    Two of my friends are in India, and posting their pics. Makes me miss that beautiful country so much.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @pnuts_mama I take 1000 mg. Seems to be helping me but if we have more rain/gloom like we've been having, I'm upping that mofo.    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama @readergirl I've heard it does help. My husband is now convinced I need to live somewhere further south than here.    
    
    
    Little one is going to a sleepover & we have two parties to attend tonight! Now, if I can just find something cute to wear...    
    
    
    My New Year is already off on the right foot (er...shoe) thanks to a gift card to the best little shoe… http://instagram.com/p/imHdGpgkDi/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Can we make this the 11th Commandment? RT @JesusOfNaz316: Stop watching TV shows that degrade human dignity. #NewYearResolution    
    
    
    Comcast isn't so "comcastic" at the moment. S L O W internet connection. A modem *might* be faster.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Thankfully I don't have any real work to do, but it's annoying as hell.    
    
    
    @leoghann @stacyreno I knew you were to blame. ;-)    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Actually, I'm ending up with something very close to that. Glittery sweater, jeggings, boots. :-) #greatmindsthinkalike    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate LOL! I tend to keep it simple anyway. Plus, both are house parties, so I don't have to dress to the nines this time. :-)    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Me too. I just don't have it in me to suffer needlessly. ;-)    
    
    
    Heading to H.Harper Station for dinner with @_SethYoung!    
    
    
    Yeah kid, why not wear all black and skateboard down the middle of Dekalb Ave. #smh    
    
    
    Happy New Year! http://instagram.com/p/inTgXHAkAm/     
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Happy New Year to you! #sparkling    
    
    
    The Bufala Negra is my new libation for 2014.    
    
    
    Watching @mustangmelatl break it down to "Baby Got Back" at @thetheimperialbar.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @mustangmelatl Seriously!  Where are you?!    
    
    
    @abba_ks You ain't going nowhere yet! Your life isn't a "sell by" date. But sequins and caviar anyway. Just fucking because.    
    
    
    @stacyreno @mustangmelatl Sling her over your shoulder and come on over. ;-)    
    
    
    I do not like black eyed peas or collards. Are there other good luck New Years' Day foods?    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama Ugh. Really?!    
    
    
    @mamaerika Yum. Sounds good!    
    
    
    @francesk I can do apples and honey! :-)    
    
    
    NOW they tell us. ;-) RT @grist: Asparagus may keep you from getting a hangover http://bit.ly/1cY6x6U     
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Drives me nuts when manufacturers made a great product & then stopped producing it or made changes.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Yes, completely agree! Or they change the sizing model they use for the product so nothing fits the same way.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate I have trouble finding pants that fit b/c I'm tall & thin. So if I find something that works for me, I buy them all up.    
    
    
        
    
    
    See my sparkly sweater @semiotic_pirate! :-) (Never mind the deer in headlights look we both have!) pic.twitter.com/HevF4bZmxp    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Actually, it was a little bit itchy but many sweaters tend to be on me.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Thanks mama! :-)    
    
    
    Lighting the way. Happy 2014! http://instagram.com/p/ipWKxwAkGR/     
    
    
    Photo: Lighting the way. Happy 2014! http://tmblr.co/ZsRElu12zeFkP     
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Yep although thankfully this was nice and stretchy.    
    
    
    First fortune of 2014. My lucky color! @ The Golden Buddha http://instagram.com/p/ipcCoFgkPw/     
    
    
    Starting off 2014 with the spiritual teachings of Hildegard of Bingen. http://instagram.com/p/ipjRSeAkMc/     
    
    
        
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Ah, the Palladium!    
    
    
    @livyloorose Stay warm!    
    
    
    @LynnATL I loved "Murphy Brown"too!    
    
    
    @pnuts_mama That's over in Whitestone?    
    
    
    @stacyreno I will be so sad when we take ours down. I love having colors out at night b/c otherwise it's so dark on my block.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Still have the clothes rack? I could probably use it.    
    
    
    @Carl @stacyreno People think the day after Christmas means the holiday is over, when in fact, it has just begun!    
    
    
    @Carl And so why don't you live in Portland? Seems like more your speed, weatherwise. :-) As for me, more vitamin D please!!    
    
    
    Stay warm and safe, everyone in the Northeast! I miss a good blizzard every now and again (except for the shoveling.)    
    
    
    @stacyreno Oh that is the WORST. :-(    
    
    
        
    
    
    @blessinger @Salon What does the fox say? ;-)    
    
    
    @Carl Whatever magic filter you possess is one I am going to need. 5 days of gloom are starting to make me wig out.    
    
    
    After 5 days straight of some combination of gloom/clouds/rain/coldness,  I decided to double my Vitamin D dose.    
    
    
    @francesk For a second, the sky brightened and I got excited. And then, more gloom. #SAD #gloomy #rainlanta    
    
    
    There is a ladybug crawling around my kitchen.    
    
    
    @francesk Maybe I should just put up TV screens around my house, showing continuous footage of the sun. #gloomy #stormy #SAD #rainlanta    
    
    
    @Carl I am going to need a ceiling full of SAD lights if this keeps up. #rainlanta    
    
    
    This weather is about to make me go into hiding.    
    
    
    It's getting even windier, darker and gloomier outside. Make it stop! #SAD #rainlanta    
    
    
        
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate I hate those interview bait & switch tactics. Either you support WRFM or you don't.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate I think policies need to be consistent across the board at companies. Otherwise applicants/employees get mixed messages.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate I was fortunate to have WRFM flexibility the years I worked for companies, but some managers were less supportive.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Now there is no way I could imagine being in an office for 35-40 hrs a week. I'd die.    
    
    
    Brought loving care into a tragic situation > Nurses, family bond online as Iranian dies in US http://shar.es/9tELm     
    
    
    @carrievandelac @georgiayoga Thank you both!    
    
    
    @Carl You and I are definitely wired differently. Although I can have flat affect sometimes if it is VERY bright and sunny.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @d3bbie Ruff day, perhaps? ;-)    
    
    
    @Carl Between the two of us, there must be a moderately nice Spring or Fall day in there somewhere.    
    
    
    There's some serious wind blowing outside. And it's COLD. Not going anywhere if I can help it.    
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate A heated driveway? I would just love heated seats in my car!    
    
    
    @stacyreno Now?    
    
    
    @stacyreno What's on Saturday?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @semiotic_pirate Mmmm...chai...    
    
    
    I need one of those down stadium coats that can double as a quilt. Or maybe I can just use the one on my bed...    
    
    
    Those fleece-lined tights I got for Xmas will go great - under my jeans.    
    
    
    Can you tell I have *zero* tolerance for cold weather?    
    
    
    Yes! @marlatiara: @danayoung I moved here to escape the cold - WHAT IS THIS NONSENSE? ;) Next up - moving to the Equator.    
    
    
    @stacyreno Or Caribbean ones!    
    
    
    @auntie_jenn At least you have a snowblower. I used to shovel out my parents' double driveway. Stay warm!!!!    
    
    
    @gbkgwyneth @stacyreno OK, you and @Carl clearly live in the wrong state.    
    
    
    @leoghann @marlatiara @stacyreno You will never hear me complain about warm weather in Feb or otherwise.    
    
    
    The teen boy just showed up with a box of NERF guns. Foam madness is soon to ensue.... #takesaim    
    
    
        
    
    
    @RandomOenophile @leoghann @stacyreno @marlatiara Eh, bro?    
    
    
    @leoghann @RandomOenophile @stacyreno @marlatiara The real test is if he can ice skate backwards drunk while shooting the puck.    
    
    
    @marlatiara @leoghann @stacyreno @RandomOenophile And she knows a thing or two about hockey. Maybe drunk too?    
    
    
    @marlatiara @leoghann @stacyreno @RandomOenophile Oh wait. Confusing hockey with karaoke. Carry on.    
    
    
        
    
    
    As the manifestation candle burns down, the dragonfly is revealed. Thanks @marlatiara! http://instagram.com/p/isgBC6AkDU/     
    
    
        
    
    
    I knew I should have gotten that longer down puffer jacket I wanted. The parka I have is just a wee bit short.    
    
    
    @3Quarters2Day The drill instructor was a lot nicer than the ones I saw at my niece's graduation from Parris Island!    
    
    
    @readergirl Teachers deserve better than what they frequently receive.    
    
    
    @readergirl I know. It makes me so angry to hear how teachers are devalued. I understand why parents are always being asked to give.    
    
    
    @Carl @DecaturSquared @stacyreno Mine are still up! You probably saw some of my Instagram pics of them too.    
    
    
    Reiki fundraiser Jan 18 to support @AndrewJTriumph's Team in Training to race across America! http://bit.ly/KcRD0j     
    
    
    @stacyreno Fingers and toes crossed for you!    
    
    
    NERF wars have commenced at our house. No one, not even @JazzTheDog, is safe now.    
    
    
        
    
    
    