Agency of the year? @BBDO New York. Congrats! #clioawards    
    
    
    Wow @LeoBurnett, never saw the #bookburningparty campaign before... but not surprised at its effectiveness #clioawards    
    
    
    Hall of fame spot is a trip: Honda GRRR #clioawards    
    
    
    Annie Leibovitz, honorary CLIO winner, takes the stage #clioawards    
    
    
    Exclusive: @moat Partners With 24/7 Media With Hopes of Shaking Up Analytics http://shar.es/2SgKJ  via @Adweek @cwarzel    
    
    
    Just ahead of the #Facebook IPO, @GM decided to pull its underperforning @Facebookads. Wonder if other major brands will start pulling out?    
    
    
    #Exclusive with Alan Siegel, who's leaving @SiegelGale to pro-bono try to make the world a better place. http://ow.ly/aWZLh  @adweek...    
    
    
    Story about to break via @adweek via RT @katyonthehill: @FTC's #40 million settlement w/Sketchers is largest ever for the FTC #advertising    
    
    
    @hesherman @SiegelGale He said he'd focus on nonprofits and orgs that don't have the money to enlist an agency, so some work must be free.    
    
    
    I gave @Adweek +K about Media on @klout http://klout.com/plusk/gave/67554001408473758/85568398087860756/2423542?n=tw&v=plusk_gave …    
    
    
    #Breaking via @KatyontheHill: Skechers settlement w @FTC for deceptive advertising is largest ever @Adweek @SKECHERSUSA http://ow.ly/aXdfO     
    
    
    I can't believe I forgot about some of these! RT @adfreak: The 20 Most-Viral Ads of 2012 (So Far) http://bit.ly/KPuL2W  #advertising    
    
    
    That cute furry #kitty or puppy is really a dirty #slut. Keep it from getting knocked up and off #reality #TV http://j.mp/JhTwkq     
    
    
    "The difference between the almost right word and the right word is the difference between the lightning bug and the lightning" #advertising    
    
    
    Brands will experience #socialmedia gaffes. Key to recovery is how they're handled. Brand #fail http://j.mp/J8uMkn  @adweek    
    
    
    Too busy to attend #InternetWeek myself, but @Adweek has it covered. http://j.mp/JTcMJA     
    
    
    "I have learned that any fool can write a bad ad, but that it takes a real genius to keep his hands off a good one." @LeoBurnett #quotes    
    
    
    From trapezes and burlesque dancers to robots, these are the 10 best #upfront parties so far: http://ow.ly/aYpwx  #cable #broadcast @hulu    
    
    
    "I do not regard advertising as entertainment or an art form, but as a medium of information." - @David_Ogilvy #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    @dennisjansen Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @Diaiyc Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    Almost too many celebrity deaths to keep up with, but particularly sad about Donna Summer #RIP @TheDonnaSummer #TheLastDance    
    
    
    Do Not Track gets traction RT @niemanlab: @Twitter is offering users an opt-out for tracking personal data http://nie.mn/JiL0Yh     
    
    
    Why did @Twitter decide to implement #donottrack? @Adweek's @Petersontee has the details. http://ow.ly/aYI6V     
    
    
    .@amalisam What about this air-filtering plant billboard for Coca-Cola? I wrote about it last year. http://ow.ly/aYItJ  #ad #BBDO    
    
    
    !!! @SkechersUSA should probably have not paid a staffer's doc husband to lie about #ShapeUps http://j.mp/JkJeA1  #lies #badvertising #ads    
    
    
    .@skechersUSA pulled girls' ShapeUps. #Ads said they make girls more popular. Quite the opposite #uglyshoes #lies http://ow.ly/aYMre     
    
    
    .@HuffingtonPost Why nine? You couldn't find a 10th top tech CEO?    
    
    
    "I'm going to stop going to the gym and just wear Skechers ShapeUps." @skechersUSA #ThingsNotToSayOnTheFirstDate    
    
    
    Condom makes cuts to the chase: What won't you put in your vagina? http://j.mp/KoLcRN  @adfreak @adweek #NSFW #sexsells #ads #womenshealth    
    
    
    Thanks to @jezebel for passing along story by @Adweek's @nudd about new condom campaign - "What won't you put in your vagina?"    
    
    
    I actually thought this # would be higher. RT @comScore: #Mobile approaching 10% of e-commerce sales #SOR12 #advertising    
    
    
    Thursday #advertising tip: Create alignment between #CRM and social media teams #tips #socialmediamarketing    
    
    
    Email of the day in Melissa's @Adweek inbox. Please send me a free Beer Tower Sample, Frank Ma! #spam #gimmemybeertower pic.twitter.com/PS8GfiD7    
    
    
    Incredibly misleading headline from @nyt makes it seem like #FacebookIPO is a done deal and/or they can see the future. http://ow.ly/aZ8hI     
    
    
    Enjoying #networking with #advertising folks @Adroll's 'Adperitif.' Great name for an industry mixer.    
    
    
    Tomorrow is the much-anticipated #FacebookIPO. Zuckerberg no doubt has his lucky hoodie on! Some other predictions: http://j.mp/JTfUFb     
    
    
    If the cup comes filled with @Guinness, count me in! http://j.mp/MoSf1l  @gbeltrone @adweek #QRcode    
    
    
    Take a look at 20 #ads you'll be dying to share: http://j.mp/MkTHSm  @adweek @adfreak    
    
    
    "The very 1st law in advertising is to avoid the concrete promise and cultivate the delightfully vague." -Stuart Chase #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    Here we go $FB    
    
    
    #OMFG #Facebook is trading    
    
    
    @cwarzel Gosh. Just 'cause he's "CEO, Bitch," doesn't mean he can keep us all waiting. $FB #DelayedFreakoutIsAlsoDelayed    
    
    
    @levimcconnell This is just as fantastic as you said. Thanks so much! Was terrific to meet you and the rest of the @Velocidi team    
    
    
    It could be the biggest #IPO in history, so why not obsessively read @NYT's liveblog of #Facebook's first trading day. http://ow.ly/b079D     
    
    
    @adroll Terrific event! Thanks for inviting me. Met your team, plus some other great people. Enjoy the rest of your stay in NYC!    
    
    
    Surprise, surprise. http://buff.ly/KuRZJG  @adweekemma @adweek    
    
    
    Impact of the $FB #IPO on tech PR industry: tsunami. Where a tsunami is a sunny Friday off from work. http://ow.ly/b0bgw     
    
    
    Proof that boatloads of money hasn't made Mark Zuckerberg less weird-looking http://ow.ly/b0jGY  $FB @Instagram #facebookIPO    
    
    
    Ad-skipping DVR technology gets @TheOnion treatment http://ow.ly/b0mVo     
    
    
    @slarkpope Or admen    
    
    
    @slarkpope Jesus must be too busy with the clowns and stucco    
    
    
    Interesting technique used to create a great car #ad. http://ow.ly/b0pGa     
    
    
    @ivanlajara Please no, my mind is tired of being blown. ENOUGH IS ENOUGH http://ow.ly/b0suo     
    
    
    Will @SouthwestAir be another big win for @arnoldworldwide? @adweek @mcmains1965 #advertising #review http://ow.ly/b0tik     
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg rang the @NASDAQ's opening bell and #InternetWeek will ring in the close. Reminds me how crazy this week has been. $FB #TGIF    
    
    
    Personally, I'd rather let men handle these tough life situations. #vintageads pic.twitter.com/t7UKjPM5    
    
    
    Am I jealous that @samthielman got to go to @AdultSwim's #upfront party and see people in bunny suits simulate sex? Yup http://ow.ly/b0yFe     
    
    
    Holy crap @GM, first dissing #Facebook advertising ahead of its #IPO and now this?! Not advertising in the #Superbowl? http://ow.ly/b0EqO     
    
    
    Already, #Facebook has made its first acquisition as a public company. Karma - the company, not the concept. http://bit.ly/LkObzM     
    
    
    The Internet Week that was: http://buff.ly/JTcMJA  @adweek #internetweek #IWNY #IW    
    
    
    The 10 best TV parties you didn't go to! http://buff.ly/KvEpJU  #upfronts #upfront @hulu @AETV @ABC @disney @discovery @MTV @syfy @oxygenpr    
    
    
    Without enough soda, your baby is doomed to be dull, lethargic, unpopular. It's never too soon! #vintageads #crazy pic.twitter.com/coDqaZXB    
    
    
    "It's your life. You don't know how long it's gonna last, but you know it doesn't end well." -Don Draper #madmen #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    Awesome old piece of #advertising in Astoria shoe repair shop. Gonna see if they'll let me buy it. http://lockerz.com/s/210163763     
    
    
    Finally got to the one where Don Draper loses his Clio in a bar (s.4) #madmen #clioawards @amc @dondraper    
    
    
    .@TheDouville It was surreal - just went to the #CLIOawards last week with @adweek. So cool to see what the show was like in the 60s #madmen    
    
    
    @TheDouville No, but if anyone, it would have been #CLIOawards host @Joan_Rivers. Awesomely inappropriate jokes, 1 was about Casey Anthony.    
    
    
    5 cable companies linking up their #WiFi to provide nationwide access. http://buff.ly/Keugj2  @adweek @comcast @cablevision @twxcorp @cox_comm    
    
    
    Some #reporters get to have all the fun? @Gawker reporter on 'shrooms at #CLIOawards freaks out in the Whale Room. http://buff.ly/Kf4ivT  #LOL    
    
    
    Wonder how Zuck's honeymoon is going? RT @politico: Facebook shares plummet far below its $38 price for the #IPO: http://politi.co/KFYpcS  $FB    
    
    
    BREAKING: #NASCAR down to 4 agencies in #advertising review. @Adweek's @mcmains1965 has the #exclusive report. http://ow.ly/b3gEQ     
    
    
    My mind is in the gutter. RT @tonymedia: Poor #ChanningTatum is mobbed. Can't even sit to enjoy his rubber chicken. #peabodyawards    
    
    
    Facebook and media still don't know for sure where this relationship is going. http://buff.ly/Krnx16  @adweek @digitalshields #advertising    
    
    
    "Advertising is fundamentally persuasion and persuasion happens to be not a science, but an art." - William Bernbach #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    Because we women just adore the smell of your cigarette smoke. #vintageads #advertising #ads #badvertising pic.twitter.com/hjCnngiL    
    
    
    .@crupicrupicrupi http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/keep-your-kitten-or-puppy-becoming-town-whore-140559 …    
    
    
    Drinking a beer, wish I had this. http://ow.ly/b3Oxw  #beer #advertising #qrcode @guinness    
    
    
    Top execs are placing more importance on #socialmedia, according to @IBM study http://buff.ly/LaPQCj  @adweek @petersontee    
    
    
    These cover images make you go "whoa." http://ow.ly/b4FY9  @adweek @time @bw #magazines #controversial @newyorker @nymag @rollingstone    
    
    
    @HuffingtonPost Not in it?    
    
    
    @ivanlajara Thought you might have been moonlighting    
    
    
    @ivanlajara Chirp chirp. You mean to say you didn't? If I see you in the lobby of my office building, the jig is up (AOL HQ)    
    
    
    @ivanlajara Better than under it.    
    
    
    Are we totally desensitized? Do any of these "controversial" magazine covers offend you? http://ow.ly/b4UzB  #controversial #magazines    
    
    
    These magazine cover images got the country talking. http://shar.es/qfxmX  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Only the U.S is "mom enough" apparently... check out different TIME covers distributed to different countries! http://buff.ly/Kx7Rvy  @Time    
    
    
    .@pubexec Thanks for the pick-up! Which cover is your favorite? http://www.pubexec.com/aggregatedcontent/the-10-most-controversial-mag-covers-recently-published?e=rmccabe%40baumpub.com …    
    
    
    @lgranatstein Somehow, some way, @TIME has to top the #boob cover. Best guess as to how?    
    
    
    Breaking #agency news from @adweek's @noleary: http://ow.ly/b552z  @MEC #breakingnews    
    
    
    Unrelated to #advertising, but had to share. #einstein #truth pic.twitter.com/PGbUWaqh    
    
    
    @FastStat Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @diginnow Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @KevinJSmith Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @David_Hall Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    Wow. #News designed 4 the @TMZ set. I can feel the nation's collective IQ rising slightly. http://buff.ly/KaeMeS  @samthielman @adweek    
    
    
    New #meme I found - Advertising Professor. #interactive #advertising #twitter #LOL pic.twitter.com/Bi50r9bm    
    
    
    Controversial magazine covers. Are they really that offensive? You tell me: http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  #controversy #magazines #momenough    
    
    
    More from the #Advertising Professor #meme! pic.twitter.com/PMZJfO22    
    
    
    The magazine covers that shocked you: Are they really that offensive? http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  #controversy #magazines #momenough    
    
    
    Analysts say the $FB share price should really have been around $10, and @MorganStanley may have botched the #IPO http://ow.ly/b66Tu     
    
    
    Breaking news about a #shakeup at @AOL http://ow.ly/b6c5W  via @adweek's @digitalshields #breaking    
    
    
    The #broadcasters vs. @Aero arguments will be hashed out in court next week. @adweek @katyonthehill    
    
    
    Now with a link! The #broadcasters vs. @Aero arguments will be hashed out in court next week. @Adweek @KatyontheHill http://ow.ly/b6mkK     
    
    
    Captain Morgan gets a bold makeover. Hope they don't change their delicious rum! http://buff.ly/KfYoKj  @CaptainMorgan @uppereastrob @adweek    
    
    
    Oprah's new best buddy: Arianna Huffington. @HuffingtonPost will feature @OWNTV content. http://buff.ly/KLEIQW  #partnerships @ariannahuff    
    
    
    I think my money's still on Hova. http://buff.ly/KLHCVU  @cwarzel @adweek @s_c_    
    
    
    First it was @SKECHERSUSA and bullshit ShapeUps #ads. Now @Pomwonderful's claims are #lies too? Is nothing sacred? http://buff.ly/KLJaPC     
    
    
    Ridiculous email of the day in my @Adweek inbox. Unsolicited free training to make a profit of $600 per day! #spam pic.twitter.com/TMjsReGY    
    
    
    Time for some more #madmen catch-up!    
    
    
    Is the implied #sex on this cover too hot for newsstands? See more shocking #magazine images here: http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  pic.twitter.com/bDRizcT2    
    
    
    Don Draper needs earplugs for a Beatles concert? #noway #madmen #ihopedondraperisdeadanddoesnthavetoknowjustinbieberexists    
    
    
    Bored? Need to jazz your grey matter? How about a look at @Wikipedia's history of #advertising? Papyrus started it all. http://buff.ly/KLIrOu     
    
    
    We all know @Instagram is popular, but will the concept work for video? @Adweek looks @Viddy and others. http://buff.ly/KLH2r0  @petersontee    
    
    
    Does this offend you? See more of the most shocking covers on newsstands recently. http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  #controversial pic.twitter.com/8decJtou    
    
    
    Yet another quip from the Advertising Professor #meme. #advertising #LOL pic.twitter.com/rnbYy1tw    
    
    
    "What you say in advertising is more important than how you say it." - @David_Ogilvy #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    @A_Rot The one where Roger has to get Joan an abortion. Agreed that this season is one of the best (so far). #madmen    
    
    
    This has already been going on, but I'm creeped out nonetheless. http://ow.ly/b7FuO  @adweek @petersontee    
    
    
    Magazine turn to shock value http://shar.es/qs1lz  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Nice job @cwarzel - think we have the next Letterman on our hands here! http://ow.ly/b7P7q  @IWNY #internetweek    
    
    
    Breaking news: @Marriott launched creative review http://ow.ly/b7SlL  via @adweek's @mcmains1965 #breakingnews    
    
    
    Did the bodypaint burqa take it too far? More #controversial #magazine covers here: http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  pic.twitter.com/LUwNeYJR    
    
    
    Hey @emilysteele, congratulations on the new gig at the @FinancialTimes!    
    
    
    Agency @Coudal Partners decided to purge its client list—completely. Sound crazy? Read all about it: http://buff.ly/KdOU3q  @adweek @nudd    
    
    
    Are ladies gonna respond positively to being called #chubbies? Good thinking, Lane Bryant! @LaneBryantWNY #vintage #ads pic.twitter.com/e6Xe0TqK    
    
    
    Breaking: @NBC Universal is exploring a buyback of http://MSNBC.com . http://ow.ly/b8lJ9  via @adweek's @digitalshields #breakingnews    
    
    
    .@npamani I'd love to be the @foursquare mayor of a couch. Sounds pleasant.    
    
    
    @JBFlint Why? What happened? (Sorry - on deadline myself; haven't been trolling the Web enough today)    
    
    
    .@jbflint Oh no. Do the paper's puppetmasters think they're going to increase their relevance by pubbing just 3 times a week? #printisdead    
    
    
    Bizarre email of the day in my @Adweek inbox: "Maybe our souls belong to each other." OK, Suzzy. #spam #soulmates pic.twitter.com/6gILfw5B    
    
    
        
    
    
    Breaking: Analyst says @dishnetwork Auto Hop suit just a gimmick to set precedent. http://ow.ly/b8AmK  @Adweek @crupicrupicrupi...    
    
    
    Bonus #bilingual bizarre email in today's @Adweek inbox: "I am willing to be your friend." #spam #ihaveenoughfriends pic.twitter.com/YWd8xWwY    
    
    
    Does this image offend you? More here: http://buff.ly/Ka5kYU  #controversy #controversial pic.twitter.com/YPSd9exH    
    
    
    "Advertising is the life of trade." - Calvin Coolidge #advertising #quotes #presidents    
    
    
    Regardless of what they say, sometimes it's a necessary evil. Isn't it? #memes #advertising pic.twitter.com/FkzdgQ63    
    
    
    What do you think of this list of effective #advertising techniques? http://buff.ly/KdOv0P  #marketing #tips    
    
    
    #Followfriday #advertising agency edition! @LeoBurnett @Draftfcb @72andsunny @mcgarrybowen @groupmworldwide @hugeinc @jwtinside @digitas #FF    
    
    
    @agencypja trying my damnedest to #disengage from technology. Til monday at least!    
    
    
    Really into #advertising #memes this week. This one is "Creative Director." pic.twitter.com/2xDEeSsF    
    
    
    Pup looks like he had a long week. RT @wiedenkennedy: TGIF. #wkdogs http://instagr.am/p/LDmDbXQn3G/  #squee #TGIF    
    
    
    Imitation is the sincerest form of flattery, no? My #controversial covers slideshow: http://ow.ly/b9D7k . Theirs: http://ow.ly/b9Da3     
    
    
    Thanks for the shoutout, Levi! Have a great holiday! RT @levimcconnell: Highly recommended #FF @AdweekMelissa !    
    
    
    I was once that woman. RT @mashable: Grown Woman Watches 'Star Wars' for the First Time [LIVE BLOG] http://on.mash.to/LNdmLJ  #StarWarsVirgin    
    
    
    MT @crupicrupicrupi: Broadcast's 10 p.m. time slot is dead. In 2011-12 season, not one 10 o'clock show cracked top 30: http://www.adweek.com/news/television/ghost-town-vanishing-10-pm-broadcast-drama-140772 …    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 15 retweets received, 1 new listings, 25 new followers, 14 mentions. Via: http://20ft.net/p     
    
    
    Will Obama turn to @Reddit's "Ask Me Anything" forum to get votes? http://adweek.it/KOlEzX     
    
    
    In this bizarre spot for a social-event site, a man headbutts his wife: http://adweek.it/MVAcQs  Thx to @jezebel for the pickup #badvertising    
    
    
    Who doesn't check their sources? RT @huffpostmedia: Fox News chief makes false attack on New York Times http://huff.to/LBU6Lk     
    
    
    Charles Schwab tries to talk us out of that kobe beef burger topped with foie gras. I kind of still want the burger. http://buff.ly/LbWGZc     
    
    
    @ivanlajara Upsetting, though the fact that I often get "kobe beef balls" at my local Chinese joint didn't make it likely to be real anyway.    
    
    
    Ha MT @thedailybeast: John Edwards's Twitter provides public timeline of his life around time of his baby's conception http://thebea.st/M3mHiy     
    
    
    Have you met this Creative Director? A few of you might've. #meme pic.twitter.com/s9v63BgL    
    
    
    Much ado about nothing? Or is this a case of #badvertising? http://ow.ly/becF7     
    
    
    In the age of #Twitter, longform still lives! http://buff.ly/JyZPFW  @adweek @emmabazilian    
    
    
    Facebook's stumble continues as options prices soar: http://buff.ly/Jz0kzE  #FacebookIPO    
    
    
    Is Charlie Sheen rebrandable at this point? Or is he too typecast? http://buff.ly/Jz03wL  @charliesheen @adweek    
    
    
    Dwight Schrute would have been a ruthless adman. #meme #advertising pic.twitter.com/qyY9MQ1P    
    
    
    While you enjoy a delicious breakfast, vote for the most #tasteless ad! http://buff.ly/Lc60fF  @adweek @nudd #badvertising    
    
    
    Made my day! RT @cwarzel: Make Your Own 'Amercia' Mittstagram http://shar.es/qdSL0  via @Adweek @mittromney #amercia    
    
    
    Here's to preserving fuckups for posterity! RT @gizmodo: Read every politician's deleted tweets http://gizmo.do/fHwQ     
    
    
    Being that I haven't yet watched #MadMen Season 5—just finished 4—I wish people would stop talking abt Peggy Olson quitting. #spoilers #argh    
    
    
    Seven Behavioral Ad Companies Called Out http://goo.gl/fb/kRbr4  #onlineprivacy #advertising    
    
    
    .@mcaldecutt I'm hoping to find new eps online soon. Adweek covers Mad Men (duh), & all my friends watch it, so I can't avoid the spoilers.    
    
    
    MT @mccann_ny: Average time an investor holds a share of US stock? A) 4.8 yrs B) 1.5 yrs C) 5 mos D) 22 secs. Yep: D. http://huff.to/y8s9AM     
    
    
    .@GooglePlus goes local with @GooglePlaces. Am I really starting to like Plus? http://ow.ly/bhbHw  @adweek @petersontee    
    
    
    I always just thought of it as a fun app. Not a career: Instagrammers in Demand by Major Brands http://shar.es/qw3RP  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Although @AdvertisingWeek isn't until October, a "disruptive" tech showcase is already out there: http://buff.ly/JPumR4  #advertising    
    
    
    @KatharineKellar Hey - welcome to twitter!    
    
    
    @crupicrupicrupi You better not be talking about me!    
    
    
    Auto Hop lawsuit stalls - sister Prometheus Global Media pub The Hollywood Reporter has the exclusive: http://ow.ly/bhsND  @THR #autohop    
    
    
    @KariMcCullough Hi Kari!    
    
    
    My latest joy of the Web is @Politwoops, but does the tweet tracker violate #Twitter terms of service? http://buff.ly/L1yR6a  @adweek @cwarzel    
    
    
    The #upfront marketplace is officially out of hibernation: http://buff.ly/JCDkji  @adweek @crupicrupicrupi    
    
    
    Some promotions at McCann: http://buff.ly/JCCF1q  @adweek @noleary #advertising    
    
    
    Worst email received in my Adweek inbox during the holiday weekend (I'm catching up). My hotel's reputation sucks? pic.twitter.com/hBmF1i09    
    
    
    New @Microsoft Windows 8 browser default opts consumers out of targeted ads: http://ow.ly/biob0  @adweek @katyonthehill #breakingnews    
    
    
    Watch what you Facebook "like" - this guy became a Sponsored Story ad by jokingly posting about a 55-gallon drum of lube:...    
    
    
    Breaking News: Another top exec at an Omnicom agency heads for the @NBA: http://ow.ly/biCgs  @adweek @noleary    
    
    
    Busy busy Friday with an @Adweek exclusive: @KBSP will be launching a campaign to brand #diesel for German #auto brands:...    
    
    
    Guess who made the most hated #ad in Britain's history? (Hint: it comes in a bucket): http://ow.ly/biMnS  #badvertising    
    
    
    Happy Follow Friday (journo edition)! @romenesko @emilybell @niemanlab @paleycenter @ivanlajara @ftmedia @jmimpoco #followfriday #FF    
    
    
    @ivanlajara You *kind of* deserve it, IMO. You tend toward curating bizarrely cool news for your feed, so some roses here I toss at its feet    
    
    
    Ad of the day = dog in @Diesel sunglasses. Happy Friday!  http://ow.ly/bj3i0  #ads #squee    
    
    
    "The light is your friend." RT @huffingtonpost: WATCH: Little boy gives his parents sex advice  http://huff.to/KxoGJk     
    
    
    Are you a high-rolling major brand? Might want a category-exclusive spot on a new ferris wheel on the Vegas strip: http://adweek.it/KEFWMM     
    
    
    Agreed - thanks for sharing! RT @cwarzel: a pretty wild chart: http://tmblr.co/ZyJzTyMkdeHp  #iheartinfographics #barackobama #stocks    
    
    
    I gave @tonymedia +K about Branding on @klout. http://klout.com/plusk/gave/67554001408473758/56295000107784293/96934558?n=tw&v=plusk_gave …    
    
    
    The Breast of Advertising: Sex sells (@Time is the latest to prove that), but can it also repel? http://shar.es/qIUCv  via @sharethis    
    
    
    It better count as OT. RT @mccann_ny: CEO of AIG says retirement age might creep up to 80. Next: Working after you die. http://bloom.bg/LdwGLf     
    
    
    @mccannkz At least no need for health insurance benefits. And I hear vacation spots in hell are nice and tropical.    
    
    
    ...and many more! MT @4as: Today the 4A's celebrates its 95th birthday! Congratulations and thanks to everyone http://fb.me/29iTaKLDT     
    
    
    Nice, Ron. You've obvs been waiting to use that. RT @rodson68: Breastvertising (.Y.) | http://shar.es/q8v29     
    
    
    .@Amex knows you even better than you think: http://shar.es/qDNP3  via @adweek    
    
    
    Branding beyond the #MadMen formula of bourbon and a pack of smokes, via @forbes: http://bit.ly/M6ilqU     
    
    
    What do you think? Will @Facebook fade out? RT @iwantmedia: Facebook Will Disappear in 5 to 8 Years: Analyst http://bit.ly/KKc8yT     
    
    
    @katyzack I think the hard part is deciding what our national trending topic should be?    
    
    
    Airtime: Chatroulette without all the dicks? http://ow.ly/bnuAh  @adweek @petersontee    
    
    
    Looks like @Facebook is finally monetizing #mobile (maybe should have rolled this out pre-IPO): http://ow.ly/bnGSd  @adweek #facebookIPO...    
    
    
    If you ask #history, it would say @GM's closed-wallet #upfront stance is a BIG goof.  http://ow.ly/bnMiS  #breaking @Adweek...    
    
    
    Is #Facebook just background music? RT @socialmedia411: Facebook 'Boring'? 1 in 3 Users Are Tuning It Out: http://cnet.co/KuyDJP     
    
    
    It seems @Kraftfoods and #MiracleWhip not only can bring us all together, but save us! http://buff.ly/L1o2T4  @adweek #exclusive #breaking    
    
    
    "Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising." - Mark Twain #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    Pic is the upside to the feline #obesity epidemic. http://buff.ly/L1oKjn  #NotThatKindOfFatCat #advertising #lolcat pic.twitter.com/3m7IdBNW    
    
    
    'Atlantic,' 'Economist' Duke It Out for Elites http://shar.es/qU9Qm  via @adweek @lmoses    
    
    
    Web designer in love with @GameOfThrones starts wave of ppl asking @HBO to offer sub rates with hashtag #TakeMyMoneyHBO:...    
    
    
    #RIP Ray Bradbury    
    
    
    Effective. RT @draftfcb @bestads: Falling #outdoor billboard via @DraftFCBUlka demonstrates how seatbelts save lives. http://ow.ly/boPwL     
    
    
    Don't let us down, Tim! RT @kbsp_agency Schooling @petersontee on #BeatBolt @Adweek High score so far! pic.twitter.com/wo1k7aNl    
    
    
    Because of a "love for ornithology?"RT @adweek: Twitter Rebrands, Modifies Logo http://goo.gl/fb/I3HS3  @Adweek @cwarzel    
    
    
    Lovely zoetrope spins a global story for Fuze Tea. http://adweek.it/JXkvaD  #AdOfTheDay @FUZEBeverage @215mccann    
    
    
    This new @Tide detergent viral video will fucking blow your mind! http://adweek.it/Lm7Qyu  @adweek @TheOnion #tidepower    
    
    
    Boobvertising? @Jezebel looks at the well-endowed arguments in @Adweek's cover feature "The Breast of Advertising:" http://buff.ly/LtQBFV     
    
    
    "To swear off making mistakes is very easy. All you have to do is swear off having ideas." - Leo Burnett @LeoBurnett #advertising #quotes    
    
    
    As far as detergent brands go, @Tide is fucking awesome and totally relevant! http://buff.ly/LtQ6vp  @TheOnion #tidepower    
    
    
    Hotel ads, 1954 vs. 2011. Have they become more or less hospitable over the years? http://adweek.it/LuHkBB  #Perspective    
    
    
    It seems @Facebook isn't the only company w/ mobile news this week: @Google melds @Adwords & @Admob: http://ow.ly/bqu0Z  #breaking @Adweek    
    
    
    Interesting talk w @JWT_Worldwide China chief Tom Doctoroff on the impact of #Communism on #China commerce & consumers: http://ow.ly/bqzLp     
    
    
    @digitalshields Time is suspended in the airport. You can have Combos AND a beer if you want.    
    
    
    Also answering polls while driving? RT @consumerist: One In Three Teens Admits To Texting Or E-Mailing While Driving http://bit.ly/LywB4W     
    
    
    This should be a series. God knows there's enough material. RT @randylewiskemp: 10 signs of a horrendous press release http://bit.ly/L6uSH5     
    
    
    Does it work? @Google spoofs science videos in its latest #GooglePlay ad: http://goo.gl/fb/iqUp1  @adweek @adfreak    
    
    
    If you eat a dinner from Colgate, can you skip brushing your teeth? http://ow.ly/bshZh  @colgatesmile @mental_floss #gross #branding #ads    
    
    
    Follow Friday colleagues edition: @cwarzel @crupicrupicrupi @lgranatstein @tonymedia @digimatized @rodson68 @jcoopernyc @adweekemma @nudd FF    
    
    
    @cwarzel That is the only way they can get anyone to watch that movie #conspiracy    
    
    
    B/c some ppl are just dumb? RT @consumerist: Why Is Big Corn Continuing To Run 'Corn Sugar' Ads Even After FDA Denial http://bit.ly/MoVzII     
    
    
    Hey @PokJournal, I see you copied portions of @DailyFreeman's DCC budget hike story. Do the right thing and apologize & delete the story!!!    
    
    
    The Zombie Apocalypse: Now on YouTube! http://goo.gl/fb/E9ni2  #zombieapocalypse #zombies #TheEndIsNigh    
    
    
    With 1,900 top-level #Web domains being snapped up, should the marketplace be bracing for a bonanza or a bust? http://adweek.it/MC2Jtw     
    
    
    BREAKING: Struggling @USATODAY just lost its ad sales chief: http://ow.ly/bvi5r  @adweek @lmoses #breakingnews    
    
    
    Are the new interactive tombstones taking the #QRcode craze a little too far? http://ow.ly/bvifx  #news #dying    
    
    
    “Good #advertising does not just circulate information. It penetrates the public mind with desires and belief.” - Leo Burnett #quotes    
    
    
    Gone are the days when dads played the #parenting sidelines (or only dealt out discipline): http://adweek.it/KgGucS  @adweek #MrMom #dadpower    
    
    
    Punishment for early adoption. RT @lanceulanoff: Trying to digest the fact that my iPad 1 is ineligible for iOS 6. #thishurts #wwdc    
    
    
    A glimpse behind the curtain of the @mittromney presidential campaign: http://ow.ly/bvDer  @adweek @cwarzel #pdf12    
    
    
    @ObviouslyBen Back atcha! Pleasure to virtually meet you :)    
    
    
    "Reveal Day" (June 13) is NOT a magician's event, but rather the unveiling of nearly 2,000 new top-level Web domains: http://buff.ly/N1tj1o     
    
    
    In today's "Ad of the Day," #MadMen's copywriter Ginsberg stars in a short film at 35,000 feet, for @Virgin: http://buff.ly/LEA4Vo  @adfreak    
    
    
    Really?! #DonDraper is an iconic TV dad? http://buff.ly/LEzxCG     
    
    
    "Truth in advertising." #LOL #memes pic.twitter.com/cytFAKm1    
    
    
    Will #Foursquare succeed in becoming an essential tool, rather than just a fun check-in game? http://buff.ly/Mnstcf  @adweek    
    
    
    MT @robbiesenbach: Is the cover letter dead? http://bit.ly/KpmzFh  I hope not. For writers and communicators, they are a critical test.    
    
    
    A #xenophobic ad from #Egypt, now pulled by the government, cautions against talking to foreigners: http://ow.ly/bwLE9     
    
    
    .@smeevolutions Did you see that @Adweek actually featured the New World ads in its mag this week? Check it out: http://adweek.it/KAEbfI     
    
    
    One reader was not so #lucky: @LuckyMag printed a terrible false quote and had the cojones to defend this practice: http://ow.ly/bx6hi     
    
    
    Wanna win $60 grand? All you need to do is make an awesome #fantasyfootball app: http://ow.ly/bxdT2  @cbssports    
    
    
    @smeevolutions I totally see the "non-pretentious Calvin Klein ad" angle... I wonder if that's what they were going for?    
    
    
    So happy that #Spokeo has to pay $800k to the @FTC for messing with people's lives. Should pay addtl fine for stalking: http://ow.ly/bxeAA     
    
    
    Although @Adweek showed Dads' roles have changed (http://adweek.it/KgGucS ), http://Insure.com  thinks its the 50s: http://ow.ly/bxhUn     
    
    
    What makes a perfect news tweet? Hint: This isn't one. http://ow.ly/bxm9J     
    
    
    Those cheap car rentals are apparently lucrative. RT @adweek: A Growing #Zipcar Contacts Creative Shops http://goo.gl/fb/IOW8g     
    
    
    #Upfronts nearing end: @ABC finishes its deal-making: http://ow.ly/bxx3n  @adweek #breakingnews    
    
    
    BREAKING: @CNBC and @Yahoo Finance teaming up to provide branded content: http://ow.ly/bxx7b  @adweek @cwarzel #breakingnews    
    
    
    BREAKING: @GoDaddy actually hires an agency: http://ow.ly/by1nR  @DeutschInc @adweek #breakingnews    
    
    
    BREAKING: What will the new top-level Internet #domains be? Reveal Day is here! (.sex and .sucks are on the list) http://ow.ly/byhpA     
    
    
    I think I'm one of many unaware this show existed. RIP? RT @adweek: CNN Cancels 'John King USA' http://goo.gl/fb/oc1CQ     
    
    
    @dylanbyers Everything.    
    
    
    Why is the U.K. National Lottery the subject of @Adweek's "Ad of the Day?" See for yourself: http://goo.gl/fb/TQhr4     
    
    
    Will @StephenAtHome be the next person to take over @Sweden's #Twitter account? http://ow.ly/bySAr  #ColbertNation    
    
    
    Seems a little pricey for a one-time connection. RT @mashable: Share Your Wi-Fi, Get Rewarded http://on.mash.to/KE7zDA     
    
    
    Neat idea by @DesignByIkea: Posters that fold into actual moving boxes! http://ow.ly/bAhO0  #moving #awesome    
    
    
    @amedio3k I would guess that answer is a "yes." Glad to see someone has guts!    
    
    
    @amedio3k Hiding behind anon means they're aware of their stupidity/offensiveness. If they truly believed their words, it wouldn't be anon.    
    
    
    Unrelated to advertising MT @breakingnews: US FDA says some Korean seafood may have been exposed to human fecal waste, norovirus @Reuters    
    
    
    Today's @Adweek Ad of the Day involves security camera footage, stolen kisses and a sweet drink http://ow.ly/bAEKV  @cocacola @landianews    
    
    
    Another self-regulatory step for the #advertising industry. Is it enough to root out bad actors? http://goo.gl/fb/Eamur  @adweek @katyonthehill    
    
    
    Doesn't #Facebook already know enough about me? MT @mryouth: Do you have your number on #Facebook? Why or why not? http://rww.to/LMwpUC     
    
    
    @mryouth And to you! How is Mr Youth celebrating the looming and expectedly gorgeous summer weekend?    
    
    
    It's almost time to get vocal about the love you have for your dad! Get in the mood with 10 #ads starring great #dads: http://ow.ly/bBFJZ     
    
    
    @mryouth I'm guessing this party is indoors, 8 hrs in length and completely dry? If not, where's my invite?! Also #JustSayin    
    
    
    Wondering what's the deal with that Donuts company that wants all the generic #internet #domains? @Adweek has the scoop http://ow.ly/bBQG9     
    
    
    Resignations always after 5 pm on Friday! MT @techcrunch: Top Facebook Exec Bret Taylor Out, More Departures May Follow http://tcrn.ch/LhptQH     
    
    
    Leaving @Facebook to launch a #startup? Maybe he's still pissed about the #IPO? http://ow.ly/bC89R  @adweek @petersontee    
    
    
    BeastTV and @Adweek's own Lucia Moses take a look at the #media week that was: http://ow.ly/bC8Fc  @thedailybeast @newsweek    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 17 retweets received, 3 new listings, 38 new followers, 8 mentions. Via: http://20ft.net/p     
    
    
    The personal costs of website comment moderation: http://adweek.it/NJ97R0  @adweek    
    
    
    Health advocates say @NestleNesquik co-branded candy with @GirlScouts violates pledge to not market candy to kids: http://adweek.it/LAxEmx     
    
    
    A guy finds the confidence to be cool with his ex in @WiedenKennedy's first @stridegum #ad: http://adweek.it/LBRi1x     
    
    
    If you're lucky & get a job at @NewYorker, you might want to put in the time necessary to write original articles. http://ow.ly/bGvMx ...    
    
    
    Premiere of @GlassHouseABC (alleged Big Brother ripoff) didn't even do as well as a @TwoHalfMen_CBS rerun: http://adweek.it/Mc0CJZ  @adweek    
    
    
    Leveraging @LinkedIn - #Professional #networking site adds #targeting options: http://adweek.it/LfnHAa     
    
    
    Hey, kids! @Claritin is DEFINITELY not candy! Don't be fooled: http://ow.ly/bI7ZW  @adweek @FTC #badvertising #deceptive #advertising    
    
    
    Finally! Something indicates mobile isn't wantonly murdering #print! http://ow.ly/bI9xo  #printisdead #newspapers #journalism #news #media    
    
    
    Dealing with clients while casting a commercial? @DrewMagary has been there: http://ow.ly/bIitx  @gawker #advertising    
    
    
    Two politicians, sitting in a tree... http://goo.gl/fb/lgQsH     
    
    
    It's no wonder this @Benetton ad won a #CannesLions Grand Prix. It certainly catches the eye! http://buff.ly/KNDeqT  pic.twitter.com/vUVBwPtl    
    
    
    "Great minds discuss ideas. Average minds discuss events. Small minds discuss people." -Eleanor Roosevelt #quotes    
    
    
    Although #controversial, the @Sweden Twitter account won a #CannesLions Grand Prix along w/ @Nike: http://buff.ly/KNDrum  pic.twitter.com/kcJm9Enx    
    
    
    BREAKING: Supreme Court bounces #broadcast indecency rule back to @FCC: http://ow.ly/bJJiD  @adweek @katyonthehill #profanity #breakingnews    
    
    
    Thank god, @Twitter is back. WTF happened? I feel like I got hit over the head.    
    
    
    up down up down up down... @twitter, I'm feeling nauseous...    
    
    
    An interview with a lawyer who argued the broadcast indecency case in the Supreme Court: Carter Phillips http://goo.gl/fb/Gvlu4     
    
    
    @kristinedearing What's your favorite article in this week's issue? Anything in particular grab your eye?    
    
    
    No better way to end your Friday than with the top 5 on-air newsroom meltdowns! http://ow.ly/bLQLw  #thenewsroom #journalism #news    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 2 retweets received, 7 new followers, 2 mentions. Via: http://20ft.net/p     
    
    
    There's a new channel catching #tweens' attention and it's not on TV: http://adweek.it/LvJLGO  @YouTube @awesomenesstv    
    
    
    #Thunder and #lightning outside @Adweek's East Village headquarters. Taking cover in the warm, soothing glow of my Mac. #weather #nyc    
    
    
    #Thunder and #lightning outside Adweek's headquarters. Taking cover in the warm, soothing glow of my Mac. New York City East Village NYC    
    
    
    @kristinedearing What did you like about the @StrideGum spot?    
    
    
    Gawker Media blog @Jezebel's lead story right now is a breakdown of @Adweek's feature on the marketing power of #Tweens http://ow.ly/bOLnV     
    
    
    How dare this @JustinBieber kid compare himself to the #Beatles? The Beatles didn't need to hock perfume: http://goo.gl/fb/mxhrh  #crazy    
    
    
    What brand did Levon Helm sue in 2004 over an unauthorized use of "The Weight?" See if you're right: http://adweek.it/QcCytm     
    
    
    My week on twitter: 4 retweets received, 1 mentions. Via: http://20ft.net/p     
    
    
    I'm back from vacation! What did I miss?    
    
    
    .@dfnewscat ... when there's breaking news that MUST BE REPORTED IMMEDIATELY. http://ow.ly/c3Qab     
    
    
    Wondering what's new with http://Will.i.am ? He wants to know how to get to @sesamestreet! http://adweek.it/NUv8ai  @iamwill @bep    
    
    
    Scheduled tweets are not working AT ALL - don't post and don't appear in the publisher. When will it be fixed? @hootsuite @Hootsuite_help    
    
    
    @HootSuite_Help When will this be fixed? My company relies on my ability to schedule tweets properly. Should I switch to @tweetdeck?    
    
    
    @JenRemsik @hootsuite_help You're lucky you're seeing them at all! No scheduled tweets showing or posting at all for most ppl.    
    
    
    .@tristanbailey Ha! I never thought it could mean that, but it certainly sounds social, doesn't it? However, #tween refers to preteens.    
    
    
    @GrassrootsIntl @HootSuite_Help Having same problem. When will this be fixed?    
    
    
    .@tristanbailey I guess he's a pre-tween (pre-pre-teen)?? Good luck with that!    
    
    
    Of course they would say that. MT @romenesko: Study: 60% of tablet owners say reading mobile news is better than print. http://bit.ly/NbwgYJ     
    
    
    @MadSocial You're not alone. Try tweeting to @hootsuite_help so they're aware that you are also affected.    
    
    
    @llihcruhc @hootsuite Yeah, this is a known problem. Everyone who has a job requiring scheduled posts (who use hootsuite) is screwed today.    
    
    
    @madsocial No problem! We're all twitterpated about this stupid glitch today. Happy Monday indeed!    
    
    
    Law enforcement agencies can willy-nilly read your text msgs and access your location! http://ow.ly/c6YpV  @adweek @katyonthehill #privacy    
    
    
    @KateNasser @Hootsuite Kate, tweet to @Hootsuite_help with issues... I don't think they ever check the posts in Help Desk.    
    
    
    @KatyontheHill @MarkeyMemo Katy, your link to the memo doesn't work here. Link to your story perhaps? Unsettling news for sexters for sure!    
    
    
    Tea bag quote reflects @Adweek theme of #philanthropy :) "Your greatness is not what you have, it's what you give." http://ow.ly/c76uR     
    
    
    Note from the mayor of @NYC: PRT @mikebloomberg: Proud to be among @Adweek’s “The Givers” portfolio of philanthropists: http://bit.ly/Lbj21f     
    
    
    .@Hootsuite @Hootsuite_help Now scheduled posts are showing, but they're not posting- they just disappear. Can we get an ETA on a fix now?    
    
    
    The Real Battle for @Olympics Gold - Athletes seek their own piece of the action amid games' corporate takeover: http://adweek.it/LESNBN     
    
    
    ...is thankful today for a functioning @Hootsuite.    
    
    
    .@AXE jumps on the #blockbuster bandwagon that is #Ted. http://ow.ly/c8Vwq  @whattedsaid    
    
    
    Broadcasters File With Court to Halt Online Political File Rule: http://ow.ly/c9qh8  @FCC @NABtweets #politicaladvertising    
    
    
    @slowhoneybee @adweek @katyonthehill True for the target of the investigation but not for "bystanders" who used same cell tower, for example    
    
    
    @slowhoneybee @adweek @katyonthehill That's how it should be, but the NYT report cited in the story indicates that's not always the case.    
    
    
    @slowhoneybee @adweek @katyonthehill Closing such loopholes would serve to strengthen the validity of L.E. investigations, not vice versa.    
    
    
    @crupicrupicrupi What an atrocity - haven't they seen 'The Fantastic Mr. Fox?'    
    
    
    @amedio3k Hootsuite's just one I'm used to, and I pay for Pro. Do expect consistent service for the price, so might be eying Seesmic soon!    
    
    
    @tacobell It feels too early to be craving a seven-layer burrito... thanks a lot.    
    
    
    .@DesignTaxi auctions off its 2008 Mini Coupe after losing account, proceeds going to charity: http://adweek.it/NlGmrG     
    
    
    Good news for #booze brands: @Twitter now has an age verifier to weed out the minors: http://ow.ly/ccBMY  #drinking #marketing...    
    
    
    @8kevinsheen6 Only works for booze... minors on Twitter can still get stoned to their hearts' content.    
    
    
    @angelicaraven Curious... do adult profiles perform some kind of age check in DMs since there's no tool (yet)? Must be a pain to track.    
    
    
    Today's a big news day for @CocaCola - got 2 stories in @Adweek! http://ow.ly/ccFPO  and http://ow.ly/ccFSa  #soda #marketing    
    
    
    @nathandarnold @CocaCola @Adweek Sounds like someone's tweeting from the other side of the pond? #popiscrappymusic #soda    
    
    
    Why the hell would @Reuters' social media maven give up @Twitter? @Adweek asks him: http://ow.ly/ce8JJ  #socialmedia #quittingtwitter    
    
    
    Cookie Monster Records #Viral Video, Wants You to 'Share It Maybe': http://adweek.it/LUANPh  @muppetcentral @stcookie    
    
    
    "Facebook could easily have a face print for one out of every 20 people on the planet." http://ow.ly/cgPyA  #scary @facebook #privacy    
    
    
    Can you spot what's wrong with these @Colgate ads? http://adweek.it/NvwbiC     
    
    
    .@BurgerKing scrambling after feet-in-lettuce photo hits web. http://adweek.it/LXA58v  (via @AdFreak)    
    
    
    Thunder in the environs of Adweek HQ in the East Village. #stormwatch #thunderbuddies4life    
    
    
    Oooh, now there's hail!    
    
    
    I'm already tired of P&G's 'Moms' #Olympics commercial. I think it was just on 5 times in a 2 hr period.    
    
    
    First sign of impending News Corp split: Rupert Murdoch resigns from boards http://ow.ly/cpaUR  @NWScorp @Adweek @RupertMurdoch    
    
    
    Tired of super-meaningful #Olympics ads? @OldSpice just wants to make you laugh. http://adweek.it/MA4V5c  #AdOfTheDay    
    
    
    Yes, ladies can code too! @Adweek looks at the struggle of women seeking seed funding in the tech world http://adweek.it/NN7QaY  #sexism    
    
    
    This is already happening in NYC. RT @consumerist: Are Retail Trucks The Next Wave Of Shopping? http://bit.ly/OvUjk0     
    
    
    Graphically pleasing breakdown of ad spending for @BarackObama and @MittRomney in battleground states: http://adweek.it/LNqK1E  #infographic    
    
    
    Fisher Nuts launched a baseball sweepstakes 4 months ago that has raised more than $15k for charity http://adweek.it/LNxSeo  @fishernutsbrand    
    
    
    .@Gawker media's blog @Jezebel reads @Adweek! Picked up @Adfreak's story about some #nasty ads: http://ow.ly/cuzob  &...    
    
    
    @SpareRoomHwood @hugeinc HUGE BALLS is really your league name? That takes some, um, guts.    
    
    
    Everyone who ever dated a douchebag just got served. Someone married Kim Jong Il's son. #northkorea    
    
    
    @ivanlajara I refuse    
    
    
    My week on twitter: 1 retweets received, 2 new listings, 12 new followers. Via: http://20ft.net/p     
    
    
    Hey, @hootsuite @hootsuite_help WTF is going on with scheduled Tweets (again)? I'm done: gonna delete my "pro" account and head to @Seesmic.    
    
    
    @shesallwrite I'm feeling same. Sneezed a million times between yesterday and today. There's something especially cruel about summer colds.    
    
    
    Are the candidates turning this campaign into a case of one-appsmanship?http://adweek.it/QaOihK  @MittRomney @BarackObama #Amercia    
    
    
    A billboard that enjoys the nightlife as much as its target market! http://adweek.it/RAqQw2     
    
    
    Trojan misses a great social media opportunity with its vibrator giveaway: http://adweek.it/O7ckZ1  @trojanconnects @sextoynews @cheine    
    
    
    10 ads that killed dubstep. (it needed to die) http://adweek.it/RHMTzb  via @AdFreak @adweek    
    
    
    .@mtn_dew asks the Internet to name its new soda. The Internet chooses "Diabeetus." http://adweek.it/RL5ydA     
    
    
    Trying this with reporters = not smart. RT @huffpostmedia: Biden aides reportedly tried to edit pool reports http://huff.to/PnLCN8     
    
    
    Make or break news. @Mediabistro @AllTwtr #mbchats    
    
    
    .@Mediabistro @NewYorkObserver The primary author. #mbchats    
    
    
    .@ActiveMktg glad you enjoyed it!    
    
    
    Did you happen to see the best 10 commercials of the week for last week? http://ow.ly/dhUX8     
    
    
    Are you still playing #DrawSomething? Get a job with it! Whaaa? http://adweek.it/NA3Tmq     
    
    
    .@AlyssaAnndria I'd just get rid of it...the FTC just sued the company for false advertising, citing deceptive health claims.    
    
    
    @Visada_Myleti Just FYI, the FTC sued the company today for false advertising. Says the program doesn't work.    
    
    
    No, Your Baby Can't Read. Yes, you are gullible. #FTC #deceptiveads http://adweek.it/NUi1Nf     
    
    
    #VoteSuicide? MT @MTV: NEW #VMA CATEGORY! Tweet #VoteBieber #VoteOneDirection #VoteCarlyRae for Most Shareworthy http://at.mtv.com/e45     
    
    
    @amedio3k Ugh, I just saw your posts on FB. Sounds like he's not completely playing by the rules; use that to your advantage. Hang in there!    
    
    
    @shashib Is Karl Rove a corporation yet? He follows back; it's fun to get an email saying "Karl Rove is following you."    
    
    
    @amedio3k It really sounds like you're gonna be just fine. Big mistake to try to evict a bunch of people at once - every case is different.    
    
    
    A deal with the devil? @espn closes on massive new @MLB rights deal for $666 million. http://adweek.it/Ou0YjA     
    
    
    @ProfNet Too much ancillary noise #ConnectChat    
    
    
        
    
    
    @tweetsbyjmiller Glad to hear it! Thanks!    
    
    
    I hate to think I'm so predictable, but yes, I check my email on my phone during TV shows (and while surfing the Web): http://adweek.it/QT2sQw     
    
    
    #breakingnews from @Adweek's @cwarzel... @BarackObama is about to be available on #reddit's "Ask me Anything" forum!! Story to follow...#AMA    
    
    
    Are you tuning in to hear what @BarackObama is saying to folks on Reddit? http://ow.ly/dkrbp     
    
    
    You mean I don't get to watch the red-butted monkeys handily remove the weatherstripping from my car anymore? http://bit.ly/S1qobr     
    
    
    Stunned and stalled by the glut of digital election tools? @Adweek rounded up the best for ya: http://ow.ly/dlAEL  @cwarzel #election2012    
    
    
    More bad news coming for $FB investors? RT @eMarketer eMarketer Reduces Estimates for Facebook Revenues - http://bit.ly/OuUUpd     
    
    
    Interesting @slate story about the upside of #hurricanes like #Isaac - an economic boost! http://ow.ly/dm0qd     
    
    
    Here are this week's best commercials! http://adweek.it/NGHcNt  @adweek #best #ads    
    
    
    Didn't know 'like' fraud was a thing now. RT @clickz: Facebook Cracks Down on Like Fraud http://bit.ly/NOyKvN     
    
    
    @Mediabistro @alltwtr Yes. Permitting paid followers dilutes the perceived influence of popular profiles that use no such tactics. #mbchats    
    
    
    Thanks @jezebel, for the (somewhat delayed) pickup! Art director #fail = 'Whore' mag: http://ow.ly/duDoC  via @adweek...    
    
    
    Unless you close your eyes & chug! MT @time: Study says glass shape determines how fast you drink your beer http://ti.me/NSbbSU     
    
    
    A pretty flight attendant demonstrates #condom use in @adweek's list of the 10 best commercials of the week. http://adweek.it/POsAxt     
    
    
    Wow. Gonna have to say, #askjulius is the #fail of the day. http://adweek.it/NmNaI7  #katyonthehill @adweek @FCC    
    
    
    More on the @FCC Twitter #fail! @Adweek's own @katyonthehill gets a shoutout from @BloombergNews: http://ow.ly/dDGOI     
    
    
    .@JessicaSimpson, you're doing great! Here's her @WeightWatchers spot and the other 10 best commercials of the week! http://adweek.it/TSoOIE     
    
    
    @huffingtonpost This has been making the rounds, but it's not really that notable. Slow news week makes me want to cry, too.    
    
    
    AFG& is an advertising agency. I checked the name several times, but the ampersand on the end is still making me twitch! @afgnow #editing    
    
    
    Double #Deadline Day! Not only does our venerable mag go to the printer, but it's also my last day as a "single" woman! #gettinhitched #yay    
    
    
    Jennifer Aniston @jenniferani proves tabloids right with a tummy full of triplets! Here are @adweek's best TV spots http://adweek.it/QI080J     
    
    
    What do headbangers and Toyotas have in common? http://adweek.it/V02iN2  @scionAV @adweek    
    
    
    All your kids are dying young... because it's the Top 10 Commercials of the Week: http://adweek.it/Q7ZxpS  #top10 #advertising    
    
    
    An @adweek writer on #awix RT @cwarzel Content. Content. Funnel. Mobile. Mobile. Engagement. Content. Storytelling. Hashtag. Mobile. Content    
    
    
    @ivanlajara Sounds dirty, but not as dirty as googling.    
    
    
    @ivanlajara Thanks! It's definitely been a busy few months!    
    
    
    I find the idea of a brand leading the country alarming. You? http://adweek.it/Wg7XhH     
    
    
    .@thesmarmybum I agree with you, but still, it was just selling a candidate & his ideals, not that plus smartphones and tablets.    
    
    
    Yet another reason you should keep your young children away from @justinbieber: http://adweek.it/QFvB36     
    
    
    Dead @BarackObama grandma joke from @KitchenAidUSA: Asleep at the wheel or just plain insensitive? http://adweek.it/UGoHMq     
    
    
    .@SamuelLJackson wants you to "Wake the fuck up!" and check out these Top 10 spots of the week! http://adweek.it/OHlL5r  #ads #top10 #tv    
    
    
    @donita_dazed If this is true, I'm due to ask some fucked-up questions.    
    
    
    Obama ad ruffles Big Bird's feathers. Sesame Workshop says it's nonpartisan. http://adweek.it/QR2Rrh  #Election2012 #PBS    
    
    
    Big fan of broadcast TV? You're probably an old coot. http://adweek.it/R99tyh  @adweek @crupicrupicrupi    
    
    
    Chicago ad man uses his "junk" to get auto industry clients: http://adweek.it/OWQsnb  @adweek    
    
    
    Adweek rides along as @reddit takes its open-Internet battle into the real world, in a cross-country campaign: http://adweek.it/Xd7ZY0     
    
    
    @jbruin Congrats! Still waiting on mine to ship... bought it Sept. 29. Feels like forever ago.    
    
    
    Facebook giving some brands a sneak peek at fans' other likes. Testing new data offering for priority marketers. http://adweek.it/S1lNnd     
    
    
    @Mediabistro @alltwtr You certainly can't tell from Twitter's stream.    
    
    
    @nottheword I thought this was something they just started testing. Have they done it for some brands already?    
    
    
    .@BradPitt and @JeffGoldblum star in this week's Ads of the Week! http://adweek.it/RKUlHT     
    
    
    The surprisingly large #brony herd decided to trot all over @adweek's Hot List, so we gave @mylittlepony its own poll! http://adweek.it/XUNYWO     
    
    
    TV news reporters getting blown away and swept away by #Sandy! http://adweek.it/QSEbgR  #hurricanesandy    
    
    
    @cwarzel I'm in Astoria, had the same problem earlier. Now I just can't stream.    
    
    
    Nate Silver appears to have correctly predicted all 50 states. http://adweek.it/WA5dzA  #Election2012 @fivethirtyeight    
    
    
    Anyone in the NYC/NJ/LI areas ready for #Noreaster #Athena? Cuz here she comes. http://huff.to/YIPj4a     
    
    
    Nick Brien was surprised & angry to find out he was being canned by McCann [updated]: http://adweek.it/RCVZNq  @adweek @noleary @mccann_wg    
    
    
    .@atomictango I believe you are correct, and from what we hear, some more related McCannings (n) may be on the horizon...    
    
    
    .@spikejones @redbull We made this one of Adweek's Ads of the Day: http://adweek.it/PSkQ1f     
    
    
    .@publicisusa Surprising, no? Or have we exceeded our saturation point with faceless communication?    
    
    
    .@tristens Yes. Google employees do.    
    
    
    Mall of America uses #sms program to help #BlackFriday shoppers find their cars in the gigantic lot: http://ow.ly/fs0Nc  @uppereastrob    
    
    
    Vote now for the best commercial of the year! http://ow.ly/fAkLv  #top10 #commercials #ads    
    
    
    And many more hours left to shop RT @mashbusiness: Cyber Monday Sales Are up 24.1% So Far  http://on.mash.to/10Z0NAK     
    
    
    So... how was Cyber Monday (so far)? Check out @adweek's gallery! http://ow.ly/fAJCd  #cybermonday #blackfriday    
    
    
    The best #ads this week feature @NBA players and @SnoopLion. Check out @Adweek's Top 10! http://bit.ly/QStgaS     
    
    
    Nooooo.... Bazooka Joe comics are no more! Now it's just gum!    
    
    
    Disgusted by the @nypost cover today - #DOOMED? How about try to help the poor guy and maybe he wouldn't be! http://ow.ly/fOs2F     
    
    
    .@Adweek's @cwarzel rounds up some of the backlash targeted at the @nypost's "snuff" cover: http://bit.ly/Udkb6T     
    
    
    @amedio3k Hard to believe, isn't it? Shame on the editors who approved the use of the photo! Photog's explanation is bullshit too.    
    
    
    @amedio3k Questionable judgment doesn't discriminate btw pubs, but is a requirement at @nypost. At least they didn't argue "news value."    
    
    
    @amedio3k And even if you can't lift him, you can yell for him to lay down btw the tracks. They're designed to let the train pass over you!    
    
    
    @amedio3k taking a picture is simply NOT what you do in this situation!    
    
    
    If u don't vote on @facebook's governance changes, new privacy policies will be decided behind closed doors. Vote here: http://bit.ly/TDVfZY     
    
    
    tip @mediagazer Adweek was all over this NewsBeast layoffs breaking news story: http://bit.ly/TK89Ws     
    
    
    Wow! @AdweekMelissa has reached 700 followers! See more stats at http://twtr.to/jWvR     
    
    
    Great first week of #2013 for some #brands - here were the best #commercials: http://bit.ly/RwyJTU     
    
    
    Getting this for sure, as my brain is increasingly unreliable. http://mashable.com/2013/01/04/never-lose-keys-or-kids-again/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Want to know the latest and greatest from #CES2013? Check out @Adweek's live coverage: http://www.adweek.com/ces-2013     
    
    
    .@bmorrissey Wait, so they're pitching for sxsw at CES? Seems a little gun-jumpy.    
    
    
    .@bogusky Article says diet soda is the culprit, but I would assume the rolls of extra fat induced by sugared stuff is similarly depressing.    
    
    
    @bmorrissey Ah, makes more sense. Though not much more.    
    
    
    OK, @TMobile wins the prize for the #worst customer service EVER. I am SO glad I canceled my account! #FAIL    
    
    
    @juliancole I don't see that i did. Happy to take a look. Maybe spelled my LN wrong? Lots of people do. Melissa.hoffmann@adweek.com.    
    
    
    Top 10 Commercials of the Week: Jan. 11-18 http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/top-10-commercials-week-jan-11-18-146621 … via @sharethis    
    
    
    We aren't the only ones, @prhomkow http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bdR01DsmQe0&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite Congrats on the pregnancy!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Big @bestbuy #oops http://consumerist.com/2013/01/22/best-buy-posts-50-off-coupon-on-internet-forgets-how-internet-works/ …    
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite I knew this lil one was a boy - makes total sense :) Good luck at the appt next week and be sure to update us!    
    
    
    @prhomkow http://bit.ly/XB1Br5  #LOL    
    
    
        
    
    
    @crupicrupicrupi They've got a tree sloth doing my job?! I'd be offended, but it looks like it's one of my relatives (choloepus hoffmanni)    
    
    
    @crupicrupicrupi How am I supposed to compete with that?? I guess I'll just have to steal Nudd's space. Or share @michaelburgi's cube...    
    
    
    #equality. That is all.    
    
    
    Thinking about the hardworking reporters, editors and staff subject to layoffs and other BS at my hometown paper @dailyfreeman. #printisdead    
    
    
    @stuartenyt Same thing here in Astoria. Have we checked on North Korea lately? It doesn't sound like mere weather!    
    
    
    @digitalshields You're not sorry.    
    
    
    OK, I'm convinced. http://gothamist.com/2013/04/12/please_work_from_home_today.php … via @gothamist    
    
    
    Wow! @AdweekMelissa has reached 800 followers! See more stats at http://twtr.to/aZVc     
    
    
    upcoming, synergy, glocal, actually, curate, artisanal
#5WordsIHateToHear #editors #journalism    
    
    
    @AdweekMelissa Oops, that's 6. A few more: brogrammer, historical, trending, bipartisan, ping #needsediting #editors #5WordsIHatetoHear    
    
    
    Are first kisses better if the girl tastes like @tacobell? http://adweek.it/YX2obC     
    
    
    Beer should be like domestic violence? Not a well thought-out billboard ad. http://bit.ly/1369vSm  #badvertising #no #ads #advertising #fail    
    
    
    Today's reason @justinbieber sucks... after going to visit Anne Frank's house, says he hopes she would have been a #belieber. #no #RIP    
    
    
    This is neat RT @NiemanLab The New Yorker looks at income inequality in NYC as tracked along the city's subway lines. http://nie.mn/ZoriAn     
    
    
    A touching campaign from @Dove that shows how we really see ourselves. http://adweek.it/11a3rlc  @adweek @nudd    
    
    
    Has anyone seen Walter White lately? MT @TerryMoran: BREAKING @ABC has learned a 2nd letter sent to the Senate has tested positive for ricin    
    
    
    Kmart sh--s its pants in this week's top 10 commercials (it's not what you think) http://adweek.it/VvDo9h  #LOL #ads    
    
    
    Read about Silk Road last year & totally not surprised to see #bitcoin finally make its way into the headlines.    
    
    
    Cool, @AdweekMelissa is about to reach 800 tweets! See the rest of the stats http://twtr.to/faRy     
    
    
    Teens are @CocaCola's target market in the new AHHH initiative, and #mobile is how it's gonna get them. http://adweek.it/ZGI7qt     
    
    
    "You can't swing a dead cat without grazing a digital distributor who is expanding into original content creation." http://adweek.it/ZGGLvS     
    
    
    .@EvianWater goes young, @JaguarUSA goes long and @AXE goes all the way in Adweek's top commercials of the week.  http://www.adweek.com/news-gallery/advertising-branding/adweeks-top-10-commercials-week-april-19-26-148933 …    
    
    
    How a phony tweet and computer trades sank stocks (from @AP) http://apne.ws/13wNHvI     
    
    
    @kenrearley And, tasty as I can attest. @direcTV just mailed me and my colleagues some slim jims.    
    
    
    @kenrearley I think I'd take the ribs over the slim jims, but I also got a small bottle of @chivas in my little package. Not complaining!    
    
    
    @kenrearley Also came with a jock strap. Some may say @directv mistargeted, but I say slim jims, chivas, jock strap... that's a party!    
    
    
        
    
    
    .@yahoo's Marissa Mayer <3s advertising. http://adweek.it/Yjvx2b     
    
    
    @soulkhan The soft spot is great for dips and sauces.    
    
    
    Man #murdered and stuffed down ad agency toilet... or at least it looks that way on @Google Street View. http://adweek.it/YbNfT8  @adfreak    
    
    
    Why everything you THINK you know about @AmericanIdol is dead wrong: http://adweek.it/158ss8c     
    
    
    Mountain Dew wisely decides to pull 'most racist commercial in history': http://adweek.it/12V6YY1  #badvertising @mtn_dew @Chris_Heine    
    
    
    .@Digiday Anyone who's drunk texted knows "connecting with friends while drinking" can be dangerous.    
    
    
    OK, I live in @NYC and almost nothing shocks me... except seeing a guy in Union Square waving a sign that says 'Long Live Kim Jong Un' - WTF    
    
    
    Brands like @mtn_dew want to be edgy, but often #FAIL http://adweek.it/ZWSlDj     
    
    
    Off topic, but this is hilarious. #kids http://www.buzzfeed.com/mattbellassai/the-creepiest-things-a-child-has-ever-said-to-a-parent … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    The @instagram #hashtag thing gets annoying, but allowing users to tag brands is a great idea http://adweek.it/12wkyhN     
    
    
    Guy makes an animated short film out of his #drunk wife telling a lame joke. Happy Friday! http://bit.ly/134WSok     
    
    
    Love is in the air - and in this week's best ads: http://adweek.it/YrS5h9  @adweek @IBM @CocaCola @Microsoft @Newcastle @CallofDuty @hm #ads    
    
    
    MT @Chris_Heine: @ChampsSports, @ColeHaan and @CalvinKlein are giving precious space to @Tumblr via @adweek    
    
    
    @DylanByers Everything.    
    
    
        
    
    
    H&M has a "normal" looking woman model its beachwear. Good job, since normal women are likely your target audience. http://adweek.it/16euOlE     
    
    
    Gimmicky but a great idea nonetheless: A child abuse ad only visible to children. @GreySpain @adfreak http://adweek.it/16NkMrG     
    
    
    .@NNanwa Do "normal" women in Canada all look like Beyonce?! Or is H&M only targeting heavier American women? @hm Hmmmm    
    
    
    @NNanwa @hm I think "normal" is referring to body type only. Hoping H&M goes with your idea, big & tall northern dudes need swimsuits too!    
    
    
    So, @DrPhil's suing @Gawker over #copyright. Why hasn't he been sued 4 impersonating a medical professional? http://j.mp/10DbRAx  via @THR    
    
    
    April showers are running late, they were relying on the #NYC #subway system. @MTAinsider    
    
    
    #rain + #work = Chinese food delivery    
    
    
    Worst twitter feed ever! MT @nudd Agency behind Dove beauty sketches continues with diapers that tweet when peed in. http://adweek.it/10iJMi9     
    
    
    No question that the husband and I are @vw's target audience here. http://adweek.it/13hXHu5  @nudd #babies #parenting #newborns #help    
    
    
    Finally, the @AP updated its social media guidelines & offered best practices for reporting stories like #Boston. http://adweek.it/YDHjoh     
    
    
    #Cleveland's Charles Ramsey to @AndersonCooper: "bro" and "It's about the cojones." So many quotables. #hero #riveted http://bit.ly/YFPAba     
    
    
    .@VW Was I riveted to the spot? Yes. Did it resonate w/ this mom of a newborn? Yes. Did I run out on my lunch break and buy a car? No.    
    
    
    Good on you, @cocacola. http://adweek.it/13ixUC8     
    
    
    Ha! @McDonalds tries to make #Shamrocking a thing, but it already has a pretty dirty meaning in the @UrbanDictionary. http://bit.ly/AteACy     
    
    
    .@lexikon1 @studentactivism Bad idea for students' credit. Just like w/federal tax protests, the protesters are the only ones that get hurt.    
    
    
    Headed to @carnegiehall soon for a great night of Rachmaninoff and Ravel. Ooo and the tix were a steal. Yay!    
    
    
    How @HillHoliday's Karen Kaplan rose from receptionist to CEO: http://adweek.it/13tOS0j     
    
    
    Bakers Burn Their Brand to a Crisp in Epic Facebook Meltdown http://adweek.it/129r0MP     
    
    
    California wine goes great with... sex? drugs? both? http://adweek.it/17uyTT3     
    
    
    .@Amazon's partnership with @LaserShip seems to be a flop. The shipper loses packages, doesn't respond to inquiries. http://www.yelp.com/biz/lasership-woburn-2 …    
    
    
    @brknglassstudio They lost my package and refused to respond to several inquiries. Very shady company. I am now boycotting @Amazon.    
    
    
    @LSShipAssist @LaserShip Already got a refund from @Amazon. Maybe you should start answering customer inquiries or actually deliver pkgs.    
    
    
    @brknglassstudio Unfortunately, it was a 3rd-party seller. So I got a refund from @Amazon. But not ordering again @LaserShip is out.    
    
    
    'Subway Etiquette' is an oxymoron. MT @Gothamist On your commute, don't break any of these subway etiquette rules http://gothamist.com/2013/05/15/etiquette_week_subway.php … … …    
    
    
    For a billboard that pulls water from air & makes it potable, Mayo Draftfcb takes @Adweek Project Isaac Gravity award http://adweek.it/YXwNbF     
    
    
    @zombieparmesan Nah, it's more like winning a Purple Heart.    
    
    
    .@GettyImages skillfully weaves 105 video clips into one beautiful story in @adweek's Ad of the Day http://adweek.it/16kVyBD  #advertising    
    
    
    OK, this beautiful 85-second spot for @GettyImages almost made me cry. http://adweek.it/16kVyBD  @Adweek #emotional #advertising #ads    
    
    
    It takes a lot to get ahead in #advertising, but it's not worth dying over! WTF re: China work death rate http://bit.ly/14sG8Xe  Via @Gawker    
    
    
    @NKArch Great idea, but how does this work for super slow/super fast readers?    
    
    
    #IfYouKnowMeYouKnowThat I don't usually bother with trending hashtags.    
    
    
    @NKArch Ok for the faster eyes, but would be kind of shitty for slower-than-avg readers, who would likely end up missing the ending.    
    
    
    @digimatized @snooki stop thinking about picking your nose, it's gross    
    
    
    @NKArch Agreed. Taste is big variable. Give me the right book & I'd prob zip thru. But I often have to reread the same boring graf 20 times.    
    
    
    Poop humor—it never fails. Fitness company video goes viral thanks to dude taking a dump in the background: http://adweek.it/12Ef5qC  @adfreak    
    
    
    @mashable I remember that 867-5309 story from a couple years ago... why the rehash?    
    
    
    .@Twitter and @foursquare partner with @NCMNews to ID #trending #movie topics: http://adweek.it/10PUDWG     
    
    
    The best #ads of the week, from @hot_wheels, @KAYAK, @Oreo, @GettyImages, @VW, @OldSpice, @SLODownWine http://adweek.it/12gpQPo  #advertising    
    
    
    .@_mediaspace @ThinkDevGrow This innovative campaign just won @Adweek's first Project Isaac Gravity Award.    
    
    
    @adland To share your content with @Google employees? I know they use it!    
    
    
    .@Adweek gets a shout-out on @Jezebel for its coverage of the new, racy @SLODownWines ads. http://jezebel.com/heres-wine-to-enjoy-whilst-high-and-or-during-your-nex-507773696 …    
    
    
    Yes? YES! RT @deliverydotcom Hey #NYC did you know you can order liquor online for delivery? Now you do. #GetDelivery http://dlvry.cm/YY9Jaf     
    
    
    @Chris_Heine RT @LenKendall Has Adweek written this up as an article yet? pic.twitter.com/9hBuALvHoI    
    
    
    Adweek picks the five best and five worst new TV shows: http://adweek.it/160lbb3     
    
    
    Advertising student ships his pants to @Kmart's agency, lands internship. http://adweek.it/14K22p3  #winning    
    
    
    Beardvertising: Sell space on yo' hairy face. http://adweek.it/13I66qT  @adweek #beards #hipsters #guerillamarketing #gorillamarketing    
    
    
    A scripted drama about an unscripted reality show? The entertainment snake has begun swallowing its tail. http://adweek.it/ZaZaTQ  #Siberia    
    
    
    Dude on 8th street in a suit just broke into an air drum solo. #onlyinnewyork #nyc    
    
    
    I do love me some alliteration. & a good discussion. Digital Dignitaries Debate Display's Death http://adweek.it/13IGfPA  @digitalshields    
    
    
    @shaneadams Getting an alert that this link has been flagged as unsafe...    
    
    
        
    
    
    First #ad I've seen directly referencing @MikeBloomberg's controversial attempted #soda ban. #onlyinnewyork pic.twitter.com/FwrH8jNOxs    
    
    
    @digimatized You need some hashtags there, pal.    
    
    
    @MarketingBuddy Hey Buddy. Nice to "meet" you. What kind of marketing do you get into?    
    
    
    Happy Hump Day from @GEICO! http://adweek.it/11bAZoa  via @adfreak    
    
    
    @samthielman No. Yes?!    
    
    
    @samthielman I am still finding it very difficult to come to terms with the fact this show is going to end. #WHY #GOD #WHY    
    
    
    Can you sympathize? 38 Signs You’ve Been in Advertising Agencies Too Long | Digiday http://www.digiday.com/agencies/38-signs-youve-been-in-advertising-agencies-too-long/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    @MarketingBuddy Indeed! 10 yrs ago, back in the early Web ad days, could you even imagine this world? What were you doing then?    
    
    
    @samthielman I'm going to need a couple bereavement days come September.    
    
    
    @LPT No effing way. Really? #wth    
    
    
    @prhomkow look: RT @benphoster5m Electric car maker Tesla to pay off $465M in federal loans  http://j.mp/14yuP0n     
    
    
    @LPT that's no small difference! But they do have their redeeming qualities...    
    
    
    The @AP hosted a @reddit #AMA about social media best practices: http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/1eu546/we_are_aps_social_media_editors_and_we_want_to/ … #journalism #IamA #AP    
    
    
    Ha!—@kmart & @Draftfcb try to recreate the success of 'Ship My Pants' ad with sequel 'Big Gas Savings' http://adweek.it/10pxHJc  #biggassavings    
    
    
    @ICEFactorBrand Hi! On pre-holiday deadline, but if u have some info for me to peruse when possible, plz send to melissa.hoffmann@adweek.com    
    
    
    Oh boy! I may need my thunder buddy. #thunder #lightning and severe #weather in the East Village #NYC    
    
    
    .@draftfcb goes with another almost-profane gag in @kmart's latest ad. http://adweek.it/10pxHJc  #biggassavings    
    
    
    Embattled @ProcterGamble CEO out, replaced by his predecessor. Shades of  @jcpenney. http://adweek.it/13PP7iX     
    
    
    Which 10 big brands are expected to die this year? @jcpenney, @LivingSocial and @MarthaStewart's #mag made the list. http://adweek.it/124jZBX     
    
    
    @digitalshields http://gothamist.com/2013/05/17/something_or_someone_has_already_po.php …    
    
    
    @callmemochelle @TheBigDebowski The big problem with @BestBuy is that people window-shop there and then buy from @amazon.    
    
    
    Oh boy. @jcpenney puts up billboard with tea kettle that looks like Hitler: http://adweek.it/19jA47d  via @AdFreak #thisthinglookslikethatthing    
    
    
    Sigh. Really? A #trending topic #hashtag is misspelled. Guess #spelling is @twitter's weakness! #tweatyourweakness #FAIL    
    
    
    The @Waze deal has a ways to go: The hot map app is still on the table after @apple, @facebook pass on $1B deal. http://adweek.it/ZektBH     
    
    
    @digimatized I'm endorsing you on LinkedIn for chin hairs.    
    
    
    @digimatized They're the only real stand-outs.    
    
    
    @digimatized Hopefully this is what your side-face needs to finally grow some balls and step it up.    
    
    
    @eddiebrannan @MoveOn I am having a similar issue after buying tickets to @carnegiehall. Stop calling my cell phone!! #spam #telemarketing    
    
    
    @eddiebrannan @MoveOn @carnegiehall I was tricked by the fact that they have a 212 exchange! I'm used to ignoring calls w/wacky area codes.    
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite Blame the fetus.    
    
    
    Here's what broadcast TV is planning to do to try to not suck this summer: http://adweek.it/18IiHM9  via @Adweek @crupicrupicrupi    
    
    
    Here's a sneak peek at the Store of the Future, via @Adweek. http://adweek.it/11hwTGq     
    
    
    According to this #infographic, women like e-readers more than men do. Format, or b/c we're just bigger readers? http://adweek.it/11DEOwT     
    
    
    Just got this pitch from @boostmobile's PR. I refuse to watch an ad about "junk dunking" or tea-bagging. #gross #no pic.twitter.com/EnaZ2uvLaF    
    
    
    This poop monster is just adorable! @Adweek's Ad of the Day is "Swaddle Master" via @samsungmobileUS. http://adweek.it/17pcEOI  #cute #babies    
    
    
    @AdamMoran @lizwah I finally mastered the swaddle, just in time for my newborn to start hating being swaddled. #thebabywinsagain #fail    
    
    
    A 15-year-old's suicide attempt really shouldn't be considered news.    
    
    
    @TBWAChiatLA You'd think they'd know better. Just too many jokes to be made there.    
    
    
    LOVE this @72andSunny spot for @SamsungMobile. Being a new parent is tough stuff! http://adweek.it/17pcEOI     
    
    
    Online ad #scams suck. Here are some alleged perpetrators: http://adweek.it/16VJqrk     
    
    
        
    
    
    Stuck on an N/Q Astoria #NYC train with a random toddler that is mewling like a cat in heat.    
    
    
    Flip-flops are dangerous when among hundreds of people being herded like cattle toward a single subway staircase. #NYC @GrandCentralNYC    
    
    
    #Advertising is totally #gay. http://adweek.it/19HKpLT     
    
    
    No, @ConanOBrien, tell us how you REALLY feel. http://adweek.it/141E9Zb  #canneslions    
    
    
    Watching @yankees v. @dodgers? Be sure to tune into baseball legend #VinScully's first-ever tweetcast of the game. http://adweek.it/11z6iVS     
    
    
    Today in Scary: Facebook reports privacy breach. http://adweek.it/184G8BO  #privacy #facebook @katyonthehill    
    
    
    @digimatized This is a question that has haunted me for years.    
    
    
    @Mindshare_NA @Dove @MediaPost What a great win for @OgilvyBrasil! @Adweek broke this story days ago... http://adweek.it/19qQrOj  #CannesLions    
    
    
    This cleaning product has a dirty, dirty mouth. http://adweek.it/19qdKv6  @CLRcleaners #branding    
    
    
    A @USGAO report says the @FCC should quit filing so many damn reports. http://adweek.it/149SLHq  #bureaucracy #government @KatyontheHill    
    
    
    So, @Hostess_Snacks is bringing #Twinkies back! Rare for a brand to pull a Lazarus act... now what? http://adweek.it/19ycLsU  @UpperEastRob    
    
    
    Best way to get me to ignore your email: Throw around terms like "synergy" and "marketing solutions." Zzzzzzz    
    
    
    Other ways to get me to ignore your email: Tell me how big a fan you are, then send the email to a blind list; or CC our entire masthead.    
    
    
    This is cool: a map that shows the top #brand in each of the 50 states. http://adweek.it/18ibRzi     
    
    
    Acquisition makes @TribuneCo the biggest TV station operator in the country. http://adweek.it/129DORu     
    
    
    @freelancecomJob FYI, this listing tries to get content for free from writers, under the guise of a "test": http://www.freelance.com/en/mission/view/dbf92bec3f8a87fd013f8fae33df3867 …    
    
    
    .@Groupon gets into the high-end restaurant reservation game. http://adweek.it/10uDX5K     
    
    
    @digimatized Wow! Paula Deen got a new job so quickly!    
    
    
    Kenny G is the ultimate buzzkill in new @SNICKERS ad. http://adweek.it/13jo7ib     
    
    
    Don't fall asleep on the train... the windows may soon vibrate advertising directly into your skulls!! http://adweek.it/18ra23h  #scary    
    
    
    What's your state's biggest #beer or #booze brand? Check out this awesome map! http://adweek.it/12bO4sy  via @AdFreak    
    
    
    Who's making #LA the #hot place to be right now? These 10 agencies and producers: http://adweek.it/10I04FN  via @adweek    
    
    
    @Mister_Wang The awards show has to be no more than six seconds long.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Eating caprese salad with my fingers on the N train in Astoria because major freakin subway delays make me #hungry.    
    
    
    Outside @adweek's offices this morning. #borntobun pic.twitter.com/nR8pfkT4uX    
    
    
    Ok, this is how you get my attention in an email. #sex #party #sexparty #pitches #goodPR #emailoftheday pic.twitter.com/ZhKALISyHU    
    
    
    Well, @McCann_WW, maybe we're just not on the right lists... after all, "It is really fun and a great way to meet other cool people."    
    
    
    The @tribunecompany is following in @nwscorp's footsteps in splitting its #newspapers and #broadcast assets: http://adweek.it/186QXR9     
    
    
    @RobLongert Hi there! I read your email; if we pursue a follow-up on the Lat Am trend, I will surely consider your source. Thanks!    
    
    
    As a mom of a NYC baby, I'm freaked by the "harmless" gas released by the govt into the subways. Just test the already-present diesel fumes!    
    
    
    Why is my MetroCard red? Here's the answer: http://adweek.it/18NRA53  #NYC @mta    
    
    
    This #NeverWet stuff... truly #awesome innovation in waterproofing or #awful #toxic chemical lie? You be the judge. http://adweek.it/15eBufm     
    
    
    Adweek is extending the deadline for submissions to this year's Media Plan of the Year until Thurs! Go to http://www.mediaplanoftheyear.com  to enter.    
    
    
    Surprise, surprise: Saturday night's miscarriage of justice meant big ratings for @CNN and @FoxNews. http://adweek.it/13m9C62  #TrayvonMartin    
    
    
    .@BBDONY has reportedly won #Viagra's business away from @mcgarrybowen. http://adweek.it/15iGbVB  @pfizer    
    
    
    Today in crap emails: @chrisbrown wants to help a sick kid, because... #PR. Presumably he will help the kid "beat" it pic.twitter.com/DdTyX2ca4B    
    
    
    How do you feel about #marijuana advertising? Is it any worse than the myriad #pharma ads on the tube and in print? http://adweek.it/14WscG9     
    
    
    Follow-up to yesterday's crap email: @chrisbrown is no longer helping a sick kid. #jerks #sorrykid #BeatCancer pic.twitter.com/m7v4PRWo3C    
    
    
    Stores are boycotting @RollingStone because of its #Boston Bomber cover. http://adweek.it/14eIeNF     
    
    
    Surprise! Ads above the fold are actually NOT more viewable—they just cost more.  http://adweek.it/18xsIiH  via @Adweek    
    
    
    ESPN, Turner Sports Pulling Out of Nascar http://adweek.it/136ZQou     
    
    
        
    
    
    I have to admit that @HIMYM_CBS is a bit of a guilty pleasure for me, and its promo did not disappoint. http://adweek.it/1374dzW     
    
    
    Kelly Cutrone's response to @Dove Real Beauty campaign: Consumers don't like fat people in #ads. True? http://adweek.it/13Ef6h1  @peoplesrev    
    
    
    Check out this terrific analysis & slideshow of potential conflicts of the @PublicisGroupe-@OmnicomMediaGrp merger: http://adweek.it/16zagRf     
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out Japan's favorite ad family, the Whites: http://adweek.it/169kMlY  #Japan    
    
    
    Finally, @Twitter has decided to get in on the D.C. #lobbying game. http://adweek.it/18pfVuy  via @adweek @KatyontheHill    
    
    
        
    
    
    You mean a @CoorsLight can won't cure cancer? http://adweek.it/1cxS5mb     
    
    
    My Favo(u)rite Magazine benefits ailing industry vet Bob Newman: http://adweek.it/14ESQnQ     
    
    
    Is this the most hilarious and depressing @JELLO ad ever?! http://adweek.it/1eJhMfm  via @adweek @AdFreak    
    
    
    Whoa, @CocaCola comes out in defense of its use of Aspartame. I would've thought they'd just be silent on that one. http://adweek.it/17NvBpg     
    
    
    Today's Ad of the Day is a heartrending PSA about texting and driving. #worthit to watch. http://adweek.it/16PZoAI     
    
    
    .@DuckDynastyAE: More addictive than quack? Ratings would say yes. http://adweek.it/128eb8d  via @Adweek    
    
    
    .@bustle CEO opens mouth, inserts foot. Tone-deaf comments called "dispiriting." Can the launch be saved? http://adweek.it/17sSzmP     
    
    
    Adweek speaks with social startup @rallyverse about its @LinkedIn deal & how brands can tune out social media noise. http://adweek.it/13Gf6zK     
    
    
    .@doran_joe Happy to provide our readers w/info about such a quickly evolving area of the biz. Plz alert me to any @Rallyverse developments!    
    
    
    .@doran_joe @Rallyverse  As a fellow fan of the Rooster sauce, I will certainly be keeping my eye on that yellow guy.    
    
    
    #Seattle police are awesome, handing out free @Doritos (and safe #marijuana use tips) to stoners at #hempfest. http://adweek.it/18FP51D     
    
    
        
    
    
    .@LawrenceBland This is quite sexist.    
    
    
    Summer sickness stinks.    
    
    
    @LawrenceBland Of course, and I know you're joking... but in my opinion, just not a particularly enlightened or funny joke this time.    
    
    
    @LawrenceBland This is not a reflection on you personally or your general content, though!    
    
    
    Apparently, @YouTube is where shoppers are doing all their research, not @amazon. http://adweek.it/15iMt5M  #interesting #trending    
    
    
    @LawrenceBland Hey, none of us is perfect, on or off social media! Happy to see that you can appreciate my opinion. Have a great day :)    
    
    
    Be careful what you say about @TacoBell in Canada—they may etch your rants on tacos and force them down your throat. http://adweek.it/14DrFKD     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Back from #vacation ... what did I miss?    
    
    
    Make sure your media favorites get to the top of @Adweek's #HOTLIST by voting (as often as you want) in this poll: http://bit.ly/19ZkAoz     
    
    
    I think I'm going to stick with my assertion that @paxdickinson is not a real person and/or was paid. So many targets looks amateurish.    
    
    
    I just found out that @onedirection has a song called "Best Song Ever" and the irony is physically painful.    
    
    
    The @FEMA has a new #terrorism #PSA aimed at kids. http://bit.ly/17VfN5r     
    
    
    @JulienBIT Likewise, Julien. Story coming soon!    
    
    
    With smoking banned everywhere, @bandsintown is turning phones into virtual @zippo lighters to hold up at concerts. http://bit.ly/14LNZ1r     
    
    
    @lorilewis "windowlickers" is now my favorite compound word.    
    
    
    Did you serve in the #military and are now looking for a job in #advertising? Here's the agency for you: http://bit.ly/18NMFgK  #veterans    
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite I see you had your baby! He's perfect! Congrats.    
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite *SHE (the blue threw me off)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @samanthamcgarry Thankfully, it was under an hour, but it was a fellow passenger who saved us (he pulled a kill switch and got doors open)    
    
    
    @sonadelite Yeah, we were freed in under an hour (by a fellow passenger, though... the bldg/emergency services was taking too long)    
    
    
    .@soulkhan #BestRapper    
    
    
    Is the #tagline dead? This marketer says it is. http://bit.ly/16ggrvO     
    
    
        
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite Your little one also kind of reminds me of my own little baby (who happens to be a boy)! pic.twitter.com/BlmtXNmlxO    
    
    
        
    
    
    It has been brought to my attention that I was not the only editor trapped in an elevator yesterday. http://nymag.com/thecut/2013/09/desperate-editors-climbing-out-of-stuck-elevator.html …    
    
    
    Meet @Adweek's new video columnist, @laurenreeves, as she dissects the latest work from @TheMissAP. http://bit.ly/15moDLh     
    
    
    @ShesAllWrite 7 months old, already! It seems like just yesterday he looked like this... pic.twitter.com/8I8tJCNfum    
    
    
    @jimpoco Congrats on the new gig!    
    
    
    Has @chipotletweets struck gold again with a new campaign featuring Fiona Apple and a gaming angle? http://bit.ly/1aESItG     
    
    
    Today's terrible #email #pitch: "We saw your coverage of twerking and wanted to share a video response we made to the @jimmykimmel skit."    
    
    
    @Velocidi Interesting counterpoint, but Voice is a column, not an editorial or article. So it's the marketer making an assertion, not Adweek    
    
    
    @ivanlajara I did nothing of the sort. I am merely an editor. Any twerking is incidental.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ivanlajara If you're dying to know (and I know you are) email subject was "Real-Time Marketing: Electric Fireplaces Twerks it Out."    
    
    
    @cwarzel hola    
    
    
    Let's Remember Weiner This Way | Adweek http://www.adweek.com/videowatch/lets-remember-weiner-way-152413#.UjMtXwJYzhI.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Velocidi If you think you'd like to throw your hat in the ring for Voice, check this out, and reach out to Jim. http://bit.ly/RES5Ai     
    
    
    Retailers are choosing to use social pics and endorsements in #ads over product shots. Smart move, IMO. http://adweek.it/163vMTd  via @Adweek    
    
    
    .@nbcuniversal paid $1.4 million per episode to air @modernfam. Will it pay off? http://adweek.it/14YL8lR  #tv    
    
    
        
    
    
    Eating lunch... where did the day go?!    
    
    
    I do hope you voted for your fave #TV, #magazine, news #website and more on @Adweek's #Hotlist. If not, do it now! http://adweek.it/19ZkAoy     
    
    
        
    
    
    My @Adweek colleague @nudd developed this awesome map of the top #advertising #agency in each state. Do you agree? http://adweek.it/1eJ12KI     
    
    
    @mediagazer I actually think @KatyontheHill had the @ftc #native #advertising story first: http://adweek.it/1djeqRv     
    
    
    What is it about @lilycollins (daughter of singer Phil) that makes her a good channel for #malware distribution? http://mashable.com/2013/09/17/most-dangerous-celebrities-2013-lily-collins/ …    
    
    
    @MetaSchool @FastCompany Happens this way in "real" life too.    
    
    
    @MetaSchool @FastCompany Well, the the world might be a nicer place if it's weren't true, but it'd be mega boring.    
    
    
    Of course Grumpy Cat is now a spokescat for @Friskies. http://mashable.com/2013/09/18/grumpy-cat-friskies/ … @realgrumpycat #endorsements    
    
    
    .@facebook has a quarter TRILLION user photos, it has revealed. A few hundred of those are sans #duckface. http://mashable.com/2013/09/16/facebook-photo-uploads …    
    
    
    Hey it's @72andSunny right now! #nice #weather    
    
    
    A big thanks to the guy yapping his face off on a packed rush hour @LIRR train. #Commuting wasn't nearly annoying enough.    
    
    
    Have you checked out @Adweek's "Mad Woman" @laurenreeves yet? Here she examines the relationship btw women and #cars. http://adweek.it/1bt4GGa     
    
    
    @A_Rot Not only was he obviously (and pitifully) hitting on a much younger guy, he also made 3 unnecessary "whassup" phone calls. So rude!    
    
    
    Works for me - I grew up watching these guys in reruns. http://adweek.it/1eUiR9L     
    
    
    @A_Rot Indeed. Doesn't everyone understand that? Not a moment of silence all the way to Penn. I learned a lot about both parties, though.    
    
    
    @A_Rot Someone's on that already! https://www.facebook.com/pages/I-hate-the-LIRR/142062669212218 …    
    
    
    This New Zealand PSA about the dangers of smoking #weed is hilarious. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0UbARVx-cq8 … #thenaughtycigarette    
    
    
    Whoa, it's 5 o'clock. What happened to today?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tonight's a big night for @Adweek, as we honor this year's #brandgenius winners, including @UncleRUSH. @baratunde will be hosting.    
    
    
    Very excited... it's almost time for the #BrandGenius awards! It's my first time at the fete, and I'm a huge fan of @DefJamRecords.    
    
    
    Time to honor some great ideas and great minds! #BrandGenius    
    
    
    .@nfl doesn't do any marketing per se - still as @baratunde noted, it has some of the best marketing imaginable #BrandGenius    
    
    
        
    
    
    My gamer friends would be happy about our next #BrandGenius. @Activision  CMO Tim Ellis honored for @CallofDuty's monumental success.    
    
    
    .@beatsbydre is a personal favorite and another #BrandGenius    
    
    
        
    
    
    Holy smokes, @laurenreeves had some serious moves! #BrandGenius afterparty    
    
    
    The last day of Advertising Week #AWX in #NYC. Bittersweet.    
    
    
    If M&Ms and #sriracha can cure the common cold, I should be all set.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Now you can own #WalterWhite's Albuquerque home. Priced to sell! RV parking available. @CENTURY21 #BreakingBad http://adweek.it/16D9bwU     
    
    
    The latest in @adweek's ad #fraud investigation: Home sites that have millions of ads and few actual users. http://adweek.it/1g2ipnZ     
    
    
    Yes, BODY SUSHI is eating sushi off a naked woman. Seems a bad association & also super-unhygienic! #NYC #ads pic.twitter.com/LiMbodocng    
    
    
    This marketing study about women is depressing & cynical. Who doesn't feel ugly in the morning and when they're sick? http://adweek.it/18snD8p     
    
    
    Hey @SureFitInc, you're about to lose a customer! I am appalled by how you are handling a basic customer service issue. #badbusiness    
    
    
    @SureFitInc Thank you. Please restore my confidence in your company!    
    
    
    Now, why the hell would a mega-successful company like @BurgerKing go and change its name? http://adweek.it/1g3U3Kw  #madness    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SureFitInc Checking back in since it's been a few hours... was the cust serv manager able to rectify this?    
    
    
    Capitol on lockdown after shots fired - Jake Sherman - http://POLITICO.com : http://www.politico.com/story/2013/10/shots-fired-capitol-hill-97808.html#.Uk29Wjb-oHQ.twitter … via @POLITICO    
    
    
    Aren't you supposed to leave the baby at home when committing any kind of domestic terrorism?    
    
    
    @tejadaj1 If you're calling what I do here terrorism... well, I've been called worse    
    
    
    @SureFitInc Thank you for being responsive to my complaint! I'm glad to see this is how you do business.    
    
    
    .@Sinead_OConnor and @MileyCyrus. #Thunderdome Who makes it out alive? #questions http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/sinead-oconnor-writes-miley-cyrus-best-tough-love-letter-all-time-152875 …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Using the bathroom on the @LIRR during the AM rush is not nearly as stomach-turning as it is during the PM rush. #commuterproblems    
    
    
    @LIRR Hey! Thanks for responding, and for the link to the comment form. Will be useful for this new LI resident, I'm sure!    
    
    
    Think women are the only ones objectified in #ads? Not true. #Sex sells both ways. http://adweek.it/GElIUB     
    
    
    Despite the fact that #NYC is filled with hipster #beards and #Movember 'staches, barbershops are making a comeback. http://adweek.it/1cuFLCJ     
    
    
    No more "desk-side meetings" or "desk-side briefings" please. #jargonwatch    
    
    
    .@pug Only as long as you don't create any synergies or paradigm shifts, leverage anything, calibrate expectations, or try to be impactful.    
    
    
    .@pug You fared better than me. I tried to be proactive by leveraging my synergies and I died.    
    
    
    @MTA please turn off the A/C on the N/Q/R line. It's cold and rainy outside. #wasteful #government    
    
    
    @Dropbox I have dupes of my properly date-formatted pics in "missing dates" folder... basically dupes of every photo. Is this a bug?    
    
    
    Are you a rich dude obsessed with living the good life? Got a #magazine for ya: http://adweek.it/1hEoCV3     
    
    
    @OSchiffey @G2USA @CadburyMY My sweet tooth has been activated.    
    
    
    Lotsa ladies in this week's #top10 #ads, from @GreyGoose @hotpockets @Samsungtweets @Gillette @Dodge @PaulSmithDesign http://adweek.it/1biA5rP     
    
    
    The same lame-o songwriter who wrote 'Friday' for Rebecca black wrote this silly ode to Chinese food for #AlisonGold. http://adweek.it/GPnhiE     
    
    
    Meet the man behind the world's best ad agency Twitter feed. (HINT: It's @RGA) http://adweek.it/1hTQfcL     
    
    
    My esteemed @Adweek colleague, historian @UpperEastRob, relates the #shutdown to the near-razing of the #WhiteHouse. http://huff.to/19PVYQ2     
    
    
    This weeks #Top10 #best #ads come from @redbull @Verizon @sprint @PlayStation @MercedesBenz @JackandJonesTM @DieHard http://adweek.it/1atuOvg     
    
    
    Thanks to wine for cats, it's now no longer necessary to drink alone. http://adweek.it/17bTrRY     
    
    
    @malki @ja3 Most commonly experienced on the #NYC #subway    
    
    
    @amazon Your store card payment portal is down. Tried to access it via several different browsers.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Mind = blown. http://adweek.it/178gOtA  @Honda    
    
    
    This is the #1 most popular story on @Adweek's website right now, and with good reason. It's powerful. http://adweek.it/19WySsT     
    
    
    @zipporahs Great tweet. Thanks for sharing. The "squish" is a temporary unpleasantness leading to a more lasting peace of mind!    
    
    
    Idiotic (and expensive)? Or absolutely brilliant? http://adweek.it/17bK16T  #ads @nytimes #TheBookThief    
    
    
    I have a new most-hated non-word that someone decided to sling as a verb: PRODUCTIZE. #JargonWatch    
    
    
    I'm also tired of names that start with l/c letters, use ALL CAPS but aren't acronyms, include symbols, or otherwise look misspelled.    
    
    
    Hey did you guys see the 10 #best ads of last week? From @BenjaminMoore @bookingcom @Honda @miniusa @Sony @VW http://adweek.it/1gM9yts  #top10    
    
    
        
    
    
    Creepy interactive #app for new #StephenKing book lets you in the mind of a grown-up & troubled Danny Torrance. http://adweek.it/1aWl1xO     
    
    
    Like the @HISTORY show Counting Cars? Positec is hoping its Rockwell power tool line will be up your alley, too. http://adweek.it/16RvaQD     
    
    
    Editing a story that says women are supposed to have no more than 6 tsp of sugar a day. I just ate 22 mini Snickers. How many tsp is that?    
    
    
    @lorilewis What are you talking about? Wine is a health food!    
    
    
    OK, so to balance out the 22 Snickers, I'm going to ingest an entire head of cauliflower. Cauliflower negates chocolate calories, right?    
    
    
    Today is an important day in history: @twitter will have the second biggest tech #IPO ever, and rapper Ja Rule has been released from prison    
    
    
    I hope this was staged. I'd sue the shit out of them... especially if I was the pregnant one. #WTF #prankvertising http://adweek.it/17GBFXn     
    
    
    Is this the best #movie #trailer of the year? http://adweek.it/1iOXjb1     
    
    
    Vote 4 the week's #best #ad! Contenders are @LEGO_Group @Skype @YorkshireTea @Activision @CallofDuty @marksandspencer http://adweek.it/1iRs0fS     
    
    
    Happy 35th birthday to @adweek, who may have grown older and wiser w/ the years, but hasn't lost her youthful charm. http://adweek.it/16W5D6R     
    
    
        
    
    
    #gnomespotting #home @ChouffeUSA pic.twitter.com/2gwOy9szQ4    
    
    
    As seen on the @LIRR... great #juxtaposition of new @drakes #ad and a sleepy #NYC commuter. pic.twitter.com/qGQESaQNBc    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @Kai_Hazlewood I'm surprised it wasn't spam-filtered...    
    
    
    @RossSheingold True, but I thought it was going to be a pitch about a 12-step program for beastiality addicts. I'm disappointed.    
    
    
    @A_Rot Does it being Thursday mean that they're already drunk?    
    
    
    @A_Rot At least they're not pitching gluten-free dental dams.    
    
    
    Check out my profile of @Decon, a #NYC #creative studio with #hiphop at its roots and a diverse set of talents. http://adweek.it/1b9cvRA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Vote for the best ad of the week! Results later today. Contenders include @footlocker @Baileys_GB and 3 more brands. http://adweek.it/17yvylf     
    
    
    Wish you could play @CallofDuty online with @AdrianPeterson & other NFL stars? Now you can. http://adweek.it/1bPylEQ  pic.twitter.com/mYU9Iv3qxd    
    
    
    Getting excited! It's almost #HOTLIST time here at @CapitaleNY! pic.twitter.com/wE2RkkfgdF    
    
    
        
    
    
    Adweek is 33 years old! First gala though. Beyond time for a big party! #HOTLIST    
    
    
    @rorypw @Aflac what do you think is sexist about it? It's not the best spot I've seen, but I don't see any sexism here.    
    
    
    I was enjoying the @pace_foods debacle... why can't it be real?! I hate #hoaxes. http://adweek.it/1gyHAO3     
    
    
        
    
    
    @rorypw I feel like that stat makes it even less sexist... There's so much other real sexism in the world - no flack for Aflac from me.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out these interviews w/ @louisck @cecilybecily and other awesome people at Adweek's #HOTLIST gala last night! http://adweek.it/1eMTRNJ     
    
    
    Interesting that @Newsweek is now going back to #print after earlier deciding to go digital-only. http://adweek.it/1eNrwHf  #journalism    
    
    
    Got a pitch today about the #BakedInBoulder campaign... and it wasn't what I thought! But yes, cooked tofu is now legal in #Colorado.    
    
    
    @Nick314 I see what you did there!    
    
    
    @crupicrupicrupi The most important thing I got from this is that Gillian Anderson has a navel ring and needs a good night's sleep.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Do you agree with our picks for the Top 10 #Ads of 2013? http://adweek.it/19dK7f6     
    
    
    The difference in how #men and #women are perceived. A moving effort from @Pantene. http://adweek.it/1dhlflY  #ads #sexism    
    
    
    Need to know which #brands will be wowing you during the #SuperBowl?  Adweek's tracker is constantly updated: http://adweek.it/1hKnYd2     
    
    
    Only about 1 hr left to vote for the #ad of the week @pantene @mcgarrybowen @themartinagency @Heineken @Oreo @WestJet http://adweek.it/1eauQjh     
    
    
        
    
    
    Chuck Norris wins #Christmas with his epic split.  http://adweek.it/1beQewb  @chucknorris    
    
    
    This week's Top 5 #ads got me in the #Christmas spirit! From @Apple @netflix @CocaCola @Airbnb @UNICEF Pick the best! http://adweek.it/19h8YAV     
    
    
        
    
    
    