@TwoThirdsHazel ME TOO!!! It makes me so sad that he has to find a new home for his pup. :(    
    
    
    @TwoThirdsHazel HE DOES!? That makes me so happy!!    
    
    
    I just checked my email 15 minutes ago. And now I have 13 spam emails. Uhm, is 10:30 p.m. the start of the witching hour?    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @AspiringPR love this.    
    
    
    "Do we like her?"    
    
    
    i know there is like a foot 'o snow outside, but I swear I can hear crickets...    
    
    
    blessed to have grown up in a small town where we not only have our small town beliefs but RESPECT those who believe differently than we do.    
    
    
    I miss the days when the biggest scandal of they day was who was picked last for kickball...    
    
    
    I don't have to be hateful,
I can just say, "bless your heart."    
    
    
    missing the country tonight. in need of a good cow tippin'. ;)    
    
    
    "You are such a superficial space cadet!"    
    
    
    I think the Internet needs to shut down to EVERYONE for a few days so we can examine the things we say to one another...    
    
    
    We demand respect for our opinions yet berate others when they voice theirs? When did this become OK?    
    
    
    I miss days where we smiled all the time and laughed and lame jokes. Maybe that's lame but I just can't deal with mean...    
    
    
    So i can't decide if still sleeping with my teddy bear is pathetic or endearing...    
    
    
    Fan of @Beyonce or @MileyCyrus? Here's What You're Likely to Buy http://bit.ly/1h7oxuH     
    
    
    Who just paid $2.78 for gas? Oh. Yeah, that would be me.    
    
    
    @Kris234Kris @CatsOutOfTheBag AWWW, thank you! and trust me, he knows! ;) haha    
    
    
    YOU GUYS! #Toby is getting so much love from #Purina @CatsOutOfTheBag!! #MerryChristmas <3 <3    
    
    
    @enigmachine @CatsOutOfTheBag dot worry...I definitely belong to him!!    
    
    
    @enigmachine @CatsOutOfTheBag he's very good with the tree...surprisingly. He's very protective of it and LOVES the lights.    
    
    
    @DevilishMendez @CatsOutOfTheBag thank you! he's a charming little fellow!    
    
    
    @laurenkgray i miss AIM... I was just thinking about how lame away messages used to be!    
    
    
    @CatsOutOfTheBag aww thanks! :)    
    
    
    @laurenkgray like the clever shower one where everyone was "hot and steamy" ...haha    
    
    
    @alaurazmom thank you!! He's very loved! :)    
    
    
    @niki_harman @CatsOutOfTheBag omg! She's beautiful!!    
    
    
    10 Tips for Proper Holiday Social Media Etiquette http://bit.ly/JyaEtx     
    
    
    .@jasonthescott underestimates my impatience...especially about the Queen.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott I hate you.    
    
    
    @gkern not so much a dud...it's just not very Britney. it's VERY different than we normally get from her. she did a lot of spiritual things.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq what? Lol    
    
    
    @gkern yeah it was primarily marketed towards her "die hard" fans so a lot of people don't even know it was out.    
    
    
    3 Steps to Becoming a Better Version of Yourself http://bit.ly/19y3O1n     
    
    
    Merry Christmas from my little village! http://instagram.com/p/iHzeW_RAHz/     
    
    
    Ok guys...where can I get one of those dancing dashboard daisies for my car??    
    
    
    @BFSEsq @yndige23 I was thinking, great, now what offensive thing did the great Barry Manilow day.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq @yndige23 or say...    
    
    
    ICYMI: #toby is twitter famous. #purina http://instagram.com/p/iIETmjxAOB/     
    
    
    Snow fan for life. #tbt http://instagram.com/p/iIH_SjxAC2/     
    
    
    @ENews wasn't there supposed to be a @britneyspears clip from #IAmBritneyJean tonight?    
    
    
    How to effectively work from home http://bit.ly/19y3Ne3     
    
    
    @rmiller_08 that's cuz this weekend took FOREVER.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 ME TOO!! For commencement? I'll be there, I can sneak you into the fancy lunch if you need.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 haha OK, I'll text you tomorrow when we head up for lunch.    
    
    
    7 Ways Twitter Can Help Juice Your Content Creation http://bit.ly/JBV4x3     
    
    
    @rachmariepr I love the variety!    
    
    
    i've pretty much had lunch out every day this week. #sorrynotsorry    
    
    
    @rachmariepr @PRDivaBlog @FashionPennPal @YazminaCabrera @thebanjogirl @thePRwoman thank you love!    
    
    
    @carleebb HAHAHA!    
    
    
    does anyone know why Washtenaw and the US23 exit ramp are horribly backed up?    
    
    
    @marykatemchugh @rachmariepr no way... they're so... ridiculous.    
    
    
    @britneyspears me too, Britney... it's my most favorite thing in the world. #twinzies    
    
    
    @keith_caulfield @Beyonce @GooglePlay Isn't it exclusively on iTunes for the first week?    
    
    
    @keith_caulfield @Beyonce @GooglePlay @amazonmp3 ohhh...weird. sorry :(    
    
    
    What Makes a Presentation Great? Deconstructing an Awe-Inspiring TED Talk http://bit.ly/19y3TlD     
    
    
    I'm so exhausted that I'm dizzy and I'm still waiting for my sister to get off work...    
    
    
    @breatheheavycom I don't think that's final...    
    
    
    @RedHeaded was like that earlier, too... 1p.m. Earlier.    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe I mostly buy on CD... except Beyoncé, that's shhh*t ain't worth the monies. ;)    
    
    
    @mz duh.    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe😘    
    
    
    @thePRwoman oooo what kinda of changes?    
    
    
    @thePRwoman but I hate waiting!! I'm the most impatient person alive! ;)    
    
    
    @thePRwoman hahaha    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 we still on for the @britneyspears docu tomorrow night? :)    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 @britneyspears haha, sounds good... It doesn't start until 9 p.m. that's sooo late. agh!    
    
    
    been on my feet since noon. who wants to come over and give my feet a massage? ;)    
    
    
    @AdrianCGiovanni haha my friends do that to me, "hey did you hear Britney.." and I'm always like, "think before you ask me about britney."    
    
    
    5 #PR lessons from 'It's a Wonderful Life' http://bit.ly/1cZGzOx  #MerryChristmas    
    
    
    @Brit_News ptsh, the question should be who DOESN'T!?    
    
    
    when rebranding, what are the first steps you take? #personalbranding #branding #pr #sm    
    
    
    @Brit_News i'd love an updated Chris Cox Megamix!!    
    
    
    @djchriscox so, how do we get an updated @britneyspears 'Chris Cox Megamix' from you sir??    
    
    
    normally i very much look forward to seeing my cousins + family. but all i want to do tomorrow is sleep. :(    
    
    
    don't bite the hand that feeds you.    
    
    
    Help the Smurfs build a village to call home! Play on iOS and Android. @BeelineGames #SmurfsVillage http://bit.ly/10o2xW5     
    
    
    @DebWDW safe travels!!    
    
    
    The best way to spread Christmas cheer a by singing loud for all to hear.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 I don't even care if I get sick, I'm still coming over to watch @britneyspears' docu.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 even if you did I wouldn't care. Lol    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 hey, do I need your address to get in at the gate? If so, will you text it to me? I'm too lazy to find my phone and ask. haha    
    
    
    Smurfy Tip: Use stardust to clear new areas on the Swoof planet in #SmurfsVillage outer space.  http://bit.ly/SmurfVillage  @BeelineGames    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 yeppers... is it OK if I come over a bit earlier? I don't wanna be at home. lol    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 okie dokie, sounds good. :)    
    
    
    @BFSEsq is that Valentine's Day stuff?    
    
    
    @TheMadamEditor @AlizaLicht YES! It comes out this spring... It's called The Pirate Fairy or something like that! my niece is so excited.    
    
    
    let's go #LIONS!    
    
    
    "I'm too busy sellin' 50 million records."    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica OMG! We're like the same person... I'm eating Oreos, too!    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica rats! mine are just plain 'ole double stuf. the flavored ones creep me out. #weirdo    
    
    
    baby thinkin' of you keeps me up all night.    
    
    
    Longest 8 minutes ever has started.    
    
    
    ITS BRITNEY BxxCH!    
    
    
    Cue a million sales of watermelon bubblegum.    
    
    
    I love you @britneyspears! Thanks for sharing your journey through #IAmBritneyJean xxoo    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe who doesn't!? @britneyspears    
    
    
    @bitty_boop @britneyspears #flawless    
    
    
    @mz hot stuff 😉    
    
    
    @MuuMuse I just told my friend that...how funny. Wonder how @Allure_magazine feels about their pic going unremembered. @britneyspears    
    
    
    .@britneyspears your daddy is adorable. #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    SPARK! and it's like gasoline. #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica kitty kitty!? Wtf! Haha    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS awww and you're my lobster. (You've seen this #friends episode yes?) #army    
    
    
    Britney breaks her neck.

"Oh I'm good, thank you."    
    
    
    Go beyond reason to love because it's the only safety there is.    
    
    
    Did @britneyspears just announce #alien as a single? #notalone    
    
    
    "Are you ever lonely?"    
    
    
    THANK YOU BABY JESUS. Everytime is in the show. @britneyspears #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    I kinda feel like a jerk for being upset about the lack of #BritneyJean promo now... she's working her @$$ off for Vegas...#IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 it's AMAZING! It's definitely as amazing as FTR, but better 'cuz she's SO HAPPY in this one.    
    
    
    @djchriscox I'm asking!! @britneyspears -- you're up! :)    
    
    
    @MEGABRITNEYFAN and I wasn't all THAT upset with the lack of promo, but I was still bummed she didn't get her well deserved 7th #1!    
    
    
    @MEGABRITNEYFAN I think they shoulda waited until March to release the album... she woulda knew the routines +  more time for promo.    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS thank God! I was sooo debating about sending that #FRIENDS reference. hahaha    
    
    
    Go beyond reason to love — it is safe. It is the only safety. ~ Thaddeus Golas    
    
    
    @mz @britneyspears I'm coming for my birthday on April 25!! And hopefully on April 25 next year if she's performing for the big 3-0!!    
    
    
    @SamanthaLuthra yes. that sounds very horrifying. hahaha    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 perfection is an understatement.    
    
    
    wired from #IAmBritneyJean but sinus migraine wants me to sleep. i'm a mixed bag of emotions.    
    
    
    Smurfy Tip: Use stardust to clear new areas on the Swoof planet in #SmurfsVillage outer space.  http://bit.ly/SmurfVillage  @BeelineGames    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious I'm so happy she's doing Everytime... Those set lists going around we're breaking my heart without it!    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa seriously! It's been nearly 13 years! How did they even think that!?    
    
    
    @tkylemac @MuuMuse so amazing! What did you contribute exactly?? :)    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious Ahhh I wish this was being shown live on TV opening night!    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious yeah - that would be awesome, too.    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS and me please!!! ;)    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS all #hail the kweens!    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious @britneyspears @LarryRudolph @mz @AdamLeber SRSLY!! Don't want to wait I NEED it now!    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS @Lisaney83🎶😘😍🎶    
    
    
    Counting "neys"... Starting with BOMTney. Sweet dreams, tweethearts...xo    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS👑👑👑    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa @ZeroSuitBritney no, she's one of Larry's minions. Her new Brett is named Robin. Haha    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 backatcha! Xo    
    
    
    This little kitten is about to get his little kitten butt kicked if he does not stop racing shadows across my bed.    
    
    
    What happened to his adorableness 30 mins ago when he was asleep on my back?? #toby    
    
    
    7 Ways to Build a Following on Instagram http://bit.ly/JBVsf0     
    
    
    "I went looking for camouflage the other day, but I couldn't find any!"    
    
    
    Facebook Promotions: 5 Things That Are Still Illegal http://bit.ly/JDpOxL     
    
    
    me. always. #awkward http://bit.ly/1jB149U     
    
    
    @Cherrow414 so how do you say Xoco?    
    
    
    @gkern I know, I have CS6. Some others might want it, though... :)    
    
    
    @cubanalaf I do. And kiss him forever and ever.    
    
    
    @Cherrow414 OK, thanks! :)    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 hooray! congrats. :)    
    
    
    @Cherrow414 no...I just didn't know! Haha    
    
    
    THANK YOU SO MUCH @SamBourque23! He is thrilled! :) pic.twitter.com/Z0SB0h5efX    
    
    
    so grateful for friends who go above + beyond to make the lives of others amazing. <3    
    
    
    @SamBourque23 he says "All anyone else got was the name plate, I 'made out like a bandit'!" hahaha he's so excited! :) thank you again!    
    
    
    Leverage Blog Content Seeding to Gain New Readers http://bit.ly/19yMHg7     
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS confession: Wizard of Oz gives me nightmares.    
    
    
    How to find ‘the one’ in PR http://bit.ly/1huOzYV     
    
    
    Have a rewarding week! Use your Smurfberries to smurf something new in your #smurfsvillage @BeelineGames http://bit.ly/SmurfApp     
    
    
    Brand journalism is the new PR  http://bit.ly/J6Of6c     
    
    
    @malrich10 girl! -3 is nothin! Wait for th -15degree windchill! Haha    
    
    
    God bless us, every one! #merrychristmas    
    
    
    #LGRW #winterclassic #goblue http://instagram.com/p/iUVS29xAKz/     
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious same here. Winter needs to come or go...make up it's dang mind!    
    
    
    @bitty_boop it's a classic,    
    
    
    @JasontheScott JTT's "Home for Christmas", Jim Carrey's "The Grinch" and Care Bear's Nutcracker. :)    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 "Do You Hear What I Hear?" and "Oh Holy Night"! :)    
    
    
    8 Simple Scientifically Proven Ways to Improve Your Writing http://bit.ly/19y4Dat     
    
    
    @BFSEsq mine won't leave his present alone.    
    
    
    @TiffanyHoughton yes!! @crowdsurf is amazing!! One of my dream companies to work for one day! ☺️you're amazing, too - love the new song! Xo    
    
    
    Hurry up darkness! Can't wait to get home to Dexter for luminaries tonight! #merrychristmas    
    
    
    @TreeTownSound @Madonna only if Like a Prayer does, Too!    
    
    
    Praying the weather forecast holds true and we get out 2" of snow. I love waking up to a white(er) Christmas! ❄️    
    
    
    Christmas Eve cuddles... http://instagram.com/p/iUjYYoxAC2/     
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 that was just on the radio! I like Carrie Underwood's... It's beautiful and very simple!    
    
    
    Is "stress Emily out and ruin every holiday for her" written on my forehead or something? :(    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 I love Transiberrian's "Christmas Cannon!"    
    
    
    my little village is more adorable and perfect on Christmas Eve than anywhere in the world...    
    
    
    "you're defined by who you become when you're under pressure."    
    
    
    i've been watching @MichaelPhelps swimming videos on @youtube for like, an hour...#teamUSA    
    
    
    and now it's gymnastics and figure skating which will turn into snowboarding and skiing. can the @Olympics get here already? #teamusa    
    
    
    @alyssalynnwaid @KTvontom @amymfarley a nice foot massage would be pretty nice...    
    
    
    i don't know how my mother can sleep with a speaker blaring in her ear.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm not a Bieber fan per sey, by my five year old niece just started falling in love with him. poor baby.    
    
    
    @bwerde you didn't see his tweet?    
    
    
    @bwerde you must be missing the Tweet...    
    
    
    i'm so confused. is bieber retiring or not?    
    
    
    .@JasontheScott saw this and thought of you... haha pic.twitter.com/CvFXb4fGyl    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck i am one of those 5.    
    
    
    @mary_obrien for realz! plus, i feel like his tweets were contradictory. "i'm retiring" but "i'll always be here." uhm, what?    
    
    
    @Cherrow414 her and toby should hook up. he's always getting into purses. backpacks. shopping bags. trash bags...    
    
    
    @carleebb Merry Christmas and God's blessings, Carlee! xxoo    
    
    
    i've never blogged this consistently before, guys. i'm so proud of me.    
    
    
    Santa just flew by Dexter!! #PureMichigan pic.twitter.com/eg50wiAi9Y    
    
    
    Have a rewarding week! Use your Smurfberries to smurf something new in your #smurfsvillage @BeelineGames http://bit.ly/SmurfApp     
    
    
    Why not spend my Christmas watching #BigBangTheory?    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 @OnceABC I need to do that... I'm still on season 2... Lol    
    
    
    @thePRwoman it's hard...    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 @OnceABC I'm at the mid season finale still...haha    
    
    
    I love you, baby Jesus. #merryChristmas    
    
    
    @rachmariepr merry Christmas love bug! xxoo    
    
    
    merry Christmas to you @thePRwoman - you're one of the most amazing and inspiring women I know! xxoo    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan merry christmas Lil B! you're such a sweetheart, so happy to "know" you! xo    
    
    
    As children we believed, the grandest sight to see was something lovely wrapped beneath the tree...    
    
    
    But heaven only knows that packages and bows can never heal a hurting human soul...    
    
    
    popcorn.    
    
    
    @thePRwoman I saw this and thought you might be interested... interesting retrospective way too look at 2013! http://lifeisasunset.blogspot.com/2013/12/25-questions-to-ask-yourself-before-2014.html …    
    
    
    @thePRwoman :) xo    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 what update?    
    
    
    @jesslaw Boy Meets World!    
    
    
    @bitty_boop memememe! ;)    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR I've only seen it once...like 10 years ago.    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 hooray!! what a great gift! :)    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR you'd be surprised at the movies I haven't seen, though. haha... Goonies, Ferris Bueller, Dirty Dancing...    
    
    
    @MileyCyrus he is just the cutest! what breed of pup is he?    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR I own Dirty Dancing... it will happen sooner or later! haha    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 Santa definitely got lots of treats for the Tobesters.    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR haha... will do! :)    
    
    
    "But I haven't sang 'Sometimes' yet!"    
    
    
    @TheeLifeOfB an easy bake oven!?    
    
    
    @TheeLifeOfB hehehe    
    
    
    i sang so much that i smiled,
i made it worth my while.
i drank some white wine,
now i'm walkin' on the sky.
i had the time of life.    
    
    
    hi.    
    
    
    @smwatson92 what?

lol    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck i don't get it.    
    
    
    @smwatson92 LOL ok :)    
    
    
    i've seen so much more than you know now,
so don't tell me to shut my eyes.    
    
    
    two things: i really don't like dry skin and someone needs to get me off @pinterest.    
    
    
    40 Quotes to Help You Follow Your Passion http://bit.ly/JBVhAv     
    
    
    I honestly don't know. #tbt http://instagram.com/p/iZJBpgRAP0/     
    
    
    4 Journalist Secrets Every PR Should Know http://bit.ly/1huOBA9     
    
    
    11 Celebrity Tweets You Can Learn From http://bit.ly/1juyEOA     
    
    
    Advice for #PR and communications graduates http://bit.ly/1fwa2PS     
    
    
    Leverage Blog Content Seeding to Gain New Readers http://bit.ly/1cZGvhT     
    
    
    8 LinkedIn Mistakes You Should Never Make http://bit.ly/1cZGz10     
    
    
    #notamodel http://instagram.com/p/icqhlHxAAu/     
    
    
    What I'd give to be in #Vegas right now...    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 did you get both? Lol the yawn + follow up?? Haha    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa I KNOW!!    
    
    
    kick #Vegas butt tonight @britneyspears! You're gonna rock it! #PieceOfMe #LivingLegend    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa I'm *hoping* to see her on my birthday in April, but I don't think it's gonna happen :(    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 lol oh good!!    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa I think @chasebenz tweeted It out.    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa http://instagram.com/p/icpEozJZds/     
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa😘☺️😊    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa dang! I turn 30 in 2015...want to get a fancy table! You should join! :)    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 which vid!?    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa I want it soooo bad!! Haha    
    
    
    .@jtimberlake is in #Vegas...    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 only britney can crack her voice and millions fawn over it. Haha #truelove    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa me too! I'm considering starting a job hunt there just to see @britneyspears weekly!! Haha #stan    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa lol right!? I'll waitress in Vegas for two years...#justsaying    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS at least they look good with the costume this time! Haha    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 why am I waiting!?    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS @Lisaney83 LARRY! Fireworks!    
    
    
    "If @BritneySpears jumped 30' off a tree would you?"
"Uh, duh."    
    
    
    @thePRwoman that must be such a blessing. I can't wait to get to that point!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman can't wait!!    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS hamhocks?? Lol    
    
    
    The dancing...I'm in awe. #PieceOfMe    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS I don't get it, but OK. Haha    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS @Lisaney83 I HAVE VIRGIN EARS, OK!?!? ;)    
    
    
    If you don't go see @britneyspears in #Vegas before her residency is over you're missing out on a huge part of pop music history. #legend    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS I'm not sure those are sprayed...any other angles?    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS I don't know I don't have them! Lol    
    
    
    @pieceofB watch Break the Ice, MATM, BOMT :)    
    
    
    wired from adrenaline for a show I wasn't at...that's powerful. #PieceOfMe    
    
    
    @pieceofB and the rest, too... hahaha    
    
    
    @pieceofB the perfume and lucky vocals >>>>>    
    
    
    I am @britneyspears, Britney Spears is me. pic.twitter.com/GH7uOuN0I2    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 SRSLY.    
    
    
    OMG there is a dog sled race up near Tahquamenon. WHY AM I NOT GOING. #puremichigan    
    
    
    @rachmariepr LOL no big deal...I was being an insomniac!    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR yeah, me, too... I think there are more on my floor than I have in my hair care storage. lol    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 when are you seeing Britney?    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 oh hooray!! that's so soon, very jealous!    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan @britneyspears THAT'S WHEN I'M GOING! THAT'S MY BIRTHDAY!!    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan @Dream_JT I'm never going to give up this dream, Lil B! BRUSTIN 4 LIFE! ;)    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan @britneyspears Uh, yeah, especially since I'm probably going by myself... lol    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 whatcha researching?    
    
    
    I Will Defend My 'Real' Job to the End of Time http://huff.to/1fOJtGg  !!! This 15-year-old is more inspiring than most of the women my age.    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan AND IT'S MY BIRTHDAY!    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan @britneyspears I don't have them yet... person I was going with isn't being very communicative...where are yours?    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS YO! What's the quote on your Twitter header from Marilyn?? :)    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan :) ...next year is the BIG 3-0! I want to get a fancy table in #Veags for #PieceOfMe...that would be a dream (within a dream).    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS what's the quuuoteeee though. lol    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS you're so wonderful to me! http://bit.ly/1eLVIGL  xxoo    
    
    
    i wish I could shimmy...    
    
    
    oh, hi!    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan I will!! :)    
    
    
    so proud of all the work I got caught up on today! and now - time to clean!    
    
    
    cleaning break? sure, why not.    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan duh!! Hope we get #pieceofme on DVD soon...and #IAmBritneyJean, too!!    
    
    
    @BFSEsq ooohhh that's a meat slicer. got it.    
    
    
    @RedHeaded is there such a thing?    
    
    
    sometimes a girl doesn't need someone to solve the problem. sometimes she just needs to vent about it. #MYOB    
    
    
    It's heartbreaking when you come to the realization you have nowhere to go...    
    
    
    @GUBLERNATION that sounds perfect...    
    
    
    @uPRise_PR gorgeous!    
    
    
    those who stay will be champions.    
    
    
    @Brit_News stay strong my friend...I hear it gets better. xxoo    
    
    
    @Brit_News lets stick together ☺️😊    
    
    
    @thePRprincesss @thePRwoman agree and the subsequent posts following :)    
    
    
    @Brit_News oh good! It's so much more amazing than FF - energy, dancing, everything.    
    
    
    @Brit_News me too. What's your IRL name?    
    
    
    @Brit_News haha I figured that wasn't your name!! Mike! Hi Mike...my nephew is a Michael, too. :)    
    
    
    @Brit_News aww my nephew is opposite. He also does not like "Mikey" haha (he is 9)    
    
    
    @Brit_News oh good you're not a crazy young Britney Stan. Haha    
    
    
    @Brit_News I was 13 when BOMT was released, that's the right age to be! Haha    
    
    
    @Brit_News yeah, I'm 28.    
    
    
    @Brit_News I'm trying to!! Haha    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @xstephanieclark Ahhh what brand/shade is that??    
    
    
    Hi. @amymfarley    
    
    
    @amymfarley 'sup?? pic.twitter.com/ajJCrF1pc0    
    
    
    Ahhhh! We're going to Cedar Point! Ahhhh! http://instagram.com/p/ihX-V1xAEA/     
    
    
    "Why do you need to blog? Don't you tweeterface and vineagram already?" - my brother.    
    
    
    Hahahahah http://instagram.com/p/ihZxQBxAGy/     
    
    
    @amymfarley I took two strawberry cupcakes and no vanilla! dang!    
    
    
    hiccups.    
    
    
    @amymfarley rats! 😇😉thats OK, cupcakes ate worth it!    
    
    
    Hi. Single men. Let's talk.    
    
    
    @blogilates hi Cassie! Is your DVD at all Targets? I can't find it!!    
    
    
    @blogilates OK, thanks! I'm trying a cpl more tomorrow!! Wish me luck!    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR @rachmariepr my snapchats should cure her in no time!! Haha    
    
    
    i swear, @Snapchat with my nieces is the best ever.    
    
    
    @jesslaw what is it for?    
    
    
    my #toby is being the cutest little thing. he's "helping" me clean.    
    
    
    @jesslaw gotcha! hmmm...    
    
    
    ugh, now he's surfing on computer paper. this kitten just never learns... #toby    
    
    
    @jesslaw that's great! i was going to suggest passion. what about moment. like a "live in the moment" kinda thing.    
    
    
    @MackenzieLauka @jesslaw My resolution this year is to just be happy. :)    
    
    
    @rachmariepr @OliviaAdamsPR hooray #SnapChatQueen    
    
    
    @MackenzieLauka @BeckuhBeck @jesslaw exactly!!    
    
    
    Coca-Cola digital chief: 'Kill the press release' http://bit.ly/K5bYEG     
    
    
    @carleebb @lifetimefitness just laughed so hard at this.    
    
    
    Why Insecurity May Be The Key To Success http://bit.ly/JuZiWZ     
    
    
    Stop Rushing At Work: Stress Makes You Less Productive http://bit.ly/JuZk1d     
    
    
    @blogilates found it!! Yay! (At a @target I already check out - go figure!) Excited to start! ☺️😊pic.twitter.com/IYpCEqa0x7    
    
    
    @RedHeaded packing!? Where are you going!    
    
    
    @RedHeaded oh right! I knew that...have...fun!?    
    
    
    @citygirlhanna @blogilates me too!! I was so motivated with it last summer, can't wait to get back at it! :)    
    
    
    @RedHeaded ahaha, you're running outta time...    
    
    
    congrats on the launch, ladies! @uPRise_PR @emilyjoyPR @kayla_hollatz xxoo #upriselaunch    
    
    
    .@uPRise_PR happy to be here with you, lady bugs!! excited to chat. :) #upriselaunch    
    
    
    @uPRise_PR A2: stay passionate! #upriselaunch    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 you're in Vegas tonight, right, babes?? #PieceOfMe    
    
    
    you only need one ! ...it's exclamation enough. promise!!!!!!! ;)    
    
    
    A3 Definitely Twitter...so real, so fun. #upriselaunch    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 omg!! have so much fun, love bug!! where are your seats?    
    
    
    @LanceBass when do you get to see @britneyspears perform in Vegas?? She's gonna take you on stage during #Freakshow, right?? ;)    
    
    
    A4 ALWAYS include the who, what, where, when, why. if you target the release effectively, you'll get the coverage you deserve. #upriselaunch    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 Are you gonna send pix?? ;)    
    
    
    "it's been a while.
i know i shouldn't have kept you waiting.
but i'm here now."

#pieceofme pic.twitter.com/LOpkxyhx8b    
    
    
    @amymfarley I got this for you! :) pic.twitter.com/vC5JqOLq1a    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 yay!! :)    
    
    
    #LGRW    
    
    
    hockey town is taking over ann arbor! #LGRW! (pic from @annarbornews) http://www.mlive.com/news/ann-arbor/index.ssf/2013/12/photo_gallery_view_of_winter_c.html … pic.twitter.com/JccrsAuALM    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa it's supposed to be snow, actually, I think.    
    
    
    I think I'm getting sick. #dislike    
    
    
    @Robin_Leach @britneyspears  who got to go on stage during #Freakshow?? Please tell me it was @LanceBass!    
    
    
    YES!! I love when @britneyspears brings @LanceBass on stage with her! #nsync    
    
    
    @britneyspears britney jean, you are the queen! #hail the queen of #Vegas! #pieceofme    
    
    
    Whoever got me sick is going to rue the day!    
    
    
    An ode to AP style, and why it matters in PR http://bit.ly/Jg0bTJ     
    
    
    @alyssalynnwaid @Kyle_Farley2 @KTvontom did you three have a blast??    
    
    
    @alyssalynnwaid @Kyle_Farley2 @KTvontom :(    
    
    
    7 Things Your Social Media Consultant Should Tell You http://bit.ly/JuZntR     
    
    
    we drop hockey pucks at midnight. #LGRW    
    
    
    Whether you turn to the right or to the left, your ears will hear a voice behind you, saying, 'This is the way; walk in it.' - Isaiah 30:21    
    
    
    @myprerogative15 i loveee when britney brings him on stage. reminds me of *NSYNC + Britney always together days. #truelove #00s    
    
    
    steve #yzerman is my soulmate. #LGRW    
    
    
    always has been, always will be. #truelove ;)    
    
    
    VLAAAADYYY!! <3 <3 #LGRW    
    
    
        
    
    
    Dear Lord, thank you for blessing us with hockey. And Steve Yzerman. Love, Me. #LGRW #Hockeytown    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @prgirldanni sadly, this #NYE, I've been given the gift of sinusitis. so no.    
    
    
    @prgirldanni @thePRwoman it struck about 11 p.m. last night. talk about a surprise! ugh. hahah    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @prgirldanni true...but not after I've already OD'd on Benadryl!! LOL oops.. ;) have fun tonight and be safe! :)    
    
    
    I don't think you guys understand how big my crush on Steve #Yzerman actually was when I was 12 years old.    
    
    
    Could totally deal with some Chelios chili right now. #justsaying    
    
    
    @B_Helderop @Matthops82 HAHA!    
    
    
    @SamanthaBankey right?! at LEAST once a season.    
    
    
    #dreamteam #LGRW    
    
    
    despite being sick, the @DetroitRedWings alumni games are proving to make for the BEST #NYE ever. <3    
    
    
    What does content marketing mean for the PR industry? http://bit.ly/Jg0lKO     
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 you rock! and you're such an inspiration to me! happy new year, Katie!! :)    
    
    
    very much wish i could be downtown ann arbor tonight to see the puck drop at midnight. instead i'm curling up with #Qdoba and #PLL marathon.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq SO glad I read your entire Tweet before I Googled "how many inches is 10-15cm" ....#americanprobs #lol    
    
    
    @BFSEsq HAHAHA!    
    
    
    hey, hey, hockeytowwwwn.    
    
    
    ugh. i forgot to get kleenex. i think i have to run out again... booo!!    
    
    
    Happy New Year! #NYE #2014 http://instagram.com/p/imy37rRAEc/     
    
    
    @teganzimmerman carrie underwood hair AND legs!    
    
    
    i still maintain that @Puffs with Vicks are the only thing in the world that matters.    
    
    
    @TinaSmithers awwwwww! now, find me one tonight!! ;)    
    
    
    @JasontheScott I swear, if beYAWNce is top 5...    
    
    
    @JasontheScott  but I think Madonna, Mariah and Whitney will get top 3. Britney hopefully top 5...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TinaSmithers ugh, that's in two years... happy new year!! have fun, be safe! xo    
    
    
    i'm sending #snapchats of me lip-synching to brit brit tonight. be prepared to be blown away. #imthequeenofpop #happynewyear ;)    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 haha... deal. if i make any good ones.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott is this just a list of 30 or the list of 30 in order? that's repulsive!    
    
    
    @JasontheScott I have some people to start yelling at...    
    
    
    @JasontheScott yeah, I'm sick. :(    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @carrieuobsessed Dolly Parton IS country music.    
    
    
    $5 says I call the cops on my upstairs neighbors tonight. #SHUTUP    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @carrieuobsessed she'll definitely be one someday, that's for sure!    
    
    
    #puckdropshere    
    
    
    @JasontheScott got the top 10 yet? wish i had cable...    
    
    
    Seriously, who created this list? #disgraceful    
    
    
    Happy New Years @NSYNC! My resolution is to talk y'all into giving me new tunes... ;) xo    
    
    
    I swear @rmiller_08 favorites all my tweets. ;)    
    
    
    I do love me some Blondie.    
    
    
    holiday! celebrate! holiday! celebrate!

if we took a holiday, took some time to celebrate, just one day out of life.
it would be so nice.    
    
    
    I think I need to take my Nyquil and say hello to my pillow before I head over to @ABC and teach them a thing or two about music... ;)    
    
    
    @JasontheScott i can't believe how angry i am over this list. hahaha    
    
    
    @mashable @BAHjournalist I don't think Beyonce deserves to be in top 5...what about Celine? Janet? SO MANY amazing artists left off.    
    
    
    If it's the last thing I do in 2013, I'm going to get @NSYNC to say "emily is the best fan ever"...#thingsiobsessoverwhensick    
    
    
    @BFSEsq so Fox News/Fox Sports...same ownership right?    
    
    
    @vogueandcoffee @andersoncooper I think he's the only reason I watch #CNN...    
    
    
    @BFSEsq so MSN and MSNBC are the same ownership, too, right?    
    
    
    @LuxuryPRGal oh. my. gawd. that looks amazing. #delish    
    
    
    all eyes on us tomorrow, ann arbor. let's do #puremichigan proud. #LGRW #WinterClassic #PuckDropsHere    
    
    
    @BFSEsq well, i'm askin' cuz when I go to Fox Sports they have the little msn logo and its http://msn.foxsports.com .    
    
    
    @BFSEsq and when i went to either nbc or msnbc's site today they had it, too... (I don't see it now) and thought it was ironic that the most    
    
    
    @BFSEsq liberal/conservative news networks both are MSN. anyway... lol    
    
    
    @BFSEsq (oh, remembered - it was NBC News).    
    
    
    @JonathanKinard @Lisaney83 @RyanSeacrest RIGHT!? #travesty    
    
    
    speaking of the @chickfilabowl ...I really, really would love some delish @ChickfilA ...    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck i know, right? i can't even wear kitten heels!!    
    
    
    @BFSEsq yeaaaah, anyway, so i obsesses over ridiculous things when I'm sick. haha    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck me either. flats for the win! (but i really just don't like shoes in general!)    
    
    
    @TinaSmithers best drink ever. (Except not really, 'cuz I don't like coffee...but y'know...)    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck awww we're like twinzies! ;)    
    
    
    @thePRwoman LOLz a the "health" part as I hack up my lungs! #irony ...anyway. HAPPY NEW YEAR G! so proud to "know" you! :) xo    
    
    
    @SimonOh HAHA! Wow... I didn't even remember that until now. :) Happy New Year, @SimonOh! So glad I got to meet you in Philly!    
    
    
    @tkylemac have a great time love! xxoo    
    
    
    @BFSEsq or when we all go to bed and they're up partying still...and it's still not their midnight. #losers ;)    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa i don't know, but i wish i were her.    
    
    
    THE PUCK DROPS HERE! #LGRW #WinterClassic    
    
    
    This is a hockey game! #LGRW RT @Mark__Snyder: Winter Classic minutes after face off pic.twitter.com/XtfEsDfqu4    
    
    
    Ahhh I love when my perfect stadium is broadcast all over the world...#intheBIGHOUSE! #goblue #gowings #lgrw #winterclassic    
    
    
    @MarioAndretti @NHL 110,000 fans! ;)    
    
    
    So wrong to be cheering for the team in red at The Big House...#winterclassic #gowings #ilovegoblue #lgrw    
    
    
    @MuuMuse this will be such a Spearitual moment...    
    
    
    I'm going to @panerabread...    
    
    
    Have they released official attendance at the #WinterClassic yet?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @annarbornews is there an official attendance yet? #winterclassic    
    
    
    @JasMollica you hush! #gowings    
    
    
    @Breezie_123 I could deal with a foot of snow!! Haha    
    
    
    All #WinterClassic games should be played in #AnnArbor and at #TheBigHouse...#perfection    
    
    
    @EricLacy truth!    
    
    
    and today just clarifies things more.    
    
    
    looking forward to waking up to nearly a foot of snow. and hopefully to feeling better, too...    
    
    
    Now that I'm hacking up my lungs, too, maybe I should call the doctor in the morning...    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan YEP! Story of my life...    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan being sick right now is making it worse. I'm exhausted, but like sleeping all day, but still exhausted. And can't sleep.    
    
    
    i get all settled and comfy in my bed and then...remember my contacts are still in.    
    
    
    3 Questions PR Pros Should Ask Before Posting on Facebook http://bit.ly/JuZup6     
    
    
    Detroit! RT @MarkRaganCEO 10 happiest cities for PR and marketing pros. Where you do you live? http://bit.ly/WmCDPH     
    
    
    @MackenzieLauka where do you get yours from? :)    
    
    
    @MackenzieLauka haha idk about that but it is fun!! :)    
    
    
    any one been out on the roads between Ypsi and Briarwood? I have to go to the doctor... #annarbor    
    
    
    12 Top Tips for #PR Interns http://bit.ly/JiyucU     
    
    
    #pll marathon thoughts: emily is the worst character.    
    
    
    @JaredEvans77 This is what I've seen: http://fox17online.com/2014/01/01/few-couches-burn-in-east-lansing-following-rose-bowl-win/ …    
    
    
    @R_Gardiner14 right!?    
    
    
    @R_Gardiner14 Oh, I'm completely caught up and rewatcing for the millionth time. I have it on DVD.    
    
    
    @elizalouisebell exciting!! what kind of planner?    
    
    
    @elizalouisebell that's cool...I almost bought a Target planner, but I'm so picky about them, I couldn't commit! haha    
    
    
    It's still snowing...    
    
    
    @R_Gardiner14 me too! Just a few more days!    
    
    
    What app do y'all use to make text posts on Instagram?    
    
    
    29 Ways to Instantly Boost Your Creativity  http://bit.ly/19Z8UUy     
    
    
    @britbrit1fan have you seen the one where Britney's face looks all twisty? lol    
    
    
    fell asleep just now with gum in my mouth. woke up moments later choking on the gum. 'cuz i'm a rockstar, obviously.    
    
    
    Well I was hoping to work today and tomorrow but it looks as though I'm gonna have to take another sick day! Sorry @DebWDW! :(    
    
    
    Get it Sooners!!    
    
    
    on my fourth box of Kleenex in two days...    
    
    
    ps: #GOBLUE!    
    
    
    @IowaHawkeyeMeg should work! can't do Tuesday but any other day should work! :)    
    
    
    @IowaHawkeyeMeg is evening better for you? And you're central time, yes?    
    
    
    YES. -7 DEGREES.    
    
    
    @Brit_News thanks love bug! i think i've caught the plague. uuuggghhh... :'|    
    
    
    @elysa so, tell me about this @Wunderlist ..I've been thinking about trying it.    
    
    
    @Brit_News nope, not the flu!!    
    
    
    @DebWDW if by some miracle I wake up tomorrow and can breathe/swallow, I'll come in...don't count on me, though!! :)    
    
    
    Every time a Detroit team plays I wanna yell "eat 'em up..." But then I remember that's only OK for the @tigers ... #eatemupREDWINGS?? Ha.    
    
    
    4 Advanced Social Media Marketing Strategies For Bloggers http://bit.ly/1cJvem4     
    
    
    -8.    
    
    
    Uhm, we are supposed to get up to another 8 inches of snow by Monday...    
    
    
    16-point checklist for SEO newbies and veterans http://bit.ly/1cJvdyt     
    
    
    How brands are embracing big social data http://tnw.co/1cJve5t     
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS agreed. the only great about her album was the "marketing" behind it.    
    
    
    @teganzimmerman jealous! I could use a tan! ;)    
    
    
    @teganzimmerman yeah...we are expecting up to 8 (more) inches!! Stay warm!    
    
    
    excited that i get to actually take a yoga class this winter...5 (maybe 6!) days/week!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman oh I love Pilates, too! I used to take a PIYO (mix of both) class, but they aren't offering this sesh!    
    
    
    @elizalouisebell it's actually a Beach Boys song... 😇🎶    
    
    
    #goblue #beatNW    
    
    
    how hard is it to move from USA > UK? I've been thinking about it a LOT lately.    
    
    
    @beckwoodward gotchaaaa... do you know if seeking out an employer who wants someone in the UK hard?    
    
    
    @_NicoleESpears @cpacelli22 so jealous - i'm snowed in!!    
    
    
    @_NicoleESpears haha...I don't mind, praying for a snow day tomorrow!! ;) ❄️    
    
    
    @beckwoodward OK, thanks for the insight/advice! ☺️    
    
    
    YAY SNOW DAY TOMORROW!! THANK YOU #EMU! One more day to attempt to get healthy! #snowday    
    
    
    thank you #Snowmageddon2014.    
    
    
    @adv_clara @netflix right?! it's so disappointing.    
    
    
    @Breezie_123 yeah, we have a snomergency...no school. basically EVERYTHING is closed... plus we have subzero temps. l    
    
    
    @BFSEsq uhm. hello. we're in michigan. if we call snow emergency we're just a bunch of pansies.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq "snow condition yellow"? really?    
    
    
    @BFSEsq i can't.    
    
    
    oh, winter storm ion. you. you and your ways.    
    
    
    IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE 40DEGREES ON SATURDAY! BREAK OUT THE BIKINIS AND MARTINIS!    
    
    
    @emilyjoyPR Hahaha... I don't actually mind the cold, definitely prefer it to sweltering summers. #confessional    
    
    
    @SoFabulousx7 hi!    
    
    
    @rachmariepr I finished! Text me tomorrow when you can take a look! :)    
    
    
    @JasontheScott hello darling! how are you? xo    
    
    
    @rachmariepr guess what! i finished. text me in the morning or whenever you have time to check it out.    
    
    
    @rachmariepr also, I emailed you some info about it!    
    
    
    does your cat ever try to jump through glass to catch snowflakes? no? just mine?    
    
    
    Have a rewarding week! Use your Smurfberries to smurf something new in your #smurfsvillage @BeelineGames http://bit.ly/SmurfApp     
    
    
    5 Media Relations Tips to Memorize During a Crisis http://bit.ly/1cJvotq     
    
    
    @SoFabulousx7 it's a snow day...so fab! 😊❄️    
    
    
    Kayakers in the "flood"'last summer downtown Ann Arbor...and snowmobilers...I love my city.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @comcast oh yuck! Have you tried doing the whole unplug and reset everything? Or is it for sure down-down?    
    
    
    @TheMadamEditor I know, right!?    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @comcast OK, gotcha. How lame! Mine was down for a month once, even had a guy come out. NOT ONE PERSON told me to reset.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @comcast He finally came out, reset it and boom. fixed. and I had to pay for his visit, too! was NOT happy.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @comcast awww, OK, good luck, buttercup! :)    
    
    
    i love snow. i love the cold. today is perfect.    
    
    
    10 misconceptions about #PR http://bit.ly/1cJvq4L     
    
    
    @rachmariepr awww, thanks!! :)    
    
    
    @JasontheScott @comcast hooray!! :)    
    
    
    one day, i'm going to go to greece. and take @kirasabin with me. 'cuz i know how much she loves it. ;)    
    
    
    @kirasabin do you speak greek?    
    
    
    #sorrynotsorry for spamming you're @pinterest feeds. i'm still sick and need something to do. ;)    
    
    
    @thePRwoman HOORAY! Hope I can make this one!! :D    
    
    
    @kirasabin ahaha! good to know..    
    
    
    snow days never lose their excitement. i feel bad for all y'all who don't get snow. you'll never get to experience this feeling. #sogood    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe duh.    
    
    
    @LauraBellBundy #LMFAO, yes? my niece's favorite lyric. ever.    
    
    
    SNOW DAY TOMORROW, TOO!! I LOVE YOU #SNOWMAGEDDON!!    
    
    
    Why Millennials Need A Personal Brand Identity http://bit.ly/19Nre57     
    
    
    @PRNewser @Cosmopolitan yeah, who doesn't wish that?    
    
    
    5 Reasons It's Totally Fine Britney Spears Is Lip Syncing In Vegas http://huff.to/1dlGO6X  (plus, she is singing live...sometimes).    
    
    
    @GUBLERNATION aaahhh! ;)    
    
    
    wireless battery chargers need to be a thing.    
    
    
    Fitness Tips To Keep Up With The Demands Of Social Media http://bit.ly/1cJvtgS     
    
    
    @breatheheavycom @RealBRITannica jealous!! ;)    
    
    
    @Popdust @britneyspears Well, that interview is from her June 2013 Shape Magazine cover story! She didn't release a statement about this. :)    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR I swear, every time you have a new site design I need the font you use. WHAT IS THAT FONT!? lol    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR sure thing jelly bean! once my new design is ready I'll give you mine! And I'll add yours! :)    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR hopefully this week if I get better...ever...haha. And thanks for the font! 😊    
    
    
    dear neighbor spinning your tires in the parking lot outside my window: i think you're snowed in. give up, you're disturbing SVU time. xo    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR check out @rachmariepr's blog... she has a new button up! take hers. :)    
    
    
    @LisaCroccoPR backatcha girl! :) can't wait to connect more! :)    
    
    
    my web browsers keep disabling scrolling with my track pad. anyone know why this is and/or how to fix it?    
    
    
    I'm going to keep my mouth shut until this game is over 'cuz every time I cheer for my preferred team lately, they lose. #emilyprobs #cursed    
    
    
    #FSU!    
    
    
    @YazminaCabrera hello! long time no chat! how are you? :)    
    
    
    @emilyjoyPR @rachmariepr found this tweet in my faves+forgot to respond. HAVE THIS BOOK, haven't read it yet. move it to top of my list?    
    
    
    @britneyspears I've been sick so sadly, I haven't been able to get to the gym to #WORKBxxCH and get #HotLikeBritney! :(    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 those are the people who need ...well, you know.    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck that's still on?    
    
    
    @andieallthetime ohhhh, I love him... my daddy's fave.    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck wow... I thought that was over years ago. hahaha    
    
    
    Is It Time For A Digital Detox? http://bit.ly/1cJvNfI     
    
    
    @citygirlhanna same here! stay warm!:)    
    
    
    How to win the ‘branding marathon’ http://bit.ly/1cJvMbv     
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR oh thanks! i'm still playing with it... any critiques? :)    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR oh thanks! i'm not crazy about the header yet. I don't like the gold and gray...    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR oh, OK, so it doesn't look as bad as I think it looks then?    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR oh thanks! :)    
    
    
    bitterly cold. yeah, that's how i describe it, too, @weatherchannel... at least it's sunny? pic.twitter.com/DE4Hf7LLuM    
    
    
    Why Young Professionals REALLY Switch Jobs http://bit.ly/1cC2FT0     
    
    
    It's #PLL night! I'll be live tweeting with @thecollegecrush tonight! Join me at 8 p.m. :)    
    
    
    @JasontheScott duh!    
    
    
    palying "which #PLL would you be" with @rmiller_08 and @SterraBella    
    
    
    clearly, i'm a hannah.    
    
    
    OMG I cannot stop laughing at this @detroitzoo #meme on Facebook. #hahahaha pic.twitter.com/YtRvKheip2    
    
    
    it's warmer in alaska than it is in michigan. when does that EVER happen?    
    
    
    heading on over to @thecollegecrush for some #PLL convo! join me, won't you?    
    
    
    what answers will be left to have answered in #PLL season 5? will we still be question who A is? #AskMar    
    
    
    @jesslaw aww thanks!! :) appreciate that  and you're welcome!    
    
    
    This Resume Alternative Could Land You Your Dream Job http://on.mash.to/19Y4cTC     
    
    
    The heat in my entire apartment is officially out. They are "working on the water heater." Which makes no sense 'cuz we have hot water...    
    
    
    @jesslaw thanks :)    
    
    
    high of 15. loving this heatwave. ;)    
    
    
    I get worried sometimes when @RedHeaded isn't on gchat.    
    
    
    back to work and I love that @DebWDW has her @Disney soundtrack to life playing already. (:    
    
    
    How social media schedules thwart writer's block http://bit.ly/1iaEfFK     
    
    
    What to do when your 'perfect' PR pitch is less than perfect http://bit.ly/1iaEnVK     
    
    
    @myprerogative15 awesome! Where ya working?    
    
    
    World notices that (a) it's cold, (b) Michigan has a city named Hell http://bit.ly/1d0cT45     
    
    
    @myprerogative15 aww ... We all gotta do it!    
    
    
    And now a pipe burst in my bedroom and everything is soaked.    
    
    
    @RedHeaded I'm so done.    
    
    
    6 Skills You Need To Be A Social Media Professional http://bit.ly/1iaFIMh     
    
    
    Brand Marketing Success with Instagram http://bit.ly/1f8KNqB     
    
    
    i'm really excited for the #NAIAS this year..    
    
    
    Yeah, I could deal with winning this @lululemon giveaway... http://bit.ly/1cSqkin     
    
    
    @B_Helderop uhm, what are these?    
    
    
    @teganzimmerman @lululemon more than i can purchase now!! haha    
    
    
    The Six Dimensions of Sharing  http://bit.ly/1cIyh9x     
    
    
    more snow. good.    
    
    
    @EAHarter happy birthday! 🎂    
    
    
    The 10 Biggest Mistakes People Make in Setting Goals http://bit.ly/1cIysSi     
    
    
    This week could not be going any worse...    
    
    
    A Crash Course In Leadership For 20-Something CEOs http://bit.ly/1cIyzNT     
    
    
    Some say in the most impatient person alive, and that's true. But I get most impatient when my appointments run 1HR+ late.    
    
    
    First Day of Internship: What to Bring http://bit.ly/1lQhWFj  via @KatieReilly06    
    
    
        
    
    
    @amymfarley sparkling silver linings!    
    
    
    40degrees has never felt so warm.    
    
    
    all i want is to go to bed wake up and go swim laps. #simplelife    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR I have one button up now, but I might change it...or add another or something.    
    
    
    i hope my landlord gets the carpet cleaners in here monday. i can't deal with this wet carpet smell anymore. this is ridic.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 mine too. but i'm never a bridesmaid either.    
    
    
    @ChrisColePR what's the difference between a bronzer and highlighter? #makeupprobs    
    
    
    Thank you Lord, for the gift that is Tom Brady. #beautiful    
    
    
    Pushing through. #hotlikebritney #workBxxCH pic.twitter.com/IH8DHBv4aZ    
    
    
    @ChrisColePR oh! Thanks love. xx    
    
    
    @carleebb I was hoping to swim today but there are tiny brats in the pool. Ugh. 😉    
    
    
    YOGA!! in the morning. can't. wait.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott her hair bugs me. Haha    
    
    
    so TSwifty is at the #GoldenGlobes because her song "Sweeter Than Fiction" is nominated. Stop whining. KTHXBYE.    
    
    
    but you went away,
how dare you.
i miss you.    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 which perfume?    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 never heard of that one!    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS i'm going to have to investigate this perfume now. haha... I'm a big fan of "Hello" by Harvey Prince.    
    
    
    4 skills PR newbies should possess (if they want a job) http://bit.ly/1e9G59l     
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious what is this CRFTY?    
    
    
    In social media, it's not the x-factor that counts, it's the 'why' factor http://ca.finance.yahoo.com/news/social-media-not-x-factor-192300553.html …    
    
    
    Hey #PRSSA! What kind of topics would you be interested in discussing your Chapter meetings?    
    
    
    DEEEEETOOOIIIIIT AUTO SHOW.    
    
    
    @VanessaSalman For real? on purpose?    
    
    
    @uPRise_PR you are so very welcome! xo    
    
    
    @VanessaSalman wow... I'd go to the department head, actor or not! that's not OK! scary!    
    
    
    Can You Launch a Brand in 24 Hours? http://bit.ly/L37rDE     
    
    
    Think it'll take 21 days to make your resolution a habit? Try tripling that! http://on.today.com/1d1hmiQ     
    
    
    @thornybleeder there's a new layout?    
    
    
    finding large bruises on my arm is always the most confusing part of my day.    
    
    
    @thornybleeder wish I had it! :)    
    
    
    Looking for some #Fashion #PR people in the Southeast Michigan area...#PRSA #PRSSA #HAPPO #Backchannel    
    
    
    30 Instagram Photos That Will Make You Fall In Love With Ann Arbor http://bit.ly/1fvpHD8     
    
    
    Reducing the stress in your professional life http://bit.ly/1alLAjH     
    
    
    watching #PLL with @CEC_PR and livetweeting over at @thecollegecrush! join me at 8 p.m. :)    
    
    
    I don't think my mom understands that having to listen to the same 15 songs that one doesn't like 24/7 is crazy inducing.    
    
    
    @JackShellWYCD I always wanted Charlie Brown to try to kick her instead of the football.    
    
    
    @liz_chapman1 ...does that mean you're getting one?    
    
    
    @rachmariepr hey love bug! I'll be working on your Pinterest/Tweet question first thing in the a.m.! Sorry I couldn't get to it tonight...    
    
    
    @rachmariepr my #PRSSA meeting was wild and fun - in a good way! and then I got held up with #PLL. sigh. :)    
    
    
    You all make me feel so blessed. :)    
    
    
    @liz_chapman1 haha, just making sure!! ;)    
    
    
    @thePRwoman just read your 14 things to do in 2014 list...your handwriting is so pretty. xo    
    
    
    Storytelling drives air of optimism in Detroit http://bit.ly/1iUCkph     
    
    
    How to *really* annoy someone from Michigan http://bit.ly/1fyMQEQ  via @MatadorNetwork    
    
    
    @thePRwoman can't wait for this discussion!! #PRwChat :)    
    
    
    been craving #BlueTractor... need to head downtown #AnnArbor ASAP!    
    
    
    @eonline Zack & Kelly. Ross & Rachel.    
    
    
    @StyleWatchMag definitely @JLo.    
    
    
    Do you really need a cover letter with that resume? http://bit.ly/1fyMqye  via @arikhanson    
    
    
    I feel like I don't remember a time when it wasn't snowing.    
    
    
    @JennMuscat eew! Lol    
    
    
    just keep swimming 🏊😊(@ EMU Rec/IM) http://4sq.com/1mau2Mw     
    
    
    5 flawed social media strategies you should shun http://bit.ly/1iWxtUp  #SM #SoMe    
    
    
    bagels are proof that God loves me and wants me to be happy. #carbaddict    
    
    
    so, like, what exactly is 'American Hustle' about?    
    
    
    @JessEnglish35 i've been wanting to see it since it came out! maybe this weekend.    
    
    
    19 Hard Things You Need To Do To Be Successful http://read.bi/1d6o4ra  via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    #PRwChat tonight at 7 p.m. ET!! Hope I make it home from yoga in time to play! :)    
    
    
    How to Identify Your #PR Niche http://on.mash.to/1j1E8gj     
    
    
    @RealBRITannica you have your own poster at @target! pic.twitter.com/weyFR9el2r    
    
    
    So very bummed I missed the #PRwChat tonight. :( sorry @thePRwoman ...hope to see a recap soon and I'll be going through all the tweets!    
    
    
    I smell like a mix of chlorine and musk. It's not good.    
    
    
    Maybe it'll attract me a handsome swimmer, though. @MichaelPhelps !?    
    
    
    'Cuz even the stars they burn
Some even fall to the earth
We've got a lot to learn
God knows we're worth it    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica awwww... Those were from @target, too! ;) xxoo    
    
    
    Does Scandal's Olivia Pope represent the #PR industry well? http://bit.ly/1fBU1Ml  via @arikhanson    
    
    
    @kayla_hollatz thanks love bug! :) xo    
    
    
    #FF shout out to my girls! @BeckuhBeck @rachmariepr @thePRwoman @kayla_hollatz @EmilyL_Langford @emilyjoyPR @OliviaAdamsPR xo #PR    
    
    
    What city should YOU live in? I got Los Angeles - fitting since I want to move eventually!  http://bzfd.it/1dXRWDS     
    
    
    @thePRwoman hooray! So sorry I missed last night. :(    
    
    
    i'm ready to know what the people know
ask 'em my question and get some answers.
what's a fire and why does it...what's the word? burn?    
    
    
    @CarmanPlank daily.    
    
    
    @smwatson92 that made me feel creepy. hahaha    
    
    
    i keep thinking, "i can't wait to run tonight." and then i remember, "you can't go running tonight. you're taking a class." #bummer    
    
    
    @JackShellWYCD story of my life, man.    
    
    
    @CarmanPlank i am so sorry.    
    
    
    @CarmanPlank we were a Coke campus a bit ago, now we're Pepsi. But we do sell some coke products in the Student Center.    
    
    
    @CarmanPlank that's so miserable. :(    
    
    
    Job Interviews: 5 Questions Great Candidates Ask http://bit.ly/1fCFO1L     
    
    
    @keith_caulfield agreed JT. I think @britneyspears could have if she hadn't released anything since Blackout. Possibly T Swifty.    
    
    
    @thePRwoman congrats, girl! proud of ya... xxoo    
    
    
    @amymfarley is that your kitty??    
    
    
    10 more words you're probably misusing http://bit.ly/1j3D23G     
    
    
    class tonight.
and designing a blog.

cool.    
    
    
    holla    
    
    
    back in class.
and i forgot my slippers. boo.    
    
    
    newest annoyance: when people leave the manufacturing plastic cover on their phone...computer...iPad.    
    
    
    @thePRwoman taking an assertiveness class...    
    
    
    @thePRwoman thanks! Next month it's a conflict resolution class. haha...I learn a LOT from this lady, she's great. And really funny.    
    
    
    @thePRwoman Ohh, that's a good idea! If I do, I'll definitely share with you! :)    
    
    
    it has just been pointed out to me that i've been alive for four decades. which makes me feel really, really old. and i'm not even 30 yet.    
    
    
    or *during for decades, rather.    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @kayla_hollatz @TEDTalks that's so exciting... I don't think I'll ever be a public speaker like that, but admire those that are!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman I've been to San Remo on the Mediterranean Sea ...so beautiful. Where do you want to visit in Italy?    
    
    
    @HeatherRipley I've been to Geneva! It was just a day trip on the way to  Chamonix in France, but so amazing!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman Greece and Italy are on my next overseas trip "wish list." I just have to Santorini, Rome, Milan...no way it won't happen.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SparkPR no. :'(    
    
    
    Tips! #annarbor http://instagram.com/p/jUyI2_RAF0/     
    
    
    i know that since i'm learning to be assertive in my class right now i shouldn't be passive aggressive to my neighbors and their loud music.    
    
    
    but...i'm pretty sure i'm going to leave them a really mean note anyway.    
    
    
    @RedHeaded duh.    
    
    
    so...is saving 5% the same as getting 5% cash back?    
    
    
    "a ship at harbor is safe, but that's not what ships are for."    
    
    
    #GOBLUE!    
    
    
    @delucare ahaha with tattoos, so do I!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @delucare clearly we all need to get this tattoo together!! #TwitterTats    
    
    
    @CorynMarie you're so pretty. I hate you.    
    
    
    i love wolverines!!

#goblue #BeatWisconson    
    
    
    @CorynMarie i need to put you on my fridge as HOTspriation. hahaha...or not, that's creepy. lol (I LUV U 2!) xo    
    
    
    @hiyaluv I couldn't watch! :(    
    
    
    i miss @carleebb + @RachastaPR.    
    
    
    @hiyaluv sadly no, I don't have cable right now.    
    
    
    @carleebb @RachastaPR YES PLEASE!!!    
    
    
    @carleebb @RachastaPR @MeghanBSears OK :)   can it be a fancy PR girl meet up where we get dressed all pretty and drink cocktails!?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Detroit turns 313 years old on March 13 (313) which is also Detroit's area code.    
    
    
        
    
    
    I am craving a Dexter Pub grilled cheese...    
    
    
    that wind tho    
    
    
    go tom brady, go tom brady!
go tom brady, go!

#MichiganMan    
    
    
    i never understood how people can listen to music so loud in small spaces. like cars. or my annoying upstairs neighbors. #cantdeal    
    
    
    @MeghanMcCain I looooveeee my Ford Focus.    
    
    
    Does one have to wait until after a certain time to file a noise complaint with the police department?    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck I can Shazaam their music and it tells me what it is. It's THAT loud and I've knocked twice and they haven't answered.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 their music upstairs is so loud I can't think. :(    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 huh?    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 I knocked twice and nobody answered. Did the ceiling thing and they turned it up louder.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 I am talking to management tomorrow for sure...but that doesn't help my headache right now :(    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 hahaha    
    
    
    @EricLacy it's kinda country...mom...ish.    
    
    
    Miner Smurfs says, -Have a rich week!- Help Miner dig up jewels in #smurfsvillage @BeelineGames http://bit.ly/Smurf82  @BeelineGames    
    
    
    10 PR mistakes you need to resolve in 2014 http://bit.ly/1dY0Hhh     
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck I ended up having to call the cops. He said they've given them at least half a dozen tickets for complaints. ridic. :(    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck the cop said they're trying to get them evicted but it's hard to do with noise issues.    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck thanks, me too! Haha    
    
    
    serendipity is such a beautiful word with a beautiful meaning.    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck @EmilyL_Langford sometimes you can mail out from grocery stores! it won't go out until tomorrow, but you'll have it done! :)    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck @EmilyL_Langford do you have a Meijer near you? they do! Kroger might. :)    
    
    
    Enough with the ‘death of the press release’ already http://bit.ly/1dDRlJY     
    
    
    today at work i did budgeting. it hurt my head. but i got errr done! cc: @DebWDW #numberQueen?? ;)    
    
    
    @FitBottomedGirl any tips for keeping OUT of the work candy bowl?  #fitfluential    
    
    
    @FitBottomedGirl it's hard to avoid seeing it, it's on the desk in front of me!! haha! I need to find some healthy snacks to bring in. thx!    
    
    
    @bitty_boop right!?    
    
    
    @bitty_boop at least! And a lot of times I feel like the writers are making much ado about nothing.    
    
    
    What Your Favorite Disney Characters Look Like As Real People http://bit.ly/LvV8A3     
    
    
    @FitBottomedGirl thanks! Just had a nice yummy salad for dinner! :)    
    
    
    @vogueandcoffee I AM ALWAYS EXCITED ABOUT THE @OLYMPICS.    
    
    
    @citygirlhanna @emuPRSSA @msuprssarc I'm trying to get a couple of people out there! :)    
    
    
    let's be real. it's 2 degrees outside (oh haaaaay polar vortex 2.0!) and I'm about to go swim laps. probably not the smartest idea.    
    
    
    The Complete Guide to LinkedIn Etiquette http://on.mash.to/1jedLDQ     
    
    
    30 tools #socialmedia professionals can't live without http://bit.ly/1fJum4z     
    
    
    @rmiller_08 can i come over and watch #PLL with you tonight?? :)    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 yay!    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 I have a meeting until 7... depends on what time I can get there.    
    
    
    @ENews BRITNEY JEAN. It's always Britney who is is snubbed by the @TheGRAMMYs.    
    
    
    @RobMarciano @LoniLove @NancyODell you have Britney on your screen! why!? ;)    
    
    
    Personal Brand vs. Personal Life http://bit.ly/1jeknlC     
    
    
    learning about the @ideaLabHeritage and @CommunityMediaL tonight in our #ePRmtg with @emuprssa!!    
    
    
    the @CommunityMediaL seeks to get regular people to see what goes on behind the scenes of the news! #ePRmtg @emuPRSSA    
    
    
    want to learn to publish your own book? check out the @CommunityMediaL on Feb. 5 at 6 p.m. to hear from an author on how to self publish!    
    
    
    the @CommunityMediaL does one-on-one instruction like help people set up #SM accts. #ePRmtg @emuprssa    
    
    
    is it wrong that i'm jealous SE Michigan isn't getting the snow!? :( #snow ...please?? #snow?    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR I'm never over winter! haha    
    
    
    @tressalynne @thePRprincesss when I worked at a non-profit we used glue sticks because we sent out thousands every month!    
    
    
    tout captures short video updates via mobile or desktop apps. #ePRmtg @emuprssa    
    
    
    @CEC_PR I don't even know.    
    
    
    @CEC_PR awkies.    
    
    
    @CEC_PR awkward said cutely. lol    
    
    
    I'll be live tweeting #PLL tonight with @thecollegecrush! Join me at 8 p.m.! :)    
    
    
    @jackshellwycd did you know that @rmiller_08 is devastated that you don't follow her on Instagram. http://instagram.com/rmiller_08  ;) :)    
    
    
    @JackShellWYCD @rmiller_08 you follow her roommate. so she's sad. :( lol    
    
    
    "Are you happy now?"    
    
    
    "Yeah, maybe jut a little."    
    
    
    @OliviaAdamsPR it is a little much this year. and i'm already craving summer - i didn't get to do anything fun last year, so i need it now.    
    
    
    @rachmariepr hi love bug. would you like to write another guest post for me? :)    
    
    
    Jelly: The Latest App PR Pros Should Add to Their Toolkit http://bit.ly/1cScpZQ     
    
    
    @rachmariepr whatever you want. :)    
    
    
    @WarJessEagle agree with this while heartedly!    
    
    
    How To Turbocharge Your Writing For Public Relations  http://onforb.es/1dUzVtM     
    
    
    @elizalouisebell yeah, i can take it off.... at work now though. :)    
    
    
    @elizalouisebell if you have InDesign, it's not that hard...select the text tool and click it and you can delete it. :)    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 @TheEllenShow didn't get a Sub job?    
    
    
    @britbrit1fan @britney1army @britneyspears MY birthday people. it was mine first. ;)    
    
    
    @shoshannastone @Popjustice @AlexaGoddard i say "marshmEllow." But, I've heard both ways. :)    
    
    
    nothing is more attractive than a grown man throwing a temper tantrum after being scolded by the police/apt mgmt for playing music too loud.    
    
    
    i mean seriously, how can someone be SO disrespectful to other people? he has CHILDREN up there, too.    
    
    
    Oh, hey guys, I benched 65 lbs tonight. Take that Hulk Hogan. ;)    
    
    
    do you ever see pictures of old roommates wearing a shirt that looks like one you had that went missing and think, "bxxch stole my shirt!"?    
    
    
    @MattLaCasse Like you crushed Michigan in Ann Arbor? ;) #GoBlue #ThemIsFightinWords    
    
    
    @delucare I used to feel the same way about Aria, but now I can't stand Emily. #PLL    
    
    
    @MattLaCasse ahaha, sadly, I didn't watch the game so I have no idea what you're talking about...but...bring it on! #goblue    
    
    
    @MattLaCasse awww, I'm so sorry you feel that way, we're actually a super fun bunch. ;)    
    
    
    @delucare me too! I love her AND Hanna... they're just both amazing.    
    
    
    @MattLaCasse oh really!? they've brought me nothing but joy! ;) heheh    
    
    
        
    
    
    @McCollumAshley me too! Maintenance is supposed to come fix it but...we'll see.    
    
    
    @CarmanPlank yikes! Where are you headed?    
    
    
        
    
    
    i honestly don't get the big deal about the @beatsbydre headphones. but gosh darnit! i want the bright pink set.    
    
    
    #SugarFreeThursday... and @Alynn193 brought @insomniacookies to work. ugh. Thanks a lot @DebWDW!! ;)    
    
    
    @JasMollica @BeckuhBeck FOR REALZ!    
    
    
    @OhSaranizah I WANT THE PINK ONES SO BADLY.    
    
    
    @BeckuhBeck @JasMollica have everyone you know tweet it to him, haha... he can't ignore it that way. ;)    
    
    
    @Alynn193 @insomniacookies @DebWDW if I can pass it up, then I can conquer the world.    
    
    
    @LuxuryPRGal happy birthday!! congrats on the baby! :)    
    
    
    @Alynn193 Can't I be Emily the Conqueror and sad a the same time??    
    
    
        
    
    
    @laurenkgray WOW! It's coming out this year already? Wasn't there a bug break between the first two?    
    
    
    @colormelauren yep, I saw one.    
    
    
    @laurenkgray I still need to see Catching Fire! #slacker    
    
    
    @Alynn193 if you fall, who cares? Do it on purpose?    
    
    
    @DebWDW I have gone NO SUGAR all day and I'm about to go to bed! I earned that @insmoniacookie!    
    
    
    @thePRwoman awww, thanks love bug! I'm still playing around with it, it might be too pink for me.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @TwoThirdsHazel ME TOO!!! It makes me so sad that he has to find a new home for his pup. :(    
    
    
    @TwoThirdsHazel HE DOES!? That makes me so happy!!    
    
    
    I just checked my email 15 minutes ago. And now I have 13 spam emails. Uhm, is 10:30 p.m. the start of the witching hour?    
    
    
    @thePRwoman @AspiringPR love this.    
    
    
    "Do we like her?"    
    
    
    i know there is like a foot 'o snow outside, but I swear I can hear crickets...    
    
    
    blessed to have grown up in a small town where we not only have our small town beliefs but RESPECT those who believe differently than we do.    
    
    
    I miss the days when the biggest scandal of they day was who was picked last for kickball...    
    
    
    I don't have to be hateful,
I can just say, "bless your heart."    
    
    
    missing the country tonight. in need of a good cow tippin'. ;)    
    
    
    "You are such a superficial space cadet!"    
    
    
    I think the Internet needs to shut down to EVERYONE for a few days so we can examine the things we say to one another...    
    
    
    We demand respect for our opinions yet berate others when they voice theirs? When did this become OK?    
    
    
    I miss days where we smiled all the time and laughed and lame jokes. Maybe that's lame but I just can't deal with mean...    
    
    
    So i can't decide if still sleeping with my teddy bear is pathetic or endearing...    
    
    
    Fan of @Beyonce or @MileyCyrus? Here's What You're Likely to Buy http://bit.ly/1h7oxuH     
    
    
    Who just paid $2.78 for gas? Oh. Yeah, that would be me.    
    
    
    @Kris234Kris @CatsOutOfTheBag AWWW, thank you! and trust me, he knows! ;) haha    
    
    
    YOU GUYS! #Toby is getting so much love from #Purina @CatsOutOfTheBag!! #MerryChristmas <3 <3    
    
    
    @enigmachine @CatsOutOfTheBag dot worry...I definitely belong to him!!    
    
    
    @enigmachine @CatsOutOfTheBag he's very good with the tree...surprisingly. He's very protective of it and LOVES the lights.    
    
    
    @DevilishMendez @CatsOutOfTheBag thank you! he's a charming little fellow!    
    
    
    @laurenkgray i miss AIM... I was just thinking about how lame away messages used to be!    
    
    
    @CatsOutOfTheBag aww thanks! :)    
    
    
    @laurenkgray like the clever shower one where everyone was "hot and steamy" ...haha    
    
    
    @alaurazmom thank you!! He's very loved! :)    
    
    
    @niki_harman @CatsOutOfTheBag omg! She's beautiful!!    
    
    
    10 Tips for Proper Holiday Social Media Etiquette http://bit.ly/JyaEtx     
    
    
    .@jasonthescott underestimates my impatience...especially about the Queen.    
    
    
    @JasontheScott I hate you.    
    
    
    @gkern not so much a dud...it's just not very Britney. it's VERY different than we normally get from her. she did a lot of spiritual things.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq what? Lol    
    
    
    @gkern yeah it was primarily marketed towards her "die hard" fans so a lot of people don't even know it was out.    
    
    
    3 Steps to Becoming a Better Version of Yourself http://bit.ly/19y3O1n     
    
    
    Merry Christmas from my little village! http://instagram.com/p/iHzeW_RAHz/     
    
    
    Ok guys...where can I get one of those dancing dashboard daisies for my car??    
    
    
    @BFSEsq @yndige23 I was thinking, great, now what offensive thing did the great Barry Manilow day.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq @yndige23 or say...    
    
    
    ICYMI: #toby is twitter famous. #purina http://instagram.com/p/iIETmjxAOB/     
    
    
    Snow fan for life. #tbt http://instagram.com/p/iIH_SjxAC2/     
    
    
    @ENews wasn't there supposed to be a @britneyspears clip from #IAmBritneyJean tonight?    
    
    
    How to effectively work from home http://bit.ly/19y3Ne3     
    
    
    @rmiller_08 that's cuz this weekend took FOREVER.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 ME TOO!! For commencement? I'll be there, I can sneak you into the fancy lunch if you need.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 haha OK, I'll text you tomorrow when we head up for lunch.    
    
    
    7 Ways Twitter Can Help Juice Your Content Creation http://bit.ly/JBV4x3     
    
    
    @rachmariepr I love the variety!    
    
    
    i've pretty much had lunch out every day this week. #sorrynotsorry    
    
    
    @rachmariepr @PRDivaBlog @FashionPennPal @YazminaCabrera @thebanjogirl @thePRwoman thank you love!    
    
    
    @carleebb HAHAHA!    
    
    
    does anyone know why Washtenaw and the US23 exit ramp are horribly backed up?    
    
    
    @marykatemchugh @rachmariepr no way... they're so... ridiculous.    
    
    
    @britneyspears me too, Britney... it's my most favorite thing in the world. #twinzies    
    
    
    @keith_caulfield @Beyonce @GooglePlay Isn't it exclusively on iTunes for the first week?    
    
    
    @keith_caulfield @Beyonce @GooglePlay @amazonmp3 ohhh...weird. sorry :(    
    
    
    What Makes a Presentation Great? Deconstructing an Awe-Inspiring TED Talk http://bit.ly/19y3TlD     
    
    
    I'm so exhausted that I'm dizzy and I'm still waiting for my sister to get off work...    
    
    
    @breatheheavycom I don't think that's final...    
    
    
    @RedHeaded was like that earlier, too... 1p.m. Earlier.    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe I mostly buy on CD... except Beyoncé, that's shhh*t ain't worth the monies. ;)    
    
    
    @mz duh.    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe😘    
    
    
    @thePRwoman oooo what kinda of changes?    
    
    
    @thePRwoman but I hate waiting!! I'm the most impatient person alive! ;)    
    
    
    @thePRwoman hahaha    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 we still on for the @britneyspears docu tomorrow night? :)    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 @britneyspears haha, sounds good... It doesn't start until 9 p.m. that's sooo late. agh!    
    
    
    been on my feet since noon. who wants to come over and give my feet a massage? ;)    
    
    
    @AdrianCGiovanni haha my friends do that to me, "hey did you hear Britney.." and I'm always like, "think before you ask me about britney."    
    
    
    5 #PR lessons from 'It's a Wonderful Life' http://bit.ly/1cZGzOx  #MerryChristmas    
    
    
    @Brit_News ptsh, the question should be who DOESN'T!?    
    
    
    when rebranding, what are the first steps you take? #personalbranding #branding #pr #sm    
    
    
    @Brit_News i'd love an updated Chris Cox Megamix!!    
    
    
    @djchriscox so, how do we get an updated @britneyspears 'Chris Cox Megamix' from you sir??    
    
    
    normally i very much look forward to seeing my cousins + family. but all i want to do tomorrow is sleep. :(    
    
    
    don't bite the hand that feeds you.    
    
    
    Help the Smurfs build a village to call home! Play on iOS and Android. @BeelineGames #SmurfsVillage http://bit.ly/10o2xW5     
    
    
    @DebWDW safe travels!!    
    
    
    The best way to spread Christmas cheer a by singing loud for all to hear.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 I don't even care if I get sick, I'm still coming over to watch @britneyspears' docu.    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 even if you did I wouldn't care. Lol    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 hey, do I need your address to get in at the gate? If so, will you text it to me? I'm too lazy to find my phone and ask. haha    
    
    
    Smurfy Tip: Use stardust to clear new areas on the Swoof planet in #SmurfsVillage outer space.  http://bit.ly/SmurfVillage  @BeelineGames    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 yeppers... is it OK if I come over a bit earlier? I don't wanna be at home. lol    
    
    
    @rmiller_08 okie dokie, sounds good. :)    
    
    
    @BFSEsq is that Valentine's Day stuff?    
    
    
    @TheMadamEditor @AlizaLicht YES! It comes out this spring... It's called The Pirate Fairy or something like that! my niece is so excited.    
    
    
    let's go #LIONS!    
    
    
    "I'm too busy sellin' 50 million records."    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica OMG! We're like the same person... I'm eating Oreos, too!    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica rats! mine are just plain 'ole double stuf. the flavored ones creep me out. #weirdo    
    
    
    baby thinkin' of you keeps me up all night.    
    
    
    Longest 8 minutes ever has started.    
    
    
    ITS BRITNEY BxxCH!    
    
    
    Cue a million sales of watermelon bubblegum.    
    
    
    I love you @britneyspears! Thanks for sharing your journey through #IAmBritneyJean xxoo    
    
    
    @itsmemikepe who doesn't!? @britneyspears    
    
    
    @bitty_boop @britneyspears #flawless    
    
    
    @mz hot stuff 😉    
    
    
    @MuuMuse I just told my friend that...how funny. Wonder how @Allure_magazine feels about their pic going unremembered. @britneyspears    
    
    
    .@britneyspears your daddy is adorable. #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    SPARK! and it's like gasoline. #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    @RealBRITannica kitty kitty!? Wtf! Haha    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS awww and you're my lobster. (You've seen this #friends episode yes?) #army    
    
    
    Britney breaks her neck.

"Oh I'm good, thank you."    
    
    
    Go beyond reason to love because it's the only safety there is.    
    
    
    Did @britneyspears just announce #alien as a single? #notalone    
    
    
    "Are you ever lonely?"    
    
    
    THANK YOU BABY JESUS. Everytime is in the show. @britneyspears #IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    I kinda feel like a jerk for being upset about the lack of #BritneyJean promo now... she's working her @$$ off for Vegas...#IAmBritneyJean    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 it's AMAZING! It's definitely as amazing as FTR, but better 'cuz she's SO HAPPY in this one.    
    
    
    @djchriscox I'm asking!! @britneyspears -- you're up! :)    
    
    
    @MEGABRITNEYFAN and I wasn't all THAT upset with the lack of promo, but I was still bummed she didn't get her well deserved 7th #1!    
    
    
    @MEGABRITNEYFAN I think they shoulda waited until March to release the album... she woulda knew the routines +  more time for promo.    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS thank God! I was sooo debating about sending that #FRIENDS reference. hahaha    
    
    
    Go beyond reason to love — it is safe. It is the only safety. ~ Thaddeus Golas    
    
    
    @mz @britneyspears I'm coming for my birthday on April 25!! And hopefully on April 25 next year if she's performing for the big 3-0!!    
    
    
    @SamanthaLuthra yes. that sounds very horrifying. hahaha    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 perfection is an understatement.    
    
    
    wired from #IAmBritneyJean but sinus migraine wants me to sleep. i'm a mixed bag of emotions.    
    
    
    Smurfy Tip: Use stardust to clear new areas on the Swoof planet in #SmurfsVillage outer space.  http://bit.ly/SmurfVillage  @BeelineGames    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious I'm so happy she's doing Everytime... Those set lists going around we're breaking my heart without it!    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa seriously! It's been nearly 13 years! How did they even think that!?    
    
    
    @tkylemac @MuuMuse so amazing! What did you contribute exactly?? :)    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious Ahhh I wish this was being shown live on TV opening night!    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious yeah - that would be awesome, too.    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS and me please!!! ;)    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS all #hail the kweens!    
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious @britneyspears @LarryRudolph @mz @AdamLeber SRSLY!! Don't want to wait I NEED it now!    
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS @Lisaney83🎶😘😍🎶    
    
    
    Counting "neys"... Starting with BOMTney. Sweet dreams, tweethearts...xo    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 @ItsDanielCS👑👑👑    
    
    
    @OutrageousNessa @ZeroSuitBritney no, she's one of Larry's minions. Her new Brett is named Robin. Haha    
    
    
    @Lisaney83 backatcha! Xo    
    
    
    This little kitten is about to get his little kitten butt kicked if he does not stop racing shadows across my bed.    
    
    
    What happened to his adorableness 30 mins ago when he was asleep on my back?? #toby    
    
    
    7 Ways to Build a Following on Instagram http://bit.ly/JBVsf0     
    
    
    "I went looking for camouflage the other day, but I couldn't find any!"    
    
    
    Facebook Promotions: 5 Things That Are Still Illegal http://bit.ly/JDpOxL     
    
    
    me. always. #awkward http://bit.ly/1jB149U     
    
    
    @Cherrow414 so how do you say Xoco?    
    
    
    @gkern I know, I have CS6. Some others might want it, though... :)    
    
    
    @cubanalaf I do. And kiss him forever and ever.    
    
    
    @Cherrow414 OK, thanks! :)    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 hooray! congrats. :)    
    
    
    @Cherrow414 no...I just didn't know! Haha    
    
    
    THANK YOU SO MUCH @SamBourque23! He is thrilled! :) pic.twitter.com/Z0SB0h5efX    
    
    
    so grateful for friends who go above + beyond to make the lives of others amazing. <3    
    
    
    @SamBourque23 he says "All anyone else got was the name plate, I 'made out like a bandit'!" hahaha he's so excited! :) thank you again!    
    
    
    Leverage Blog Content Seeding to Gain New Readers http://bit.ly/19yMHg7     
    
    
    @ItsDanielCS confession: Wizard of Oz gives me nightmares.    
    
    
    How to find ‘the one’ in PR http://bit.ly/1huOzYV     
    
    
    Have a rewarding week! Use your Smurfberries to smurf something new in your #smurfsvillage @BeelineGames http://bit.ly/SmurfApp     
    
    
    Brand journalism is the new PR  http://bit.ly/J6Of6c     
    
    
    @malrich10 girl! -3 is nothin! Wait for th -15degree windchill! Haha    
    
    
    God bless us, every one! #merrychristmas    
    
    
    #LGRW #winterclassic #goblue http://instagram.com/p/iUVS29xAKz/     
    
    
    @ViviLiiiicious same here. Winter needs to come or go...make up it's dang mind!    
    
    
    @bitty_boop it's a classic,    
    
    
    @JasontheScott JTT's "Home for Christmas", Jim Carrey's "The Grinch" and Care Bear's Nutcracker. :)    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 "Do You Hear What I Hear?" and "Oh Holy Night"! :)    
    
    
    8 Simple Scientifically Proven Ways to Improve Your Writing http://bit.ly/19y4Dat     
    
    
    @BFSEsq mine won't leave his present alone.    
    
    
    @TiffanyHoughton yes!! @crowdsurf is amazing!! One of my dream companies to work for one day! ☺️you're amazing, too - love the new song! Xo    
    
    
    Hurry up darkness! Can't wait to get home to Dexter for luminaries tonight! #merrychristmas    
    
    
    @TreeTownSound @Madonna only if Like a Prayer does, Too!    
    
    
    Praying the weather forecast holds true and we get out 2" of snow. I love waking up to a white(er) Christmas! ❄️    
    
    
    Christmas Eve cuddles... http://instagram.com/p/iUjYYoxAC2/     
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 that was just on the radio! I like Carrie Underwood's... It's beautiful and very simple!    
    
    
    Is "stress Emily out and ruin every holiday for her" written on my forehead or something? :(    
    
    
    @KatieReilly06 I love Transiberrian's "Christmas Cannon!"    
    
    
    my little village is more adorable and perfect on Christmas Eve than anywhere in the world...    
    
    
    "you're defined by who you become when you're under pressure."    
    
    
    i've been watching @MichaelPhelps swimming videos on @youtube for like, an hour...#teamUSA    
    
    
    