@tjfaust nice! have an amazing time. you going to be blogging or anything?    
    
    
    @KHil i think she's circa 30    
    
    
    Not gonna lie, a little offended that Google thinks I'm a dude. MT @bgreinhart: Link to see who Google thinks you are: http://bit.ly/tRQbjw     
    
    
    @pug JRTs are the best (pugs are pretty cute too tho...)    
    
    
    Oh snap, here we go: RT @SarahFKessler: RT @mashable: BREAKING: Facebook to File for IPO Next Week [REPORT] - http://on.mash.to/zFqxwH     
    
    
    What up Big Blue RT @BostonTweet: Belichick has won 5 conference titles (2001, 2003, 2004, 2007, 2011) since being hired on this day in 2000    
    
    
    (No, I don't care about football, just can't resist a little alma mater pride)    
    
    
    Disappointing to me that someone as talented and creative as JF doesn't see the possibilities of ebooks. Paper's dead. http://tgr.ph/yTzKcG     
    
    
    Cool infographic explaining how pasta, not bacon, makes you fat: http://bit.ly/AkVmh8  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Boston mayor wants more tech startups to hire high school interns: http://b.globe.com/wGorDf  (by @GlobeMBFarrell) Good idea or no?    
    
    
    Love it! Might be taking my first Uber... MT @danprimack: @Uber_BOS will be providing half-off rides for #GetLiquid attendees tonight    
    
    
    @ZachServideo Yep. Kindof creepy..    
    
    
    Incredible RT @stefugee: 1865 letter from emancipated slave to former master. http://bit.ly/xwcmkr     
    
    
    Makes me want to start a new tradition! RT @jolieodell: Tea: the best meal of the day http://bit.ly/yI8i0d     
    
    
    Alleyoop launches! Pearson-backed startup aims to be the Zynga of education: http://on.mash.to/z0qMWM  via @SarahFKessler for @mashable    
    
    
    Who owns FB? Fascinating: MT @ScottKirsner: In advance of the FB filing, there's this: http://bit.ly/jztKQ5     
    
    
    Kudos! RT @CDiRusso: Congrats to @LaunchSquad clients @Fab and @evernote for winning big at the #crunchies last night    
    
    
    @tjfaust LS does, I don't personally. They are indeed awesome.    
    
    
    Need a judge? cc @BKramer MT @BostonTweet: Burrito Bowl, comp to create the best burrito, this Sat @Poes_Kitchen 1-4pm http://bit.ly/wW5PCI     
    
    
    @CBM I need something like that for Twitter....    
    
    
    @CBM the problem is people I like & whose tweets I otherwise care about. Just want to filter out the football mania...    
    
    
    Check it out: RT @TechCrunch: Pearson-Incubated Startup Alleyoop Launches To Gamify Adaptive Learning  http://tcrn.ch/weVk9V  by @ripemp    
    
    
    @fvinh now *that* is a good channel.    
    
    
    Bought a hard copy of GOOD magazine this weekend, and have been very impressed. Check it out if you haven't, for sure. http://bit.ly/sZESgF     
    
    
    Great post: MT @usnews: Could Alleyoop Be the Spotify of Math Education? http://bit.ly/yMP9Du  by @jason_koebler    
    
    
    @Michele_Moore Never been a big fan of the cold, haha. ;) Went to college in TX to escape it -- looks like we have lots in common!    
    
    
    @Michele_Moore Rice -- never thought I'd end up back here, but Boston's such a great city I'm learning to deal with the cold :)    
    
    
    It's true. Awww. #puppyclout RT @mfarbs: LaunchSquad Boston swooning over this bundle of cuteness: http://bit.ly/Aaq523  cc: @kcinnamond    
    
    
    @ing_infocus wait.. what?! i'm intrigued..    
    
    
    @ing_infocus Very cool! Lemme know when you're soliciting donations :)    
    
    
    @paulbtucker @awhitelie Goodreads got me on that (and then told me what a bajillion random acquaintances were reading) #dislikeautofriending    
    
    
    Rather unfortunate RT @fvinh: Oh, Mittens. This is not subtle at all. http://twitpic.com/8glbi8     
    
    
    No joke. Amazing story. RT @mfarbs: Wonder Dog. I dare you not to well up while reading: http://nyti.ms/y7eJv3     
    
    
    Love that the post on Agile dev I just read had a shout-out to Dickens and his "too easily overlooked" contributions to lit #literategeeks    
    
    
    Puppy thieves?! Off with their heads! http://bit.ly/wilpyL     
    
    
    @adayal on behalf of Cambridge, you're welcome.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker good date?    
    
    
    Phew. Who steals a puppy? MT @BostonTweet: Pebbles, dog stolen from Beacon Hill, was just found 30 mi away in Lowell http://on.fb.me/z6GPpA     
    
    
    Very cool. MT @ScottKirsner: @MassGovernor is planning to tour a "net zero " house in Newton: http://bit.ly/rbqmnn  (1st one in BOS area?)    
    
    
    @8bitJay Aww! Dachsund? Yours?    
    
    
    @8bitJay nice! all the fun, none of the poop duty    
    
    
    Gourmet restaurant lends kitchen to aspiring chefs: http://bit.ly/xL2xNo  Cool idea!    
    
    
    Seriously! RT @Zims: Great @Fab profile from @pandodaily: "That isn’t an etailer. That’s Anna Wintour."    
    
    
    USA! USA! RT @nath_on_fire: "The Pile of Poo registered 3.3/2.8 in the key demos, while the Parks & Rec airing opposite it scored 1.3/0.9."    
    
    
    And this is why we can't have nice [television shows] #coughcommunitycough    
    
    
    Holy crap, Google. When did you learn this trick? http://yfrog.com/ketajjp     
    
    
    The theme is sunshine & energy :) RT @mfarbs: Just picked out some paint/carpets for new offices w/ @MegScarborough. "Grassy Fields" anyone?    
    
    
    @petfurniture ha. love.    
    
    
    Just passed a place selling single roses for $6.50. So yeah.    
    
    
    On a cheerier note, hope you get to spend your Valentines Day with someone you love, snuggled up like lil buuunnnnies.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus Fair point. Maybe some of the boys were buying flowers for their boyfriends...    
    
    
    @onewil that's a great photo    
    
    
    @onewil nah. i'm a dog person.    
    
    
    @onewil wait... sweatshirt or cat? ha    
    
    
    @onewil ahh... boyfriend just got one in the mail, loves it. they're a client of ours, super high-quality, american made.    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris totally depends on whether they're on land or in the water    
    
    
    @AbbyVW Do you know yet what you want to specialize in when you're done?    
    
    
    @charlesmhampton yes    
    
    
    Oh, that sounds divine MT @tosci: Andy made Semla ice cream based on Swedish Fat Tuesday pastry.  Cardamom, marzipan, cake, mascarpone.    
    
    
    Uncharted territory. Westward ho! RT @mat: Hey tech journos, has anyone written about Pinterest yet?    
    
    
    Great time at #RubyRiot. Very impressed with Gov. Patrick. Thx guys! #payitforward    
    
    
    Think I helped a couple techstars dudes refine their elevator pitch while in line for #RubyRiot last nite. Does that count as #payitforward?    
    
    
    @AbbyVW Okay, little Bobby. Time for your Jagermeister. Open up!    
    
    
    @jenniroja meh. i just did, and i'm unimpressed so far.    
    
    
    @tjfaust oh, don't hate on Carole    
    
    
    @tjfaust ha. totally misread that. GOOD.    
    
    
    @Hey_Billy their tourism board needs to hire you    
    
    
    Check out @Unrollme - http://mashable.com/2012/02/27/unroll-me/ … - http://signup.unroll.me  unsubscribe from all email newsletters at once    
    
    
    NOT bummed that mozzarella-making just got added to the agenda for our lake weekend. @notABBY: Future Astronaut & Fearless Queen of Dairy.    
    
    
    Okay, I need to know this. What is up with fashion bloggers who don't put their arms in their sleeves?    
    
    
    @awhitelie @tjfaust seconded. but I get most of my news from NPR, so ...    
    
    
    Rescued yet another piece of furniture from the curb. The drawer pull screams 1980s Miami, but nothing a visit to Anthropologie can't solve.    
    
    
    Down with Paypal! RT @cheryllmorris: AmEx launches Serve Facebook app for friend-to-friend payments http://bit.ly/yq6Nto     
    
    
    Cool thought piece on how mobile payment systems could make us more financially responsible http://bit.ly/w9T8Ym  from @wfrick @BostInno    
    
    
    @paulbtucker, other Austin ppl: good central restaurant recs at places unlikely to be booked for SXSW? Nicer bar-type setting? cc @ESal    
    
    
    @paulbtucker gracias    
    
    
    Welp! Looks like @LaunchSquad is officially moving. Like, right now.    
    
    
    @bgreinhart http://bit.ly/9l6Hx6     
    
    
    @bgreinhart it's never in the idea, always in the execution ;)    
    
    
    Barbara Lynch launches a nutrition startup: http://bit.ly/yuMBjy  That lady is on fire. via @bbjnewsroom    
    
    
    Woo! RT @clreisman: SessionM comes out of stealth today! Check out details in NYT (http://nyti.ms/w62LL9 ) and WSJ (http://on.wsj.com/waKHea )    
    
    
    Startup with a sense of humor taking on a sucky leech of an industry (see: razor blades)? Sign me up: http://bit.ly/AE8yOl     
    
    
    I've bounced around to do list apps for the last 6 months and finally landed on one I love -- Workflowy. Not for everyone, but I'm happy.    
    
    
    Today marks my debut as a hand model. Look out for my right thumb at @HealyHoops 's awesome SXSW presentation, #SMBGoliath this Saturday!    
    
    
    You're gonna change your mind about this rain business, aren't you now, Austin?    
    
    
    Bummed I missed this - Elizabeth Warren Visits Zume's Coffee House http://charlestown.patch.com/articles/elizabeth-warren-visits-zume-s-cafe …    
    
    
    Had AA force me to size check my carry on 3 times. Fit every time. They still made me check it. Uncool.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker the latter. I mean, at least I didn't pay a fee, but delays galore often = lost baggage    
    
    
    Breakfast tacos = officially in Tejas pic.twitter.com/F198pP7A    
    
    
    Quality smoked meats and deer processing pic.twitter.com/EH62SBrc    
    
    
    Weather may not be ideal, but the company is. Also: friggin love this city. #austin pic.twitter.com/4rmgQdAQ    
    
    
    To the lake!    
    
    
    Huh. Apparently Skrillex is playing in New Braunfels, TX in May. You heard it here first.    
    
    
    How you know we're not in college anymore pic.twitter.com/L4DE1bs9    
    
    
    How would you recommend a startup approach a larger vendor to OEM its products? #SMBGoliath    
    
    
    Yeah! RT @mfarbs: @healyhoops in action at #SXSW2012 http://twitpic.com/8umvym     
    
    
    We made mozzarella! @notabby @paulbtucker @betsylo9 pic.twitter.com/R6IbY8xf    
    
    
    Bottomless mimosas $5 (we're not in Boston anymore, Toto) pic.twitter.com/COagoxEV    
    
    
    Just saw a dude in a gstring and nothing else riding a bike under the bridge. #keepaustinweird    
    
    
    My Austin food binge continues back home with a humongous cream puff from Modern Pastry. Mmmm... Thanks, @annafarnum & @LaunchSquad Boston!    
    
    
    @melodytran Thank you so much! We miss you too!! Hope NYC is treating you well -- come visit soon.    
    
    
    Better to pay the grocer RT @DKThomp: Family spending on food/drink down 18% since 1947, spending on health care up 13% http://bit.ly/yDxEhV     
    
    
    @acgaughen HOLY CRAP girl. That's amazing.    
    
    
    @acgaughen wowza. reminds me of http://bit.ly/yiQ0iz     
    
    
    Soo tasty! RT @mfarbs: Birthday treats for @megscarborough! Yum. Thanks for bringing them in @annafarnum! http://twitpic.com/8wcfd7     
    
    
    First day leaving work while it's still light  in a long time. Woo!    
    
    
    Best part of working from home? Canine productivity boosters. pic.twitter.com/e13iT5iu    
    
    
    Went to the Pru last night assuming the power would be back. It wasn't, but the building was open. It was eerie, zombiepocalypse-style.    
    
    
    Good thing it's not a typical frosty March in Boston, considering all these blackouts.    
    
    
    No kidding! RT @sweller: I cannot wait until Google adds real-time drone footage to Google Maps. That would be sweet. "Google Drone". ;)    
    
    
    Mom has some OT clients who don't speak English, so I downloaded and showed her how to use Google Translate app yesterday. Technology FTW!    
    
    
    Nice find! cc @awhitelie RT @HealyHoops: RT @Alltop: Guinness vs Beer: Which is the healthiest? [infographic] http://post.ly/61rZg     
    
    
    Startup brewery Trillium coming to the Innovation District: http://bit.ly/FQTX8Q  Exciting!    
    
    
    A little girl encounters non-streaming TV for the first time: http://bit.ly/w6SEti  Hilarious, oddly poignant & also: the future.    
    
    
    @tjfaust non-native English speaker?    
    
    
    @acromp Yep. So true. Love me some Lana, do not care what she's like in real life.    
    
    
    Really fun, full Interprep event tonight! But where's my Andover '05 representation??    
    
    
    Well, New England failed at the whole winter thing, but so far so good in the spring department. #77andsunnyftw    
    
    
    Man I hate misleading SEO. If you show up when I google "conference table," you better damn well sell conference tables. #firstworldproblems    
    
    
    Should be illegal. MT @Pistachio: we were JAWS AGAPE when we read about the @USPS "Every Door Direct Mail" campaign. ENCOURAGING junkmail?    
    
    
    Collectivism leads to groupthink; collaboration leads to innovation. The differences & why they matter on @inc http://bit.ly/GGRBFo     
    
    
    That VIEW. Now I'm jealous. RT @awhitelie: 85 & Sunny on March 22? Well, Boston. You're alright by me. http://bit.ly/GJrJJv     
    
    
    I predict a not-far-off future when companies will be chastised for building sites that aren't pin-friendly. Optimize for Pinterest now.    
    
    
    @aechase eh, I think they'll figure that out.    
    
    
    Why working too many hours is bad for productivity: http://bit.ly/GNT0Kc  via @EntryLevelRebel on @inc    
    
    
    @magdawis yeah, I'm with you. It was all over the place.    
    
    
    @JFGIV Nice! Congrats! They are awesome. You going to take it?    
    
    
    [spews beverage] RT @tjfaust: Death is bad enough, but having your heart keep Dick Cheney alive must be among the worst possible fates.    
    
    
    @mattyoun I feel like he's the kind of comedian who needs to play off others...    
    
    
    @trevoragilbert any idea yet when your travels will carry you to Boulder?    
    
    
    @mattyoun gotcha. yeah, my bf's a big fan. he's absurd and awesome on parks    
    
    
    @trevoragilbert awesome, thanks! happy travels    
    
    
    Possible Wegman's in Boston? Sign me up. http://bit.ly/GXia9s  via @GalenMoore on BBJ. How about Kendall Sq? Hint hint...    
    
    
    Why restaurants can't stop using OpenTable, even if they're sick of the fees http://b.globe.com/GWI4ip  interesting piece by @GlobeMBFarrell    
    
    
    Seriously inspiring story: http://nyti.ms/H0DI7m  How a South Sudanese orphan made it to Yale    
    
    
    Good plan. RT @kramerbot: Hey guys, if I won the Megamillions I'd buy a lifetime supply of mini Diet Coke cans.    
    
    
    Worth a read: RT @awhitelie: Hollywood's Waning Creativity: http://bit.ly/HovPpv  -- Short films (and television - ed.) will lead the way.    
    
    
    Best line? "But I was an English major." MT @Zims: A stump speech from 2052 in McSweeney's by @twsl http://bit.ly/HzedJs     
    
    
    Hey @imJmi, I'd love to chat with you about MTV Act -- would you mind pinging me at mscarborough at launchsquad dot com?    
    
    
    @imJmi thanks for the response -- follow me & I'll DM some more info? :)    
    
    
    Minerva - reinventing the Ivy League w/ a startup mentality: pretty fascinating idea - http://bit.ly/HeoYpq  by @danprimack    
    
    
    Boston is the most organized city come tax time http://onforb.es/HhCipm  So proud.    
    
    
    So cool! MT @LaunchSquad: Client @RallySoftware's CEO Tim Miller invited to White House today for JOBS Act signing! http://apne.ws/HiwCi5     
    
    
    Me too. <3 Hill. RT @landnau: Loving "Texts from Hillary Clinton" Tumblr: http://textsfromhillaryclinton.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Interesting choice. RT @karaswisher: Breaking: Facebook to Acquire Instagram for $1 Billion http://dthin.gs/HBJzkA     
    
    
    I want false spring! MT @landnau: “When spring came, even the false spring, there were no problems except where to be happiest." - Hemingway    
    
    
    Amazing that this needs to be said, but it does: http://bit.ly/Hr9TeB  A very eloquent @AshleyJudd on misogyny in the media.    
    
    
    Let Your Employees Design the Office. Seriously. http://bit.ly/Hxu2F4  via @Inc @rallysoftware    
    
    
    Not perfect, but a very interesting take on the possible future of magazines - make 'em more like Spotify? http://bit.ly/GScRdC  @pandodaily    
    
    
    You may not be able to see this from my vantage point, but believe me: my brother joined LinkedIn today, and the apocalypse is upon us.    
    
    
    She even has a sense of humor! Swoon: http://gaw.kr/HyE5Ii  #hillzftw    
    
    
    An "eclectic gumbo of gurus" - this is real copy, folks. All too real.    
    
    
    My buddy @jsmangat in a very cool NYT article today on teaching docs & med students how to cook healthy meals: http://nyti.ms/HwGcZw  Love it    
    
    
    @paulbtucker dude. same shit here with the MBTA.    
    
    
    How to make online education work better RT @Nathan_S_Scott: Read @km's latest for The Atlantic. http://theatln.tc/IFq3E2     
    
    
    Great WBUR piece on the space squeeze in Kendall: http://bit.ly/IGVFGv  w/ @officedrop's @HealyHoops. We need more dog-friendly office space!    
    
    
    Breaking news: I share a birthday with Shredder from the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turles. You can thank @awhitelie for that fun fact.    
    
    
    @landnau Nikka the spambot :P    
    
    
    @landnau haha, certainly not. just cracks me up.    
    
    
    @acromp that tweet is giving me flashbacks to a bad, bad choice I made at Mai's    
    
    
    To be fair, it's a small table. RT @kramerbot: We couldn't hear the presentation in Boston so I tipped over the conference table.    
    
    
    Agreed. MT @laurenfitte: I vouch for the shout outs to Houston Vietnamese restos: 6 Rules for Dining Out - The Atlantic http://bit.ly/HDYEEs     
    
    
    Meet Cash, our awesome new dog. Came from a shelter in CA, is the coolest. pic.twitter.com/qXsUH5n1    
    
    
    @paulbtucker @alanaatucker haha. Other two are my parents. He's our first!    
    
    
    Good luck to everyone running the #bostonmarathon today. Hydrate!    
    
    
    Agreed! RT @sweller: What bubble? Its a technology renaissance, with mobile leading the way.    
    
    
    @sweller @cheryllmorris Haha. Good point & awesome metaphor.    
    
    
    @tjfaust He is excited to lick you in return. You guys can have a "who has more hair" competition.    
    
    
    @KHil It has been described in my office as "Twilight fanfic" and "softcore mommy porn." If that helps...    
    
    
    Pinterest and Polyvore need to get married, Facebook & Instagram style. #justsayin    
    
    
    Great thought piece on how our paradigms re: money need to change to embrace tech: RT @megangarber: The death of money? http://bit.ly/HOkssi     
    
    
    @landnau I just watched it for the first time last night! I found it awkward but wonderfully well-written and painfully realistic...    
    
    
    Mind.blown. RT @kramerbot: You know what's crazy? I like banana flavoring, but not bananas. Think about that.    
    
    
    Two things that made my night: dinner at my fave restaurant w/ my fave dog & boy and hemp ice cream from emack & bolio #friday #happy420    
    
    
    Europe can. RT @acromp: Can we all take a step back and admit that cars (including coupes and sedans) are all just unreasonably large?    
    
    
    No fun rainy walk. pic.twitter.com/UXMenysk    
    
    
    Dude next to me at apple counter had the oldest mac laptop I've ever seen in person. At least 12 yrs old! Powerbook g3. Amazed it still runs    
    
    
    Ouch. RT @kramerbot: I hit rock bottom this weekend when my wife's uncle cut me off at a Bar Mitzvah. #truestory #ikeptdrinking    
    
    
    Now that's some PR. RT @km: "Airbnb Saved My Life" http://bit.ly/IM6l83  Crazy town.    
    
    
    OfficeDrop opens to all file types & doubles storage: http://bit.ly/Jvwg7M  Check it.    
    
    
    That book club idea is so. cool. RT @petfurniture: Let's brag on my shop for a second, can we? via @MaggieGalehouse:http://bit.ly/K1RRzA     
    
    
    Austin restaurant bans tipping (and pays waitstaff a living wage): http://bit.ly/K6JqTJ  Love this. Anyone eaten at Black Star Coop?    
    
    
    @laurenfitte Report back if you do!    
    
    
    Love that my bf now goes to SF and hangs out with my college friends without me. Warms my little heart. cc @paulbtucker @tjfaust @awhitelie    
    
    
    I'm getting really good at eyeballing a tweet-length text snippet. #sadlifeskills    
    
    
    @paulbtucker Zenni Optical.    
    
    
    Hmm... A simple but powerful idea. I could see this being really useful for out-of-classroom learning: http://bit.ly/I901uV  #edtech    
    
    
    Is everyone else being inundated with fake FB friend requests? Today it's Shalolo Donga. Heh. Great name. But no.    
    
    
    Fan Accidentally Douses Obama in Fro-Yo, But He’s Cool With It http://flpbd.it/Av3pV  one more reason to <3 this man    
    
    
    A somewhat infuriating way to start your Thursday: http://bit.ly/IFx61p  The Awl on why all 25 ASME noms went to men.    
    
    
    So... I shit you not, my bro picked up a roadkill skunk, froze it in my parents' basement freezer and then skinned it yesterday. For a hat.    
    
    
    Peak plastic: http://bit.ly/IHfJe3  An interesting thought...    
    
    
    Tech's brogrammer problem: http://bit.ly/JIaN9S  - the sexism's beginning to look increasingly endemic. Has to stop.    
    
    
    Could I just have all the cupcakes that get left behind when people make disgusting things like frosting shots?    
    
    
    Should any emergencies arise, you should all know that I have poop bags in every pocket of every piece of clothing I own. #regulargirlscout    
    
    
    MT @KvnLhy: Preview of Boston's Startup Weekend EDU by @laurlandry w/ insight from @msmamet of @alleyoop http://bit.ly/Kg3unf  via @BostInno    
    
    
    @AlexSmith4000 Run.    
    
    
    @carowhack Glad to hear you're okay. Scary stuff.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus ha, what?! @awhitelie  got one saying his Amazon package was delayed due to "train derailment." And it was.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus That's amazing. Postal service equivalent of "dog ate my homework."    
    
    
    17! RT @aseitzwald: Find out how many times your [home] would fit inside Mitt Romney's car-elevator equipped manse. http://bit.ly/IYUKmG     
    
    
    For those of you who enjoy Google's Easter eggs... RT @awhitelie: Google: 'Zerg Rush'. RIGHT NOW.    
    
    
    More people listen to Rush Limbaugh than Morning Edition? This makes me want to hit all the !*&#$*#$% punctuation keys.    
    
    
    How to ditch happily ever after & build your own narrative: http://bit.ly/Io6UK8  A really important way to think about relationships. Read.    
    
    
    Sneaky photographer! RT @awhitelie: Post-Brunch Naptime http://instagr.am/p/KAoMvYxz9j/     
    
    
    One of my favorite of this talented lady's drawings: RT @danamarcelle: little red:) http://tmblr.co/Z4gxwxKd8F1r     
    
    
    Lobster gnocchi with black truffle cheddar sauce on the Mother's Day menu at Navy Yard Bistro (my fave.) I will die if I don't eat this.    
    
    
    Having a rainy Tuesday? Provided you like canines, I can cheer you up: http://bit.ly/K3VZFr     
    
    
    Spambot of the Week. RT @DealforkPORT: @MegScarborough Salmon Hash. Mother's knows best.    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott I think some of the characters are shallow at times, but the show is not shallow at all.    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott I'm ok with it in the sense that there's not a whole lot of stuff like it out there, and 20 somethings need a louder voice    
    
    
    @fvinh UM. Of happiness. Happily.    
    
    
    Very much worth a read in light of recent political events: @The_Rumpus: On Pregnancy and Privacy and Fear http://bit.ly/KPR2iQ     
    
    
    Agree, strongly. RT @km: RIP Junior Seau. Gladwell on why NCAA football should be banned. http://slate.me/JU8e6K  Football is an ugly game.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus digital inspiration board/visual bookmarking tool. check it out - i bet you'd like it. (can send an invite if you want)    
    
    
    Looking forward to @dartboston #techstars afterpart-ay. Got a serious @LaunchSquad Boston crew heading over.    
    
    
    @sweller at dartboston?    
    
    
    So good to see @RSprung @dartboston!    
    
    
    All the truths MT @jolieodell: Why geeks (and other lean machines) need high-intensity workouts: http://venturebeat.com/2012/05/05/fitness-for-geeks/ …    
    
    
    @gilbertjasono ahead of the curve    
    
    
    @nath_on_fire so much good sunday teevs    
    
    
    And take a course! RT @km: Just had a mind-expanding conversation with Andrew Ng. Follow @Coursera, y'all. They're damn serious.    
    
    
    Why the campaign to stop America's obesity epidemic keeps failing: http://bit.ly/IQ8ALq  More wisdom from @garytaubes    
    
    
    @ing_infocus @KHil i love that you both tweeted the same thing one right after the other. girls is killing it. can't get over lena being 25.    
    
    
    Underwear bomber was a double agent? I didn't dream this?    
    
    
    @katherinedally popsicles! chloraseptic if it's really bad.    
    
    
    An important question for big co's w/o a cloud sol'n RT @HealyHoops: Do I Build or OEM My Cloud Service?  http://bit.ly/IUH9Qr  via @BostInno    
    
    
    The science of spilling your coffee: http://bit.ly/IEUeKm  Well, at least our physicists are doing something useful with their time.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus repinning is always fun, but uploaded content is the most common (surprisingly I think) so yeah. that's how it's done. :)    
    
    
    Could the right combination of online tools replace the MBA? http://bit.ly/KCjikq  Cool post from @wfrick #edtech    
    
    
    @landnau jealous! have fun!    
    
    
    About that... RT @DKThomp: Our bad! The shocking graphs that prove human activity caused the drought in Texas http://bit.ly/Lx2DRM     
    
    
    People who work in advertising are more likely to misbehave at office parties. I'm looking at you @nanigans http://bit.ly/JYLVXN     
    
    
    Yup. And not buy Dell products. RT @CBM: Why we need to keep talking about women in tech http://cnet.co/IQHYu7  #dell #Denmark    
    
    
    Conclusive proof that MA is the best state: http://slate.me/J4T66v  #suckit    
    
    
    Six reasons non-geeks might want to learn to code http://bit.ly/JETlCB  via @ESal - Easy to imagine a future where everyone is taught code.    
    
    
    @RWHBray See that's the part I'm confused about. I'm pretty sure the South is the punching bag here. But I suppose my perspective is skewed.    
    
    
    @onewil and vice versa    
    
    
    @tjfaust dude, you really should sign up to be a dog babysitter @dogvacay or something. get paid to cuddle.    
    
    
    Love it. Stevie Wonder never fails. MT @gilbertjasono: Michelle Obama releases workout playlist on Spotify: http://spoti.fi/L0vYlu     
    
    
    Haha. Amazing MT @petfurniture: Not that anyone has ever ASKED me to, but this is how indies can compete with Amazon: Couples counseling.    
    
    
    For real. RT @jsmangat: "few people take the role of livestock in producing greenhouse gases srsly enough." @bittman http://nyti.ms/IYzKuV     
    
    
    "This isn't just a farm bill -- it's a food bill, helping to dictate what kinds of food people can afford." http://huff.to/JKTQfj     
    
    
    Why you should wear pants even if you WFH: http://on.wsj.com/LXiSI7     
    
    
    @petfurniture i think it's on you, girlfriend. capture the zeitgeist!    
    
    
    Common is lovely at twilight pic.twitter.com/wwS3fPXN    
    
    
    @petfurniture it can. but don't delete. you never know when you might need to reconnect w/ someone. devil's advocate here.    
    
    
    @megangarber just don't take away our animated GIFs!    
    
    
    If I don't eat the frosting, it's just a muffin, right? #breakfastcupcakes #dontjudge (thanks for the treats @mfarbs!)    
    
    
    Hey @megangarber -- sent you an email earlier in the week re: your piece on big data in education. Would love to chat edtech with you!    
    
    
    @thetacotruck right outside my gym? Please and thank you. #oasis    
    
    
    Oh noes... RT @awhitelie: Who has two thumbs and just accidentally set off a fire extinguisher in a 3'x8' space? #thisguy    
    
    
    Pintern? Really? Too soon.    
    
    
    @pug permanently? whoa!    
    
    
    @paulbtucker Ha. #usafail. Pretty sure that would take like 2 hours in Europe.    
    
    
    Watched Tiny Furniture last night. Cements my worship of @lenadunham. Girlfriend can write.    
    
    
    Can easily count the number of ppl I will voluntarily talk to on the phone for 2 hours on one hand. @BetsyLO is one.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog i cannot lie. i like big phones.    
    
    
    Not not in a stretch hummer... pic.twitter.com/J9srBow5    
    
    
    Great post in @theatlantic on client @Alleyoop's very cool learning technology: http://bit.ly/LrtU9g  by @megangarber    
    
    
    Yep RT @TheBloggess: There is something wonderful though about Ray Bradbury taking over the twitter trends.  Gives me hope for humanity yet.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog So glad you're ok, and so glad you wore a helmet.    
    
    
    @wfrick breakfast *tacos* are where it's at. imo sandwiches are always going to win in Boston, tho, bc Tex Mex is not our forte.    
    
    
    @wfrick unfortunately no. i've yet to encounter one. next time you're in Austin. :)    
    
    
    An absolutely lovely day of wine tasting in Napa. Feeling lucky to have such a wonderful family.    
    
    
    Crossing a big one off the bucket list today... pic.twitter.com/gO7mjwff    
    
    
    @petfurniture i read that as pants the first go round. and totally understood what you meant. oops?    
    
    
    @BostInnovation: .@Alleyoop: Making College Readiness Attainable for High School Students http://bit.ly/LGWHJv     
    
    
    Amazingly depressing animated gif/graph of the obesity trend: http://bit.ly/Mm01Za     
    
    
    Cool RT @CurtNickisch: Can't be at #TEDxBoston to learn about ideas worth spreading? @WBUR goes live from the conference at 1pm @RadioBoston    
    
    
    ! MT @educationdebate: Congrats to @yesprep on winning the Broad Prize to increase college readiness among low-income students. Great work!    
    
    
    Not very subtle, Magic Hat, but point taken. pic.twitter.com/5yRemRtI    
    
    
    Who *wouldn't* want to watch an episode called "One Voice in the Cosmic Fugue" ?    
    
    
    @drlieber You too!! Look forward to it :)    
    
    
    @alexismadrigal congrats!! looks like it was beautiful. :)    
    
    
    @petfurniture haven't gotten to Cosmicomics but I think "Winter's Night" is the only experimental lit I ever really and truly loved, so YES.    
    
    
    Good work, team.    
    
    
    Man just looking at a picture of a TI-83 gives me the shivers    
    
    
    That thing where you look up and suddenly the office is completely empty and you wonder if you missed the apocalypse memo    
    
    
    Great post, excellent points MT @thefilmgoer: @Nathan_S_Scott & I hate-watch the shit out of The Newsroom today on SFTB http://bit.ly/LfT79P     
    
    
    Yup. RT @czsays: I cannot express how vehemently I support the views in this post. "Quit Telling Us We're Not Special." http://bit.ly/LxfQ0U     
    
    
    @giornalista515 congrats on the new gig, Victoria!    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd clairvoyant    
    
    
    Mmmm... first good peach of the season. Gotta be one of my favorite parts of summer.    
    
    
    @czsays NERD ALERT RED.    
    
    
    @CDiRusso that sounds delicious. i haven't graduated to grilling fruit yet but i need to give it a whirl! how's the new gig?    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris @czsays truly momentous. Cannot wait.    
    
    
    Perfect night for some summer softball pic.twitter.com/JviIKDxH    
    
    
    My bf legit has more shoes than me. Just brought home some espadrilles. Does your bf even know what espadrilles are?    
    
    
    The eternal question of what to do with old receipts: http://bit.ly/OtSC7w  @halophoenix offers some tips on @lifehacker. ck out @officedrop!    
    
    
    @landnau haha. that's fantastic. it hasn't come to that yet chez nous, but no doubt someday it will.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker @landnau I didn't say there was. Mainly I feel sorry for my own shoe collection. FWIW I quite like having a well-dressed beau.    
    
    
    Cash & Dash: the official meeting cc @cheryllmorris @czsays pic.twitter.com/foeRislo    
    
    
    What kind? hint hint @tosci RT @GalenMoore: Statement: @Uber_BOS promises an ice cream truck 10 minutes after you call. http://bit.ly/LbLVKt     
    
    
    @KHil Way to go! I'm sure it was a tough decision, but you gotta do the right thing for you. :)    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris awww! #7 kinda looks like Dasher    
    
    
    A fantastic, surprising & accurate essay: Why Go Out? by Sheila Heti http://www.sheilaheti.net/whygoout.html     
    
    
    @Hey_Billy what good is social media if we can't use it to measure our moral worth?    
    
    
    @laurenfitte glad you enjoyed! she's got a new book out that i'm intrigued by...    
    
    
    Great cause! MT @mfarbs: #Prouty: 200 mi bike ride in the mtns to fight cancer. Please help if you can: http://youtu.be/M8Q-lQvJvV8     
    
    
    @acromp I swear I'm not being cheeky, but... http://bit.ly/dOHzoG  Would that work?    
    
    
    @acromp more ROBUSTNESS for everyone    
    
    
    Yeahhh! RT @ESal: Awesome! Go, go, go! RT @mfarbs: Halfway home!  http://twitpic.com/a73vq8  #prouty    
    
    
    What did you accomplish before 8 a.m. today? Cuz this guy... RT @mfarbs: 25 down! #prouty    
    
    
    A male comedian responds to the Tosh controversy and gets it very very right http://bit.ly/Sf79aT     
    
    
    Hilarity ensues RT @Nathan_S_Scott: For those who missed it -- I make fun of @ThoughtCatalog and they publish it. http://bit.ly/M7cAYH     
    
    
    @KHil She's so fresh.    
    
    
    My stinking carpetbag owners need to get a car with a/c pic.twitter.com/NnjLHJ9y    
    
    
    Accepting a CEO position while pregnant. I want to give Marissa Mayer a big hug on behalf of womankind. Esp post Atlantic cover story.    
    
    
    Great post RT @megangarber: Marissa Mayer is a role model. I can't wait for the day when she no longer has to be. http://bit.ly/NG65YX     
    
    
    Great advice. http://witanddelight.tumblr.com/post/27406251945 …    
    
    
    Had a great time at last nights #muckedupboston - thanks for organizing!    
    
    
    @drlieber I was thinking the same thing. My hydrangeas have been looking seriously crispy of late. #cantremembertowatereveryday    
    
    
    Took the dog for his first legit run. He performed admirably for a smidge. #tired #gladitcooledoff pic.twitter.com/Ob1X9dNV    
    
    
    Oh golly, sign me up! Area Four Brings Lawn Games (and Soft Serve) to Kendall Square http://flpbd.it/bQSnI     
    
    
    @drlieber aww shucks. we are pretty fond of the booger.    
    
    
    Ha. MT @harrymccracken: Beginning to think that if singletasking had been invented after multitasking, we'd regard it as a great leap fwd    
    
    
    @LaunchSquad Boston Beach Olympics 2012, here we come !    
    
    
    Djibouti planning to sweep, you guys might not want to bother coming #launchsquadbeacholympics #trashtalk    
    
    
    Cuba wins the costume contest #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/uwVZkZSO    
    
    
    Canadian biathlon complete with dizzy bat and squirt guns #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/Bok4RQhf    
    
    
    L'equipe de France #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/pN06p5FL    
    
    
    Canada goes for the dive #croissanttoss #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/LEby8hs6    
    
    
    Seafulls are thrilled. Canada is victorious and buttery. #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/lXPjQmi9    
    
    
    France competes in the #cubanmissilecrisis event. #launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/d2Jxy2UZ    
    
    
    Can you beat them at their own game ?#launchsquadbeacholympics pic.twitter.com/Vq1uAdw1    
    
    
    And the tiebreaker: Hunger Games Croissanthole #launchsquadbeacholympics    
    
    
    Such a great idea for moving without the waste of cardboard boxes! http://flpbd.it/n95JR     
    
    
    Nothin like the wind in your ears on a fine summer day pic.twitter.com/RcSd2RjS    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog Congrats! That's awesome!    
    
    
    Do it! RT @sessionm: Vote for @sessionm in the MassTLC Awards: Startup to Watch category http://ow.ly/csnRz     
    
    
    Read this. "Thank You, Mr. Romney" by @km http://bit.ly/P4EJjl  #obamacare #aca    
    
    
    Nice. RT @km: In the last 18 months, Boston vs. New York high-tech: 9-0 in IPOs and 3-1 in big M&A http://bit.ly/LGwpSF  Advantage: Boston.    
    
    
    Coolest infographic I've seen in a long time: MT @stefugee: this is neat. envisioning future technology http://bit.ly/LLhStq     
    
    
    Guys I'm going to stare at that infographic and drool for a while, so just move along #nothingtoseehere    
    
    
    @drlieber Don't know if it's the same thing, but I remember NPR did a story last year on test tube hamburger meat - fascinating    
    
    
    @drlieber http://n.pr/qILlBi  See, and ironically enough, this makes me reconsider eating meat.    
    
    
    @drlieber Most likely -- crazy stuff    
    
    
    If you aren't eating a whole lot of @tosci ice cream this summer, believe me, you're doing it wrong. @LaunchSquad Boston yum!    
    
    
    Love me a good summer afternoon thunderstorm #boston    
    
    
    @stefugee Oh yeah, I have no idea what many of them are. Fascinated by interface & biotech generally, most excited for embedded screens    
    
    
    @stefugee true, but ads will get smarter and less annoying too. evetually they'll just be helpful/exactly what you need #wishfulthinking    
    
    
    @stefugee yeah, haha. tbh i think they missed a big one by skipping "media."    
    
    
    @petfurniture oh lord me too. #raisedontheeagles    
    
    
    Need help! What's your fav productivity/to do app? Simple=good, but RTM and Teuxdeux (and the other 10 i've tried) just aren't cutting it.    
    
    
    @pithyblahblah tried Workflowy. It's a cool interface, but no apps and it doesn't organize by deadline, etc. It's good for outlining    
    
    
    @pithyblahblah And Things is $$. I'm hesitant to pay money for a to do list app when I'm as picky as I am.    
    
    
    @EntryLevelRebel reports on the benefits of having a drink or two at work: http://bit.ly/HXKZ6H  Cheers, indeed.    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @sweller: Forbes: @larsalbright 's SessionM is a Game Changer for Mobile Apps and Ads. http://tinyurl.com/bw7cspe  @sessionm    
    
    
    @petfurniture he's there to meet with the lizard.    
    
    
    @katherinedally lucky duckies! love @drafthouse    
    
    
    @somespecialist congrats!    
    
    
    @petfurniture you could probably publish that... just saying.    
    
    
    Nice to see Houston get some love in @Forbes http://onforb.es/SWls4w  It's a hidden gem in many ways.    
    
    
    Checked out the new pedestrian bridge from Ctown to Boston - beautiful pic.twitter.com/CAKOfSG1    
    
    
    @felicitylingle paul rever park in charlestown, science park in boston    
    
    
    Maybe I've become the kind of person who calls her favorite yogurt brand's hotline to talk about a change in the recipe. Maybe. So what?    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott Agree that it doesn't belong at #1, but Houston is much, much cooler than people realize. Driving thru it you couldn't tell.    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott For real, there are some awesome things in those strip malls. Fantastic ethnic food, for example.    
    
    
    Boulder! MT @trevoragilbert: All I’m saying is if there’s a startup disrupting the wildlife recapture space, it’s not going to be in SV.    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott ugh. moving is the worst. hope it's an upgrade at least!    
    
    
    Whoa linkedin redesign! #latetotheparty    
    
    
    At 900+ pgs, nothing to sneeze at! RT @jccronin: Not the fattest pb of all time but damn close  #proudpapa #bucketlist http://bit.ly/PjzQ26     
    
    
    @jccronin Big congrats!    
    
    
    Only problem with @VoltageCoffee chai is how fast I drink it.    
    
    
    @katherinedally OMG! Everything okay?!    
    
    
    @katherinedally glad to hear it! Scary stuff. Feel better real soon!    
    
    
    @drlieber dude. $5 precooked lobsters. all i'm saying.    
    
    
    @drlieber That's a true statement. Also CZ votes Journeyman for our first dinner foray -- have you already been?    
    
    
    @drlieber Sounds fun!    
    
    
    Fascinating. I see a place for this for sure: MT @SarahFKessler: Do Books Need A Beta Version? http://bit.ly/OJxnBT  #writerchat    
    
    
    Not as radical as it sounds! RT @glafond: #140edu what if we added video gaming to our high school curriculum ?    
    
    
    @drlieber Cute! You should totally put that on Pinterest    
    
    
    Sounds familiar, ahem @LaunchSquad Boston. Fork gremlins!  MT @Nathan_S_Scott: The daily Freecycle update: http://bit.ly/OLQmvF     
    
    
    @drlieber Dude. Sign me up.    
    
    
    Charlestown ppl who happen to follow me, sign this petition for the Hubway: http://chn.ge/T5dWV7  Don't let perfect be the enemy of good!    
    
    
    @drlieber i think that's just the wine talking    
    
    
    Blang RT @czsays: For Cash: YES. http://etsy.me/PK2Xw9     
    
    
    So there's that. RT @KHil: Life is perfect because here is the CorgiCam: http://youtu.be/zS8QI-j8yb8  cc @czsays    
    
    
    Hey @AndreaSmith just shot you an email to let you know about some cool edtech news coming up this week - would love to get your thoughts!    
    
    
    @drlieber Happy first day!    
    
    
    Days I wish @notABBY was still tweeting... #curiosity    
    
    
    @petfurniture do they make gummy anti-depressants yet? that would probably work on a couple levels    
    
    
    How Apple & Amazon security flaws led to an epic hacking: http://bit.ly/MZqkH5   - You need to read this. @wired    
    
    
    @KHil well, that seems apt.    
    
    
    Great points! RT @sweller: Our very own @larsalbright "Win With Mobile Ads: Focus on Value" http://bit.ly/MKyqPl  #mobile #boston #sessionm    
    
    
    MT @KvnLhy: If you're into #iPhone rumors @gazelle_com is giving away a new iPhone if you guess the release date: http://on.fb.me/P3N5JU     
    
    
    Hey @harrisonweber - got some cool East Coast edtech news coming up later in the week -- interested in taking a look?    
    
    
    @lilsmcc dude those things are expensive. you need to get a fly swatter.    
    
    
    MT @petfurniture: EVERYTHING Is Giving You Cancer, Might As Well Just Consume Whatever Makes You Happy & Is Not Produced Unethically    
    
    
    @magdawis haha. you are *not* kidding. #humanitiesmajorproblems    
    
    
    Cash went for a walk today with a dog named Meatball. Kudos.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog dude, that is exactly my system. #greatminds    
    
    
    Wisdom. RT @DeanAtWork: history and reality are at best cousins.    
    
    
    @pithyblahblah dream job.    
    
    
    It's only August 9. Can we please not say the F word for a few more weeks?    
    
    
    @paulbtucker whoo! fingers crossed for ya!    
    
    
    @drlieber yes! good stuff.    
    
    
    Amazing RT @czsays: An Unexpected Ass Kicking (or: Doing Things That Have Never Been Done Before), courtesy @joelrunyon http://bit.ly/P7LxuO     
    
    
    On the entrepreneurial employee http://bit.ly/NyjFyA  by @katherinelewis on @fortune    
    
    
    Your new favorite tumblr, right here: Pictures of Alleged Social Media Gurus - http://bit.ly/PhpW6K  (You did the right thing, @SystemOfADog)    
    
    
    “You would be disgusted at what you’re missing,” says @hoppertravel CEO Frederic Lalonde: http://tcrn.ch/NppCDo  @TechCrunch - Good stuff!    
    
    
    Disgusting. Shame on you, @united . RT @erin719nyc: @united airlines lost a 10-year-old girl & didn't even care http://ow.ly/cZkXm     
    
    
    And I'll note that while it's not nearly as awful as losing a CHILD, @united has been utterly indifferent in handling a lost item of mine.    
    
    
    @onewil Because sometimes one does not really have a choice (destinations, prices, etc.) Believe me I am now avoiding at all costs.    
    
    
    @onewil They were the most reasonably priced option by a long shot on the most recent flight I took (& the one I am angry about)    
    
    
    @lilsmcc et où vas-tu?    
    
    
    Alleyoop partners with NASA & Nat Geo to bring science education to teens http://bit.ly/OAjIiD  from @bonnyglen on @wired    
    
    
    How to get students interested in space & science: http://bit.ly/PtHjRR  by @megangarber on @theatlantic    
    
    
    @lilsmcc haha. je comprends maintenant. toujours une mauvaise idée de boire et tweet. :p    
    
    
    @lilsmcc les deux je pense, mais "ils vont me manquer" = le futur, "ils me manquent" = le present (but my mon français est bigtime rusty...)    
    
    
    Boyfriend is home again and things are as they should be pic.twitter.com/aIlFwNhu    
    
    
    Freedom from expense report hell, courtesy of @officedrop & ExpenseMagic http://bit.ly/NN4DFr  on @FastCompany    
    
    
    Those of you familiar with my rants re: American work schedules will be unsurprised that I love this: http://nyti.ms/PIOnKw     
    
    
    Ooo fun! Love ours. RT @AndreaSmith: Now You Can Color the Jawbone Jambox as Loud as It Plays http://on.mash.to/O0nVr0     
    
    
    Mine too. Embarrassing how hard this makes me laugh: RT @kaylawebley: My new favorite tumblr: http://bit.ly/PuuGT9     
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott So good. On Beauty, not so much (IMO). Interested to see how NW is.    
    
    
    Awww RT @ESal: I particularly love the evil look on this Dogshaming candidate's face: http://bit.ly/OabyvS     
    
    
    File under "signs of the end times" : I've joined a Fantasy Football league    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog @DeanAtWork @KHil if you guys haven't read chronology of water, i very much recommend it.    
    
    
    @petfurniture please tell me the actual species is "poodle moth"    
    
    
    Why inertia kills companies: http://bit.ly/NUcpm1  on @fastcolead from @RallySoftware CEO Tim Miller - great post!    
    
    
    @jccronin Whoa! Congrats.    
    
    
    @jccronin an excellent point. I totally use it to spy on @czsays    
    
    
    @Dan_Rowinski that is way meta    
    
    
    Urban gardening ftw plus a Cash cameo pic.twitter.com/XbzpDXR1    
    
    
    Fantasy Football for beginners - awesome piece from @ESal on @thoughtcatalog http://bit.ly/Rq044n     
    
    
    @paulbtucker i'm going to go w "it sounds Greek" & "it's easy for an American to pronounce" -- but i am not either of your target answerers    
    
    
    MT @helacool: A deep dive into multi-screen for SXSW featuring @eprize, @vitrue, @monetate and @usablenet. Vote today! http://shar.es/7yF2y     
    
    
    @helacool Congrats!! And yay for geek girls & science camp. Raise 'er right! :)    
    
    
    So psyched to check out Rockland/Camden for the first time and enjoy some relaxation Maine-style #laborday    
    
    
    Dapper gents in my life, take note: RT @KurtGeigerSF: Did u know Kurt Geiger has a mens collection? #shoechandelier : not just for stilettos    
    
    
    @stefugee yes! and they're opening up a presence in the US of A now!    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog You might seek some words of wisdom from @czsays first. It's a dangerous, dangerous pastime.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog @czsays have you considered a wheelchair?    
    
    
    @DeanAtWork @SystemOfADog or heck! an ambulance! those things go fast. (tho are not very cost-effective, imo.)    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog that's quite the superlative. how can you be sure she's the worst?    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog that's some circular logic right there    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog but i'll allow it    
    
    
    Love it! RT @HackerChick: Requited Love: 7 factors that attract entrepreneurs to Boston - @scottkirsner http://j.mp/TRXjdY     
    
    
    Hi @hootsuite_help - could use some assistance with transferring ownership of a social profile    
    
    
    @HootSuite_Help Thanks. Already checked that out - I'm getting an error message saying I'm not the owner. Could you open a support ticket?    
    
    
    @paulbtucker that phrase is absurd!    
    
    
    Woo comments in Google spreadsheets! (It's the little things, guys.)    
    
    
    @jmandell on the innovation scene in Russia: http://bit.ly/Oqhs9Y     
    
    
    THIS HAPPENED TO ME: http://bbc.in/vbWA2A  I seriously had a box of 12 eggs with all double yolks (in France)    
    
    
    @KHil dude. that's a superpower, and you should find a way to put it to good use.    
    
    
    @petfurniture holy material.    
    
    
    @ScottKirsner brushing up on their tennis/golf games ?    
    
    
    No mistaking that crisp autumn air    
    
    
    @landnau Sounds like an interesting class. I'm of the mind that this type of thing should be required at all undergrad schools!    
    
    
    @landnau no, bummed :( you?    
    
    
    True - heartbreaking RT @km: We often forget that Joe Biden lost half of his immediate family when he was 30 years old. http://bit.ly/QEiPnS     
    
    
    MT @SystemOfADog: The "LIBYANS APOLOGIZING TO AMERICA THROUGH SIGNS" thing got me thinking. !آسف عن القنابل http://i.imgur.com/kvSrH.jpg     
    
    
    Lukewarm on whether I want to read NZ but pretty dang psyched about Junot Diaz's new collection fwiw    
    
    
    Hey guys... Are there any corporate/company blogs that you really enjoy reading? (Serious question)    
    
    
    @fabrahamlincoln @aarongraves i'm with fabian on this one: @Alleyoop @Knewton @codeacademy @edxonline + tons more - @edsurge keeps track    
    
    
    Oct 17 I hope! RT @jccronin: #ThePassage peeps: tour dates for #TheTwelve roadshow.  See you down the road:http://on.fb.me/OKkCWd     
    
    
    @aarongraves @fabrahamlincoln this is one of my favorite topics - we should argue in person over delicious cocktails    
    
    
    @sarahcuda Good for you! Congrats!    
    
    
    @drlieber @fabrahamlincoln @aarongraves sold. i sense more slapbets in my future.    
    
    
    CONGRATS! RT @glafond: We won!!! MassTLC 2012 Best Use of Technology - Alleyoop recommendation engine. Boom! @Alleyoop http://bit.ly/Q8nOuA     
    
    
    @drlieber @fabrahamlincoln @aarongraves cool. also forgot one of my personal faves, the Minerva Project @criticalwisdom    
    
    
    @acromp bahaha    
    
    
    @czsays @Nathan_S_Scott not really a pun... but Harry is a huge and very cute dog fwiw    
    
    
    Pop quiz: RT @SystemOfADog: Do you know *all* the diffs bw the iPhone 4S and 5? How ab in which countries we have active military presence?    
    
    
    Just donated to Wikipedia for the first time #keepitfree    
    
    
    OH YES OH YES OH YES. Weekend *made*: http://bit.ly/U30ySI  @somdogfest (redo tweet)    
    
    
    Saw this in Charlestown the other day. Could not help smiling: http://bit.ly/PgqnvV     
    
    
    @Evanish If not, you can always try a cocktail cocktail    
    
    
    @ESal It's good to have options.    
    
    
    Ctown hubway ftw! pic.twitter.com/85lso3ro    
    
    
    My boys had a tough night :( pic.twitter.com/5fINEWuJ    
    
    
    This week's green bean haul. More veg than we have dog, according to @czsays pic.twitter.com/QZSzvttb    
    
    
    Well said, sir. -- Stonyfield Chairman Sides With Consumers on GMO Labeling - http://NYTimes.com  http://flpbd.it/ETmvh     
    
    
    @KHil hahaha. yes.    
    
    
    I'm confused by the shock over this Romney video. Isn't he just being a little more candid than usual? P. sure we all knew he believed this.    
    
    
    @briankspears Oh, definitely. Agree with that. In a way, it's a good thing to catch people being extra candid. Rhetoric clouds beliefs.    
    
    
    @aarongraves @fabrahamlincoln http://nyti.ms/PpHUS5  On computerized tutors - fuel for our upcoming debate (also a great read.)    
    
    
    @onewil ya lost me there.    
    
    
    @onewil It's a real problem when saying what you actually believe out loud shocks people & is a "stupid" move.    
    
    
    @onewil In a certain sense, it's nice to hear what he actually thinks (assuming here that he wasn't pandering to the audience, also a poss)    
    
    
    Yay! MT @drlieber: Just in time to rescue me from Allston tonight, @Uber launches taxi service in Boston today: http://bit.ly/RsJ7w7     
    
    
    Don't walk dogs near the Bricklayers bldg (int of Bunker Hill & Medford St.) in #Charlestown. Someone trying to poison: http://bit.ly/S6qNse     
    
    
    @acromp nonononobadwhy    
    
    
    @acromp uhohs. and thanks for the well wishes for dogman. people can be so very awful!    
    
    
    Love that when I look up Vegas flights on @hipmunk (research, don't get excited), the city appears as "Vegas, Baby" +1    
    
    
    Kids explain how to decide who to marry: http://bit.ly/Lo1kY7  "...even if she looks like a truck" Amazing. h/t @annafarnum    
    
    
    Nice little write-up on my alma mater @RiceUniversity in @USNewsEducation today: http://bit.ly/QHOZgq  #beeeerbiiiiike    
    
    
    See you in Boston! MT @jccronin: #ThePassage #TheTwelve peeps: tour dates and cities now posted on http://bit.ly/NGNeT5   Hope to see you    
    
    
    ahaha RT @SystemOfADog: @paulbtucker http://bit.ly/TbI450     
    
    
    Guys, there is a waterfall in Hawaii called Pe'epe'e. You can't make this stuff up.    
    
    
    Did we just eat and entire Santarpios pie and then get a lobster roll and fried oysters? Yes. #dontjudge    
    
    
    @nath_on_fire yeah. eff that noise. modern family's solid and homeland is fine, but no way they deserved all those emmys.    
    
    
    MT @petfurniture: one IMPORTANT thing I did: put all the apps on my iPhone into 3 folders: ID (games)/EGO(photography)/SUPEREGO (bank & AAA)    
    
    
    @petfurniture well, now i hate you. #sojealous    
    
    
    Unbelievable. RT @GlobeMetro: Judge said of Huffman's case, "To me that's the only fair result" -- as state drug lab scandal continues.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog the interface is super easy/awesome, but the doc they sent me to was sketch central. better in sf?    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @zackbogue: Baby boy Bogue born last night. Mom (@marissamayer) and baby are doing great--we couldn't be more excited!    
    
    
    Hey @staples, enough with the hyperbolic mktng emails. "Immediate action required" and "we've been trying to reach you" = not appropriate    
    
    
    @charnsandwich NO!    
    
    
    A Vacation From 'Homeland' http://huff.to/RAGO7Z  by @hoppertravel on @HuffPostTravel #travel #homeland #hopper    
    
    
    15 airports with the most delays & cancellations from @hoppertravel on @bi_thelife Both Houston airports + Dallas. Oh, TX.    
    
    
    Coat I left on an @united flight is being returned 4 months later. And the woman who called could not have been nicer. Redeeming.    
    
    
    Great interview w @jccronin on @thedailybeast: http://bit.ly/RPgbwo  Bonus: Stealth Dickenson reference    
    
    
    That's fair! MT @katherinedally: Blaming @karlthefog for SFO's inclusion – @hoppertravel's15 worst US airports http://read.bi/TC6Jig     
    
    
    All ma single friends - have you checked out @grouper ? Talk of the office today. Sounds like a really cool concept!    
    
    
    @onewil I've only done it once, but was a good experience for sure.    
    
    
    @drlieber haha! uh ohs. planning ahead, i guess... my december's fairly open. :)    
    
    
    @drlieber nah! the opposite. so much less awk than a blind date. don't you think?    
    
    
    @drlieber ew. don't bring those ones! we were discussing whether it's fair play to bring a non-single frnd who's a good wingwoman. i say no.    
    
    
    @drlieber fo sho    
    
    
    Truth. RT @metaweiss: Everyone register to vote! Last day!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SystemOfADog or is it an awful way to feel important?    
    
    
    Seriously incredible #felix #spacejump    
    
    
    Best accomplishment so far today: got someone to register to vote. Last day for MA. Don't forget!    
    
    
    @acromp that's amazing.    
    
    
    @charnsandwich splurge -- also, sell your 3GS on gazelle & use the money for your upgrade.    
    
    
    Can't wait! RT @jccronin: Thanks NYC for a great launch day. Speaking 2nite at Porter Square Books in Cambridge MA. #TheTwelve    
    
    
    Quora asks what murder feels like, San Quentin inmates answer: http://bit.ly/RC6oqY  Quite bizarrely heartwarming (the eloquence, regret.)    
    
    
    Pretty psyched to see @jccronin @portersqbooks tonight! #thetwelve    
    
    
    @drlieber save it and use it for voodoo...    
    
    
    Aww! Great to see you too! RT @jccronin: Great night at @PorterSqBooks. Great to see @MegScarborough, fave student. On to @RiverRunBkstore    
    
    
    Hamazing. MT @cheryllmorris: I love the internet RT @ryandawidjan Binders of women on Amazon #greatreviews http://amzn.to/Ty2XBx     
    
    
    @landnau haha i love it. i read about something like that on a parenting blog (don't ask). such a good call.    
    
    
    Order a cab, get a cadillac with a driver who smells like fancy cologne. For free. #uberboston #winning    
    
    
    Current status: http://flpbd.it/ly9ps     
    
    
    A love letter to Reddit: http://bit.ly/PonTiT  from @joyent    
    
    
    Check it out - RT @clreisman: This rocks! America's Worst Travel Hubs via @Thrillist http://thrl.st/X8EqYy  (data via @hoppertravel)    
    
    
    Mitt "Teetotaler" Romney may not be your guy RT @paulbtucker: Voting for candidate who comes out as coffee hawk - weak coffee is a menace...    
    
    
    I'm pro-coffee choice. RT @DeanAtWork: I hear Paul Ryan voted to oppose coffee even in cases of morning meetings, long drives, and decaf    
    
    
    @paulbtucker That's very insensitive, Paul. Some unlucky citizens face debilitating caffeine intolerance.    
    
    
    @DeanAtWork Perker. Ha. This thread made my morning.    
    
    
    File under: cheese that will make you sweat http://bit.ly/S58DXo     
    
    
    My Facebook feed is totally clogged with dog photos, and I love it very much.    
    
    
    NoRedInk - tackling grammar and writing using technology in a really smart way. Really cool stuff: http://tcrn.ch/PvTNKe  #grammarnerdalert    
    
    
    Wondering where to go when the zombie apocalypse hits? http://thrl.st/Rnw1LG  Now you know.    
    
    
    Oooo. Love new gmail compose window. Can already tell it will save me time. #productivitynerd    
    
    
    Well now it's really raining in Boston. Wind thunder lightning the works. Much heavier than during the hurricane.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog Cash is a honey badger    
    
    
    Pretty sure I saw someone dressed as Sandy on my way to work today.    
    
    
    Boo! pic.twitter.com/vrQ8RA1Q    
    
    
    Really love to see people focus on the positive aspects of tech (in this case Twitter w/r/t Sandy): http://nyti.ms/TurD1q  ht @mfarbs    
    
    
    @stefugee that's awesome. sold my volvo sta-wag to a couple who'd lost both their jobs in the previous month + had a med emergency. #karma    
    
    
    @stefugee Well, it was about as cheap as a car gets, in good working order, and absolutely necessary to get to job interviews (in Houston)    
    
    
    @stefugee So I'd say yes, though I see your point.    
    
    
    @stefugee also the medical emergency was a car crash (that totaled the car).    
    
    
    @stefugee haha. that they are! mine was a '96, so a bit newer. no a/c of course (typical volvo) but still built like a tank. served me well.    
    
    
    Most underrated candy bar? 100 Grand.    
    
    
    Welp looks like bar results came out. Guess I'll stay off FB for a while. #worsethanweddingseason #jkcongratsguys    
    
    
    In my office, we're saving my boss's children. #communityservice RT @jccronin: Saving children from their own Halloween candy since 1996.    
    
    
    @kimieOng haha. great [nerdy] minds, as they say!    
    
    
    MT @petfurniture: the way I'm going to survive another retail xmas is: pretend everyone's buying each other books for the apocalypse instead    
    
    
    @onewil it's so true! i'm out of my rhythm this week (and i usually swap in a dog) but it's a wonderful peaceful time.    
    
    
    Once I tried every froyo place in Manhattan (try me) to find the best one. I'm getting a weird urge to do that to Boston pizza now... Recs?    
    
    
    Standing desks are stupid. This, on the other hand? http://fitdesk.net/  cc @mfarbs - calling your name!    
    
    
    @acromp Don't you just want to know who Daemon is?!    
    
    
    SoWa Food Trucks Will Serve All Winter Long http://flpbd.it/oDnHz    Cuz that's how we roll. Good decision!    
    
    
    . MT @jm_lev: Unless u live in NC, VA, NH, OH, WI, IA, CO - literally nothing to lose by voting ur hopes rather than ur fears in nat'l race.    
    
    
    Someone left this in the bathroom at work. I want to be her friend. pic.twitter.com/sdKZf2iz    
    
    
    Welp, I officially regret googling posole while eating it. http://bit.ly/3wkhEv  #wtfcannibalism    
    
    
    Wow. Harris County (a.k.a. Houston) went for Obama by a margin of TWO votes.    
    
    
    @pithyblahblah @petfurniture good work, you two.    
    
    
    @SystemOfADog 69 drafts?!?! i would blow 69 blood vessels in my brain    
    
    
    First snowflakes of the season in Boston! #countit    
    
    
    Some legit snow on our deck. White winter a comin' pic.twitter.com/AVjgzPHN    
    
    
    @landnau Congrats!!    
    
    
    Inspiring interview with the CEO of @37signals: http://bit.ly/YSO1Us  Great company, visionary CEO who gets what really matters.    
    
    
    Wow. Quite a speech from Gabby Giffords' husband at Loughner's sentencing: http://bit.ly/YSLtWq     
    
    
    @acromp niiiiice    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris growing pains :)    
    
    
    Not that you need any more reasons to support gay marriage, but... http://huff.to/SgpRx6  #watchout    
    
    
    @KHil Am massively jealous right now    
    
    
    MT @SystemOfADog: Send thousands into war, cool! Destroy opponents, rad! Civilians on accident, oops! Boink some1 who's into it -- NO BAD NO    
    
    
    Ha MT @TheBloggess: As a Texan, I like to think that most of the ppl signing the petition to secede just don't know how to spell "succeed".    
    
    
    A good thing: RT @JustinPopeAP: #Coursera/#ACE deal could bring MOOC students step closer to college credit. http://bit.ly/SZEet2     
    
    
    Do it! RT @ESal: Join me and nominate @Alleyoop for the Best Education Startup 2012 Crunchie! http://is.gd/O09tlX  #crunchies    
    
    
    "There are trappist monks in the Ozarks? Do they brew artisanal meth?" Taking the Williams Sonoma catalog down a peg http://deadsp.in/SZChwC     
    
    
    Wow. Almost everything currently in my gmail spam folder is *not* spam. When did their filters get so crappy?    
    
    
    @mattyoun ding ding ding    
    
    
    @BostonTweet Yum!! Come visit @LaunchSquad Boston in the American Twine building in Kendall!    
    
    
    @fvinh Most of our career ambitions come from TV or movies. At least you picked a good one. Could've been Legally Blonde....    
    
    
    This week's Modern Family was pretty genius.    
    
    
    Screw Twinkies. Butterscotch Krimpets all the way.    
    
    
    And, spectacular. Raymond Carver's OKCupid profile, edited by Gordon Lish. http://bit.ly/UIPm0h  only @mcsweeneys    
    
    
    Yay secret boards on Pinterest! That took way too long. Holiday gift list commence.    
    
    
    @fvinh what column?!    
    
    
    Brand Networks rides Facebook economy to Toronto http://m.bizjournals.com/boston/news/2012/11/20/brand-networks-rides-facebook.html?r=full …    
    
    
    @fvinh Nice! Love the description of how Brody talks. So true.    
    
    
    Haha RT @DKThomp: People offering diet tips for Thanksgiving should be prosecuted, and possibly jailed    
    
    
    Cambridge's Lorem Ipsum books, founded as on/offline hybrid, looking to hackers for a new biz model: http://bo.st/Tm7k3D  by @ScottKirsner    
    
    
    Love it. RT @laurenfitte: Here's a laugh for my fellow INFJ sisters http://bit.ly/mRgohD  @petfurniture @ashleyOo @MegScarborough    
    
    
    @TimGunnge mine too! #forlife    
    
    
    @TimGunnge i knew you couldn't be an INFJ. Tim Faust ain't no judger.    
    
    
    The Zombie States of America: Where to hide when the apocalypse comes http://bit.ly/YqnbUP  on @buzzfeed    
    
    
    It's beginning to look a lot like xmas... pic.twitter.com/z6xKF3el    
    
    
    Let the games begin! RT @LaunchSquad: It's @LaunchSquad Holiday Week, excited to have entire team in SF! http://ow.ly/i/1cICE  #LSHolidayWeek    
    
    
    View from Starlight Lounge. #lsholidayweek pic.twitter.com/NvPdkpFY    
    
    
    I just blew chocolate icing out of my nose. That's the kind of day we're talking about.    
    
    
    @DeanAtWork that happened too    
    
    
    Oh what's that? 2nd place? Boom. #lsholidayweek    
    
    
    Warming up for first annual #lsholidayweek basketball tourney pic.twitter.com/HbgGGdWO    
    
    
    Bball warmups. Place your bets. #lsholidayweek pic.twitter.com/7GmdN8Bh    
    
    
    Uh oh. Man down. #lsholidayweek pic.twitter.com/SjbDeSuO    
    
    
    @TimGunnge oh no! hope you're feeling better    
    
    
    @paulbtucker well @BetsyLO should have first dibs, but if she doesn't want it...    
    
    
    @nath_on_fire word. so much anger.    
    
    
    @nath_on_fire i always think about how it's so much harder to get mad at fellow pedestrians (not impossible, mind you.)    
    
    
    The silver (black) lining of sick days pic.twitter.com/AwcYqNjM    
    
    
    Seriously, 6 phone calls (and counting) to make an appointment with a new PCP? Not cool, MGH.    
    
    
    @kvnlhy's definition of integrity: "When he wants to throw a phone at you, he does." #wisdom    
    
    
    Well worth a read. Insightful, heartfelt. MT @thefilmgoer: Emily Witt's @LRB essay on online dating: http://bit.ly/RCrAgq     
    
    
    Check out @thefilmgoer's feed today for his top 10 films of 2012. This is a person whose opinion you should heed.    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer oh hardly. get ready for me & @czsays to pick your brain on this come holidaytime!    
    
    
    MT @YousefMunayyer: 1 jackass tries to light his shoe & every1 has to take their shoes off at airports. Mass gun violence? nothing we can do    
    
    
    McSweeneys tells you how to write better, and it's funny too: http://bit.ly/Hu5jfD  h/t @ESal    
    
    
    Anybody ever tried reusable moving boxes (a la http://bungobox.com/ ) in Boston? Recs?    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris that's cool. so you can donate to the charity of your choice?    
    
    
    @paulbtucker good thing or bad thing?    
    
    
    @Dan_Rowinski you need to ask a savant    
    
    
    Someone just butt-dialed me from Houston. Background conversation = people yelling about "taking all my $$"... ???    
    
    
    Plz send help: RT @clreisman: Audio gold! RT @mfarbs: @esal just won t@launchsquad Boston Yankee Swap. http://bit.ly/R7OjFh     
    
    
    @charnsandwich: @paulbtucker agreed. tho i've only been to LA like twice.    
    
    
    Downvote @czsays for Weatherman of the Year.    
    
    
    Powerful, reasonable. RT @aseitzwald: Professor who experienced 2009 school shooting: Teachers Are Not Soldiers. http://bit.ly/U9Qw3t     
    
    
    @TimGunnge so. cute.    
    
    
    @TimGunnge although she is a little... husky. (ba dum)    
    
    
    @DeanAtWork a little ruff teasing never hurt anyone    
    
    
    @czsays you stay out of this. you're already in the doghouse.    
    
    
    Part of my body most looking forward to vacation: elbows.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker that black dog looks like our munchkin!    
    
    
    Dog fort, come in. Cc @czsays pic.twitter.com/p88rmGtP    
    
    
    Blades on my new Ninja blender? Sharp. Brain wasn't surprised, but finger was.    
    
    
    Whoa. Hope this doesn't end badly. RT @BostonTweet: @Zipcar being acquired by Avis for approximately $500 million. http://bit.ly/Uk1JLr     
    
    
    @jm_lev hm. not currently true in Boston or a lot of other cities I've been to, but we'll see I guess!    
    
    
    Is COLD. RT @drlieber: 28 years living in New England and today is the first day that I've ever seriously considered buying ear muffs.    
    
    
    Good stuff in here. Humans are not going obsolete: RT @bbosker: Yes, the machines are getting better. But so are you. http://huff.to/Zgs2c9     
    
    
    @czsays googled that. it took me to the 'wookiepedia.' nerd.    
    
    
    My bad. *nerdS RT @TimGunnge: @MegScarborough @czsays uh, that's Wookieepedia. *pushes glasses up nose*    
    
    
    I started reading the War of Art last night and it's already kicking my ass in the best way. #recommend    
    
    
    UGH. Well-put. MT @jolieodell: ‘Play with my V spot’ | VentureBeat http://bit.ly/136QYSw  (I don't often get angry online, but this...)    
    
    
    @czsays that's gotta be good for the left brain-right brain connection...    
    
    
    MT @petfurniture: feeling ovrwhlmed by yr workload? try breaking it down into chunks, lighting those chunks on fire & feeding them to sharks    
    
    
    Here we go. RT @kramerbot: I think it's important that I tweet a few of my New Year's resolutions today. It's a courtesy thing. Stay tuned.    
    
    
    Google searches during a 3-day juice fast - hilarity from my awesome coworker @ESal on the Hairpin: http://bit.ly/100HDOi     
    
    
    Good man. RT @thefilmgoer: Saw headline, "Brennan to Head CIA" and thought, "Barry never calls to ask first, but if my country needs me..."    
    
    
    We missed Cash's puppy stage, but I'm just going to tell myself he looked exactly like this: http://bit.ly/U1Csr2     
    
    
    @Dan_Rowinski curious why you think that is    
    
    
    @Dan_Rowinski I know. I'm asking what you think the reasons are behind it.    
    
    
    @Dan_Rowinski hmm. yeah. wonder which direction it'll trend this year...    
    
    
    “I just got out on Annie Dookhan and I ain’t going back to jail” - suspected crack possessor. http://bo.st/UAOC8J  #facepalm    
    
    
    My 2008 Macbook is, amazingly, still chugging along. Prob is no more new software/updates & hardware won't talk to it (incl. iphone) :/    
    
    
    ... and I was just served a FB ad for an "escape-proof dog diaper." Pink, resembles bondage equipment, I feel weird.    
    
    
    Flu shot in one arm, tetanus in other. C'mon, World. Bring it.    
    
    
    Motion to require all congressional candidates to prove they can speak in full sentences: http://bit.ly/XVGx56     
    
    
    Still. Get your shot. RT @GlobeMetro: CDC: Flu vaccine is only 55% effective against H3N2 strain circulating in MA. 37% of infected got shot    
    
    
    2013: The Year Payments Finally Emerge From the Dark Ages? http://dthin.gs/UbyOep  Let's hope so!    
    
    
    Always good to see Houston get a little love (from the NYT no less): http://nyti.ms/VR8J3Y  Amazing museums & food. #represent    
    
    
    @TimGunnge i am sorry for your lots    
    
    
    . RT @KHil: "The question is not 'will I survive if I step out of my comfort zone?' The real question is 'will I survive my comfort zone?'"    
    
    
    womp womp RT @levie: Disappointment sets in as regular ppl discover that FB launched a graph search engine, not a giraffe search engine.    
    
    
    Dining nook painted. This one's called "pewter." #movingtime pic.twitter.com/F9tnGubm    
    
    
    @manzalena it's also against the (AP) rules. #downwithextraspaces    
    
    
    hahaha. also: thank you. RT @Nathan_S_Scott: The Non-Sports Fan Guide To The Manti Te'O Story http://tcat.tc/10BGiOa     
    
    
    @Hey_Billy well, i mostly just enjoyed that tweet. u know how i feel about sports. fascinating the things ppl think they can get away w tho.    
    
    
    Ha! cc @esal, nerd whisperer RT @czsays: I see you, you little rats: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage&v=iQpD9LolO-k …    
    
    
    What's hot (and not so hot...) for mobile payments in 2013: http://onforb.es/UVNs8e  by @hhelgeson, CEO of @merchantwh    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd I'd say it's pretty popular in MFA-grad literary fiction, too, though a bit out of favor in the last 10-15 years    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd pshhh lies.    
    
    
    @BKramer has solved the office Tupperware proliferation mystery: the containers are mating. Now the q is how to handle custody battles...    
    
    
    @katherinedally such a good call! go tubing on the guadelupe!    
    
    
    I just read an article that misspelled clout as klout and now I feel sad about the internet.    
    
    
    Never paint without the right equipment #movingtime pic.twitter.com/edeVxQwJ    
    
    
    The puppy scene on Girls this week was so random, but I didn't hate it.    
    
    
    "When you have the opportunity to walk as means to an end, take it" - Making me feel good about my new, longer commute: http://bit.ly/VXZUbt     
    
    
    Love to see Hillary givin' 'em hell on her way out the door. #2016    
    
    
    "Pay yourself first" - great post from @jowyang on doing the really important stuff first, always    
    
    
    Yikes: http://bit.ly/WunZnC  RT @acromp Rice's new website makes it look like it hasn't received angel funding yet.    
    
    
    If you're looking for a pet, or pet supplies, or a great cause, Katherine Heigl's doing great work: http://huff.to/X8EqV9  Got Cash thru her!    
    
    
    Really enjoying the new Saunders and already dreading the inevitable void when I finish it... Recs?    
    
    
    @Nathan_S_Scott awesome - will check it out! (& i've never been his #1 fan, but am starting to understand the fuss for sure. wrenching.)    
    
    
    @mattyoun George Saunders, new short story collection: http://amzn.to/UJF5PZ  It's good stuff, I bet you'd enjoy.    
    
    
    Wow. I suck at Vine. But I will (I will!) get an excellent video of Cash chasing his new laser.    
    
    
    Loved that. RT @KHil: "Best friend is not a person, it's a tier" which is the wisest thing I've heard from a tv show    
    
    
    Why dogs are smarter than cats: http://on.wsj.com/UnAzsK  via @WSJ    
    
    
    @HealyHoops Congrats, Healy!    
    
    
    @mattyoun ha. agree. i'm two in. i think i like it, but i hate when he talks the camera. i feel like it would work so much better w/o that.    
    
    
    @bgreinhart Def. As @czsays pointed out, v. theatrical show. It just beats you over the head when it could be subtle (and better for it.)    
    
    
    @bgreinhart But I will keep watching. Spacey's magnetic enough for me to give it a 2nd chance. Plus love the concept of Netflix original.    
    
    
    @czsays @breinhart but shakespeare *needed* that - didn't have any of the subtle tools of modern film. It's too much on a screen.    
    
    
    @czsays exactly    
    
    
    I@czsays @bgreinhart I'd rather imagine what Spacey's thinking and plotting than have him tell me. It doesn't flatter the audience.    
    
    
    @bgreinhart As an aside, you were totally in Huston's Shakespeare class with me, weren't you? Oh, Richard III.    
    
    
    @czsays only when it serves the story. in this case, i think it dilutes.    
    
    
    @bgreinhart full-circle, eh? esp nice with the news today. :)    
    
    
    @mattyoun @bgreinhart and man, what a class.    
    
    
    So this just happened... pic.twitter.com/6q2skSdX    
    
    
    Kitchen porn at its finest: http://flip.it/MWxEU     
    
    
    The magic happens OUTSIDE your comfort zone.    
    
    
    Mango creme girl scout cookies taste just like a Lipsmacker I had when I was 8.    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer wowza. congrats!    
    
    
    @KHil accurate.    
    
    
    Now that's some winter RT @GlobeMetro: Forecasters warn of possible blizzard conditions as storm drops up to 2' of snow http://bo.st/XkyaLP     
    
    
    Great post from @jamietedford on how to kick-start your social marketing program in 2013: http://read.bi/123O8LG  on @BI_Advertising    
    
    
    We forgot how to deal with snow. Thanks, global warming. pic.twitter.com/6XsW5CtV    
    
    
    Exciting news: I may have found a new favorite yogurt (to replace my dearly departed liberté). @korudairy getting the creaminess down.    
    
    
    Scenes from a snow day part 1 http://vine.co/v/bnEJJF2JLZ5     
    
    
    Math: overrated. MT @ESal: My husband asked me last night if I remember the blizzard of '78. He knows I'm only 30... really?    
    
    
    @paulbtucker this made me laugh out loud    
    
    
    Yay! Congrats! RT @LaunchSquad: Today our Boston team celebrated @KvnLhy's recent engagement... congrats Kevin! http://ow.ly/i/1vSkT     
    
    
    @Triposo find the top 10 most romantic restaurants in the world according to social media: http://huff.to/Zae7ow  #travel #valentine    
    
    
    Haha RT @Rylanmi: The "meh" crowd #stateoftheunion http://bit.ly/11GryhF     
    
    
    Some great tips: RT @triposo: Travel: How to Actually Act Like a Local When Traveling - @Lifehacker http://bit.ly/Vdr2Ta     
    
    
    @TimGunnge Nouvelle Vague    
    
    
    @KHil that's amazing. why do i feel like @TimGunnge wrote it?    
    
    
    Haha: RT @BostonTweet: This Valentine's Day @SavMorSpirits sign reveals; "I have a secret crush on the McDonald's sign" http://bit.ly/YgG9tw     
    
    
    "You are what you read" - @jmandell just now.    
    
    
    @acromp the cloud is where the party's at    
    
    
    @timgunnge @paulbtucker twitter besties    
    
    
    @wfrick It does seem like more this year than usual! (We are.)    
    
    
    @czsays how is that even possible? @thefilmgoer yes, i will. immediately.    
    
    
    @timgunnge well, if anyone can do that, it's you.. but where are all the ladies?    
    
    
    @q0rt I empathize with that so hard. Coalition to Get Better [Full-fat, Real-fruit] Yogurt in America.    
    
    
    Hi @strandbookstore - working on an article, would love to chat with your social media mgr. Could you follow so I can DM details? Thank you!    
    
    
    Interesting to see Gabriel Gomez using promoted tweets... Don't think I've ever seen one from a politician before. #MAsenaterace    
    
    
    Shame on you, @onion. http://ow.ly/i2tnO  You're in the business of comedy; you should know where the line is, and that's waaay over it.    
    
    
    @theonion rather.    
    
    
    Anthony Bourdain AMA. Yes. Monday is better now: http://ow.ly/i2BiD     
    
    
    "I'm proud of the fact that I can be friends with someone with whom I disagree violently about absolutely everything." - Anthony Bourdain    
    
    
    Aaand I just found out he's going to be on Archer this week. Let's do this.    
    
    
    @timgunnge doitdoitdoitdoit.    
    
    
    I once interviewed with Yahoo for a remote position. Glad that didn't work out...    
    
    
    @lilsmcc Bribe friends with beer...    
    
    
    @nath_on_fire OMG I forgot about changnesia until I saw your tweet. So much to look forward to.    
    
    
    @lilsmcc pizza works well too. Also, moving is the worst. Good luck!    
    
    
    Fun times! RT @esal: The Boston office of @LaunchSquad at Employee Appreciation lunch pic.twitter.com/KW6Lh8qtvW    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd did you just watch Happy?    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd it's pretty good (documentary.) and there's a piece about Dutch (I think?) single moms living in a commune-type thing, v. cool    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd 'tis!    
    
    
    That's some seriously unnecessary packaging @staples pic.twitter.com/tm7Anq8auz    
    
    
    @esal I can see the missed connection now: "You spilled coffee on me. It was so hot."    
    
    
    F yes. RT @bostontweet: On Sun, the sunset in Boston will occur after 6pm (6:45pm) for the first time since October 16, 2012. #SpringIsNear    
    
    
    Hi @shawmu, tried emailing, was wondering if you'd be interested in doing a short interview for a post I'm writing - follow& I'll DM details    
    
    
    Love my new earrings, @katespadeny, but the shoebox they arrived in was a bit much. #packaging    
    
    
    <3 RT @petfurniture: be certain that yr definition of beauty is much broader than yr definition of perfection    
    
    
    8 of the most bizarre (and mostly disgusting) foods in the world, for your reading pleasure: http://ow.ly/iPdCS     
    
    
    @timgunnge yikes. are you ok?    
    
    
    mmm.. Salzburger nockerl. I still don't totally understand what you are, but I want to eat you: http://ow.ly/iTatf  via @triposo    
    
    
    Birthday pizza by the talented @czsays :) pic.twitter.com/sKcORrMa5D    
    
    
    Took a barre class tonight. It felt weird and vaguely sexist. Think I'll stick with real weights. #twopoundsareyoukiddingme?    
    
    
    @ntlandau ooo, yes! when?    
    
    
    Hangover cures from around the world: http://ow.ly/j9H3g  h/t @triposo    
    
    
    @ntlandau done & done!    
    
    
    Are you a good tourist? Which country do you think behaves most scandalously while traveling? Take @triposo's survey: http://ow.ly/jbs7t     
    
    
    @paulbtucker valhalla!    
    
    
    MT @new_edu: We're hiring a Product Manager of #Personalized #Learning @RiceUniversity. http://bit.ly/11gO0Lw  #dreamjob #job #edtech #OER    
    
    
    This search for dog #2 is getting pretty intense. There may or may not be a spreadsheet.    
    
    
    Ron, I feel you on the whole banana thing. #gag    
    
    
    Beyond horrifying. RT @bostonglobe: BREAKING NEWS: Two powerful explosions detonated in quick succession next to the Boston Marathon finish    
    
    
    Don't agree with every word of this, but there's a lot of solid #realtalk here. Quora advice for 20-somethings: http://ow.ly/k7Rx6     
    
    
    Of all the reporters & media outlets I follow, @antderosa has been the most informative and least trigger-happy through all this. Props.    
    
    
    What if we made a breathalyzer-style device that forced you to take 8 nice, deep yoga breaths before retweeting news outlets?    
    
    
    @deanatwork exactly.    
    
    
    Once again, shame on you, Congress. Background checks should be the easiest, most bipartisan possible measure. You fail.    
    
    
    MT @aarongraves: Every single victim who was alive when the first responders hit the scene has survived. Inspiring. http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/newsdesk/2013/04/why-bostons-hospitals-were-ready.html?mobify=0 …    
    
    
    MT @bostonglobe: Were you on Boylston on Monday? Tell us your story and where you were on this interactive map. http://bo.st/XH5eAl     
    
    
    Well, Apartment Therapy says lambrusco is trendy now. Don't have to pull my arm.    
    
    
    Doesn't sound like background checks wld have caught either of these guys. Need real gun control laws, and can't even pass watered-down BS.    
    
    
    Today = important opportunity for us (Americans) to consider what it's like to live with this kind of fear/uncertainty every day, as many do    
    
    
    How I Met My Dead Parents - really lovely piece of memoir BuzzFeed Mobile http://flip.it/qKlQb     
    
    
    Happy Birthday, Bard: RT @triposo: if you love Shakespeare these places should be on your bucket list:
http://blog.triposo.com/2013/04/if-you-love-shakespeare-these-places.html …    
    
    
    Just completed a 1.74 mi walk with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a2u6nmr  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Just completed a 2.95 mi run - Beautiful night for a run.  http://rnkpr.com/a2u7430  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @nathan_s_scott whoaaaa. them's fightin' words. i effing loved the Killing. where's @thefilmgoer on this?    
    
    
    @nathan_s_scott did you finish it?    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer @nathan_s_scott some of the best character dvpmt i've ever seen on tv, slow but gripping plot. the ending is p damn courageous.    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer @nathan_s_scott linden is a very unique female lead too (not overly sexualized, deeply flawed, challenging). loved it all.    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer great analysis -- and i see what you mean about the coincidences. still, the ending shocked me, and i give it an A- overall.    
    
    
    @nathan_s_scott @thefilmgoer haha. that is a fair point. my tolerance for it is admittedly high. looking forward to checking out HM & TotL    
    
    
    Took my sweet time trying out Mailbox bc of mixed reviews, but so far I like. Similar workflow to my Active Inbox/Boomerang combo hack    
    
    
    This is precisely how I feel about the internet: evrythg good & bad about it is our fault, not its. Kudos @futurepaul http://ow.ly/kEd14     
    
    
    @alexsmith4000 don't bother.    
    
    
    Cinco De Drinko? The Best Places To Drink Tequila On May 5th: http://ow.ly/kGdJ3  from client @Triposo on @buzzfeed    
    
    
    True. So does Texas. If you want to go to TN, go to Nashville. RT @mattyoun: @AlexSmith4000 @MegScarborough apparently they have great BBQ?    
    
    
    @drlieber Whoaaa!!! You go girl!    
    
    
    Re: Bangladesh I keep thinking of the (ancient) TAL ep about clothing factories in Cambodia. Food for thought: http://ow.ly/kH7GL     
    
    
    Just completed a 3.03 mi run - First jog on the embarcadero http://rnkpr.com/a2xoi84  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @khil ha. know EXACTLY what you mean. why do toxic people always get cool jobs?    
    
    
    @khil maybe they just miss us and want to be better people so they can have nice (girl)friends again... jerks.    
    
    
    Who are the world's worst tourists? Check out our survey results on @businessinsider: http://ow.ly/lfeDH     
    
    
    The 10 countries with the most notoriously ill-behaved tourists: http://ow.ly/lfgyM  Wonder how much of this is self-fulfilling prophecy?    
    
    
    Bostonians, if you're out and running this spring, pledge your miles with @_runnow (powered by @brandnetworks) (& track 'em with @RunKeeper)    
    
    
    Conversations with my 2-year-old (OMG please make a million of these): http://ow.ly/lkacm     
    
    
    Our robot wall is complete muahahaha cc @launchsquad pic.twitter.com/3IqlYql44L    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer some great points. tho to the profession's credit, that's a better % than many major pubs' bylines these days. much work left.    
    
    
    @thefilmgoer insidious and self-exacerbating issues. on a semi-related note, if you hvn't, check out http://velamag.com/  - love the credo    
    
    
    Fiddleheads are delicious but I have to not look at them while I eat them    
    
    
    @paulbtucker that's awesome @crulge fb status made me think of that earlier. Rip volvo    
    
    
    "Employing the Power of Writing Fast and Slow" - interesting take on the value of metaphor http://contently.com/blog/2013/05/31/employing-the-power-of-writing-fast-and-slow/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just swept all the pollen off our patio. Literally as I finished the upstairs neighbors did their deck. Pic is now. pic.twitter.com/1yNqCogqb3    
    
    
    The worst part is my neighbors are too nice for me to even get mad. Time for a glass of wine.    
    
    
    Great multimedia article explaining #quantum computing on @pandodaily : http://ow.ly/lEXKq  #nerdtastic    
    
    
    "Delicious Bites: Strawberry Swirl Cheesecake" good read http://feedly.com/k/18QPWiV     
    
    
    Huge news for client @brandnetworks: $68 million financing from AEA - their first round. Inspiring bootstrap story: http://ow.ly/lM2lI     
    
    
    Pretty psyched to start paying rent with @dwolla. Will report back! #nomorechecks    
    
    
    @crulge yeah, and pardon my language but eff paypal.    
    
    
    @mattyoun just starting to use it, but have heard good things. have had terrible experiences with paypal in the past, so i avoid them.    
    
    
    @mattyoun worth noting that google recently announced that they're going to let people do peer-to-peer pmt via gmail soon    
    
    
    Rainbow over the Zakim pic.twitter.com/kMtWkrxdUp    
    
    
    Gotta give it up to @overstock. Their customer service is beyond rad. Kudos, guys.    
    
    
    @triposo iOS travel app helping you explore the world's small, cool towns: http://ow.ly/m2gC4  Great update, just in time for summer!    
    
    
    Way behind here, but damn. Mad Men is killing it this season. The writing is 1000% better.    
    
    
    @nikkimetz reading too much Atlantic?    
    
    
    @nikkimetz close second. but what would we do without their incisive social commentary?    
    
    
    Future (approx. 7 p.m. ET) status: http://ow.ly/m2BC9     
    
    
    Pretzels, beer & ac: hot weather survival kit. http://instagram.com/p/a_pZxrQYwZ/     
    
    
    Learned a new word this am thx to @anniemurphypaul: "nachas," Yiddish for taking pride in others' accomplishments. Take that, schadenfreude.    
    
    
    Yeah, I waited until today to port my work RSS to feedly, what of it? #livingdangerously    
    
    
    Still seething about this NYT piece on the cost of giving birth: http://ow.ly/mAMGK  Not even close to convinced that Obamacare will help    
    
    
    @onewil yep. that TIME op-ed from last fall was even more maddening. i don't know how, but it has to stop.    
    
    
    Well, this has been a Sisyphean week.    
    
    
    Just completed a 4.05 mi run - Pretty idyllic, but I wouldn't mind clearer street names #solost http://rnkpr.com/a3e2e2g  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    I can't even articulate how much I love this. Hating on millenials is lazy and absurd. Find something better to do. http://ow.ly/mOeso     
    
    
    Well, I guess the future's here. Rent #paidwith @Dwolla this month.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker yes...    
    
    
    My mom's garden is better than your mom's garden. http://instagram.com/p/buV1hLQY9D/     
    
    
    @MonstahTruck: Really don't want to be wiping tears off @jmtortor's (lame) birthday cake. Need some ice cream sammies in Kendall stat.    
    
    
    @_katcampbell Hahaha oh no... Already? T troubles?    
    
    
    @_katcampbell don't even feel bad. i get lost on the T all the time. (shhh don't tell @czsays)    
    
    
    Maybe I shouldn't be this excited about a grocery store opening, but I. am. http://ow.ly/mZbwZ     
    
    
    @nath_on_fire @mekncl I wish it was a Wegman's. It's a lowly Whole Foods, but we've had no grocery store in my nabe for almost a year, so...    
    
    
    @mekncl I haven't, but my coworker @jmtortors is a bit of an evangelist. My current local(ish) favorite is Russo's in Watertown    
    
    
    @crulge Look, Tim. I don't want to have to get in my car to go to the grocery store. Surely you can appreciate that.    
    
    
    @crulge Whoa. Go get 'em!    
    
    
    Dudes, if you like good TV and you're not watching Orange is the New Black, I strongly suggest you rectify that.    
    
    
    @acromp 2 years of hard-earned wisdom right there.    
    
    
    @acromp But what do they know about the robustness of content marketing? NOTHING.    
    
    
    Single quotes are a scourge. #grammarscrooge    
    
    
    Just completed a 3.01 mi run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a3hxtmf  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Interested in #contentmarketing? Check out my latest post: RT @newscred: Using offline events for online content: http://ow.ly/n7RaX     
    
    
    @crulge that or "our coffee totally doesn't suck! but it's practically free!"    
    
    
    @nikkimetz Not sure this officially counts, but I adored an Everlasting Meal.    
    
    
    @czsays who, me?    
    
    
    Rainy Friday morning treat even more fun bc I #paidwith the sbux app.    
    
    
    @ the Folk Festival enjoying some perfect weather @ Newport, RI http://instagram.com/p/cSOMXewY8n/     
    
    
    That thing where you look at your calendar and realize you have no meetings scheduled all. day. #happiness #productivity    
    
    
    Lady next to me on Sbux patio got her bull mastiff his own frappe. Vanilla bean.    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris They let Dasher in Bed Bath & Beyond?!    
    
    
    @onewil Nice kicks. Happy birthday!    
    
    
    Breaking Bad is pretty much the only show I will brave live cable commercials for. #sayingsomething    
    
    
    Some days I just don't even know. http://ow.ly/nVHNm  #bustle #whatplanetamion    
    
    
    What I See When You’re Using Your Smartphone (via @Pocket) My sentiments precisely. http://pocket.co/s4thy     
    
    
        
    
    
    Arianna Huffington killing it on stage at #INBOUND13, inspirational. "Failure not the opposite of success but a stepping stone to it."    
    
    
    "It's not just about leaning in, it's about leaning back (to recharge)" - Arianna Huffington #INBOUND13    
    
    
    Current status pic.twitter.com/PIBd3LJmWa    
    
    
    Fantastic post on how we view and treat strong, complex female characters by Anna Gunn (aka Skylar White) http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/24/opinion/i-have-a-character-issue.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    I think they're competing for best bed head http://instagram.com/p/d9gOxtwY7Y/     
    
    
    @ing_infocus after midnight (the eric clapton version)    
    
    
    If Breaking Bad Had Been Set in the UK: http://ow.ly/oKdZI  #sadbutfunny #butalsosad    
    
    
    @benjerrystruck We do! @LaunchSquad over at the American Twine Building in Cambridge (222 3rd St.) cc @jmtortors @ESal    
    
    
    Scoring a little PR for dogchild #2, all in a day's work: http://ow.ly/oPe0a     
    
    
    I'm cleaning up my twitter using http://www.justunfollow.com  Useful..    
    
    
    Dogcouch http://instagram.com/p/eS0vxwQY5l/     
    
    
    Nooo RT @nwsboston: Its official, Boston has dropped to 44 degrees this morning, breaking the old record low for the date of 45 set in 1986.    
    
    
    A refreshing political ad featuring a liberal MA candidate & his Tea Party dad: http://ow.ly/oZo0u     
    
    
    Jennifer Weiner bites back: http://ow.ly/oZM7I  #franzenfreude    
    
    
    "choose which paper runs his 5600-word condemnation of self-promo that ends with an unironic hyperlinked invitation to buy his new book."    
    
    
        
    
    
    @crulge it's less dope than it seems, unfortunately. was super buggy for me.    
    
    
    If Google does manage to solve death, I will get a Droid. #calico    
    
    
    @anatescott Fuck 'em.    
    
    
    @crulge sure. but i gots stuff to do in this lifetime, wouldn't mind a little extra yardage.    
    
    
    @a1icey filing that away!    
    
    
    Really looking forward to diving into this book by @elizhydestevens: http://ow.ly/p1ujq  #artandmoney    
    
    
    "Walter, like you, like me, like everyone, can be more than one thing at the same time, just as a great work of popular art can be"    
    
    
    That and more commentary that would put an English doctorate to shame: http://vult.re/15DjMW8  #breakingbad    
    
    
    I wonder a bit about shows with one writer vs. a team. Are the characters more cohesive? Sometimes fissures seem unavoidable w/ team.    
    
    
    NO and YES RT @joycecaroloates: Is "nonstop recognition" truly a problem in schools?   In adult life, "nonstop nonrecognition" is the norm.    
    
    
    @zlilgrnbrd I think you mean benefactor? :)    
    
    
    MT @joycecaroloates: Though subj may suggest gender "specialties" there is no diff btwn sexes in writing: voices, language, talent, energy.    
    
    
    Weird to see Boston so foggy this am. For a moment thought I woke up on the west coast.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus :( Hope he's okay! Poor little guy    
    
    
    @ing_infocus Dogs will be dogs?    
    
    
    Why France used to work more than the US, and why they don't any longer: http://ow.ly/pCiWY  Fascinant.    
    
    
    School aren’t emasculating boys; American masculinity is dehumanizing them: http://ow.ly/pETPi  - Great piece on gender roles @salon    
    
    
    Welcome! Glad to see another incredible writer reject the Franzen haterade. RT @aliceannmunro: Welcome! I join Twitter today. Interesting!    
    
    
    Why the Hyperloop is the most important tech innovation this year http://ow.ly/pEV4W  Great piece in @Wired from client QWave Capital    
    
    
    First morning I've seen my breath. pic.twitter.com/zFKWQEIbqz    
    
    
    Beyond psyched for Alice Munro to win the Nobel. One of my earliest favorites and for all her accolades, never thought she got enough credit    
    
    
    Alright, garlic soup. You win this round. #sorrycoworkers cc @czsays    
    
    
    On the plus side I'm probably legit vampire PROOF for at least the next 48 hours.    
    
    
    Just completed a 2.03 mi run - First training run for the Run Fur Fun #mspca These two are slooowww http://rnkpr.com/a48rqib  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    I just set a goal on @RunKeeper! I want to run in a 5K race. Show your support! http://bit.ly/1630aN8     
    
    
    @thefilmgoer @czsays Belatedly, Matty, I'm so glad you agree with me about the direct address. I stopped watching because of it.    
    
    
    . MT @magplease: Only ever 7 emails, 90 phone-min w/insurance, 7 signed forms and a privacy waiver away from the medical attention you need.    
    
    
    MT @petfurniture: happy possibly working govt day! don't forget John Boehner looks like one of those circus peanut candies that no one likes    
    
    
    Sour beer? I can drink to that: http://ow.ly/pVrGv     
    
    
        
    
    
    @p_brady aand that's perfect.    
    
    
    Excellent rebuttal to abhorrent victim-blaming earlier this week in Slate - "College Men: Stop Getting Drunk": http://ow.ly/pXmr0     
    
    
    So nice waking up with the windows open in the burbs in Oct. Dad's babbling brook doesn't hurt either. pic.twitter.com/TiZZg0rU6Y    
    
    
    Very few apps as seamless as @Dropbox. Automatic screenshot storage? Don't mind if I do. #fangirl #nerd    
    
    
    If you're in Boston right now, check out the sunset. #dayum    
    
    
    Good morning, says the emegency warer removal man. Bad morning, he corrects himself. pic.twitter.com/MMx7na4fTm    
    
    
    Hell yeah Sox! Love this city so    
    
    
    The sigh of relief when I discover I actually have 2 bags of hot cinnamon sunset left when I thought I ran out last week (!) #teafreak    
    
    
    Okay http://change.org . This is officially in(s)ane. Unsubscribe. http://ow.ly/qmZZB     
    
    
    4 Real-World Uses for Quantum Cryptography: http://ow.ly/qDsUT  Cool post from client QWave Capital    
    
    
    Thank heavens. RT @KHil: LADIES: your biggest holiday concerns addressed http://the-toast.net/2013/11/11/eating-tips-for-holiday-parties/ …    
    
    
    “Join Healthworks. Get fit for your big day.” X —> Hide this ad. —> Why did you hide this? —> Offensive. #dailygooddeed    
    
    
    Symptoms of hereditary dog obsession pic.twitter.com/M0GCY0QEKL    
    
    
    Just completed a 2.11 mi run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a4hoeuc  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    Write your reps (quickly & simply) here: http://ow.ly/r5OR4  and tell them to support cyclist and pedestrian safety reform    
    
    
    I’m flattered? http://imgur.com/AHCwBwW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just completed a 2.02 mi run with @RunKeeper. Check it out! http://rnkpr.com/a4k0r44  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    @paulbtucker I’m putting my toes on a plane now    
    
    
    Is it just me or does the sriracha shortage feel like yet another of their brilliant undercover PR moves?    
    
    
    Major fail @amazon. #packaging pic.twitter.com/wv0yRzFeaa    
    
    
    With any luck, my oddly vast knowledge of title insurance is going to come in handy in 2014. #househunting    
    
    
    The furry housebeasts are decidedly pro-Snow Day. #snuggles #fireplace #letitsnow    
    
    
    These dogs play Russian roulette with the fireplace. How close can I sit without singeing my fur? #snowday    
    
    
    @tjfaust nice! have an amazing time. you going to be blogging or anything?    
    
    
    @KHil i think she's circa 30    
    
    
    Not gonna lie, a little offended that Google thinks I'm a dude. MT @bgreinhart: Link to see who Google thinks you are: http://bit.ly/tRQbjw     
    
    
    @pug JRTs are the best (pugs are pretty cute too tho...)    
    
    
    Oh snap, here we go: RT @SarahFKessler: RT @mashable: BREAKING: Facebook to File for IPO Next Week [REPORT] - http://on.mash.to/zFqxwH     
    
    
    What up Big Blue RT @BostonTweet: Belichick has won 5 conference titles (2001, 2003, 2004, 2007, 2011) since being hired on this day in 2000    
    
    
    (No, I don't care about football, just can't resist a little alma mater pride)    
    
    
    Disappointing to me that someone as talented and creative as JF doesn't see the possibilities of ebooks. Paper's dead. http://tgr.ph/yTzKcG     
    
    
    Cool infographic explaining how pasta, not bacon, makes you fat: http://bit.ly/AkVmh8  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Boston mayor wants more tech startups to hire high school interns: http://b.globe.com/wGorDf  (by @GlobeMBFarrell) Good idea or no?    
    
    
    Love it! Might be taking my first Uber... MT @danprimack: @Uber_BOS will be providing half-off rides for #GetLiquid attendees tonight    
    
    
    @ZachServideo Yep. Kindof creepy..    
    
    
    Incredible RT @stefugee: 1865 letter from emancipated slave to former master. http://bit.ly/xwcmkr     
    
    
    Makes me want to start a new tradition! RT @jolieodell: Tea: the best meal of the day http://bit.ly/yI8i0d     
    
    
    Alleyoop launches! Pearson-backed startup aims to be the Zynga of education: http://on.mash.to/z0qMWM  via @SarahFKessler for @mashable    
    
    
    Who owns FB? Fascinating: MT @ScottKirsner: In advance of the FB filing, there's this: http://bit.ly/jztKQ5     
    
    
    Kudos! RT @CDiRusso: Congrats to @LaunchSquad clients @Fab and @evernote for winning big at the #crunchies last night    
    
    
    @tjfaust LS does, I don't personally. They are indeed awesome.    
    
    
    Need a judge? cc @BKramer MT @BostonTweet: Burrito Bowl, comp to create the best burrito, this Sat @Poes_Kitchen 1-4pm http://bit.ly/wW5PCI     
    
    
    @CBM I need something like that for Twitter....    
    
    
    @CBM the problem is people I like & whose tweets I otherwise care about. Just want to filter out the football mania...    
    
    
    Check it out: RT @TechCrunch: Pearson-Incubated Startup Alleyoop Launches To Gamify Adaptive Learning  http://tcrn.ch/weVk9V  by @ripemp    
    
    
    @fvinh now *that* is a good channel.    
    
    
    Bought a hard copy of GOOD magazine this weekend, and have been very impressed. Check it out if you haven't, for sure. http://bit.ly/sZESgF     
    
    
    Great post: MT @usnews: Could Alleyoop Be the Spotify of Math Education? http://bit.ly/yMP9Du  by @jason_koebler    
    
    
    @Michele_Moore Never been a big fan of the cold, haha. ;) Went to college in TX to escape it -- looks like we have lots in common!    
    
    
    @Michele_Moore Rice -- never thought I'd end up back here, but Boston's such a great city I'm learning to deal with the cold :)    
    
    
    It's true. Awww. #puppyclout RT @mfarbs: LaunchSquad Boston swooning over this bundle of cuteness: http://bit.ly/Aaq523  cc: @kcinnamond    
    
    
    @ing_infocus wait.. what?! i'm intrigued..    
    
    
    @ing_infocus Very cool! Lemme know when you're soliciting donations :)    
    
    
    @paulbtucker @awhitelie Goodreads got me on that (and then told me what a bajillion random acquaintances were reading) #dislikeautofriending    
    
    
    Rather unfortunate RT @fvinh: Oh, Mittens. This is not subtle at all. http://twitpic.com/8glbi8     
    
    
    No joke. Amazing story. RT @mfarbs: Wonder Dog. I dare you not to well up while reading: http://nyti.ms/y7eJv3     
    
    
    Love that the post on Agile dev I just read had a shout-out to Dickens and his "too easily overlooked" contributions to lit #literategeeks    
    
    
    Puppy thieves?! Off with their heads! http://bit.ly/wilpyL     
    
    
    @adayal on behalf of Cambridge, you're welcome.    
    
    
    @paulbtucker good date?    
    
    
    Phew. Who steals a puppy? MT @BostonTweet: Pebbles, dog stolen from Beacon Hill, was just found 30 mi away in Lowell http://on.fb.me/z6GPpA     
    
    
    Very cool. MT @ScottKirsner: @MassGovernor is planning to tour a "net zero " house in Newton: http://bit.ly/rbqmnn  (1st one in BOS area?)    
    
    
    @8bitJay Aww! Dachsund? Yours?    
    
    
    @8bitJay nice! all the fun, none of the poop duty    
    
    
    Gourmet restaurant lends kitchen to aspiring chefs: http://bit.ly/xL2xNo  Cool idea!    
    
    
    Seriously! RT @Zims: Great @Fab profile from @pandodaily: "That isn’t an etailer. That’s Anna Wintour."    
    
    
    USA! USA! RT @nath_on_fire: "The Pile of Poo registered 3.3/2.8 in the key demos, while the Parks & Rec airing opposite it scored 1.3/0.9."    
    
    
    And this is why we can't have nice [television shows] #coughcommunitycough    
    
    
    Holy crap, Google. When did you learn this trick? http://yfrog.com/ketajjp     
    
    
    The theme is sunshine & energy :) RT @mfarbs: Just picked out some paint/carpets for new offices w/ @MegScarborough. "Grassy Fields" anyone?    
    
    
    @petfurniture ha. love.    
    
    
    Just passed a place selling single roses for $6.50. So yeah.    
    
    
    On a cheerier note, hope you get to spend your Valentines Day with someone you love, snuggled up like lil buuunnnnies.    
    
    
    @ing_infocus Fair point. Maybe some of the boys were buying flowers for their boyfriends...    
    
    
    @onewil that's a great photo    
    
    
    @onewil nah. i'm a dog person.    
    
    
    @onewil wait... sweatshirt or cat? ha    
    
    
    @onewil ahh... boyfriend just got one in the mail, loves it. they're a client of ours, super high-quality, american made.    
    
    
    @cheryllmorris totally depends on whether they're on land or in the water    
    
    
    @AbbyVW Do you know yet what you want to specialize in when you're done?    
    
    
    @charlesmhampton yes    
    
    
    Oh, that sounds divine MT @tosci: Andy made Semla ice cream based on Swedish Fat Tuesday pastry.  Cardamom, marzipan, cake, mascarpone.    
    
    
    Uncharted territory. Westward ho! RT @mat: Hey tech journos, has anyone written about Pinterest yet?    
    
    
    Great time at #RubyRiot. Very impressed with Gov. Patrick. Thx guys! #payitforward    
    
    
    Think I helped a couple techstars dudes refine their elevator pitch while in line for #RubyRiot last nite. Does that count as #payitforward?    
    
    
    @AbbyVW Okay, little Bobby. Time for your Jagermeister. Open up!    
    
    
    @jenniroja meh. i just did, and i'm unimpressed so far.    
    
    
    @tjfaust oh, don't hate on Carole    
    
    
    @tjfaust ha. totally misread that. GOOD.    
    
    
    @Hey_Billy their tourism board needs to hire you    
    
    
    Check out @Unrollme - http://mashable.com/2012/02/27/unroll-me/ … - http://signup.unroll.me  unsubscribe from all email newsletters at once    
    
    
    NOT bummed that mozzarella-making just got added to the agenda for our lake weekend. @notABBY: Future Astronaut & Fearless Queen of Dairy.    
    
    
    Okay, I need to know this. What is up with fashion bloggers who don't put their arms in their sleeves?    
    
    
    @awhitelie @tjfaust seconded. but I get most of my news from NPR, so ...    
    
    
    Rescued yet another piece of furniture from the curb. The drawer pull screams 1980s Miami, but nothing a visit to Anthropologie can't solve.    
    
    
    Down with Paypal! RT @cheryllmorris: AmEx launches Serve Facebook app for friend-to-friend payments http://bit.ly/yq6Nto     
    
    
    Cool thought piece on how mobile payment systems could make us more financially responsible http://bit.ly/w9T8Ym  from @wfrick @BostInno    
    
    
    @paulbtucker, other Austin ppl: good central restaurant recs at places unlikely to be booked for SXSW? Nicer bar-type setting? cc @ESal    
    
    
    