Trip planning all through Europe, Brussels this weekend. Then France, Dublin, London, Amsterdam, Germany, Italy, Spain, France.    
    
    
    Bastille Day in San Francisco, gotta love a city that loves everyone's holidays.. find me at Irish Bank for a street party!    
    
    
    NCC PCMA Summer Mixer tonight at Infusion Lounge, should be some good networking.    
    
    
    Chianti tasting last night at the Palace Hotel... a blast was had by all!    
    
    
    delighted to live in such a wonderful city like San Francisco but wishing the weather was a bit warmer.    
    
    
    Giants Industry Night this evening, so excited!!! Who could pass up 2 hours of free cocktails, a Giants T-shirt and a ticket to the game!    
    
    
    Mexico is not only safe but an amazing time and super cheap!    
    
    
    you will never know how many documents are behind a large conference... and yes folks, I make them happen.    
    
    
    You know you work at a start up when you can load your nerf gun while talking to your COO :)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Mustache Harbor at 111 Minna and the Loveboat party was a major hit!!!! Everyone was looking hot in their Aloha wear and sailor hats!    
    
    
    Please make the midriff shirts go away!!!! That was so jr high    
    
    
    @JessicaGomez13 You go to Crunch?  I just started at ClubOne but maybe I should try crunch if people I know go there!    
    
    
    @JessicaGomez13 @CrunchGym Which one do you go to??    
    
    
    @JessicaGomez13 @CrunchGym Fabulous, lets go next week so I can try it out!!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @no_inbetween @day_nightevents Just checked its June 23rd at ATT Park.... Maybe depends on price? Ps wanna come to happy hour today taco tue    
    
    
    It's tough being an event planner #pressclubsf pic.twitter.com/A1pgeAZH    
    
    
    Yo pic.twitter.com/u4kyg7Ny    
    
    
    Best way to start a morning :) pic.twitter.com/JGwbTxhH    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    US denies evidence of mermaids@LSH ...wow we knew it as kids..  http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-us-canada-18692830 …    
    
    
    Best part of my day: kombucha at Eventbrite @Bartozone    
    
    
    Tahoe today... Yes please @Bartozone    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Taking a much needed night off!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Come take sake shots at barracuda @marly2_2    
    
    
        
    
    
    @marly2_2 Hey it was just 4 drinks and a few bottles of wine... isn't that one drink?    
    
    
    I'm at AT&T Park for Los Angeles Dodgers vs. San Francisco Giants (San Francisco, CA) w/ 189 others [pic]: http://4sq.com/Q1Cqi4     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/LXczao     
    
    
    Putting together the photo shoot list for Oracle OpenWorld 2009    
    
    
    I love it when a vendor saves my life, if you need quick printing go with Leewood Press in SF!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    TL history art gallery opening, Rogue Trivia Night, Cat Club 80's night. Events, Events!    
    
    
    All signs point me to Austin.... The Best Places For Business And Careers @forbes http://onforb.es/NOOXUL  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Tonight's events, A's game, BENNY BENASSI at Ruby Sky... Life is good. Happy Friday!    
    
    
    The one day I need a pep talk and no one answers..... @LSH @berrytj and @Bartozone- not the one to call he sucks at them    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm pretty sure Stevie Ray Vaughan just saved my life #chilltime #longweek @LSH    
    
    
    @marly2_2 That's why apple makes your phone useless... so you will buy a new one. I say do it!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Lots of OpenWorld meetings today and training on a new Champion tool.    
    
    
    @berrytj You know Davy Crocket is my cousin right?    
    
    
    @joeyhinson  I see how it is, no friendly tweets for me :(    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Not coming back @LSH    
    
    
    @LSH @bartozone I lied, San Diego beat me up... We're better off long distance #cominghome #exhausted    
    
    
        
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Jetsetter" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different airports! http://4sq.com/QA3Lsf     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Is looking into money saving and green drinking water use ideas for OpenWorld.  Any ideas?    
    
    
    @TechCrunch Meet Up's are coming to Toronto 11/5, Detroit 11/7 and Chicago 11/9! Tickets: http://tcrn.ch/NQ9LNp  @LSH @1871Chicago @Bartozone    
    
    
        
    
    
    @JackGavigan sorry bad at twitter its January 31!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Shutterbug" badge on @foursquare for adding photos to my check-ins. Say cheese! http://4sq.com/R3loRt     
    
    
        
    
    
    Hardly Strictly Blue Grass, ALL WEEKEND LONG!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Halloween 2012” badge on @foursquare! Has anyone seen my Honey Boo Boo mask? http://4sq.com/TMJlJI     
    
    
    @Engadget SIC Meet Up in Seattle tonight, excited to see you! @LSH    
    
    
    I unlocked the “Zombie Swarm” badge on @foursquare for checking in with a crowd on Halloween! Gangnam Style galore. http://4sq.com/S9SsoG     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Greasy Spoon" badge on @foursquare for checking in at diners! Bring on the burgers! http://4sq.com/QibzRw     
    
    
        
    
    
    #TCDetroit is rocking Hockey Town Cafe, come grab a drink with @TechCrunch    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Bender" badge on @foursquare for checking in four nights in a row! http://4sq.com/WIqas6     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare for checking in at pizza joints! Pies all around! http://4sq.com/RJSiH5     
    
    
    Going to the PCMA Networking event tonight at Sens.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Headed to Los Angeles and San Diego for Sand Castles and Over the Line, should be great festivals!    
    
    
    A fine meal after whale shark swimming :) (@ Bismark-cito) [pic]: http://4sq.com/ShGXOI     
    
    
    Back at work, ready to take on the week. Really excited to see No Doubt tomorrow!    
    
    
        
    
    
    not a fan of this rain but still happy to be home    
    
    
    MTR Invades Engadget NY Meetup: 2012 Edition and I got a shout out :) http://www.mytakeradio.com/2012/11/mtr-invades-engadgets-ny-meetup-2012-edition/ …    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different pizza joints! http://4sq.com/YPkbmz     
    
    
        
    
    
    Going on a vacation in my own city- 10 days of tourism, only difference, I know how to use public transit and how to get deals on tickets!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Mall Rat” badge on @foursquare for checking in at malls! Time for a fancy pretzel. http://4sq.com/Rbst3H     
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different coffee shops! http://4sq.com/VohOTN     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Mall Rat" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different malls! http://4sq.com/UtKgQZ     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Players Club” badge on @foursquare for a late night check-in at a place that's swarming! http://4sq.com/ZFGqWE     
    
    
    We're on the side of a bus.... Hope you got your ticket! #crunchies @Bartozone @LSH @joeyhinson @JamieQuiocho pic.twitter.com/tyjqSO2C    
    
    
        
    
    
    @LSH it's the only way to listen to electronic music!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Urban hiking #sunday pic.twitter.com/l4HlrD2V    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I just unlocked the "7-10 Split" badge on @foursquare for checking in at bowling alleys! The Dude is in the house! http://4sq.com/Z2769h     
    
    
        
    
    
    I just reached Level 3 of the "Jetsetter" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 10 different airports! http://4sq.com/13qZE9b     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Crunked" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/XKcrwh     
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Greasy Spoon" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different diners! http://4sq.com/Z8W11M     
    
    
        
    
    
    Trying to figure out what to wear tonight to the Yelp Elite Event at newly re-opened, The Cafe... Put The Disco Back in Frisco!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @marly2_2 when you coming home now??    
    
    
    Doing our part to clean Ocean Beach #MonsterHelpDay with @TechCrunch @neddesmond @JamieQuiocho @LSH @nicolasvincent #AOL    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Wow @Comcast I'm on the phone for an hour and then when I'm escalated, I'm sent to a forever ringing phone number. I'm so annoyed!    
    
    
        
    
    
    