    
    
    
    Looking forward to networking @thekeyshudds this afternoon, will be great to see everyone and meet new people    
    
    
    Berri girls are really looking forward to our pamper session @AlexHouseSpa tomorrow, strictly a works outing ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @catcreativem Happy Friday indeed!  Thanks for the tweet, great working with you too, we must do it again sometime! :)    
    
    
    @catcreativem Theres ones more now :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    xmas must be getting near, currently planning how to treat our clients this year... lucky lot! :)    
    
    
    Have a Berri Christmas, your chance to win free design time!
Now assuming you’ve all been good little boys and... http://fb.me/vTGW7O8V     
    
    
    Have a Berri Christmas, your chance to win free design time! - http://eepurl.com/hNwxA     
    
    
    Mmm mulled wine and minced pies this afternoon (and networking of course), best go easy on the mulled wine! @KeyWordsCopy @cafeollo    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @catcreativem noooooooo you can't hate Joomla, Joomla is my friend #Iamsad #getalife    
    
    
    @MosaicVO Merry Xmas to all at Mosaic from the Berri girls    
    
    
    Don’t miss out on the opportunity to win 5 hours free design time http://bit.ly/uBZU8c  #whodoesntlikeafreebie    
    
    
    Networking@Café Ollo in Media Centre, then back to Berri HQ for a de-brief on 2011 & a plan to take over the world in 2012! HAHA! #evillaugh    
    
    
    "Good design is obvious, great design is transparent" Joe Sparano    
    
    
    Krista's just built and sent an emailer for one of our clients to 23'000 of their subscribers!! #thatssomefanclub    
    
    
    Interesting article on BBC about our ever growing expectations from our favourite websites http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-16300000 …    
    
    
    Congratulations to Janet Wood from @Inmindhealth on winning our free design time competition #whosaluckygirlthen    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    starting my research on social networking pro's and con's and came across this article, well worth the read when you h…http://lnkd.in/J6cdHm     
    
    
        
    
    
    Killin time on M1 & naming fonts used on company logos on the side of lorries&vans!punisment4making me listen to TalkSport #Ilovetypography    
    
    
    Had great afternoon brainstorming with Krista on ideas to boost an already successful business for a client.A rolling stone gathers no moss!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rNzJxY  Hi Jo, I'd like to put Berri forward! we can offer a broad range of graphic design and web solutions for small to...    
    
    
        
    
    
    want to know what everyones talking about?? get ahead of the game with social trends? this may prove a useful tool http://topsy.com/     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Follow Berri on Facebook, we've shown examples of our work and up and coming projects, we look forward to seeing you t…http://lnkd.in/zXuYYy     
    
    
    Great quote... “I like to say that Twitter is like a bar, Facebook is your living room&LinkedIn is the local chamber of commerce" BSStoltz    
    
    
    @AlexHouseSpa I don't think modern technology could manage it! you're at a whole new level! hehe    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @KeyWordsCopy there used to be!it was set up in 1994 but went out of production in 2004 according to Wikipedia http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_Magazine …    
    
    
    I just can not get warm today! brrrrrrrrrr    
    
    
    should I consider these in the name of keeping warm at my desk? ... http://www.thefashionpolice.net/images/Beard-hat-moustace-gloves.jpg …    
    
    
    http://soloround.blogspot.com/  well done Abby! what an inspiration to any age group! I think my priorities left something to be desired when I was 16!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @CallTeam great to talk earlier! thanks for a great service too! :-)    
    
    
    @Platypus_ why thank you,we are trying to be super efficient with this social networking malarkey & attempting witty&informative banter!    
    
    
    Share what you're viewing on your screen with people working on another comps!handy for making amendments etc https://join.me/  its FREE    
    
    
    @CallTeam cheers for the shout out :-)    
    
    
    I'd like to say thanks to Sarah @MosaicVO for yesterdays networking lunch & chance to meet the rest of the team & other devotees to MosaicVO    
    
    
    Currently writing Berri’s emailer ready for Valentine’s day, no holding back on the cheesy romance quips in this one! #cheesetastic    
    
    
        
    
    
    Finishing touches being completed by Krista to the soon to be launched website for @life4todayltd very excited! Watch this space!    
    
    
    @solopress must be 'no rest for the wicked' your end, we're saint-like here lol    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/KcrJhE  Hi Diane have you tried the networking group Ladies-4-Networking? I find them a friendly, inviting group! Next...    
    
    
    Great to see @AlexHouseSpa in the @huddersfieldeye again this month, Maxine will be buying shares at this rate! :-)    
    
    
    3rd happiest place in the country is Huddersfield? I'll take that! http://lnkd.in/c9arr9     
    
    
    read about the next big thing in Social Media ... http://lnkd.in/vBxxAn     
    
    
    Creepy I think someones been reading my mind - apart from the bit about mac's v pc's! http://www.linkedin.com/news?actionBar=&articleID=5567498259158540288&ids=cPsVdPgNc38VdzcMdPsSe3oRdiMPd38Md3sMcj8Sc3oUczwVdzkRb3wUcz0QdjwRcjARczwVd3sSdjkIcj0UdzsMc38TdzcTe30Nc3sRdiMSczkNdPwRdPcOcjoScPoOdPkR&aag=true&freq=weekly&trk=eml-tod2-b-ttl-2&ut=3tsjV88QjhXB41 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @life4todayltd proud to be part of your website design&build,hope you're as chuffed with results as we are http://www.life-4-today.co.uk     
    
    
    "Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving." - Albert Einstein. great inspiration @ahmetorta    
    
    
    Hi all I was wondering if anyone had a contact for someone who can design and create smart phone apps? Cheers :-)    
    
    
        
    
    
    had a fantastic massage @AlexHouseSpa today, a well needed start to my weekend - well not before I finish off a few bits of work! #busyweek    
    
    
    @AlexHouseSpa I wish the spa every success in flying through the till rolls & that I shall be contributing to their demise in near future!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KeyWordsCopy I can't wait! my 3 favourite things; Coffee, Cake and People (in no particular order!!)    
    
    
    look forward to the networking at 4.30 Cafe Society organised by @KeyWordsCopy if you miss this one makesure you get signed up for the next!    
    
    
    Turned up to networking ... Without my business cards!! What a dingbat!    
    
    
    @TandCakeCafe @BluebellAlmond sounds delicious I'll try very hard to arrange a 'business meeting' asap!! it's been too long!    
    
    
    Not just any old networking event! Check out "Key Words Coffee & Cake May 2012" …http://coffeeandcakemay2012-estw.eventbrite.co.uk  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    another great edition of @huddersfieldeye great article from Michelle @KeyWordsCopy, & lots of vouchers! booked in for pamper ones already!    
    
    
    As someone who has spent hours dealing with IE7 bugs when building websites I couldn't help but chuckle at this article http://tinyurl.com/6wf7jfg     
    
    
    CALLING ALL PRINTERS!! I'm needing a printing quote please ... 12pp including cover A4 landscape brochure printed full colour throughout on…    
    
    
    Opening ceremony showed our history, quirkyness, creativity, humour and the chaotic brilliance that is GB #olympicceremony #London2012    
    
    
    heading to @AlexHouseSpa to help celebrate their 5th Birthday then to Cafe Society for networking with Michelle @KeyWordsCopy. Busy, busy!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @CinnamonGirlUK    
    
    
    @solopress are giving away an iPad mini + £250 of luxury Christmas gifts. To enter the comp visit http://blog.solopress.com/competitions/win-apple-ipad-mini-and-christmas-goodies-solopress-competition-december-2012/ … #solocomp    
    
    
    @life4todayltd @BerriDesign excited to be once again working with Joanne, developing her business & updating her website/marketing materials    
    
    
        
    
    
    Been busy FINALLY updating our Twitter page with a new design, take a look and see what you think    
    
    
    