@joncoffey I try not to be obnoxious :) RT @hipstermermaid: First rule of gluten free club:Only talk about gfree club.All the time. Forever.    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Saw this piece on #drones in latest @wired and knew it would be up your alley! http://www.wired.com/dangerroom/2012/06/ff_drones …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Fascinating article, those are some good superpowers of startups :) RT http://www.xconomy.com/san-francisco/2012/07/11/startup-superpowers-and-how-big-companies-can-get-them-too/ …    
    
    
    At Bernstein for the @founders event - very energizing already!    
    
    
    @smart startups interested to hear you speak at @founders event!    
    
    
    @smartstartups love the candor!    
    
    
    A fascinating new book tackling #resilience - financially, ecologically, politically @wdeggers http://www.time.com/time/health/article/0,8599,2119663,00.html?xid=rss-health&utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+time%2Fscienceandhealth+%28TIME%3A+Top+Science+Stories%29&utm_content=Google+Feedfetcher …    
    
    
    Grim #healthcare stats and lots of #startups tackling the problem: http://healthydoseofimagination.com/  #digihealth @wdeggers @TMFPapester    
    
    
    A new exhibit comes to the #Smithsonian on American Enterprise. Surprised we didn't have one sooner, but good to see http://www.washingtonpost.com/entertainment/museums/smithsonian-announces-new-exhibit-dedicated-to-business-at-american-history-museum/2012/07/18/gJQARAdgtW_story.html …    
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell well even as a "work in progress" you are one of the boldest people I know!    
    
    
    Where in the US foreign tech workers are in hottest demand: http://www.wired.com/business/2012/07/h1-bs-in-the-heartland/ … #jobs    
    
    
    What does it mean to be "happy"? The UK attempts to measure it with a new #wellbeing index: http://www.economist.com/blogs/blighty/2012/07/national-well-being?fsrc=scn/fb/wl/bl/importanceofbeinghappy …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Cool piece on Social+Capital's #activist investing approach to create  social impact - thanks for sharing! http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2012-07-26/social-plus-capital-the-league-of-extraordinarily-rich-gentlemen#p2 …    
    
    
    Marne Levine, head of Policy for Facebook, talks to an older audience at Chautaqua. Top concern (no surprise http://instagr.am/p/Nt_W7Tohlf/     
    
    
    Ammo belts and hand guns confiscated from carryons, seriously Cleveland? http://instagr.am/p/NwWNRMohk2/     
    
    
    28x growth in 6 years? What do you think, realistic for #gamification?http://www.engineyard.com/infographics/gamification … @JoshFolk @davidzfang    
    
    
    @sheikhandbake Just check out some of the groups I follow on Twitter, I find many of them to be useful sources on tech and social...    
    
    
    "because we didn't know it was impossible, we went out and did it" - awesome insight from Scott Sherman at #startingbloc    
    
    
    Great quote at #startingbloc design thinking training http://instagr.am/p/N4fZ9zohvp/     
    
    
    "How do I do so much? For every action I aim to produce at least 2 positive results." Insight from Hatchery's Yao at #StartingBloc summit    
    
    
    Building a better Buffalo, so many neat ideas and pitches shared at #SBNY12, from block parties to bio incubators    
    
    
    Writing down our personal commitments and sparking all sorts of dialogue at SBNY12 http://instagr.am/p/N9brnvohkr/     
    
    
    "What can we do to help startups grow, and build loyalty among nascent companies?"- American Airlines did that with Groupon #SBNY12    
    
    
    @EmilyShroder great quote! @Zen_Moments: I am not young enough to know everything. ~ Oscar Wilde    
    
    
    My favorite thing about #sbny12: every person here is uniquely, boldly at the center of his/her story and each are creating amazing progress    
    
    
    Awesome #SBNY12  speaker from Purpose, "we need leadership that is not about the hero but the host" - dialogue and cohesion are key to scale    
    
    
    @weggers Interesting framework of the New Economy from Purpose http://instagr.am/p/N_YUthohnp/     
    
    
    @mitgc_cm well said! #SBNY12: Intuitive mind is a sacred gift; rational mind is a faithful servant. http://bit.ly/OPgBRS     
    
    
    Fun launch party with Starting Blockers! #sbny12 http://instagr.am/p/OAAeFvohg6/     
    
    
    Commitments among #StartingBloc Fellows spark all kinds of conversation http://instagr.am/p/N9brnvohkr/     
    
    
    Team Optimus Prime - awesome individuals work (and win!) with at #SBNY12 :) http://instagr.am/p/OEVwLTIhmv/     
    
    
    StartingBloc NY '12 Recap! http://sfy.co/h1cC  #storify #sbny12 #socent    
    
    
    @nyvarch @katejloose @sjw @mitgc_cm @BobbyHertz You've been quoted in my #Storify story "StartingBloc NY '12 Recap!" http://sfy.co/h1cC     
    
    
    @badboyboyce @Montero @alexandracholi You've been quoted in my #Storify story "StartingBloc NY '12 Recap!" http://sfy.co/h1cC     
    
    
    @drobertsenator You've been quoted in my #Storify story "StartingBloc NY '12 Recap!" http://sfy.co/h1cC     
    
    
    @sjw Glad you enjoyed it!    
    
    
    @joncoffey Hah. You may be right on the #nerdalert; #sorrynotsorry - ps great to see you and the Hoya crew this weekend!    
    
    
    Cost of #HigherEd rose at triple rate of inflation since 1983, now student debt=$1t --> makes cheap #EdTech look nice! http://www.economist.com/node/21559936?fsrc=scn/fb/wl/pe/collegecostcalamity …    
    
    
    @alexandracholi @startingbloc thanks, I love using #Storify!    
    
    
    @mitgc_cm Thanks! Glad you found it useful! Thanks do much for all the insights you captured from the sessions!    
    
    
    Fascinating. What your internet activity says about your mental health: http://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=what-internet-habits-say-about-mental-health …    
    
    
    @wdeggers @roonooc @howardhyeung  This site offers great research on #socents - they bring £8.4b/year to the UK economy http://tsrc.ac.uk/Research/SocialEnterprise/tabid/510/Default.aspx …    
    
    
    The biggest predictor of corporate #failure? When success sparks "the undisciplined pursuit of more" http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2012/08/the_disciplined_pursuit_of_less.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+harvardbusiness+%28HBR.org%29 …    
    
    
    Why can't every Consumer be a #Changemaker? 3 all-star innovators swap stories at #SXSW 2013! @kiva @kaggle @avego http://panelpicker.sxsw.com/vote/4164     
    
    
    Wow. People tweet more in Jakarta than Tokyo, London, or NYC! LA has the most top-followed users, no surprise there http://www.theatlanticcities.com/arts-and-lifestyle/2012/08/world-cities-tweet-most/2944/ …    
    
    
    Neat to see what @Uber ride data says about the schedule a city, and its neighborhoods, keep @gokateshoot http://www.theatlanticcities.com/commute/2012/08/using-uber-ridership-data-compare-cities-and-neighborhoods/2890/ …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg I want to use @airbnb to rent a treehouse, how awesome would that be??    
    
    
    Will be cool to watch how ideas catch fire! RT @dannieves: #Analytics Bring Transparency To How Research Spreads http://tcrn.ch/S5mSM3     
    
    
    @vferragut Agreed! Smiles outlast styles (cheesy, but couldn't resist!) Seen OECD's Better Life Index? http://www.oecdbetterlifeindex.org/     
    
    
    This piece on microbiomes hits close to home: http://www.economist.com/node/21560523  Certain mixes of internal bacteria linked to autoimmune diseases #Celiac    
    
    
    Fun girls night at advanced screening of #foragoodtimecall - very funny. More like Lauren (at times a little too practical :) )! #giltcity    
    
    
    Half in US have a chronic health condition. Now they can swap tips and support on social networks built just for them http://ow.ly/dbA2Q     
    
    
    Wow. #Singles are the fastest growing global demographic, 20% up by 2020. Trend spans all regions, a cause for concern? http://www.economist.com/node/21560844?fsrc=scn/fb/wl/pe/attractionofsolitude …    
    
    
    Delish treats at @madcap @eventstir coffee & cocktails event! So fun! http://instagr.am/p/OupbB8ohht/     
    
    
    Coffee infused cocktails and choco hazelnut macaroons - its what's for dinner! @madcap @eventstir http://instagr.am/p/Ous4j6Ihk6/     
    
    
    Sim City, anyone? Getting reacquainted with the game, and tons I don't know at Smithsonian. Great for anyone http://instagr.am/p/Ow2c5BohtN/     
    
    
    Mine too! @milouness: Valuing clarity over chaos may be flawed if reality is more swirl than stasis. But my brain prefers the former    
    
    
    @milouness perhaps a more chaotic moment that one of clarity? Regardless, I appreciate the insight, and agree (assuming I understand ;) )    
    
    
    What a plunge RT @bloombergnews: Samsung loses $12 billion in market value after Apple patent trial verdict | http://bloom.bg/PmjkAe     
    
    
    Wow. When a calorie is less than a calorie - whole grains and nuts vs. processed foods #nutrition @sciam http://bit.ly/QmGsCX     
    
    
    What's next in health? A few Boston-based startups share novel ideas,supported by @Rock_Health CC @mbgrinberg @wdeggers http://www.xconomy.com/boston/2012/08/27/9-takeaways-from-rock-boston-demo-day-health-it-firms-up/ …    
    
    
    Even with the gender wage gap remaining a nagging issue in the US, women control $14 Trillion in assets - nothing to scoff at! via @CfWBR    
    
    
    Question: are there more or less rats living in #DC than people? After the rat revival I just witnessed, I'm leaning towards rats.    
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell I know the feeling! There's something instantly replenishing about seeing open water. Enjoy it!    
    
    
    @annafru Spaniard Lopez v. Olympic gold medalist Murray - neck and neck so far! http://instagr.am/p/PCsDe8IhuL/     
    
    
    One talented monkey! http://instagr.am/p/PHroW3ohva/     
    
    
    How does US #Debt compare to the rest of the world? The Economist's Global Debt Clock, nice #vis @wdeggers @DanielByler http://www.economist.com/content/global_debt_clock?fsrc=scn/tw/te/bl/globaldebtclock …    
    
    
    @fastcoexist Seen @EGGERS_LAW & #826?All about this! @826DC RT:To Raise Creative Kids, Let Them Make Their Own Stories http://bit.ly/Sgtf0n     
    
    
    @joncoffey Friday tip for laughs: Have you seen @KimJongNumberUn? Totally your sense of humor, no?    
    
    
    @joncoffey Clearly. Given that you are always serious. All. The. Time. Right?    
    
    
    Can't wait to read, er, "visually digest" this new Info Graphics book. How do we consume data #vis? #NeedNewVocab http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2012/05/01/information-graphics-taschen/ …    
    
    
    @joncoffey Man, this man knows his memes. Emoticons? So passe.    
    
    
    @elleGHAP Will do. Was up last weekend for the #USOpen (Murray was awesome!) and planning to be back mid-October. Will let you know!    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg: Give yourself some cred, you helped make this #competitiveness  piece on #talent pop! Great stuff http://ow.ly/dASEs     
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Ditto. Always a treat, especially when we all start the week with laughs over indulgent desserts. Just because. The best!    
    
    
    @howardhyeung what about "chocolate beer"? Even better??    
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell Have you read "Let the Great World Spin?" Reading it now, exquisitely written.    
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell The rec fits w/ 9/11:stories coalesce around a '74 tightrope walker btwn the World Trade Center bldgs http://www.nytimes.com/2009/08/02/books/review/Mahler-t.html?pagewanted=all …    
    
    
    Jim Moffatt, CEO of @Deloitte Consulting's leadership advice to #Hoyas: be authentic! http://instagr.am/p/Pf964pIho-/     
    
    
    A game app that funds entrepreneurs with microloans? I like it @mintigal! #TheSeeds http://www.fastcoexist.com/1680519/seeds-a-microlending-game-where-farmville-meets-kiva …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg interesting piece, he makes a good point on why/how #tech geeks can weigh into #policymaking http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2012/09/geeks-are-from-mars-wonks-are-from-venus/ …    
    
    
    HBR said it, not me: Data Science is sexy. Ranks it sexiest job of the 21st century :) http://hbr.org/2012/10/data-scientist-the-sexiest-job-of-the-21st-century/ar/1 …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Lots of cool stuff! The World in 2112 Workshops http://flpbd.it/FPlVo     
    
    
    Curious what comes out of this Equal Futures #Apps Contest to empower #Women & Girls: http://EqualFutures.Challenge.gov  #womenlead    
    
    
    Wish I could go to this awesome DC art fest, where @bitsofanna is highlighting the emerging artists via #socialmedia! http://www.emergeartfair.com/visitor-info/     
    
    
    @bitsofanna I'll be in Chicago, otherwise I'd definitely check out @emergeartfair! Should be neat!    
    
    
    Enjoyed the #visualization training by @GA today! Great tips on how to view #Twitter and #Election data different ways http://generalassemb.ly/education/     
    
    
    @826DC I liked your #infographic! Fancy! Makes a good case for kids boosting their creative writing chops http://826dc.org/?p=2698     
    
    
    Are patents a new asset class? CC: @DanielByler @NGruen1 http://dealbook.nytimes.com/2012/09/24/with-smartphone-deals-patents-become-a-new-asset-class/?partner=rss&emc=rss …    
    
    
    How does a 9 yr old's food blog change school lunch menus? Great #Ted talk on opensource gov @wdeggers @mbgrinberg http://www.ted.com/talks/clay_shirky_how_the_internet_will_one_day_transform_government.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+TEDTalks_video+(TEDTalks+Main+(SD)+-+Site …)    
    
    
    "#Transparency is open in only 1 direction. A dashboard W/O a steering wheel was never the core promise of #democracy" http://www.ted.com/talks/clay_shirky_how_the_internet_will_one_day_transform_government.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+TEDTalks_video+(TEDTalks+Main+(SD)+-+Site …)    
    
    
    Found this helpful: 20 tools to generate & manage passwords: http://www.hongkiat.com/blog/password-tools/ …    
    
    
    Is #startup the new #hipster? Funny contrast http://fosslien.com/startup/     
    
    
    #TEDxGU what does #power look like now? Moises Naim argues power is decaying for big inst. and rising at the grassroots http://www.georgetown.edu/webcast/tedx-2012.html …    
    
    
    More than 1/2 the world's population now lives in a democracy - very different from decades ago #TEDxGU
http://www.georgetown.edu/webcast/tedx-2012.html …    
    
    
    Derek Brown takes an unexpected look at alcohol & humanity, and the "drunken monkey hypothesis"  #TEDxGU Streaming now: http://tedxgeorgetown.com/speakers.html     
    
    
    @mbgrinberg What does #sequestration do to the #defense budget and DoD #jobs? #Infographic http://www.powelltate.com/insights/infographic_the_potential_impact_of_sequestration_on_defense_spending/ …    
    
    
    Optimus Prime reunites in Chicago!! #StartingBloc #sbny12 http://instagr.am/p/Qapho1ohjb/     
    
    
    The Plant, awesome hydroponic, urban garden in Chicago. Great find @bobbyhertz ! http://instagr.am/p/QdMDirIhsT/     
    
    
    Hearing about #biodiversity at #sbchi12 There are thousands of edible species, yet most calories come from : corn, rice & wheat    
    
    
    "a diverse system is a robust system." lack of crop diversity heightens vulnerability to massive crop wipeouts from disease #sbchi12    
    
    
    We've lost 90% of crop variety for apples. Enter Dave Snyder's Chi orchard for rare fruit. Sounds delicious! #sbchi12 pic.twitter.com/W9l0Q0MQ    
    
    
    "You can't plant a seed without the right  fertile conditions. People, partners are part of those conditions" Dave Snyder #sbchi12    
    
    
    "Planting an apple seed won't work. Every apple or grape in mainstream sources here comes from grafted trees." #sbchi12    
    
    
    "we didn't know we'd make a book, but we started w/ the question: how can design transform teaching an learning" #sbchi12    
    
    
    "we're concerned about ecology of learning.We believe in T shaped ppl - breadth of awareness, but a depth of knowledge too"@cannon #sbchi12    
    
    
    Great workshop from #designforamerica: "we want the simplest solutions, smallest changes to yield impacts" #sbchi12    
    
    
    @designforamerica "now a school uses 42% less water at lunch by getting kids to clear dishes and put them on a dish rack" #sbchi12    
    
    
    Our generation is one of creative activists NOT waiting to change the world #sbchi12 #designforamerica    
    
    
    Taking in an epic sunset over Chicago with fellow StartingBloc-er @MattLDuffy #sbchi12 http://instagr.am/p/Qf7lwJohiF/     
    
    
    #StartingBloc field trip to The Boring Store, aka mustachio fest! @826CHI #sbchi12 pic.twitter.com/rDh5MRPT    
    
    
    Loved when @design4america taught us to understand-create-implement w design thinking @CannonDesign for #sbc http://instagr.am/p/QkMofGIhob/     
    
    
    #StartingBloc Takes Chicago! Full recapfrom 1 fun, productive weekend! http://sfy.co/b9q4  #storify #sbchi12 #startingbloc    
    
    
    @BobbyHertz @NilsJK @kbierce @Schumenu You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#StartingBloc Takes Chicago!" http://sfy.co/b9q4     
    
    
    @Montero @TheThirdTeacher @LegacyMovement1 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#StartingBloc Takes Chicago!" http://sfy.co/b9q4     
    
    
    @designforamerica @CannonDesign @design4america You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#StartingBloc Takes Chicago!" http://sfy.co/b9q4     
    
    
    @wdeggers @howardhyeung @mbgrinberg @roonooc @DanNieves @RobHamHam @chinchilla3000 #StartingBloc weekend! #sbchi12 http://storify.com/Schumenu/startingbloc-takes-chicago …    
    
    
    Thanks @mbgrinberg! RT: Read up on how @Schumenu took #Chicago by storm w her @StartingBloc fellows. Fantastic #storify http://storify.com/Schumenu/startingbloc-takes-chicago …    
    
    
    @melaniekahl Thanks! #Designthinking workshop was awesome. I'll use playdough & "bodystorming" more often when I design! @CannonDesign    
    
    
    @roonooc Wow, how was the Bill Clinton speech? What did he talk about? Can't wait to heard about it!    
    
    
    How do we use #maps, then v. now? Fun #infographic & report on The Power of Zoom! Great work @nesdiazuda @joeleinbach!  http://www.deloitte.com/assets/Dcom-UnitedStates/Local%20Assets/Documents/Federal/us_fed_govlab_powerofzoom_localintel_infographics_100512.pdf …    
    
    
    @joncoffey showing off your "power of zoom" mad mapping skillz? I assume you aren't in DC...    
    
    
    @adamspence loved your livetweeting from #socap - definitely made it easier to follow all the great conversation on #impinv!    
    
    
    @Montero @Wim_Bollen You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @tonyklai @bekurtz @CannonDesign @BluePlanetNet You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    SOCAP12: All About the Impact http://sfy.co/a9ve  #storify #socap12 #impinv    
    
    
    @JoshMoskowitz @urbanthinkers @george_manju You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @LawForChange @sharedimpact @socialVCs You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @Silvabee @socialfinance @GlobalEnvision You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @farmerline @elizlk @magnetofgood @uncompromise You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @HUB_Boulder @theminimalina @rebeccaapeel You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @demvalue @Alliancemag @PublicMediaX You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @Samhallsentrepr You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @InvestedD @SOCAPlive @GlobeIn_World You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @HandsOnTechATL @ImpactInSight @InvestorsCircle You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @SauderISIS @CapInstitute @Nextgenvestor You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @socapmarkets You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @BartSkorupa @bjornfalkevik @wdephillips You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @honeybeecap @resilience @alongsworth You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @ABLImpact @BlendedValue @narinderdhami You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @karapecknold You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @vicvrana @arjanschutte @TheOpenLabel You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @IAimpactassets @microplace @briandhardwick You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @wefunder @kiva @adamspence @joreynolds You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @robreich @omidyarnetwork @GrameenFdn You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @jimkucher @nff_news @BCorporation @razoo You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @FoodShift @villagecapital @goldieblox You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @SugharWomen @apps4africa @indigotrust You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @codeforamerica @AKF_USA @gaffta @Aurelio_Lamb You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @MarketsForGood @TechSoup @sheila_warren You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @kristingilliss @Joyzhang8 @CKent_7 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @RubyCup @newmediaventure @pointsoflight You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @SFGate @Oxfam @Ashoka You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @nesstorg @LGTVP @BeUnreasonable @HubVentures You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @SustainBrands @fenixintl @PeterJGlenn You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @conches @lfrankli @lauratomasko You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @AuntBertha @RobHamHam You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @StartingBloc @WHC_SA @indiegogo @whatsupsmiley You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @AhernKate @brattray @soujoyce @j0nathanjenkins You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @GovLab @gatesfoundation You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @Persistance @Kevindoylejones @RockefellerFdn You've been quoted in my #Storify story "SOCAP12: All About the Impact" http://sfy.co/a9ve     
    
    
    @chinchilla3000 @mbgrinberg @DanNieves Looking for recap of #SOCAP12? New Gates platform launched, new stats on #impinv http://storify.com/Schumenu/socap12-all-about-the-impact …    
    
    
    @SOCAPmarkets No, thank YOU for convening so many dynamic changemakers - lots of great insights and inspiring stories out of #SOCAP12!    
    
    
    Thanks @Ivy_So! You are too! RT #FF - A few of the pioneers of innovation at @Deloitte: @howardhyeung @Schumenu @mattjhaigh”    
    
    
    @Ivy_So @howardhyeung when I was pulling together this recap of #SOCAP I was impressed w the strong Canadian showing! http://storify.com/Schumenu/socap12-all-about-the-impact?utm_source=embed_header …    
    
    
    @goldieblox Thanks! Excited by what you are doing. Cool to see a fellow @StartingBloc fellow doing awesome things!    
    
    
    @vicvrana glad you enjoyed it! @jeffraikes gave an intriguing intro to @marketsforgood, didn't he? Excited to see what happens!    
    
    
    @mitgc_cm thanks for sharing the @StartingBloc love! Hope all's well with everything you're doing.    
    
    
    @Nextgenvestor thanks! Glad you enjoyed it!    
    
    
    1 min it's a throwdown debate, gloves are off.  Next min: who can be more empathetic about troops in Benghazi? #youtubepolitics    
    
    
    Interesting health fact RT @Slate: Why do doctors tell women to drink less than men? EXPLAINED: http://slate.me/RCGUNy     
    
    
    "Network failure": a new form of market failure? @shrupti @roonooc http://econ.st/RBXRYp     
    
    
    Cool! RT @Montero: 4.0 #Schools Named a Coolest #EdTech Incubator in the Country http://siliconbayounews.com/2012/10/16/4-0-schools-named-one-of-the-coolest-ed-tech-incubators-across-the-country/ … via @siliconbayou #edu #tech #cities    
    
    
    Just decided what sessions I want to attend at #DCWeek - so many awesome techie events to choose from! http://digitalcapitalweek.org/dcweek-2012-the-one-post-you-need-to-read/ …    
    
    
    Just when you thought robots couldn't be more awesome, one starts dancing to #Gangnamstyle...http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=kmeJvkN4ntI# …!    
    
    
    A social experiment on a global level: The Human Face of Big Data @wdeggers @mbgrinberg http://www.guardian.co.uk/news/datablog/2012/oct/02/human-face-of-big-data-smartphone-app-launch …    
    
    
    Woah. Ben & Jerry's becomes a #BCorp! What other big companies will follow suit? @howardhyeung @Montero @Ivy_So #socent http://www.fastcoexist.com/1680771/ben-and-jerry-s-becomes-a-b-corporation …    
    
    
    @Montero @howardhyeung @Ivy_So Yes, @benandjerrys is also unique as a #BCorp since it's a subsidiary of publicly traded company @Unilever    
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell Yes, very cool! Interested to see how that shapes @benandjerrys! CC: @Montero @howardhyeung @Ivy_So    
    
    
    Fun to see Seth Goldman of Honest Tea, a fellow Bethesdan, kick off #NetImpact12!    
    
    
    Neat that MD tracks 26 metrics of progress: volunteerism, crime rates, graduation rates #NetImpact12    
    
    
    Keynote on unique partners #NetImpact12: CEO of @Recyclebank and WM Exec:added 63 addtl cities in past yr thanks to partnership @wdeggers    
    
    
    Single stream recycling has increased recycling 50% where WM has introduced it #NetImpact12    
    
    
    On July S.C Johnson and @Recyclebank  co-launched 50 state recycling challenge, big boost in recycling rates @wdeggers #NetImpact12    
    
    
    Now at #NetImpact12: short video on the DEKA  Slingshot water filter pilot CocaCola sponsored in Ghana, now scaling via kiosks @wdeggers    
    
    
    Fresh tea at scale through innovation, w a machine brewing ~500k bottles/day, keeping @HonestTea fair trade inputs #NetImpact12    
    
    
    @marcgunther you read our minds! Curious what Coke will say about health issues of soda consumption #NI12    
    
    
    "Is the obesity rate a risk to your sales of sugared beverages?" to Coke: "soda is the flatter side; tea is our fast growing segment" #NI12    
    
    
    "stand up if you think the healthcare system is currently attuned to the impact of place on health." No 1 stood up #NI12    
    
    
    It's not enough to talk healthy food. Q: How can we build inclusiveness in the food system, food equity? #NI12    
    
    
    A: one solution - let food stamps function at farmer's mkts #ni12    
    
    
    25% of elementary schools in the US don't have recess #NI12    
    
    
    David Griswold at #BCorp breakout: a single cert doesn't hit all aspects of CSR - they use organic, Rainforest Alliance +own metrics #ni12    
    
    
    #BLab cofounder Kassoy: there are 100s of product social resp certifications out there, none that looked at the company integrity. #NI12    
    
    
    Kassoy: We are not an activist playing gotcha, we want to help companies improve if they are floundering, but in cases revoke a cert #NI12    
    
    
    Beth Shiroishi of AT&T: "Our 'Do One Thing' mission: Choose it. Do it. Share it. And if you really love it - lead it" #NI12    
    
    
    Marilee McInnis of @Southwest: We engage employees to save $5/day, like not switching 'no smoking' lights, branded trash bags #NI12    
    
    
    Evan Hochberg of Deloitte at #NI12: we changed our pro bono support to incent fully committed work; Partners get revenue credit for pro bono    
    
    
    #ni12 Beth of AT&T: You can't win over all the cynics, even internally. Important to listen, but they can't steer the ship"    
    
    
    #ni12 Beth if AT&T: Millennials don't demand more volunteering that boomers, they talk about it and bring those expectations to work    
    
    
    Carol Cone at #NI12: What are the attributes of trust? @edelman i.d'ed 16. Table stakes for companies to connect w consumers    
    
    
    UPS was largest IPO in 20th century + acquired 40 companies. CFO Kurt Kuehn on "organizational judo" of working on sustainability. #NI12    
    
    
    "Internal, quiet revolutionaries" helped current UPS CFO sync consumer choices via tools like carbon calculator for the environment #NI12    
    
    
    UPS helps CARE manage its supply chain for disaster relief, unlike sep indep efforts post-Haiti crisis that got stuck in bottlenecks #NI12    
    
    
    In 20th century, life expectancy went from 45 yrs to 80 years, half attributed to new meds thru pharma - J &J    
    
    
    J&J now in partnership w TB Alliance to deliver the first multi-track TB vaccine in 50 yrs. #NI12    
    
    
    Expensive dev! It takes 5k-10k variations to yield one vaccine, avg of $4b to develop new vaccine. 1 or 2 in 10 breaks even #NI12    
    
    
    Kurt of UPS: Sustainability, to be operationally sustainable, can't reside w one leader. Lead from behind, listen to employee's push #NI12    
    
    
    J&J exec: Sustainability can't be limited to the supply chain/operations ppl in a company, business advocates needed throughout #NI12    
    
    
    Lisa Manley of Edelman on their trust index: trust in government and business  are at an all time low #NI12    
    
    
    Manley of Edelman: 1-way communication won't suffice for consumers to trust. CEO not most impactful, they value employee views more #NI12    
    
    
    Anna Kearney in Trust of Era of Distrust at #NI12: for us trust is a peer conversation since @BNYMellon is a B2B    
    
    
    Jim Turner of Humana: company was losing consumers so they asked, "what does perfect service look like to consumers?" #NI12    
    
    
    Answer: Factors like accurate, courteous, personalized, proactive care matter #NI12    
    
    
    World Wildlife Fund identified 19 areas critical for wildlife preservation, like Yangtze or Amazon #NI12    
    
    
    Just a few companies control 70% of global trade that passes through critical environs. WWF works w them to I.D opps for shared value #NI12    
    
    
    When brainstorming a good message get to the true benefit. Keep asking, " the benefit of the benefit is the what?" #NI12    
    
    
    Opposite of progress: U.S men 25-34 are less likely than their fathers to have a college degree... http://www.economist.com/node/21564418     
    
    
    Singapore's vertical #garden breaks the trade-off of #urbanag convenience and commercial-scale harvest HT @vzinsou http://inhabitat.com/the-worlds-first-commercial-vertical-farm-opens-in-singapore/ …    
    
    
    Love this quote: "The day before something is a breakthrough, it's a crazy idea" -king of crazy ideas Diamandis    
    
    
    @JigarShahDC great contributions to the #NI12 summit! Enjoyed the informal Q&A post-breakout    
    
    
    See any fun #Halloween costumes on pets? Evidently a good coping option for empty nesters w kids in college. Like $370m this season good    
    
    
    Well here's 1 approach to partisanship on the Hill :) http://instagr.am/p/Rfd3gWohvT/     
    
    
    Poses interesting questions, good find @nikitatmitchell: Your Employee Is an Online Celebrity. Now What Do You Do? http://on.wsj.com/RYAgOG     
    
    
    Enjoying looking back on great ideas exchanged during our #socent sesh at #NI12 @roonooc & @Shrupti - that was fun! pic.twitter.com/TN6GVTMl    
    
    
    Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap http://sfy.co/nB7x  #storify #ni12 #water    
    
    
    @SSUCCE @ReachScale @Beunreasonable @Ashoka You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @SouthwestAir @NetImpact You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @Kate4Good @clorox @LesleyLammers @ajlovesya You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @JessyWC @SustainBrands @Cone @PresidioGrad You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @schwild @LisaGreenHall @AvonFoundation @ATT You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @Jennika_1231 @TimMohinAMD You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @bizinovationist @klugesan @LambOntheRocks You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @DowCorningCSR @ChrisCarmody @ColumbusCTC You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @JigarShahDC @Montero @roonooc @cocacola You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @3MNews @melissamistero You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @UPS @3MCareers @KylaGruen @patrickhermann You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @asheen @hermanmiller @wpresourcefla You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @lodon11 @chinthoughts @MissionMeasure You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @Recyclebank You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @CEP_Rachel @peerinsight @EllenEileen You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @jessalynish @ecodevo1 @tennajepsen You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @ellierogerz @Lia_Bia @hitendraPatel You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @lizmaw @alexapitoulis @HilaryKilgour You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @BrenNetImpact You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @AMLazareff @kbierce @smilbergs @FastCoExist You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @coolmindee @gibbulloch You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @WEF @britttnnaayy @Charm_CityCakes @brenucsb You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @Southwest @edelman You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @toilethackers @nsansatweets @melissabethhall You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @imlwilliams @clairelives @GSVC @AnneWallin You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @theoathproject @ch2mhill @carrwest @seemz00 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @Ecolab_Inc @lauraclise You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
        
    
    
    @DawnShiang @CocaColaCo @Water_Match You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap http://sfy.co/nB7x  #storify #ni12 #water    
    
    
    @do_good_jobs @kaboom @Pnhegde You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @mkngood @devaujla @echoinggreen You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @catapult_design You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @IronShawna @beverlyschwartz @davidpurdie You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @_ramon78 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @WadeKeech @SCJ @WM @intesacom @CoreyLanders You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @hultprize @ilyesel @fsg @Tod_Arbogast You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @neilchawkins @CliffGMJ @askashkar You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @oikosPenn @ilkitaG @MeghanMColeman @yasmin_a You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @JillyBadanes @amaryl1ia @elliebuechner You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap http://sfy.co/nB7x  #storify #ni12 #water    
    
    
    @TrueImpact @bencirillo @TanyaSpencer38 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @WellsBringHope @DBNess @dogfishbeer You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Net Impact '12 Baltimore Recap" http://sfy.co/nB7x     
    
    
    @wdeggers I know next year you'll be at #NetImpact, but in the meantime here's a recap from #NI12! http://storify.com/Schumenu/net-impact-12-descends-on-baltimore …    
    
    
    @montero Thanks! Too bad we didn't cross paths at #NI12!    
    
    
    @nikitatmitchell Thanks! Can't wait to see you again - let's make it soon!    
    
    
    The Economist: "both men have it in them to be their better selves; but the sad fact is neither candidate campaigned as if that's the plan"    
    
    
    @drbelotto thanks for a blast from the past! Hope you had fun last night!    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Great @kaggle piece, thanks for sharing! Didn't realize some of their #competitions are invite-only    
    
    
    @joncoffey for some gluten free mixes, that's how it tastes unfortunately :( - but now there's some better options since so many are gf now!    
    
    
    Nothing like breathtaking time lapses of falling glaciers to highlight #climatechange. A Sundance must-see on my list: http://www.chasingice.com/     
    
    
    @JoshFolk @davidzfang look forward to seeing you at the #DCWeek keynote tonight!    
    
    
    Awesome RT @TechCrunch: Airbnb Partners With http://NYC.gov  To Provide Free Housing For Hurricane Sandy Victims http://tcrn.ch/Ux4Xu8     
    
    
    @corbett3000 #DCweek keynote  kicks off! http://instagr.am/p/Rv36Mdohtr/     
    
    
    Mayor Vince Gray is talking about everything he's doing to amp up tech in DC,  eg 5 yr tax abatement for tech startups +enticing VCs #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Vince Gray: jobs in DC tech center grew 4% last year, goal to grow it more. USAToday ranked it 3rd best city for tech startups #DCWEEK    
    
    
    "#Gaming isn't something that you do, it's something that you are" #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Travis of @Uber_DC talking awesomeness about crazy logistics of getting a town car in 5 min via real time heatmaps pic.twitter.com/YG8AW2GR    
    
    
    Girl Effect creator: "when you are talking about a deep systemic issue (like the girl funding gap), you need to talk to everyone!" #DCWEEK    
    
    
    How to get ppl who don't think "girls" are their issue interested? "Invest in a girl, everyone wins. Best investment NO 1 is making #DCWEEK    
    
    
    @JasonBilog me too! Headed to the @OPower after party in a few?    
    
    
    @JasonBilog sounds good!    
    
    
    would you "bedshare" at a hotel? Sketchy? @rmchase forbade others at @zipcar from calling it carsharing. Weird & unfamiliar term #DCWEEK    
    
    
    @rmchase: @zipcar:industrial:: @buzzcar: peer-to-peer. Peers are less consistent (need ratings), but innovation of e/user iterating #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Truth. @Noahkunin: we aren't wed to institutions in how we give, we put our money, as citizens, where the solutions are #DCWEEK    
    
    
    @Noahkunin: the transit subsidy app we helped w/ (via CFPB) is an example of transferable solutions via an API. GitHub enables this #DCWEEK    
    
    
    @noahkunin: we are uniquely positioned to bend the steel pipe of feedback loops to see complaints via CFPB + how theyre shared w us #DCWEEK    
    
    
    At CFPB they have UX gurus in house see where users defect on site, where they fall off, so they can change how they adapt support #DCWEEK    
    
    
    With disasters like #sandy people aren't waiting for institutions to ask how to help, they just do it. Using their own networks #DCWeek    
    
    
    Steve of @Spacex: we built in failures, made low cost rockets at first so that if it failed hadn't blown all $100m startup funds #DCWEEK    
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/RyQMYjIhtq/     
    
    
    Next up: by 2015 Spacex to get humans into orbital space, contracted by NASA, $20m/seat instead of now: we pay $65m/seat to Russia #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Right now Orbital, Boeing, Spacex are IT for orbital space travel in US! #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Steve Davis: We build 92% of our parts in house, it keeps costs down #DCWEEK    
    
    
    Steve Davis: we ( @Spacex) are hiring about an engineer a day currently #DCWeek cc: @wdeggers    
    
    
    Steve Davis: In next 5 yrs, I'm most excited or Falcon Heavy, w 27x the engines as Falcon! Biggest since Saturn 5 @SpaceX #DCWEEK    
    
    
    @Spacex Steve: All the $$ NASA gives us is performance based; if we don't perform: $0    
    
    
    @chrisheuer hey, are you at the @TechCocktail event for #DCWeek? I'm here w/ Deloitters!    
    
    
    @mikejsiegel great to meet you too, see you tomorrow!    
    
    
    @chrisheuer enjoy Mexico City, @techcocktail was a fun end to a full day!    
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing @GoKateShoot's film & stills at tonight's #DCWeek closing party with @achoueiki and @PWLovejoy!    
    
    
    #DCWeek closing party - eclectic art, Shake Shack pumpkin custard, and loud pop mashups oh my! http://instagr.am/p/R2bC_8ohh8/     
    
    
    When tech companies and state govs are on the same side of the fence @wdeggers http://m.fastcompany.com/?m=fastcompany/node/3001748&url=http://www.fastcompany.com/3001748/amazon-has-friend-state-governors-and-other-allies-tech?utm_source=twitter …    
    
    
    So impressed by these kids competing with their Lego robots at the #FIRST competition! http://instagr.am/p/R3C9bnIhm9/     
    
    
    I think it's official. I have a complete magazine addiction. http://instagr.am/p/R5cgovohnZ/     
    
    
    @drajwfu How was #rebootamerica on Friday? I didn't join that part of #DCWeek    
    
    
    Love that frugal #innovation in action :) RT @mbgrinberg: $20 Indian tablet could blindside industry, educate billions http://flpbd.it/2hebV     
    
    
    @osanderson I think gov succeeds at the carrot-not-stick approach where consumer options are rich but tough to compare, e.g health & finance    
    
    
    Will we see more city-run new media hubs like the Brooklyn-based "Made in NY" Media Center? http://buildingstoryworlds.tumblr.com/post/33404107843 …    
    
    
    @osanderson Exactly. That's why there's a need to curate the smart choices. Re/ participation, reputation-boosting incentives don't hurt :)    
    
    
    @drajwfu Cool. See you at a future Sandbox event!    
    
    
    Denise Rollins of @USAID quoting Shah: "talent is everywhere, opportunity is not" - tapping that talent for social impact #impinv #socent    
    
    
    Most architectural use of acorns and twigs I know of! http://instagr.am/p/SJQ5NsIhs1/     
    
    
    So who really creates the jobs? Unless you answered "gazelles", may be surprised by findings in this @Inc piece http://www.inc.com/magazine/201209/bo-burlingham/who-really-creates-the-jobs.html …    
    
    
    Curious what top schools graduate the most lucrative #entrepreneurs? This #infographic lays it out https://s3.amazonaws.com/infographics/The-University-Entrepreneurship-800.jpg …    
    
    
    Finally Social Enterprise Census and @ImpactInSight bring us some real data on #SocEnt in the US! @wdeggers @Ivy_So http://www.huffingtonpost.com/ben-thornley/social-enterprise_b_2090144.html …    
    
    
    Good food for thought on learning to love volatility from @nntaleb @WSJ HT: @milouness http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324735104578120953311383448.html …    
    
    
    @badboyboyce what's your #winning habit(s)? RT @badboyboyce: "Motivation is what gets you started. Habit is what keeps you going." ~Jim Ryun    
    
    
    What a dusk. What a beauty to share it. http://instagr.am/p/SY7c5oIhie/     
    
    
    @elleGHAP recognize this? Toured the sculpture garden on @Pepsi grounds today. Some beautiful pieces. pic.twitter.com/TfXPc346    
    
    
    @elleghap Unfortunately was just passing through. If you are in DC around the holidays though it would be great to catch up!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @piyaradia! http://instagr.am/p/St6kOlIhuv/     
    
    
    The search is on for a #datascientist to join our small, dynamic team! Know someone who may be a good fit? Let me know! http://careers.deloitte.com/jobs/eng-US/details/j/E12MCLSMGRAW022-CL5/data-scientist-public-sector …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg @RRocketto neat Google event on the role of data scientists in the latest campaign: http://www.meetup.com/Data-Science-DC/events/87687152/ …    
    
    
    @NathanMaton going to the Game developers conference next March? Looks up your alley! http://www.gdconf.com/conference/gamesforchange.html …    
    
    
    Thanks for the RT @joncoffey! RT The search is on for a #datascientist to join our small, dynamic team!  http://careers.deloitte.com/jobs/eng-US/details/j/E12MCLSMGRAW022-CL5/data-scientist-public-sector …    
    
    
    @nikitatmitchell Thanks!!    
    
    
    Great #Storify recap of Obama's Twitter Town Hall from @AlexJamesFitz http://storify.com/mashable/barack-obama-s-fiscal-cliff-twitter-town-hall …    
    
    
    One energizing Tiny Desk Concert over at @NPR by Mackelmore and Ryan Lewis http://www.npr.org/event/music/166256822/macklemore-ryan-lewis-tiny-desk-concert …    
    
    
    @nathanmaton No, but I'll let you know if that changes. Just wasn't sure if that one was already on your list of awesome game conferences!    
    
    
    @joncoffey Def! If Mackelmore comes back to @npr by popular demand, I want IN - ESP if the saxophonist comes too :)    
    
    
    Glad you enjoyed! RT @kbierce: Secret to success anywhere:"Listen to the rhythm of the new place; let it inform your actions."via @Schumenu    
    
    
    @dannieves Neat infographics! The Batman Physics one reminds me of a "flying monkey physics" diagram I did on Wizard of Oz in high school :)    
    
    
    @badboyboyce @jordancooper Yes, but the awesomeness of @factual is more than maps, talk about creative use of BIG data!    
    
    
    @NGruen1 Thought you'd appreciate this #infographic on the high cost of patent wars. http://visual.ly/patent-wars-1     
    
    
    Creative (informative!) uses of the Pinterest platform RT @mediatwit: 5 ways journalists are using Pinterest (Poynter) http://bit.ly/YTDbjR     
    
    
    @GovLab Thanks, I always enjoy it too! RT @GovLab: Special shout out to @Schumenu for being #amazing + helping with #socent #impinv research    
    
    
    Mesmerizing #visualization of how a viral post spreads on @Facebook @mbgrinberg @DanNieves @joncoffey @wdeggers https://www.facebookstories.com/stories/2200/     
    
    
    What's intrapreneurship? Join tomorrow's #socint Google #hangout and chat with @Ashoka 10AM EST! CC: @MarzenaZukowska http://ow.ly/g3k6n     
    
    
    @Ashoka Following the livestream of Google #hangout on #socint - hope to hear some unique intrapreneurship experiences. http://www.youtube.com/user/ChangemakersNet/featured?v=_CDjG2edYog …    
    
    
    @changemakers Agree w the woman from @PepsiCo jam that articulating the biz case for  #socint in a company is key. Tips on how to do this?    
    
    
    While I love @Economist, this made me laugh! RT @robterrin: Fantastic caricature of @TheEconomist
http://6thfloor.blogs.nytimes.com/2012/12/12/17-things-i-learned-from-reading-every-last-word-of-the-economists-the-world-in-2013-issue/?smid=tw-share … #PartySmallTalk    
    
    
    Travellers - @Sitegeist #app helps to get the pulse of where you are via snazzy #infographic! Pretty fun. http://flowingdata.com/2012/12/14/sitegeist-a-mobile-app-that-tells-you-about-your-data-surroundings/ …    
    
    
    @elisabethcramer Thanks! Are you a fan of mindmapping too? We did this one at our #socent workshop at #NI12    
    
    
    @osanderson No problem - you'll be schooling me on #socialmedia tips in no time :)    
    
    
    @antgoldbloom Ditto to @PaulBassat's Congrats -So glad to see you in 30 Under 30- exciting for all us fans of @Kaggle!! http://www.forbes.com/special-report/2012/30-under-30/30-under-30_tech.html …    
    
    
    Yikes. @Forbes enjoyed the #30Under30 lists, but there are a cringe-worthy # of typos. http://www.forbes.com/special-report/2012/30-under-30/30-under-30.html …    
    
    
    What [designs/ideas/data/movements/media] were  most contagious in 2012? Love this recap @DanNieves @mbgrinberg http://www.mostcontagious.com/2012/     
    
    
    @JoshFolk did you already check out this @Deloitte report on #gamification? http://dupress.com/articles/the-engagement-economy-how-gamification-is-reshaping-businesses/ … How's @IdeaScale doing?  :)    
    
    
    Sasha Issenberg of @Slate at #datasciencedc event: the hardest central targeting decision in a campaign is knowing who NOT to talk to    
    
    
    Issenberg: campaign outreach was used to get out the vote, now it persuades and guages who responds to diff modes of contact #datasciencedc    
    
    
    Ken.Strategic Telemetey:my phone's computing power is > what I used for micro targeting for Al Gore campaign. World changed. #datasciencedc    
    
    
    Ken: even more important - and harder-  than I.ding who is persuadable in campaign is knowing what to say to them #datasciencedc    
    
    
    @alexlundry data dir. of Romney campaign shares time series #vis of media spots of campaigns #datasciencedc @weggers pic.twitter.com/0JRFTFPL    
    
    
    Ken: to predict voter turnout, can't rely only on voter history (omits current election feel) or self reported (people lie) #datasciencedc    
    
    
    @jfranks03 Funny RT from @kentonallen. There is some irony about that response to @Instagram, isn't there?    
    
    
    @DataCommunityDC Really enjoyed last night's event on #datascience in the campaigns! Great panelists    
    
    
    @poliroots1 Agreed! Really fascinating insights from @kstrasma on why campaign microtargeting has improved so much since 2006 #dsdcmeetup    
    
    
    Best #opendata from #cities in 2012 by @emilymbadger. SF data revealed that 5% of streets accounts for 55% injuries http://www.theatlanticcities.com/technology/2012/12/best-open-data-releases-2012/4200/ …    
    
    
    What countries are most emotional? Fascinating #geo #datavis, although in Comments some really jump to conclusions  http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2012/11/28/a-color-coded-map-of-the-worlds-most-and-least-emotional-countries/ …    
    
    
    Cool, hadn't seen that!Great work:) RT @joshfolk: @Schumenu did you see how NASA is #crowdsourcing its website redesign?http://fcw.com/articles/2012/12/07/nasa-website-redesign.aspx …    
    
    
    @jfranks03 Haha too true! It's also an outcome of poorly phrased legalese though, which they are understandably rethinking now    
    
    
    Fun Xmas interactive musical greeting from @DeloitteDIGI_UK http://www.deloittedigital.co.uk/christmas-card     
    
    
    "Monotony collapses time; novelty unfolds it" Great counter to "time flies when you have fun" on memory from #walkingwitheinstein #bookrecc    
    
    
    Curious what type of plants you're looking at? Just discovered the #app @Leafsnap with photo recognition of plants! http://leafsnap.com/     
    
    
    Good intro to a number of fantastic (free) social media and trend-tracking tools I use daily on @HarvardBiz IdeaCast: http://blogs.hbr.org/ideacast/2012/12/boost-your-productivity-with-s.html …    
    
    
    The top social innovations to hit the #BOP in 2012 #silverlinings http://www.fastcodesign.com/1671480/10-of-the-years-best-designs-for-social-good#1 …    
    
    
    The most "typical" person of 2012, and how it varies by country. @natgeo offers a composite portrait #demographics http://ow.ly/gpAZi     
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Fascinating! ESP given the newfound role of our microbiomes for health, eg incidence of autoimmune diseases http://www.economist.com/node/21560523     
    
    
    Why vote on #fiscalcliff today when you can be a hero cutting tax hikes tomorrow? Political antics or pure procrastination? Which is worse?    
    
    
    @AMCaccavale yes, political cover if it weren't so transparent. After wks of #fiscalcliff press are Americans so easily fooled? I bet not    
    
    
    @AMCaccavale or at least, as Americans, let's hope not! But enough of political dysfunction. Happy NYE from Capital Hill!!    
    
    
    @chinchilla3000 Ha true.But in reality how we feel 1/1 re #fiscalcliff is prob nbd to them next to impact on all-too-critical voting records    
    
    
    "We see the world as much more coherent (less ambiguous) than it actually is" Kahneman on biases is a good disclaimer for #2013 forecasts    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg what do you think about "how to be nicer?" topping Russia's @google searches of 2012? Lol. HT @AMCaccavale http://qz.com/39672/things-the-world-wants-to-know-how-to-do/ …    
    
    
    @osanderson Thanks for sharing @Joi's view on 2013. Hadn't heard of @littlleBits but I love the concept!    
    
    
    Great quote RT @forbes: For success, attitude is equally as important as ability. -- Harry F. Banks http://bit.ly/Zc7nWA     
    
    
    Planet Money's Adam Davidson breaks down #FiscalCliff in historic context as war btwn two very diff econ philosophies http://www.ted.com/talks/adam_davidson_what_we_learned_from_teetering_on_the_fiscal_cliff.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+TEDTalks_video+%28TEDTalks+Main+%28SD%29+-+Site%29 …    
    
    
    Interesting RT @alexhaseley: Of the total of immigrant-founded companies, 33.2% had #Indian founders @KauffmanFDN http://ow.ly/gASMs     
    
    
    @dannieves There is nothing like a good flan, ESP of the pumpkin variety by @milouness :)    
    
    
    @beth_schill Ditto. Jared Diamond + @NatGeo? This should be good!    
    
    
    Best prevention against Alzheimer's according to Jared Diamond? Being multilingual buys you at least 5 years in old age against it! @natgeo    
    
    
    @JamesKotecki @osanderson I went last year and #CES was cool, if overwhelming. Happy to just tune in to the media covering it this time!    
    
    
    How will @SpaceX try to top the successes of 2012? Carrying people to ISS would do it! http://venturebeat.com/2013/01/09/spacex-ccdev-updates/ …    
    
    
    @DeloitteDIGI_US Fun new campaign! http://drivenby.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Could there be a better time for curious people to be alive than today? The answers within immediate reach are astounding. #TY internet!    
    
    
    Doom and gloom abounds, but what keeps these intellectuals up at night is news to me: http://edge.org/responses/q2013   Still, let's #staypositive #2013    
    
    
    Jon Ronson, on how his "precarious sense of beliefs" helps see through eyes of who he writes about  - even psychopaths http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffbercovici/2013/01/14/lost-at-sea-author-jon-ronson-on-psychopaths-conspiracy-theorists-and-why-introverts-make-the-best-war-reporters/?utm_campaign=forbestwittersf&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social …    
    
    
    If you missed #CES2013 this is a great recap, HT @milouness http://ow.ly/gW6B5     
    
    
    Good tips! RT @will_reynolds: 8 Pub Speaking Lessons from 57 Inaugural Speeches:  Great 4 any orator w a vision- Forbes http://onforb.es/WtTgXy     
    
    
    @AlexHaseley you say “entre-ployee”, I say intrapreneur, @milouness says "rebel at work" - diff language, shared spirit of bold idea sharing    
    
    
    If only human #trafficking in "Taken" were just a fictional plotline. 1/30 Gtown Symposium tackles the very real issue. http://ow.ly/gPgVc     
    
    
    A Business Case for Bedtime? Sounds good to me! http://on.wsj.com/VRPUQ4  via @WSJ    
    
    
    Neat to see suite of  #mgov apps in Brazil for citizens: find wifi hotspots, compare grocery prices, chat w neighbors http://www.passaportecuritiba.org.br/     
    
    
    Curious to see creativity packed into 6s! RT @milouness: Why Experts Think Twitter's 6-Second Videos Could Be Huge http://Wired.com     
    
    
    Design as a Discipline, beyond just thinking about UX, is my fave of the #TechTrends2013 from @MarkAtDeloitte http://www.deloitte.com/view/en_US/us/Services/consulting/technology-consulting/technology-2013/tech-trends-2013-sneak-peek/index.htm …    
    
    
    Nice piece on #gamification @aaron_j_patton @steve @dslunceford! http://dupress.com/articles/the-engagement-economy-how-gamification-is-reshaping-businesses/?id=us:scm:twt:dr11:read:dup:012513 …    
    
    
    Just painting ceiling tiles in blue & green mosaic at work. Normal Friday. http://instagr.am/p/U65Qf8oht1/     
    
    
    Cube of Light. Ai Wei Wei captivates at the Hirschorn. http://instagr.am/p/U9q00FIhpm/     
    
    
    Squandered talent was my biggest pet peeve. Now I see neglected opportunities (more broadly) as grave loss. Can't do all; priorities are key    
    
    
    "Squandered talent" oversimplifies. Raw skills are only part; creativity in applying skill is key to finding & inviting new opportunities    
    
    
    What ignites breakthrough creativity? An Openness to Experience and burning Need for Cognition HT @milouness http://99u.com/tips/7269/Picasso-Kepler-and-the-Benefits-of-Being-an-Expert-Generalist …    
    
    
    @milouness Absolutely, one without the other is incomplete. It's refreshing when someone confirms your own experience in such an elegant way    
    
    
    Don't know what there's more of at this @DataCommunityDC event: data scientists or people hiring them :) #datasciencedc    
    
    
    John Morton, ICE Director: "part of the solution for #humantrafficking is also a solution for immigration reform" #ihts2013    
    
    
    John Morton: 2 wks ago #humantrafficking coalition was discovered in GA where women were on 4 state circuit, $30/30 customers/day #ihts2013    
    
    
    Last year was a record for # ICE arrests under human trafficking (90 arrests) and federal prostitution charges. #ihts2013    
    
    
    John Morton: "we'll do a better job as a law enforcement agency if we take a victim centric approach." #ihts2013    
    
    
    John Morton: T&U visas would encourage illegal immigrants to come forward [I.d #trafficking], to reassure they won't be deported #ihts2013    
    
    
    John Morton (ICE): I don't lose a min of sleep putting someone away for 20 yrs/life who trafficks people, destroying their lives" #ihts2013    
    
    
    Case for comprehensive #immigration reform:"too many in this country have uncertain status, and ppl are preying on vulnerability" #ihts2013    
    
    
    Tony West, Assn. US Attorney General: "in last yr DOJ had 200 cases against human traffickers, a 39% inc, sending unequivocal msg #ihts2013    
    
    
    Tony West: Last yr DOJ paid $5.3m to NGOs providing services to those in recovery from #trafficking, to help rebuild lives #ihts2013    
    
    
    Karima Maloney of DOJ: prosecution is how we have declared trafficking intolerable in the US. #ihts2013    
    
    
    Maggie Wynne of HHS on need for collab w NGOs: they help victims stabilize and build trust. Many not trusting of law enforcement #ihts2013    
    
    
    Rogers: we share goal to eliminate #trafficking but may misunderstand roles. Must see how we augment not compete w e/o's efforts #ihts2013    
    
    
    Karima: we're seeking to take out entire #trafficking networks; these cases are interconnected and we need to connect the dots. #ihts2013    
    
    
    Most of these #trafficking prosecutions begin with tips from NGOs, goal is to open it up more to tips from citizens. #ihts2013    
    
    
    Primary goal is to find victims, not reverse sting to locate victimizers (Swedish model), deemed not efficient in US model #ihts2013    
    
    
    Rogers, FBI: most who are trafficked don't initially see themselves as the victim and us as their savior, we have to earn trust" #ihts2013    
    
    
    palantir and deloitte data and geospatial analytics at work to locate human traffickers! #ihts2013 http://instagr.am/p/VHSYRDIhnW/     
    
    
    @Deloitte's Mike Kim on analytics w Palantir,using tech former PayPal-ers use to catch fraud on traffickers #ihts2013 pic.twitter.com/p2u2Y9uM    
    
    
    UN Goodwill Ambassador & Actress Mira Sorvino on #humantrafficking: only 1/100 victims are found and helped #ihts2013    
    
    
    Mira Sorvino: it shouldn't just be outsiders saying what is best for exploited ppl, victims need a seat at the table. #ihts2013    
    
    
    Why the gap between cases of #trafficking and prosecution, even in US? 1 factor: States w/o regs on #trafficking undercount #ihts2013    
    
    
    Alice Hill,DHS: outreach & education must hit every person that may bear witness to #trafficking, they can tip off enforcement #ihts2013    
    
    
    Genevieve from Coke: Why do I care? 68% of #trafficking victims connect in some way w global supply chains. We're global, >200 Cs #ihts2013    
    
    
    @Deloitte's Dan Helfrich asks the #ihts2013 panel: how does mounting data help you pin down #trafficking in your supply chain or otherwise?    
    
    
    Scott Carpenter of @Google Ideas: so much unproductive data now;we need to liberate it without revealing PII. Need data standards #ihts2013    
    
    
    Idea from the audience: to open up data that could help spot #trafficking,clean data like HIPPA did for health data, then open up #ihts2013    
    
    
    @palantir on q "how to open up data to spot traffickers?": access controls get very granular, so only share PII-free part of data #ihts2013    
    
    
    Ambassador CdeBaca: we need to confront untrue beliefs on #trafficking. Too many believe labor type hits men and sex only women #ihts2013    
    
    
    Ambassador CdeBaca: I don't know how many #fiscal cliffs you can have before it's a slope...    
    
    
    Bottom line from Amb CdeBaca: Confront reality, and don't let  gov off the hook.They aren't only key player. Smart engagement key #ihts2013    
    
    
    Instead of griping "someone should do something" ask, "what can I do?" #ihts2013    
    
    
    Mira Sorvino gets passionate about #humantrafficking. "They can avoid prison better than drug traffickers!" #ihts2013 pic.twitter.com/5N380tJz    
    
    
    @areddie89 Nice talking today at #ihts2013 - welcome to DC!    
    
    
    Neat concept, but "institutionalized"? WC RT @jhagel: Using coffee to create institutionalized space for serendipity http://bit.ly/VpQK3R     
    
    
    @IdeaXplorer nice recent profile of the #HIVE from @washtechnology!  http://ow.ly/hjAp4     
    
    
    Short attention span? Neural evidence explains why - and when - city living shortens attention http://ow.ly/hjBap     
    
    
    The Mobile Chasm: How do Fortune100 v. startups apply mobile? Fortune100=mostly marketing; startups=new problem solving http://ow.ly/hjBBK     
    
    
    I'm using @simplymeasured to analyze my Twitter followers in Excel. http://bit.ly/owpX5r     
    
    
    Remaining Q:Slacktivism or real progress? RT @quise7: The business of campaigning: Profit with @Purpose | The Economist http://econ.st/W2mKPb     
    
    
    @IdeaXplorer Thanks for the FF! BTW I love using SiteGeist, interesting to see how demographics differ across DC! @SunFoundation @DanNieves    
    
    
    Wooot @piyaradia @nikitatmitchell @ChiefHotMomma RT @forbes: The nation's capital Is 2013's best-paying city for women http://bit.ly/Tsiqby     
    
    
    Actually kinda true RT @brainpicker: "Rule: The more emotionally engaging the ad, deeper the letdown when you learn what product it's for."    
    
    
    These companies were quick on their feet to take advantage of the #SuperBowl #blackout http://ow.ly/hnRyZ  @forbes    
    
    
    Great parting speech: Love Clinton's Frank Gehry metaphor on need for new structures to maneuver complex world obstacles...    
    
    
    Why hire a company when you can hire a cluster of productive workers? Will this become a thing? @harvardbiz bets "yes" http://ow.ly/hqfF6     
    
    
    @dannieves Interesting. @Stublisher gives the visual recap, @Storify gives the sound bytes    
    
    
    Terrible. RT @HalaGorani: JUST IN - UN Human Rights chief: #Syria death toll "probably now approaching 70,000."    
    
    
    Truth. "The only change that matters is the change that happens after you leave." #SBLA13    
    
    
    Why are we here with @StartingBloc? Agile, aspiring minds and hearts. #SBLA13    
    
    
    The first responsibility of the leader is to define reality. The last is to say #TY. In between the leader is a servant. #SBLA13    
    
    
    How do you want to change the world? Uncertainty in your answer is OK. Certainty is overrated. Act boldly anyway. #SBLA13    
    
    
    Be bold enough - and vulnerable enough - to change the world. Have the hubris AND the humility to work beside AND lead others. #SBLA13    
    
    
    Morning run on the Santa Monica beach. Am I in heaven? #sbla13 http://instagr.am/p/VwhguCohsq/     
    
    
    Acting it out in @design4america workshop, @bobbyhertz hams it up #sbla13 http://instagr.am/p/VwzPMgohuW/     
    
    
    Just happy. #sbla13 kinda feels like the best version of summer camp. Except also defining life goals.… http://instagr.am/p/VyD7RtIhty/     
    
    
    Thanks for spreading the word! RT @bmonroe2: Gov on the Go -- via @DU_Press #mobile #mobileGov #eGov #digitalGov http://dupress.com/articles/gov-on-the-go/ …    
    
    
    @lauratomasko I'm here too at the #socent event @Hudson Institute is hosting, let's chat after!    
    
    
    Rick Cohen on #socent; "we are more focused on the entrepreneurs, rather than the bigger ecosystem. Broader social innovation is key"    
    
    
    Rick Cohen: How do we insert innovation into the multiple sectors? Business, gov, #socents without viewing this as a panacea?    
    
    
    Wow RT @HansRosling: Globally suicide is #1 cause of death in Women 15-19 yrs, #2 pregnancy complications, #3 traffic http://www.healthmetricsandevaluation.org/gbd/visualizations/gbd-2010-change-leading-causes-and-risks-between-1990-and-2010 …    
    
    
    Best read on US #healthcare this year in @Time: http://healthland.time.com/2013/02/20/bitter-pill-why-medical-bills-are-killing-us/ … Explains why US will overpay $750B on a $2.8T #health tab in 2013    
    
    
        
    
    
    @melaniekahl love your #readinglist on human-centered #design! Thanks for sharing with the @StartingBloc community! http://www.amazon.com/registry/wishlist/20CPGLL311SUG/ref=cm_wl_rlist_go_o_C-4 …    
    
    
    Gluten free high tea for outnaboutdc's birthday - such a treat! http://instagr.am/p/Wa5rb_ohj7/     
    
    
    @NikitaTMitchell loved catching up today on #socint and how to apply creativity to motivate people and systems to change - Exhilirating!    
    
    
    The advantages of #telework, visualized. Interesting contrast to @Yahoo's recent decision to reduce telework http://bit.ly/Z9QaId     
    
    
    3 defining traits of #bigdata: more, messy, correlations @newamericafoundation    
    
    
    Instead of getting tied up looking for causal relationships,correlations from #bigdata may suffice for many businesses @newamerica @drajwfu    
    
    
    #datafication: not just volume of data as byproduct from the digital age, it's info rendered in formats that allow it to be better analyzed    
    
    
    @inrix data on traffic intensity in shopping centers is used by investors as a leading indicator of earnings #bigdata @arasin @wdeggers    
    
    
    Risk: we may fetishize data, place too much trust in #bigdata and ignore our instincts @NikitaTMitchell @newamerica    
    
    
    @Economist Data Editor: Just like robber barons of past,may need to constrain data barons who amass large volumes of #bigdata @wdeggers    
    
    
    We need algorithmists, aka data auditors, to peek in black box of #bigdata and unveil the inner workings for regulators @drajwfu @wdeggers    
    
    
    What happens when the #sharing economy is the norm, and actually isn't as disrupted as we thought? @mbgrinberg http://www.economist.com/news/technology-quarterly/21572914-collaborative-consumption-technology-makes-it-easier-people-rent-items …    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Agreed on the #snl - really good!    
    
    
    @DanNieves Since they did @GA I'm already interested :) RT: Incubator Bringing Wash DC Together: http://ow.ly/iPXzj  #dctech @mbgrinberg    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ooof. For so many reasons... RT @WSJ: 2012: >1.7m cosmetic surgical procedures in U.S. That's an 80% jump from 1997.  http://on.wsj.com/15JY8x8     
    
    
    6 steps to successful #mgov implementation  from @wdeggers
http://bit.ly/ZIgPO2 
@bethnoveck @NeelieKroesEU    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg We'll feel the absence of @googlereader. Now the big Q is what's next?? Can we go beyond the feed to better recommended content?    
    
    
    @dylan20 OR do we need migration services that adapt to new tools? RT: lesson is: Do not rely on free cloud services. Nothing is permanent.    
    
    
    Hmm worth checking out in quest to replace @googlereader RT @mbgrinberg: Perhaps a solution http://www.engadget.com/2013/03/13/feedly-rss-service-promises-seamless-transition-after-google-r/ … @Schumenu @CalvinCheng3    
    
    
    @dylan20 would be great if who you follow in @GoogleReader informed Feedly pushes via their new backend; we'll see! http://engt.co/WIF2qX     
    
    
    How can DC boost US #innovation? Bold ideas from @brucenussbaum http://bit.ly/14zx55m  @ideaXplorer @drajwfu    
    
    
    @natenash203 Congrats on #Hord - awesome app! http://tech.co/government-contracting-done-right-with-hord-2013-03 …    
    
    
    @arasin Maybe the next work jam sesh should include the best #coffee on the East Coast... http://inthecapital.com/2013/03/15/peregrine-coffee-is-officially-the-best-coffee-shop-on-the-east-coast/#ss__44299_1_0__ss …    
    
    
    Uber, Data Darwinism and the future of work http://gigaom.com/2013/03/17/uber-data-darwinism-and-the-future-of-work/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Check out @AMCaccavale + @samrakasim's interesting piece on #drones in @Nextgov http://www.nextgov.com/technology-news/tech-insider/2013/03/commentary-five-ways-integrate-drones-domestic-airspace/61951/ … @GovLab    
    
    
    Truth. Outside w blue skies is my favorite reminder RT @jeffweiner: Sometimes it's easy to lose sight of the fact happiness is a choice.    
    
    
    Proof that humor really is best way to sell anything, even candy RT @jack: Sorry, Bunny. From @getunreal candy. http://sorrybunny.com/     
    
    
    Writing on walls at work, all about the #bigdata :) ideaxplorer dan_nieves http://instagram.com/p/XIOrQKohqu/     
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Curious how Zuckerberg's econ advocacy group would differ in position from all the existing orgs. Any predictions?    
    
    
    @AshleyWells87 Sounds good. Long time no talk - let's catch up soon!    
    
    
    Beautiful world. Captured for the 2013 @smithsonian photo contest @mbgrinberg @Ivy_So @GoKateShoot http://www.theatlantic.com/infocus/2013/03/smithsonian-magazines-2012-photo-contest/100466/ …    
    
    
    Ever wondered what a web of lobbyists looked like, #visualized? @SunFoundation's piece on #immigration is fascinating http://bit.ly/14pPrdN     
    
    
    A compelling #datavis on fatalities from military #drones @mbgrinberg @AMCaccavale @samrakasim http://drones.pitchinteractive.com/     
    
    
    Who needs personality tests when that insight comes, w greater accuracy, from public Facebook data? -Jennifer Goldbeck @milouness @wdeggers    
    
    
    My childhood kite flew so high today! @mbgrinberg milouness http://instagram.com/p/Xf8sU2ohqR/     
    
    
    @DanNieves @thenextweb Thanks, always love a good #tech event discount. Looking forward to #bigdata week!    
    
    
    @DanNieves Fascinating, I'll have to check out the Vizible app!    
    
    
    Thanks @sheiladcusa - enjoyed your contributions to the #socialmedia discussion! Hopefully the 1st of many :)    
    
    
    @milouness Creative uses other Google Glass Early Adopters intend to try w the glasses http://flip.it/E9B88  HT @mbgrinberg    
    
    
    @LBRosa great to meet you as well on Friday! Looking forward to more good conversation!    
    
    
    @dfroms I'll be in your hood Brooklyn this weekend and am going to Smorgasbord. Will you be there, fellow foodie?    
    
    
    @dfroms BTW my friend @GeorgeRoche22 just started a Ethiopian hot sauce #socent - check it out! http://www.washingtonian.com/blogs/bestbites/from-the-magazine/fire-it-up-five-hot-sauces-we-love.php …    
    
    
    @dfroms Oh man, it is the foodie holy grail of Brooklyn! Well tweet me if you end up showing up, I'll be there w some other foodies :)    
    
    
    Great conversations w @ValSrinivas and @deloitte team on the future of research using financial #bigdata @wdeggers    
    
    
    Contently cofounder Shane Snow kicks off the #scsummit dan_nieves @mbgrinberg http://instagram.com/p/XsNA4PIhux/     
    
    
    #Scsummit AmEx Open Forum's scottroen: getting to connect & support entrepreneurs gets me up in the… http://instagram.com/p/XsPGaHIhhY/     
    
    
    #scsummit AmEx's @scottroen: we don't have to guess what ppl want to see when we plug in to curated and user generated content    
    
    
    #scsummit Ebay's @jeanniereeth: how do we move ppl's view of our brand beyond "heritage" of c2c collectibles to today's small biz models?    
    
    
    eBay's @JeannieReeth: how tweets are shared helps find common elements of art &science of a hit. Emotions? Engaging stats? #scsummit    
    
    
    AmEx's @scottroen: Shares are a proxy for "good content" but some pieces like "how to fire" it doesn't work, social sensitivity #scsummit    
    
    
    #scsummit @contently can we do a live poll of what services people use for social metrics? Like hearing about these tools CC @DanNieves    
    
    
    "@forbes is a 96 yr old start up; today we care more about brand content than ever before" Acquired TrueSlant to engage brand fans #scsummit    
    
    
    Orgs like @ashoka are good at tapping this "Our @forbes platform brings more journalists w deep domain expertise an audience" #scsummit    
    
    
    Banner blindness - is it real? @petespande "content on the margins CAN engage ppl when we learn how to talk to humans again!" #scsummit    
    
    
    @mashable's Innovation Index aims to anticipate which media strategies via Brand Speak will catalyze #social audiences #scsummit @wdeggers    
    
    
    Hits=still wildly unpredictable. @forbes Mark Howard: can't put all budget in 1 basket by expecting a thing to go viral #scsummit @wdeggers    
    
    
    But it's a delicate line to walk. Panelist: "Brands and big media platforms don't need to be separate. It's an artificial divide" #scsummit    
    
    
    True @drelly: "You can't be trying to sell w sponsored content on media sites; the quality of content needs to stand on its own." #scsummit    
    
    
    Can I live here?? contently great venue choice for #scsummit! bowery hotel http://instagram.com/p/XseJo0ohkY/     
    
    
    On user gen content: @jonathansackett: Be careful how u seed it. There's risk in transparency & letting others control your brand #scsummit    
    
    
    Humor always helps @jonathansackett: We used gecko so ppl knew how to pronounce Geico. That sense of humor stuck w the brand. #scsummit    
    
    
    So true, humor does humanize RT @DanNieves: Humor can also help show the "human" side of a brand. Imp to have a personal touch #scsummit    
    
    
    Journalists aren't taught to listen to trends & jump in the conversation early. Those doing well learned to that fast. #scsummit @wdeggers    
    
    
    Eerie, tranquil exhibit at New Museum https://vine.co/v/bTA7qOlTiHa     
    
    
    The opposite of a tweet http://instagram.com/p/XtSjEfIhsP/     
    
    
    Great venue at the #scsummit! pic.twitter.com/qXN0YJ7m1r    
    
    
    A good kickoff to #scsummit @contently pic.twitter.com/nFetqheuQR    
    
    
    @scottroen talks Am Ex Open Forum impact stats pic.twitter.com/Xe5wEQprYS    
    
    
        
    
    
    Social Content Summit 2013 http://sfy.co/dGoC  #storify #scsummit #contentmarketing    
    
    
    @CarolynVadino @StephenTBradley @dailycandy You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @Margit @PitaGroup @melodyhan You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @AmyVernon @thatDanCohn @erbinstitute @Schumenu You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @jenneldin @jekeleme You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @shanesnow @DFMomentStudio @ElishaHartwig You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @socialmediamos @mmrothenberg @DawnPapandrea You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @saying_grace @AudreyGray You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @davidlook @lisakaykay @contently @nealunger You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @RicochetMedia You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @DegreeMen @scottroen @boweryhotelnyc @sunminkm You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @jeanniereeth You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @forbes @ChristianHJorg @kk4i @Evan_TFJ @drelly You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @mashable @LoyalCX @OPENForum @AuthorBee @eBay You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @markdhoward @laurenpassero You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @wdeggers @PeteSpande @businessinsider You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @cperry248 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @chaseneil You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @WeberShandwick @keithobrien @DanNieves @GEICO You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    @Jake_Blatt You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Social Content Summit 2013" http://sfy.co/dGoC     
    
    
    Beautiful evening to take in the cherry blossoms http://instagram.com/p/X5q6lHIhvu/     
    
    
    How do social networks explain inequality? Fascinating blend of ethnographic and mathematic network analysis http://ow.ly/jWZg5     
    
    
    Pushback on policies favoring the creative class- Thoughts @majoracarter? Great to meet you at the @GA event last wk! http://ow.ly/jWZOV     
    
    
    .@IdeaXplorer I love that the @SSIReview piece highlights @lab4mind - visited last yr. Was inspired by their work & gorgeous work space!    
    
    
    @christianbason great @SSIR piece on design-led innovation! Your MindLab team knows a thing or 2 about #coproduction http://ow.ly/jX16a     
    
    
    @natenash203 awesome catching up this morning - excited to follow the evolution of your @govtribe app, hord!    
    
    
    @IdeaXplorer here's my recap from the #scsummit! http://storify.com/Schumenu/social-content-summit-2013 …    
    
    
    Mark Zuckerberg weighs in on the #immigration debate http://www.washingtonpost.com/opinions/mark-zuckerberg-immigrants-are-the-key-to-a-knowledge-economy/2013/04/10/aba05554-a20b-11e2-82bc-511538ae90a4_story.html … @nesdiazuda @AlexHaseley @abedsali    
    
    
    @TeeGrec Ohhh yes. I know that volun-told word well :)    
    
    
    Ha. University websites really are a classic "what NOT to do" for #UX design, so true. http://xkcd.com/773/     
    
    
    So terrible. RT @AmyJoMartin: If you know #BostonMarathon runners, you can see where they last checked-in here: http://raceday.baa.org/individual.html     
    
    
    Everyone's hosting branded #social content RT @steverubel: The Atlantic will launch a paid content offering http://flip.it/QrzYj  #scsummit    
    
    
    My data team now tweets - check out @Data4Gov! We'll post neat interactive #vis, pieces on #analytics, and our own data-driven research    
    
    
    "How do you create a national constitution when country borders aren't even decided yet?" Fascinating talk on @Deloitte work w/ S. Sudan gov    
    
    
    Enjoyed "Tim Ferris' 4 hr reality check" piece in latest @Inc http://www.inc.com/magazine/201304/tom-foster/tim-ferriss-four-hour-reality-check.html … @wdeggers @tmfpapester @drajwfu    
    
    
    A whole new bevy of cool #edtech startups, spotlighted by @BillGates in the latest @FastCompany http://www.fastcompany.com/3007841/tech-forecast/bill-gates-education-we-can-make-massive-strides …    
    
    
    So True! @RosabethKanter: The Happiest people solve the most difficult problems: http://blogs.hbr.org/kanter/2013/04/to-find-happiness-at-work-tap.html … @Montero @BobbyHertz @MattLDuffy    
    
    
    Awesome RT @ChelseaClinton: .@dosomething announced 1m teens now use SMS program for social change. #millennials http://on.mash.to/11aBegY     
    
    
    Big decisions w #bigdata: how much do you condense & smooth data, do you sacrifice accuracy to pack a punch? At @DataCommunityDC event    
    
    
    The #bigdata challenge: build scalable algorithms to process imperfect data across distributed systems @DataCommunityDC    
    
    
    Good #dayavis isn't enough. Domain knowledge and storytelling on how you get to the insights are key. #bdw13 @DataCommunityDC @IdeaXplorer    
    
    
    #datavis tip via @benbendc: With multidimensional data, don't cram in a single window; show dimensions w multiple adjacent visuals #bdw13    
    
    
    Congresswomen Schultz: Of the ~12k ppl to have served in Congress over US history, only 296 have been women. #globalWIN CC @NikitaTMitchell    
    
    
    So about that memory implant...MIT's top tech breakthroughs of the past yr HT @mbgrinberg http://ow.ly/kmxky     
    
    
    Not the smart ones RT @brainpicker: “Institutions will try to preserve the problem to which they are the solution.” The Shirky Principle    
    
    
    @om sad but true for Wired. @aepstein32 Agreed, the JCrew @FastCompany  piece was great.    
    
    
    @NickKristof if you had taken a gap yr, how would you spend it?    
    
    
    @wdeggers :) RT @brit: Did you know it's WAY healthier to stand at your desk? 10 standing desks to make yourself. http://bit.ly/11DDfCz ”    
    
    
    Yes, taking that time to reflect is critical RT @jhagel: "If you want your future to be different than your past, study your past." -Spinoza    
    
    
    Good Q! RT @avantgame: Why do NYT profiles of leading women in tech&science often wind up in Fashion&Style section? http://nyti.ms/104UHM5     
    
    
    @majoracarter I've been slightly obsessed w/ how cleverly they use space in that compact apt! Enjoy the visit!    
    
    
    Me too! RT @bmonroe2: wanted this feature for a while! "Twitter Testing New Local Discovery Features" http://zite.to/14TxB3K  HT @DanNieves    
    
    
    Busted! RT @lizgannes: Funny list of those who may have bought fake followers: Diddy, 50 Cent, Mercedes and Pepsi. http://nyti.ms/10DyKuT     
    
    
    Very neat RT @milouness: Gas grows on trees? Bacteria can turn plant matter, manure into real gasoline http://bit.ly/ZRPtn6     
    
    
    Morbidly curious to see how this plays out: Gov debates what to do when #Socialmedia moves financial mkts http://ow.ly/kvFXg  @joncoffey    
    
    
        
    
    
    @orenjacob love Alpine, just beautiful. @brit gorgeous outdoor concert weather in DC yesterday, rare for us too!    
    
    
    @jasonhirschhorn True, probably because within 1 min of reading they can cure the typical reader's news FOMO :)    
    
    
    Art of a good interview: homework and humility via @brainpicker http://ow.ly/kvHMC  @NikitaTMitchell @MarzenaZukowska @larnold630    
    
    
    Fascinating to find out what already-influential people admire about the @time 100 influencers; neat personal stories http://ow.ly/kvHEY     
    
    
    Will #bigdata applied to "workforce science" overcome unconscious gender and race biases people make when hiring? http://ow.ly/kvJSK     
    
    
    Our kind of day @NikitaTMitchell RT @lenadunham: Let's be reasonable and add an 8th day to the week that is devoted exclusively to reading.    
    
    
    How what you "Like" on Facebook can predict your weight range and level of physical activity. #health http://www.forbes.com/sites/clareoconnor/2013/04/26/do-you-like-game-of-thrones-or-soulcycle-new-study-links-facebook-activity-to-obesity/?utm_campaign=forbestwittersf&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=social …    
    
    
    Loved @BeUnreasonable's call for "creative bravery" in tackling societal challenges for #unreasonableatstate.    
    
    
    "#entrepreneurship is the new diplomacy" - heard @ #unreasonableatstate    
    
    
    Great catching up at #unreasonableatstate yesterday @pummer @nilsjk @lauratomasko @yonibinstock @soapboxsoaps @millennialtrain!    
    
    
    Current obsession: Great Gatsby soundtrack streaming on NPR. Really unique genre mix.    
    
    
    Excited for a day o storytelling bootcamp with @PrideCollab and @tdoveyfishman #storieslab    
    
    
    "Transmedia is a unique way to communicate both ways; understand who is watching, and tell stories people connect with" #storieslab    
    
    
    Evolution of storytelling over the ages: From 'I am (Here)' to 'I am (human > aware >involved >curious >connected) #storieslab    
    
    
    Each person is now a mini media shop; when they enter your storyworld they bring their experiences + are in the habit of sharing #storieslab    
    
    
    Aina from StoryCode: "Stories aren't 'the answer' but they respond to lots of questions" #storieslab    
    
    
    #storieslab "if you're not rapid prototyping, you're not learning"    
    
    
    @terryscott nice meeting you at #storieslab - let's talk maps!    
    
    
    Life hacks from the savvy founder of TaskRabbit, Leah Busque. Some good tips! http://ow.ly/kS4wR     
    
    
    "Can the Big Four crack the elite tier?" Good question, @theeconomist. @milouness @shrupti @chriscgdc
http://ow.ly/kStIl     
    
    
    Meet Alvarez, the "last living dinosaur" at @826DC https://vine.co/v/b0wValIpzVQ     
    
    
    A very inquisitive dinosaur https://vine.co/v/b0wlFWWU1lj     
    
    
    Solar rentals via @sunrun land in @FastCompany's 100 Most Creative list. Knew you'd appreciate @weggers @jigarshahdc http://ow.ly/kZNh8     
    
    
    My top 5 of the @FastCompany 100 Most Creative: @aiwwneversorry @GirlsWhoCode @littleBits @medium @fivethirtyeight http://ow.ly/kZMMX     
    
    
    Scary #sentiment, mapped RT @fastcompany: See Twitter's bigotry hot spots with the "hate map": http://trib.al/1BDUI6g     
    
    
    The "Budget airline" of healthcare RT @TheEconomist: Sweden leads world in private co running public insts @wdeggers http://econ.st/YRKuGP     
    
    
    Van Jones at #scsummit: "we shouldn't be looking down into dead holes for our future; why not look UP at the sun (as an energy source)?    
    
    
    Van Jones: #Millennials may not have the financial capital but they use social capital and savvy to get. Stuff. DONE. #scsummit @bobbyhertz    
    
    
    .@BobbyHertz your ears must be burning! At #scsummit @vanjones68 talked about how Millennials mobilize around issues like Keystone XL    
    
    
    .@vanjones68: we don't want "eco-artaid" with big disparities btwn who gets a healthy environment and who doesn't #scsummit CC @jigarshah    
    
    
    What did the housing bubble look like across different country markets? Great interactive vis from @TheEconomist http://www.economist.com/blogs/dailychart/2011/11/global-house-prices?Fsrc=scn/fb/wl/dc/housingmarkets …    
    
    
    Lots of good stories RT @DanDzombak: What's the shrewdest, smartest maneuver you've ever seen in business? http://www.quora.com/Business/Whats-the-shrewdest-smartest-maneuver-youve-ever-seen-in-business …    
    
    
    Let's hope Airbnb rallies RT @jhagel: The incumbents mobilize to block the attackers - Airbnb declared illegal in NYC http://bit.ly/183oONg     
    
    
    @jhagel where is this tree house?? I want to visit!    
    
    
    @rexster agreed, fascinating read.    
    
    
    I'm actually MORE excited about sequencing my #microbiome than DNA,w this handy kit to thank-- http://ubiome.com/  @wdeggers @davidzfang    
    
    
    This Digital Tools Tutorial for interactive storytelling looks cool! @DanNieves @bmonroe2 @LynnMyWin http://www.newsu.org/digital-tools-zeega …    
    
    
    @PhilDahlin Ooof that @sciam article isn't exactly a ray of sunshine, but has some interesting figures!    
    
    
    Sometimes simple medical solutions are all we need... http://www.economist.com/news/science-and-technology/21578025-medical-technology-need-not-be-sophisticated-be-effective-mat-red?fsrc=scn/fb/wl/pe/matred …    
    
    
    @melaniekahl Ooo really? You're swaying me - even after running a @Deloitte #SocInn wkshp 6/6 and @Ashoka volunteer day 6/7! #sleepwhenidie    
    
    
    And guess what @melaniekahl? Fellow @StartingBloc-ers @dardenhayley & @aryacetas are coordinating the @Deloitte +@Ashoka volunteer day too!    
    
    
    @melaniekahl thanks! Any plans to visit DC? If you do, definitely let me know!    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Some mkt gaps can be met w low/shared cost models, but @GovLab has a pt: who will incent/subsidize serving the hard to reach?    
    
    
    Breakfast chat that spans Agra-drones, health startups & insurers working Obamacare, +models that hack talent? Check @drajwfu! Always fun :)    
    
    
    @GovLab @mbgrinberg @wdeggers Agree. Not all models that reach marginalized are effective +financially sustainable.Big q: Who pays the diff?    
    
    
    Thrilled to see new series on health costs from @nytimes:Colonoscopies explain why US leads world in $ http://nyti.ms/1aRCKa0  @tdoveyfishman    
    
    
    @Lwsplash The shelf life of food! via @pinterest http://pinterest.com/pin/34973334579034050/ …    
    
    
    What's more short/sweet/&moving than when outstanding writers recall the 1st #books that moved them? http://ow.ly/lDjs9  @NikitaTMitchell    
    
    
    Oh no - does this work @NikitaTMitchell? http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/02/books/review/what-i-read-that-summer.html?pagewanted=all&_r=0 …    
    
    
    Nice piece in @TechCocktail, @vferragut!    
    
    
    @nikitatmitchell I had a feeling it would be up your alley! I found them beautiful to read too.    
    
    
    The solitude of a quiet walk in fragrant rain can be so restorative. Everything else dissolves. Just step to step. On to the next.    
    
    
    #ImpactDay2013 with ashoka - What an energizing day! milouness @datanorms @davispj http://instagram.com/p/aRjC1rohtE/     
    
    
    Great lineup of speakers @TEDxRosslyn thanks to @YoniBinstock, including friend @AlanJHolden -check out livestream! http://new.livestream.com/tedx/tedxrosslyn …    
    
    
    Excited to hear @milouness speak at @TEDxRosslyn all about #RebelsatWork via livestream. Love her perspective on #intrapreneurs!    
    
    
    Pups = priorities! :) RT @valsrinivas: Crazy about pets: Recession Didn't Impact Pet Consumer Spending http://www.millionairecorner.com/article/consumer-spending-trends-recession-didnt-impact-pet-spending#.UbkonnZC2Fo.twitter …    
    
    
    Chat w @davidzfang about 4) #Bioelectronics @mbgrinberg :) RT @mbgrinberg: 5 inventions waiting to happen - http://FT.com  via @FT    
    
    
    Truth! Data science is #storytelling. It's all in the analysis http://ow.ly/lYTTt     
    
    
    "We often use illness to disparage a way of being,& identity to validate that way of being.This is a false dichotomy" http://ow.ly/lYSYH     
    
    
    The respite (and productivity) of writing and working alone, from Ernest Hemingway http://ow.ly/lYTiS     
    
    
    Creativity in color. Fun user generated #socialcontent via @pantone. @drelly @carloynvadino @tdoveyfishman http://ow.ly/lYTrJ     
    
    
    Well done, @mariapacheco4! @wakamiUSA Guatemalan social entrepreneurs hitting the big time, in Ann Taylor Loft stores http://ow.ly/lYUGW     
    
    
    More US doctors need this RT @davemcclure: Singapore’s DocDoc & DoctorPage merge to expand Web-based bookings in Asia http://tnw.to/b0Ync     
    
    
    Wow, really? RT @niemanlab: Would you click “Respect” button more than you click a “Like” button? This study says yes http://nie.mn/19qOjss     
    
    
    Oh, you don't view your data on 10 screens? @datanorms at the helm http://instagram.com/p/ajEuCrIhtk/     
    
    
    Good acronym via @dannieves RT @valaafshar: be S.O.C.I.A.L. sincere open collaborative interested authentic likeable #socialmedia    
    
    
    Summer wandering #Dublin http://instagram.com/p/aor9z_IhkM/     
    
    
    Crazy that only 1/5 of Americans have jobs that involve communicating w ppl in diff countries from them. 27% is global avg @Deloitte #GPS13    
    
    
    "Households need 2.1 kids to maintain a country's pop. Too many are 1/2 baby short per house."Great pres at @Deloitte #GPS13 conf in #Dublin    
    
    
    Which countries have ppl willing to move for a good job? Mexico tops list. Great @IPSOS talk at @Deloitte #GPS13 pic.twitter.com/1ivKXUEErM    
    
    
        
    
    
    Creativity-harnessing Paper app for IPad gets $15m from @a16z RT @a16z: Big ideas need big partners http://news.fiftythree.com/post/53274096628/its-about-ideas … CC: @IdeaXplorer    
    
    
    Lots of enthusiasm from deloitte global leaders about the #SolutionRevolution! At #GPS13 @ Four… http://instagram.com/p/atL2B1Ihne/     
    
    
    All sorts of passive tracking apps on display at IIEX conference - interesting to see how that data will be used http://ow.ly/mbg0j ...    
    
    
    @jarobmc I agree! By most measures Don's life is in shambles, but he's being honest w himself and others, a sign of growth #madmen    
    
    
    Nice #socialcontent recs in your latest op ed, @DanNieves! Very cool :) http://latinbusinesstoday.com/2013/06/view-these-5-web-content-tools-for-your-business/ …    
    
    
    Fascinating to contrast polling v. Twitter sentiment on politics, shows who is on #socialmedia @datanorms @jarasin http://twitpic.com/czab8c     
    
    
    @tommywporter Just discovered your great Twitter list of @StartingBloc fellows - can you add me to the list?    
    
    
    Headed to the beach and curious about the water quality? This handy interactive map will help: http://www.nrdc.org/water/oceans/ttw/default.asp …    
    
    
    The endless question of happiness, gets me every time. Can't wait for this week's @time mag! http://instagram.com/p/bD6t4iK684/     
    
    
    Here's to green cities @ RT @IdeaXplorer: Visionary designs aiming to breathe life back into our cities... literally. http://ow.ly/mw9XU     
    
    
    Sweet email #lifehacks @wdeggers RT @lifehacker: Gmail is awesome. IFTTT is awesome. Combine together and you get: http://lifehac.kr/RsKEl5t     
    
    
    More reason to love #gamification RT @Upworthy:What a biologist couldn’t figure out in 10 yrs only took gamers 3 wks! http://u.pw/11OAdcU     
    
    
    Excited to see NII announced at #G8 take shape. Nice coverage from @RRocketto @Shrupti @RobTerrin @GovLab #impinv http://www.forbes.com/sites/skollworldforum/2013/06/27/how-the-u-s-government-can-accelerate-the-impact-economy/ …    
    
    
    Sabbaticals. Not just for sr leaders anymore. Great piece from friend @GeorgeRoche22 on seizing opp to start #socent http://www.forbes.com/sites/ashoka/2013/06/20/start-a-benefit-company-on-sabbatical-5-tips-to-make-it-happen/ …    
    
    
    My answer to Why are so many companies opposed to letting people work from home? http://qr.ae/I15im     
    
    
    My answer to What do you think are effective measures to evaluate the impact of corporate social responsibility acti… http://qr.ae/I1wIi     
    
    
    Hi #Newsgames."Tell me & I'll forget;show me & I may remember;involve me & I'll understand.” http://ow.ly/mVn5K  @chinchilla3000 @vzinsou    
    
    
    Nerding out with #GoogleGlass at lunch - thanks for sharing @milouness! @ Deloitte Center For Federal… http://instagram.com/p/b2B2bdIhlh/     
    
    
    Thoughts on these @arasin? More pretty than useful? RT @FastCompany: Social media portraits of 11 cities http://trib.al/T7rsJXh     
    
    
    The appetite for game apps is just as fickle as fashion RT @NielsHoven: Zynga lost ~half its players this yr. Brutal. http://techcrunch.com/2013/07/26/after-losing-nearly-half-its-users-in-a-year-investors-dock-zyngas-valuation-by-400-million/ …    
    
    
    In the push to share ideas on #socialmedia, volume of sharing often gets more attn than quality of ideas. TY to nuanced thinkers who share!    
    
    
    .@Quip is pretty cool. Like the clean interface, feels like @Google Chrome, which makes sense given the lineage of the programmers    
    
    
    Good! "Microsoft and Google scrambling to make products that reflect work where PCs exist w other devices."HT @arasin http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/01/technology/as-work-habits-change-software-makers-rush-to-innovate.html?_r=0 …    
    
    
    Why do the @Deloitte interns have to leave?? Love the enthusiasm and energy they bring. Will miss @ben_hsieh @ellie_bellie3 and others!    
    
    
    Check out latest on #intrapreneurship @NikitaTMitchell @MarzenaZukowska from @GovLab pals @larnold630 @shanimagia! http://cdn.dupress.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/07/DUP424_Intrapreneurs-in-government_vFINAL.pdf?397dc7 …    
    
    
    Great news for all w #Celiac! RT @davidzfang: FDA approves GF labeling reqs - step in the right direction, @Schumenu http://www.npr.org/blogs/thesalt/2013/08/01/208024023/fda-approves-gluten-free-label …    
    
    
    Really inspiring to see what fellow #Hoya alum @AlexBTrust is doing with #GoogleGlass despite paralysis http://alexbtrust.org/google-glass/  @milouness    
    
    
    After a tough week, a good swim is my favorite meditation. Funny how once you find rhythm in 1 thing, others fall into step.    
    
    
    Is the news getting weirder? RT @businessinsider: Venezuelan thieves hold women at gunpoint to steal their hair http://read.bi/1bhw5rQ     
    
    
    #Datascience conference that covers #semantics is coming in Sept FYI @weggers @dbyler http://datacommunitydc.org/blog/2013/08/cloud-soa-semantics-and-data-science-conference/ …    
    
    
    "Infrapreneur" - person that builds law/policy infra. to support #socent. Nice piece @lauratomasko! http://ow.ly/nMcmT  @georgeroche22    
    
    
    My creation from a fun typography tutorial w @nokingsdc, finished up in the sculpture garden! http://instagram.com/p/c5O3hkohth/     
    
    
    Searches of terms like "depression"&"symptoms" are a boon for medical researchers that know how to analyze #bigdata http://ow.ly/nRKWg     
    
    
    What happens when #design meets #policy to drive improvements for immigrant day laborers?  http://ow.ly/nRLrc  @AlexHaseley @Nesdiazuda    
    
    
    So cool! RT @socinnovators: Meds that change color when unfit for consumption:Self-Expiring #Medicine http://stnfd.biz/nRlHQ  CC: @PhilDahlin    
    
    
    Good Q! RT @theatlantictech: Hyperloop would be awesome. http://theatln.tc/14qvfTN  But will its awesomeness put other public projects on hold?    
    
    
    "Opportunity looks a lot like work" leave it to @aplusk to get kids excited about hard work at the Nickolodeon awards http://ow.ly/nS4K6     
    
    
    Sometimes, OCD can be channeled into something brilliant and beautiful http://gawker.com/man-with-ocd-blows-internet-away-with-hauntingly-stirri-1111560858 …    
    
    
    Now #Digitalmedia is finally starting to bring in more than pennies, and media companies are taking notice @shanesnow http://www.economist.com/news/business/21583687-media-companies-took-battering-internet-cash-digital-sources-last?fsrc=nlw|hig|8-15-2013|6397721|38062047|NA …    
    
    
    So true, well said. http://instagram.com/p/dC23wmpJSg/     
    
    
    Cool! RT @mbgrinberg: A visual guide to where you federal tax dollars go @wdeggers @schumenu @DanNieves http://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0177/6150/t/2/assets/WATERMARK-DNT-0712.png?173 … #infographic    
    
    
    The many faces of international #trade @SherifNagui http://mkshft.org/2013/07/infographic-sizing-the-swap/ …    
    
    
    Great @SSIReview piece from colleague @cdebruin08 on how mature orgs can adapt for greater social #impact http://www.ssireview.org/blog/entry/tackling_changing_markets_with_enterprise_community_partners#When:16:21:00Z …    
    
    
    Don't buy into hoopla around #prizes & challenges? Interesting @SSIReview piece highlights some of the inefficiencies http://www.ssireview.org/blog/entry/dump_the_prizes#When:17:03:00Z …    
    
    
    It's not all bliss in the #sharingeconomy. Good to see a balanced critique from @ecolibris in @TriplePundit http://ow.ly/ocuC9 .    
    
    
    @mbgrinberg Agreed, Affleck as Batman seems strange to me too    
    
    
        
    
    
    Who needs a man cave when there's a man cube? Brilliant design for small spaces @mbgrinberg @joncoffey HT @davidzfang http://ow.ly/ocGay     
    
    
    Thanks!! RT @BobbyHertz: Megan @Schumenu is a BOSS, so psyched to see the book when it comes out http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZHreSAXePYw … #SolutionRevolution    
    
    
    Alas, NYC. DC real estate isn't much easier @joncoffey @mbgrinberg @davidzfang    
    
    
    One more reason to like #bikesharing: they boost revenues for local vendors http://www.triplepundit.com/2013/09/bike-lanes-boosts-revenue-for-retailers/ …    
    
    
    Glad to see @MillennialTrain written up by @gatesfoundation! Looked like a neat cross country adventure http://ow.ly/oAuuH     
    
    
    Thanks, have fun! RT @NikitaTMitchell: Great #SOCAP13 session on #solutionrevolution. Special shoutout to @schumenu for working on this…    
    
    
    How will YOU tackle tough societal issues? Check out my + #HIVE's latest #infographic @nikitatmitchell @lauratomasko http://ow.ly/oJNCr     
    
    
    Thanks @Yoprado! I agree, really happy with how the #solutionrevolution infographic turned out! http://www.solutionrevolutionbook.com/ideas     
    
    
    Good news @ivyso! RT @VoluntouristKen: What do 10 most livable cities have in common? Most in Canada and Australia http://ow.ly/oLNr5     
    
    
    Neat to hear about Jerry the bear, a toy @AaronJHorowitz and others from #dfa created to train kids w diabetes for better health #fablabdc    
    
    
    Thanks! Glad you like the infographic @AleciaKintner!    
    
    
    "To ppl angsty re how 3D Printing will disrupt, skip 1st mistake of music + other industries: see as opp don't try to sue away @mweinbergPK    
    
    
    "Companies like Nike show they are in vanguard by testing out new tools like 3D printing, better approach than fighting it" @mweinbergPK    
    
    
    Woo #SolutionRevolution book launches today! Meet the Changemakers, explore the #infographic, vids, + podcast + more! http://www.solutionrevolutionbook.com/     
    
    
    What does a life embracing #risk look like? Artfully captured, @therisklife! (also makes me want to visit Colombia!) http://bit.ly/17ZD08E     
    
    
    Tons of opinions lately on whether women should get MBA/#leanin/kids. Share pros/cons, but these are personal choices http://ow.ly/oY7QE     
    
    
    @Myrmecos @sciam Wow, had no idea being a postdoc was such a 20+ yr struggle. Illuminating piece. http://www.johnskylar.com/post/61507282912/why-you-dont-fucking-love-science …    
    
    
    Thanks @dannieves @catchsarah @lauratomasko! Exciting to have the #SolutionRevolution book officially launch! #seeimpact    
    
    
    Still reveling in all the fantastic people met at @fablabdc last wknd. Neat network of people bringing #tech creativity & #solutions to #dc!    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @Paul_Ledwell: Fantastic launch today of #SolutionRevolution. Excellent leading thoughts from @Paul_Macmillan @wdeggers @Schumenu    
    
    
    "Sometimes I believe as many as 6 impossible things before breakfast" (Alice). I love people like this, who think & share adventurously    
    
    
    If I hear "doing well by doing good" one more time... Like the sentiment, but phrase is just so overused. #overit.    
    
    
    Sweet! A hyperlocal Twitter filter will beta in Capitol Hill+3 other cities. Just what we've wanted @DanNieves!  http://ow.ly/p4j7x     
    
    
    Hmm keep many pwords or be an easy hack? Whatta choice. OR:a wristband that authenicates w/ a heartbeat!HT @chriscgdc http://ow.ly/p4kks     
    
    
    Yes! Speak your space savvy to the universe @mikelapidus! RT @mbgrinberg: @Schumenu look who we got to join Twitter! Welcome @mikelapidus    
    
    
    Cool! TY :) RT @lauratomasko: At #COF13, Gabriel @MntrInstitute mentions #SolutionRevolution http://bit.ly/1gWDPjL  (Go @Schumenu!)    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @IdeaXplorer: What type of wavemaker are you?Terrific #infographic by @Schumenu & @DeloitteHIVE http://bit.ly/17zJ6vA  #seeimpact    
    
    
    Awesome to see @BeUnreasonable profiled in this wknd's @nytimes! CC @epsteindaniel @ http://ow.ly/pllFe     
    
    
    Enjoyed dynamic conversation w new Fellows last night! RT: @alexmsimon The DC Fellows have arrived! @CompassPartners...    
    
    
    @sonalrshah enjoyed Ignite @Georgetown seminar last Fri! Tried your "musical chair" conversation w @CompassPartners new Fellows -great rec!    
    
    
        
    
    
    City with £25.4bn #green economy? @MayorofLondon consistently kills it on #sustainability. CC @PhilDahlin @bobbyhertz http://ow.ly/poe9D     
    
    
    An improbable victory you thought you knew, retold. @Gladwell's riveting twist on David & Goliath http://ow.ly/pok1j     
    
    
    Wow RT @FastCoDesign: "We've put down, since 2007, almost 400 miles of bike lanes on the streets of New York." -Janette Sadik-Khan, @NYC_DOT    
    
    
        
    
    
    Proof of what we knew all along! RT @nytimeshealth: Research shows that exercise feels harder when brain is tired http://nyti.ms/16h9mvC     
    
    
        
    
    
    Now the economists are irked RT @TimAeppel: Prolonged #shutdown wouldn't only delay Sept job report, maybe Oct's too http://blogs.wsj.com/economics/2013/10/04/will-shutdown-screw-up-next-months-jobs-report-too/ …    
    
    
    .@rockfellerfdn reports 17 state&local govs now use SIBs to finance social projects @cdebruin08 @weggers #infographic http://ow.ly/puR8X     
    
    
    The Great Jack O'Lantern Blaze 2013 at Van Cortlandt Manor, Croton | Historic Hudson Valley: http://www.hudsonvalley.org/events/blaze#.UlCQh4AqnP0.twitter …    
    
    
    Fascinating RT @kdnuggets: Data Mining reveals the emotional differences in emails written by Men and Women http://bit.ly/GEZbqx     
    
    
    .@davidzfang more good stuff @nest RT @AustinCarr: 6 headaches that Nest's new gorgeous smoke detector finally cures http://www.fastcodesign.com/3019638/6-headaches-that-nests-smoke-detector-finally-cures …    
    
    
    The #shutdown's reach is starting to hit international trade ttp://ow.ly/pBXUL    
    
    
    "Where are the solutions?" to social issues, asks @MichaelEPorter. Biz can help. Very aligned w #solutionrevolution http://ow.ly/pCdo9     
    
    
    So are we really workaholics? Most people in OECD countries actually work less than they did in 1990. TY computers! http://ow.ly/pCDN4     
    
    
    Watching 16 yr old Malala leave John Colbert speechless w the power of her courage is pretty wonderful http://ow.ly/pGw2h  @cdebruin08    
    
    
    "The Curse of the Connector" is stirring up all kinds of conv re: what does "friend" mean today, anyway? http://ow.ly/pGXoY     
    
    
    Crowdsourced...black mkt drug prices?? Coming to an academic journal near you... http://ow.ly/pGYvx  @mbgrinberg @ideaxplorer @dannieves    
    
    
    Since 2011 political squabbling equates to a $261B uncertainty tax that cost up to 1m new jobs, says Vanguard Group http://ow.ly/pJQbs     
    
    
    Dilbert's Scott Adams considers it a personal win if his comics cut down on mgmt jargon thru mockery - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/10/scott-adams-on-whether-management-really-matters/ …    
    
    
    Wondering whether that Kickstarter will be a hit or a lemon? This algorithm knows in the 1st 4 hrs. http://ow.ly/qfbsO  HT @mbgrinberg    
    
    
    Yes please! RT @scottbix: Airlines race to be 1st to lose travel's most pointless rule: Turn off  electronic devices http://bloom.bg/1ctH4i3     
    
    
    6 degrees of separation between you & a stranger? Now it's more like 4. http://ow.ly/qvs9H     
    
    
    Inspiring hearing Nigerian Tokunboh Ishmael on our panel speak about her work bringing financial… http://instagram.com/p/gYPpccohlV/     
    
    
    New models and tech for social change, meet the UN. Great #SolutionRevolution panel at the UN. Livestream: http://webtv.un.org/     
    
    
    A 1 hr DC>NY commute would be awesome, but how much more expensive would this 300MPH train be than Amtrak? http://f-st.co/cZkBo81     
    
    
    #bpsummit "Good social has to be authentic to what author usually writes about and provide value to the reader"    
    
    
    Social content strategy from @robin_riddle at #bpsummit: "Graceful transparency is key, w no element of blur around commercial relationship"    
    
    
    GE's @tomkellner: a good story has something at stake; a company needs to be honest about challenges, that makes it interesting #bpsummit    
    
    
    Why companies struggle online, @robin_riddle: compliance depts are overwhelmed by volume/speed of social media, so they ignore it #bpsummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lots o coffee/music/humor at moth storytelling event #bpsummit @ The Bowery Hotel http://instagram.com/p/gbKfnKohox/     
    
    
    Dell @ #bpsummit: We can't write authoritatively on cloud unless we are truly engaging w the space, we want productive conversations    
    
    
    Working across silos in a large company, from Citi: answer can't be 'no', start early so it's "what is the path to 'yes'"? #bpsummit    
    
    
    Storytelling platforms are big @ #bpsummit. Microsoft's new story page reminds me of our #solutionrevolution @Deloitte Changemakers platform    
    
    
    .@Microsoft pitched story of its digitally networked campus to media, no interest since not "news". Instead ran story themselves #bpsummit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Neat to hear social media guru from Sunday's @nytimes @garyvee talk about how sales skills translate to reach readers #bpsummit    
    
    
    "Back when people sought TV as escape, ads natively brought characters to sell stuff" says @garyvee Today I think it's experiences #bpsummit    
    
    
    "So many companies tell stories in places where everyone runs away from them - we mute, FF, seek distraction to avoid watching" #bpsummit    
    
    
    "For 1st time ever, quality of content IS the distribution" $$ moves to what attracts an audience instead of paying for spots" #bpsummit    
    
    
    Agree @mbgrinberg, always a pleasure!    
    
    
    Perusing notes from #bpsummit, such a great series of conversations! Made even better w storytelling from @TheMoth pic.twitter.com/s0g2IuXV6O    
    
    
    @Visible_Expert You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @mdeziel @ktyarnell You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @ellarileyadams You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @districtbelle You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @gregswan You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @courtneycolwell You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @ChristianHJorg You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @BreeSposato You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @DeannaZammit You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
        
    
    
    @steverubel You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @YoYolanne @carr2n You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @jenswartley You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @jezkablaque You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @ChannerMahoney You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @Evan_TSP @contently You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @AyeshaMathews You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @janiejaner You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @ElisaAnnCool You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @jonathanblank You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @HuffPostPartner You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @WeberShandwick You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @garyvee You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @lukekintigh You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @rodkurtz You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @tomkellner @TheMoth You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @robin_riddle You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @generalelectric You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @realdanlyons You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @Microsoft You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @seventeenmag @Poptip You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @marieclaire You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @lindadescano You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
    @NicoleSatDell You've been quoted in my #Storify story ""Make Stories, Not Ads" Brand Publishing Summit Recap" http://sfy.co/tIRH     
    
    
        
    
    
    If having friends that capture & conjure moments beautifully is 1 of life's great delights, this is 1! http://ow.ly/qLdsL  @mbgrinberg    
    
    
    Does the Vox/Curbed deal signal consolidation in the fragmented #digitalcontent/blog space? http://ow.ly/qMnoI  CC @chrisheuer @dannieves    
    
    
    God bless snarky news-devouring New Yorkers. Makes my work days so much more entertaining. Lookin at you @ChrisFaile @RyanZagone...    
    
    
    While you're in the #UK @weggers check out their unemployment map c/o @guardian http://ow.ly/qMqoU     
    
    
    Wow - State Department has 160 different Twitter accounts! The Federal Twitterverse: http://ow.ly/qYoOF     
    
    
    Big signal for social data RT @gigaom: DataSift raises $42M. Maybe there's something to this social data after all http://wp.me/p10LZV-31ux     
    
    
    Peacekeeping... Drones? What do you make of that @mbgrinberg RT @Slate: The UN deploys peacekeeping? drones to Congo: http://slate.me/J7Ssrg     
    
    
    @StephMarketer @cheeky_geeky You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @jenngustetic @1776dc @msmithDC You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    Creating Partnerships for the Public Good http://sfy.co/sKq1  #storify #partner4good #solutionrevolution    
    
    
    @KurtRwhiting @jeancase @GovLab You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @tdlowden @tdoveyfishman You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @linseyasledge @GirlTrek You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @danaodonovan @ChallengeGov You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
        
    
    
    @PrometheanComm @BUILDMetroDC You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @ashokaus @wdeggers @nfl You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @CityYear @americorps @J0NATHAN_G You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @Elinasarkisova @jonathan_g You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @Walmart @jamieoliver @letsmove You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @MaxHoblitzell @usaid_info You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @chrisjurgens11 @JeffDavis54 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @Christie_May_ @eburfield @NASA You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @newprofit You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
        
    
    
    @KarabiDC @jraders @UnSectored You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    @DrewatState @WhartonSocial You've been quoted in my #Storify story "Creating Partnerships for the Public Good" http://sfy.co/sKq1     
    
    
    The @lifehacker "How I Work" segment is always full of fun productivity-boosting tidbits + tools http://ow.ly/rBS4P  Next to try: @trello    
    
    
    A doctor's take on how to improve US #healthcare w best practices from India http://ow.ly/rCRFK  @Mahesh_Kelkar @Amrita07 @weggers    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PrometheanComm Great! Would love ideas on upping the interactivity. I always like a mix of digital/in-person connecting at events    
    
    
    Agreed, very cool! RT @JulietBourke: How good is this? Pantene Takes On The Hypocrisy Of Workplace Gender Stereotypes http://flip.it/3JlT6     
    
    
        
    
    
    Welcome to the immersive music video - it's well, Happy! Love the interactivity and spunk of @Pharrell's latest. http://ow.ly/rFyEH     
    
    
    Great conversation on #partnerships on 12/5 thanks to @DeloitteGov! Here's the recap if you missed it: http://ow.ly/rFGVD  #partner4good    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @meridith: @Schumenu Really enjoyed your Storify on the #partner4good event. Very nice job!    
    
    
    Pumped for this issue of @Wired to fuel my mag addiction. All about "fixing the world" through lens of @billgates http://ow.ly/rIzwQ     
    
    
    Bourbon and #datavis - a perfect combo :) RT @davidzfang: Know thy (bourbon) family,@Schumenu @mbgrinberg http://www.gq.com/life/food/201311/bourbon-whiskey-family-tree …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ouch! What not-to-read 2013: the year's worst writing. Some of these def got more press than deserved #sadbuttrue http://ow.ly/rIXaE     
    
    
    Awesome people, energizing community. Here's the @StartingBloc trailer for anyone considering the fellowship: http://ow.ly/rIYWL  @icesar    
    
    
    I've realized my greatest respect is for leaders who balance confidence, compassion, and humility. Too often those traits are at odds.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks @CafeImpact! The feeling - and follow - is mutual :)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    The evolving demographics of DC: 2000 v. now. Nice interactives from @urbaninstitute http://ow.ly/rOLJO  @corbett3000 @alexmsimon    
    
    
    Wow! 1 in 11 citizens in DC is a lawyer, says @GaryShapiro. Patent troll cases often a startups' big obstacle to profitability #startupgrind    
    
    
    "I share, therefore I am." Thoughtful piece from @nytimes on our hyper-documented lives http://ow.ly/rSFrF  @nikitatmitchell @dannieves    
    
    
        
    
    
    In addition to many others in DC :) RT @MichelleTalbert: Guilty as charged lol RT Wow! 1 in 11 in DC are #lawyers #startupgrind    
    
    
    Agree @bmonroe2. Quality conversations don't invite interruption from devices. You want to be present for all of it. @DanNieves    
    
    
    Gosh @nytdavidbrooks, grim picture of the "thought leader." Not all 26 yr olds push snark to emerge from obscurity :) http://ow.ly/rXphb     
    
    
    One of my top winter reads so far? Dave Eggers' "The Circle" - raises fascinating questions about #socialmedia and privacy    
    
    
    