I'm at Imagining The Lowline (New York, NY) w/ 6 others https://foursquare.com/kbedosky/checkin/5054b5d2e4b084591550c986?s=iOaf79tVHDz5fFxuNXCrNBtyoeY&ref=tw …    
    
    
    #lowline #nyc #essex #nofilters   @ Imagining The Lowline http://instagr.am/p/Pmq2AYRedg/     
    
    
    Vegetarian foods! (@ Teany) http://4sq.com/PmhaC7     
    
    
    You don't say....BBC News - Work stress 'raises heart risk' http://bbc.in/OKZDma     
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum We hate because we love.    
    
    
    @dryerdoor @twoshots @acesandrum Hmmm what time?    
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum who is the hater NOW?    
    
    
    @dryerdoor @acesandrum That could work for me quite perfectly actually. I can bring ace    
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum Don't hate. It'll give you wrinkles.    
    
    
    @AcesAndRum @dryerdoor earliest for me would be 4    
    
    
    @acesandrum @dryerdoor Gonna be getting there probably closer to 4:45. Finishing up stuff here, then headin out with Ace.    
    
    
    Why on earth is a LEGO replica of Fallingwater priced at $99.99?    
    
    
    #NYC #sunset #rooftop #Brooklyn - A pano from AutoStitch iPhone. pic.twitter.com/NjUH3puw    
    
    
    @dryerdoor OMG ITS YOUR PEOPLE!  ALAHU AKBAR (sound change): http://youtu.be/ZSEBet4HO8o  via @youtube    
    
    
    10 Ways To Create An Open Culture  http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1681531  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nathan_lacy! First stop of the evening. (@ Los Feliz w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/OK4rqs     
    
    
    I'm at Excellent Dumpling House w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/PZfErw     
    
    
    I'm at Santos Party House for Ssion, House of Ladosha, TEETH, Sasha Gothard and 4 more w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/PFbALh     
    
    
    Going super girly for afternoon coffee #coffee #nyc #polkadots #pink http://instagr.am/p/QAdqarReYq/     
    
    
    Here for a talk with @metropolismag (@ Carl Hansen & Son) http://4sq.com/SQ9NSm     
    
    
    @steelcase media:scape at UCLA, featured in @MetropolisMag pic.twitter.com/50QigUyn    
    
    
    I am always impressed with Perkins+Will projects RT @perkinswill_LAO: That's our project looking good :)    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan whoever told you that is a dirty liar. No mail or packages yet. FedEx/UPS/USPS?    
    
    
    I just reached Level 6 of the "Hot Tamale" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 25 different Mexican Restaurants! http://4sq.com/PaRiqI     
    
    
    fuckyeahsheltie: Shelties on treadmills! http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUJxdHD     
    
    
    Watching 30 Rock: Liz Lemon's Flashbacks on @hulu: http://www.hulu.com/watch/316076     
    
    
    GIF love: 33 Infomercial Characters Who Need To Get Their Shit Together http://www.buzzfeed.com/mattbellassai/51-infomercial-characters-who-need-to-get-their-sh-6z51 … via @buzzfeed @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    I wish regular hospitals looked like this! :: Most Colorful Children's Hospitals From Around The World http://www.buzzfeed.com/txblacklabel/most-colorful-childrens-hospitals-from-around-the-28m7 … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan KITTEHS!!! I'm watching AnimalPlanet's live broadcast on @Ustream! Come join me http://ustre.am/OsFM     
    
    
    Street art in Brooklyn #brooklyn #nyc #streetart #kfc http://instagr.am/p/QN3ODfxebR/     
    
    
    Photo: Street art in Brooklyn #brooklyn #nyc #streetart #kfc (Taken with Instagram) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUOpDYt     
    
    
    @UncleSophie I haven't seen you in forever. When are you free this week? cc: @dryerdoor @acesandrum @twoshots    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan The things you miss by not living here.    
    
    
    An Experimental New Starbucks Store: Tiny, Portable, And Hyper Local http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1670889  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    Dyn Inc Office Tour http://myturnstone.com/blog/dyn-inc-office-tour/#.UGm0oOdAcCI.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I just ousted autumn l. as the mayor of Café Orwell on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/2GXiQP     
    
    
    @AH_Ethan This lamp next to me is furry. It's making me uncomfortable.    
    
    
    Time Management: Break Your Workday Into Four-Hour &quot;Work Flows&quot; - @Lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5948175/break-your-workday-into-four+hour-work-flows …    
    
    
    I'm at Pho Grand Vietnamese Restaurant (New York, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/QI5nQO     
    
    
    Coworking Spaces: What You Can Expect http://myturnstone.com/blog/coworking-spaces-what-you-can-expect/#.UGyB-ciNLDI.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    No matter how clearly I state my name at coffee shops, they always get it wrong. I end up with a strippers name on my coffee cup.    
    
    
    @twoshots Oh yes.    
    
    
    Moar coffee (@ The West) http://4sq.com/T1s9zG     
    
    
    So muddy. Good for pups, not good for shoes (@ McCarren Dog Park) http://4sq.com/QQvSnt     
    
    
    Target Plaza Commons: Not your average break room | http://StarTribune.com  http://www.startribune.com/business/172360021.html …    
    
    
    Design a Space. Win a Chair!  |  Steelcase Store http://lnkd.in/uq-R7G     
    
    
    Twitter Grows Up: Tour the New Office http://www.inc.com/april-joyner/twitter-new-san-francisco-office.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    Inside the Latest Office-Design Craze: Hot Desking http://www.inc.com/flash-steinbeiser/latest-office-design-craze-hot-desking.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    30 Rock: Celebrate Tonight's Return of 30 Rock by Watching Every TGS Sketch Ever Mentioned - @Jezebel http://jezebel.com/5949039/celebrate-tonights-return-of-30-rock-by-watching-every-tgs-sketch-ever-mentioned …    
    
    
    Midday museum visit (@ The Metropolitan Museum of Art w/ 28 others) http://4sq.com/QPCijg     
    
    
    I'm at Cloud City on the Met Roof (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/UorEqu     
    
    
    After dog park romps, pups get tuckered out http://instagr.am/p/Qa6UJPxeSb/     
    
    
    Photo: After dog park romps, pups get tuckered out (Taken with Instagram) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUjF-Am     
    
    
    I'm at Custom Wine Bar (Brooklyn, New York) http://4sq.com/ST8277     
    
    
    I'm at Barcade w/ @msrachelmarie @hotlead http://4sq.com/WBroBK     
    
    
    Steelcase Store, Turnstone Introduce 3D Office Design Tool « CBS Detroit http://cbsloc.al/RdAuRz  @myturnstone    
    
    
    I love when they play Cesaria Evora (@ Boulevard Cafe w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/QhYDXk     
    
    
    Ralph Lauren says "plus size". I see normal beautiful girl: Stunning Photos Of Plus-Size Model Robyn Lawley - @Jezebel http://jezebel.com/5950621/stunning-photos-of-plus+size-swimwear-model-robyn-lawley/gallery/ …    
    
    
    Improving Workspace for Business Travel http://myturnstone.com/blog/improving-workspace-for-business-travel/#.UHZiSnt1Wyg.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Check out "Digital DUMBO's dd:SOCIAL -  A Search for Real Life Presented by Bing" http://ddsocialbing-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    @AmandaKRue I met you at @DigitalDUMBO a while ago...I'm planning on going to the Bing one next week! See you there?    
    
    
    @AmandaKRue No worries! I'll see you next time!    
    
    
    23 Reasons Why “Hocus Pocus” Is The Best Halloween Movie Of All Time http://www.buzzfeed.com/daves4/reasons-why-hocus-pocus-is-the-best-halloween-mo … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    It's a Labyrinth kind of night. David Bowies bulge and all that    
    
    
    Reading Chuck Anderson of NoPattern Meets Turnstone’s Paper Table on @designmilk http://design-milk.com/chuck-anderson-of-nopattern-meets-turnstones-paper-table/ …    
    
    
    Photographing a party (@ Dark Horse) http://4sq.com/QYrthS     
    
    
    I just reached Level 9 of the "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 40 different coffee shops! http://4sq.com/Tkhr85     
    
    
    @AH_Ethan I want winter snuggles already    
    
    
    Long distance relationships are rough. But the hard times are worth it when you have the one.    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan YAY!!! So what days are you doing again?    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan Get the ticket as early as possible for Thursday evening, and late Monday night. So excited!!!    
    
    
    Solar Power for your Workspace http://myturnstone.com/blog/solar-power-for-your-workspace/#.UHwwn7BW2zk.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan How'd you hear about her? She's good    
    
    
    Busy day. My team is coming in from Michigan for a couple days @myturnstone (@ Steelcase) http://4sq.com/RCee3L     
    
    
    5 Reasons People Fail (& What to Do Instead) http://www.inc.com/geoffrey-james/5-reasons-people-fail-what-to-do-instead.html … via @Inc @Carly_Johnston    
    
    
    Featured Story: Scout Branding @scoutbranding http://myturnstone.com/blog/featured-story-scout-branding/#.UH8cr59AGTk.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Team dinner @myturnstone (@ Landmarc) http://4sq.com/TdcYcH     
    
    
    I just ousted @dreys as the mayor of Steelcase WorkLife Center on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/r3eYhs     
    
    
    Follow lots of people and unfollow the inactives using Tweepi's geeky Twitter tools. http://tweepi.com/?3     
    
    
    I'm at Duravit NYC w/ @hotlead http://4sq.com/RFF4Z4     
    
    
    Forget Work-Life Balance:  It's Time for Work-Life Blend - Forbes http://onforb.es/TBX2LM     
    
    
    I'm at The Counting Room w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/Pgv8Jw     
    
    
    New gay bar by the same people that did Sugarland (@ This N That w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Ve8H4r     
    
    
    I'm at Cup w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/UjEsgG     
    
    
    Brunch with the boys (@ Westville East w/ @nathan_lacy) http://4sq.com/RagqlL     
    
    
    I'm at Ricky's (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/VfGMB6     
    
    
    I'm at Beacon's Closet (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/VfNs2e     
    
    
    Bacon the dog is bacon for Halloween! #baconbklynparty http://instagr.am/p/RBsBWjxebe/     
    
    
    @UncleSophie It was great seeing you! It was crazy there...thanks for the awesome table, that was bomb of you. Lets hang soon.    
    
    
    @cr_snake_bacon Bacon is meat candy    
    
    
    Bacon is tired #baconbklynparty http://instagr.am/p/RB1BVhReVE/     
    
    
    I'm at Steelcase (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/PqJQOo     
    
    
    Featured Story: Klout http://myturnstone.com/blog/featured-story-klout/#.UIgGBvL76T0.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Designer Creates Typographical Jokes, To Humor Fellow Designers - http://DesignTAXI.com  http://shar.es/chKZN  via @sharethis @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    I'm at Brooklyn Brewery (Brooklyn, NY) http://4sq.com/PVzx4H     
    
    
    I unlocked the “Zombie Swarm” badge on @foursquare for checking in with a crowd on Halloween! Gangnam Style galore. http://4sq.com/Sf8hgL     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Halloween 2012” badge on @foursquare! Has anyone seen my Honey Boo Boo mask? http://4sq.com/RTfNLA     
    
    
    Burlesque! Tim Burton (@ Matchless w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/RTfL6q     
    
    
    Inside the Offices of Meetup http://myturnstone.com/blog/inside-the-offices-of-meetup/#.UI7lp3uSpO4.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Photo: Halloween : Lady Rainicorn and Lord Monichromicorn #AdventureTime #CartoonNetwork (at Midnight Radio) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxWFaJ7D     
    
    
    Lots of debris in the street and it is still very windy and wet, but the worst is over #brooklyn #sandynyc #sandy #hurricane    
    
    
    Everyone, Don't Worry, THE PONIES ARE OKAY - Probably my favorite part of watching the storm coverage... @msrachelmarie http://tmblr.co/ZczZutWHZ37Q     
    
    
    Photoset: Jetblue has put together an apologetic yet patient-sounding explanation for all the a-holes who... http://tmblr.co/ZczZutWHP2g4  @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    The servers are down because of flooding but SOOO freakin glad I can still get @Jezebel updates thanks to @tumblr. Keep it comin!    
    
    
    Havin some drinks! You should meet us, just hop on the subw...oh wait...@dryerdoor (@ The Levee w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/TUUxK9     
    
    
    Post Sandy drinks with @hotlead and @ah_ethan (@ Harefield Road w/ @hotlead) http://4sq.com/VCluxU     
    
    
    I'm at Legion w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/SbmFU2     
    
    
    I'm at Duck Duck (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/Sbp4Og     
    
    
    @msrachelmarie I immediately thought of you!! Girls night with wine and that movie, yes? Text me! Xoxox    
    
    
    It is 2012. The dumb blonde jokes need to stop. Kthxbai    
    
    
    Watch: MTA walkthrough in flooded NYC subway station http://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch/?id=50134223n … via @cbsnews    
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: Greenbiz http://myturnstone.com/blog/customer-spotlight-greenbiz/#.UJFkzO6jcxY.twitter … via @myturnstone @greenbiz    
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Ghoul Night” badge on @foursquare for celebrating Halloween on a school night! http://4sq.com/TnDHgs     
    
    
    How Creatives Inspire Innovation and Stay Productive http://myturnstone.com/blog/how-creatives-inspire-innovation-and-stay-productive/#.UJKfREEvhk8.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    There is a line of cars abandoned because people are trying to get gas from the station two blocks away #sandy http://4sq.com/VgljNi     
    
    
    There are at least 50 cars waiting in line for gas at the corner of Bushwick ave and Metropolitan ave in Brooklyn #sandy    
    
    
    @msrachelmarie Sounds good! I will be around    
    
    
    Dark chocolate stout #brooklyn #brooklynbrewery #newyork @ Brooklyn Brewery http://instagr.am/p/Ri68wAReSu/     
    
    
    Old Rasputin at the Wythe Hotel. I love this man cc: @ah_ethan #fb    
    
    
    Too chilly for southern blood. He borrowed my sparkly scarf cc: @ah_ethan pic.twitter.com/2ATFyjIX    
    
    
    Such a puss “@AH_Ethan: “@Kbedosky: Too chilly for southern blood. He borrowed my sparkly scarf pic.twitter.com/2ATFyjIX” yea. Its 48 degrees!”    
    
    
    Angry southern face. Too cold for this Georgia boy #georgia #savannah #brooklyn #newyork #wythehotel http://instagr.am/p/RjQ5pGxeVj/     
    
    
    Here Are MTA Photos of Flooded Subway Tunnels Under the East River http://updates.gawker.com/post/34882103114/here-are-mta-photos-of-flooded-subway-tunnels-under-the …    
    
    
    Watch Bill O'Reilly's totally condescending video about single female voters. http://www.slate.com/blogs/xx_factor/2012/11/01/bill_o_reilly_on_single_women_voters_hot_good_at_costumes_not_too_smart.html?utm_source=tw&utm_medium=sm&utm_campaign=button_chunky … via @doublexmag    
    
    
    Fun.: Carry On [OFFICIAL VIDEO]: http://youtu.be/q7yCLn-O-Y0  via @youtube @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    New colors on my Twitter! All shiny and fancy now    
    
    
    Just signed up for @Newsle - check out my profile and follow your friends in the news! http://newsle.com/kbedosky     
    
    
    Your Car: The Future of Connected Health?  - http://www.xconomy.com/san-francisco/2012/11/05/your-car-the-future-of-connected-health/ … via Shareaholic    
    
    
    "I believe that when people have control over their physical space, it empowers them to take more risks...” http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1671050     
    
    
    HubSpot hits 100m  - http://www.xconomy.com/boston/2012/11/05/hubspot-hits-100m-raised-moves-closer-to-ipo-or-acquisition/ … via Shareaholic    
    
    
    Me and @AH_Ethan in #nyc http://instagr.am/p/RqOR0uxeYY/     
    
    
    Photo: Me and @AH_Ethan in #nyc http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxWgJPsF     
    
    
    I wîśh my hair was this long always #gettingwiggywithit #wigs #halloween http://instagr.am/p/RqOl1exeYo/     
    
    
    My mom drew a cartoon of NY state after the hurricane. Complete with a towel wrapped on its "head" http://instagr.am/p/RtD4pgReei/     
    
    
    The Empire State Building is lit up blue! #Election #Obama2012 pic.twitter.com/nFn5WvXO    
    
    
    Empire State Building is all blue! #obama2012 #election #nyc #brooklyn http://instagr.am/p/Rtz9MFxeZd/     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "I Voted 2012" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/RHG3cB     
    
    
    As Per Tradition, Election Results Officially Certified With Two Barks Of Approval From Electoral Collie http://onion.com/Twtm4l  @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    FINALLY!! L Train Back After Hurricane Sandy http://huff.to/Rmgs9a  via @HuffPostNY    
    
    
    New York bagels are the best bagels #NYC #brooklyn    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Must be the water. Speaking of! Is your power back on?    
    
    
    Snl: Mokiki Is Manhattan’s Most Eligible Zombie Bachelor - @Jezebel http://jezebel.com/5959556/mokiki-is-manhattans-most-eligible-zombie-bachelor …    
    
    
    Sexual Assault Survivors At Amherst College Speak Out With 'It Happens Here' Photo Series http://huff.to/RuOjwK  via @HuffPostCollege    
    
    
    Some good advice that I agree with: 4 Tips for Finding a Job in Your Niche  http://mashable.com/2012/11/11/job-seeking-niche/ … via @mashable @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    Good for job hunting as well as strengthening profesh networks: Are You Networking With The Right People?  http://aol.it/W3wkgK  via @aoljobs    
    
    
    Watch Mitt Romney's Facebook Likes Decrease in Real Time http://disappearingromney.com/     
    
    
    Veteran's Day: Dogs Welcoming Soldiers Home (VIDEO) http://huff.to/RxEWMJ  via @HuffPostComedy    
    
    
    Scaredy Dogs: 16 Pooches Who Need A Lesson In Bravery (VIDEOS) http://huff.to/XCbUAp  via @HuffPostComedy    
    
    
    Eliminate Your Keyboard and Mouse with LeapMotion http://myturnstone.com/blog/eliminate-your-keyboard-and-mouse-with-leapmotion/#.UKOwsnsad-o.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I hate Wednesdays more than Mondays    
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: RocketSpace http://myturnstone.com/blog/customer-spotlight-rocketspace/#.UKPqrx0UzE4.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Pets in the Office http://myturnstone.com/blog/pets-in-the-office/#.UKZZq1WQxpU.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    My #kloutscore is up to 56! http://klout.com  @klout    
    
    
    "Sex scandals are like Jewish New Yorkers. Eventually they all make their way to Florida" - Seth Myers on @nbcsnl    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan I ❤ bad lip reading! Have you gotten my texts? Service is spotty here    
    
    
    It is 22 degrees right now, and it feels fabulous @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    Comfy dog asleep with his paws in the air #dogslife #newyork #thanksgiving #binghamton #dog #sheltie http://instagr.am/p/SR5vb3ReT3/     
    
    
    #holidays #decorations #suburbs #newyork #joy #red http://instagr.am/p/ST6MWYxeb5/     
    
    
    3 shelties in the house for #thanksgiving (@ Vestal, NY) [pic]: http://4sq.com/SY8ZM4     
    
    
    Ace was licking dirty dishes in the dishwasher, and now his forehead is slippery and smells like turkey #dogsgiving #sheltie #dogs #fb    
    
    
    Dog snuggles with Ace, the adorable sheltie #dogslife #dogsgiving #thanksgiving http://instagr.am/p/SXNryyReYd/     
    
    
    After Thanksgiving Sale http://myturnstone.com/blog/after-thanksgiving-sale/#.UK_RNMlHzCI.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Devil dog Peaches #sheltie #dogs http://instagr.am/p/SZZMddReV6/     
    
    
    "Don't cook bacon naked" @hotlead magichat http://instagr.am/p/SZaFHyxeWx/     
    
    
    Shelties! Manny in the front, Peaches in the back #sheltie #dogs #adorable #animals http://instagr.am/p/SZ2uoyxedo/     
    
    
    Shannon Dougherty is doing shitty infomercials for http://schoolplease.com . Things aren't really working out for ya, you poor dear. Godspeed.    
    
    
    You and Bacon are hard to forget! Love, your frens @CapreeK @hotlead    
    
    
    Thank Gawd! RT: @HausofScarlett: I'm back! BOO! #FF @GlamTrotter @kmac23 @Kbedosky @daisynatuvsnurt @BettyAndBridget @LOrealParisUSA    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Swimmies" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different water spots! http://4sq.com/RaVrle     
    
    
    When Gangsters Tried to Extort Brooklyn Brewery http://www.inc.com/chris-beier-and-daniel-wolfman/brooklyn-brewery-co-founder-steve-hindy-extortion.html … via @Inc @ah_ethan    
    
    
    Why Tesla is like Amazon and Elon Musk like Jeff Bezos http://pandodaily.com/2012/12/02/why-tesla-is-like-amazon-and-elon-musk-like-jeff-bezos/ … via @pandodaily    
    
    
    Lessons For 2013: Business Wisdom From Airbnb To Zappos http://www.fastcompany.com/node/3002943  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Happy birthday @dryerdoor! (@ Greenwich Treehouse) http://4sq.com/QZxgpW     
    
    
    @NewMediaExpo Is there a way to add BusinessNext events to Sched? I'm going events from both expos    
    
    
    @NewMediaExpo Awesome, thanks!!    
    
    
    #adventuretime socks! Thanks @AH_Ethan :) http://instagr.am/p/S4VwGexea_/     
    
    
    Lighting party (@ iGuzzini North America) http://4sq.com/QLhFco     
    
    
    Hyperakt Studio Tour http://myturnstone.com/blog/hyperakt-studio-tour/#.UMKnlgk6ZVA.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    OMG where am I (@ 341 Scholes w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/VwkIlv     
    
    
    Photo: Trying to make the bed and Ace wouldn’t move. #dog #aceface #williamsburg #newyork #brooklyn http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxZ1slKf     
    
    
    I don't know why I love this so much cc: @nathan_lacy http://instagr.am/p/TEwG3WxeXS/     
    
    
    Photo: New winter jacket from my mom #winter http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxZ5IhJ8     
    
    
    @nathan_lacy poor little baybays    
    
    
    Whiteboards for Any Office Environment http://myturnstone.com/blog/whiteboards-for-any-office-environment/#.UMdKee9BNeY.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Photo: Engagement ring :) Coordinates of where we first kissed, and what he said to me @AH_Ethan http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxZADJD8     
    
    
    I just unlocked the 'Be Robin Hood #121212concert' badge for showing my support for Sandy relief efforts! http://4sq.com/SRBNIi     
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: Interaction Associates http://myturnstone.com/blog/customer-spotlight-interaction-associates/#.UMkmqCXsXB8.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I'm sick for the 2nd time in 3 weeks. My body can't handle radical temperature changes #seasons #winter #newyork #weather    
    
    
    LiveStream FTW (@ 121212 The Concert For Sandy Relief - Live Simulcast Viewing w/ @nathan_lacy @hotlead) http://4sq.com/UEoys3     
    
    
    I'm excited to try the alarm function with @songza...waking up to awesome playlists every day of the week!    
    
    
    @maryanntran are you still in town? And if so, are you going to the @projectivenyc holiday party tonight?    
    
    
    I just ousted @dchristien as the mayor of Azure Natural & Organic Foods on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/h9KuhX     
    
    
    ewwwww RT @Gothamist Pepsi And Lay's Team Up To Create "Cola Chicken" Flavored Potato Chip http://gothamist.com/2012/12/14/pepsi_and_lays_teaming_up_to_make_c.php …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Herbivore” badge on @foursquare for checking in at vegetarian spots! Vegan cupcakes for all! http://4sq.com/W6qIrl     
    
    
    I'm at The Triple Crown Ale House & Restaurant (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/WbDbtC     
    
    
    I'm at Therapy NYC (New York, NY) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/T1rL8R     
    
    
    Gay cowboy bar. You can't make this up. (@ Flaming Saddles Saloon w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/T1sUNz     
    
    
    "The gym is gay breakfast" - Rob #fb    
    
    
    I'm at Bar-tini Ultra Lounge (New York, NY) w/ 12 others http://4sq.com/UJe4d5     
    
    
    I'm pretty sure I've eaten my body weight in homemade toffee and yummy holiday treats.    
    
    
    Bacon dog snuggles pic.twitter.com/NuQyaz31    
    
    
    Photo: Bacon snuggles #holidays #party #dog #instagram http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxZVPGg0     
    
    
    @brunning I believe I met you at Kimberlys apartment in October. I had a question for you. Could you DM me? Thanks in advance!    
    
    
    @brunning Can you follow me so I can respond?...thanks!    
    
    
    Why have FOUR subscription cards in one magazine? Print media may be in trouble, but c'mon now.    
    
    
    Building a healthier workplace with the help of the e-crowd http://gu.com/p/3chjt/tw  via @guardian @OpenIDEO    
    
    
    3D printer printer pop up shop (@ 3DEA: 3D Holiday Pop Up Store w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/Yh4OSD     
    
    
    I'm at Fresh & Co (New York, NY) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/WmtUv7     
    
    
    This is the web right now - The Oatmeal http://theoatmeal.com/comics/state_web_winter_2012 … via @Oatmeal    
    
    
    Interview with Rand Fishkin on Failing Smart http://myturnstone.com/blog/interview-with-rand-fishkin-on-failing-smart/#.UNINFuurv7M.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    There is a @iHollaback holiday party at Littlefield in BK tonight! Get on your dancin shoes for a funky dance party cc: @Jezebel    
    
    
    With the @ihollaback crew (@ Littlefield for Hollaback's Holladay Party + more) http://4sq.com/VQTDJS     
    
    
    Made friends with the bartender. New favorite joint in this area! (@ 4th Avenue Pub) http://4sq.com/UOHJR5     
    
    
    Day bow bow @nathan_lacy #fb    
    
    
    I just reached Level 3 of the "Warhol" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 10 different art galleries! http://4sq.com/WzvgmC     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “City of Lakes” Minneapolis city badge on @foursquare! Is that a dove crying? http://4sq.com/Wzveej     
    
    
    Photo: Tom Dixon candle holders at Gather restaurant #mpls #minneapolis #minnesota #twincities #art... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxZ-L1yu     
    
    
    Photo: Crabby kitten face #ingrid #cat #kitten #minnesota #minneapolis #holidays http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxa2BEGY     
    
    
    Photo: Dog snuggles and Perry Mason #holidays #dog #aceface #home #minnesota #minneapolis http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxa3yKUf     
    
    
    @dryerdoor Agreed. Hopefully mr douche isn't lurking about with his gf's dog.    
    
    
    Cornell research shows bystander intervention works. Pledge to be a better bystander with @ihollaback today: http://bit.ly/UFSEj0     
    
    
    UGH. Police in Swaziland Say Miniskirts and Bare Midriffs Make Rape Easier - Global - The Atlantic Wire http://www.theatlanticwire.com/global/2012/12/police-swaziland-say-miniskirts-and-bare-midriffs-make-rape-easier/60297/ …    
    
    
    Let the "oh crapo" jokes begin: Mormon Senator Arrested for Drunk Driving, Bad Jokes Follow http://www.theatlanticwire.com/politics/2012/12/mormon-senator-mike-crapo-gets-arrested-drunk-driving-bad-jokes-follow/60290/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Christmas pup! Not happy about it #christmas #reindeer #dogs #dogslife #holidays #minnesota... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxa761mj     
    
    
    Photo: Charlie the booze hound #beer #dogs #holidays #cute http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxa77xL2     
    
    
    Photo: Jack #dog #dogsofinstagram #pets #cute #sheltie http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxa8fRdH     
    
    
    Ask Lifehacker: Is Cheap Furniture Worth Buying? - @Lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5970618/is-cheap-furniture-worth-buying …    
    
    
    Personal Finance: The Comfort Principle: Spend Money Where You Spend Your Time - @Lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5857142/the-comfort-principle-spend-money-where-you-spend-your-time …    
    
    
    Even Better Than iPhone 5: An iPhone With The 1986 Mac OS http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1669156  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    Photo: Such dorks!! W/ @msrachelmarie (at Broadway Pizza) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxaVGCVt     
    
    
    Photo: In the limo for Mikaelas birthday http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxaVjOBg     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Fixer Upper" badge on @foursquare for checking in at hardware stores! Tool Time! http://4sq.com/XbCXTP     
    
    
    Photo: NYE outfit preview. Lots of sparkles! #NYE #nyc #brooklyn #newyears http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxaevPAr     
    
    
    Photo: No more Minnesota license for me! Bittersweet transition to a New York drivers license. #newyork... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxaf1N0u     
    
    
    Happy NYE!! @hotlead, @nathan_lacy (@ Tutu's w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/UhAG54     
    
    
    20 of the Most Memorable Marketing Moments in 2012 [INFOGRAPHIC] http://blog.hubspot.com/blog/tabid/6307/bid/33896/20-of-the-Most-Memorable-Marketing-Moments-in-2012-INFOGRAPHIC.aspx … via @HubSpot    
    
    
    Car Sharing Catches On as Zipcar Sells to Avis http://nyti.ms/U9j3YO     
    
    
    I just reached Level 3 of the "Jetsetter" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 10 different airports! http://4sq.com/UwRZiB     
    
    
    Las Vegas!!! (@ Rio All-Suite Hotel & Casino w/ 18 others) http://4sq.com/WwaAtO     
    
    
    New media expo 2013 - keynote by Scott Monty of Ford (@ New Media Expo 2013 w/ 11 others) http://4sq.com/RAuXc6     
    
    
    Full day of events tomorrow! #nmx #lasvegas    
    
    
        
    
    
    Improve Communication Through Office Design http://myturnstone.com/blog/improve-communication-through-office-design/#.UOsScP5foNU.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    At a panel for #productivity at #NMX -- gonna learn some tips for blogging    
    
    
    #NMX is trending on @twitter #lasvegas    
    
    
    #Productivity panel shout-out @TMNinja @MikeVardy @InkedMN @LeoWid #NMX    
    
    
    Listening to @Scobleizer speaking at #NMX...such a nice personable guy!    
    
    
    I'm sitting behind someone that works for @HuffingtonPost. Gotta love spotting big media sites at conferences #NMX    
    
    
    @mikevardy It was my favorite panel so far....question for you: What is your ratio of writing vs reading for blog?    
    
    
    @ramonray Just saw you on stage at the #nmx keynote with Leo Laporte...had no idea you were here! I write for @MyTurnstone    
    
    
    @ramonray If you have a moment to say hey, that would be great. If not during the conference, perhaps back in NYC?    
    
    
    I think that @NewMediaExpo could be longer...5 days instead of 3 with workshops and special consulting sessions with professionals #NMX    
    
    
    Just downloaded the @bufferapp after seeing @LeoWid speak today at #NMX. Can't wait to start sharing!    
    
    
    Al Roker: 'I Pooped In My Pants' at the White House http://buff.ly/UDvV9Y     
    
    
    Just downloaded @rapportive. It shows details about contacts in Gmail (twitter, facebook, etc). Super nice feature!    
    
    
    I'm at Ginseng II Korean BBQ (Las Vegas, NV) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/WrgOKC     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Porky” badge on @foursquare for checking in to barbecue spots! Brisket all around! http://4sq.com/WrgMT2     
    
    
    I'm at Koi Night Club (Las Vegas, NV) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/XGIy4O     
    
    
    Eyyyy sexay ladies (@ Treasures) http://4sq.com/TI9NbO     
    
    
    @ryanniemeyer @rigoneri @keithentzeroth How do I get in touch with you about a possible interview? My email is krista.bedosky@gmail.com    
    
    
    @rigoneri @ryanniemeyer Just emailed this guy over here--->@keithentzeroth Feel free to take a look at the message I sent to him    
    
    
    When Culture Fails http://myturnstone.com/blog/when-culture-fails/#.UPAyq-W5Jlw.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I'm at World of Beer (Savannah, GA) http://4sq.com/VRtJcU     
    
    
    Photo: So blue! The background looks mad fake (even though its not) @ethan_waterman #savannah #hangfire... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbblWz8     
    
    
    Awful: Reddit co-founder Aaron Swartz commits suicide - http://NYPOST.com  http://nyp.st/WO220J  via @nypost    
    
    
    Photo: Doggie fun-day in the park #flawlesswallace #savannah #georgia @albatrosschaos (at Forsyth Park) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbhAW5B     
    
    
    Photo: Secret to a good life (at Forsyth Park Cafe) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbhdl8g     
    
    
    Inspiration always hits me in the middle of the night.    
    
    
    Video: theclearlydope: WORTH SEEING: Tina Fey and Amy Poehler 2013 Golden Globes Opening Monologue. via... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbkSfft     
    
    
    Date with my honey (@ The Distillery) http://4sq.com/X9s6V4     
    
    
    Photo: After dinner drinks #fiance #savannah #georgia #thedistillery @ethan_waterman (at The Distillery) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbn-R8n     
    
    
    Charlie Kelly's Dating Profile - Dennis: Let's talk about your likes and dislikes. How about your favorite fo… http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbpxlYU     
    
    
    bellesandwhistles: Phoebe Wahl http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbpyi36     
    
    
    “Vegas should have a casino called “Toon Town” and have it look like the sets of Roger rabbit!” - (via nickmc… http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbpzaO_     
    
    
    lomographicsociety:Introducing the New Lomography Smartphone Film ScannerWe are proud to introduce the latest… http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbq6Xoh     
    
    
    Proxibid: Creating a collaborative culture - Silicon Prairie News http://buff.ly/11n3Cyf     
    
    
    Photo: Ethan’s face of approval (or so he says…) #WOB #worldofbeer #savannah #georgia @ethan_waterman http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbsWv8Y     
    
    
    Photo: 100 beers at World of Beer - Savannah! The milestone was celebrated with a Brooklyn Brown Ale... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbsm3yb     
    
    
    Photo: Grumpy Ethan #grumpycat (at World of Beer) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxbswB2e     
    
    
    @Mr_McFly True story! :)    
    
    
    Photo: laughingsquid: Dogwool, Dog Owners Wearing Sweaters Knit Out of Their Dog’s Fur That’s one way to use... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxbw0xmj     
    
    
    Collaboration Tools for Working Online (and Offline!) http://myturnstone.com/blog/collaboration-tools-for-working-online-and-offline/#.UPgmBqSeoSo.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I just reached Level 3 of the "Bookworm" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 10 different bookstores or libraries http://4sq.com/XhUioP     
    
    
    It's different now...and it's a licensed apple retailer now #scad #art #artsupplies (@ Ex Libris Bookstore) http://4sq.com/XhUiF3     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Campus Explorer” badge on @foursquare for checking in to 10 different places on campus! http://4sq.com/XhUhBe     
    
    
    "I'm a fiddler crab! Shoot me! It's fiddler crab season!" Ethan (@ Fiddler's Crab House w/ @ah_ethan) http://4sq.com/WbR9YC     
    
    
    Photo: Savannah happy face :) #savannah #georgia (at The Mos Eisley Cantina) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc1PdZ1     
    
    
    Photo: My mom and Ace and Jack #minneapolis #minnesota #dogs #family #fun #shelties #shetlandsheepdog http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc1QY1g     
    
    
    Photo: Fun in the park with a corgi #flawlesswallace #savannah #georgia @ethan_waterman @albatrosschaos http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc1Utif     
    
    
    Photo: Butter spray. Seriously. #thisiswhyamericaisfat #lazy (at Kroger) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc4yctz     
    
    
    Photo: Afternoon walk in Forsyth park #savannah #georgia #spanishmoss #park #nature #south #southern (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc8cIxE     
    
    
    Abe's on Lincoln...get it? GET IT?!?! (@ Abe's on Lincoln) http://4sq.com/13SHOcJ     
    
    
    Photo: Last night at pedicab for @ethan_waterman! #savannah #pedicab http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcB1tnU     
    
    
    Goodbye party for @ethan_waterman! 8 years!!! (@ Savannah Pedicab) http://4sq.com/W829s0     
    
    
    Photo: Ethan and Agnes on his last night of pedicab #savannah #georgia #pedicab #ridelocal @ethan_waterman... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcBmaUX     
    
    
    I nominate @WeACTIowa for a Shorty Award in #education because they support young minds in theater http://shortyawards.com?category=education&screen_name=weactiowashortyawards.com/?category=educ …    
    
    
    When is @SlutWalkNYC 2013?? Lets get it organized!    
    
    
    RUMOR: Apple Will Release THREE New iPhones This Year http://www.businessinsider.com/rumor-apple-will-release-three-new-iphones-this-year-2013-1?0=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    What do you think of "Google goggles?" Ridiculous or a new technology win? http://soc.li/oufjEXO     
    
    
    Photo: At least it is sunny….#goodluckwiththat #minnesota #minnesota http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcK00qW     
    
    
    I'm looking for a new job for the end of February, preferably in the #socialmedia and/or #design community    
    
    
    Furniture or Booze? How Startups Spend Their Money - Businessweek via @BW http://buswk.co/WEv7h4     
    
    
    Hey Baby game - This game is a first person shooter designed to simulate the day to day life of a woman tryin… http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcTGez0     
    
    
    9 Things Women Have Been Deemed "Too Pretty" For http://www.buzzfeed.com/annanorth/8-things-women-have-been-deemed-too-pretty-for … via @buzzfeedshift    
    
    
    adubforeveryoung: My dad is going on and on about how wrong it is that women are going to be able to fight in… http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcUioNh     
    
    
    trans-par-en-cy: TRANSPARENT
not my gif, just my edit <3 http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcVOTm2     
    
    
    @Jmodio Saturday night    
    
    
    "Fucking fucks, NOT ducking ducks. I meant what I typed, you stupid phone.." - @jenbee Fucking straight.... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcVdMRn     
    
    
    Photo: poptech: Documenting the “Rise of the Reluctant Innovator” by Ken Banks (PopTech 2012) This... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcVeHAo     
    
    
    Finally here! #beer #craft #atlanta #littlefivepoints (@ The Porter Beer Bar w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/SOTJWl     
    
    
    Photo: This is what a $50 bottle of beer looks like. We found the Brooklyn black ops! #blackops... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcfRVB3     
    
    
    Photo: Brooklyn Black Ops! #brooklynbrewery #brooklyn #newyork #beer #craftbeer http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxcfhy_f     
    
    
    Photo: You’ll need the meds after eating vending machine tuna #roadtrip #gross (at Granville County Rest... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcioKzQ     
    
    
    Photo: Tristan and Fiona! Furry babies #siberianhuskies #dogs #dogsofinstagram (at Avant Apartment Homes) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxck-OL-     
    
    
    Photo: @ethan_waterman has arrived to #nyc! http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcnOSVx     
    
    
    Photo: Roomies! @ethan_waterman sleeping #roadtrip #nyc #brooklyn http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxcq8z2B     
    
    
    theroyaltenenbears: Window washers at a children’s hospital. http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcrRiWW     
    
    
    fuckyeah-nerdery: madamm:

What you know about rockin’ a wolf on your noggin?

What you know about wearin’ a … http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcrSEDe     
    
    
    inerdonthis: Last afternoon in town. Got to clean out the fridge. #gin

One of the best photo series from thi… http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxcrTd9J     
    
    
    @eagleone1776 If they are serving our country, they are not "girls". Have some respect cc: @Slate @saletan    
    
    
    Yet ANOTHER jerk blaming victims:  'Short skirts and high heels risk rape' warning lands male MP in sexism storm http://bit.ly/UuzXz7     
    
    
    "It's not personal...it's drag" @RuPaul #DragRace #fb    
    
    
    OMG tractors @BBC_TopGear @RichardHammond pic.twitter.com/PLwIjY6q    
    
    
    Looking for a new J-O-B in design and online media...any leads?    
    
    
    The unpacking is coming along. I finally have a bed that is off the floor. Officially adults! cc: @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    Photo: There was a marker next to the moving boxes and I couldn’t help myself #dirty #boxes #moving... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxczpPe3     
    
    
    I am so glad I am seeing more beat cops in my hood. It's a sketchy neighborhood #props #nypd #littlepuertorico #wiliamsburg #grahamave    
    
    
    Gays shouldn't marry because...they plan first? Bit of a shaky argument against gay marriage - "It is, to say… http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc-SWgo     
    
    
    Tappan Zee Bridge Falling Down? http://nymag.com/news/features/tappan-zee-bridge-2013-2/ … via @sharethis    
    
    
    theclearlydope: Meetings every Friday and Saturday night at your own home.
Invite list: Pets
Drink list: Wine… http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxc-ZEDR     
    
    
    Hey @MikeBloomberg, #streetharassment isn't a compliment and making NYC streets safe is YOUR JOB. http://bit.ly/VsBtRH  @iHollaback    
    
    
    Photo: Got our 7 foot-long shared desk set up! And his/hers chairs (his in black, mine in white). Also, we... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxd1mlfR     
    
    
    Photo: 3 shelves full of coffee mugs #overkill #coffee #love #joiningforces #movingintogether #brooklyn... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxd1vqqU     
    
    
    @call_me_salome Thanks! It's going to make me very productive.    
    
    
    Photo: Tshirt for sale at a rest stop in the south. Can’t get more redneck than that! #redneck #south... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxd2Z-xT     
    
    
    This #superbowlsunday, I am going to be watching closely for offensive commercials. Let's see how far they go this year!    
    
    
    Insane party! (@ Chrome Bags New York w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/11bFgsB     
    
    
    Photo: Chrome party in soho. Free beer and crazy schenanigans. #newyork #chrome #bikes #bikeculture (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxd6n2Vv     
    
    
    Photo: After too many Brooklyn Brewery beers @brooklynbrewery #brooklyn #beer (at Soft Spot Bar) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdBq_m7     
    
    
    @hotlead we miss you and Bacon!    
    
    
    Photo: Dawww @ethan_waterman #food #latenighteats #brooklyn #snacks http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdC5PtL     
    
    
    Wyoming rejects anti-discrimination bill - gaywrites: The Wyoming state senate on Thursday voted down a bill … http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdEIHyk     
    
    
    From BuzzFeed: A Photo of Hillary Clinton in Every Country She's Visited - Hil-dawg is pretty much the cooles… http://tmblr.co/ZDwl5tdEdIPl     
    
    
    RIP 30 Rock http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdGZDg4     
    
    
    Photo: (via AP - Egypt ‘bodyguards’ take stand against sex assault) http://tmblr.co/ZDwl5tdGgise     
    
    
    Photo: thugzmansion: Happy Black History Month! Marsha P Johnson and why she rules She was... http://tmblr.co/ZDwl5tdHKLtD     
    
    
    Headed to Milford for the #SuperBowl (@ Grand Central Terminal w/ @ah_ethan) http://4sq.com/14JBkhE     
    
    
    Silicon Prairie! Want to win $20,000 worth of furniture for your small business office? Apply here: http://contest.myturnstone.com/     
    
    
    To My Male Relatives on Facebook Who ‘Like’ Sexism  | The Nation http://www.thenation.com/blog/172647/my-male-relatives-facebook-who-sexism …    
    
    
    Watch this very powerful video about Kenyan girls refusing to be cut. International Day of Zero Tolerance to … http://tmblr.co/ZDwl5tdPXLAb     
    
    
    Planning for Growth: When is it Time to Expand? http://myturnstone.com/blog/planning-for-growth-when-is-it-time-to-expand/#.URKYVvdiedw.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Postal Service to cut Saturday mail to trim costs http://bo.st/YCSysw  via @BostonDotCom    
    
    
    @Patrick_AE I'm pretty sure you confused the American electronic band that hasn't toured in ages with people that deliver secret sex toys    
    
    
    Photo: Soviet Russia represent. Rabbit fur hat #cccp #cold #russia http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdZaRM_     
    
    
    Photo: I can’t hear anything. This is a heavy duty #Russian hat. And Ethan is laughing at me. #soviet #hat... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxdZhNWM     
    
    
    Read my interview with Sarah Khan at NYU for @iHollaback! http://www.ihollaback.org/blog/2013/02/07/hollawho-meet-nyu/ …    
    
    
    Join @iHollaback in solidarity with #1billionrising, and tell off your harassers. Share your "Dear John" letter here: http://dearjohnlettershollaback.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    .@metropolismag event for #gamechangers #2013 (@ Vitra / Axor w/ @hotlead) http://4sq.com/Ye2Hdk     
    
    
    Photo: Bacon kisses! #brooklyn #bacon #bostonterrier #dogs #dogwalker #dogsofinstagram http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxde_Dhb     
    
    
    The main image is a same sex couple! HAAAA - To be happy, we must admit women and men aren't 'equal' http://fxn.ws/TF0VF4  via @fxnopinion    
    
    
    We braved the storm to get some beers!  #brrr #snow #blizzard #nemo @brooklynbrewery (@ Brooklyn Brewery) http://4sq.com/WJ6JMv     
    
    
    I love the pictures attached to this check in location. (@ Winter Storm Apocalypse: Nemo w/ @ah_ethan @joeyhodges) http://4sq.com/XYmiPO     
    
    
    Made friends with some Europeans. Having drinks! (at @wythehotel) http://4sq.com/WJAvR9     
    
    
    Brunch with @hotlead! #brunch #brooklyn #waffles #bloodys (@ Ba'sik) http://4sq.com/X0tCt0     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Century Club" badge for checking in at the same place over 100 days! http://4sq.com/X3CNcc     
    
    
    Photo: This was made from the #iMadeFace #app on #iPhone http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxe6UF94     
    
    
    Photo: Selfie of my new bangs! Static electricity is not my friend tonight. Need some product in this... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxeAJi99     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxeHAApb     
    
    
    Work til 6pm. #tgif (@ 195 Chrystie Street) http://4sq.com/ZwXEuJ     
    
    
    Crazy (@ Brooklyn Brewery w/ @ah_ethan) http://4sq.com/YMO9Sj     
    
    
    I just ousted @haulingoaks as the mayor of 195 Chrystie Street on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/d2kLne     
    
    
    @verymarykate impersonation on @RuPaulsDragRace! DYYYIIINNNGGGG #marykate #DragRace    
    
    
    "I think we have a slightly different aesthetic" #dragrace @RuPaulsDragRace @nathan_lacy #fb    
    
    
    Photo: People in my building have twisted senses of humor. There is a fake bird on top of the mirror in the... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxf3q1rG     
    
    
    Photo: Picture from my mom. Doggie adventures in MN! #minnesota #pups #shelties #shetlandsheepdog #dogs http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxf4x0jm     
    
    
    Photo: Doggies at the pet store all sleeping together. So cute! (at City Pups) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxf4xjyM     
    
    
    Photo: Happy kitty. My sisters fiancés cat #cat #kitty #catsofinstagram http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxf5o5_Q     
    
    
    Photo: Yay Karen and Stephen! Finally tied the knot :) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxfJbkNw     
    
    
    Photo: Miss Bacon playtime at the dog park #dogwalker #dogpark #dog #brooklyn #bostonterrier @hotlead (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxfOBJxL     
    
    
    I just ousted @junglerock as the mayor of Sara Delano Roosevelt Park‎ on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/5hFzow     
    
    
    Sheltie spotting in Soho! #shetlandsheepdog #sheltie #dog #fluffy #nyc #broadway #soho #newyorkcity http://instagr.am/p/Wf5mRbxeWd/     
    
    
    The background of my computer. It looks like the fox is stuck inside and is trying to adorably lick its… http://instagr.am/p/WlQ7RCReUO/     
    
    
    Photo: The background of my computer. It looks like the fox is stuck inside and is trying to adorably lick... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxfmVE3i     
    
    
    Vote for Minnetonka Center for the Arts to receive @LIVESTRONG community impact funding: http://vote.livestrong.org/130     
    
    
    That was fun! RT @pantone: Flex your brain today w/ @Lumosity's Color Matching Game: http://bit.ly/12x4KkO  via @MythBusters @Discovery    
    
    
    Photo: Poochie face #bacon #brooklyn http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxgH5BoI     
    
    
    SPOTTED: hunterdouglas in the April issue of @archdigest. Hunter Douglas is one of our exhibitors for… http://instagr.am/p/W4wKDlReTm/     
    
    
    Photo: SPOTTED: @HunterDouglas in the April issue of @archdigest. Hunter Douglas is one of our exhibitors... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxgJmuIi     
    
    
    Not as crowded as you might think (@ 2013 NYC St. Patrick's Day Parade w/ 326 others) http://4sq.com/111YXm0     
    
    
    Not as rowdy upstairs if you want to sit and drink. They have a decent Irish food menu. (@ The Perfect Pint) http://4sq.com/Zy6zIa     
    
    
    I'm at Barcade - @barcadebrooklyn (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/Z61pkm     
    
    
    I'm at Twenty Sided Store (Brooklyn, NY) http://4sq.com/ZIKdlT     
    
    
    Skee ball! (@ Full Circle Bar - @brewskeeball w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/WqszXF     
    
    
    Just played two and a half hours of #AdventureTime on my DS. My brain is filled with arcade sounds.    
    
    
    Finally getting back into exercising more...hopefully I'll be in full swing by the end of this upcoming week!    
    
    
    Late lunch (@ M Noodle Shop) http://4sq.com/15enPnv     
    
    
    Burlesque! (@ The Bell House - @bellhouseny for St. Patrick's Day for Sinners w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/1056EW2     
    
    
    @OyVeySophie ZOMG sounds delish    
    
    
    @OyVeySophie That's how I feel about Veselka pierogis. I could sustain on nothing but those for ever and ever    
    
    
    @OyVeySophie a restaurant crawl. Like a bar crawl but for fatties    
    
    
    @RTKLAssociates The changes to @Pinterest are very subtle, which is better than a huge overhaul IMO    
    
    
    Yummy vegan food for a late lunch (at @Teany_newyork) http://4sq.com/15wpt46     
    
    
    Trying to find an app - starting a website w/ partner, and need a way to store information & share brainstorming ideas & assign tasks    
    
    
    I'm looking for a new job in social media - furniture, design, interior design, architecture, and hospitality    
    
    
    It's one of those nights. A tired body, but an active brain.    
    
    
    Consider building a rocket ship to the moon. Rapists can't touch you on the moon. Not enough gravity #safetytipsforladies    
    
    
    Designing for Health: How Community Informs Critical Access Hospital Design http://shar.es/dmw5N  via @sharethis @contractmag    
    
    
    BDwest is one week away!: http://lnkd.in/ZF6Vmw     
    
    
    What is the best materials resource for interior designers and architects? Material Connexion is a good one... #interiordesign    
    
    
    Not just for walls, use in unexpected areas RT @GettysWorldwide: Hip interior design trends: Innovative wallpaper http://www.sheknows.com/home-and-gardening/articles/843909/hip-interior-design-trends-innovative-wallpaper …    
    
    
    Facebook Opens News Feed to Targeted Brand Posts http://mashable.com/2013/03/27/facebook-unpublished-page-posts/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    So nice, you won't have to buy twice :) RT @OutDesignGroup: Buy the best and you'll only buy one! #design #quotes #ODG #qualityfurniture    
    
    
    So cool! Love MakerBot RT @yvesbehar: Our OUYA @playouya console now 3-d printed by you! http://techcrunch.com/2013/03/27/makerbot-to-enable-gamers-to-3d-print-their-own-ouya-android-consoles/ …    
    
    
    Some days, all you want is a beer and The Muppets. Sounds like pure bliss.    
    
    
    Why does it take 15 minutes to find my bridesmaid dress? It's been at the store for weeks. Had an alteration appointment @davidsbridal    
    
    
    What's going on in the world today?! Crazy story - Mexican Vigilantes Seize Town, Arrest Police http://huff.to/14pMj1b  via @HuffPostWorld    
    
    
    My interview! - Interview with Stackify about Culture at Work http://myturnstone.com/blog/interview-with-stackify-about-culture-at-work/#.UVRmaoQzpJU.twitter … via @myturnstone @stackify    
    
    
    Mid-afternoon disco is the perfect pick-me-up    
    
    
    This weather is bellisimo!    
    
    
    Hospitality Products http://lnkd.in/2cPm3h     
    
    
    Friday night ritual (@ Brooklyn Brewery w/ 13 others) http://4sq.com/Zt8YBJ     
    
    
    "You like me, you really like me!" ethan_waterman practicing his acceptance speech http://instagram.com/p/XioAOZxebr/     
    
    
    I can't wait for April Fools to be over...@Google thinks they are so clever    
    
    
    Interior design job alert RT @EditorAtLarge: NYC: Suzanne Shaker Inc. is seeking an Interior Designer http://fb.me/25SENZLA7     
    
    
    Wish I could afford this event to see Michael Graves cc: @EditorAtLarge http://editoratlarge.com/interiordesignevents/12th-annual-mckim-lecture-michael-graves-a-grand-tour …    
    
    
    Office Furniture Designed To Spark Inspiring, Random Encounters http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1672225  via @FastCoDesign @Knoll_Inc    
    
    
    I love and hate kale chips. They smell gross but taste...good...I think?    
    
    
    Rough and Smooth - Tom Dixon’s New Line Of Massive, Monolithic Furniture http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1672230  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    @LeoJTravis10 The workaholic in me wants to get things done, and not root through April Fools news    
    
    
    They are a fabulous hospitality design firm...follow them! RT @sfadesign: Make sure to follow us on Pinterest! http://pinterest.com/sfadesign/boards/ …    
    
    
    Hotel design is changing to accomodate healthier lifestyles RT @RashanaZ: Adding Wellness to the Equation http://bit.ly/ZYJYGg     
    
    
    BDwest will be tweeting live starting Wednesday 4/3! Join the conversation by using #BDwest    
    
    
    Why architects must lead on sustainable design http://grn.bz/16F8yj3  #GrnBz via @GreenBiz @RTKLAssociates    
    
    
    It's been 3 years since I graduated from @SCADdotedu, and I still miss it #Savannah #Georgia #school #education #art #design #college    
    
    
    I am loving the @GenslerOnCities Gensler Design Forecast 2013 pdf - http://www.gensler.com/uploads/documents/Gensler_Design_Forecast_01_04_2013.pdf …    
    
    
    Avg is 5-6am...sheesh RT @PSFK When do top CEOs wake up? The @Guardian investigates: http://bit.ly/YQEGNm  #LPT #lifehacks    
    
    
    This is genius! Boulevard 41 Could Provide Pedestrian-Friendly Connection Between Broadway and Bryant Park -  http://blog.archpaper.com/wordpress/archives/57997 …    
    
    
    Can't wait to see the final result! : Thomas Leeser Designs a Hotel for Brooklyn8217;s BAM Cultural District -  http://blog.archpaper.com/wordpress/archives/55134 …    
    
    
    I really hope I go to #NeoCon13. It's design heaven! #Chicago    
    
    
    Yes, I did. No regrets. #GoBlue #Google #Chrome #extensions https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/gmail-blue/keiffooocjpcgkpojchelkgnjmmjlbgc …    
    
    
    Oldies! RT @moen: It's time for spring cleaning. What's your favorite cleaning music?    
    
    
    Photographs of darkened cities by Thierry Cohen: http://www.designboom.com/art/photographs-of-darkened-cities-by-thierry-cohen/#.UVtEv_Ok5SM.twitter …    
    
    
    Great choices! RT @designcalendar: Our Favorite Picks From @ADShow2013! - http://tinyurl.com/cvawuhj     
    
    
    I always leave with tons of info RT @aposhgirl: A4. Also, plan to have room for lots of literature on the trip home after attending a show.    
    
    
    Blog of the day: Hiring Mistakes and How to Recover http://myturnstone.com/blog/hiring-mistakes-and-how-to-recover/#.UVxCnJ0U1NQ.twitter …    
    
    
    New York City’s Central Park from above http://pinterest.com/pin/104779128803152721/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Wish I could do that! RT @hotlead: Urban planners battle on @simcity 6 to create the ultimate fake #metropolis, via @FastCompany #cities    
    
    
    Another blog post of mine! : Starting a New Company: Learn to Allocate Resources http://myturnstone.com/blog/starting-a-new-company-learn-to-allocate-resources/#.UV7l98ZAWQ8.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    @PucciniGroup @BoutiqueDesign @amoristofficiel That's a gorgeous outfit! #BDwest    
    
    
    This made me cackle RT @zkgraff: I think @KTrinaLynn may have coined a new word. She just said "glitterally" to @StacyGarciaInc #BDwest    
    
    
    @John_Rice__ It's the most adorable thing!    
    
    
    Stewie by Luca Nichetto for Foscarini http://media.designerpages.com/3rings/2013/04/08/stewie-by-luca-nichetto-for-foscarini/ … via @designerpages    
    
    
    My post! Adding Fun in the Office: A Look at Gaming Companies http://myturnstone.com/blog/adding-fun-in-the-office-a-look-at-gaming-companies/#.UWQxei_sYfk.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    The true value of engagement in Hospitality http://shar.es/dPgz0  via @sharethis    
    
    
    No event in NYC? Bummer. San Fran and London is super awesome though RT @Responsys26 Join us at Interact 2013 http://rpsys.co/L7     
    
    
    Business travel spending gains momentum as economy improves | News | Breaking Travel News http://www.breakingtravelnews.com/news/article/business-travel-spending-gains-momentum-as-economy-improves/#.UWSmE0FjNN8.twitter …    
    
    
    First BDwest in the Books - recap of @BDwestFair @Boutique Design http://boutiquedesign.com  http://bit.ly/YLGRCu     
    
    
    Hello everyone! Had to switch accounts (still on BDwest mode). Glad to be joining on my personal account! #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Any examples you can share? RT @AMStandard: @ecomod LOVE some of the reclaimed wood projects Im seeing out there #kbtribechat    
    
    
    So true! RT @Remodel_w_Feia: lighting/sustainability: Windows in design phase can help with light/heating consumption #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Awesome use of reclaimed wood! RT @ecomod: Heres a reclaimed wood island in a modern kitchen: http://pinterest.com/pin/182466222374863705/ … #kbtribechat    
    
    
    You too! RT @Stacy__Garcia: @kbedosky Good to see you here! #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Love @DesignSponge RT @AMStandard @ecomod Reclaimed shelving in kitchen&barn door+vintage sink http://bit.ly/XsF5VO  #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Twitter is acting very slow...so I'll see you all next week! Thanks for the chat #kbtribechat    
    
    
    @Remodel_w_Feia You too!  :) #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Have a good one! See you next time RT @AM_Fanelli: Great chat! This hour always goes too fast. Have a great week everyone! #kbtribechat    
    
    
    Hot Openings: Hotel Zetta debuts in San Francisco http://shar.es/JnCoE  via @HOTELSmagazine @sharethis    
    
    
    Hells yeah RT @hotlead: tonight #brooklyn #DBA #deathbyaudio #williamsburg http://t.thisismyjam.com/hotlead/_5ce52oq …    
    
    
    Paint my nails, or take a disco nap? Decisions, decisions...    
    
    
    I'm surprised it took me this long @foursquare #wine #friends @hotlead @ Custom Wine Bar http://instagram.com/p/X8X5gQxea0/     
    
    
    Little Gold show! W/ @hotlead @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8gtmHReXK/     
    
    
    Death by Audio @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8g_T4ReXn/     
    
    
    Show me those pearly whites #deathbyaudio @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8hkhkxeYY/     
    
    
    "Odd swan" Little Gold mascot @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8mCUbReeV/     
    
    
    Little Gold w/ @hotlead @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8meTkRee-/     
    
    
    Little Gold #music #brooklyn #show @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8rMsFxeWK/     
    
    
    Little Gold #music #brooklyn #show #band @ Death By Audio http://instagram.com/p/X8rX_5xeWb/     
    
    
    Pony tails and music stands    
    
    
    @HOTELSmagazine I love the articles you publish! About to tweet two more!    
    
    
    Eye for design - Hotel kitchens http://shar.es/J0xXs  via @sharethis @HOTELSmagazine    
    
    
    @WHotels names 2013 Designers of the Future http://shar.es/J0xsM  via @sharethis @HOTELSmagazine    
    
    
    90 million?! Holy cow RT ‏@electronista LinkedIn confirms $90 million deal to buy Pulse http://dlvr.it/3Cy8K4     
    
    
    Hmm. Just ordered from @GrubHub. Lemme illustrate that feeling. http://bit.ly/K1j9Mi     
    
    
    I'm loving my new @essie nail polish. It's a blue that shows up on my nails almost black, called "No More Film". #girly #nails #polish #glam    
    
    
    Photo: So awesome. I love being an alum from @SCADdotedu! Congrats! #designer #furniture #art #design #italy... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxiWVqal     
    
    
    Twitter Music Site Goes Live, Teases Imminent Launch http://on.mash.to/Yi3Ama  via @mashable    
    
    
    Photo: Words to live by #streetart #paint #williamsburg #letters #design #brooklyn (at Brooklyn Industries) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxiXrHlO     
    
    
    Photo: Fermenting tanks at @brooklynbrewery #friday #happyhour #brooklyn #beer #drinks #nightlife (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxiXuZMC     
    
    
    Photo: Show at Pete’s Candy Shop #music #live #band #guitar #drums #brooklyn #nightlife #williamsburg (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxiYaDyE     
    
    
    Photo: Anti street harassment chalk walk. Powerful messages - men and women scribbled on the sidewalks.... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxib_IYD     
    
    
    Photo: Beautiful day in Manhattan #newyork #manhattan #city #washingtonsquare #arch #architecture #monument... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxic7prX     
    
    
    Photo: Pushing the cube #astorplace #manhattan #cube #installation #art (at Alamo “The Cube”) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxicUNQj     
    
    
    Photo: SHUT. UP. #mylittlepony #friendshipismagic #brony #toys #rainbow #soda #pony #sparkle #cartoon (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxicbT7B     
    
    
    Los Angeles Woman Fights Street Crime with Twitter http://on.mash.to/114J2xV  via @mashable    
    
    
    Love! RT @prgirlltd: pouffes by Vitra #milan13 pic.twitter.com/y5IUSeKDQr    
    
    
    Scary day RT @cnnbrk: Boston Marathon injury report: Two hospitals report total of 28 being treated http://on.cnn.com/YXVW3Y     
    
    
    Top 3 for #rupaulsdragrace! I wonder if @RuPaul drag out the announcement for top queen like last time (pun intended) cc: @nathan_lacy    
    
    
    Love you! This is so modern headbanger glam, it's sick RT @hotlead: “Bag” by White Lung is my new jam. http://t.thisismyjam.com/hotlead/_5e703jz …    
    
    
    Whenever I miss my mom, I put on "Black Boys/White Boys" from Hair.    
    
    
    Video: hotlead: Do you like books? Do you value and swoon over your favorite authors? Are you itching for a... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxiqLt-C     
    
    
    W/ @nathan_lacy. Flags are at half mast (@ Yankee Stadium - @mlb for Arizona Diamondbacks vs New York Yankees) [pic]: http://4sq.com/12ky8rI     
    
    
    Photo: New York Yankees tribute to Boston. They played “Sweet Caroline” after the 3rd inning. #boston... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxismx7b     
    
    
    Photo: Evening game #yankees #newyork #arizona #diamondbacks #baseball #stadium (at Yankee Stadium) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxit3VS3     
    
    
    East Meets West in Century-Old House South of Prospect Park http://curbed.cc/ZAaQsP  via @CurbedNY    
    
    
    Photo: Evening reading #wood #materials #interiors #sustainable #decorative #book http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxix9wai     
    
    
        
    
    
    I need to get my wanderlust fix with a vintage red mustang convertible, and an open road.    
    
    
    Catcalls, Whistles, Jeers are a Form of Harassment Argue Protestors http://thebrooklynink.com/2013/04/15/52236-catcalls-whistles-jeers-are-a-form-of-harassment-argue-protestors/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Screen is useless, and it won’t unlock. RIP iPod #apple #ipod #RIP #dunzo #music #technology http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxi_epUq     
    
    
    I updated my website a bit today...still needs lots of work! Here it is so far (works on mobile, too!) http://kristabedoskyphotography.com/     
    
    
    Photo: My weekend visitor, Miss Bacon! #baconator #bacon #dog #cute @hotlead http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxi-hYzT     
    
    
    Photo: Puppy face @hotlead http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxj02sch     
    
    
    Photo: My house guest Bacon. Little snuggle bunny @hotlead http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxj1U7Rp     
    
    
    Photo: Holy crap, bad dog farts @hotlead http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxj1VXN1     
    
    
    Photo: Bookcase treasures: @JonathanAdler for @Kohler tile samples from 2012 #ICFF http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxj85PgB     
    
    
    Getting Bacon tired out for @hotlead (@ Cooper Dog Park - @nycparks w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/ZapE6U     
    
    
    Photo: Drinks with the hubs #williamsburg #brooklyn #nightlife #drinks #love #cute #couple @ethan_waterman... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjAPR4o     
    
    
    Photo: “Paint is boring. Pattern is best!” @flatvernacular #paint #pattern #design #interiors... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjEO_mE     
    
    
    My laptop Bluetooth is on, and I didn't realize until I couldn't find my cursor...it flew over to my Apple desktop and paused my music!    
    
    
    This is absolutely awful. He had an interview with #BDwest super recently - San Diego's Architect Graham Downes Dead http://www.sandiego6.com/news/local/Nationally-Acclaimed-Architect-Graham-Downes-Dies-From-His-Wounds-204077441.html …    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Hey boo! That sounds awesome! Wanna email or DM with more info?    
    
    
    http://WordPress.com  Launches New Vertical And Theme For Hotels, Inns And B&Bs http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/22/wordpress-com-hotel-verical-and-theme/ … via @techcrunch #hospitality #hotels    
    
    
    Social media equals conversion RT @PSFK: Twitter traffic does drive sales, says @Deloitte study http://bit.ly/14JUAOL  via @brandrepublic    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Perfect! Tweet me when you do, my Gmail will bounce emails sometimes.    
    
    
    @jameswahba See you tomorrow at #digitaldumbo! Looking forward to seeing you speak cc: @projectivenyc    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Got it, thanks! Looking it over now    
    
    
    Photo: Playing #BobbyDarin on #vinyl and #reading my new #photo book that my mom sent me for an early... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjJX-HO     
    
    
    Photo: Frederik Ruysch, Thesaurus Anatomicus Primus Ah fata, ah asaspera fata! “Ah fate, ah bitter fate!” http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjOOpU3     
    
    
    Photo: Ghost Bottle from @brooklynbrewery. Cuvée de la crochet rouge beer in my adorable Vin glass, awesome... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjPVS8x     
    
    
    Photo: inerdonthis: Always makes me smile http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjPcO5U     
    
    
    @ShannonAMay yup, that works! Looking forward to seeing you too!    
    
    
    I'm at City Winery w/ @hotlead http://4sq.com/YSgjfF     
    
    
    Photo: One of the many trailers for #bluebloods, filming around my neighborhood #tv #show #newyork... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjU6MB8     
    
    
    As the quintessential dive bar, Don Pedro is located in an auspicious part of Williamsburg. http://social.partyearth.com/gGRiVUB     
    
    
    Photographing the @GreyGravy happy hour! Shannon (@ Snafu Bar) http://4sq.com/12LdGk3     
    
    
    Midwest beer night! (at @BarcadeBrooklyn w/ 18 others) http://4sq.com/10DYxTL     
    
    
    Photo: Evening read. Gorgeous photo book of #CindySherman work. #photo #photography #read #books... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjclMUP     
    
    
    An artist is not merely the slavish announcer of a series of facts, which in this case the camera has had to accept and mechanically record    
    
    
    Photoset: nymeses: This is what feminists mean when we talk about rape culture: these cards are considered... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxjfq1y9     
    
    
    Convinced Ethan to try the Bee Sting. Finally back here! (@ Roberta's Pizza w/ @ah_ethan) http://4sq.com/1254eo3     
    
    
    Photo: Shhhh don’t tell anyone! #speakeasy #sign #bar #nightlife #neon #newyork #nyc #brooklyn #bushwick... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjhKCA0     
    
    
    Photo: “Moose bite the falcon wing where vagina lies into fire begin anew self cleaning”…worst haiku ever?... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjhMNax     
    
    
    Photo: Boob poke! #streetart #brooklyn #art #bushwick #eastwilliamsburg #paint #blackandwhite (at Tutu’s) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjhsgDY     
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Hey lady! I'm actually waiting for them to finish uploading as we speak! From what I gather, I just need to share them w/ you?    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Of course! I edited some out already...there are some duplicates so feel free to pick whichever works best!    
    
    
    @ShannonAMay Much love, my dear. Let's be in touch tomorrow! I wanna make sure the photos are ok...and don't forget about my resume! :)    
    
    
    Today! Check-In to 200Lex - Explore the best in #hospitality #design with @Interior_Design magazine.  http://www.nydc.com/www/index.php/news_events/upcoming/75/check-in_to_200lex …    
    
    
    Looking forward to "Is Your Workplace Making You Sick?" tonight w/ @teknion @MetropolisMag @IIDANY http://www.metropolismag.com/cda/events.php?region=Metropolis+Events#5803 …    
    
    
    I almost spit my coffee out: "And I said: "My name is 'Sue!' How do you do! Now your gonna die!!" http://spoti.fi/MZXWRf  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Instancy Retail http://www.gensleron.com/lifestyle/2013/4/29/instancy-retail.html/ … @GenslerLfstyle    
    
    
    Here for #200lex, hospitality design event w/ @Interior_design magazine (@ New York Design Center) http://4sq.com/ZgzY9c     
    
    
    Photo: Ron Levine and Matthew Berman #200Lex #design #newyork #showroom #hospitality #hospitalitydesign... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjqkrY9     
    
    
    Photo: Old man tree on a #beer glass #nightlife #drinks #bar #williamsburg #brooklyn #newyork #nyc #design... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjsM_R4     
    
    
    Photo: I swear this dog thinks she’s a cat cc: @hotlead #bacon #middayvisit #dog #cute (at Hotlead & Bacon... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjuRFss     
    
    
    @hotlead Haha! Sorry bout it! Never seen a dog curl their paws like she does    
    
    
    Photo: By the light of the paper bag candle (at Barcade) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjxagD4     
    
    
    Photo: Awesome pen and notebook from the event last night hosted by @teknion @metropolismag @IIDANY http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxjypiZN     
    
    
    If only.....: Pacman is coming for the L Train stops http://j.mp/Zn6NBb  @freedubya @joshmorrissey    
    
    
    One of my favorite sinks in Greenwich Green from @JonathanAdler and @Kohler made the list. @KohlerPR @HGTV #KBIS2013 http://blog.hgtv.com/design/2013/05/01/kbis-2013-whats-hot-in-kitchens/#more-67161 …    
    
    
    Photo: Parmesan Herb popcorn and @Interior_Design magazine. Food for the body and mind! http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxj_xCuP     
    
    
    WeCross by Dror: Tour and Happy Hour | NYCxDESIGN: http://nycxdesign.com/events/wecross-by-dror-tour-and-happy-hour/#.UYFuwV0qPLw.twitter …    
    
    
    Wise words RT @CannonDesign: Never Be Afraid To Fail - Unless You're Failing By Default - http://ow.ly/kBp0O  #livewithcourage    
    
    
    Tiffany 1837™ narrow ring in midnight titanium. http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985578125/ …    
    
    
    @TRockiesEvents, @SkirtChaser5k, pls change the race name! Skirt Chaser sounds scary, not fun! http://tinyurl.com/cowheza#EndSH     
    
    
    Adam "MCA" Yauch Will Get Brooklyn Heights Playground Named After Him On Friday http://gothamist.com/2013/05/01/adam_mca_yauch_may_get_brooklyn_hei.php … via @gothamist    
    
    
    Iwan Baan’s Post-Sandy Manhattan Shot Makes ASME Cover of the Year http://archinect.com/news/article/72361955/iwan-baan-s-post-sandy-manhattan-shot-makes-asme-cover-of-the-year …    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk5rKat     
    
    
    Photoset: itscolossal: The World’s Largest Rubber Duck Arrives in Hong Kong http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk5rRK_     
    
    
    Photo: laughingsquid: Hand Crafted Into a Hipster in Williamsburg, Brooklyn http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk5thyk     
    
    
    Photo: Ethan surprised me with cupcakes from Brooklyn Cupcake and a cinnamon vanilla candle for an early... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk8LpFb     
    
    
    Photo: Glorious #cupcake (at The Levees Cigarette Land) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk8MUKw     
    
    
    Photo: My beautiful earrings from my beautiful mother. Silver and stone handmade from a local Minnesota... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxk9Kver     
    
    
    NYC to Binghamton (@ Penn Station Greyhound Bus) http://4sq.com/15dRd2o     
    
    
    Vegetarian-friendly haven in the middle of downtown Binghamton. (@ Lost Dog Café) http://4sq.com/138swkY     
    
    
    Photo: Amazing veggie burger and sweet potato fries (at Lost Dog Café) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkDTvOS     
    
    
    Photo: Lost Dog Cafe in Binghamton, New York (at Lost Dog Café) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkDakoP     
    
    
    Photo: Bradley Cooper, Zach Galifinakis, and Ed Helms in a Jennifer Aniston look-a-like contest on #SNL http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkFW3Wv     
    
    
    Photo: #tulips (at City of Binghamton) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkFd2Mf     
    
    
    Photo: Flowering trees in #upstate #NY (at City of Binghamton) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkFehM4     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkFgAjG     
    
    
    Photo: Creepy tunnel in downtown Binghamton (at City of Binghamton) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkI-g8T     
    
    
    Photo: #MRY offices (at MRY) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkNgqhy     
    
    
    Season finale of #rupauldragrace Love it hunty! (@ Don Pedro) http://4sq.com/16PAaUf     
    
    
    Photo: Charlie! #dog #cute #sheltie #shetlandsheepdog #minnesota #home http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPThRv     
    
    
    Photo: Bela boo kitty #cats #cat #catsofinstagram #kitty #minnesota http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPZJhp     
    
    
    Photo: Crabby kitty face Ingrid #cat #cats #catsofinstagram http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPdTbP     
    
    
    Photo: Happy tired Ace face #dog #cute #dogsofinstagram #dogs #puppy #sheltie #shetlandsheepdog http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPfJeT     
    
    
    Photo: My mom had the flu recently and this was her companion. Such a good boy! #aceface #ace #dog... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPhpBL     
    
    
    Photo: A few weeks ago, it was still snowing in Minnesota (what happened to spring?!) Poor Charlie is... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkPjFyF     
    
    
    All Social is Not Created Equal - Yahoo! Small Business Advisor http://smallbusiness.yahoo.com/advisor/social-not-created-equal-133545817.html … via @YSmallBusiness    
    
    
    @LikeableMedia How long is the chat? I have a call at 2PM but I'd love to join for a bit!    
    
    
    Traits of Successful Entrepreneurs http://myturnstone.com/blog/traits-of-successful-entrepreneurs/#.UYk2_2MrBuQ.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    An Update on TweetDeck https://blog.twitter.com/2013/update-tweetdeck …    
    
    
    What do you call a pig that does karate? A PORK CHOP! #theoatmeal #eyeroll #joke #corny #cheesy #humor    
    
    
    @LikeableMedia Awesome! I'll try to jump in! #LikeableChat    
    
    
    My great friend Tamara Garvey wrote this blog post!! http://community.feministing.com/2013/05/06/its-a-trick-question/ … via @feministing    
    
    
    It’s a trick question! - Written by Tamara Garvey, Brooklyn, NY http://tmblr.co/ZDwl5tkSE3fH     
    
    
    Just joining...catching the last 15 minutes! Hello everyone #likeablechat    
    
    
    A6 Train them, and provide support, but don't micro-manage. Keep the conversation open. #likeablechat    
    
    
    Fake Meat for the Masses? | http://Inc.com  http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUGYFF     
    
    
    Found at Auction: The Unseen Photographs of a Legend that Never Was | Messy Nessy Chic Messy Nessy Chic http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUPSeK     
    
    
    Say No To the Funhouse Mirror: Warren Buffett Joins Levo League to Advocate for Gen Y Women in the Workplace... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUSKcE     
    
    
    @hugeinc Wins Tempur-Pedic Digital Business After Review | Adweek - Digital marketing is important for... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUWFqG     
    
    
    10 Reasons Why Humor Is A Key To Success At Work - @Forbes - “…well-placed humor that is clever and apropos... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUXpzE     
    
    
    “It takes 20 years to build a reputation and five minutes to ruin it. If you think about that, you’ll do things differently.” Warren Buffett    
    
    
    @FedEx Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    Intern opportunity for Graphic Design in NYC RT @msmarypryor: Graphic Design Intern http://www.levoleague.com/companies/pencils-of-promise/jobs/graphic-design-intern--4 … cc @levoleague    
    
    
    “I have not failed. I’ve just found 10,000 ways that won’t work.” - Thomas Edison    
    
    
    New US Industry Forecast From ULI, Ernst & Young Projects Rally in Real Estate Capital Markets and Strong... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkUdDRG     
    
    
    @Veruca_Saltine Proud of you! cc: @feministing    
    
    
    Free food and drink tonight! Register for this party: Check out "NYC Posse Launch Party" http://possenyc-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Sitting is the new smoking: To Be Healthier, Stand Up From Your Desk Right Now http://www.fastcompany.com/3009421/to-be-healthier-happier-and-more-productive-stand-up-from-your-desk-right-now … via @FastCompany @metropolismag    
    
    
    The 10 Best Bars With Outdoor Space In NYC http://gothamist.com/2013/05/08/the_best_bars_with_outdoor_oases_in.php … via @gothamist    
    
    
    Klout dips into Q&A and local commerce with launch of new questions feature http://gigaom.com/2013/05/08/klout-dips-into-qa-and-local-commerce-with-launch-of-new-questions-feature/ … via @gigaom    
    
    
    Associated Press Updates Social Media Guidelines http://adweek.it/YDHjoh     
    
    
    @Jmodio Saw you were registered for the Posse party tonight...I'm going too!    
    
    
    Love the single sleeve on this little black dress! http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985608799/ …    
    
    
    Perfect outfit for work http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985608816/ …    
    
    
    Thomas Rehberger's 'lighthouse' South Pointe Park Miami beach, photo by Robin Hill http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985608828/ …    
    
    
    Obsessed with gray in home design. It is cozy and chic. #bedroom #beachbedroom #grey #gray http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985608831/ …    
    
    
    @Jmodio Bummer. I'll let you know how it was!    
    
    
    @KellyLux A4 Recharge by walking away from your computer, taking a walk with no distractions. Coffee helps too! #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @Jmodio Ahh I see...its a website that has reviews of venues (bars/restaurants/etc), and I think they are launching an app?    
    
    
    Amenities We Wish Every Hotel Stocked (for Free!) http://shar.es/l8pq1  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Side Tables, Geometric Chrome Nesting Tables, InStyle Decor Beverly Hills Hollywood Luxury Home Decor http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985609252/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Jodi Arias Guilty Of First-Degree Murder In The Killing Of Travis Alexander http://huff.to/18ZJ52e  via @HuffPostCrime    
    
    
    Posse party (@ Butterfly Studio Salon - @butterflynyc w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/17MHQ7M     
    
    
    Photo: Ingrid #kitty #meow #purr #catsofinstagram #cat #cats #pets http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkaoseT     
    
    
    @brooklynbrewery tap night! (at @BarcadeBrooklyn w/ 10 others) http://4sq.com/147OGCR     
    
    
    First day of freelance! (@ MRY) http://4sq.com/13me1tG     
    
    
    Try Blackberry 10 in your mobile browser. Pretty close simulation of the UI with a walkthrough http://blackberry.com/glimpse     
    
    
    Steampunk Nintendo Controller Coffee Table Made of Recycled Parts http://laughingsquid.com/steampunk-nintendo-controller-coffee-table-made-of-recycled-parts/ … via @LaughingSquid    
    
    
    Photo: Sunset over manhattan from my rooftop in Brooklyn. http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxkiFNqZ     
    
    
    21 Things New Yorkers Do Better http://www.buzzfeed.com/h2/shtc/inteliq/21-things-new-yorkers-do-better … via @intel    
    
    
    33 Super-Cool Popsicles To Make This Summer http://www.buzzfeed.com/rachelysanders/super-cool-popsicles-to-make-this-summer … via @buzzfeedfood    
    
    
    Check out "Lunch Talk with Institute of Play" http://lunchtalk29-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite @hotlead    
    
    
    Because I connected my Gmail account, I got an email reminder from @LinkedIn about today's schedule. Weird.    
    
    
    Gothamist Wants Your Freelance Submissions http://gothamist.com/2013/05/14/gothamist_wants_your_freelance_subm_10.php … via @gothamist    
    
    
        
    
    
    #IWish there was an app that could plug-in to Gmail to easily unsubscribe from newsletters.    
    
    
    @CeaseTheDay My wish came true! (err almost...need to see it in action). Link me when you can! Thanks!    
    
    
    Found it! @CeaseTheDay  "I am cleaning up my 78 email subscriptions using @unrollme " https://bit.ly/106SUaq     
    
    
    @CeaseTheDay I have yet to see it in action (cause most of my newsletters come in the morning), but I think it just solved my woes!    
    
    
    @CeaseTheDay Thanks! I am really enjoying it! Great place to work    
    
    
    Yahoo in Talks to Acquire Tumblr  http://adweek.it/17BN2Or     
    
    
    Event with @metropolismag @hotlead (@ Snøhetta w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/17Hejig     
    
    
    Omg yes veggie burger (@ Mother's w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/14eafSE     
    
    
    Why does it always rain during #ICFF? (@ ICFF Javits w/ 20 others) http://4sq.com/17L7In4     
    
    
    Bite to eat before #icff parties (at @CuppingRoomCafe) http://4sq.com/10MCTa7     
    
    
    Photo: Vodka mint lemonade at @bludot #icff #nydw (at Blu Dot Soho) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlHvoNp     
    
    
    Any recommendations for other events for New York Design Week in the soho area? At @bludot right now...    
    
    
    Photo: At Capellini for #nydw #icff. Oh hai @hotlead I see you! (at Cappellini) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlIBxDY     
    
    
    Photo: 3rd year in a row at @bobbyberk for #icff #nydw @bobbyberkhome (at Bobby Berk Home @bobbyberkhome) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlIKvRA     
    
    
    Photo: Sitting in designer adirondack chairs outside of @bobbyberk @bobbyberkhome #nyc #nydw #icff (at East,... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlIP3UW     
    
    
    Photo: East meets west #nyc #nydw #icff @bobbyberk (at Bobby Berk Home @bobbyberkhome) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlIWfSS     
    
    
    Photo: My dress matches the random teepee at @bobbyberk #icff #nydw #nyc (at Bobby Berk Home @bobbyberkhome) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlIXTuI     
    
    
    Day 2 (@ ICFF Javits w/ @hotlead) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1129RYQ     
    
    
    Photo: #iwoodlikeit handmade & digital wood carving. They are making a model car right at #icff! (at ICFF... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlMvfDg     
    
    
    Photo: #architecture #building #newyork #nyc #icff #javits #nydw (at ICFF Javits) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlNYj5t     
    
    
    GrubHub to Merge With Seamless as Food Orders Go Mobile http://bloom.bg/14IR432  via @BloombergNews    
    
    
    Photo: Technologic connects with setting sun beams http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlSeBU0     
    
    
    Photo: Found treasures #rooftime http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlSfD9C     
    
    
    Photo: Vegetation amongst brick and steel in #nyc #rooftime http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlSgJnV     
    
    
    Photo: Foggy morning. You can barely see the MetLife building up Park ave #nyc (at Union Square Park) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlU_ihl     
    
    
    Photo: MRY office on Park Avenue South #nyc #socialmedia #agency #design #green #digital http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlYMXAK     
    
    
    hahaha @hotlead #humpday http://youtu.be/kWBhP0EQ1lA  via @youtube    
    
    
    Photo: Lobster roll, bay fries, and asperol spritzer @nathan_lacy (at The Mermaid Inn) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxlbyo_0     
    
    
    Photo: Not a bad view from the office. Looking uptown on Park Avenue South #nyc #city #parkave (at 225 Park... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxlfc8We     
    
    
    Photo: Super cool logo by Bronx Brewery. I am in love with the font. In the glass is the Singlecut Billy... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxlgn-BF     
    
    
    Photo: Whiskey Breath in #Brooklyn at pine box rock shop #music #musicians #live #nightlive #bar (at Pine... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlgxyP5     
    
    
    Photo: Karaoke at pine box! #brooklyn #music #nightlife #grave #graphicdesign #typography #poster #musician... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxlgyX6z     
    
    
    Happy birthday @hotlead!!! (@ Custom Wine Bar) http://4sq.com/18qUXMq     
    
    
    Facebook Says It Failed to Bar Posts With Hate Speech http://nyti.ms/19kyrpR     
    
    
    My blog post: Collaboration Tools for Working Online (and Offline!) http://myturnstone.com/blog/collaboration-tools-for-working-online-and-offline/#.UaYjKl8SeYo.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Penn Station, Re-Imagined http://www.archdaily.com/379436/penn-station-re-imagined/ … via @archdaily    
    
    
    Photo: People looking at the #manhattanhenge phenomenon on 14th and Ave A http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxm8Vxjg     
    
    
    I really don't like when I unsubscribe from an email newsletter, and I get ANOTHER email confirming my choice #marketing #socialmedia    
    
    
    Friday tradition! @brooklynbrewery (@ The Brooklyn Brewery w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/17Gm5tS     
    
    
    Photo: Princess the poodle on the counter of @brooklynbrewery (at The Brooklyn Brewery) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmISpZP     
    
    
    Photo: Day at the #coney #island #beach! #sun #brooklyn #surf #weekend (at Brooklyn Beach Shop) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmMYZve     
    
    
    Remembered why i followed you...you have rebelmouse in your profile, and I was stalking them! Glad to have you on the team! #TeamBlackBerry    
    
    
    Photo: It’s totally normal to carry a hamburger balloon around town #nyc #brooklyn #food #celebrate (at... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmXLa7K     
    
    
    W/ @nathan_lacy for Walking the Dead (@ The Secret Theatre for Walking the Dead) http://4sq.com/ZMJq9M     
    
    
    I keep getting all of these emails for @NeoCon and I'm getting sad that I can't go :( #NeoCon13 #Chicago #interiordesign    
    
    
    Took an HOUR to get here. Minneapolis bound! (@ LaGuardia Airport (LGA) w/ 167 others) http://4sq.com/19MMYL9     
    
    
    Photo: Artifacts from my childhood #minnesota http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmmtpiB     
    
    
    Rehearsal dinner. Can't complain about the view overlooking the harbor (@ Harbor House Grill) [pic]: http://4sq.com/14GYPEQ     
    
    
    Photo: Part of the #beer selection at #dinner (at Harbor House Grill) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmrLwFf     
    
    
    Photo: View of Lake Superior from our cabin #minnesota #lakesuperior #greatlakes #north (at Lutsen Sea... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxmrMiZ1     
    
    
    Wrong day to wear a skirt #windy    
    
    
    Photo: Lone fisherman. Up north in #Minnesota on #lakesuperior http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxn8XJwY     
    
    
    The Inside Scoop on Google's Visual Design Guidelines http://on.mash.to/1btkKD5  via @mashable    
    
    
    "Google Visual Assets Guidelines - Part 1", a project on @Behance ::  http://www.behance.net/gallery/Google-Visual-Assets-Guidelines-Part-1/9028077 …    
    
    
    MakerBot Opening Bigger Factory, Hiring More Employees http://on.mash.to/10U43Mo  via @mashable    
    
    
    You Can't Follow the Fiat Abarth 500 on Twitter http://on.mash.to/13Efrzq  via @mashable    
    
    
    BBM Channels Update Now Available in Beta http://blogs.blackberry.com/2013/06/bbm-channels-beta-update/ … via @blackberryblog    
    
    
    Maple latte (@ Gorilla Coffee w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/147XUhT     
    
    
    Photo: #citibike in #FortGreene #brooklyn (at Citi Bike Station) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxnPcUOo     
    
    
    Iconic Notebook Brand 'Moleskine' Gets A Logo Update And Debuts A New Monogram http://shar.es/x7JT8  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Study: U.S. Smartphone Penetration Now at 61% http://on.mash.to/13nS4Kq  via @mashable    
    
    
    Photo: #sunset over #nyc #brooklyn #nofilters http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxnnjha7     
    
    
    Photo: Today @facebook announced #video for @instagram. I took a screenshot of the announcement in the app,... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxnns4st     
    
    
    Black and white on Metro North #video #connecticut #train http://instagram.com/p/a4Jm9Cxeed/     
    
    
    Afternoon wine @ Café Atlantique http://instagram.com/p/a4QMvWxebj/     
    
    
    Morning jam ♫ Fast In My Car – Paramore http://spoti.fi/XTsVm4  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I'm going to add a middle initial to my Twitter account because I want my name to look more hoity and toity and whatnot.    
    
    
    What is the best service for finding an #NYC apartment?    
    
    
    A bird almost flew into my face #UnionSquareProblems (@ Union Square Park - @nycparks w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/13cjjex     
    
    
    Ernst & Young re-brands, professional services firm to be known as EY http://www.irishtimes.com/business/sectors/financial-services/ernst-young-re-brands-1.1449229#.UdLPqDkIoJ0.twitter … via @IrishTimes    
    
    
    Leaked photos may reveal new iPhone shell in green, yellow and red http://bgr.com/2013/07/01/iphone-6-photos-case-colors/ …    
    
    
    Up your alley? - SOCIAL MEDIA STRATEGIST AND COMMUNITY MA at FACTORY PR @TheLexIsaacs #jobs http://lnkd.in/7T9qVP     
    
    
    Delicious gin drink, and a rooftop with a view of Manhattan. Beautiful day! (at @WytheHotel w/ 3 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/13slsCZ     
    
    
    Fresh lavender #brooklyn #bar @ Night of Joy http://instagram.com/p/bcHqs5ReXR/     
    
    
    Happy birthday Tamara!! (@ Night of Joy) http://4sq.com/17X7I1a     
    
    
    @jkovalak love you. Hopefully soon! We are moving at the end of the month, so money is tight. Maybe around the holidays! xoxo    
    
    
    My mom is mentioned in this article! : SummerWood Art Classes in Plymouth | Minnetonka art | Plymouth Magazine http://plymouthmag.com/article/minnetonka-art/summerwood-art-classes-plymouth …    
    
    
    I'm a full time employee at @MRY now! YAYYY (@ 225 Park Ave South) http://4sq.com/18Liz1f     
    
    
    @MRY Thank you!! Glad to be here :)    
    
    
    Just tried @Chobani Flip, and it is a genius idea! Perfect for at my desk. #yogurt #yum    
    
    
    I CAN'T EVEN.  https://vine.co/v/bEWhTXqr7Xa     
    
    
    Lazy #howto #scare #ninja #cat https://vine.co/v/h7b2JMEvhBt     
    
    
    Start Walkin' RED 6 Monday #mashup @hotlead https://vine.co/v/h7eiXIpIVdz     
    
    
    @Jmodio I just missed you! I was at that branch 45 minutes ago.    
    
    
    @Jmodio Wait, why did you? I'm not following    
    
    
    This capybaras is called Garibaldi Rous, and the cats name is Flopsy. http://pinterest.com/pin/135811744985952591/ …    
    
    
    My Ace stand-in til the real thing gets back to #brooklyn  in the fall #dog #pets http://instagram.com/p/b5LBn4xeay/     
    
    
    Hanging by the pool (@ Soho House Rooftop) http://4sq.com/13odg3F     
    
    
    So proud of my girl Karen! You are an incredible designer and friend. Go #ProjectRunway! @LetsGoSeeDo    
    
    
    YUM YAM YAM YUM YAM @hotlead https://vine.co/v/hmpEzwYUeBA     
    
    
    Bacon the dog @hotlead #dog #bostonterrier https://vine.co/v/hmQm3KDjtwe     
    
    
    Whine whine whine #bostonterrier @hotlead https://vine.co/v/hmQKdBDui6V     
    
    
    #Baconthedog #bostonterrier @hotlead https://vine.co/v/hmQA5YbwMe3     
    
    
    @hotlead haha! She's so adorable. She whines at me to play. Girl knows what she wants    
    
    
    @hotlead I'm a pushover    
    
    
    Shake that ball! @hotlead #dog #bostonterrier https://vine.co/v/hmlTQvuxgOF     
    
    
    10 Things You Need To Know This Morning http://www.businessinsider.com/10-things-you-need-to-know-this-morning-apple-q2-2013-7 … via @mediafed    
    
    
    Book Review: The Seven Success Factors of Social Business Strategy by Brian Solis and Charlene Li  http://fw.to/6f56YpM     
    
    
    centipede by Childish Gambino via #soundcloud http://soundcloud.com/childish-gambino/centipede/s-PmfHZ …    
    
    
    @Jmodio @evanhamilton @JPedde @KellyLux I was going to join today too! Drat. Talk soon! #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @Jmodio Awesome, thanks! I'm always looking for twitter chats to join.    
    
    
    @Jmodio Anything tomorrow or Friday you can recommend?    
    
    
    C'mon @Oreo, you are better than this: pic.twitter.com/BTduaw69ah    
    
    
    The last thing you want to see when you are trying to leave the office early. #evilupdates #Friday… http://instagram.com/p/cPbIEVxec5/     
    
    
    I have a little fuzzy buddy next to my bar stool #dog #bar #newfriend @ Lady Jay's http://instagram.com/p/cPsD2LReYH/     
    
    
    'Murica 

#dog #bar #brooklyn #animals http://instagram.com/p/cPuhVCRecs/     
    
    
    MRY party with changing screens. Happy hour with open bar! @ The 13th Step http://instagram.com/p/caFVo0xeUO/     
    
    
    UNO mas @hotlead https://vine.co/v/hmpEzwYUeBA     
    
    
    Last check in ever! Just left for the good. Bye ghetto house! (@ El Adobe Photo Shoppe w/ @ah_ethan @dryerdoor) http://4sq.com/16K3M1R     
    
    
    Vintage Coach from the 70's. Noce little find at Brooklyn Flea today. http://instagram.com/p/cm-wR_xefW/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Sometimes you need hair metal to finish out your afternoon http://spoti.fi/NqhEE7  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    @kdr I'm sorry, WHAT?!    
    
    
    @lisettevoytko Well hello miss! Care for a cocktail? *mixes liquid and ice in shaker*    
    
    
    @lisettevoytko Haha yesss! Can't wait to see you, too!    
    
    
    Was There an Explosion in Bushwick? http://www.complex.com/city-guide/2013/08/explosion-bushwick-brooklyn … via @ComplexGuide    
    
    
    @hotlead Yeah just saw an update. Whew that's cray    
    
    
    Mad respect for @BioWare and @davidgaider - http://community.feministing.com/2011/03/28/%e2%80%9cstraight-male-gamer%e2%80%9d-told-to-%e2%80%98get-over-it%e2%80%99-by-bioware/ … via @feministing    
    
    
    Thank you @Squarespace for the great @Meetup last night! Couldn't nab a shirt, but got one of the flexi tripods for my camera    
    
    
    @hotlead @spielster I might be able to get there in 30...I'll text when I'm leaving the office. I'm not far away!    
    
    
    @hotlead Ace was my ad-hoc workspace when I was working remotely. Good times cc: @acehotel    
    
    
    @hotlead I am en route! Be there in roughly 10 mins    
    
    
    Photo: Beautiful late afternoon light #nyc (at St. Mark’s Place) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxsMi2-S     
    
    
    If you are stressed out, this song will relax you - Marconi Union - Weightless by emersonhurtatis via #soundcloud https://soundcloud.com/emerson-hurtatis/marconi-union-weightless?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=wtshare&utm_medium=Twitter&utm_content=https://soundcloud.com/emerson-hurtatis/marconi-union-weightless …    
    
    
    Fresh guac right at the table for #cm lunch @ Rosa Mexicano http://instagram.com/p/dFJxiLxec0/     
    
    
    Photo: Fresh guac right at the table for #cm lunch (at Rosa Mexicano) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxsQcUs3     
    
    
    My afternoon needs some #Manilow ♫ Copacabana - Radio – Barry Manilow http://spoti.fi/IwtcHf  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Photo: Northside #Williamsburg #brooklyn #nyc (at Williamsburg) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxsS5Zba     
    
    
    Photo: View to the outside #brooklyn #williamsburg (at No Name Bar) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxsXfdbJ     
    
    
    Photo: Yummy wine Nathan brought over for dinner #wine #brooklyn #nyc http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxswwuwD     
    
    
    On repeat for a cloudy and rainy morning ♫ On'n'On – Justice http://spoti.fi/KAVlzB  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    New favorite song ♫ New Lands – Justice http://spoti.fi/KHEGqw  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I hope my weekend embodies this song ♫ Rum & Coca Cola - JoJo Effect Remix – Andrew Sisters http://spoti.fi/Ueodje  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    I <3 @uber! Used them yesterday, and I highly recommend the service. There is a deal for #brooklyn… http://instagram.com/p/davaCpxeW-/     
    
    
    Photo shoot! (@ Pin-Up Queens) http://4sq.com/14vzKRr     
    
    
    Part two of photo shoot (@ Hell Gate Social) http://4sq.com/16JleVZ     
    
    
    Photo: Pretty #dog close up. My baby is coming home to #nyc! #aceface http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxu6qXI1     
    
    
    I'm at Santos Party House for MC Chris, dr. awkward, Tribe One and Jesse Dangerously Tribe One w/ @ah_ethan http://4sq.com/15FsAgt     
    
    
    Photo: Dining in sand (literally). Amazeball seafood restaurant and bar in #Williamsburg #brooklyn (at Surf... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxuPo75T     
    
    
    Photo: Bowl of chowdahhh and a lobster roll (at Surf Bar) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxuPw1IU     
    
    
    Omg! RT @hotlead: @AH_Ethan @ComedyCentral: #Futurama Live! The cast & crew talking about their finale is online http://on.cc.com/1fRCudE     
    
    
    Photo: Cat silhouette #brooklyn #williamsburg http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxuedSPS     
    
    
    Photo: #Vintage sign (at Extra Fancy) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxurOLXi     
    
    
    Talking to dogs is exactly like this: DOG LANGUAGE w/ Buster Beans @hotlead https://vine.co/v/h13OOhrVAap     
    
    
    Another one!!!:  OOO YUM YAM YAM YAM Curtis Lepore @hotlead https://vine.co/v/h1dpw2VwQQl     
    
    
    Go to San Gennaro on a Sunday, they said. It will be fun, they said... (@ Feast of San Gennaro - @sangennaronyc) http://4sq.com/1eSnm1P     
    
    
    I'm at Bus To Camp MRY (New York, NY) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/16glYiJ     
    
    
    @lisettevoytko thanks lady! :)    
    
    
    Riding through #NYC. Busin it up to Kent, CT https://vine.co/v/hvB1e5OaEFD     
    
    
    #NYC in the early morning https://vine.co/v/hvBvndTPgVB     
    
    
    Photo: #NYC buildings in the early morning sunlight http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxvHDADI     
    
    
    Camp @mry! (@ Club Getaway) http://4sq.com/1aQ9Psx     
    
    
        
    
    
    Bus ride home MRY https://vine.co/v/hvW00z7mIeh     
    
    
    https://vine.co/v/hv7U6MnIJ10     
    
    
    Pin up club shoot! (@ American Airpower Museum) http://4sq.com/1bAb6mZ     
    
    
    New York Burlesque Festival!!! (at @BrooklynBowl w/ 10 others) http://4sq.com/14Q8cX5     
    
    
    My mothership. New York Burlesque Festival #showmehowyou #burlesque @ Brooklyn Bowl http://instagram.com/p/eyVFZMRebp/     
    
    
    Photo: My mothership. New York Burlesque Festival #showmehowyou #burlesque (at Brooklyn Bowl) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxwBTYEc     
    
    
    I'm at @BoweryBallroom for Superchunk (New York, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/15Ck4sX     
    
    
    Photo: I love the lower east side. Listening to some tunes! #nyc (at Bowery Ballroom) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxwH0tLD     
    
    
    Photo: Peek-a-boo, I see you! http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxwHEAUB     
    
    
    Superchunk! https://vine.co/v/h6puWHFunvn     
    
    
    Photo: Superchunk #nyc (at Bowery Ballroom) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxwHXtEk     
    
    
    Dance on. Dance on. https://vine.co/v/h6DmFhw3O1e     
    
    
    Dinner date! (@ Lucien w/ @nathan_lacy) http://4sq.com/1bkChmv     
    
    
    Photo: Fabric socks and ink socks #tattoos #ink #hisandhers http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxwNvQq_     
    
    
    Photo: Her name was Lola, she was a showgirl #fanilow @amyswater (at Surf Bar) http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxwu4866     
    
    
    Photo: New Essie nail polish! Over the Edge is a rock and roll metallic black/charcoal color http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxw_78i2     
    
    
    Photo: Sleepy Sunday #aceface #dogs #dogsofinstagram http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxw-2JF9     
    
    
    Photo: #Motorcycle kitty. The local neighborhood #cat likes to hang out on the bike outside my apartment.... http://tmblr.co/Zj-Fhxx1L5YO     
    
    
    Photo: Puppy dawg #aceface http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxxATsLu     
    
    
    Photo: The most New York-y breakfast, perfect for a chilly day #NYC (at 225 Park Ave South) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxxC08RI     
    
    
    Photo: What a little turd #aceface http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxxEiW-p     
    
    
    Play time! #aceface #dog #dogs #pets https://vine.co/v/hHu69tPIUJq     
    
    
    Photo: Tired pup, and @ethan_waterman doing his best Grumpy Cat impression in the background. #dogs... http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxxWLZdk     
    
    
    At #CMMeetup listening to @DavidSpinks @ThomasKelly @AdamBritten @carlablumenthal talk food and social media    
    
    
    @hotlead Heck yes we do! Thanks @threeze! :)    
    
    
    @thomaskelly Thanks for joining the #CMmeetup last night!    
    
    
    @hotlead I'll get some popcorn and an Icee for my inevitable stress-eating    
    
    
    @DavidSpinks Thanks for the awesome words of wisdom at #CMmeetup! Your laid back social media attitude is refreshing    
    
    
    @mmsuperflyjr It was great to see you last night! I had to rush out right after, so let's catch up soon!    
    
    
    @AdamBritten I really enjoyed hearing about @16Handles social media last night at #CMmeetup, especially use of @Snapchat. Major props!    
    
    
    @hotlead There is a 7:45 and 8:30 showing tonight at @WBURGTHTR. Either works for me! #GravityMovie    
    
    
    @hotlead Hmm probably after (I wanna hit up the dog park with the mutt). So let's do 7:30!    
    
    
    @hotlead Ha! Touche my friend #slam    
    
    
    Thanks @threeze for the movie tickets! I was so wobbly afterwards...I couldn't walk after watching Sandra Bullock spin through space    
    
    
    Does @Starbucks Valencia syrup exist? I used to buy orange mocha frappuccinos. it helps me sort through important issues #Zoolander    
    
    
    @h_crom it was great to meet you last night! Did you enjoy the show? @comtruise was amazing    
    
    
    Such a fun show. @comtruise on Saturday night #latergram @ Output http://instagram.com/p/ftsN4UReU4/     
    
    
    Photo: Someone stole my spot #aceface #dog #sheltie http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxyF5cjd     
    
    
    I am obsessed. It shows his great voice very well #NowPlaying Gorilla by Bruno Mars on #Spotify http://open.spotify.com/track/2ih2U8ttFzCjnQ5njF3SrR …    
    
    
    Rooftop! (at @WytheHotel w/ 9 others) http://4sq.com/1hjCZ3K     
    
    
    I'm at @BerryPark (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/1awalcs     
    
    
    Amazing campaign! MT @ASPCA: Stay tuned for LIVE coverage! #NationalCatDay #ICanHasUberKittens pic.twitter.com/pCXn4Mp78p    
    
    
    I want kittehs so bad! #ICanHasUberKittens @ 225 Park Ave South http://instagram.com/p/gDnDJIReaL/     
    
    
    Perfect playlist for a chilly fall day - #NowPlaying "All Blues" by Miles Davis (on Essential Jazz) http://songza.com/listen/essential-jazz-songza/ … via @songza    
    
    
    "It's sooo gross" #dogs #sheltie #shetlandsheepdog #pets #dog https://vine.co/v/hIFOZBYEJUi     
    
    
    Lunch & Learn with @offerpop  Eatin samiches and gobbling up hashtags.    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan Also, interesting use of hashtags. Not a compliment.    
    
    
    Bagels with butter makes me sad.    
    
    
    CM happy hour! (at @FatBuddhaBar w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/17WlvJA     
    
    
    I'm at Brooklyn Night Bazaar - @bkbazaar (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 94 others http://4sq.com/I8aqZg     
    
    
    The Goblin King ring I picked up tonight. I almost bought the matching earrings. #brooklyn #newyork… http://instagram.com/p/gzcGNTxeWZ/     
    
    
    Lavender gin. Yummers! (@ Night of Joy w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/I8nT3h     
    
    
    The pattern of my new dress. #kitties #cats #catsofinstagram http://instagram.com/p/g1O4JUxeTa/     
    
    
    Has someone mixed together @katyperry and @Drake lyrics yet?    
    
    
    Puppy kisses #dogs #dogsofinstagram #pets #cute #picstitch http://instagram.com/p/g4VfoFRedg/     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Playing catch #aceface #dogs #cute #playtime #pets https://vine.co/v/hUgluFwrpme     
    
    
    Just cuz I'm a dog doesn't mean I can't TURN UUUUUP! W/ Curtis Lepore @hotlead https://vine.co/v/hUblitwwYqx     
    
    
    Can't tell if this is on purpose...the picture is right-side up but the sign isn't.… http://instagram.com/p/hOyY8bReU0/     
    
    
    Crazy fog today (@ Union Square Park - @nycparks w/ 4 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/19jdKrS     
    
    
    Getting tons of things done, and it's not even noon yet #productivity (at @MRY w/ @jeffdm) http://4sq.com/1eSA93l     
    
    
        
    
    
    Taking the dog to meet Santa this weekend. #dogs #pets #sheltie #Afterlight pic.twitter.com/IC621C3zfe    
    
    
    @hotlead @Fab but there is a #sheltie mug...someone in the fam is getting it for Xmas, I've just decided.    
    
    
    @prettyinmypoc Do you have a handy dandy list of the bestest of the best?    
    
    
    Webcams for doggie day care is the best invention for obsessed dog owners like myself.    
    
    
    @NBCNewYork Adorable typo on the website. Aww yous guys #CentralParky pic.twitter.com/k546mHNcGe    
    
    
    Spotted @shakeshack in Madison Square: Three adorable dachshunds in matching cable-knit sweaters! #nyc #dogs pic.twitter.com/ah0JSsAtfG    
    
    
    You can order from iPads, and it gives you flight updates too! (@ Empire Tavern) [pic]: http://4sq.com/J1OKiA     
    
    
    I always end up sitting next to the most crotchety man in the world. Kindred spirits, I guess?    
    
    
    @hotlead he would probably turn to dust if I hugged him, the poor dear    
    
    
    Just landed in the twin cities! (@ Minneapolis-St. Paul International Airport (MSP) w/ 80 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Jb9X8Y     
    
    
        
    
    
    Much puppy fluff. Such cute. Mirror reflection funs. http://huff.to/1bVyFEE  via @HPGoodNews    
    
    
    Saw this photo on http://TheDogist.com ....looks like your sister's pup, yes? @hotlead http://tmblr.co/Z6MF6qyMmhka     
    
    
    Thank you @PayPal for your quick and painless resolution center! Y'all rock    
    
    
    I'm at Imagining The Lowline (New York, NY) w/ 6 others https://foursquare.com/kbedosky/checkin/5054b5d2e4b084591550c986?s=iOaf79tVHDz5fFxuNXCrNBtyoeY&ref=tw …    
    
    
    #lowline #nyc #essex #nofilters   @ Imagining The Lowline http://instagr.am/p/Pmq2AYRedg/     
    
    
    Vegetarian foods! (@ Teany) http://4sq.com/PmhaC7     
    
    
    You don't say....BBC News - Work stress 'raises heart risk' http://bbc.in/OKZDma     
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum We hate because we love.    
    
    
    @dryerdoor @twoshots @acesandrum Hmmm what time?    
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum who is the hater NOW?    
    
    
    @dryerdoor @acesandrum That could work for me quite perfectly actually. I can bring ace    
    
    
    @twoshots @dryerdoor @acesandrum Don't hate. It'll give you wrinkles.    
    
    
    @AcesAndRum @dryerdoor earliest for me would be 4    
    
    
    @acesandrum @dryerdoor Gonna be getting there probably closer to 4:45. Finishing up stuff here, then headin out with Ace.    
    
    
    Why on earth is a LEGO replica of Fallingwater priced at $99.99?    
    
    
    #NYC #sunset #rooftop #Brooklyn - A pano from AutoStitch iPhone. pic.twitter.com/NjUH3puw    
    
    
    @dryerdoor OMG ITS YOUR PEOPLE!  ALAHU AKBAR (sound change): http://youtu.be/ZSEBet4HO8o  via @youtube    
    
    
    10 Ways To Create An Open Culture  http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1681531  via @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    Happy birthday @nathan_lacy! First stop of the evening. (@ Los Feliz w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/OK4rqs     
    
    
    I'm at Excellent Dumpling House w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/PZfErw     
    
    
    I'm at Santos Party House for Ssion, House of Ladosha, TEETH, Sasha Gothard and 4 more w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/PFbALh     
    
    
    Going super girly for afternoon coffee #coffee #nyc #polkadots #pink http://instagr.am/p/QAdqarReYq/     
    
    
    Here for a talk with @metropolismag (@ Carl Hansen & Son) http://4sq.com/SQ9NSm     
    
    
    @steelcase media:scape at UCLA, featured in @MetropolisMag pic.twitter.com/50QigUyn    
    
    
    I am always impressed with Perkins+Will projects RT @perkinswill_LAO: That's our project looking good :)    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan whoever told you that is a dirty liar. No mail or packages yet. FedEx/UPS/USPS?    
    
    
    I just reached Level 6 of the "Hot Tamale" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 25 different Mexican Restaurants! http://4sq.com/PaRiqI     
    
    
    fuckyeahsheltie: Shelties on treadmills! http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUJxdHD     
    
    
    Watching 30 Rock: Liz Lemon's Flashbacks on @hulu: http://www.hulu.com/watch/316076     
    
    
    GIF love: 33 Infomercial Characters Who Need To Get Their Shit Together http://www.buzzfeed.com/mattbellassai/51-infomercial-characters-who-need-to-get-their-sh-6z51 … via @buzzfeed @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    I wish regular hospitals looked like this! :: Most Colorful Children's Hospitals From Around The World http://www.buzzfeed.com/txblacklabel/most-colorful-childrens-hospitals-from-around-the-28m7 … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan KITTEHS!!! I'm watching AnimalPlanet's live broadcast on @Ustream! Come join me http://ustre.am/OsFM     
    
    
    Street art in Brooklyn #brooklyn #nyc #streetart #kfc http://instagr.am/p/QN3ODfxebR/     
    
    
    Photo: Street art in Brooklyn #brooklyn #nyc #streetart #kfc (Taken with Instagram) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUOpDYt     
    
    
    @UncleSophie I haven't seen you in forever. When are you free this week? cc: @dryerdoor @acesandrum @twoshots    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan The things you miss by not living here.    
    
    
    An Experimental New Starbucks Store: Tiny, Portable, And Hyper Local http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1670889  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    Dyn Inc Office Tour http://myturnstone.com/blog/dyn-inc-office-tour/#.UGm0oOdAcCI.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    I just ousted autumn l. as the mayor of Café Orwell on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/2GXiQP     
    
    
    @AH_Ethan This lamp next to me is furry. It's making me uncomfortable.    
    
    
    Time Management: Break Your Workday Into Four-Hour &quot;Work Flows&quot; - @Lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5948175/break-your-workday-into-four+hour-work-flows …    
    
    
    I'm at Pho Grand Vietnamese Restaurant (New York, NY) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/QI5nQO     
    
    
    Coworking Spaces: What You Can Expect http://myturnstone.com/blog/coworking-spaces-what-you-can-expect/#.UGyB-ciNLDI.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    No matter how clearly I state my name at coffee shops, they always get it wrong. I end up with a strippers name on my coffee cup.    
    
    
    @twoshots Oh yes.    
    
    
    Moar coffee (@ The West) http://4sq.com/T1s9zG     
    
    
    So muddy. Good for pups, not good for shoes (@ McCarren Dog Park) http://4sq.com/QQvSnt     
    
    
    Target Plaza Commons: Not your average break room | http://StarTribune.com  http://www.startribune.com/business/172360021.html …    
    
    
    Design a Space. Win a Chair!  |  Steelcase Store http://lnkd.in/uq-R7G     
    
    
    Twitter Grows Up: Tour the New Office http://www.inc.com/april-joyner/twitter-new-san-francisco-office.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    Inside the Latest Office-Design Craze: Hot Desking http://www.inc.com/flash-steinbeiser/latest-office-design-craze-hot-desking.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    30 Rock: Celebrate Tonight's Return of 30 Rock by Watching Every TGS Sketch Ever Mentioned - @Jezebel http://jezebel.com/5949039/celebrate-tonights-return-of-30-rock-by-watching-every-tgs-sketch-ever-mentioned …    
    
    
    Midday museum visit (@ The Metropolitan Museum of Art w/ 28 others) http://4sq.com/QPCijg     
    
    
    I'm at Cloud City on the Met Roof (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/UorEqu     
    
    
    After dog park romps, pups get tuckered out http://instagr.am/p/Qa6UJPxeSb/     
    
    
    Photo: After dog park romps, pups get tuckered out (Taken with Instagram) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxUjF-Am     
    
    
    I'm at Custom Wine Bar (Brooklyn, New York) http://4sq.com/ST8277     
    
    
    I'm at Barcade w/ @msrachelmarie @hotlead http://4sq.com/WBroBK     
    
    
    Steelcase Store, Turnstone Introduce 3D Office Design Tool « CBS Detroit http://cbsloc.al/RdAuRz  @myturnstone    
    
    
    I love when they play Cesaria Evora (@ Boulevard Cafe w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/QhYDXk     
    
    
    Ralph Lauren says "plus size". I see normal beautiful girl: Stunning Photos Of Plus-Size Model Robyn Lawley - @Jezebel http://jezebel.com/5950621/stunning-photos-of-plus+size-swimwear-model-robyn-lawley/gallery/ …    
    
    
    Improving Workspace for Business Travel http://myturnstone.com/blog/improving-workspace-for-business-travel/#.UHZiSnt1Wyg.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Check out "Digital DUMBO's dd:SOCIAL -  A Search for Real Life Presented by Bing" http://ddsocialbing-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    @AmandaKRue I met you at @DigitalDUMBO a while ago...I'm planning on going to the Bing one next week! See you there?    
    
    
    @AmandaKRue No worries! I'll see you next time!    
    
    
    23 Reasons Why “Hocus Pocus” Is The Best Halloween Movie Of All Time http://www.buzzfeed.com/daves4/reasons-why-hocus-pocus-is-the-best-halloween-mo … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    It's a Labyrinth kind of night. David Bowies bulge and all that    
    
    
    Reading Chuck Anderson of NoPattern Meets Turnstone’s Paper Table on @designmilk http://design-milk.com/chuck-anderson-of-nopattern-meets-turnstones-paper-table/ …    
    
    
    Photographing a party (@ Dark Horse) http://4sq.com/QYrthS     
    
    
    I just reached Level 9 of the "Fresh Brew" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 40 different coffee shops! http://4sq.com/Tkhr85     
    
    
    @AH_Ethan I want winter snuggles already    
    
    
    Long distance relationships are rough. But the hard times are worth it when you have the one.    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan YAY!!! So what days are you doing again?    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan Get the ticket as early as possible for Thursday evening, and late Monday night. So excited!!!    
    
    
    Solar Power for your Workspace http://myturnstone.com/blog/solar-power-for-your-workspace/#.UHwwn7BW2zk.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    @AH_Ethan How'd you hear about her? She's good    
    
    
    Busy day. My team is coming in from Michigan for a couple days @myturnstone (@ Steelcase) http://4sq.com/RCee3L     
    
    
    5 Reasons People Fail (& What to Do Instead) http://www.inc.com/geoffrey-james/5-reasons-people-fail-what-to-do-instead.html … via @Inc @Carly_Johnston    
    
    
    Featured Story: Scout Branding @scoutbranding http://myturnstone.com/blog/featured-story-scout-branding/#.UH8cr59AGTk.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Team dinner @myturnstone (@ Landmarc) http://4sq.com/TdcYcH     
    
    
    I just ousted @dreys as the mayor of Steelcase WorkLife Center on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/r3eYhs     
    
    
    Follow lots of people and unfollow the inactives using Tweepi's geeky Twitter tools. http://tweepi.com/?3     
    
    
    I'm at Duravit NYC w/ @hotlead http://4sq.com/RFF4Z4     
    
    
    Forget Work-Life Balance:  It's Time for Work-Life Blend - Forbes http://onforb.es/TBX2LM     
    
    
    I'm at The Counting Room w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/Pgv8Jw     
    
    
    New gay bar by the same people that did Sugarland (@ This N That w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/Ve8H4r     
    
    
    I'm at Cup w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/UjEsgG     
    
    
    Brunch with the boys (@ Westville East w/ @nathan_lacy) http://4sq.com/RagqlL     
    
    
    I'm at Ricky's (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/VfGMB6     
    
    
    I'm at Beacon's Closet (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/VfNs2e     
    
    
    Bacon the dog is bacon for Halloween! #baconbklynparty http://instagr.am/p/RBsBWjxebe/     
    
    
    @UncleSophie It was great seeing you! It was crazy there...thanks for the awesome table, that was bomb of you. Lets hang soon.    
    
    
    @cr_snake_bacon Bacon is meat candy    
    
    
    Bacon is tired #baconbklynparty http://instagr.am/p/RB1BVhReVE/     
    
    
    I'm at Steelcase (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/PqJQOo     
    
    
    Featured Story: Klout http://myturnstone.com/blog/featured-story-klout/#.UIgGBvL76T0.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Designer Creates Typographical Jokes, To Humor Fellow Designers - http://DesignTAXI.com  http://shar.es/chKZN  via @sharethis @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    I'm at Brooklyn Brewery (Brooklyn, NY) http://4sq.com/PVzx4H     
    
    
    I unlocked the “Zombie Swarm” badge on @foursquare for checking in with a crowd on Halloween! Gangnam Style galore. http://4sq.com/Sf8hgL     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Halloween 2012” badge on @foursquare! Has anyone seen my Honey Boo Boo mask? http://4sq.com/RTfNLA     
    
    
    Burlesque! Tim Burton (@ Matchless w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/RTfL6q     
    
    
    Inside the Offices of Meetup http://myturnstone.com/blog/inside-the-offices-of-meetup/#.UI7lp3uSpO4.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    Photo: Halloween : Lady Rainicorn and Lord Monichromicorn #AdventureTime #CartoonNetwork (at Midnight Radio) http://tmblr.co/Zj-FhxWFaJ7D     
    
    
    Lots of debris in the street and it is still very windy and wet, but the worst is over #brooklyn #sandynyc #sandy #hurricane    
    
    
    Everyone, Don't Worry, THE PONIES ARE OKAY - Probably my favorite part of watching the storm coverage... @msrachelmarie http://tmblr.co/ZczZutWHZ37Q     
    
    
    Photoset: Jetblue has put together an apologetic yet patient-sounding explanation for all the a-holes who... http://tmblr.co/ZczZutWHP2g4  @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    The servers are down because of flooding but SOOO freakin glad I can still get @Jezebel updates thanks to @tumblr. Keep it comin!    
    
    
    Havin some drinks! You should meet us, just hop on the subw...oh wait...@dryerdoor (@ The Levee w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/TUUxK9     
    
    
    Post Sandy drinks with @hotlead and @ah_ethan (@ Harefield Road w/ @hotlead) http://4sq.com/VCluxU     
    
    
    I'm at Legion w/ @nathan_lacy http://4sq.com/SbmFU2     
    
    
    I'm at Duck Duck (Brooklyn, NY) w/ 7 others http://4sq.com/Sbp4Og     
    
    
    @msrachelmarie I immediately thought of you!! Girls night with wine and that movie, yes? Text me! Xoxox    
    
    
    It is 2012. The dumb blonde jokes need to stop. Kthxbai    
    
    
    Watch: MTA walkthrough in flooded NYC subway station http://www.cbsnews.com/video/watch/?id=50134223n … via @cbsnews    
    
    
    Customer Spotlight: Greenbiz http://myturnstone.com/blog/customer-spotlight-greenbiz/#.UJFkzO6jcxY.twitter … via @myturnstone @greenbiz    
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Ghoul Night” badge on @foursquare for celebrating Halloween on a school night! http://4sq.com/TnDHgs     
    
    
    How Creatives Inspire Innovation and Stay Productive http://myturnstone.com/blog/how-creatives-inspire-innovation-and-stay-productive/#.UJKfREEvhk8.twitter … via @myturnstone    
    
    
    There is a line of cars abandoned because people are trying to get gas from the station two blocks away #sandy http://4sq.com/VgljNi     
    
    
    There are at least 50 cars waiting in line for gas at the corner of Bushwick ave and Metropolitan ave in Brooklyn #sandy    
    
    
    @msrachelmarie Sounds good! I will be around    
    
    
    Dark chocolate stout #brooklyn #brooklynbrewery #newyork @ Brooklyn Brewery http://instagr.am/p/Ri68wAReSu/     
    
    
    Old Rasputin at the Wythe Hotel. I love this man cc: @ah_ethan #fb    
    
    
    Too chilly for southern blood. He borrowed my sparkly scarf cc: @ah_ethan pic.twitter.com/2ATFyjIX    
    
    
    Such a puss “@AH_Ethan: “@Kbedosky: Too chilly for southern blood. He borrowed my sparkly scarf pic.twitter.com/2ATFyjIX” yea. Its 48 degrees!”    
    
    
    Angry southern face. Too cold for this Georgia boy #georgia #savannah #brooklyn #newyork #wythehotel http://instagr.am/p/RjQ5pGxeVj/     
    
    
    Here Are MTA Photos of Flooded Subway Tunnels Under the East River http://updates.gawker.com/post/34882103114/here-are-mta-photos-of-flooded-subway-tunnels-under-the …    
    
    
    Watch Bill O'Reilly's totally condescending video about single female voters. http://www.slate.com/blogs/xx_factor/2012/11/01/bill_o_reilly_on_single_women_voters_hot_good_at_costumes_not_too_smart.html?utm_source=tw&utm_medium=sm&utm_campaign=button_chunky … via @doublexmag    
    
    
    Fun.: Carry On [OFFICIAL VIDEO]: http://youtu.be/q7yCLn-O-Y0  via @youtube @AH_Ethan    
    
    
    New colors on my Twitter! All shiny and fancy now    
    
    
    Just signed up for @Newsle - check out my profile and follow your friends in the news! http://newsle.com/kbedosky     
    
    
    Your Car: The Future of Connected Health?  - http://www.xconomy.com/san-francisco/2012/11/05/your-car-the-future-of-connected-health/ … via Shareaholic    
    
    
    "I believe that when people have control over their physical space, it empowers them to take more risks...” http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1671050     
    
    
    HubSpot hits 100m  - http://www.xconomy.com/boston/2012/11/05/hubspot-hits-100m-raised-moves-closer-to-ipo-or-acquisition/ … via Shareaholic    
    
    
    Me and @AH_Ethan in #nyc http://instagr.am/p/RqOR0uxeYY/     
    
    
    