Morgan Freeman deserved the OSCAR for INVICTUS. His portrayal of President Nelson Mandela was simply AMAZING!    
    
    
    @BrianWilson38 You made our race day so memorable!! :) You are the coolest!!    
    
    
    Please vote by clicking this link EVERY DAY: http://www.amw.com/allstar/2010/nominee-detail.cfm?id=7735    
    
    
    I'm at HP Pavilion at San Jose (525 W Santa Clara St, at N Autumn St, San Jose). http://4sq.com/8SVk5P    
    
    
    I'm at Alcatraz Cruises (Pier 33, Bay Street, San Francisco). http://4sq.com/6N7rM1    
    
    
    is working at 752a on a saturday. need to go back to bed    
    
    
    went back to bed until 2p. went into the office. now chilling before a night out in the big apple    
    
    
    is getting ready to head out to the Upper West Side with Elana :)    
    
    
    is exhaused from a fun night at blondie's and her new fav bar "the blue donkey" on the UWS    
    
    
    why can't i sleep? any tips for restless nights?    
    
    
    watching little miss sunshine-great movie! hilarious    
    
    
    is up and ready to ice skate and workout :)    
    
    
    Staring at Jude Law right now    
    
    
    is soo excited for Jude Law :) Can't wait for a photo with him    
    
    
    I GOT A PHOTO WITH JUDE LAW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    he rocks!    
    
    
    lil miss sunshine rocks! superfreak!!    
    
    
    trying to go back to bed-need sleep!! :(    
    
    
    http://www.davidjmccauley.org/home    
    
    
    http://www.peaceoneday.org/    
    
    
    This is Jude Law's organization - http://www.peaceoneday.org/    
    
    
    Like my new pic?    
    
    
    Me & Jude Law - cute couple, eh? :)    
    
    
    just spent dinner with her cousin David, who dove into a pool in E Hampton this past September and became paralyzed from the chest down.    
    
    
    just woke and contemplatong hitting the gym for the 6am boxgin class...leaning towards yes, but so tired :(    
    
    
    loves red wine...    
    
    
    can't sleep ... too much work to do :( can't wait for the weekend!    
    
    
    had a fun nite w lauren. worked out, made dinner and watched sex and the city. perfect girls night out!    
    
    
    getting ready to go out :)    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (JFK International Airport, at Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 38 others    
    
    
    just arrived home from a night in the UWS, LES and Latin Qrtr (place where Plexi was shot-Giants)-good times :)    
    
    
    just saw "he's just not that into you" - it rocks!    
    
    
    wonders if anyone has a cure for insomnia....    
    
    
    watching Obama!    
    
    
    off to meditate! :)    
    
    
    what is the best way to reduce stress?    
    
    
    is excited to go on vacation :)    
    
    
    is happy to be home after one week of vacation :)    
    
    
    excited for the oscars!!    
    
    
    On a weekday at 9am, Mama's still has a line! Hope the food is worth the wait! Any recos?? http://4sq.com/mPNi96     
    
    
    125 West 16th St, #130 NY NY 10011    
    
    
    Vote to give this idea 250K: Create World Virtual School to provide free courses to global students  #pepsirefresh http://pep.si/9v3JW3    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Coldplay - live stream from Madrid today at 1pm PST! Watch it! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7zLUsNU5Hpg&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    HAPPY 95th BIRTHDAY GRANDPA! :-) (@ Essex Fells Country Club) http://4sq.com/dxvOMU    
    
    
    is happy to be home from Vegas!    
    
    
    La clase en espanol con mis amigas (@ Jewish Community Center of San Francisco (JCCSF) w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/sXj9FT     
    
    
    just got stopped by a casting director on the subway-craziness    
    
    
    Really sad day! Tim is leaving us - we'll miss you!    
    
    
    is still bummed Tim is leaving Google, but happy that he will be CEO of AOL. off to yoga and journey dance now!    
    
    
    is happy for a new day!    
    
    
    Sweet!! (@ The Westin Verasa Napa w/ @narni) [pic]: http://4sq.com/thJCoW     
    
    
    at 2009 Media Summit New York    
    
    
    just had a lemon cosmo on my way home from work. why dont women go to bars alone more often?? its great!    
    
    
    such tragic news about Natasha Richardson :(    
    
    
    love good wine, good cheese and fondue :) yeah divine bar!    
    
    
    Why is it snowing on the first day of SPRING?!! Bizzaro    
    
    
    ate at craftsteak-delicious :)    
    
    
    What does "Woot, Woot" mean???    
    
    
    Coke Makes Life Better    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare! Pies all around! http://4sq.com/unoEsr     
    
    
    Best pizza in SF! (@ Tony's Pizza Napoletana w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/scC501     
    
    
    Google Latitude rocks!!    
    
    
    Amazing show! + Miguel and his mom!! (@ TOTEM by Cirque du Soleil at AT&T Park w/ 11 others) http://4sq.com/vBCBBI     
    
    
    Happy its Friday!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/kmF_kGLioY0?a  AD BLITZ 2011 Vote Now    
    
    
    1st day of snow in NYC :)    
    
    
    Wanting to relax. Awful day with the rain and stress....still working - no fun!    
    
    
    Happy it's Saturday....Go Villanova!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    http://www.tastethemadness.com/ (via @addthis)    
    
    
    at Stephen's --- can't wait for a ride in the Viper    
    
    
    On the way back home to my city :) I missed the big apple!    
    
    
    injured my ankle severely....waiting for an x-ray    
    
    
    Know any good places in Italy? Off to Vicenza tomorrow. Plan to go to Cinque de Terre, Florence and Tuscany :)    
    
    
    Currently working in London, United Kingdom    
    
    
    Currently working in Google/YouTube London, United Kingdom    
    
    
    drinking a raspberry margarita at newark airport. can't wait to be in italy and away from the stresses of work!    
    
    
    I'm at 30 Rockefeller Plaza (30 Rockefeller Plaza, at 49th St, New York) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/vviDGC     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Photogenic" badge on foursquare! Say cheese! http://4sq.com/taEOTk     
    
    
    had an amazing trip to italy!! :) pizza, gelato and wine - oh my!    
    
    
    in the windy city of chicago for work. its supposed to snow tomorrow-bizarro!!    
    
    
    flying home. turbulence sucks.    
    
    
    http://spring13run-smccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Get in shape this spring with Marathon Matt's running group! http://spring13run-smccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    nyc is beautiful! today is a day of taking care of me-facial, hair highlight, nails, meditation and journeydance!! oh how i miss italy!!    
    
    
    best thai place in manhattan-galanga west 4th and 6th ave    
    
    
    enjoying this weather!! suntanning on the deck :) off for mojitos on dave's roof! fun times :)    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Mike!!    
    
    
    @darrenrovell Please tune into YouTube's Ad Blitz program http://www.youtube.com/adblitz  at the end of the game to check out Super Bowl commercials!    
    
    
    I'm at Five Points (31 Great Jones St, Lafayette, New York). http://4sq.com/h4s1Sp    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan http://YouTube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    is it the weekend yet?    
    
    
    i miss italia :(    
    
    
    Landon Donovan just summed it up perfectly: "It Just sucks, man."    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Newbie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aESivf    
    
    
    Matzos ball soup for a sore throat!! :-) (@ Hollywood Diner) http://4sq.com/6UkFSn    
    
    
    Dump (@ Penn Station) http://4sq.com/8ZKrHd    
    
    
    I'm at Google NYC (76 9th Ave. (4th Fl.), b/w 15th & 16th, New York). http://4sq.com/4uC0th    
    
    
    My first time quoted in the press - holla :) woot woot! http://lnkd.in/VQmcC5     
    
    
    Wish I was in London right now!!!!    
    
    
    Paul McCartney's performing LIVE in Hyde Park, London: http://www.youtube.com/user/BornHIVFree    
    
    
    NYC LOVES PAUL!    
    
    
    Don't forget to sign the Global Petition to the right :) Cheers!! What a brilliant cause!    
    
    
    The Long & Winding Road......classic Beatle hit! Sweet!!!    
    
    
    #bornhivfree #HRC2010 Argentina just won World Cup!    
    
    
    Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da = my favorite Beatles song!!    
    
    
    i'm going mad......i've been at work way too long    
    
    
    toe up from da flo up    
    
    
    Soul: This or That http://www.youtube.com/kiasoul?x=showcase_3727    
    
    
    @ The City Bakery in NYC-best hot chocolate in the city and i just discovered they have my fav fruit-cherries and lychees :) xoxo happy moms    
    
    
    West Elm is the coolest store for decorating your place!! :) xoxox love it    
    
    
    I'm at Jamba Juice - Eighth Ave & 23rd (249 8th Ave, at W. 23rd St, New York). http://4sq.com/4DVi4f    
    
    
    I'm at AMC Loews Lincoln Square 13 (1998 Broadway, btw 67th & 68th, New York). http://4sq.com/3nJ8aV    
    
    
    Brunch w the girls! (@ Cafe Ronda) http://4sq.com/8DTNLE    
    
    
    Watching the World Cup!! Go Spain!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    I'm at Cafeteria (119 7th Ave, 17th St, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/2vlpni    
    
    
    I'm at Blue Light (1979 Union St, at Buchanan, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/x9pdga     
    
    
    ready for the wedding this weekend and a break from nyc! :)    
    
    
    massage at google, dinner at "casa" - best brazilian food in nyc! :) fun nite!    
    
    
    I'm at Cafeteria (119 7th Ave, 17th St, New York). http://4sq.com/2vlpni    
    
    
    I'm at West Side Highway - 10th Ave. Exit (New York). http://4sq.com/dq0GCO    
    
    
    countdown to wedding!!!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Adventurer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aj1wcd    
    
    
    I'm at Bodhizone (110 E 23rd, 3rd Fl, Park Ave South, New York). http://4sq.com/aukq9B    
    
    
    I'm at City Bakery (3 W 18th St, btw 5th and 6th Ave, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/4ro4Vk    
    
    
    Go Holland!!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    THE DUTCH ARE IN THE FINALS!!!!! YAY! GO ORANGE!!    
    
    
    I'm at Nike 255 Custom Lab (255 Elizabeth St, btw Houston and Prince, New York). http://4sq.com/4RStDF    
    
    
    I'm at Nike Sportswear (21 Mercer St, btw Grand & Howard St, New York). http://4sq.com/4QkDH4    
    
    
    Dinner w amazing friends!! :-) (@ Galanga) http://4sq.com/71EiJQ    
    
    
    Ready to fly!!!    
    
    
    #worldcup Go Holland!    
    
    
    Watching the World Cup unfold on Twitter at http://twitter.com/worldcup/home    
    
    
    #worldcup# Go Holland!    
    
    
    #world cup Go Holland!    
    
    
    I'm at Trapeze School of New York (518 west 30th st, Btw 10th and 11th, New York) http://4sq.com/g1S7Fi    
    
    
    Happy bday Tara!:-) (@ Taco Chulo) http://4sq.com/2H5L4n    
    
    
    Getting ready for wedding day! Cocktail party was a blast last nite-back to bed! :) xox    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cK4Awh    
    
    
    Go Mets! (@ Citi Field w/ 131 others) http://4sq.com/a0BDhh    
    
    
    Amazing caramelized French toast, kale, tofu & BEST hot chocolate in Manhattan (@ City Bakery) http://4sq.com/4ro4Vk    
    
    
    Study study! (@ Google NYC) http://4sq.com/4uC0th    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Local" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/91QeaE    
    
    
    Third Place World Cup time!!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    I'm at Downtown Galway Hooker (133 7th Ave. South, btw Charles & 10th Street, New York). http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    Chilling    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza w/ @shawnamcd http://4sq.com/HtWlUD     
    
    
    #OldSpice    
    
    
    @Old Spice How are you??? I love the smell of adventure!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Bender" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bL04vO    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super User" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aflwuk    
    
    
    I'm at Ziegfeld Theater (141 W 54th St, btw 6th & 7th, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/7KoTYf    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza (San Francisco, CA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/Id2fKi     
    
    
    Indy 500!! Go Helio Castroneves! Team Penske!!! :)    
    
    
    Indy 500 - Go Helio!!! Less than 15 laps to go to be a third-time Indy 500 championship!!    
    
    
    Helio is about to win-3-time Indy 500 champion in one decade    
    
    
    Helio won!!! Biggest race in the world :)    
    
    
    I love Helio-he rocks!!    
    
    
    Indy 500 Champion Helio Castroneves steals the championship a third-time!! History in the making!    
    
    
    I'm at Coachella Music Festival (Indio, CA) w/ 55 others http://4sq.com/IKBicp     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/lifeinaday #lifeinaday    
    
    
    #Helio Castroneves was robbed today at the Edmonton race......ridiculous!    
    
    
    @h3lio - you were robbed today at Edmonton! So sorry, man.....your always positive attitude is a real inspiration to all of your fans!    
    
    
    @NFNiTM Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @ronsracing88 This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @dracasaga Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @rds4life Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @RossMacLochness Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @YahooXtraSport Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @ronsracing88 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @martinpinnau Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @robertmajak Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @golic_2004 This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @kevingraham1280 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @packerfan858 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    #HelioCastroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    http://www.autosport.com/news/report.php/id/85569?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter    
    
    
    @dalejrschick he was robbed!! ridiculous    
    
    
    #HelioCastroneves was ROBBED!!!! ridiculous Indy Car!    
    
    
    #Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!!!!!!!!!! Ridiculous!    
    
    
    @brianvermette totally agree - Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    @IndyCarPR Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    @YouTube awesome!    
    
    
    off to my summer share! can't wait to drink some vino!!    
    
    
    I'm at Bodhizone (110 E 23rd, 3rd Fl, Park Ave South, New York). http://4sq.com/aukq9B    
    
    
    lying on the beach    
    
    
    1st day in my share house: met amazing ppl    
    
    
    2nd day in my share house: went jogging by the light house and accidentally ran into the "nude" beach! wow! eye opener!    
    
    
    2nd day at share house: went for a run and stumbled into a nude beach!! wow! eye opener!    
    
    
    Display in 2011: The Future Belongs to Google | ClickZ http://www.clickz.com/clickz/news/1934048/display-2011-future-belongs-google … via @clickz    
    
    
    Missing the weekend at the beach....    
    
    
    Hump Day is nearly here!!!    
    
    
    Get the hottest beauty tips from the leading beauty gurus on YouTube! www.youtube.com/destinationbeauty    
    
    
    journeydance, meditation and pilates.....beautiful weather, oh my!    
    
    
    HAPPY BIRTHDAY Johnny Depp!    
    
    
    who says white chocolate martinis from max brenners, poutene pomme frites and 16 Handles can't cheer you up? (and a good blowout)    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different pizza joints! http://4sq.com/KmRqlW     
    
    
    I'm at Delarosa (San Francisco, CA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/KmRnXg     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kfEzHdWKOoQ    
    
    
    @reggie_bush 100% agree    
    
    
    #bonnaroolive AWESOME!!!! Thanks Dell :)    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (JFK International Airport, Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 84 others http://4sq.com/i8spxn    
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (1 S McDonnell Rd, at S Link Rd, San Francisco) w/ 50 others http://4sq.com/fKeADG    
    
    
    @BrianWilson38 Brian - any shot you are in SF next week and want to swing by a surprise party for my boyfriend? He's a die hard fan"    
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (1 S McDonnell Rd, at S Link Rd, San Francisco) w/ 82 others. http://4sq.com/MTivk    
    
    
    @BlueVmovie When and where will this film be released near the San Francisco Bay area? Dying to see it! Even contemplating driving 2 LA    
    
    
    I'm at Zero Zero (826 Folsom St, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/dPXrCp    
    
    
    I'm at The Slanted Door (1 Ferry Building #3, San Francisco) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/fjqMIS    
    
    
    I'm at Googleplex (1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, at Charleston Rd, Mountain View) http://4sq.com/gImxcI    
    
    
    prayers to michael jackson and farrah fawcett    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Superstar" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/effi0q    
    
    
    BLUE VALENTINE here I come! :-) (@ Century San Francisco Centre 9 & XD w/ 9 others) http://4sq.com/iiOnsW    
    
    
    Jury Duty time! :(    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/QxGz7woiwpM?a  2012 Ad Blitz Sizzle Reel    
    
    
    I'm test driving a mini cooper (@ MINI of San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eOyPOO    
    
    
    Seth MacFarlane to Host Oscars http://abcn.ws/O40u4e  (via @ABC)    
    
    
    Can't waiting to catch up with Jess Brummer! (@ District Wine Lounge) http://4sq.com/hpub4f    
    
    
    I miss Brentwood, TN!!    
    
    
    I'm at Ozumo Japanese Restaurant (161 Steuart St, btw Howard & Mission, San Francisco) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/h6khNG    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza (San Francisco, CA) http://4sq.com/TR8YOO     
    
    
    @GoogleDisplay Can't wait!    
    
    
    Live Video! Watch our keynote at the MIXX Conference, streaming in a display ad! http://www.google.com/adwords/watchthisspace/live/    
    
    
    Watch This Space - Live Keynote at MIXX: http://lnkd.in/4RAdMz    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/8ZpPAb    
    
    
    I'm at Dos Caminos (675 Hudson St, at 14th St, New York) w/ 4 others. http://4sq.com/dy68YV    
    
    
    #rallyzito SF Giants rock! Way to bring it home!    
    
    
    I'm at 675 Bar w/ @helen_lee_. http://4sq.com/2Be6ar    
    
    
    I'm at Westville Chelsea (246 W 18th St, 7th & 8th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/9aIw9k    
    
    
    I'm at Honey (243 W 14th St, btw 7th & 8th, New York). http://4sq.com/86vPfx    
    
    
    I'm at Crooked Knife 14 (232 West 14th Street, 14th St btw 7th & 8th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/dnIArL    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Crunked" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/9bWKFF    
    
    
    I'm at JFK Int'l Airport - Terminal 7 (Terminal 7, John F. Kennedy Int'l Airport (JFK), Queens). http://4sq.com/1Qb8C9    
    
    
    I'm at Enoshima (2280 chestnut st, Chestnut & scott, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hcnEh6    
    
    
    I'm at Nectar Wine Lounge (3330 Steiner, btw Lombard and Chestnut, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eUR2J2    
    
    
    I'm at Horseshoe Tavern (2024 Chestnut St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hcwaSj    
    
    
    I'm at MatrixFillmore (3138 Fillmore St, at Greenwich St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/gRhW31    
    
    
    I'm at The Brixton (2140 Union St., Fillmore, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/faQQpE    
    
    
    I'm at Ferry Plaza Farmers' Market (1 Ferry Building, The Embaracadero, at Market St, San Francisco) w/ 11 others http://4sq.com/h9oT1w    
    
    
    I'm at YouTube HQ (901 Cherry Ave, at Bayhill Dr, San Bruno). http://4sq.com/6EZmR3    
    
    
    I'm at Daily Grill - San Francisco (347 Geary Street, btw Mason St & Powell St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/fOQZW3    
    
    
    I'm at Los Angeles International Airport (LAX) ✈ (1 World Way, at Sepulveda Blvd, Los Angeles) w/ 46 others. http://4sq.com/qm5av    
    
    
    I'm at Viceroy Santa Monica (1819 Ocean, Pico Blvd, Santa Monica). http://4sq.com/82iDQB    
    
    
    I'm at The Parkside Cafe (43 Arenal Ave., Stinson Beach) http://4sq.com/egtSaA    
    
    
    first tie in the NFL since 2008. wow. both teams look so unhappy :( 

#49ers    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Far Far Away" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bfJ1Ex    
    
    
    Delicious upper east side down pineapple dessert and fabulous company w/ my E-Fo! (@ Shake Shack) http://4sq.com/covAmR    
    
    
    I'm at Chelsea Piers Sports Center (60 Chelsea Piers, New York). http://4sq.com/50tt9u    
    
    
    I'm at Westville Chelsea (246 W 18th St, 7th & 8th Ave, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/9aIw9k    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/xWnvjHN74dk?a  Kesha- Die Young (Lyrics)    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/Ys7-6_t7OEQ?a  Justin Bieber - Beauty And A Beat ft. Nicki Minaj    
    
    
    Who was complaining about Kaepernick last week? That's right. Keep your mouths closed! #49ers Go Colin!    
    
    
    Visit the Harry Potter page for videos, photos, and more! http://www.youtube.com/harrypotter    
    
    
    #DeathlyHallows Amazing Live Stream on YouTube!!! JK Rowling just arrived!!! I love Harry!    
    
    
    #LiveCocoCam This rocks!    
    
    
    Tune in to the 24 hour live stream with Conan O'Brien! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Tune in to the 24 hour live stream with Conan O'Brien today! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Check out Conan O'Brien's 24 hour LIVE stream on YouTube! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Off to the Guggenheim for an unveiling of YT Play! http://lnkd.in/9f-5Eh    
    
    
    I'm at Marengo on Union (1980 Union Street, Buchanan Street, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/fEC34L    
    
    
    YT Play (@ Guggenheim Museum w/ @johnmilitello @helen_lee_) http://4sq.com/2Ku3x6    
    
    
    I'm at YouTube HQ (901 Cherry Ave, at Bayhill Dr, San Bruno) http://4sq.com/eJnZJU    
    
    
    I'm at City Crab & Seafood Company (235 Park Ave South, at E. 19th St, New York). http://4sq.com/7DpECW    
    
    
    I'm at XYZ Bar @ W Hotel in San Francisco (San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eGOzRo    
    
    
    Price Of Super Bowl Commercials Hit Record High | http://www.ballerstatus.com/2013/01/04/price-super-bowl-commercials-hit-record-high/ … via @ballerstatus    
    
    
    Best coffee in SF! (@ Blue Bottle Coffee w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/gdlCLJ    
    
    
    loved #niceguyjohnny and meeting @edward_burns today @google !!!    
    
    
    I'm at Google Creative Sandbox 2010 (82 Mercer St, New York) w/ 36 others. http://4sq.com/9Betm2    
    
    
    Sunday funday (@ Triptych w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/VE3FCL     
    
    
    Amazing brunch after a strenuous hike in Marin: Hill 88! (@ Bacheeso's Grand Avenue) http://4sq.com/envsRM    
    
    
    Help kick off the Pepsi Superbowl Halftime Show. Upload your photo at http://pepsi.com  #PepsiHalftime http://www.pepsi.com/halftime     
    
    
    I love #
@le_tote !    
    
    
    #iabuk    
    
    
    #iabuk Awesome! Can't wait to see Bruce Daisley from Google/YouTube!!    
    
    
    #iabuk Tune-in to IAB UK's 2010 Engage Conference being live streamed right now. Bruce Daisley is up in a few minutes to talk about VIDEO!    
    
    
    #BRHangout Which commercials do you think will "win" this Harbaugh Bowl?    
    
    
    #BRHangout this is one of the best G+ On-Air Hangouts I've ever seen....so entertaining! LOVE the surprise cameos! Woot!! :)    
    
    
    #BRHangout Where will you rewatch the Super Bowl commercials? YouTube's Ad Blitz!!! View & Vote on your favorites    
    
    
    @DeStorm Love your Ad Blitz Video! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=58Ouzhdh-j8 …    
    
    
    @DeStorm HAPPY BELATED! You are my cryptonite ;)    
    
    
    Check out as we upload all of the commercials in real-time during #Super Bowl on YouTube's Ad Blitz!http://www.youtube.com/adblitz  & VOTE    
    
    
    KICK BALL LEAGUE! (@ Bar None w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/giajbo    
    
    
    @DeStorm Happy Super Bowl Sunday!! Don't forget YouTube's Ad Blitz @ http://www.youtube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    #49ers taking it home in this year's Big Game @YouTube #AdBlitz http://www.youtube.com/adblitz?x=/s/tw     
    
    
    @YouTube #AdBlitz http://www.youtube.com/adblitz?x=/s/tw     
    
    
    Which ad ruled the Big Game? Watch, share and vote for your favorites. Visit YouTube  http://adblitz2013.appspot.com/d/     
    
    
    @le_tote  LOVE this new green silk tee. All set for my "first date" tonight thanks to Le Tote! pic.twitter.com/khZkR8oa    
    
    
    Just had lunch next to Sergey Brin! (@ Googleplex - Cafe Moma) http://4sq.com/grKZRU    
    
    
    I'm rooting for The Lumineers #GRAMMYs http://bitly.com/WssOlx     
    
    
    My #GRAMMYLegend is  http://bit.ly/yP1zvT     
    
    
    YouTube’s AdBlitz Channel Has Changed The World of Advertising http://news.yahoo.com/youtube-adblitz-channel-changed-world-advertising-says-online-070223762.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    @le_tote LOVE this dress pic.twitter.com/NHWXaNyM    
    
    
    YouTube Blog: 2013 YouTube Ad Blitz Winners Revealed http://youtube-global.blogspot.com/2013/02/2013-youtube-ad-blitz-winners-revealed.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    RAM's 'Farmer' Voted Best Super Bowl Spot in YouTube's Ad Blitz Contest http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/rams-farmer-voted-best-super-bowl-spot-youtubes-ad-blitz-contest-147367 …    
    
    
    RAM's 'Farmer' Voted Best Super Bowl Spot in YouTube's Ad Blitz Contest http://lnkd.in/-j4VwF     
    
    
    Check out the winners from YouTube's Ad Blitz being interviewed by http://Adweek.com  now in a G+Hangout On-Air! http://www.youtube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    http://money.cnn.com/2011/01/25/technology/google_hiring/index.htm?hpt=T2 Send me your resume and job listing BEFORE applying online    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/g1338a    
    
    
    I'm in Vegas baby! :-) (@ Las Vegas McCarran International Airport (LAS) ✈ w/ @flippnyc) http://4sq.com/hPLt57    
    
    
    Woot woot (@ Encore at Wynn Hotel & Casino) http://4sq.com/fgvpY7    
    
    
    Who do you think will win at the #Oscars? Join me and fill out a My Picks official Oscar ballot. http://oscar.go.com/mypicks#user=suemccauley%26ushare=7e1973af87f710b78ff51aa89a8fd095d12a1aea60ab4423 …    
    
    
    #oscar +1 a bird per bradley cooper ;)    
    
    
    Love this feed :) Yay Oscars! Thanks AP Live! - #Oscars live on http://livestre.am/rJU     
    
    
    #bestdressed I love Charlize Theron's dress!    
    
    
    #bestdressed Renee Zellwegger looks AWFUL! Did she do her own hair? fail    
    
    
    I think charlize theron is the #bestdressed on the #Oscars Red Carpet http://oscar.go.com/red-carpet     
    
    
    @SethMacFarlane was the best Oscar host I've seen in a long time :) Super funny!!    
    
    
    @LE_tote love this dress! pic.twitter.com/JjfS7MHqs2    
    
    
    FWA mobile winner | YouTube Ad Blitz http://www.thefwa.com/mobile/youtube-ad-blitz …    
    
    
    Google is hiring! Check it out: www.google.com/jobs please email me your resume and the job title/description...don't apply directly    
    
    
    Love this dress! @le_tote    
    
    
    Love this Le Tote dress! May have to keep this and the bracelet :) @le_tote pic.twitter.com/N39ZePZ49H    
    
    
    1st time skiing (@ Northstar-at-Tahoe Resort w/ 12 others) http://4sq.com/gFuwg1    
    
    
    Happy St Patty's Day @le_tote pic.twitter.com/S7jxSo1ynK    
    
    
    I'm at Sears Fine Foods (439 Powell, San Francisco) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/fsvVHo    
    
    
    Oasis (@ Yerba Buena Gardens) http://4sq.com/hMNBTz    
    
    
    @le_tote Check out this fantastic article on Le Tote! http://www.sfchronicle.com/style/article/Companies-let-users-rent-most-everything-4412989.php …    
    
    
    Companies let users rent most everything http://lnkd.in/gtjb2G     
    
    
    A comedic web series packed with a punch http://kickstarter.com     
    
    
    ME + YOU = SWEET VICTORY for @blogotheque. RT and VOTE : #Webbys http://wbby.co/f0x9     
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love this! Thanks T Mobile & YouTube!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive Love this! Woot!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive Thank you T-Mobile and Google | YouTube for making this possible!    
    
    
    Coachella LIVE on YouTube, April 12-14. Presented by T-Mobile http://www.youtube.com/coachella     
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love the harlem shake!!!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love coachella    
    
    
    Happy Wednesday!    
    
    
    Getting pumped for San Francisco :) xoxox    
    
    
    driving to Napa in a convertible....just passed .just saw my 1st live hitchhiker!    
    
    
    Loving this perfect weather in Napa......great wine, delicious food, amazing friends and my hair blowin in our convertible :) love!    
    
    
    Driving Thelma and Louise style in Napa! :)    
    
    
    amazed at God's awesome beauty in Napa - breathtaking!    
    
    
    just toured Castello di Amorosa...chocolate and wine pairings-delicious :) xoxo    
    
    
    just ate bacon chocolate-DELICIOUS-ever tried it??    
    
    
    delicious lunch at Taylor's Refresher in Napa! off to frog's leap winery. pick strawberries and drink champgane! oh my :)    
    
    
    @le_tote Just another day at the office styled in Le Tote! Yay! pic.twitter.com/6HD0SLgqkK    
    
    
    Why Women Aren't Crazy http://goodmenproject.com/featured-content/why-women-arent-crazy/ … via @goodmenproject    
    
    
    thelma and louise meets sideways is how you describe our napa valley adventure!! :)    
    
    
    foggy day in SF - barely see the tip of the golden gate bridge!! cold weather in SF!    
    
    
    THE INTERNSHIP - IN THEATERS JUNE 7 http://lnkd.in/zRxHVY     
    
    
    just landed in Chicago! I had an amazing trip to San Fran, San Bruno, Mtn View and Napa Valley. Excited to explore the Windy City! :) xox    
    
    
    off to go boating on fox lake in illinois! :)    
    
    
    W Lakeshore Hotel in Chicago is by far the BEST Starwood property (next to the Sheraton in Leblon, Brazil)....fantastico :)    
    
    
    Outside Lands rocks    
    
    
    Watch WeTV this evening - Weigh Down and Gwen Shamblin:  http://bit.ly/LsrzM    
    
    
    Very tired and happy to be going home.....    
    
    
    'http://www.wetv.com/video/34982139001/extreme-diets-eating-garbage' via @addthis    
    
    
    happy to be have arrived safely to NY....Praise God! Can't wait to sleep in my own bed    
    
    
    #geekierthanyou    
    
    
    @ijustine amazing job at VidCon! You are amazing!    
    
    
    @shaycarl awesome job moderating!!! Love the Shaytards    
    
    
    I'm at Judy's Cafe (2268 Chestnut, Scott St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/gMtn2U    
    
    
    Watching the CMA Festival on ABC...    
    
    
    Watching the CMA Music Festival on ABC    
    
    
    Martina McBride & Kid Rock just blew me away with the song "Picture" at the CMA Music Festival...    
    
    
    Taylor Swift totally ROCKED it with "Love Story"    
    
    
    Hiking in Mt Tam (@ Golden Gate Bridge w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/huq268    
    
    
    Best brunch in Stinson Beach! (@ The Parkside Cafe) http://4sq.com/f1khw0    
    
    
    I'm at Tamalpais http://4sq.com/i2xBr8    
    
    
    Golden State Warriors vs Oklahoma (@ Oracle Arena w/ 52 others) http://4sq.com/fFAV7u    
    
    
    The MTV VMAs have taken the word "distasteful" to a whole new level @vma . Thanks Miley Cyrus. Try wearing clothes next time!    
    
    
    I #votemiley for the 2013 MTV #VMA Best Song of the Summer! See who's in the lead and vote: http://on.mtv.com/17JXpec  #windowsphone    
    
    
    I #votedaftpunk for the 2013 MTV #VMA Best Song of the Summer! See who's in the lead and vote: http://on.mtv.com/17JXpec  #windowsphone    
    
    
    spending the day w my awesome cousin David, Rose and my dad in Jersey City! picture perfect day!    
    
    
    In Stone Harbor, NJ....the weather is looking dismal, but so happy to be here :)    
    
    
    I just signed up for the Urbanathalon in SF on 11/24! Join me! . Men's Health Urbanathlon: San Francisco: http://fw.to/u9p93Jh     
    
    
    Who wouldn't want to hangout and shop with @DVF? Here's your chance, courtesy of @CFDA and @Google. http://www.fashionologie.com/DVF-Host-First-Shoppable-Google-Hangout-31922917 …    
    
    
    Go shopping with one of your favorite designers http://googlecommerce.blogspot.com/2013/09/go-shopping-with-one-of-your-favorite.html …    
    
    
    #shopthehangout any discounts for people that tuned into today's live G+ Hangout?? :)    
    
    
    Weather report in Stone Harbor? RAIN, RAIN, RAIN :( Can't wait for the sunny weekend!    
    
    
    watching the surf competition at nuns' beach in stone harbor, nj. prayin for sunshine tomorrow!!    
    
    
    I voted for Rihanna to win Artist of the Year at the YouTube Music Awards. http://youtu.be/VJDa2Kbv4RM  #YTMA    
    
    
    I voted for Macklemore & Ryan Lewis's "Same Love" to win Video of the Year at the YouTube Music Awards. http://youtu.be/YZJWg-cB9rM  #YTMA    
    
    
    Russell Brand stinks as a host...very inappropriate    
    
    
    Yeah for the exclusive, extended trailer for "NEW MOON" at the VMAs in Radio City, NYC    
    
    
    Love the Pepsi Refresh commercials...great song! "May you stay ever young..may your heart always be joyful"    
    
    
    @SueMcCauley Russell Brand stinks - can we get a new host next year?    
    
    
    Beyonce just rocked it at the VMA's.....    
    
    
    @SQLChicken Beyonce rocked it with SINGLE LADIES    
    
    
    What is Lady Gaga wearing???    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/gDiim    
    
    
    Ate delicious Thai with Ms. Judd..Excited for church, Lauren's bridal shower and Nickie's visit to see WICKED on Broadway tomorrow    
    
    
    Happy New Year! Don't forget to check out YouTube's Year in Review: http://www.youtube.com/user/theyearinreview …    
    
    
    Loving my Christmas dresses - thanks @letote pic.twitter.com/ofyOfrZKmg    
    
    
    Loving my Christmas dresses - thanks @letote pic.twitter.com/e3DUjcwTmV    
    
    
    Anyone going to CES next week? If so, let's meet up!    
    
    
    Mindy From 'The Mindy Project' Is Stalking You On Tinder, Sort Of http://huff.to/1drLo3t  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Anyone heading to CES?    
    
    
    Niners are back!!!!!!    
    
    
    just had a delicious thai dinner with my fabulous pre-birthday kripalu buds!!!    
    
    
    just ate a delicious surprise pre-birthday thai dinner w my kripalu buds..now back 2 work :(    
    
    
    I'm at Resort at Squaw Creek (400 Squaw Creek Rd., Lake Tahoe-Olympic Valley) http://4sq.com/ei6PAd    
    
    
    Just ate breakfast at the fanciest bakery in Manhattan - The City Bakery! caramelized french toast and to-die-for hot chocolate :) YUM!    
    
    
    on my way to NashVegas!! woohoo :)    
    
    
    headin' home to nyc!    
    
    
    boarding in chicago-home after midnight! i miss brentwood!    
    
    
    home safely - tucked in bed! PG!! :) I miss TN and RF :(    
    
    
    back in nyc and at google!    
    
    
    Off to Fiddlesticks bar now to support Leukemia & Lymphoma Society for Jackie Bona & victims of the Ondoy (Ketsana) Typhoon    
    
    
    @MGShamblin - thanks for the shout-out! Anything I can do to help out WDW & YouTube :) Best Regards!    
    
    
    Need a @BPCleanse Blue Print Cleanse while I am in NYC Mon-Wed: where can I pick one up today/early tomorrow? Thanks! suemccauley@google.com    
    
    
    I'm at The Standard Hotel (848 Washington, New York) http://4sq.com/fZ0ie0    
    
    
    had an awesome night! TGIAF with my team at the google cafeteria....bon voyage drinks for KK @ Maritime hotel..dinner at my fav mexcian w cj    
    
    
    I'm at Chelsea Market (75 9th Ave, btw 15th & 16th St, New York) http://4sq.com/gLQt4v    
    
    
    I'm at Google NYC (76 9th Ave, btw 15th St & 16th St, New York) http://4sq.com/eTfAtN    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "School Night" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/i15YJ7    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/ijLcZI    
    
    
    Please donate and come out this evening to our happy hour fundraiser in the East Village (Sin Sin: 2nd Ave, 5th St www.davidjmccauley.org    
    
    
    Please come out this evening to our happy hour fundraiser in the East Village (Sin Sin: 2nd Ave, 5th St www.davidjmccauley.org    
    
    
    Fading.......ready to go home and sleep....Awesome fundraiser. Can't wait to go to Hoosier-land for the BIG race!!    
    
    
    off to Indianapolis to see The McCauley family and get pumped to run this half-marathon tomorrow :)    
    
    
    Rockin to Michael Shamblin's awesome new single: http://bit.ly/2ctaGc    
    
    
    just landed in indianapolis-home of the hoosiers and Indy 500! :)    
    
    
    Home in Hoosier-ville :)    
    
    
    Just ate a delicious pasta dinner with the McCauley family.....waking at 430am for tomorrow's 13.1 mile half-marathon 4 David!    
    
    
    4 1/2 hours to the start of the Marathon......can't sleep :(    
    
    
    praying for warmer weather......less than 40 mins    
    
    
    Completed the race!!!!! :) Woohoo!! Team David McCauley! Off to Scotti's 2 celebrate! :)    
    
    
    Thanks again to everyone's kind words of encouragement and generous donations for David's cause :) I did cartwheels down the finish line!!!    
    
    
    Just met Tracy Morgan from 30 Rock at Chicago's O'Hare yay!Check it out together: http://bit.ly/3STYPD    
    
    
    Tracy Morgan is on my flight back to NY too :)    
    
    
    A random guy just asked Tracy Morgan if he was with the Black Eyed Peas....d'oh! And then proceeded to get his autograph....hilarious!    
    
    
    Horribly delayed in O'Hare en route back to LGA......but Tracy Morgan is keeping us laughing :)    
    
    
    There is a ballerina performing in the middle of 14th Street.....only in NY! :) great view from the new highline!    
    
    
    Mani/Pedi and Cosmos with Jen-how fabulous! Girls Nite Out :)    
    
    
    Wait. I just found a nail salon that serves cosmos while getting a Mani/Pedi- is this not the best thing EVER    
    
    
    raining in nyc...but sunshine is arriving any moment from nashville, tn (kristen & laura) ;) xoxo    
    
    
    Having a blast with my NYC visitors....Ruby Foos.Rockefeller Center.American Girl Place.St. Pat's Cathedral.Central Park.Pedi-Cab.B'way!! :)    
    
    
    when, not if, the yankees win tonight - world series! http://sports.yahoo.com/mlb/players/5331    
    
    
    Happy Anniversary Mom & Dad! Hope you are enjoying your cruise :) xoox Love & Miss You! ~ Pooder    
    
    
    Happy Anniversary Mom & Dad! Hope you are enjoying your cruise :) xoox Love & Miss You! ~ Pooder xoox    
    
    
    Let's go YANKEES!!    
    
    
    Crosby & Nash! (@ The Warfield Theatre w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/hPuWEB    
    
    
    Let's go Yankees, Let's Go!!!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to the BEST Father a girl could ask for.......love you, xoxo, Pooder :)    
    
    
    ready for the weekend!    
    
    
    happy all saints day!    
    
    
    let's go yankees!!!    
    
    
    i love the remnant :)    
    
    
    Dinner with David & Rose....delicious sliders & fries! Time to watch "City Of God!"    
    
    
    Grickets is launching soon...get the group rate for all your events! #launch http://grickets.com/tcsjf  via @grickets    
    
    
    CREME BRULLE CART (@ Off the Grid: Fort Mason Center w/ 53 others) http://4sq.com/ifEQwp    
    
    
    I'm at Delaney's (2241 Chestnut St, Pierce, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/dRTyB0    
    
    
    @Aekae - thx 4 your tweet! "One day, NYC. London, the next. Now, SF?! You're a hard lady to keep track of:) Hope all's well out west! -A;)"    
    
    
    Currently reading http://n.pr/flrOvP     
    
    
    USGS information here on 3.8 Earthquake in Bay Area/San Francisco. http://fwd4.me/zr2    
    
    
    I'm at Off the Grid: Fort Mason Center (37.80558,-122.431435, San Francisco) w/ 60 others http://4sq.com/gahILT    
    
    
    I'm at Nectar Wine Lounge (3330 Steiner, btw Lombard and Chestnut, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hRLMSs    
    
    
    Off to Ohio! (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/eHfXjM    
    
    
    I'm at Cincinnati / Northern Kentucky International Airport (CVG) (2939 Terminal Dr, at Donaldson Hwy, Hebron) http://4sq.com/i57k5S    
    
    
    Home sweet home! (My new SF home!) (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 68 others) http://4sq.com/mufY0M    
    
    
    I'm at Park Chalet (1000 Great Highway, at John F Kennedy Drive, San Francisco) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/itG2XI    
    
    
    I'm at Ocean Beach (1000 Great Highway, at Fulton, San Francisco) w/ 15 others http://4sq.com/iteFqW    
    
    
    I'm at Target (5001 Junipero Serra Blvd, btw Serramonte Blvd and Colma Blvd, Colma) w/ 9 others http://4sq.com/lThOod    
    
    
    I'm at My Home (34 Stonewyck Dr, Chatham Township) http://4sq.com/l9w8bT    
    
    
    I'm at Aloft Harlem Hotel (2296 Frederick Douglass Blvd, btwn 123rd & 124th, New York) http://4sq.com/kST0tR    
    
    
    Flight delayed :( (@ John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) w/ 69 others) http://4sq.com/iAWEGw    
    
    
    Back to 75 degree weather! Yeehaw (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 111 others) http://4sq.com/merKCj    
    
    
    Carmel, CA (@ The Village Corner Mediterranean Bistro w/ @shawnamcd) [pic]: http://4sq.com/jHhc1n    
    
    
    Check it out: http://bit.ly/6fRGqi    
    
    
    Found this interesting. www.icantbelieveitsnotbutter.com/turnthetubaround/#/turnyourselfaround?mId=32311253.3    
    
    
    GOOGLE IO being streamed today on YouTube!    
    
    
    I'm at Flour +  Water (2401 Harrison Street, at 20th St, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/lusjJe    
    
    
    I'm at Starry Plough Pub (3101 Shattuck Ave, at Prince St, Berkeley) http://4sq.com/jUqDgv    
    
    
    I'm at Robledo Family Winery (21901 Bonness Rd, Sonoma) http://4sq.com/jtb3HI    
    
    
    I'm at Robledo Family Winery (21901 Bonness Rd, Sonoma) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/kFvCB5    
    
    
    I'm at B.R. Cohn Winery (15000 Sonoma Hwy, Glen Ellen) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/in92LB    
    
    
    I'm at St. Francis Winery http://4sq.com/lmAjvu    
    
    
    My 1st B2B!! (@ Bay To Breakers w/ 68 others) http://4sq.com/jBA3aU    
    
    
    http://city13-suemccauley.eventbrite.com/    
    
    
    Bridesmaids (@ AMC Loews Metreon 16) http://4sq.com/lDaCza    
    
    
    Go Giants (@ AT&T Park w/ 91 others) http://4sq.com/jhTxul    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/iKCu7x    
    
    
    @SFGiants 4 homeruns    
    
    
    Best pizza in bay area! (@ Pizza My Heart) http://4sq.com/mDq9Xm    
    
    
    YouTube hit Cahill at Wednesday's game http://sanfrancisco.giants.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20110524&content_id=19493468&vkey=news_sf&c_id=sf&tcid=tw_article_19493468 … via @sfgiants    
    
    
    I'm at Velvet Cantina (3349 23rd St, at Bartlett St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/m05FcM    
    
    
    alicia keys rocked at the apollo this evening in harlem, nyc    
    
    
    http://www.tennessean.com/article/20100110/WILLIAMSON01/1100323/2023/WILLIAMSON/Weigh%20Down%20grows%20large%20online%20following    
    
    
    I'm at Zero Zero (826 Folsom St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/lOg1rW    
    
    
    I'm at Chouquet's (2500 Washington St, Fillmore, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/kFDJTE    
    
    
    Yeah Google's America's Sales Conference 2011 (@ GFest w/ @jtcooper) http://4sq.com/ipaZ7C    
    
    
    GOOGLE SALES CONFERENCE! ! (@ ASC 2011) http://4sq.com/m48li6    
    
    
    http://www.wdyl.com/#     
    
    
    I LOVE GOOGLE + PLUS PROJECT! 
http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2011/06/introducing-google-project-real-life.html …    
    
    
    http://halloween13-suemccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Snow, Snow & More Snow in Manhattan :)    
    
    
    Best Show on Television? NBC Universal's "THE OFFICE" (Hands-Down)!    
    
    
    I'm at PDX (NE Airport Way, Portland). http://4sq.com/dzqNx9    
    
    
    time to get my "inner nasty" on and start running 13.1 miles! woot woot!    
    
    
    Go Team USA!! Who's watching the Olympics??!    
    
    
    Watch “And Then There Was Salsa” on Vimeo! http://vimeo.com/9194146    
    
    
    Delicious brunch w/ B & L! (@ Tipsy Parson) http://4sq.com/B9rqs    
    
    
    Yummy mimosas w/ CJ! :-) (@ Central Park - Loeb Boathouse Restaurant w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/6T9BaK    
    
    
    http://mashable.com/2010/03/03/twitter-10-billion-tweets/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=Feed:+Mashable+(Mashable)    
    
    
    Morgan Freeman deserved the OSCAR for INVICTUS. His portrayal of President Nelson Mandela was simply AMAZING!    
    
    
    @BrianWilson38 You made our race day so memorable!! :) You are the coolest!!    
    
    
    Please vote by clicking this link EVERY DAY: http://www.amw.com/allstar/2010/nominee-detail.cfm?id=7735    
    
    
    I'm at HP Pavilion at San Jose (525 W Santa Clara St, at N Autumn St, San Jose). http://4sq.com/8SVk5P    
    
    
    I'm at Alcatraz Cruises (Pier 33, Bay Street, San Francisco). http://4sq.com/6N7rM1    
    
    
    is working at 752a on a saturday. need to go back to bed    
    
    
    went back to bed until 2p. went into the office. now chilling before a night out in the big apple    
    
    
    is getting ready to head out to the Upper West Side with Elana :)    
    
    
    is exhaused from a fun night at blondie's and her new fav bar "the blue donkey" on the UWS    
    
    
    why can't i sleep? any tips for restless nights?    
    
    
    watching little miss sunshine-great movie! hilarious    
    
    
    is up and ready to ice skate and workout :)    
    
    
    Staring at Jude Law right now    
    
    
    is soo excited for Jude Law :) Can't wait for a photo with him    
    
    
    I GOT A PHOTO WITH JUDE LAW!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    he rocks!    
    
    
    lil miss sunshine rocks! superfreak!!    
    
    
    trying to go back to bed-need sleep!! :(    
    
    
    http://www.davidjmccauley.org/home    
    
    
    http://www.peaceoneday.org/    
    
    
    This is Jude Law's organization - http://www.peaceoneday.org/    
    
    
    Like my new pic?    
    
    
    Me & Jude Law - cute couple, eh? :)    
    
    
    just spent dinner with her cousin David, who dove into a pool in E Hampton this past September and became paralyzed from the chest down.    
    
    
    just woke and contemplatong hitting the gym for the 6am boxgin class...leaning towards yes, but so tired :(    
    
    
    loves red wine...    
    
    
    can't sleep ... too much work to do :( can't wait for the weekend!    
    
    
    had a fun nite w lauren. worked out, made dinner and watched sex and the city. perfect girls night out!    
    
    
    getting ready to go out :)    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (JFK International Airport, at Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 38 others    
    
    
    just arrived home from a night in the UWS, LES and Latin Qrtr (place where Plexi was shot-Giants)-good times :)    
    
    
    just saw "he's just not that into you" - it rocks!    
    
    
    wonders if anyone has a cure for insomnia....    
    
    
    watching Obama!    
    
    
    off to meditate! :)    
    
    
    what is the best way to reduce stress?    
    
    
    is excited to go on vacation :)    
    
    
    is happy to be home after one week of vacation :)    
    
    
    excited for the oscars!!    
    
    
    On a weekday at 9am, Mama's still has a line! Hope the food is worth the wait! Any recos?? http://4sq.com/mPNi96     
    
    
    125 West 16th St, #130 NY NY 10011    
    
    
    Vote to give this idea 250K: Create World Virtual School to provide free courses to global students  #pepsirefresh http://pep.si/9v3JW3    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Coldplay - live stream from Madrid today at 1pm PST! Watch it! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7zLUsNU5Hpg&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    HAPPY 95th BIRTHDAY GRANDPA! :-) (@ Essex Fells Country Club) http://4sq.com/dxvOMU    
    
    
    is happy to be home from Vegas!    
    
    
    La clase en espanol con mis amigas (@ Jewish Community Center of San Francisco (JCCSF) w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/sXj9FT     
    
    
    just got stopped by a casting director on the subway-craziness    
    
    
    Really sad day! Tim is leaving us - we'll miss you!    
    
    
    is still bummed Tim is leaving Google, but happy that he will be CEO of AOL. off to yoga and journey dance now!    
    
    
    is happy for a new day!    
    
    
    Sweet!! (@ The Westin Verasa Napa w/ @narni) [pic]: http://4sq.com/thJCoW     
    
    
    at 2009 Media Summit New York    
    
    
    just had a lemon cosmo on my way home from work. why dont women go to bars alone more often?? its great!    
    
    
    such tragic news about Natasha Richardson :(    
    
    
    love good wine, good cheese and fondue :) yeah divine bar!    
    
    
    Why is it snowing on the first day of SPRING?!! Bizzaro    
    
    
    ate at craftsteak-delicious :)    
    
    
    What does "Woot, Woot" mean???    
    
    
    Coke Makes Life Better    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare! Pies all around! http://4sq.com/unoEsr     
    
    
    Best pizza in SF! (@ Tony's Pizza Napoletana w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/scC501     
    
    
    Google Latitude rocks!!    
    
    
    Amazing show! + Miguel and his mom!! (@ TOTEM by Cirque du Soleil at AT&T Park w/ 11 others) http://4sq.com/vBCBBI     
    
    
    Happy its Friday!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/kmF_kGLioY0?a  AD BLITZ 2011 Vote Now    
    
    
    1st day of snow in NYC :)    
    
    
    Wanting to relax. Awful day with the rain and stress....still working - no fun!    
    
    
    Happy it's Saturday....Go Villanova!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    http://www.tastethemadness.com/ (via @addthis)    
    
    
    at Stephen's --- can't wait for a ride in the Viper    
    
    
    On the way back home to my city :) I missed the big apple!    
    
    
    injured my ankle severely....waiting for an x-ray    
    
    
    Know any good places in Italy? Off to Vicenza tomorrow. Plan to go to Cinque de Terre, Florence and Tuscany :)    
    
    
    Currently working in London, United Kingdom    
    
    
    Currently working in Google/YouTube London, United Kingdom    
    
    
    drinking a raspberry margarita at newark airport. can't wait to be in italy and away from the stresses of work!    
    
    
    I'm at 30 Rockefeller Plaza (30 Rockefeller Plaza, at 49th St, New York) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/vviDGC     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Photogenic" badge on foursquare! Say cheese! http://4sq.com/taEOTk     
    
    
    had an amazing trip to italy!! :) pizza, gelato and wine - oh my!    
    
    
    in the windy city of chicago for work. its supposed to snow tomorrow-bizarro!!    
    
    
    flying home. turbulence sucks.    
    
    
    http://spring13run-smccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Get in shape this spring with Marathon Matt's running group! http://spring13run-smccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    nyc is beautiful! today is a day of taking care of me-facial, hair highlight, nails, meditation and journeydance!! oh how i miss italy!!    
    
    
    best thai place in manhattan-galanga west 4th and 6th ave    
    
    
    enjoying this weather!! suntanning on the deck :) off for mojitos on dave's roof! fun times :)    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Mike!!    
    
    
    @darrenrovell Please tune into YouTube's Ad Blitz program http://www.youtube.com/adblitz  at the end of the game to check out Super Bowl commercials!    
    
    
    I'm at Five Points (31 Great Jones St, Lafayette, New York). http://4sq.com/h4s1Sp    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan http://YouTube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    is it the weekend yet?    
    
    
    i miss italia :(    
    
    
    Landon Donovan just summed it up perfectly: "It Just sucks, man."    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Newbie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aESivf    
    
    
    Matzos ball soup for a sore throat!! :-) (@ Hollywood Diner) http://4sq.com/6UkFSn    
    
    
    Dump (@ Penn Station) http://4sq.com/8ZKrHd    
    
    
    I'm at Google NYC (76 9th Ave. (4th Fl.), b/w 15th & 16th, New York). http://4sq.com/4uC0th    
    
    
    My first time quoted in the press - holla :) woot woot! http://lnkd.in/VQmcC5     
    
    
    Wish I was in London right now!!!!    
    
    
    Paul McCartney's performing LIVE in Hyde Park, London: http://www.youtube.com/user/BornHIVFree    
    
    
    NYC LOVES PAUL!    
    
    
    Don't forget to sign the Global Petition to the right :) Cheers!! What a brilliant cause!    
    
    
    The Long & Winding Road......classic Beatle hit! Sweet!!!    
    
    
    #bornhivfree #HRC2010 Argentina just won World Cup!    
    
    
    Ob-La-Di, Ob-La-Da = my favorite Beatles song!!    
    
    
    i'm going mad......i've been at work way too long    
    
    
    toe up from da flo up    
    
    
    Soul: This or That http://www.youtube.com/kiasoul?x=showcase_3727    
    
    
    @ The City Bakery in NYC-best hot chocolate in the city and i just discovered they have my fav fruit-cherries and lychees :) xoxo happy moms    
    
    
    West Elm is the coolest store for decorating your place!! :) xoxox love it    
    
    
    I'm at Jamba Juice - Eighth Ave & 23rd (249 8th Ave, at W. 23rd St, New York). http://4sq.com/4DVi4f    
    
    
    I'm at AMC Loews Lincoln Square 13 (1998 Broadway, btw 67th & 68th, New York). http://4sq.com/3nJ8aV    
    
    
    Brunch w the girls! (@ Cafe Ronda) http://4sq.com/8DTNLE    
    
    
    Watching the World Cup!! Go Spain!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    I'm at Cafeteria (119 7th Ave, 17th St, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/2vlpni    
    
    
    I'm at Blue Light (1979 Union St, at Buchanan, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/x9pdga     
    
    
    ready for the wedding this weekend and a break from nyc! :)    
    
    
    massage at google, dinner at "casa" - best brazilian food in nyc! :) fun nite!    
    
    
    I'm at Cafeteria (119 7th Ave, 17th St, New York). http://4sq.com/2vlpni    
    
    
    I'm at West Side Highway - 10th Ave. Exit (New York). http://4sq.com/dq0GCO    
    
    
    countdown to wedding!!!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Adventurer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aj1wcd    
    
    
    I'm at Bodhizone (110 E 23rd, 3rd Fl, Park Ave South, New York). http://4sq.com/aukq9B    
    
    
    I'm at City Bakery (3 W 18th St, btw 5th and 6th Ave, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/4ro4Vk    
    
    
    Go Holland!!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    THE DUTCH ARE IN THE FINALS!!!!! YAY! GO ORANGE!!    
    
    
    I'm at Nike 255 Custom Lab (255 Elizabeth St, btw Houston and Prince, New York). http://4sq.com/4RStDF    
    
    
    I'm at Nike Sportswear (21 Mercer St, btw Grand & Howard St, New York). http://4sq.com/4QkDH4    
    
    
    Dinner w amazing friends!! :-) (@ Galanga) http://4sq.com/71EiJQ    
    
    
    Ready to fly!!!    
    
    
    #worldcup Go Holland!    
    
    
    Watching the World Cup unfold on Twitter at http://twitter.com/worldcup/home    
    
    
    #worldcup# Go Holland!    
    
    
    #world cup Go Holland!    
    
    
    I'm at Trapeze School of New York (518 west 30th st, Btw 10th and 11th, New York) http://4sq.com/g1S7Fi    
    
    
    Happy bday Tara!:-) (@ Taco Chulo) http://4sq.com/2H5L4n    
    
    
    Getting ready for wedding day! Cocktail party was a blast last nite-back to bed! :) xox    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cK4Awh    
    
    
    Go Mets! (@ Citi Field w/ 131 others) http://4sq.com/a0BDhh    
    
    
    Amazing caramelized French toast, kale, tofu & BEST hot chocolate in Manhattan (@ City Bakery) http://4sq.com/4ro4Vk    
    
    
    Study study! (@ Google NYC) http://4sq.com/4uC0th    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Local" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/91QeaE    
    
    
    Third Place World Cup time!!! (@ Downtown Galway Hooker) http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    I'm at Downtown Galway Hooker (133 7th Ave. South, btw Charles & 10th Street, New York). http://4sq.com/2JfPkV    
    
    
    Chilling    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza w/ @shawnamcd http://4sq.com/HtWlUD     
    
    
    #OldSpice    
    
    
    @Old Spice How are you??? I love the smell of adventure!    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Bender" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bL04vO    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super User" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aflwuk    
    
    
    I'm at Ziegfeld Theater (141 W 54th St, btw 6th & 7th, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/7KoTYf    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza (San Francisco, CA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/Id2fKi     
    
    
    Indy 500!! Go Helio Castroneves! Team Penske!!! :)    
    
    
    Indy 500 - Go Helio!!! Less than 15 laps to go to be a third-time Indy 500 championship!!    
    
    
    Helio is about to win-3-time Indy 500 champion in one decade    
    
    
    Helio won!!! Biggest race in the world :)    
    
    
    I love Helio-he rocks!!    
    
    
    Indy 500 Champion Helio Castroneves steals the championship a third-time!! History in the making!    
    
    
    I'm at Coachella Music Festival (Indio, CA) w/ 55 others http://4sq.com/IKBicp     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/lifeinaday #lifeinaday    
    
    
    #Helio Castroneves was robbed today at the Edmonton race......ridiculous!    
    
    
    @h3lio - you were robbed today at Edmonton! So sorry, man.....your always positive attitude is a real inspiration to all of your fans!    
    
    
    @NFNiTM Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @ronsracing88 This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @dracasaga Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @rds4life Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @RossMacLochness Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @YahooXtraSport Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @ronsracing88 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @martinpinnau Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @robertmajak Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @golic_2004 This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @kevingraham1280 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    @packerfan858 Totally agree! This is CRAZY!! Helio should have won!    
    
    
    #HelioCastroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    http://www.autosport.com/news/report.php/id/85569?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter    
    
    
    @dalejrschick he was robbed!! ridiculous    
    
    
    #HelioCastroneves was ROBBED!!!! ridiculous Indy Car!    
    
    
    #Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!!!!!!!!!! Ridiculous!    
    
    
    @brianvermette totally agree - Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    @IndyCarPR Helio Castroneves was ROBBED!!!!    
    
    
    @YouTube awesome!    
    
    
    off to my summer share! can't wait to drink some vino!!    
    
    
    I'm at Bodhizone (110 E 23rd, 3rd Fl, Park Ave South, New York). http://4sq.com/aukq9B    
    
    
    lying on the beach    
    
    
    1st day in my share house: met amazing ppl    
    
    
    2nd day in my share house: went jogging by the light house and accidentally ran into the "nude" beach! wow! eye opener!    
    
    
    2nd day at share house: went for a run and stumbled into a nude beach!! wow! eye opener!    
    
    
    Display in 2011: The Future Belongs to Google | ClickZ http://www.clickz.com/clickz/news/1934048/display-2011-future-belongs-google … via @clickz    
    
    
    Missing the weekend at the beach....    
    
    
    Hump Day is nearly here!!!    
    
    
    Get the hottest beauty tips from the leading beauty gurus on YouTube! www.youtube.com/destinationbeauty    
    
    
    journeydance, meditation and pilates.....beautiful weather, oh my!    
    
    
    HAPPY BIRTHDAY Johnny Depp!    
    
    
    who says white chocolate martinis from max brenners, poutene pomme frites and 16 Handles can't cheer you up? (and a good blowout)    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Pizzaiolo" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different pizza joints! http://4sq.com/KmRqlW     
    
    
    I'm at Delarosa (San Francisco, CA) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/KmRnXg     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kfEzHdWKOoQ    
    
    
    @reggie_bush 100% agree    
    
    
    #bonnaroolive AWESOME!!!! Thanks Dell :)    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (JFK International Airport, Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 84 others http://4sq.com/i8spxn    
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (1 S McDonnell Rd, at S Link Rd, San Francisco) w/ 50 others http://4sq.com/fKeADG    
    
    
    @BrianWilson38 Brian - any shot you are in SF next week and want to swing by a surprise party for my boyfriend? He's a die hard fan"    
    
    
    I'm at San Francisco International Airport (SFO) (1 S McDonnell Rd, at S Link Rd, San Francisco) w/ 82 others. http://4sq.com/MTivk    
    
    
    @BlueVmovie When and where will this film be released near the San Francisco Bay area? Dying to see it! Even contemplating driving 2 LA    
    
    
    I'm at Zero Zero (826 Folsom St, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/dPXrCp    
    
    
    I'm at The Slanted Door (1 Ferry Building #3, San Francisco) w/ 6 others http://4sq.com/fjqMIS    
    
    
    I'm at Googleplex (1600 Amphitheatre Pkwy, at Charleston Rd, Mountain View) http://4sq.com/gImxcI    
    
    
    prayers to michael jackson and farrah fawcett    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Superstar" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/effi0q    
    
    
    BLUE VALENTINE here I come! :-) (@ Century San Francisco Centre 9 & XD w/ 9 others) http://4sq.com/iiOnsW    
    
    
    Jury Duty time! :(    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/QxGz7woiwpM?a  2012 Ad Blitz Sizzle Reel    
    
    
    I'm test driving a mini cooper (@ MINI of San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eOyPOO    
    
    
    Seth MacFarlane to Host Oscars http://abcn.ws/O40u4e  (via @ABC)    
    
    
    Can't waiting to catch up with Jess Brummer! (@ District Wine Lounge) http://4sq.com/hpub4f    
    
    
    I miss Brentwood, TN!!    
    
    
    I'm at Ozumo Japanese Restaurant (161 Steuart St, btw Howard & Mission, San Francisco) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/h6khNG    
    
    
    I'm at Patxi's Chicago Pizza (San Francisco, CA) http://4sq.com/TR8YOO     
    
    
    @GoogleDisplay Can't wait!    
    
    
    Live Video! Watch our keynote at the MIXX Conference, streaming in a display ad! http://www.google.com/adwords/watchthisspace/live/    
    
    
    Watch This Space - Live Keynote at MIXX: http://lnkd.in/4RAdMz    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/8ZpPAb    
    
    
    I'm at Dos Caminos (675 Hudson St, at 14th St, New York) w/ 4 others. http://4sq.com/dy68YV    
    
    
    #rallyzito SF Giants rock! Way to bring it home!    
    
    
    I'm at 675 Bar w/ @helen_lee_. http://4sq.com/2Be6ar    
    
    
    I'm at Westville Chelsea (246 W 18th St, 7th & 8th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/9aIw9k    
    
    
    I'm at Honey (243 W 14th St, btw 7th & 8th, New York). http://4sq.com/86vPfx    
    
    
    I'm at Crooked Knife 14 (232 West 14th Street, 14th St btw 7th & 8th Ave, New York). http://4sq.com/dnIArL    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Crunked" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/9bWKFF    
    
    
    I'm at JFK Int'l Airport - Terminal 7 (Terminal 7, John F. Kennedy Int'l Airport (JFK), Queens). http://4sq.com/1Qb8C9    
    
    
    I'm at Enoshima (2280 chestnut st, Chestnut & scott, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hcnEh6    
    
    
    I'm at Nectar Wine Lounge (3330 Steiner, btw Lombard and Chestnut, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eUR2J2    
    
    
    I'm at Horseshoe Tavern (2024 Chestnut St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hcwaSj    
    
    
    I'm at MatrixFillmore (3138 Fillmore St, at Greenwich St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/gRhW31    
    
    
    I'm at The Brixton (2140 Union St., Fillmore, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/faQQpE    
    
    
    I'm at Ferry Plaza Farmers' Market (1 Ferry Building, The Embaracadero, at Market St, San Francisco) w/ 11 others http://4sq.com/h9oT1w    
    
    
    I'm at YouTube HQ (901 Cherry Ave, at Bayhill Dr, San Bruno). http://4sq.com/6EZmR3    
    
    
    I'm at Daily Grill - San Francisco (347 Geary Street, btw Mason St & Powell St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/fOQZW3    
    
    
    I'm at Los Angeles International Airport (LAX) ✈ (1 World Way, at Sepulveda Blvd, Los Angeles) w/ 46 others. http://4sq.com/qm5av    
    
    
    I'm at Viceroy Santa Monica (1819 Ocean, Pico Blvd, Santa Monica). http://4sq.com/82iDQB    
    
    
    I'm at The Parkside Cafe (43 Arenal Ave., Stinson Beach) http://4sq.com/egtSaA    
    
    
    first tie in the NFL since 2008. wow. both teams look so unhappy :( 

#49ers    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Far Far Away" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bfJ1Ex    
    
    
    Delicious upper east side down pineapple dessert and fabulous company w/ my E-Fo! (@ Shake Shack) http://4sq.com/covAmR    
    
    
    I'm at Chelsea Piers Sports Center (60 Chelsea Piers, New York). http://4sq.com/50tt9u    
    
    
    I'm at Westville Chelsea (246 W 18th St, 7th & 8th Ave, New York) w/ 3 others. http://4sq.com/9aIw9k    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/xWnvjHN74dk?a  Kesha- Die Young (Lyrics)    
    
    
    I added a video to a @YouTube playlist http://youtu.be/Ys7-6_t7OEQ?a  Justin Bieber - Beauty And A Beat ft. Nicki Minaj    
    
    
    Who was complaining about Kaepernick last week? That's right. Keep your mouths closed! #49ers Go Colin!    
    
    
    Visit the Harry Potter page for videos, photos, and more! http://www.youtube.com/harrypotter    
    
    
    #DeathlyHallows Amazing Live Stream on YouTube!!! JK Rowling just arrived!!! I love Harry!    
    
    
    #LiveCocoCam This rocks!    
    
    
    Tune in to the 24 hour live stream with Conan O'Brien! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Tune in to the 24 hour live stream with Conan O'Brien today! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Check out Conan O'Brien's 24 hour LIVE stream on YouTube! http://lnkd.in/spUA5X    
    
    
    Off to the Guggenheim for an unveiling of YT Play! http://lnkd.in/9f-5Eh    
    
    
    I'm at Marengo on Union (1980 Union Street, Buchanan Street, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/fEC34L    
    
    
    YT Play (@ Guggenheim Museum w/ @johnmilitello @helen_lee_) http://4sq.com/2Ku3x6    
    
    
    I'm at YouTube HQ (901 Cherry Ave, at Bayhill Dr, San Bruno) http://4sq.com/eJnZJU    
    
    
    I'm at City Crab & Seafood Company (235 Park Ave South, at E. 19th St, New York). http://4sq.com/7DpECW    
    
    
    I'm at XYZ Bar @ W Hotel in San Francisco (San Francisco) http://4sq.com/eGOzRo    
    
    
    Price Of Super Bowl Commercials Hit Record High | http://www.ballerstatus.com/2013/01/04/price-super-bowl-commercials-hit-record-high/ … via @ballerstatus    
    
    
    Best coffee in SF! (@ Blue Bottle Coffee w/ 4 others) http://4sq.com/gdlCLJ    
    
    
    loved #niceguyjohnny and meeting @edward_burns today @google !!!    
    
    
    I'm at Google Creative Sandbox 2010 (82 Mercer St, New York) w/ 36 others. http://4sq.com/9Betm2    
    
    
    Sunday funday (@ Triptych w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/VE3FCL     
    
    
    Amazing brunch after a strenuous hike in Marin: Hill 88! (@ Bacheeso's Grand Avenue) http://4sq.com/envsRM    
    
    
    Help kick off the Pepsi Superbowl Halftime Show. Upload your photo at http://pepsi.com  #PepsiHalftime http://www.pepsi.com/halftime     
    
    
    I love #
@le_tote !    
    
    
    #iabuk    
    
    
    #iabuk Awesome! Can't wait to see Bruce Daisley from Google/YouTube!!    
    
    
    #iabuk Tune-in to IAB UK's 2010 Engage Conference being live streamed right now. Bruce Daisley is up in a few minutes to talk about VIDEO!    
    
    
    #BRHangout Which commercials do you think will "win" this Harbaugh Bowl?    
    
    
    #BRHangout this is one of the best G+ On-Air Hangouts I've ever seen....so entertaining! LOVE the surprise cameos! Woot!! :)    
    
    
    #BRHangout Where will you rewatch the Super Bowl commercials? YouTube's Ad Blitz!!! View & Vote on your favorites    
    
    
    @DeStorm Love your Ad Blitz Video! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=58Ouzhdh-j8 …    
    
    
    @DeStorm HAPPY BELATED! You are my cryptonite ;)    
    
    
    Check out as we upload all of the commercials in real-time during #Super Bowl on YouTube's Ad Blitz!http://www.youtube.com/adblitz  & VOTE    
    
    
    KICK BALL LEAGUE! (@ Bar None w/ 8 others) http://4sq.com/giajbo    
    
    
    @DeStorm Happy Super Bowl Sunday!! Don't forget YouTube's Ad Blitz @ http://www.youtube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    #49ers taking it home in this year's Big Game @YouTube #AdBlitz http://www.youtube.com/adblitz?x=/s/tw     
    
    
    @YouTube #AdBlitz http://www.youtube.com/adblitz?x=/s/tw     
    
    
    Which ad ruled the Big Game? Watch, share and vote for your favorites. Visit YouTube  http://adblitz2013.appspot.com/d/     
    
    
    @le_tote  LOVE this new green silk tee. All set for my "first date" tonight thanks to Le Tote! pic.twitter.com/khZkR8oa    
    
    
    Just had lunch next to Sergey Brin! (@ Googleplex - Cafe Moma) http://4sq.com/grKZRU    
    
    
    I'm rooting for The Lumineers #GRAMMYs http://bitly.com/WssOlx     
    
    
    My #GRAMMYLegend is  http://bit.ly/yP1zvT     
    
    
    YouTube’s AdBlitz Channel Has Changed The World of Advertising http://news.yahoo.com/youtube-adblitz-channel-changed-world-advertising-says-online-070223762.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    @le_tote LOVE this dress pic.twitter.com/NHWXaNyM    
    
    
    YouTube Blog: 2013 YouTube Ad Blitz Winners Revealed http://youtube-global.blogspot.com/2013/02/2013-youtube-ad-blitz-winners-revealed.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    RAM's 'Farmer' Voted Best Super Bowl Spot in YouTube's Ad Blitz Contest http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/rams-farmer-voted-best-super-bowl-spot-youtubes-ad-blitz-contest-147367 …    
    
    
    RAM's 'Farmer' Voted Best Super Bowl Spot in YouTube's Ad Blitz Contest http://lnkd.in/-j4VwF     
    
    
    Check out the winners from YouTube's Ad Blitz being interviewed by http://Adweek.com  now in a G+Hangout On-Air! http://www.youtube.com/adblitz     
    
    
    http://money.cnn.com/2011/01/25/technology/google_hiring/index.htm?hpt=T2 Send me your resume and job listing BEFORE applying online    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/g1338a    
    
    
    I'm in Vegas baby! :-) (@ Las Vegas McCarran International Airport (LAS) ✈ w/ @flippnyc) http://4sq.com/hPLt57    
    
    
    Woot woot (@ Encore at Wynn Hotel & Casino) http://4sq.com/fgvpY7    
    
    
    Who do you think will win at the #Oscars? Join me and fill out a My Picks official Oscar ballot. http://oscar.go.com/mypicks#user=suemccauley%26ushare=7e1973af87f710b78ff51aa89a8fd095d12a1aea60ab4423 …    
    
    
    #oscar +1 a bird per bradley cooper ;)    
    
    
    Love this feed :) Yay Oscars! Thanks AP Live! - #Oscars live on http://livestre.am/rJU     
    
    
    #bestdressed I love Charlize Theron's dress!    
    
    
    #bestdressed Renee Zellwegger looks AWFUL! Did she do her own hair? fail    
    
    
    I think charlize theron is the #bestdressed on the #Oscars Red Carpet http://oscar.go.com/red-carpet     
    
    
    @SethMacFarlane was the best Oscar host I've seen in a long time :) Super funny!!    
    
    
    @LE_tote love this dress! pic.twitter.com/JjfS7MHqs2    
    
    
    FWA mobile winner | YouTube Ad Blitz http://www.thefwa.com/mobile/youtube-ad-blitz …    
    
    
    Google is hiring! Check it out: www.google.com/jobs please email me your resume and the job title/description...don't apply directly    
    
    
    Love this dress! @le_tote    
    
    
    Love this Le Tote dress! May have to keep this and the bracelet :) @le_tote pic.twitter.com/N39ZePZ49H    
    
    
    1st time skiing (@ Northstar-at-Tahoe Resort w/ 12 others) http://4sq.com/gFuwg1    
    
    
    Happy St Patty's Day @le_tote pic.twitter.com/S7jxSo1ynK    
    
    
    I'm at Sears Fine Foods (439 Powell, San Francisco) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/fsvVHo    
    
    
    Oasis (@ Yerba Buena Gardens) http://4sq.com/hMNBTz    
    
    
    @le_tote Check out this fantastic article on Le Tote! http://www.sfchronicle.com/style/article/Companies-let-users-rent-most-everything-4412989.php …    
    
    
    Companies let users rent most everything http://lnkd.in/gtjb2G     
    
    
    A comedic web series packed with a punch http://kickstarter.com     
    
    
    ME + YOU = SWEET VICTORY for @blogotheque. RT and VOTE : #Webbys http://wbby.co/f0x9     
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love this! Thanks T Mobile & YouTube!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive Love this! Woot!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive Thank you T-Mobile and Google | YouTube for making this possible!    
    
    
    Coachella LIVE on YouTube, April 12-14. Presented by T-Mobile http://www.youtube.com/coachella     
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love the harlem shake!!!    
    
    
    #CoachellaLive love coachella    
    
    
    Happy Wednesday!    
    
    
    Getting pumped for San Francisco :) xoxox    
    
    
    driving to Napa in a convertible....just passed .just saw my 1st live hitchhiker!    
    
    
    Loving this perfect weather in Napa......great wine, delicious food, amazing friends and my hair blowin in our convertible :) love!    
    
    
    Driving Thelma and Louise style in Napa! :)    
    
    
    amazed at God's awesome beauty in Napa - breathtaking!    
    
    
    just toured Castello di Amorosa...chocolate and wine pairings-delicious :) xoxo    
    
    
    just ate bacon chocolate-DELICIOUS-ever tried it??    
    
    
    delicious lunch at Taylor's Refresher in Napa! off to frog's leap winery. pick strawberries and drink champgane! oh my :)    
    
    
    @le_tote Just another day at the office styled in Le Tote! Yay! pic.twitter.com/6HD0SLgqkK    
    
    
    Why Women Aren't Crazy http://goodmenproject.com/featured-content/why-women-arent-crazy/ … via @goodmenproject    
    
    
    thelma and louise meets sideways is how you describe our napa valley adventure!! :)    
    
    
    foggy day in SF - barely see the tip of the golden gate bridge!! cold weather in SF!    
    
    
    THE INTERNSHIP - IN THEATERS JUNE 7 http://lnkd.in/zRxHVY     
    
    
    just landed in Chicago! I had an amazing trip to San Fran, San Bruno, Mtn View and Napa Valley. Excited to explore the Windy City! :) xox    
    
    
    off to go boating on fox lake in illinois! :)    
    
    
    W Lakeshore Hotel in Chicago is by far the BEST Starwood property (next to the Sheraton in Leblon, Brazil)....fantastico :)    
    
    
    Outside Lands rocks    
    
    
    Watch WeTV this evening - Weigh Down and Gwen Shamblin:  http://bit.ly/LsrzM    
    
    
    Very tired and happy to be going home.....    
    
    
    'http://www.wetv.com/video/34982139001/extreme-diets-eating-garbage' via @addthis    
    
    
    happy to be have arrived safely to NY....Praise God! Can't wait to sleep in my own bed    
    
    
    #geekierthanyou    
    
    
    @ijustine amazing job at VidCon! You are amazing!    
    
    
    @shaycarl awesome job moderating!!! Love the Shaytards    
    
    
    I'm at Judy's Cafe (2268 Chestnut, Scott St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/gMtn2U    
    
    
    Watching the CMA Festival on ABC...    
    
    
    Watching the CMA Music Festival on ABC    
    
    
    Martina McBride & Kid Rock just blew me away with the song "Picture" at the CMA Music Festival...    
    
    
    Taylor Swift totally ROCKED it with "Love Story"    
    
    
    Hiking in Mt Tam (@ Golden Gate Bridge w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/huq268    
    
    
    Best brunch in Stinson Beach! (@ The Parkside Cafe) http://4sq.com/f1khw0    
    
    
    I'm at Tamalpais http://4sq.com/i2xBr8    
    
    
    Golden State Warriors vs Oklahoma (@ Oracle Arena w/ 52 others) http://4sq.com/fFAV7u    
    
    
    The MTV VMAs have taken the word "distasteful" to a whole new level @vma . Thanks Miley Cyrus. Try wearing clothes next time!    
    
    
    I #votemiley for the 2013 MTV #VMA Best Song of the Summer! See who's in the lead and vote: http://on.mtv.com/17JXpec  #windowsphone    
    
    
    I #votedaftpunk for the 2013 MTV #VMA Best Song of the Summer! See who's in the lead and vote: http://on.mtv.com/17JXpec  #windowsphone    
    
    
    spending the day w my awesome cousin David, Rose and my dad in Jersey City! picture perfect day!    
    
    
    In Stone Harbor, NJ....the weather is looking dismal, but so happy to be here :)    
    
    
    I just signed up for the Urbanathalon in SF on 11/24! Join me! . Men's Health Urbanathlon: San Francisco: http://fw.to/u9p93Jh     
    
    
    Who wouldn't want to hangout and shop with @DVF? Here's your chance, courtesy of @CFDA and @Google. http://www.fashionologie.com/DVF-Host-First-Shoppable-Google-Hangout-31922917 …    
    
    
    Go shopping with one of your favorite designers http://googlecommerce.blogspot.com/2013/09/go-shopping-with-one-of-your-favorite.html …    
    
    
    #shopthehangout any discounts for people that tuned into today's live G+ Hangout?? :)    
    
    
    Weather report in Stone Harbor? RAIN, RAIN, RAIN :( Can't wait for the sunny weekend!    
    
    
    watching the surf competition at nuns' beach in stone harbor, nj. prayin for sunshine tomorrow!!    
    
    
    I voted for Rihanna to win Artist of the Year at the YouTube Music Awards. http://youtu.be/VJDa2Kbv4RM  #YTMA    
    
    
    I voted for Macklemore & Ryan Lewis's "Same Love" to win Video of the Year at the YouTube Music Awards. http://youtu.be/YZJWg-cB9rM  #YTMA    
    
    
    Russell Brand stinks as a host...very inappropriate    
    
    
    Yeah for the exclusive, extended trailer for "NEW MOON" at the VMAs in Radio City, NYC    
    
    
    Love the Pepsi Refresh commercials...great song! "May you stay ever young..may your heart always be joyful"    
    
    
    @SueMcCauley Russell Brand stinks - can we get a new host next year?    
    
    
    Beyonce just rocked it at the VMA's.....    
    
    
    @SQLChicken Beyonce rocked it with SINGLE LADIES    
    
    
    What is Lady Gaga wearing???    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/gDiim    
    
    
    Ate delicious Thai with Ms. Judd..Excited for church, Lauren's bridal shower and Nickie's visit to see WICKED on Broadway tomorrow    
    
    
    Happy New Year! Don't forget to check out YouTube's Year in Review: http://www.youtube.com/user/theyearinreview …    
    
    
    Loving my Christmas dresses - thanks @letote pic.twitter.com/ofyOfrZKmg    
    
    
    Loving my Christmas dresses - thanks @letote pic.twitter.com/e3DUjcwTmV    
    
    
    Anyone going to CES next week? If so, let's meet up!    
    
    
    Mindy From 'The Mindy Project' Is Stalking You On Tinder, Sort Of http://huff.to/1drLo3t  via @HuffPostTech    
    
    
    Anyone heading to CES?    
    
    
    Niners are back!!!!!!    
    
    
    just had a delicious thai dinner with my fabulous pre-birthday kripalu buds!!!    
    
    
    just ate a delicious surprise pre-birthday thai dinner w my kripalu buds..now back 2 work :(    
    
    
    I'm at Resort at Squaw Creek (400 Squaw Creek Rd., Lake Tahoe-Olympic Valley) http://4sq.com/ei6PAd    
    
    
    Just ate breakfast at the fanciest bakery in Manhattan - The City Bakery! caramelized french toast and to-die-for hot chocolate :) YUM!    
    
    
    on my way to NashVegas!! woohoo :)    
    
    
    headin' home to nyc!    
    
    
    boarding in chicago-home after midnight! i miss brentwood!    
    
    
    home safely - tucked in bed! PG!! :) I miss TN and RF :(    
    
    
    back in nyc and at google!    
    
    
    Off to Fiddlesticks bar now to support Leukemia & Lymphoma Society for Jackie Bona & victims of the Ondoy (Ketsana) Typhoon    
    
    
    @MGShamblin - thanks for the shout-out! Anything I can do to help out WDW & YouTube :) Best Regards!    
    
    
    Need a @BPCleanse Blue Print Cleanse while I am in NYC Mon-Wed: where can I pick one up today/early tomorrow? Thanks! suemccauley@google.com    
    
    
    I'm at The Standard Hotel (848 Washington, New York) http://4sq.com/fZ0ie0    
    
    
    had an awesome night! TGIAF with my team at the google cafeteria....bon voyage drinks for KK @ Maritime hotel..dinner at my fav mexcian w cj    
    
    
    I'm at Chelsea Market (75 9th Ave, btw 15th & 16th St, New York) http://4sq.com/gLQt4v    
    
    
    I'm at Google NYC (76 9th Ave, btw 15th St & 16th St, New York) http://4sq.com/eTfAtN    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "School Night" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/i15YJ7    
    
    
    I'm at John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) ✈ (Van Wyck Expy, Queens) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/ijLcZI    
    
    
    Please donate and come out this evening to our happy hour fundraiser in the East Village (Sin Sin: 2nd Ave, 5th St www.davidjmccauley.org    
    
    
    Please come out this evening to our happy hour fundraiser in the East Village (Sin Sin: 2nd Ave, 5th St www.davidjmccauley.org    
    
    
    Fading.......ready to go home and sleep....Awesome fundraiser. Can't wait to go to Hoosier-land for the BIG race!!    
    
    
    off to Indianapolis to see The McCauley family and get pumped to run this half-marathon tomorrow :)    
    
    
    Rockin to Michael Shamblin's awesome new single: http://bit.ly/2ctaGc    
    
    
    just landed in indianapolis-home of the hoosiers and Indy 500! :)    
    
    
    Home in Hoosier-ville :)    
    
    
    Just ate a delicious pasta dinner with the McCauley family.....waking at 430am for tomorrow's 13.1 mile half-marathon 4 David!    
    
    
    4 1/2 hours to the start of the Marathon......can't sleep :(    
    
    
    praying for warmer weather......less than 40 mins    
    
    
    Completed the race!!!!! :) Woohoo!! Team David McCauley! Off to Scotti's 2 celebrate! :)    
    
    
    Thanks again to everyone's kind words of encouragement and generous donations for David's cause :) I did cartwheels down the finish line!!!    
    
    
    Just met Tracy Morgan from 30 Rock at Chicago's O'Hare yay!Check it out together: http://bit.ly/3STYPD    
    
    
    Tracy Morgan is on my flight back to NY too :)    
    
    
    A random guy just asked Tracy Morgan if he was with the Black Eyed Peas....d'oh! And then proceeded to get his autograph....hilarious!    
    
    
    Horribly delayed in O'Hare en route back to LGA......but Tracy Morgan is keeping us laughing :)    
    
    
    There is a ballerina performing in the middle of 14th Street.....only in NY! :) great view from the new highline!    
    
    
    Mani/Pedi and Cosmos with Jen-how fabulous! Girls Nite Out :)    
    
    
    Wait. I just found a nail salon that serves cosmos while getting a Mani/Pedi- is this not the best thing EVER    
    
    
    raining in nyc...but sunshine is arriving any moment from nashville, tn (kristen & laura) ;) xoxo    
    
    
    Having a blast with my NYC visitors....Ruby Foos.Rockefeller Center.American Girl Place.St. Pat's Cathedral.Central Park.Pedi-Cab.B'way!! :)    
    
    
    when, not if, the yankees win tonight - world series! http://sports.yahoo.com/mlb/players/5331    
    
    
    Happy Anniversary Mom & Dad! Hope you are enjoying your cruise :) xoox Love & Miss You! ~ Pooder    
    
    
    Happy Anniversary Mom & Dad! Hope you are enjoying your cruise :) xoox Love & Miss You! ~ Pooder xoox    
    
    
    Let's go YANKEES!!    
    
    
    Crosby & Nash! (@ The Warfield Theatre w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/hPuWEB    
    
    
    Let's go Yankees, Let's Go!!!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to the BEST Father a girl could ask for.......love you, xoxo, Pooder :)    
    
    
    ready for the weekend!    
    
    
    happy all saints day!    
    
    
    let's go yankees!!!    
    
    
    i love the remnant :)    
    
    
    Dinner with David & Rose....delicious sliders & fries! Time to watch "City Of God!"    
    
    
    Grickets is launching soon...get the group rate for all your events! #launch http://grickets.com/tcsjf  via @grickets    
    
    
    CREME BRULLE CART (@ Off the Grid: Fort Mason Center w/ 53 others) http://4sq.com/ifEQwp    
    
    
    I'm at Delaney's (2241 Chestnut St, Pierce, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/dRTyB0    
    
    
    @Aekae - thx 4 your tweet! "One day, NYC. London, the next. Now, SF?! You're a hard lady to keep track of:) Hope all's well out west! -A;)"    
    
    
    Currently reading http://n.pr/flrOvP     
    
    
    USGS information here on 3.8 Earthquake in Bay Area/San Francisco. http://fwd4.me/zr2    
    
    
    I'm at Off the Grid: Fort Mason Center (37.80558,-122.431435, San Francisco) w/ 60 others http://4sq.com/gahILT    
    
    
    I'm at Nectar Wine Lounge (3330 Steiner, btw Lombard and Chestnut, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/hRLMSs    
    
    
    Off to Ohio! (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 5 others) http://4sq.com/eHfXjM    
    
    
    I'm at Cincinnati / Northern Kentucky International Airport (CVG) (2939 Terminal Dr, at Donaldson Hwy, Hebron) http://4sq.com/i57k5S    
    
    
    Home sweet home! (My new SF home!) (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 68 others) http://4sq.com/mufY0M    
    
    
    I'm at Park Chalet (1000 Great Highway, at John F Kennedy Drive, San Francisco) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/itG2XI    
    
    
    I'm at Ocean Beach (1000 Great Highway, at Fulton, San Francisco) w/ 15 others http://4sq.com/iteFqW    
    
    
    I'm at Target (5001 Junipero Serra Blvd, btw Serramonte Blvd and Colma Blvd, Colma) w/ 9 others http://4sq.com/lThOod    
    
    
    I'm at My Home (34 Stonewyck Dr, Chatham Township) http://4sq.com/l9w8bT    
    
    
    I'm at Aloft Harlem Hotel (2296 Frederick Douglass Blvd, btwn 123rd & 124th, New York) http://4sq.com/kST0tR    
    
    
    Flight delayed :( (@ John F Kennedy International Airport (JFK) w/ 69 others) http://4sq.com/iAWEGw    
    
    
    Back to 75 degree weather! Yeehaw (@ San Francisco International Airport (SFO) w/ 111 others) http://4sq.com/merKCj    
    
    
    Carmel, CA (@ The Village Corner Mediterranean Bistro w/ @shawnamcd) [pic]: http://4sq.com/jHhc1n    
    
    
    Check it out: http://bit.ly/6fRGqi    
    
    
    Found this interesting. www.icantbelieveitsnotbutter.com/turnthetubaround/#/turnyourselfaround?mId=32311253.3    
    
    
    GOOGLE IO being streamed today on YouTube!    
    
    
    I'm at Flour +  Water (2401 Harrison Street, at 20th St, San Francisco) w/ 3 others http://4sq.com/lusjJe    
    
    
    I'm at Starry Plough Pub (3101 Shattuck Ave, at Prince St, Berkeley) http://4sq.com/jUqDgv    
    
    
    I'm at Robledo Family Winery (21901 Bonness Rd, Sonoma) http://4sq.com/jtb3HI    
    
    
    I'm at Robledo Family Winery (21901 Bonness Rd, Sonoma) w/ 4 others http://4sq.com/kFvCB5    
    
    
    I'm at B.R. Cohn Winery (15000 Sonoma Hwy, Glen Ellen) w/ 2 others http://4sq.com/in92LB    
    
    
    I'm at St. Francis Winery http://4sq.com/lmAjvu    
    
    
    My 1st B2B!! (@ Bay To Breakers w/ 68 others) http://4sq.com/jBA3aU    
    
    
    http://city13-suemccauley.eventbrite.com/    
    
    
    Bridesmaids (@ AMC Loews Metreon 16) http://4sq.com/lDaCza    
    
    
    Go Giants (@ AT&T Park w/ 91 others) http://4sq.com/jhTxul    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/iKCu7x    
    
    
    @SFGiants 4 homeruns    
    
    
    Best pizza in bay area! (@ Pizza My Heart) http://4sq.com/mDq9Xm    
    
    
    YouTube hit Cahill at Wednesday's game http://sanfrancisco.giants.mlb.com/news/article.jsp?ymd=20110524&content_id=19493468&vkey=news_sf&c_id=sf&tcid=tw_article_19493468 … via @sfgiants    
    
    
    I'm at Velvet Cantina (3349 23rd St, at Bartlett St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/m05FcM    
    
    
    alicia keys rocked at the apollo this evening in harlem, nyc    
    
    
    http://www.tennessean.com/article/20100110/WILLIAMSON01/1100323/2023/WILLIAMSON/Weigh%20Down%20grows%20large%20online%20following    
    
    
    I'm at Zero Zero (826 Folsom St, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/lOg1rW    
    
    
    I'm at Chouquet's (2500 Washington St, Fillmore, San Francisco) http://4sq.com/kFDJTE    
    
    
    Yeah Google's America's Sales Conference 2011 (@ GFest w/ @jtcooper) http://4sq.com/ipaZ7C    
    
    
    GOOGLE SALES CONFERENCE! ! (@ ASC 2011) http://4sq.com/m48li6    
    
    
    http://www.wdyl.com/#     
    
    
    I LOVE GOOGLE + PLUS PROJECT! 
http://googleblog.blogspot.com/2011/06/introducing-google-project-real-life.html …    
    
    
    http://halloween13-suemccauley.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Snow, Snow & More Snow in Manhattan :)    
    
    
    Best Show on Television? NBC Universal's "THE OFFICE" (Hands-Down)!    
    
    
    I'm at PDX (NE Airport Way, Portland). http://4sq.com/dzqNx9    
    
    
    time to get my "inner nasty" on and start running 13.1 miles! woot woot!    
    
    
    Go Team USA!! Who's watching the Olympics??!    
    
    
    Watch “And Then There Was Salsa” on Vimeo! http://vimeo.com/9194146    
    
    
    Delicious brunch w/ B & L! (@ Tipsy Parson) http://4sq.com/B9rqs    
    
    
    Yummy mimosas w/ CJ! :-) (@ Central Park - Loeb Boathouse Restaurant w/ 3 others) http://4sq.com/6T9BaK    
    
    
    http://mashable.com/2010/03/03/twitter-10-billion-tweets/?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=Feed:+Mashable+(Mashable)    
    
    
    