@ReikiColin Thanks for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Interested in learning Reiki for balance, healing & well-being? I hold classes monthly in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
        
    
    
    Client w/hemophilia shares how she benefits from receiving Reiki for pain relief & stress management http://bit.ly/KD9b0l     
    
    
    @NatHealthTouch Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Interested in learning Reiki for balance, healing & well-being? I hold classes monthly in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Enjoyed receiving & sharing Reiki with @Attune_ATL and @mmkandi this morning! #bliss    
    
    
    Looking forward to educating about & sharing Reiki at Hemophilia of GA's Pain Summit tomorrow!    
    
    
    Definitely a lovely addition! RT @Attune_ATL: @mmkandi @dragonflyreiki Reiki with Bergamot. Aaaaaah    
    
    
    I'm attending Pema's birthday 'Practicing Peace' retreat http://conta.cc/Kasvkn  #pemachodron    
    
    
    In-depth article on purification practice of panchakarma by @Wellth: From Here to Serenity http://shar.es/sdL6y  #ayurveda    
    
    
    Educating about & sharing Reiki samples with participants of Hemophilia of GA's Pain Summit today! #wellness #painrelief    
    
    
    We tend to think of people with hemophilia as simply having blood clotting issues, but many also experience chronic pain.    
    
    
    Listening to Dr. Jarrett Moss MD talk about the science of the pain response & medical interventions for pain management.    
    
    
    Pain management is a complex area of medical practice. Often no "cure" for pain, only improved function as a goal.    
    
    
    Effective pain manangement is a lifestyle change. What you do is just as important as the therapy you receive.    
    
    
    Awesome! RT @LoveHealsReiki Worked on a chiropractor yesterday- he said he felt as if he was floating    
    
    
    Start off your week relaxed & balanced. Free Reiki healing clinic tomorrow 11am - 3 pm at @CandlerPChiro!  http://bit.ly/MyAw2r     
    
    
    Isn't it wonderful :) RT @ProseMakerMedia: Now when I look at certain loved ones, my hands heat up. #reiki #nonduality ?!?    
    
    
    Enjoy brunch at @RadialCafe & then visit us at @CandlerPChiro for a free mini Reiki treatment - we're here until 3 pm!    
    
    
    Busy day at the Reiki Clinic! Happy so many came in & thank you to @crispix67 & @LoveHealsReiki for their Reiki hands. :)    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Wow - that is gorgeous! :)    
    
    
    Interested in learning Reiki for balance, healing & well-being? I hold classes monthly in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    @DivineLotusHeal Thank you so much! Appreciate your feedback! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TerrenceJ is growing a beard + shaving it for charity. Join #BroadCause #ShaveWithAPurpose + twitpic a beard pic http://bit.ly/MrU8sj     
    
    
    Want to learn Reiki for balance, healing & well-being?Next class July 27-28 in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Jin Shin Jyutsu Touch Therapy May Reduce Pain in Cancer Patients: http://bit.ly/Lxt8UQ     
    
    
    Highly recommend her CD! RT @GinnyMackles: Best Reiki CD 2012 Reader's Choice winner!  http://ow.ly/aqjFX  #reiki #meditation    
    
    
    Reiki is mentioned here! > Four integrative medicine modalities gaining popularity - Chicago Tribune http://bit.ly/N2aclt     
    
    
    Interested in learning Reiki for balance, healing & well-being? I hold classes monthly in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thank you for sharing my story!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Was inspired to share my story RT @Wellth: Reiki Healing: A Daughter’s Gift http://bit.ly/MJKfaB  #reiki    
    
    
    Help support my friend Jon's Kickstarter campaign - "Journey to Pangmo", a book of drawings from trip to Himalayas http://kck.st/NhOqGn     
    
    
    Happy 4th of July! - http://eepurl.com/m6JYr     
    
    
    Interested in learning Reiki for balance, healing & well-being? I hold classes monthly in Atlanta: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Now offering Foot, Hand & Ear Reflexology! Introductory pricing for July & August: http://bit.ly/NvLWEj     
    
    
    Happy Independence Day! Wishing you all fun and fireworks!    
    
    
    @RevDannyFisher Jon is a friend of mine - thank you so much for tweeting about his book project! It's going to be beautiful!    
    
    
    Thank you to @Wellth for inspiring me to tell my story of sharing Reiki w/my mom when she was in ICU http://bit.ly/MJKfaB     
    
    
    @ndcollier Oh wow, that was a tough post to read. Lost a dear friend to suicide in my 20s (same method too); still hurts my heart.    
    
    
    Reiki sparklers! ;-) #July4th http://yfrog.com/kkwrvgzj     
    
    
        
    
    
    Now offering Foot, Hand & Ear Reflexology! Introductory pricing for July & August: http://bit.ly/NvLWEj     
    
    
    So beautiful... RT @ProseMakerMedia: Christ and the Dalai Lama. http://on.fb.me/LY2vZD     
    
    
    Thank you for sharing! RT @lyndalippin Reiki Healing: A Daughter’s Gift http://pinterest.com/pin/59180182574106295/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    @TMODOM Love your pics!    
    
    
    @TMODOM Are you there for business?    
    
    
    Now offering Foot, Hand & Ear Reflexology! Introductory pricing for July & August: http://bit.ly/NvLWEj     
    
    
    @lyndalippin It certainly is - it's me and my mom! :)    
    
    
    @TMODOM Guess you need to bring your own stevia?    
    
    
    Lucky baby golden eagle survives Utah wildfire - Yahoo! News http://news.yahoo.com/lucky-baby-golden-eagle-survives-utah-wildfire-014231178.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH     
    
    
    Ever have a Foot, Hand & Ear Reflexology session?  Introductory pricing for July & August: http://bit.ly/NvLWEj     
    
    
    Nice article by Reiki practitioner Elaine Rainey RT @MindBodyGreen: The Healing Power of Reiki http://bit.ly/MdKnMj     
    
    
    Thanks to http://Reikifun.com  for sharing my guest post: Reiki Healing Saves Mother - http://goo.gl/sbDjU  via @Wellth    
    
    
    Give us this day our daily #Reiki practice: http://bit.ly/HKBI6n     
    
    
    @Chris_Eh_Young Sending you a virtual cup of joe! :)    
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH     
    
    
    Ever have a Foot, Hand & Ear Reflexology session?  Introductory pricing for July & August: http://bit.ly/NvLWEj     
    
    
    Learn the healing, balancing art of Reiki - next class July 27-28 in #atlanta http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Englewood Hospital adds Reiki healing for cancer patients: http://bit.ly/NApU7o  #wellness #stressrelief    
    
    
    Learn the healing, balancing art of Reiki - next class July 27-28 in #atlanta http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    @mmkandi Appreciate the mention! And always good to see you! :)    
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH     
    
    
    @DustyLuvv You are an old soul romantic! Headed on your way to L.A.?    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv While you're in L.A., look up my friend Kelly, who started @hiyoga & is owner of Karuna Yoga. You will adore her!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv She introduced me to yoga and Zen meditation almost 15 yrs ago - one of those people who change your life for the better! :)    
    
    
    Busy morning giving Reiki and Reflexology treatments. Life is good. :)    
    
    
    Learn the healing, balancing art of Reiki - next class July 27-28 in #atlanta http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Happy Birthday and deep bows to Ani Pema Chodron.    
    
    
    Reiki is the breath of life for this woman with lung cancer & emphysema http://shar.es/tC5jp  via @Wellth    
    
    
    Top Surgeon To Speak at Reiki Conference http://bit.ly/NtB659  via @columbiasurgery #cancer #healing    
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH  #reiki #reflexology #lifecoaching    
    
    
    "Your light fills the ocean where I live." ~Rumi    
    
    
    @simplyjikiden Very pretty! But you know me - I like dragonflies! :)    
    
    
    @BlissInMe Odd - there's no message from you on my vm. When is a good time to call?    
    
    
    The science of compassion http://nyti.ms/Ntc32l  "compassion toward a single individual does shape our actions toward others."    
    
    
    Glad to connect with @BlissInMe today! My students make me smile & I'm inspired by their enthusiasm for Reiki!    
    
    
    A nurse discusses Reiki on her blog & endorses it for wellness support: Does Reiki Heal? http://shar.es/tJrym     
    
    
    Relieve stress & create more balance in your daily life - learn the healing art of Reiki: July 27-28 http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH     
    
    
    @GinnyMackles Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic - Sun July 22 from 11am - 3pm at @CandlerPChiro #Atlanta - http://eepurl.com/nFn29     
    
    
    "Incurable is curing from within." - thanks @crispix67 for this quote! It's perfect!    
    
    
    Summer specials on ALL wellness services - http://eepurl.com/nssfH  #reiki #reflexology #lifecoaching    
    
    
    Sending light and love to the people of Aurora, CO in the wake of this senseless, horrible tragedy.    
    
    
    Relieve stress & create more balance in your daily life - learn the healing art of Reiki: July 27-28 http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Thanks for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sun at @CandlerPChiro! http://bit.ly/NCVuzp  Pls bring non-perishable items for  DEAM food drive!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv All is well & I could always use a big more good energy! :) How's LA?    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv I'm sure it must be hard to be away from your family. How old is your little guy now?    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv He's the same age as my little one! Awww...how long do you think you'll be on the Left Coast?    
    
    
    Relieve stress & create more balance in your daily life - learn the healing art of Reiki: July 27-28 http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thanks for the RTs and good words! :) Have a lovely weekend!    
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic tomorrow at @CandlerPChiro! http://bit.ly/NCVuzp  Pls bring non-perishable items for DEAM food drive!    
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic TODAY 11 am - 3pm at @CandlerPChiro! http://bit.ly/NCVuzp  Pls bring canned items for DEAM food drive!    
    
    
    Another good turnout for today's free Reiki healing clinic! And lots of donations for the DEAM food drive. Thank you all!    
    
    
    Today's #affirmation: I am healthy, happy & peaceful. My body, mind & spirit are in perfect balance. I am whole.    
    
    
    Beautifully stated. RT @ethannichtern: The point is not to be perfect. The point is to be aware.    
    
    
    University Hospitals integrating alternative therapies into patient care (& Reiki training for employees) http://bit.ly/LKQNC2     
    
    
    @Fistulanigeria Your FB page link doesn't seem to be correct. Is it this? http://on.fb.me/MGwatb  These women need so much help & support.    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my lovely & inspiring friend Kelly Wood of @hiyoga! Thank you for your gift of friendship. <3    
    
    
    Today's #affirmation: I accept myself unconditionally. I am worthy of love, abundance and joy in my life.    
    
    
    Have compassion. For others. For yourself. Everyone benefits.    
    
    
    @BillNixon4 Thanks for the retweets! :)    
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching Reiki tonight and tomorrow! That's my happy zone! :)    
    
    
    @DivineLotusHeal Thank you! :) Happy Friday!    
    
    
    My hometown! Wow! RT @ethannichtern: The most AMAZING picture of NYC last night. Photo by Rahul Sengupta http://twitpic.com/aceil3     
    
    
    Thrilled that several people signed up for my Reiki class at last minute - scrambling to put together enough manuals! :)    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia It was a lovely Reiki class tonight. There was so much peace on the students' faces. Really very moving.    
    
    
    "Are we willing to accept our own worthiness?" - Sakyong Mipham Rinpoche    
    
    
    @Stephlmcphee Can't send a PM because you're not following me. What is her name/location/issue?    
    
    
        
    
    
    New client today experienced profound relaxation during his Reiki session & realized he'd never experienced that before.    
    
    
    @KellyBeav Oh yes, right there with you! Here's my story (part of it, anyway): http://bit.ly/dvPXLf     
    
    
    My teacher, Hyakuten Inamoto, is in the hospital with liver issues. Please send Reiki, prayers & light for his healing.    
    
    
    This brought a smile to my face! :) RT @Dolly_Parton: The magic is inside you. There ain’t no crystal ball.    
    
    
    @chriscruncher Awesome! I hope you have a wonderful class!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Quoted re starting Reiki/wellness practice while working f/t RT @usnews: 8 Ways to Find More Time in the Day http://bit.ly/MjfCLt     
    
    
    @Stephlmcphee So glad to hear. If you're on FB, you can like http://on.fb.me/QymnKS  & submit a request for multiple distance sessions.    
    
    
    Dragonflies seem to be everywhere lately. I keep seeing them & so do students & clients. Such auspicious energy!    
    
    
    Dragonfly Reiki August newsletter: meditation classes & open house! - http://eepurl.com/odGmX     
    
    
    @SuzannePSA Thank you! :)    
    
    
    When you are told you have some kind of physical affliction, you can either prepare to suffer or prepare to heal ~ Dr. Wayne Dyer    
    
    
    @GinnyMackles Thank you for the RTs! Have an awesome weekend! <3    
    
    
    Dragonfly Reiki August newsletter: meditation classes & open house! - http://eepurl.com/odGmX     
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Oh no, not poo on your shoe! #stinky    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Yuuuuuuuuuuuck!!!!!!    
    
    
    Love, light & prayers to the victims of hatred & intolerance in the Sikh gurdwara. We need to do better.    
    
    
    Open House on Sat. Aug 11 from 6-8 pm! Stop by, celebrate with us & learn about services we offer! http://bit.ly/Ntyod7     
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Dragonfly Reiki August newsletter: meditation classes & open house! - http://eepurl.com/odGmX     
    
    
    When you live a life of service to others, you see that people's needs aren't really that different. Serve with love.    
    
    
    Intriguing & hopeful RT @lyndalippin: Distance Reiki for Stroke Victim http://lygl.me/MtOmtR  #Reiki    
    
    
        
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Uhhh, those are hands. LOL    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv But since you said that, I may need to change it back to the dragonfly. :)    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv It is supposed to be my hands at the crown/temple areas. #mysteryreiki indeed!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv You always make me smile! :) Next time you're back in the ATL, come see me for #reikilove!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv I will! Keep the Left Coast sparkling with energy. :)    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Thank you for sharing the link to my site on your FB feed. <3    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv I'm thinking about visiting your friend Terry - could use some spiritual guidance. :)    
    
    
    @Moonstone324 I envision the person in front of me & mentally conduct a session as if they were physically there.    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv I will get out to see her soon - need to get some $$ ducks in a row first. :)    
    
    
    Reiki misunderstood, says NZ Reiki master in response to skeptics who question effectiveness http://bit.ly/NB3waD     
    
    
    @clevemarine Thanks for the follow, Gunny. :) My husband was in the Marine Corps too (Desert Storm.) Appreciate your service.    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Heard you got a little shake there in CA! I experienced one there that was a bit stronger - very unsettling!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Yeah, the bigger ones are not so much fun.    
    
    
    Wellness & stress relief meditation series beginning next week! Please join me! http://bit.ly/QJHEPR     
    
    
    Thank you! <3 RT @DustyLuvv: Dont stop, beliiiievin'! Hold on to that feeeelin'! @nrgnfocus @dragonflyreiki @cosmotheandric    
    
    
    @Attune_ATL That's awesome! One my clients (who is facing a cancer diagnosis again) said something similar to me - helped his anxiety.    
    
    
    Beginning next week, I'm offering wellness meditation classes at @CandlerPChiro ! Hope you can join me! http://bit.ly/MA5zSy     
    
    
    @cosmotheandric Oh, thank you so much! I adore them both! :) cc@DustyLuvv    
    
    
    Lifestyle Counseling: A Missed Opportunity http://huff.to/RBkYmi  We must reduce emphasis on disease mgmt & emphasize health promotion.    
    
    
    @cosmotheandric I saw Jonathan a week or so ago in Target - he's around when he's around. :)    
    
    
    Our brains get a cognitive boost! RT @TIMEHealthland: Does meditation make you smarter? | http://ti.me/O8I3ck     
    
    
        
    
    
    @cosmotheandric He planned to move but it hasn't happened yet. Would love to have you at one of my classes - just let me know! :)    
    
    
    Excellent post on the life of Mikao Usui, the founder of #Reiki Ryoho, written by @ReikiColin for @Wellth's blog.    
    
    
    Tuesday at 6pm join me for a wellness meditation class at @CandlerPChiro. Stress less, feel better! http://bit.ly/Qn6DUR     
    
    
    Relax more, stress less! Free Reiki healing clinic on Sun Aug 19 from 11am - 3 pm at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/NsBLW7     
    
    
    @aRoaraThunder I hope there's a new wig to go with that #brandnewbag!    
    
    
    Relax more, stress less! Free Reiki healing clinic on Sun Aug 19 from 11am - 3 pm at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/NsBLW7     
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sun Aug 19 at @candlerpchiro #atlanta - http://eepurl.com/ovXt9     
    
    
    Tonight at 6pm join me for a wellness meditation class at @CandlerPChiro. Stress less, feel better! http://bit.ly/Qn6DUR     
    
    
    Deep bows to Mikao Usui on the 147th anniversary of his birth. Grateful for the practice of Reiki he shared with the world.    
    
    
    Relax more, stress less! Free Reiki healing clinic on Sun Aug 19 from 11am - 3 pm at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/NsBLW7     
    
    
    Signs you may be a healer: http://huff.to/OjtvXf     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thanks for the RT! Hope to see you soon!    
    
    
    I join @TwitCause to demand that our presidential candidates #DontForgetEd this election season. Make your voice heard: http://bit.ly/N1fKeq     
    
    
    Thank you Ginny! RT @GinnyMackles: #MustFollow #Reiki Wonders!  @simplyjikiden @RAAcademy @DinahKCohen @DragonflyReiki @usui2102 #FF    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Wishing you and your family well!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ndcollier Kotodama is such a powerful aspect of practice. I chant the Reiki Principles in Japanese daily, even silently during Reiki.    
    
    
    @ConsumerSheek Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy Birthday and deep gassho bows to Komyo Reiki Kai founder, Hyakuten Inamoto Sensei!    
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic TODAY at @CandlerPChiro from 11am - 3 pm! Stress less, relax more! http://bit.ly/NsBLW7     
    
    
    The Reiki Principles and living with chronic illness: http://bit.ly/RczcJb  #wellness #selfcare    
    
    
    Join me at 6pm tonight for a wellness meditation class at @CandlerPChiro. Stress less, be well! http://bit.ly/Qn6DUR     
    
    
    Do you live with chronic illness? Learn how the Reiki Principles can aid in healing & wholeness http://bit.ly/RczcJb     
    
    
    We honor with gratitude the life & work of Reiki Master Don Beckett, who passed away in his sleep this week.    
    
    
    @mmkandi @Attune_ATL I can do 10, although 10:30 or 11 would be a little bit easier.    
    
    
    Reiki For Cancer Patients- Dispelling Common Reiki Myths | Focus on Cancer http://shar.es/7v4f2  via @PennMedicine    
    
    
    Return to balance. Tonight at 6pm join me for a stress relief meditation class at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/Qn6DUR     
    
    
    @ndcollier Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Gratitude to @ReikiColin for his lovely musical version of Reiki Principles in English & Japanese http://youtu.be/re6SZz1O5DU     
    
    
    @mmkandi @Attune_ATL I might have a conflict - will let you know in a day or so.    
    
    
    Reiki in cancer care - how it complements & balances conventional medical treatment http://bit.ly/OenJpB  via @Wellth    
    
    
    @ndcollier Me too. :(    
    
    
    @ndcollier I know that feeling. Worse is getting a notification on an account months after the person has already passed.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Breathe into balance. Join me tomorrow evening at 6pm for Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/RcAy6G     
    
    
    Tap into your wellness center! Join me tonight at 6pm for Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/RcAy6G     
    
    
    You cannot change darkness by telling darkness it is wrong. You change darkness by being light. - Sherri Lane    
    
    
    Thank you to @komyoreikikainy for sharing the story of my journey thru Reiki practice & Komyo Reiki Kai http://bit.ly/PPsS7y     
    
    
    @Attune_ATL Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    @mmkandi @Attune_ATL I will be able to make it this Friday! Yay!!    
    
    
    @mmkandi Will you send address info?    
    
    
    Stress less, feel better! Join me tonight at 6pm for Stress Relief Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/TwUkHz     
    
    
    @Attune_ATL Awwww, bummer. Well, @mmkandi and I decided to reschedule since it's nicer to have 3 sets of Reiki hands instead of 2. :)    
    
    
    Your room feels so healing! "MT @Attune_ATL: Todays client: "The only time I don't have a knot in my stomach is when I am in this room."    
    
    
    Spinal cord injury and #Reiki healing: David's story http://bit.ly/N7NXMK     
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Thank you so much for sharing my story! <3    
    
    
    Grateful for very busy month & grateful for the past 2 days off with family & friends. A healthy life is a balanced one.    
    
    
    Spinal cord injury & Reiki healing: David's story http://bit.ly/N7NXMK     
    
    
    What's in your wellness toolkit? - http://eepurl.com/o8Cn5     
    
    
    Reiki can help support people living with a spinal cord injury. Here is David's story: http://bit.ly/N7NXMK     
    
    
    Ease into your weekend with Stress Relief Meditation w/me tomorrow night at 6pm at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/NN4OWW     
    
    
    @digitalzendo Hope you are doing well, Seiho!    
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching Reiki Level I this weekend to a group of childbirth educators/providers. :)    
    
    
    Join me tonight at 6pm at @CandlerPChiro for my Stress Relief Meditation class http://on.fb.me/NN4OWW  #wellness    
    
    
    @HealMainStream Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    @DustyLuvv Thanks for the RT! :) <3    
    
    
    Thank you! RT @Naware: #FF @DragonflyReiki @Starlene @ReikiAwakening @    
    
    
    The Reiki class I'm teaching for birth doulas is inspiring. They honor the sacred journey of birth & see Reiki practice in that light.    
    
    
    Feedback from this weekends's Reiki class: "I love it when I leave an event with a renewed sense of self & purpose."    
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Sign up for the free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro Sun Sept 23 http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    Join @JohnLegend + share a story about a teacher who made a difference in your life! http://bit.ly/OdNoTf  #JCPCares    
    
    
    Beginning again & again is the actual practice, not a problem to be overcome. - @SharonSalzberg #spiritualpractice    
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Sign up for the free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro Sun Sept 23 http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    What's in your wellness toolkit? - http://eepurl.com/o8Cn5     
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Sign up for the free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro Sun Sept 23 http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    Happy Birthday to my lovely friend (and Virgo buddy) Dale of @Attune_ATL ! xoxo    
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Sign up for the free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro Sun Sept 23 http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Sign up for the free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro Sun Sept 23 http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sunday, September 23 at @CandlerPChiro - http://eepurl.com/o_hFL     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Glad you enjoyed it! And hope you feel better soon too!    
    
    
    Reiki brings warmth and compassion at Portsmouth Regional Hospital http://bit.ly/QxhxJx     
    
    
    Escape from the rain & spark your internal sunshine tonight at 6pm w/ Wellness Meditation $12 drop in http://on.fb.me/V6jyiE     
    
    
    Start off your week stress-free! Come by for a FREE mini Reiki session Sun Sept 23 11am - 3 pm http://bit.ly/OEYn3O     
    
    
    @Carl Thank you for the RT! :) <3    
    
    
    <3 RT @ProseMakerMedia: Student with an "intellectual disability" upon hearing a Renaissance motet: "Is that God music?" #joy #musictherapy    
    
    
    Beginning next week, my Wellness Meditation classes are Sun morn at 9:30am & Tues eve at 6pm.  http://bit.ly/OG4iEw     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia It's amazing. Of course, having an intellectual disability doesn't mean having a creative or spiritual disability. :)    
    
    
    Beginning next week, my Wellness Meditation classes are Sun morn at 9:30am & Tues eve at 6pm.  http://bit.ly/OG4iEw     
    
    
    Beginning next week, my Wellness Meditation classes are Sun morn at 9:30am & Tues eve at 6pm.  http://bit.ly/OG4iEw     
    
    
    Spark your inner sunshine! Join me tomorrow morning at 9:30 am for Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/OG4iEw     
    
    
    Join me to relax & heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation tonight at 6pm at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Join me tonight at 6pm to relax & heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Sign up for the Connecting with the Archangels workshop Oct 20 http://bit.ly/QHBwIc     
    
    
    Need CE credits for massage/bodywork professions? My Reiki classes are approved for CE credit http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Join me Sunday mornings at 9:30am to heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Join me Sunday mornings at 9:30am to heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Join me tonight at 6pm to relax & heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Reiki as a pain management adjunct in screening colonoscopy http://1.usa.gov/WMRVw1     
    
    
    Excited to be participating in @WebMD's Health & Wellness Fair today!    
    
    
    My Reiki information table at the @WebMD Health & Wellness Fair! pic.twitter.com/12LJPwZk    
    
    
    Join me Sunday mornings at 9:30am to heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sunday, Oct 21 at @CandlerPChiro #atlanta - http://eepurl.com/qzf_b     
    
    
    Restore well-being & balance energy at Wellness Meditation with me TONIGHT at 6pm at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/TtztnV     
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thanks for the RT! Hope you are well!    
    
    
    Space is still available for Saturday's "Connecting with the Archangels" workshop! http://bit.ly/QHBwIc     
    
    
    Hunterdon Medical Center Reiki therapists lend their hands to help patients heal | http://NJ.com  http://bit.ly/Rb8oa5     
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching Reiki this morning to a great group of students!    
    
    
    Sending good thoughts to the East Coast, including my hometown of NYC, as Sandy makes her arrival. Be safe!    
    
    
    East Coast: sending you love & good energy! Please be safe!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wishing my family & friends in the NYC area well. Please be safe! Sending you all much love.    
    
    
    Join me tonight at 6pm to relax & heal body, mind & spirit w/ Wellness Meditation at @CandlerPChiro http://on.fb.me/SZp2IG     
    
    
    Thanks-giving every day! - http://eepurl.com/rjVS5     
    
    
    Meditation helpful for easing chronic pain symptoms http://huff.to/Y26oWx  #wellness    
    
    
    One week only! Special pricing on wellness sessions! - http://eepurl.com/ryM5z     
    
    
    I'm offering special pricing on Reiki & Reflexology sessions all next week! - http://eepurl.com/ryM5z     
    
    
    "The important point of spiritual practice is not to try to escape your life, but to face it - exactly and completely.” Dainin Katagiri    
    
    
    Mini-relaxation exercises: A quick fix in stressful moments http://hvrd.me/Q61dnN  #wellness    
    
    
    Special pricing on Reiki & Reflexology sessions this week ONLY! http://bit.ly/Q61OGg     
    
    
    Support emotional & spiritual healing of our veterans & their families. Donate to @veteransheartga today! #veteransday    
    
    
    So grateful that my husband gave me Reiki treatment with me this morning.  This viral bug should be going away soon!    
    
    
    Reiki, other integrative treatments helping cancer patients heal http://bit.ly/T69nLu     
    
    
    Love 1 another & help others to rise to higher levels, simply by pouring out love. Love is infectious & greatest healing energy. -Sai Baba    
    
    
    Good post: Reiki and Consent - where do we draw the line? http://bit.ly/Uon0GQ  via @lyndalippin    
    
    
    Start off your holidays stress-free at this Sunday's free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro ! http://bit.ly/Vbtfjx     
    
    
    Join us for holiday cheer & healing at the Free Reiki Clinic this Sun Dec 2 - http://eepurl.com/sdkNz     
    
    
    Start off your holidays stress-free at this Sunday's free Reiki healing clinic at @CandlerPChiro ! http://bit.ly/Vbtfjx     
    
    
    Reflexology reduces stress, improves health http://bit.ly/11shULr  #wellness    
    
    
    Join us tomorrow for the Free Reiki Healing Clinic at @CandlerPChiro 11am - 3 pm http://bit.ly/Vbtfjx  #wellness    
    
    
    Gift loved ones with wellness...holiday gift certificate specials for Reiki & Reflexology! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Stop by today for the Free Reiki Healing Clinic at @CandlerPChiro 11am - 3 pm http://bit.ly/Vbtfjx  #wellness    
    
    
    Gift loved ones with wellness...holiday gift certificate specials for Reiki & Reflexology! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Beautiful story about healing power of Reiki treatment given to inmates in prison http://bit.ly/VnTP9e  via @Wellth    
    
    
    Gift loved ones with wellness...holiday gift certificate specials for Reiki & Reflexology! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Gift certificate sale for Reiki & Reflexology! - http://eepurl.com/suQsP     
    
    
    @ClickAClass Can't make your upcoming Meetup, but might like to host one at CPC soon...let's talk?    
    
    
    Sitting in the park while my little girl plays is the perfect opportunity to give myself a mini Reiki self-treatment. :-)    
    
    
    Love! "@Wellth: En route to NY Presbyterian Hospital to teach Reiki to staff, the cab door says... http://instagr.am/p/SyHQ7FDa7F/ "    
    
    
    Daily Reiki self-treatment is an opportunity to give yourself loving attention. You deserve it!    
    
    
    As can prednisone for asthma treatment "@Wellth: Steroid injections can lower bone mass http://ow.ly/fLSd7  #steroids #back"    
    
    
    @ClickAClass Will do!    
    
    
    Gift loved ones with wellness...holiday gift certificate specials for Reiki & Reflexology! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    @ZenergeticReiki Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    Gift loved ones with wellness...holiday gift certificate specials for Reiki & Reflexology! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Give the gift of wellness - holiday gift certificate packages for Reiki & Reflexology sessions! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Gift certificates are selling like hot cakes! Treat a loved one to Reiki or Reflexology this holiday! http://bit.ly/VcemHD     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Very helpful for PTSD RT @Wellth: Reiki Healing for the Military http://shar.es/6RHJK  #Reiki #veterans    
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Practice Reiki! RT @DrOz: Stress can have a hugely negative impact on your health. What do you do to keep yours in check? #OzQuestion    
    
    
    Welcome the holidays with our meditation, yoga & Reiki party this Sunday at 5pm @CandlerPChiro http://bit.ly/UEjLc5     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Meditation, Yoga & Reiki for you this Sunday! - http://eepurl.com/sXWKT     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & spiritual growth. Register for Winter 2013 classes in Atlanta http://bit.ly/120shGC     
    
    
    Sending healing & love to everyone affected by the heartbreaking tragedy in Newtown, CT.    
    
    
    Give the gift of wellness with Reiki & Reflexology! - http://eepurl.com/te9Yb     
    
    
    Healing a broken world starts with us http://wp.me/p1j208-db  #reiki #compassion    
    
    
    @HartReikiCURES Thank you for the RTs! Peace to you!    
    
    
    Happy Winter Solstice!    
    
    
    Quote of the day: "Mommy, you smell like Reiki!" :)    
    
    
    Wishing you all the peace, magic & miracles of the holiday.    
    
    
    @Pamcakes1010 Thanks for the RTs!    
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Effects of Reiki on Pain & Anxiety in Patients Attending Day Oncology & Infusion Services Unit http://bit.ly/12OsA8P     
    
    
    @Pandorasboxheal Thank you for the RTs! :)    
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Wishing you peace, good health and abundance in the New Year!    
    
    
    Complementary Medicine Saves Money, Study Says http://bit.ly/ZPrqLR  #wellness    
    
    
    New Year, New You! Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    New Year, New You! Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    @reikitimes Thank you for promoting our free Reiki healing clinic! Happy New Year!    
    
    
    You are perfect just as you are http://bit.ly/12W33uH  #spirituality    
    
    
    “You are the sky. Everything else – it’s just the weather.” - Pema Chödrön    
    
    
    Perfect Just as You Are - Happy 2013! http://eepurl.com/tzNSb     
    
    
    Winter 2013 schedule for Reiki training & personal development workshops: http://bit.ly/Vwb06D     
    
    
    Message on the Change of the Era in the Mayan Calendar by Don Tomás Calvo Mateo http://bit.ly/VwbWrv  (via @Wellth)    
    
    
    Perfect Just as You Are - Happy 2013! http://eepurl.com/tzNSb     
    
    
    New Year, New You! Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Perfect Just as You Are - Happy 2013! http://eepurl.com/tzNSb     
    
    
    New Year, New You! Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    New Year, New You! Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a deeper, more meaningful life! Workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    @Wellth Thanks for the RT! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Healing yourself is connected with healing others. - Yoko Ono    
    
    
    Use your gifts to create a more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Reiki During Cancer Treatment | Focus on Cancer http://shar.es/4hDj8  via @PennMedicine    
    
    
    Doctors  are embracing lower-cost medical solutions & inclusion of integrative therapies http://huff.to/UKMsVH     
    
    
    Be relaxed & peaceful.  Free mini Reiki treatment at the Reiki Healing Clinic! Sun Jan 20 http://bit.ly/RGwGwr  #atlanta    
    
    
    Discover your gifts & create a more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    Be relaxed & peaceful.  Free mini Reiki treatment at the Reiki Healing Clinic! Sun Jan 20 http://bit.ly/RGwGwr  #atlanta    
    
    
    Discover your gifts & create a more meaningful life! Register for workshop on Jan 26 - Atlanta http://bit.ly/U0eU5L     
    
    
    @DivineLotusHeal Thank you for the RT! :)    
    
    
    The Reiki Principles & living with chronic illness: healing, wholeness & self-care http://bit.ly/RczcJb     
    
    
    Receive a free mini Reiki treatment at the Reiki Healing Clinic! Sun Jan 20 http://bit.ly/RGwGwr  #atlanta    
    
    
    Receive a free mini Reiki treatment at the Reiki Healing Clinic! Sun Jan 20 http://bit.ly/RGwGwr  #atlanta    
    
    
    I endorse @TwitCause in the Shorty category #activism because they empower people who want to help causes http://bit.ly/UWDtod  RT    
    
    
    Restore well-being with a free mini Reiki treatment! - http://eepurl.com/t5blT     
    
    
    Heartfelt thanks to you! RT @ProseMakerMedia: So grateful for the learning and deepening of practice at @DragonflyReiki.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Stressed? Anxious? Feeling blue? Reiki helps restore balance. http://bit.ly/VacxS3  #wellness #healing    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thank you for sharing! The next few weeks should be a fun ride. :)    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Your friend? Sending hugs your way.    
    
    
    Reading Frank Arjava Petter's new book "This is Reiki." Interesting historical facts about Usui Sensei & early history of Reiki.    
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki for improved health, stress relief & emotional well-being: http://bit.ly/Vwb06D     
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki for improved health, stress relief & emotional well-being: http://bit.ly/Vwb06D     
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki for improved health, stress relief & emotional well-being: http://bit.ly/Vwb06D     
    
    
    Harmony for Heart & Mind - http://eepurl.com/uMjBj     
    
    
    You have to remove the cause, and then the effect. - Hawayo Takata #reiki    
    
    
    Glad to see inclusion of Reiki! RT @ClevelandClinic: Reiki therapy: what you need to know | http://ow.ly/hoD2Y  #CCHealthTip    
    
    
    “Love begins by taking care of the closest ones – the ones at home.” – Mother Teresa    
    
    
    Working with Mental/Emotional Healing & Distance Healing Workshop: Feb 9 http://bit.ly/WpVXMR  #reiki    
    
    
    :) RT @lyndalippin: A Little Reiki Humor http://lygl.me/N9cC4X  #Reiki    
    
    
    Signed the lease on new office space for my healing center in Decatur! Thrilled to be serving my community once again!    
    
    
    Moving in to my new office today! :)    
    
    
    @ReikiRyann Thank you! :)    
    
    
    @ProseMakerMedia Thank you! Can't wait for you to see my new place! :)    
    
    
    I trust my body's urge to heal. I don't have to make it get well. All I have to do is support it. #affirmation #healing    
    
    
    I continue to receive the energy coming forth from the perfect spiritual pattern for my body. #affirmation #healing    
    
    
    I allow my body to more fully receive the light of who I am. #affirmation #healing    
    
    
    Dragonfly Reiki has a new office location! - http://eepurl.com/u7YTz     
    
    
    The Five Pillars of Good Health - Dr. Andrew Weil: http://bit.ly/WxsnFn  #wellness    
    
    
    @DivineLotusHeal Thank you so much! I'm very happy to be in my own place (& can put up my signage etc!)    
    
    
    I noticed I have 1,111 "likes" on my Facebook page! That's a very auspicious number!    
    
    
    Had a great first day in my new office!    
    
    
    @tdragonfly Ooh, pretty!    
    
    
    @LalaWeathington Awww, thank you! :)    
    
    
    @DivineLotusHeal The "little" things are sometimes really BIG things. :)    
    
    
    How Reiki healing can help reduce post-surgical pain & speed up recovery time http://bit.ly/Y1sCUR  Via @Wellth    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Try a free Reiki healing treatment next Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Reflexology for managing pain and anxiety - The Clinical Advisor http://bit.ly/VKcgpm  #wellness    
    
    
    I feel the presence of healing energy in my body. #affirmation    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic on Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic on Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Dragonfly on the grounds of the Jekyll Island Club Hotel. pic.twitter.com/keT4OTlx    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic on Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic on Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic on Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #atlanta    
    
    
    Love this story about one of my Reiki clients who is thriving after an accident left him a quadriplegic: http://bit.ly/XSw7Pr     
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sunday, February 17! - http://eepurl.com/vtkPr     
    
    
    Thanks! "@simplyjikiden: #ff @Wellth @dragonflyreiki for positive thought leadership in the global #reiki community"    
    
    
    My husband did some guerrilla marketing for me using chalk at our local playground today! So sweet! pic.twitter.com/peoP98ZI    
    
    
    Stressed out? In pain? Visit our monthly free Reiki healing clinic this Sunday Feb 17! http://bit.ly/Yi6W7D  #wellness    
    
    
    Regular rest periods throughout day helps boost productivity (make time for wellness too!)  http://nyti.ms/12dSHms     
    
    
    How does #Reiki help? By helping your self-healing mechanisms to function at their very best http://bit.ly/12yZjRl  via @Wellth    
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & improved well-being! Next class - Feb 22 & 23 (Register now!) http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Learn Reiki for healing, balance & improved well-being! Next class - Feb 22 & 23 (Register now!) http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Please vote for me in http://About.com 's Readers' Choice Awards for Favorite Reiki Teacher! http://bit.ly/W1IxbA  Vote daily!    
    
    
    Learn traditional Japanese-style Reiki for improved health & well-being. Next class this Fri & Sat: http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Please vote for me in http://About.com 's Readers' Choice Awards for Favorite Reiki Teacher! http://bit.ly/W1IxbA  Vote daily!    
    
    
    Please vote for me in http://About.com 's Readers' Choice Awards for Favorite Reiki Teacher! http://bit.ly/W1IxbA  Vote daily!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Attune_ATL I was totally floored by the cookies! And they taste amazing too.    
    
    
    My teacher profile is up on http://About.com 's 2013 Readers' Choice Awards for Favorite #Reiki Teacher: http://bit.ly/12XkqwW     
    
    
    Please take a moment to vote for me for Favorite Reiki Teacher! Thank you!  http://bit.ly/W1IxbA     
    
    
    Great video! Pamela Miles: Reiki, Recovery and Optimal Health: http://youtu.be/At7cW44CTh4  cc: @Wellth    
    
    
    Get relief from seasonal allergies with Reiki & Reflexology http://bit.ly/ZM8I7k  #wellness #healing    
    
    
    @Nigaya Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    Check out my @cafepress shop! Dragonfly Reiki Healing Center http://bit.ly/15UFns3     
    
    
    Seasonal allergies got you down? Get relief with Reiki and Reflexology http://bit.ly/ZM8I7k  #wellness    
    
    
    I've got a sweet deal for you! $5-10 off your next Reiki or Reflexology session! http://bit.ly/13zJjz6     
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki as it was traditionally practiced in Japan! Register for Mar 15-16 class http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    March 2013 newsletter: get allergy relief with Reiki + Reflexology - http://eepurl.com/v75xz     
    
    
    Dale is fantastic! RT @Attune_ATL: "I come out of Reiki sessions more relaxed than when I receive massage therapy." - tonights client    
    
    
    Need seasonal allergy relief? Try Reiki or Reflexology to nip those symptoms in the bud http://bit.ly/WDEXzf  #wellness    
    
    
    Thank you to one of my students for her lovely review on @yelp http://bit.ly/14pNCsD     
    
    
    Louisville hospitals embracing alternative medicine, including #Reiki http://cjky.it/YpBSEF  #wellness    
    
    
    "Natural forces within us are the true healers of disease" - Hippocrates #health #wellness    
    
    
    Put the little one to bed tonight with some Reiki and chanting the Reiki Principles in Japanese.    
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki as it was traditionally practiced in Japan! Register for Mar 15-16 class http://bit.ly/aQ6sTO     
    
    
    Want to relieve stress & feel better ? Visit the free Reiki healing clinic next Sun Mar 17 in #decaturga http://bit.ly/YPbd24     
    
    
    Stress Less infographic lists Reiki, massage & acupuncture as being effective for stress reduction  http://bit.ly/YgKvPN     
    
    
    Want to relieve stress & feel better ? Visit the free Reiki healing clinic next Sun Mar 17 in #decaturga http://bit.ly/YPbd24     
    
    
    Want to relieve stress & feel better ? Visit the free Reiki healing clinic next Sun Mar 17 in #decaturga http://bit.ly/YPbd24     
    
    
    "Gratitude is a great cure for the mind." - Hawayo Takata #reiki #spiritualpractice    
    
    
    Did you know that we have a Google+ page? https://plus.google.com/b/109594926474533041801/109594926474533041801/about …    
    
    
    Want to relieve stress & feel better ? Visit the free Reiki healing clinic next Sun Mar 17 in #decaturga http://bit.ly/YPbd24     
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sunday, March 17 in Atlanta! - http://eepurl.com/wLJaP     
    
    
    I will be teaching Komyo Reiki in Birmingham AL in early May! More details soon!    
    
    
    Irish eyes will be smiling & Reiki hands will be healing at our free Reiki healing clinic on St. Patrick's Day! http://dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/free-reiki-healing-clinic-sun-march-17/ …    
    
    
    My new sandwich board for outside the office arrived today! :) pic.twitter.com/qwj3rpmYsU    
    
    
    Connect with the Archangels for healing, guidance & manifestation! Register now for Apr 6 workshop http://dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/connecting-with-the-archangels-workshop-april-6/ …    
    
    
    Learn to heal yourself & others! Komyo Reiki Level I class May 10-11 at Embody Practice Center, Birmingham AL http://www.embodybirmingham.com/#!workshops/c13oi …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thank you to Abbadabba's for inviting me to talk about health & wellness benefits of Reiki & Reflexology last night!    
    
    
    And to you! RT @simplyjikiden: Thanks! and happy Friday everyone :) @ReikiHealingNu @OmTimes @blissfullight @Wellth @DragonflyReiki    
    
    
    Japanese-style Reiki comes to Birmingham AL! Learn this healing art for health, well-being & balance. May 10-11 http://www.embodybirmingham.com/#!workshops/c13oi …    
    
    
    Very excited that my Komyo Reiki teacher (& founder) Hyakuten Inamoto, is returning to Atlanta to teach this Fall!    
    
    
    Being more present for myself & others @Wellth: What do you get better at when you practice #Reiki? http://shar.es/eQ0Pq     
    
    
    Military Pathways describes the benefits of #Reiki healing for alleviating stress: http://shar.es/eTHjI  #ptsd    
    
    
    Check out my Reiki classes & workshops for spring/early summer 2013! http://dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Reiki, a Japanese healing technique, brings relief to patients | http://lehighvalleylive.com  http://www.lehighvalleylive.com/entertainment-general/index.ssf/2013/03/reiki_a_japanese_healing_techn.html …    
    
    
    In the Birmingham AL area & want to learn the healing art of Reiki? Register for May 10-11 class! pic.twitter.com/u59y7Yhojz    
    
    
    Google Offers - 20% off 60 min Reiki or Foot Reflexology session http://bit.ly/10ERmYu  #atlanta #wellness #relax    
    
    
    Seasonal allergies throwing you for a loop? Get relief with #Reiki and #Reflexology! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/02/get-relief-from-seasonal-allergies-with-reiki-and-reflexology/ …    
    
    
    If you're stressed, anxious or depressed, take heart. Reiki healing can help you feel better http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/01/reiki-for-stress-anxiety/ …    
    
    
    Good news! Reiki, Rolfing and Reflexology: Proposed Exemption in Colorado http://www.massagemag.com/News/massage-news.php?id=13815&catid=reiki-rolfing-and-reflexology-proposed-exemption-in-colorado&title=#.UVRX81TcSqA.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Wellth Wonderful! Please send Robert my regards - hope to meet him in person one day soon. :)    
    
    
    Join me in Birmingham AL to learn the healing art of Reiki! May 10-11 class at Embody Practice Center http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    @Wellth Were you on a layover for several hours? Had I known, I might have popped down there to keep you company. :)    
    
    
    @Wellth I'm sorry we missed each other this time, but one day in the not-too-distant future, I'm sure we'll get to catch up in person. :)    
    
    
    Spring tune-up for body, mind & spirit - http://eepurl.com/xzDQ9     
    
    
    I'm teaching Japanese-style Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    Grateful for a lovely evening of Reiki and discussion with my students tonight. Warms my heart and soul!    
    
    
    Was up early, listening to the rain while spending a few extra minutes treating myself to Reiki. #morningwakeup    
    
    
    Report: Alternative Medicine Providers Can Help Meet Nation's Primary Care Needs http://www.beckershospitalreview.com/hospital-physician-relationships/report-alternative-medicine-providers-can-help-meet-nations-primary-care-needs.html#.UV1_VVHs2Eo.twitter …    
    
    
    I'm teaching Japanese-style Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    You know you're a Reiki mom when your daughter insists to her friends that you can help make their boo-boos feel better. :)    
    
    
    I'm teaching Japanese-style Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    Some thoughts on how to be a friend to someone with a serious illness http://lisabadams.com/2013/04/05/some-thoughts-on-how-to-be-a-friend-to-someone-with-a-serious-illness/ …    
    
    
    Reflexology may be as effective as painkillers, according to scientific survey http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/9981099/Reflexology-as-effective-as-pain-killers.html … #wellness    
    
    
    I'm teaching Japanese-style Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    I'm teaching Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered. Register now! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    Free Reiki healing clinic this Sun April 21 11am - 2 pm http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/04/free-reiki-healing-clinic-sun-april-21/ … #atlanta #decaturga    
    
    
    @ndcollier Yes, I am. April 26-27. http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/reiki-classes/     
    
    
    Sending prayers for peace & comfort to the city of Boston, marathon runners & families. Our world is in need of deep healing.    
    
    
    An order I can support & follow! Doctor’s Orders: 20 Minutes Of Meditation Twice a Day http://on.wsj.com/139F9e3  #health    
    
    
    Look for the helpers (to quote Mr. Rogers' mom.) There is still more good & light in this world than evil & darkness.    
    
    
    How to Hold The Light When Tragedy Strikes… Especially If You’re an Empath http://www.intuitivebody.com/how-to-hold-the-light-when-tragedy-strikes-especially-if-youre-an-empath/ … via @intuitivebody    
    
    
    Integration of alternative therapies shows promise in PTSD treatment http://www.healio.com/psychiatry/ptsd/news/online/%7BD1791419-A12F-4B18-A07D-511D63EDE9C9%7D/Integration-of-alternative-therapies-shows-promise-in-PTSD-treatment …    
    
    
    Donations we rec'd from yesterday's free Reiki healing clinic will benefit Decatur Farm To School #decaturga #earthday    
    
    
    Space available for upcoming Reiki Level I class in Birmingham AL on May 10-11 http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ … CE credits    
    
    
    Happy #EarthDay! Use your healing hands to plant a new tree or flowers today. Mother Earth will thank you!    
    
    
    Creating safe space & a place for healing. How Reiki can help with trauma http://reikiinmedicine.org/clinical-practice/reiki-healing-for-trauma/ … (via @Wellth)    
    
    
    Learn how Reiki can alleviate symptoms & promote healing of pelvic pain & Interstitial Cystitis http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/04/reiki-healing-for-interstitial-cystitis-and-pelvic-pain-disorders/ …    
    
    
    Learn Japanese-style Reiki healing in Birmingham AL on May 10-11. CE credits offered http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/03/reiki-level-i-training-birmingham-al/ …    
    
    
    Reiki healing for Interstitial Cystitis & Pelvic Pain Disorders http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/04/reiki-healing-for-interstitial-cystitis-and-pelvic-pain-disorders/ … #wellness    
    
    
    Daily Reiki self-treatment is my favorite immune-booster! #wellness #healing    
    
    
    Stressed? Anxious? Feeling blue? Reiki can help. http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/01/reiki-for-stress-anxiety/ … #wellness #healing    
    
    
    Waving to my neighbors at @DancingGoatsATL & enjoying their yummy chai. Warming up now!    
    
    
    A second bride-to-be this month just left to get ready for her wedding after receiving Reiki healing. :)    
    
    
    Reiki & Ear Reflexology on sliding scale fee - Tuesdays 10 AM - 1 PM starting May 7 http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/reiki-treatment/sliding-scale-healing-sessions/ … #decaturga    
    
    
    Reiki & Ear Reflexology on sliding scale fee - Tuesdays 10 AM - 1 PM starting May 7 http://dragonflyreiki.net/reiki-treatmen … #decaturga    
    
    
    So pleased by interest from Dekalb Co employees interested in receiving Reiki healing today at their wellness fair!    
    
    
    Holistic healing for chronic health issues #reiki - http://eepurl.com/zbXLj     
    
    
    My order this morning at @DancingGoatsATL rang up to $4.44. It's going to be an auspicious day!    
    
    
    @ellenmgregg_nh Glad to be of service!! Love angel numbers!    
    
    
    @ReikiHealingNu Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    Sliding scale Reiki or Ear Reflexology sessions every Tues 10 am - 1 pm http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/sliding-scale-healing-services/ … #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    Sliding scale Reiki or Ear Reflexology sessions every Tues 10 am - 1 pm http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/sliding-scale-healing-services/ … #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    Reiki Masters: learn Komyo Reiki Kai from founder Hyakuten Inamoto. Weekend class Nov 1-3 Atlanta http://bit.ly/15UVXKX     
    
    
    Treat the hard-working mama in your life to a Reiki healing session #BookADeal http://bit.ly/10nTcJe  #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    Treat the hard-working mama in your life to a Reiki healing session #BookADeal http://bit.ly/10nTcJe  #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    Reiki Masters: learn Komyo Reiki Kai from founder Hyakuten Inamoto. Weekend class Nov 1-3 Atlanta http://bit.ly/15UVXKX     
    
    
    Reiki Masters: learn Komyo Reiki Kai from founder Hyakuten Inamoto. Weekend class Nov 1-3 Atlanta http://bit.ly/15UVXKX     
    
    
    Reiki Masters: learn Komyo Reiki Kai from founder Hyakuten Inamoto. Weekend class Nov 1-3 Atlanta http://bit.ly/15UVXKX     
    
    
    Sliding scale fee healing sessions now available #reiki #reflexology - http://eepurl.com/zs8T1     
    
    
        
    
    
    Tuesdays 10 AM - 1 PM - sliding scale fee Reiki & Ear Reflexology sessions! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/sliding-scale-healing-services/ … #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    Sending the people of the Oklahoma City area prayers and wishes for their safety and well-being. #tornadoemergency    
    
    
        
    
    
    Help someone in need today. It doesn't have to be a big act, but something that demonstrates goodwill & lovingkindness.    
    
    
    @MidwestReiki thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    Komyo Reiki Kai Training with Hyakuten Inamoto in Atlanta! Nov 1-3 - http://eepurl.com/zQsJv     
    
    
    Integrative Medicine: Work stress increases heart-attack risk http://sacb.ee/14Sn5pq  Mind/body practices can help help!    
    
    
    Sliding scale Reiki & Ear Reflexology sessions offered every Tues 11am - 1 pm http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/sliding-scale-healing-services/ … #decaturga #atlanta    
    
    
    @JuliesFitBit I generally tell people - don't try to convince. Receive Reiki yourself & he will see the benefits to you! That's motivating!    
    
    
    Discover Your Life Purpose Workshop - June 29 http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/discover-your-life-purpose-workshop-june-29/ … #atlanta #personaldevelopment #coaching    
    
    
    Good stuff! RT @Wellth: Last day to register for June 4 MAINSTREAMING #REIKI: Where's the Proof? w/ Pamela Miles http://ow.ly/lEcIO     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Happiness is less a set of circumstances that surround you than a set of conditions that exist within you." - @robmackofficial    
    
    
    There's always room for a miracle.    
    
    
    Can reflexology help with infertility? http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/06/can-reflexology-help-with-infertility/ … #healing    
    
    
    Was a skeptic & left happy & pain-free after Reiki! Love this new http://Kudzu.com  review! http://kudzu.com/r/20828794     
    
    
    Perfect just as you are http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/06/perfect-just-as-you-are/ … #lifecoaching #spirituality    
    
    
    A mama & her eight year old girl came in this morning for #Reiki. Love working w/ families to support #healing & #wellbeing!    
    
    
    Register now for Reiki Level I training in Birmingham, AL Sept 28 http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/06/reiki-level-i-training-in-birmingham-al-sept-28/ …    
    
    
    Heralded cancer surgeon from York County embraces holistic healing strategies - The York Daily Record http://www.ydr.com/living/ci_23461961/heralded-cancer-surgeon-from-york-county-embraces-holistic …    
    
    
    "Reiki awakens the natural powers we all possess but which lie dormant, untapped." Tadeo Yamaguchi    
    
    
    Learn traditional Japanese Reiki with me in Birmingham AL! Sept 28 class at Embody Practice Center pic.twitter.com/5AR0QrPG5C    
    
    
    Discover your life purpose, Reflexology for fertility and more! - http://eepurl.com/A-E4b     
    
    
    Peace. It begins with us. pic.twitter.com/WxRx1l20QR    
    
    
    Beautiful & insightful @tinybuddha: Tragedy Can Help Us Find Our Life's Purpose http://buff.ly/11YRT8n     
    
    
    A few spaces still available for Komyo Reiki Level I on July 26-27. Learn this life-changing healing practice! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Looking forward to teaching my Discover Your Life Purpose Workshop tomorrow! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/05/discover-your-life-purpose-workshop-june-29/ …    
    
    
    Happy Independence Day, U.S.A.!    
    
    
    yes! RT @kelly_carlin: What this country needs is a Declaration of Interdependence. #July4th #Namaste    
    
    
        
    
    
    How has your Reiki practice changed over time? http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2010/06/the-changing-nature-of-reiki/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tips on how to avoid absorbing other peoples' emotions http://www.healerslibrary.com/news/articles/tip-week-avoid-absorbing-emotions/ … via @drbradleynelson #healing #energy    
    
    
    Good morning beautiful people! What are you doing today to bring more love into the world?    
    
    
    Volunteering this morning at my church's outreach ministry, which provides support & resources for the poor & homeless.    
    
    
    @usui2102 May God offer healing & comfort to you. You are whole, perfect & loved beyond measure in God's eyes.    
    
    
    @Wellth Beautiful! I miss my beautiful, vibrant hometown! #NYC Hope you are well, dear friend!    
    
    
    Well-researched @komyoreikikainy: Hawayo Takata's 22 Master Students
- Robert Fueston
http://www.robertfueston.com/reiki/articles/reiki_people.html …... http://fb.me/6p58JToqd     
    
    
    This was my morning too! @DharmaTalks: I'm thankful for this moment the colors & breeze through my window with a cardinal calling    
    
    
    One of the men volunteering at church this morning has been member for 60 years! So much love, wisdom & service here.    
    
    
    @Wellth I may have some exciting Reiki-related news soon to share with you. Will know more by next week. :-)    
    
    
    Stop by my table at the Team Decatur kick-off on July 22 to say hi & enter a drawing to win a Reiki gift certificate! #decaturga    
    
    
    My personal story of Reiki helping my mother heal from a near-fatal dosing error http://reikiinmedicine.org/reiki-stories/reiki-healing-mom/ … (via @Wellth)    
    
    
    Join me in Birmingham AL on Sat Sept 28 to learn the Japanese healing art of Reiki! pic.twitter.com/kFEcr3pGE1    
    
    
    Love this! RT @serenityreiki: Keep a green tree in your heart and perhaps a singing bird will come.  ~Chinese Proverb    
    
    
    At the Team Decatur kick-off event at the Rec Center in #decaturga! #wellness #health pic.twitter.com/iDu4ojyrn4    
    
    
    Dana offering Doc Broc some hand reflexology! :-) pic.twitter.com/H0Y1XfClPw    
    
    
    How can Reiki healing help if you're a runner/walker or recovering from injury? http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/07/reiki-healing-at-team-decatur-get-active-event/ … #wellness    
    
    
    Thanks to @abba_ks for her lovely review of how Reiki helped her stay well during cancer treatment! http://www.yelp.com/biz/dragonfly-reiki-decatur-2#hrid:YFQ2TezRBqrMOnw2G15FQA …    
    
    
    My Komyo Reiki Shoden class is full to capacity tonight - a good problem to have!    
    
    
    Lunch with my Reiki students at @chaipanidecatur #yum pic.twitter.com/3SEO2VlKTr    
    
    
    Practicing group hands-on Reiki treatment during our Komyo Reiki Shoden class. pic.twitter.com/FDcF9dpqPE    
    
    
    Congratulations & gassho bows to today's Komyo Reiki Shodem students! pic.twitter.com/DAP4ZRpjTA    
    
    
    @ClickAClass Thank you for the testimonial! @DivasRun, happy to help if you're on the road to recovery! :-)    
    
    
    Learn the Japanese healing art of Reiki with me in Birmingham, AL Sept 28! Register now! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/06/reiki-level-i-training-in-birmingham-al-sept-28/ …    
    
    
    My student @ProseMakerMedia's article at @MindBodyGreen on qualities to seek in a #Reiki teacher http://www.mindbodygreen.com/0-10458/5-things-to-look-for-in-your-reiki-teacher.html …    
    
    
    Things I love about Reiki #1 http://wp.me/p1VyF6-ns  via @simplyjikiden    
    
    
    Learn the healing art of Reiki with me at Embody Practice Center in Birmingham, AL on Sept. 28. http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/06/reiki-level-i-training-in-birmingham-al-sept-28/ …    
    
    
    My student @ProseMakerMedia's article at @MindBodyGreen on qualities to seek in a #Reiki teacher http://www.mindbodygreen.com/0-10458/5-things-to-look-for-in-your-reiki-teacher.html …    
    
    
    Had a wonderful Reiki-filled day - client sessions and led a workshop on the Reiki Principles. Lots of great energy!    
    
    
    Sounds lovely! #japan RT @IHReiki: Walking the sacred path: http://fb.me/Jn1UZ9pR     
    
    
    There is no quick fix for the healing process, but commitment to diet, lifestyle & supportive therapies makes a difference.    
    
    
    How can Reiki healing or acupuncture help you? http://www.utsandiego.com/news/2013/aug/06/tp-nontraditional-practices-offer-healing-therapy/ … via @utsandiego    
    
    
    We are all innately capable of healing. http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/08/healing-the-reintegration-of-self-and-source/ … #reiki    
    
    
    Transformative healing for mind, body & spirit http://eepurl.com/Dn4tf     
    
    
    @HappyReiki Thank you for the RT! Blessings!    
    
    
    "Address the root cause of suffering within yourself. There is no greater difference one can make in the world than this." - @jimpalmer    
    
    
    Healing is the reintegration of Self and Source http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/08/healing-the-reintegration-of-self-and-source/ … #reiki #wellbeing    
    
    
    "Don't let people pull you into their storm. Pull them into your peace." My reminder for today.    
    
    
    @simplyjikiden Thank you for sharing!    
    
    
    Learn to heal & care for yourself & others with Reiki! Sept/Oct classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Learn to heal & care for yourself & others with Reiki! Sept/Oct classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Awesome! @GinnyMackles: #Reiki in Twin Cities #PriorLake https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=652446801434896&set=a.652446778101565.1073741826.305472626132317&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    Today only http://wp.me/p1j208-il  #reikiprinciples    
    
    
    Healing takes courage, and we all have courage, even if we have to dig a little to find it. 
-- Tori Amos    
    
    
    Learn Reiki the Japanese way! Register now for Sept & Oct classes in #Atlanta GA & #Birmingham AL http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    @JyoganReiki You are in esteemed company!    
    
    
    Expressing gratitude for the life and spiritual gifts of Mikao Usui, the founder of Reiki Ryoho. Happy 8/15 Birthday Usui-sensei!    
    
    
    Learn Reiki the Japanese way! Register now for Sept & Oct classes in #Atlanta GA & #Birmingham AL http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to Mikao Usui, the founder of Reiki Ryoho (Reiki Healing Art.) Grateful for his gift of practice!    
    
    
    Miracles of healing happen every day.    
    
    
    Follow Dragonfly Reiki on Pinterest! https://pinterest.com/dragonflyreiki/     
    
    
    “The practice of forgiveness is our most important contribution to the healing of the world.” Marianne Williamson    
    
    
    Grateful for the opportunity for healing & wholeness that is always present through the work of Spirit.    
    
    
    Teaching Reiki today, bringing the sunshine of the soul in on this rainy morning! :-)    
    
    
    Happy Birthday and blessings to Hyakuten Inamoto, my teacher and the founder of Komyo Reiki Kai.    
    
    
    “I feel the healing hands of God touch my heart and kiss my soul.” - Harley King #inspiration #quotes    
    
    
    "Consider the holiness of your hands. They are how you do your work on this earth..." - Dianne Sylvan #Inspiration    
    
    
    Lovely story of how Reiki helped heal a child & gave his mother a practice for life http://www.dnaindia.com/analysis/1875926/report-reiki-changed-my-life-and-healed-my-child …    
    
    
    “Even when muddy your wings sparkle bright wonders that heal broken worlds.” - Aberjhani #healing #Inspiration    
    
    
    The wounded heart is the healer http://wp.me/p1j208-iu  #healing #wholeness    
    
    
    @AquaGoddessDC Definitely a worthy cause!    
    
    
    Relieved that no one was injured in today's school shooting here in Decatur, GA. #gratitude    
    
    
    Prayers for comfort and care for the children, teachers and parents affected by the school shooting.    
    
    
    “Healing is achieved through turning on the light of your soul and allowing it to shine.” - Janet Gallagher Nestor    
    
    
    How have you been called to serve others in love or with healing?    
    
    
    Two Americans (mom & daughter) who live & work in Myanmar are here to learn Reiki with me this weekend! What a blessing!    
    
    
    "Some things need to be let go before other things can be let in." - Marianne Williamson #wisdom #spirit    
    
    
        
    
    
    Learn the Japanese origins of Reiki healing with Hyakuten Inamoto, founder of Komyo Reiki Kai http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/reiki-classes/komyo-reiki-kai-immersion-with-hyakuten-inamoto/ … #atlanta    
    
    
    Are you living well today? pic.twitter.com/IklUCqqYMk    
    
    
    Always remember that you are Beloved.    
    
    
    Shana Tova and wishes for a sweet New Year!    
    
    
    "The reconciled heart says that everything that has happened to me had to happen to make me who I am - without exception." Brendan Manning    
    
    
    Ask and you shall receive. But remember to pay it forward in gratitude.    
    
    
    Heal yourself & others! Register now for upcoming Reiki classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Happy Friday! You are Beloved because a spark of Divine Being dwells within you.    
    
    
    Heal yourself & others! Register now for upcoming Reiki classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Got to meet one of my "Reiki babies" today! She is so beautiful & her parents gave her a Japanese name too!    
    
    
    Heal yourself & others! Register now for upcoming Reiki classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Heal yourself & others! Register now for upcoming Reiki classes in Atlanta GA & Birmingham AL! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/classes-events-calendar/ …    
    
    
    Line I overheard from the movie my daughter is watching: "Remember, positive energy always wins out over negative energy."    
    
    
    "Grace removes obstacles that we don’t even know are there. Grace is what arranges our lives so we are forced to look within." ~Krishna Das    
    
    
    Get 10% off a Reiki or Reflexology session now through Oct 5! http://bit.ly/15EYpFX  #atlanta #decaturga    
    
    
    A few spaces still available to learn the spiritual healing art of Komyo Reiki in Birmingham AL on 9/28! pic.twitter.com/wiMqae5UGD    
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
        
    
    
    An Introduction to Reiki: What It Is and How It Works: http://www.bostonmagazine.com/health/blog/2013/09/18/what-is-reiki/#.UjtJnIdJVxM.twitter …    
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
    Good insight for new practitioners/debunking #Reiki myths @Wellth: Is the #Reiki Practitioner Safe? http://shar.es/KmokK     
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
    Reiki has made its way into mainstream healthcare http://mycj.co/1e5SHxU  via @MyCentralJersey    
    
    
    Healing transformation sessions for an abundant life. Learn more! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/09/healing-transformation-for-an-abundant-life/ …    
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
    “But listen to me. For one moment
quit being sad. Hear blessings
dropping their blossoms around you.” ~ Rumi    
    
    
    Fall wellness sale Sept 16 - Oct 5! Book now & get 10% off your Reiki or Reflexology sessions http://bit.ly/15EYpFX     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Your Reiki hands give you a sacred opportunity to offer love & care to others without trying to fix them.    
    
    
    I consciously call for love & communion. Let there be peace in my life. I recognize each call for love. Let there be peace in my mind    
    
    
    "Give a good treatment & release it to God. Leave it to God how healing will come about." - Hawayo Takata #reiki    
    
    
    Vote for Dragonfly Reiki in http://Kudzu.com 's Best of 2013 contest for local businesses! http://www.kudzu.com/m/Dragonfly-Reiki-16931602 …    
    
    
    Vote for Dragonfly Reiki in http://Kudzu.com 's Best of 2013 contest for local businesses! http://www.kudzu.com/m/Dragonfly-Reiki-16931602 …    
    
    
    How are you living well today? Oct 2013 newsletter & more! - http://eepurl.com/GcPQP     
    
    
    Vote for Dragonfly Reiki in http://Kudzu.com 's Best of 2013 contest for local businesses! http://www.kudzu.com/m/Dragonfly-Reiki-16931602 …    
    
    
    Simply BE the Light to those around you.    
    
    
    Portsmouth Regional Hospital embraces relaxation & Reiki for breast cancer patients http://www.seacoastonline.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?aid=%2F20131013%2FLIFE%2F310130307#.UlwpUSc1ysM.twitter …    
    
    
    Fall wellness sale: save 10% now & 20% later! #reiki #atlanta - http://eepurl.com/GXKwX     
    
    
    Komyo Reiki Kai founder Hyakuten Inamoto to give talk on Reiki history Nov 1 in #atlanta http://bit.ly/1cZvONK     
    
    
    Fall wellness sale: save 10% now and 20% later on Reiki & Reflexology sessions! http://bit.ly/1gojp8r     
    
    
    Join us to hear Hyakuten Inamoto give talk on Reiki healing - http://eepurl.com/G_La1     
    
    
    Fall wellness sale: save 10% now and 20% later on Reiki & Reflexology sessions! http://bit.ly/1gojp8r     
    
    
    Komyo Reiki Kai founder Hyakuten Inamoto to give talk on Reiki history Nov 1 in #atlanta http://bit.ly/1cZvONK     
    
    
    Fall wellness sale: save 10% now and 20% later on Reiki & Reflexology sessions! http://bit.ly/1gojp8r     
    
    
    @JuliePetulengro It sounds lovely! :-) Thank you for sharing!    
    
    
        
    
    
    A registered dental assistant offers Reiki & Reflexology to patients during procedures. #healing http://www.dentistryiq.com/articles/2013/10/reflexology-in-the-dental-chair.html …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    "How long have you been practicing? Once more again, practice. This is my hope."
~ Kanjuro Shibata Sensei #spirituality    
    
    
    Be love! Sign up now for my upcoming workshop "Embracing Your Belovedness" on Nov 23 http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/09/embracing-your-belovedness-workshop-nov-23/ …    
    
    
    My Reiki teacher Hyakuten Inamoto arrives in Atlanta today! Excited to see him again!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wow. Just had lunch with Hyakuten Inamoto and Rick Bockner, who was one of 22 Reiki Masters initiated by Mrs. Takata.    
    
    
    Enjoyed a lovely, transformational weekend with Hyakuten Inamoto, founder of Komyo Reiki Kai! pic.twitter.com/PrlfpXYCLH    
    
    
    Lineage starts w/commitment RT @Wellth: Are you up for asking yourself a few tough #Reiki lineage questions? http://shar.es/IDC9j     
    
    
    Funny! RT @phylameana: My husband thinks he is being clever whenever he drinks my Chai Tea while I'm practicing my Tai Chi.    
    
    
    Beautiful photo of Hyakuten Inamoto in front of Reiki altar during Komyo Reiki Kai weekend in Atlanta pic.twitter.com/VLVys8YbTw    
    
    
    "The most eloquent prayer is the prayer through hands that heal and bless." ~ Billy Graham    
    
    
        
    
    
    Vote Dragonfly Reiki for Atlanta "Best of" Business!: http://eepurl.com/IqwRH  #healing    
    
    
    Thank you @gomommy for the awesome review! Family healing time for mama & child! http://www.kudzu.com/r/30072472     
    
    
    Praying for the people of the Philippines to remain safe from Super Typhoon #Haiyan.    
    
    
    Life is my dojo.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Vote for @DragonflyReiki for Atlanta's "Best of" Business in Alt Medicine on http://Kudzu.com !: http://eepurl.com/IqwRH     
    
    
    Sign up for "Embracing Your Belovedness" Workshop Nov 23 #atlanta #healing - http://eepurl.com/IDko9     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks to @Wellth for great interview with #Reiki Master Hyakuten Inamoto about Usui Reiki Ryoho Gakkai http://reikiinmedicine.org/reiki-basics/mikao-usui-gakkai/ …    
    
    
    In truth everything & everyone
Is a shadow of the Beloved,
& our seeking is His seeking
& our words are His words... - Rumi    
    
    
    Sign up for this Saturday's workshop "Embracing Your Belovedness." Reconnect with your Beloved Self! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/2013/09/embracing-your-belovedness-workshop-nov-23/ …    
    
    
    I chatted this week about Reiki on Energy Healing As A Spiritual Growth Path by Awakening to Miracles http://bit.ly/1axyH65     
    
    
    I love it when a client's inner child makes an appearance - it is usually accompanied by an empowering message.    
    
    
    Waving hi to @KaizenReiki!    
    
    
    @KaizenReiki Definitely - just let me know! Hope all is well.    
    
    
    “There is in each of us an inner voice of Love that says: ‘You are the Beloved of God!’” – Henri J.M. Nouwen    
    
    
    I am #thankful for all of you!    
    
    
    Receive (and give) a gift that will keep on giving...learn Reiki healing!    
    
    
    10 days left to vote @DragonflyReiki as http://Kudzu.com 's "Best of 2013" business! http://www.kudzu.com/m/Dragonfly-Reiki-16931602 … #atlanta    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm thankful for all of you! #Thanksgiving    
    
    
    Healing techniques - including #Reiki & #Reflexology - that can improve your modern life  http://huff.to/1eJnbFu  via @HealthyLiving    
    
    
    Save now on specially-priced Reiki, Reflexology/combo sessions & gift certificate packages! http://bit.ly/1c77vYO  #CyberMonday    
    
    
        
    
    
    Watch how @ChevroletFC & @OneWorldFutbol are educating kids in Ol Pejeta, Kenya through the #powerofplay. http://spr.ly/opk     
    
    
        
    
    
    @rachelfeit Yes, it does! Thank you! :-)    
    
    
    @ReikiAwakening Thank you! :-)    
    
    
    Christina Aguilera credits Reiki with helping her lose weight & feel better http://www.starpulse.com/news/Lucy_Hobson/2013/12/13/christina_aguilera_lost_weight_by_reik …    
    
    
    Dragonfly Reiki Awarded Best of 2013 on Kudzu! http://www.dragonflyreiki.net/?p=2710  #healing #Atlanta    
    
    
    Have you seen @Wellth's new site? A lovely place to share her spiritual guidance & healing work! http://pamelamiles.com/     
    
    
    Save now! Give a gift of healing this holiday! - http://eepurl.com/KQEqX     
    
    
    “Treat every moment as your last. It is not preparation for something else.” - Shunryu Suzuki #wisdom #zen    
    
    
    One of my Reiki students is in labor, awaiting her Christmas baby. Please send prayers & good energy for a peaceful arrival!    
    
    
    Happy Holidays to all! Wishing you the love, joy, hope and peace of the season.    
    
    
        
    
    
    A respected healer & teacher RT @GinnyMackles: #Reiki offered in Prior Lake, MN http://www.myin8chiro.com/services.html     
    
    
    Reiki fundraiser Jan 18 to support @AndrewJTriumph's Team in Training to race across America! http://bit.ly/KcRD0j     
    
    
    Atlanta! Feel well, live well, BE well now! Sign up for your "Resolution for Transformation" session: http://bit.ly/1fWJI1A     
    
    
        
    
    
    “It is in the stillness that we save and transform the world." - Eckhart Tolle    
    
    
    Reiki fundraiser Jan 18 to support @AndrewJTriumph's Team in Training to race across America! http://bit.ly/KcRD0j     
    
    
    Want to get happier and healthier in 2014? Here's how! - http://eepurl.com/LJEkn     
    
    
        
    
    
    Client to me today: "My Reiki sessions are always relaxing, but I'm realizing that Reiki is bringing me back to myself."    
    
    
    