I can not live without coffee.    
    
    
    5 Typography Devices to Help Increase Readership by David Ogilvy http://pinterest.com/pin/268316090271631412/ …    
    
    
    @thienkim scoundrels!    
    
    
    @thienkim I need to get a back up for such an emergency. I'm doing good. Just starting off my Monday trying to organize my week :)    
    
    
    Photo: Step 7: Plan ahead for a healthy tomorrow One big barrier to treating oneself well is lack of... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfVSOOD     
    
    
    Rep Orcutt Responds to his INSANE claim that biking is bad for the environment http://sco.lt/7s2vc9  #seabikes    
    
    
    16 Ways Businesses Are Using Twitter Vine  http://sco.lt/7tBK8P     
    
    
    @LoudSeahawksFan yeah, I'm wondering what a realistic solution might be.    
    
    
    @CEM_Social you're welcome! I have here and there. It's a fun tool and I love seeing what brands and businesses have been doing with it.    
    
    
    @CEM_Social I am waiting patiently for it to come out on Droid :)    
    
    
    Carrot Cake Oatmeal - yum! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfVjtP7     
    
    
    @adamholdenbache I noticed 1 of your @socialfresh posts was taken down (22 Social Media Alerts Your Biz Should use) is it posted elsewhere?    
    
    
    Amanda Palmer is a goddess. Watch her TED Talk on: The art of asking http://bit.ly/13C9pSb  (I nearly cried)    
    
    
    Happy Monday everyone! I'm listening to Lily Allen today. It's a Lily Allen day for sure. Yup. #musicmonday    
    
    
    @LoudSeahawksFan I actually fell asleep last night trying to puzzle it out. lol    
    
    
    Photoset: How to properly treat deadlines…… http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxfW60h4     
    
    
    @AdamHoldenBache oh, duh, I didn't check to see if the entire site was working. Sorry if I caused a mini-panic :)    
    
    
    Photo: My neighbor’s homemade ranch dressing and @metmarket croutons made salad the easy choice today.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfWB75J     
    
    
    @MetMarket thank you! Your croutons are like crack.    
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ actually, those are black beans. #nom    
    
    
    @socialfresh @AdamHoldenBache thanks for letting me know. I wanted to link to that article in a blog post. Will wait patiently :)    
    
    
    18 Social & Local Marketing Ideas Based on the Consumer Journey  http://bit.ly/14l7v3U     
    
    
    Photo: Pre-Body Pump. Taking it easy. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfYE80y     
    
    
    Photo: Getting excited for Seattle Bike Expo. Yoga for cyclists sounds awesome. #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfYF2SY     
    
    
    Loving this show. I'm such a geek. http://is.gd/1Z1H7e  #GetGlue @HistoryVikings    
    
    
    Photo: I miss yoga!! I need to get it back into my exercise routine. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfaPe-P     
    
    
    lol. This is awesome. RT @buzzfeed: This mashup of Nine Inch Nails and "Call Me Maybe" is perfect http://bzfd.it/XKNqmG     
    
    
    @donpower I can help!    
    
    
    @seattleweekly that's more than a slip up! That's stupidity at it's best    
    
    
    @captainchunk I know what you mean. I kept wishing I could rewind time just a bit.    
    
    
    @charlesredell it's a crowded place, maybe they felt bike racks would cause more congestion?    
    
    
    @cascadebicycle I look forward to it. I was just telling @yogaforbikers how much I miss yoga. I need to work it back into my schedule.    
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ it's funny you say that. I planned on adding it and forgot last minute.    
    
    
    How I often feel on my bike ;) -- It's like learning my city all over again #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfbgLZm     
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ @EarlsBellevue I will have to check them out!    
    
    
    @CharlesRedell it's been awhile since I was last at Pike Place. I don't remember car parking either? lol    
    
    
    @CharlesRedell I didn't even realize there was parking there. I thought the cobbled street was just for thru traffic/vendors.    
    
    
    Facebook Is Making The Most Critical Update To News Feed In 7 Years Tomorrow! http://read.bi/14tDgId     
    
    
    @downwarddog agreed. It will be interesting to see how this effects Pages. Prepare for the complaints!    
    
    
    Congrats!! RT @iamqdot: Announcement: BET selected me to perform at their #MusicMatters showcase in NYC May 14th! =) mmmhhhmmm.    
    
    
    Heading out for a 20 mile bike ride. Anyone in #Auburn wanna join me? ;)    
    
    
    Photo: Things that suck: Freezing rain, helmet hair, knee pain. Things that rock: husbands, t-bone steaks,... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfhjwiC     
    
    
    Finished my ride for the day. Freezing rain and wind suuuuck!  #strava #seabikes http://app.strava.com/activities/43446725 …    
    
    
    Photoset: sassypantzz: Wall Piece With 200 Letters, Mikko Kuorinki  Love this. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxfjjgzZ     
    
    
    Going to be watching Facebook Livestream Announcement in a few mins... --> http://bit.ly/14yqh82     
    
    
    Waiting to watch this announcement >> Facebook’s Redesign Hopes to Keep Users Engaged - http://nyti.ms/14ytdBt     
    
    
    @iamqdot have you seen this? http://youtu.be/IGH2HEgWppc     
    
    
    So far nothing surprising >> UI consistent with mobile, bigger pictures, richer links, emphasis on visuals etc. #FacebookUpdate    
    
    
    See The New Facebook News Feed http://bit.ly/14yF02M     
    
    
    Google Plus update info complete with photoshop template (nice) http://bit.ly/14yqrMy     
    
    
    How NOT to Have Your Social Media Accounts Hacked http://linkd.in/13J8RKc     
    
    
    @bbangie @howiecohen @evonnebenedict @Martha_Kang you're welcome! I try to stalk as many awesome ppl as possible!    
    
    
    5 Tips to Enhance Your Facebook Graph Search Ranking http://bit.ly/14yA0Lz     
    
    
    Know. Your. Audience >>> Sephora: Our Pinterest followers spend 15X more than our Facebook fans  http://bit.ly/13JyOt1     
    
    
    "Most of all, people matter. Individual human beings with names and wants and interests." http://bit.ly/13L913Q     
    
    
    Photo: Feeling like a bit of a badass! 26.7 miles on a gorgeous day. I may even have a bit of a sunburn.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfv2mLD     
    
    
    Photo: This is actually a thing. #bikeexpo (at Pier 91 - Smith Cove Terminal) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfyZzIo     
    
    
    Photo: For big kids. Want. #bikeexpo http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfyqNU2     
    
    
    Well. Have you? #funnysign http://instagr.am/p/Wsn98yrKVa/     
    
    
    Photo: Well. Have you? #funnysign http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_QbeR     
    
    
    Photo: I love the Burke-Gilman trail! Fun houses and beautiful views. Also, day #2 on a bike is much harder... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_SBig     
    
    
    Photo: My baby. Hoping she’ll take me from Seattle to Portland and back. She still needs a name! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_nl7-     
    
    
    10 Minutes of Prep: 10 Amazing Meals http://pinterest.com/pin/268316090271674550/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Step 8: Eat more fruits and vegetables It’s no surprise that there are many benefits to eating fruits... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yg1Dwx-     
    
    
    @gigharborlive I'd love to help if you're still looking for a community manager!    
    
    
    @outdoorsnwmag hope I win it! My hubs needs one :)    
    
    
    @cyu888 that explains so much!    
    
    
    @yogadork *sigh* I just HAD to click that. Didn't I? lol    
    
    
    This is cool! RT @bikewa: They're all the buzz at #SXSW: Bikes made out of junked cars http://ow.ly/iL7Pr . 3K preordered #bicycledbikes    
    
    
    @bikewa absolutely the best. Very cool.    
    
    
    Pinterest quietly pops out a fantastic new layout http://bit.ly/ZB8mhC     
    
    
    Photo: Inhaled! #fitfoodie http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yg3WAx1     
    
    
    I'm watching Vikings (150 others checked-in) http://is.gd/1Z1H7e  #GetGlue @HistoryVikings    
    
    
    I rated Vikings 10/10 http://www.imdb.com/title/tt2306299  #IMDb    
    
    
    7 Ways To Value Yourself Beyond Social Media http://onforb.es/Y8qITD     
    
    
    Facebook tests new ways to promote page content organically in users’ feeds http://bit.ly/Y8qSuh     
    
    
    "Your magical, vulnerable work changes everything" -- Seth Godin http://bit.ly/ZFGgSo     
    
    
    Foods For Energy: How To Eat To Stay Awake And Alert http://huff.to/Y8s158     
    
    
    Nice! >> Pinterest Introduces Analytics Platform http://on.mash.to/Y8KYEw     
    
    
    Terrible news! Official Google Reader Blog: Powering Down Google Reader  http://bit.ly/13X8vji     
    
    
    Got chills watching @JonAntoine 's audition on Britian's Got Talent http://ow.ly/iVT1C     
    
    
    @iamqdot nice!    
    
    
    @anikamarketer would love that role!    
    
    
    @coolcaiti start networking!    
    
    
    Happy Pi Day everyone!    
    
    
    @jonantoine <3    
    
    
    Reading about @CycleOregon 's week long trips and dreaming about next year. Have to tackle #BikeSTP first. ;)    
    
    
    @JoeM_PM_UK @JonAntoine I've seen the video once before, but every time I watch it = chills!    
    
    
    @joem_pm_uk @JonAntoine that shouldn't discourage him. His appeal is to more niche, sophisticated listening audiences not the general public    
    
    
    @nikhewitt did you hear about Google Reader? :(    
    
    
    @moxie_hart who needs a reason? ;)    
    
    
    Love this #CreativityThursday Wisdom RT @anandaleeke: "Painting is just another way of keeping a diary."  ~Pablo Picasso    
    
    
    Love this! Cycling can help small towns RT @pathlesspedaled: How bikes can bridge the urban/rural divide. http://youtu.be/HCSbpMsNgmw     
    
    
    Yup RT @benjaminellis: Stop trying to be famous. Start trying to be useful.    
    
    
    Good luck with future endeavors, Chuck! RT @cascadebicycle: Chuck Ayers announces resignation from CBC: http://wp.me/pMYUc-5fb  #SEAbikes    
    
    
    Gonna listen! RT @ellyblue: Listen to @yogaforbikers talk about yoga, bikes, & her nxt book on the @yogachat podcast: http://ayogist.podomatic.com/entry/2013-03-13T22_01_32-07_00 …    
    
    
    "It's not about the size of the community. It's how engaged that community is and how that aligns with the brand's strategy" Blake Chandlee    
    
    
    @_chrisrojas_ wow, that's some pretty impressive geek speak    
    
    
    Still upset about this >> Google Reader Is Dead, Long Live These Alternatives, Which May Include Digg  http://bit.ly/ZQwL2R     
    
    
    @anikamarketer I applied for an earlier one and it wont let me reapply. I fear I am stuck at the bottom of a digital pile.    
    
    
    Wonderful advice >> Rethinking Unpopular: Erika Napoletano at TEDxBoulder 2012 http://bit.ly/YelHck     
    
    
    Wow, @Lacma is giving away nearly 20,000 high-res images of art for free! http://bit.ly/ZVbPro     
    
    
    I'm at Bamboo Vietnamese (Seattle, WA) http://4sq.com/15bRRIx     
    
    
    Photo: Can you name that park? Short ride today with great friends. Now for some pho. #epic #cycle #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygQmBVP     
    
    
    Photo: 27 miles, over 1000 vertical feet, avg. speed 10.5. Great weather! #epic #cycling http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygVQ3h7     
    
    
    Happy Saint Patty's Day! (@ Harmon Brewery & Restaurant - @harmonbrewingco) http://4sq.com/1428IRN     
    
    
    Happy St. Pattys! Can you spot the baby in the pipe band? http://vine.co/v/bpKHEpam3Ql     
    
    
    Name that tune? #bagpipes http://vine.co/v/bpA7DHh6r6z     
    
    
    My cheesy husband http://vine.co/v/bpAmKItdltl     
    
    
    Irish #pipeband! Happy Saint Patricks Day http://vine.co/v/bpAA5VxBZuV     
    
    
    Photo: Rant: Don’t make assumptions about my health This weekend I was the victim of an assumer. I hate... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygZ4M-b     
    
    
    Loving this list! >> 21 Quick Actions You Can Do Today to Set Your Blog Up for Massive Success http://bit.ly/Ymulp9  via @thinktraffic    
    
    
    @anandaleeke yeah! It's been more than a minute ;) Loving #CreativityThursday :)    
    
    
    @bbangie I've got a Specialized Dolce & I love it! On my last ride I saw many ladies on the same bike.   http://ow.ly/jaZ0x     
    
    
    @bbangie I'm not completely sure if my bike is women specific but I tried a few and I liked that I was still a little upright in it.    
    
    
    @bbangie thanks! I'm trying my hardest and that lady was a huge self-esteem suck. If I end up in her group again I'll request a switch    
    
    
    @feralization thank you! I'm never sure if it's my insecurity or if people are being genuinely rude. I've decided this lady was just rude.    
    
    
    @bbangie  I was on a hybrid before and I feel it's a good transition into road bikes. I also tried this guy: http://ow.ly/jb2uS     
    
    
    @feralization and that's why I decided to share. It's amazing what she did to my self esteem and determination. It was like I was punched    
    
    
    @bbangie so cool! New bike day is the best of all the days -- I'm looking forward to the pics on Instagram :)    
    
    
    Love! RT @lifehacker: Gmail for Android just updated with shortcuts in the notification drawer, better search: http://lifehac.kr/X1nQ04U     
    
    
    @feralization I love it! :)    
    
    
    @yogaforbikers discovered this weekend my friend practices at your studio! I'm very jealous!    
    
    
    @yogaforbikers we've decided the next Yoga for Cyclists workshop we can attend together at @TheGrinningYogi we will!    
    
    
    @moxie_hart CONGRATS :)    
    
    
    @k1k1chan wait, a college campus without wifi?    
    
    
    @heidimiller I don't know why but this annoys me just a little.    
    
    
    Always a good idea MT @nwjerseyliz: I recommend  logging in, going to Settings>Apps and see who you've given permission to send out Tweets.    
    
    
    @captainchunk congrats! Sounds like a fun role :)    
    
    
    @jeremyjrussell very cool. I love yoga!    
    
    
    Love this! Wonder if @haleykilgour has seen it? RT @gaiam: Yoga Gets Funky: Playlists for your #yoga practice http://yogagetsfunky.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    @nwjerseyliz Ugh. I hate that. I also noticed somehow my hubs is tweeting on my account from games. Whoops. Time to block.    
    
    
    @heidimiller all of the above!    
    
    
    @haleykilgour exactly!!    
    
    
    @yogaforbikers I will let him know and keep an eye out!    
    
    
    @nwjerseyliz Hmmmm, I will check it out. I use both of those apps.    
    
    
    Twitter is changing Ads (again!) http://bit.ly/Yn0aOw     
    
    
    Photo: Rant: Don’t make assumptions about my health This weekend I was the victim of an assumer. I hate... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygaWXUA     
    
    
    @bbangie Yay! I know what you mean. I don't have the triple and wish I had it ;)    
    
    
    @nikhewitt @Mannaz @Karen_Woodward I see it here: http://ow.ly/jdtbg     
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 congrats! That is hard work, but Ben loves doing it!    
    
    
    Six Steps to Becoming a Good (Social) Listener  http://bit.ly/YoPWxd  via @bryankramer    
    
    
    @nikhewitt @Mannaz @Karen_Woodward I see the old rules    
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 yes, he went to school for it while in HS!    
    
    
    @patmrhoads @MollieinSeattle @Starbucks yeaaaah, I'm an addict!    
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 2 years I think?    
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 yeah, every program is different! I hope you have fun with yours :)    
    
    
    Just got a message from a family member who wanted me to know they didn't approve of a "like" I made on Facebook. *facepalm*    
    
    
    5 Reasons to Use Facebook's Power Editor http://bit.ly/VG1IFP  via @jasonkeath    
    
    
    @bryankramer of course :)    
    
    
    @revfry exactly!    
    
    
    Photo: First to respond gets to pick my workout. Plyo or Kenpo? #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygfynwT     
    
    
    My most popular post this year. People love a good rant: Don’t make assumptions about my health http://bit.ly/10efalv  #fitblog    
    
    
    Photo: Green River Trail and a surprising amount of sun today. The over-the-top wind was not a surprise. At... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygkwp0T     
    
    
    Photo: Riding on the Green River Trail today along Riverbend Golf Course made me think of my Dad. The cherry... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygkyck8     
    
    
    Love this movie! http://is.gd/3ZxV0y  #GetGlue @TheHobbitMovie    
    
    
    Facebook Now Allows Calls to Action on Facebook Page Cover Images  http://bit.ly/ZfZrOw  Mr. @NikHewitt spotted this a few days ago    
    
    
    @genn_m love it! It's been awhile since I listened to that album    
    
    
    @bbangie congrats on your new bike! You should join us this weekend *hint hint* >> http://ow.ly/jir1I  #seabikes    
    
    
    @ohhsuzannah I didn't. I thought about it, but family is family - might as well play nice!    
    
    
    @mannaz @Karen_Woodward @nikhewitt just now seeing the changes too!    
    
    
    @akasqueezer you're right it does sound like Mom's side, but it was actually someone from my Dad's side. Basically, I get it frm everyone ;)    
    
    
    @shoehornent thanks for the RT. Long time, no talk!    
    
    
    Met a "G+ Expert" who doesn't have a G+ page for their business. Uhm, are you for real???    
    
    
    @imadid virtual workers?    
    
    
    @moniguzman I love those!    
    
    
    @bikewa sadly, even with bike parking I'm still afraid to leave my baby unattended    
    
    
    @moxie_hart uh oh *hugs*    
    
    
    Ugh, I'm feeling sick today. Kinda wanna get some Starbucks to see if it peps me up.    
    
    
    @noscrunchie Apparently!    
    
    
    @akasqueezer lol, you're right, it really does!! Hee hee    
    
    
    @tcgmc I'm trying to be good and limit the 'Bux to only twice a week. lol. I'm an addict!    
    
    
    @akasqueezer @Genn_M I'm a fan of that one too. Those were the good ole days    
    
    
    @ohhsuzannah that's a really good idea    
    
    
    #FYI --> Everyone needs a Shelli http://ow.ly/jiGHS     
    
    
    This >> Sometimes, more is not what you want http://bit.ly/ZhxSnY     
    
    
    @loudseahawksfan congrats! You are the nerdiest of the nerdies! ;)    
    
    
    @moxie_hart I have one. It's not the latest version, but I like it.    
    
    
    @imadid virtual workers are real! ;)    
    
    
    @BikeWA I wouldn't leave my bike OR a baby unattended  -- my bike just happens to be my baby. lol ;)    
    
    
    So cool! >> "[The]“Cycle House” features a bike room that would make any avid cyclist green with envy." http://bit.ly/Y4dJ9c     
    
    
    @bbangie nice! Will potentially see you the. I invited a few friends but none could make it :/    
    
    
    Photo: Today’s ride was tough. A chest cold left me GASPING for air, nauseous, and sloooow. Finished though!... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ygyVUEP     
    
    
    Food for thought >> Pick One http://bit.ly/Yz9qiK     
    
    
    Minimizing My Life   http://bit.ly/XygQT6  << Inspiring. I have a closet or two I should tackle.    
    
    
    Being sick is no fun. I really need to practice some hills on my bike!    
    
    
    @rainnwilson autocorrect is getting sassy!    
    
    
    @hipsforhire luuckyyyy!!    
    
    
    @wanelo grumpy cat is your hiring manager? Sounds like a tough sell ;)    
    
    
    @marikamalaea Yes! I can't wait either -- didn't realize there was new Doctor Who coming too! #bonus    
    
    
    @tacomafoodie it's pretty all around the #PNW today. Loving it!    
    
    
    @projectline my favorite platform. I'm a bit of a Tumblr addict.    
    
    
    @jessekelber do you have a link?    
    
    
    "Everyone who is selling you dissatisfaction is working for their own selfish ends." http://bit.ly/ZnEG3l     
    
    
    Best week ever! #watchathon RT @marikamalaea: @shellimartineau Yes! Dr Who on Saturday, GoT Sunday. Mad Men the week after.    
    
    
    Photo: Step 9: Help Others When your airplane is going downand the oxygen masks are deployed the... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yh5tyyW     
    
    
    @moxie_hart that is creepy!    
    
    
    @coolcaiti ha ha, of course!    
    
    
    20 Easy to Use, Free, and Reliable Tools for Social Media Management http://wp.me/p2clDK-B6     
    
    
    Homeless Man, Ganjdalf the Green, has the best Facebook Page in all of Facebook http://funni.ly/YaPqXb     
    
    
    So cool >> "I'm scared of heights, so I went hang gliding the other day. I'm still scared of heights; but I'm not afraid of fear." - @kavla    
    
    
    @zelkovavc I'd love to help if I can!    
    
    
    @nikhewitt I remember that was one of the big selling points initially    
    
    
    Some people, some of the time, are going to do amazing &generous work...just give them tools and get out of their way http://bit.ly/YaPJBp     
    
    
    @jessekelber thank you!    
    
    
    Exciting! >> Facebook Lookalike Audiences: Target Users Similar to Your Customers http://bit.ly/Yd03c7  via @JonLoomer    
    
    
    Got mine today! >> Facebook finally started adding 'reply' buttons to comments - http://nbcnews.to/11IjLf5     
    
    
    Questioning All Advice, Rules And Best Practices For Social Media Success  http://bit.ly/11Is9v5     
    
    
    @projectline love it!    
    
    
    Social Media Meta Tags: How to Use Open Graph and Cards http://bit.ly/11I1Xkb     
    
    
    Gay marriage: Facebook turns red - http://trib.in/YdgDbU     
    
    
    I've been watching "I Have Your Heart" by @mollycrabapple & @KimBoekbinder on repeat all morning.  http://ow.ly/jtBHZ     
    
    
    @jeremyjrussell beautiful pic!    
    
    
    Neat! RT @projectline: Love Prudential's innovative use of crowdsourced real-time data visualization. Very clever! http://ow.ly/jtA4Z     
    
    
    Having trouble finding motivation for today's ride. Anyone out there have some wisdom, advice, or encouragement for me? #seabikes #bikeSTP    
    
    
    My birthday is coming up. #justsayin RT @kentsbike: RT @BookRiot The Best Coffee Mugs for Book Lovers: http://ow.ly/jta4g     
    
    
    @thienkim I haven't done a thiiiing!    
    
    
    @thienkim time for some self care (when you get time)! Hee. Hee    
    
    
    @revfry becaue we hate buying new pants. ;)    
    
    
    @RevFry I know. It was a terrible joke. :) I think Seth Godin explains it best: We let the Lizard Brain take over    
    
    
    @RevFry yep. Working for Start-ups has ruined me in that respect. It's extremely difficult for me to follow a set job description.    
    
    
    @nikhewitt ah! Nice :)    
    
    
    Interesting! Going to look at some of these >> Facebook Insights: Monitor These 8 Ratios  http://bit.ly/YfWceh     
    
    
    This. RT @heidimiller: Today is one of those days for which I can (a) answer email or (b) get your projects done for you. Can't do both.    
    
    
    @heidimiller oh I completely understand. I've been there. Lmk if you need a virtual hand.    
    
    
    Photo: Semi-dangerous selfy taken during today’s #bikeride. Totally worth it. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhIQX_3     
    
    
    Catching up! http://bit.ly/M09mrm  #GetGlue @girlsHBO    
    
    
    @rchelrene ha! Love it.    
    
    
    @moniqueelwell loved that one!    
    
    
    @michaelfulwiler shhhh he's got a good thing going for himself. Don't ruin it!    
    
    
    @seabikeblog what's a bicycle Sunday?    
    
    
    @sarahgilbert psychic!    
    
    
    Sign! RT @kentsbike: Help me and @railstotrails urge WA state senators to invest in trails across the state. Act now: http://bit.ly/YEh4LW     
    
    
    @bikehugger so coooool. I tried to sign up for one. Didn't work :(    
    
    
    @bikehugger man! Lucky :)    
    
    
    @sarahgilbert worth a try! ;)    
    
    
    @bikehugger I wrote to them and told them I was doing my first ever STP and wanted to record my training and the big day, etc.    
    
    
    Yoga for Cyclists is now available on DVD. Saw Ryan Leech at #BikeExpo. Great class!  http://bit.ly/11SydkP  #seabikes    
    
    
    @yogaforbikers @seabikeblog Ohhh awesome! I did a chunk of that ride last Sunday with @cascadebicycle    
    
    
    @bikehugger I may just!    
    
    
    @heidimiller ouch. Maybe time for some self spoiling? Yoga? A super long bike ride? Something to clear the head?    
    
    
    @rchelrene as am I, my friend.    
    
    
    "Effective marketing amplifies awareness of a problem or an opportunity" http://bit.ly/YhU3yG     
    
    
    Touching images from one woman's fight with cancer >>The Battle We Didn't Choose http://bit.ly/11SXzPx     
    
    
    Reading: 8 Principles That Can Make You an Analytics Rock Star  http://bit.ly/11TDvfN     
    
    
    Photo: At your size and your age, you can amaze yourself. I promise.I witnessed the coolest thing today. A... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhNGm-x     
    
    
    4 Facebook Updates you Must Know About http://bit.ly/11TDTek     
    
    
    Photo: the miles wont peddle themselves. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhNssP_     
    
    
    all i want is forward progress http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhPTZm5     
    
    
    Photo: Clearly too much free time. ;) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhPka96     
    
    
    TRON helmet! RT @fastcompany: This new bike helmet design incorporates 10 wide-angle LEDs: http://trib.al/gyVFR9B  pic.twitter.com/E2bkfkTuZ1    
    
    
    @iamqdot you go there a lot. If you're ever missing that's the first place I'm sending people. ;)    
    
    
    @joannalord @SEOmoz @renoodles this looks like a fun role! I love teaching/coaching.    
    
    
    @jeremyjrussell we're going to have some beautiful weather!    
    
    
    This! RT @anikamarketer: Workaholism and the myth of hard work: http://ow.ly/jyK9r     
    
    
    @jshuey when they cost you more time, money, grief and stress than they return in worthwhile projects, compensation, and chances to grow    
    
    
    Neat! -- IKEA Parts for Stool Hacked to Build #Bicycle http://on.mash.to/164GnHc     
    
    
    Is This The Mythical Facebook Phone being unveiled on Monday? Do you care?? http://onforb.es/164GXEZ     
    
    
    Happy Friday! It's time for social media pet peeves. What's yours? I hate "letters to no one" as status updates. "Dear large corporation.."    
    
    
    @hanniespice yes! So annoying or the same but asking for free advertising on your blog    
    
    
    SQUEEEEE RT @projectglass: @ShelliMartineau You’re invited to join our #glassexplorers program. Woohoo!    
    
    
    @projectglass of course I'm already following. :) Thanks!    
    
    
    @RevFry @projectglass I know, right? My nerd future is so bright I needed nerd shades :)    
    
    
    Photo: Love this! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhQwK29     
    
    
    Amazon plans to buy @goodreads. I love this community! Hopefully the added attn only serves to improve it http://reut.rs/YkxnxL     
    
    
    Photo: My thoughts exactly http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhU9H9I     
    
    
    Doing Foothills Trail today. Should be beautiful!    
    
    
    Photo: Pretty much. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhUt2yj     
    
    
    Photo: Gorgeous 30 mile ride on the Foothills Trail today. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhVmPHw     
    
    
    Photo: This poor dog was no doubt wondering what he did to deserve this torture. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhVmtNx     
    
    
    Photo: Mt. Rainier even decided to come out today. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhVnC-p     
    
    
    Photo: Snacks on the trail. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhVnhBH     
    
    
    Photo: Today’s ride! Loved this trail so much I think I’ll do it tomorrow. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhW1GSB     
    
    
    @Kaela907 yeah, Today was insanely gorgeous here in Seattle    
    
    
    So excited for the new season! http://bit.ly/14x0HVf  #GetGlue @bbcdoctorwho    
    
    
    Wow, this looks interesting http://bit.ly/X5lwD3  #GetGlue @orphanblack    
    
    
    Photo: 30 miles today! Now for Easter dinner with family. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhaec5s     
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (20897 others checked-in) http://bit.ly/heeWXp  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    Reading: Facebook’s Android Homescreen Could Expose Apple’s Inflexibility  http://tcrn.ch/YqRQRL     
    
    
    @orbike thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @lanewood remote workers ok?    
    
    
    Training update: Last week I put in a little over than 86 miles on bicycle. Wowza.    
    
    
    Seems appropriate to share this today >> "We can't deny the difficult parts, we have no choice but to embrace them." http://bit.ly/16fkKE6     
    
    
    52 Steps to Health - Step 10: Embrace the difficult - 52 steps to help - Step 10: Embrace the Difficult “I... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhfuXHX     
    
    
    My new favorite: 15 Facts Brands Should Know About Reddit  http://bit.ly/YqWPSg     
    
    
    @wiiwendy to work for free? or free to work? ;)    
    
    
    Congrats @NapaWineLady >> Wine Sisterhood Opens Digital Marketplace Dedicated To Women Who Love Wine http://bit.ly/16krhNR  via @newsle    
    
    
    I'm watching On the Road http://is.gd/d052Cf  #GetGlue @OTR_official    
    
    
    May is Bike To Work Month. Kinda wish I had a commute. lol. http://bit.ly/XNtOkr     
    
    
    Reading: Google Upgrades Its Google Places Dashboard With Google+ Local Integration http://selnd.com/16zra38  via @PPCStrategies (Thanks Barb!)    
    
    
    Photo: New diet idea: Pizza and wine. All the time. ;) (at Tutta Bella Neapolitan Pizzeria - Columbia City) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhxNsS9     
    
    
    Photo: Awww. Did I miss #throwbackthursday? Oh well, here’s where all my fabulousness started. ;) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yhzHYoa     
    
    
    @iamqdot  On my bike ride two weeks ago the park next to his house was CROWDED. I can only imagine what I'll see this weekend.    
    
    
    RIP MT @iamqdot: 19 years ago Kurt Cobain killed himself...do you remember where you were when you heard the news? http://fb.me/CnHmJ87A     
    
    
    Finally checking out Facebook Home http://on.fb.me/16BRgm3     
    
    
    @IAMQDOT and he was so, so sad. :-(    
    
    
    Hilarious >> This Facebook Phone Parody Actually Makes Some Good Points  http://tcrn.ch/16BTv8Y     
    
    
    Photo: Nice ride today. I could’ve done without the freezing rain and gigantic rain puddles though. #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yi3tEEd     
    
    
    Photo: Freezing, wet, and windy time on the Foothills Trail today. We could only put in about 15 miles... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yi8-HvR     
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (592 others checked-in) http://is.gd/H0B4RI  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (20984 others checked-in) http://is.gd/H0B4RI  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    @beinpulse congrats!    
    
    
    @iethanology what's the app called?    
    
    
    Happy Monday Morning Twitterverse! What do you have for me?    
    
    
    @anikamarketer excellent ideas, all    
    
    
    So well said: "Let’s choose community. Let’s stop comparing. Let’s start connecting." http://bit.ly/YaNCyy  via @Relevant    
    
    
    @coolcaiti that is terrifying on so many levels.    
    
    
    @coolcaiti I take that back?    
    
    
    "We always compare the worst of what we know about ourselves to the best assumptions we make about others." http://bit.ly/YaPVl9     
    
    
    Reading now about #ReduceMonth http://bit.ly/YaSBza     
    
    
    Just realized I can now view my Instagram feed from my computer. There goes my free time.    
    
    
    Video: Gizmo and I have a lot in common. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxiKgeQQ     
    
    
    Services like this one are popping up a lot now >> Now You Can Buy and Sell Items Directly in Your Twitter Feed  http://on.mash.to/1549VJn     
    
    
    Photo: Step 11: Make yourself proud Today I read a great blog post by And Then We Saved called, “17 Things... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yiOCbtO     
    
    
    Watching: #Yoga for #Cyclists Tip - Tight Hips & Balance with @Rleech http://bit.ly/10ZJr7a     
    
    
    Facebook Ads Manager: Making it Easier to Track Campaign Performance http://bit.ly/17vAmXB     
    
    
    Facebook Home is now available on Android. Are you going to download it? http://bit.ly/115cUfT     
    
    
    Photo: 30 miles plus coffee. Now for some Pho! #cycling #seabikes #epic (at Pho Than Brothers - Federal Way) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yicirMx     
    
    
    Photo: The idea that you have to be thin or smart or strong or wise or brave or good or fierce or tough or... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yiiwiQl     
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (6118 others checked-in) http://is.gd/H0B4RI  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    Photo: tumblrgymyoga: Follow Tumblr Gym: Yoga if you love yoga http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yiljuUW     
    
    
    Photo: harderbetterfasterdonda: doing it! I do this! So yummy. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yimGFJK     
    
    
    @iethanology yikes! Hope you like.    
    
    
    The Tweets coming out of #Boston right now are terrible :( http://www.theatlanticwire.com/national/2013/04/boston-marathon-explosions-live/64246/ …    
    
    
    @AskWifey @BostonDotCom thought about you. Was hoping you weren't at this one!    
    
    
    @iethanology yikes cause I know I can be a bit cheesy :)    
    
    
    @iethanology thank you! How are you changing yours?    
    
    
    Can't image running for 4 hours and being greeted by an explosion.    
    
    
    @iethanology I know I've read your cancer one previously. Very inspiring as well    
    
    
    Sports and races are going to change forever. So sad.    
    
    
    Photo: But do you live? http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yimyL86     
    
    
    @AskWifey very sad. Can't stop watching the news.    
    
    
    Photo: Flexible is beautiful. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yiqTjDU     
    
    
    WHEN EPICURIOUS MADE A HUGE FAIL. - whatshouldwecallsocialmedia: What happened in Boston was a horrifying... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxiqxv_W     
    
    
    Boston Marathon Tragedy Met With Unbelievable Acts Of Kindness http://bit.ly/Z0p8Y8  << So beautiful    
    
    
    @supersushi yeah. That was pretty frickin shameless    
    
    
    Photo: So true. Stop saying, “I’m not…..” http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yirfmQs     
    
    
    Yet more customizing for your Facebook Personal Profile http://bit.ly/15iVb9u     
    
    
    35 Truths That Every Seattleite Is Aware Of http://bit.ly/17lidc9     
    
    
    Video: Talk about a powerful ad campaign. This video left me in tears. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yivHVZn     
    
    
    Exactly. http://bit.ly/ZrnHSb     
    
    
    Learning about the New Keyword Targeting for Twitter Ads http://tcrn.ch/ZrMHc1     
    
    
    "Let go or be dragged." — Zen Proverb    
    
    
    Facebook Adds Groups To Timeline  http://bit.ly/15mV50F     
    
    
    When we finally learn to let go of the things that don’t matter, we discover all the things that really do.    
    
    
    Photo: Pretty ride on the Foothills Trail today. Got 5th overall on Strava! #cycling #bikeporn #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yiy4-o8     
    
    
    Reading about: Twitter #music App and Service http://on.mash.to/11hL0xQ  cc: @IamQDot    
    
    
    "The quality of your commitments will determine the course of your life.” – Ralph Marston http://bit.ly/11hKFv0     
    
    
    @IAMQDOT nice :-)    
    
    
    Is Facebook Still Cool (and Why Should Marketers Care) http://bit.ly/11hL9kH  via @heidicohen    
    
    
    Love the idea behind @FLOATapparel >> $8 of your purchase will be donated to Wild B.I.R.D. Rehab. Center of Denver http://bit.ly/11hZ0Yt     
    
    
    @floatapparel of course :)    
    
    
    Looks like another day of me not getting anything done because I'm glued to the news.... *sigh*    
    
    
    @haleykilgour that commercial left me in tears.    
    
    
    @seditiouscanary *claps* Yay for fenders :)    
    
    
    I see yoga in my future. All this stressful news is bugging me out.    
    
    
    Time for some Dropkick Murphys http://bit.ly/15rVY8g     
    
    
    Have been using @Chatwork_en recently for business IM's and communication. Really liking it http://ow.ly/ket7y     
    
    
    Going! RT @swiftindustries: Dear @cascadebicycle members: please join us at #pedalersfair this weekend. http://pedalersfair.com  #SEAbikes    
    
    
    Photo: Gonna go ahead and call this 50 miles. #seabikes #cycling #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yjA9oed     
    
    
    Why aren’t younger Americans driving anymore? | @scoopit http://sco.lt/8ZLVdB     
    
    
    I love Dropbox because Dropbox just introduced Albums. Pretty cool, Dropbox!  http://db.tt/xTTEsIeR     
    
    
    Updated my Seattle to Portland story on #Storify http://sfy.co/bEfk  #cycling    
    
    
    Photo: Accurate. #WWSCSM http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxjRRg1t     
    
    
    Adwords Adds Social Annotations, Targeting For In-App Ads To Enhanced Campaigns http://selnd.com/Zl01PV     
    
    
    This >> Still using stock photos on social? Why it’s really time to stop.   http://bit.ly/YVVzDz     
    
    
    Social Media Management and the Myth that "Anyone Can Do It"   http://bit.ly/15RTGiG  #wwcsm #cmgr    
    
    
    Are you using Keyword Targeting for Twitter? http://bit.ly/ZRqT5H     
    
    
    How Game of Thrones Can Make You A Better Cook http://bit.ly/11FVQhe     
    
    
    How to Make a (Wo)Manly Salad http://bit.ly/11FWKdv     
    
    
    @heidimiller awww. A good friend once told me that Acupuncture helped with severe pet allergies    
    
    
    Watching! Love that @AmberCadabra said "tool agnostic." I'm always telling ppl that. MT @jfouts Social Biz Hangout http://thefridayhangout.com/social-business-hangout-with-amber-naslund/ …    
    
    
    @captainchunk I did it and there are times I regret it. Of course I have another "fun" handle for the really good stuff ;)    
    
    
    @captainchunk about time!    
    
    
    Yay! *throws confetti* >> The creators of Vine promise an Android app 'soon' http://bit.ly/ZTva8J     
    
    
    This is cool! RT @laughingsquid: Minimalist Star Wars-Themed Art Prints http://squid.us/11IEz7f     
    
    
    Yum! (@ Crêpe de France) http://4sq.com/11KFCCc     
    
    
    Accurate >> How 99.9% of people judge the quality of their coffee http://bit.ly/15Xrjj3     
    
    
    Photo: Art not ads. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yjclird     
    
    
    Photo: Guess where? (at Gum Wall) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yjcnHTY     
    
    
    Photo: Rude! #seabikes #cycling http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yji53hf     
    
    
    I'm watching Django Unchained (175 others checked-in) http://bit.ly/1887Bh2  #GetGlue @UnchainedMovie    
    
    
    Photo: 50 freakin’ miles around Lake Washington today. I’m exhausted. It was gorgeous, of course. #seabikes... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yjmRWA0     
    
    
    Photo: Step 12: Trick yourself into changing your choices For some reason we humans tend to look at things... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yjpgkKm     
    
    
    Posters of Angry Eyes Actually Scare Off Bike Thieves http://sco.lt/8dUSll     
    
    
    Google's 10-Minute Guide to SEO Basics  http://sco.lt/6bSZ17     
    
    
    Anais Nin?? Nahhh XD RT @chrisvoss: Good things happen to those who hustle.  Anais Nin    
    
    
    Reading: "How Much Is a Facebook Friend Worth? $174.17" http://bit.ly/10nLBtR     
    
    
    Love this! --> Identity-Based Habits: How to Actually Stick to Your Goals This Year http://bit.ly/ZLH7CV  #healthyliving #fitness    
    
    
    What Facebook Graph Search Means for Your Business http://bit.ly/ZvOOfF  -- Excllent insights and tips from @kellyjohorton    
    
    
    Need a Job? Invent It http://nyti.ms/10nNK90     
    
    
    "The big secret in life is that there is no big secret. Whatever your goal, you can get there if you’re willing to work." -Oprah Winfrey    
    
    
    Very cute > Jamin's Downtown Disney Flashmob Proposal http://bit.ly/ZQMp03     
    
    
    "The value of your Facebook fans is directly associated with the retail amount your customers spend on your product." http://bit.ly/13JlT7r     
    
    
    Excellent suggestions --> 11 Powerful Ways to Increase Relevant Facebook Likes with Ads  http://bit.ly/10SgoGK  via @JonLoomer    
    
    
    “To live fully, we must learn to use things and love people, and not love things and use people.” - John Powell    
    
    
    Our lives are not defined by the things we have. Our lives are defined by the things we pursue.    
    
    
    @dgkh2 congrats!    
    
    
    @hipsforhire I work at home!    
    
    
    @moxie_hart I saw that!    
    
    
    @k1k1chan I've always wanted to try pilates. Do you do it with the machines?    
    
    
    @hipsforhire any chance to get up and move around.    
    
    
    @k1k1chan yeah, I'm the same way. I'll try a machine class someday.    
    
    
    Yup RT @nikhewitt: Here's a tip: If you make me wait 60 secs to view your content I'll leave your site & got to the next link in my search.    
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 it's sunny here too. I say we skip work!    
    
    
    @melfass so many emails. That's how. Oy    
    
    
    6 Interesting Facebook Tricks You Might Not Know http://bit.ly/ZpAS3b     
    
    
    So cool! RT @goodreads:  A son shares his late father's reading list of 10,000 books! http://bit.ly/11YGRiB     
    
    
    Trying out Google Keep - Google's Standalone Note-Taking App http://bit.ly/ZCuQzJ     
    
    
    Gotta stop doing this >> Stop Eating Lunch at Your Desk  http://bit.ly/ZCuXLC     
    
    
    7 Ways to Improve Your Social Media Engagement http://bit.ly/13Q5RbM     
    
    
    This is sad. -- NYC Bike Share Program Bars Obese Riders From Making Healthy Life Choice http://bit.ly/13S1ay6     
    
    
    Watching Regena Thomashauer's TedTalk. @MamaGena sounds like a lot of fun :) http://bit.ly/ZFUiV3     
    
    
    Photo: CTS #5 - 56+ miles! #seabikes #cycling #bikeporn #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykEdmf3     
    
    
    Photo: Playing #Munchkin for the first time. Hopefully we’re doing this right. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykG1Ux3     
    
    
    Photo: The Cedar River Trail on Cinco De Mayo. It was a tough ride after yesterday’s but very pretty. #epic... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykJexap     
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (8612 others checked-in) http://is.gd/H0B4RI  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    Very truthy. I check Reddit daily >> The Truth About Reddit  http://bit.ly/13Z7LHd     
    
    
    For those Seeking Proof that Social Media Drives Sales http://bit.ly/13Z7Qe4     
    
    
    Started the day off with some much needed yoga. http://wp.me/pUJVT-X4     
    
    
    Just discovered @DoYogaWithMe - Very cool free/donation-based Yoga resource  http://bit.ly/10gwjrd     
    
    
    So you’re making a Facebook profile for work? No. Just. No. http://wp.me/p2clDK-Bi     
    
    
    @haleykilgour Happy Birthday Haley! Miss you :)    
    
    
    Photo: My mantra on long rides. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykX3bc-     
    
    
    Really frustrated with the @Starbucks app. Why reload my card if I always have problems and/or can't use it??    
    
    
    Permanent changes lead to permanent results. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykbm7b1     
    
    
    Photo: My husband is building a chair. This combined with my knitting skills make us highly desirable post... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykdT-m9     
    
    
    This is hilarious and exactly why people don't watch the traditional news as much as they used to http://bit.ly/10lLH5z     
    
    
    Photo: “It’s a pretty good chair, huh?” - Ben. It’s part of a set that we can put together to format a... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykdvs5-     
    
    
    As a former teacher this makes me sad & excited all at once > 'Get up & teach us' Student's classroom rant goes viral http://bit.ly/13kWYbG     
    
    
    Photo: Something I have to remind myself of often. ;) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ykgJpUH     
    
    
    Not a fan >> Facebook video ads incoming, will autoplay in your feed http://bit.ly/10nIRwR     
    
    
    @mehalchin agreed. I hate the idea.    
    
    
    @alielombardi I know right? It's a horrible response to Vines popularity    
    
    
    I'm watching The Great Gatsby (776 are watching) http://bit.ly/1610ATF  #GetGlue @GatsbyMovie    
    
    
    Reading: Is Measuring Your Facebook Edgerank Useful? http://bit.ly/10tX8bj     
    
    
    Reading: Is EdgeRank Checker valid? on @Quora http://b.qr.ae/17lIb3E     
    
    
    16 Ways To Get More Comments On Your Facebook Page http://bit.ly/10tXAqj     
    
    
    @iamqdot congrats!!!!    
    
    
    So excited for you!!! RT @theangelah: Anything That Can Go Wrong Will At Least Give Us a Good Story to Tell http://wp.me/p2NoaZ-40     
    
    
    @briancjohnson if I actually like the company I don't mind the occasional update email.    
    
    
    Love this commencement address to the 2005 graduating class by author David Foster  >> THIS IS WATER http://bit.ly/13xDrot     
    
    
    .@briancjohnson I also use a "junk email" account for signing up for discounts/newsletters I might want but don't want in my main inbox.    
    
    
    This. RT @projectline: Marketing Challenge: Balancing big data insight with free flowing creativity  http://ow.ly/l3WVT     
    
    
    @jamesmann23 Hi James! Thanks for the follow! I see you have a bit of a 49ers obessesion. I love San Fran.    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 day is going well. Hoping to finish work early so I can do a bike ride around Mercer Island :)    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 it's a fun loop!    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 definitely! I've been out since February training for Seattle to Portland. Now is much better than Feb :)    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 yep! We start in Seattle (UW Stadium I believe) and ride 200 miles to Portland. I'm doing it in 2 days, but some finish in 1    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 I'm a little bit excited, a little bit nervous. Getting out there and getting in the miles helps    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 it changes every week. Last week I did 120 miles total :)    
    
    
    @jamesmann23 thanks! http://25.media.tumblr.com/860d2c660e09a887b121c3362d9be8a7/tumblr_mmsnf3qwZS1ql2603o1_500.gif …    
    
    
    The only decorating tip you'll ever need http://bit.ly/16A6Tgu     
    
    
    "How wonderful it is that nobody need wait a single moment before starting to improve the world.” – Anne Frank    
    
    
    Reading about the Google+ updates. http://bit.ly/10yVYvl     
    
    
    I have to say I'm loving the new look and all the added goodies. Well done Google.    
    
    
    Love this - so true! Gonna check out @TheCR >> The Dark Side of Community Management  http://bit.ly/10AY3qH  #CMDarkSide    
    
    
    Love. http://amzn.com/k/Kq8KaHNfQVOd2ROg8uwtpg … Things aren’t all so tangible and sayable as people would usually have us believe; most experiences are ...    
    
    
    I'm watching Game of Thrones (5641 others checked-in) http://is.gd/H0B4RI  #GetGlue @GameofThrones    
    
    
    9 Social Marketing Metrics That Actually Matter http://on.mash.to/12pXz9b     
    
    
    Just wow. --> “I knocked a cyclist off his bike. I have right of way, he doesn’t even pay road tax” http://bit.ly/10J43hb     
    
    
    @tezza_lou88 love it. lol    
    
    
    Love this. RT @kristy: Super Mario Dog -- http://i.imgur.com/6ZKcbwc.gif  via @stentontoledo    
    
    
    @jeremyjrussell yeah, that's an awesome area.    
    
    
    @projectline wow, that's depressing.    
    
    
    @briancjohnson that's good to know!    
    
    
    @cascadebicycle dream job!    
    
    
    @seabikeblog congrats!    
    
    
    Love >> Products Added to Pinterest  http://bit.ly/16Mm32o     
    
    
    I'm loving the new G+. Need to revamp your design? Here's a Guide to the New G+ Cover Photo Size w/ Bonus Inspiration http://bit.ly/16OyVVH     
    
    
    Good stuff! >> Nutrition Tips for Cycling and Training http://sco.lt/8RGvIH     
    
    
    I would love to do a #cycling tour like this some day. Sounds amazing! --> "Best of Hokkaido - Japan" http://bit.ly/12Wa5hj     
    
    
    Facebook gives admins new way to create ‘unpublished posts’ directly from page http://bit.ly/10M5GL4     
    
    
    Proud of my friend Dan who is revolutionizing a 100-year-old industry w/ the release of a cloud-based time clock http://bit.ly/10QsOfi     
    
    
    Reading more on Twitter's Lead Generation Cards http://bit.ly/10UfbMa     
    
    
    Why PTAT Doesn’t Correlate with Engagement on Facebook http://bit.ly/14DK87S     
    
    
    Really good Google+ Resources here: http://bit.ly/16cGRRg     
    
    
    Tomorrow's ride is 76 miles w/ 3500' elevation gain! Not gonna lie, I'm a tad bit terrified. ;)  Mostly.http://bit.ly/13QqZAl  #seab…    
    
    
    Dozens Of Top E-Commerce Retailers Find It Pays To Put Customers’ Instagram Photos On Their Sites http://tcrn.ch/13QMHUR     
    
    
    “I may not agree with you, but I will defend to the death your right to make an ass of yourself.” ― Oscar Wilde (Happy #MemorialDay!)    
    
    
    “The unhappiest people in this world, are those who care the most about what other people think.” ― C. JoyBell C.    
    
    
    Love this! >> 33 Things You Never Knew About The Women Of "Game Of Thrones" http://bit.ly/16ppFbq     
    
    
    5 Examples of Brands Using Google Plus Hangouts http://bit.ly/16puwt3     
    
    
    The Ultimate Guide to Google Plus http://bit.ly/16puLo2     
    
    
    Is listening to @IamQDOT on Juice Radio had to get my s/o this afternoon. ;) http://bit.ly/12Q4gBB     
    
    
    Great tips! --> How to Gain More Followers on Google Plus http://bit.ly/12OYLTM     
    
    
    Hmmmm >> ‘Vicious cycle’ in brain keeps obesity going http://bit.ly/16pB9f3     
    
    
    @ScottReviews thank you for the awesome site and for noticing my awesomeness. ;)    
    
    
    @ScottReviews *curtseys*    
    
    
    Love, love, love this >> How to Love Your Authentic Self http://bit.ly/16pCMt6  via @tinybuddha    
    
    
    FINALLY. Have been waiting for @mommyniri's (Masala) Chai recipe for a long time. Can't wait to try it. http://www.mommyniri.com/2013/05/how-to-make-masala-chai-easy-recipe-for-ginger-or-cardamom-tea/ …    
    
    
    Facebook launches verified pages and profiles to help users identify authentic accounts http://bit.ly/15as9GD     
    
    
    Loving this --> 9 Rules for a Simpler Day http://bit.ly/140TkUJ     
    
    
    Photo: So, I got two more flats on my ride and a stranger hugged me. Last Saturday I was supposed to go on a... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymCngdY     
    
    
    You don't have to engage http://bit.ly/12RyFzq     
    
    
    @bbangie the lady who helped me was amazing. I sent her a little guardian angel necklace.    
    
    
    @bbangie I'm such a baby. I was upset because it was the second long ride in a row in which that happened to me. :/ I have new tires now.    
    
    
    @bbangie yeah, totally already on it! lol    
    
    
    @bbangie I need to go a little easier on myself when it comes to training expectations. I'm hard on myself because I'm slow.    
    
    
    @bbangie only a month and a half away -- eep. I've been training really hard. I know I'll be ready (another reason I shouldn't be hard on me    
    
    
    @nikhewitt can't believe i almost missed the catbeard!!    
    
    
    Yikes only 44 more days until #ridestp! I feel like I'm nearly ready...    
    
    
    Anniversary dinner! (@ Tutta Bella Neapolitan Pizzeria - Columbia City - @tuttabellacc) http://4sq.com/10LWmYM     
    
    
    Interesting insights on Twitter + TV http://bit.ly/12RC29H     
    
    
    6 Tools to Analyze and Improve Your Website Search Engine Ranking http://bit.ly/12REayj     
    
    
    Internet issues this a.m. Called Xfinity. They troubleshot & my modem was busted. Went to the store & they replaced it. Great service.    
    
    
    Loved watching this unfold (Warning Swears!!) >> Samuel L. Jackson's Awesome, Game-Changing Reddit Contest http://bit.ly/143PkTm     
    
    
    Reading: Lowe's Embraces Six-Second Vine Videos for Spring Campaign http://bit.ly/12Uk5r4     
    
    
    Photo: Another couple of flats. Have to admit I’m feeling sad and discouraged at this point. #cycling... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymNlm6H     
    
    
    Photo: Got my ride bib today! Nervous + Excited for #FlyingWheels. Hopefully no more flats. Ugh. #seabikes... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymS8bEd     
    
    
    @karen_woodward woot!    
    
    
    Someone should tell @PlaySaveUp that a new bike costs *way* more than $100 ;) http://bit.ly/15ybLzG  #justsayin    
    
    
    I am excite! (You can now download Vine for Android) https://blog.twitter.com/2013/vine-android-every-robot-has-its-day …    
    
    
    @playSaveUp bike fund is a great idea. I just don't know of a bike worth purchasing that costs a mere $100.    
    
    
    I love this! >> Cute video of the day: http://bit.ly/16KnoHS     
    
    
    Photo: We added cushions and an umbrella to the chairs Ben made. Our little deck is finally more comfy. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymgiNm5     
    
    
    Photo: One more shot. It’s coming together nicely. #outdoorliving #DIY http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymhgVzw     
    
    
    It's been a crazy busy week. Excited to have a new client, but can't wait to get out on my bike!    
    
    
    Doing my first ever #FlyingWheels tomorrow (65 miles). Everything is packed & ready, but I'm still a little nervous! #seabikes    
    
    
    @cascadebicycle I am! Doing the 65 mile version. Hopefully no flat tires (I've been having bad luck)    
    
    
    Going thru my gear checklist. Ready for #FlyingWheels #seabikes https://vine.co/v/bLrAdunX7lK     
    
    
    Photo: Just finished #FlyingWheels. One of the more challenging rides I’ve attempted. Proud I finished.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ymvPKZB     
    
    
    Adding to my Seattle to Portland 2013 story: http://sfy.co/bEfk  #storify #epic #bikestp #seabikes    
    
    
    Facebook Streamlining Ad Offerings: 4 Outstanding Questions - http://bit.ly/13ue98u  http://bit.ly/16Xjf3E     
    
    
    Is. So. Busy.    
    
    
    "Yarn bombing becomes a global phenomenon" http://on-msn.com/14vqgEQ     
    
    
    “The real measure of your wealth is how much you’d be worth if you lost all your money.” ~ Unknown    
    
    
    @iethanology we live in such a classy town ;)    
    
    
    Life is short. Live accordingly.    
    
    
    Barry Schwartz: The paradox of choice http://bit.ly/11vXmzq     
    
    
    #Hashtags have finally come to Facebook http://on.mash.to/14x3QmS     
    
    
    Evernote Reminders Are Here on Mac, iOS and Web http://bit.ly/11INsP8  #evernote #blog    
    
    
    Photo: 67 miles, 3000+ elevation gain, 0 flats. #cycling #seabikes #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ynQdcvI     
    
    
    Saw on the news that another cyclist was killed in Washington this weekend. Of course I had nightmares last night. :/ #seabikes    
    
    
    UPDATED: Complete Social Media Image Size Guide http://bit.ly/17gZtjE     
    
    
    Reading: Facebook Hashtags for Brands: What You Need to Know http://bit.ly/17gZyUm     
    
    
    STUDY: News Feed Page Post Ads Deliver 26X More ROI, 20X Greater CTR Than Facebook Right-Hand-Side Ads http://bit.ly/14GHOxX     
    
    
    Love this film http://is.gd/RtdwHd  #GetGlue #MoonriseKingdom    
    
    
    Photo: (is freakin’ out) 22 days does not seem like very many. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ynjMUKu     
    
    
    We all thought this was coming --> Facebook introduces 15 sec video support w 13 filters for Instagram http://tnw.co/1c0lr79     
    
    
    Beautiful! Can't wait to play around with it --> Introducing Video on Instagram on Vimeo http://bit.ly/1c0BIck     
    
    
    ATTN DATA JUNKIES! Facebook Redesigns Page Insights To Give Businesses Clearer, More Actionable Data http://tcrn.ch/14Mnqvy     
    
    
    I'm watching Seeking a Friend for the End of the World (10 others checked-in) http://bit.ly/16W56jx  #GetGlue    
    
    
    Photo: #Cheers http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ynyGaWa     
    
    
    Ambers Wedding Smiles https://vine.co/v/huUXPhLx16r     
    
    
    DJ Seth (aka The Intern) https://vine.co/v/huUDH0iT7Q5     
    
    
    Photo: Scheduled ride was canceled, so we came up with our own. I had to keep up with a much quicker group.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yo16K3i     
    
    
    Photo: Someone got her #bikestp packet in the mail today. Shit just got real. Eep. #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yo17V6z     
    
    
    Amazing finale. Bravo. http://bit.ly/12jRc5z  #GetGlue @NBCHannibal    
    
    
    Watching under strict orders from a friend. http://bit.ly/11XCTol  #GetGlue #Newsroom    
    
    
    Updated my Seattle to Portland 2013 Story: http://sfy.co/bEfk  #storify #epic #bikestp    
    
    
    @RollerEclipse I will!! Or you should come to the festival at the end to see me... I'll be drunk from exercise so I might not remember...    
    
    
    @lindzeemccain I really enjoyed it. I ended up watching 5 episodes last night. Very good show.    
    
    
    @RollerEclipse No, that's the only thing I'm not sure about. I have another Portland friend asking the same. Maybe I could tweet it? FB it?    
    
    
    @lindzeemccain it starts next week right?    
    
    
    @lindzeemccain awesome! Plenty of time for me to finish Season 1.    
    
    
    Photo: Ms. @SocialPup showing off some of her moves. #dogstagram http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yo6FKb4     
    
    
    @RollerEclipse will do :)    
    
    
    @chatterboxcgc iiiiiiiiii am a maaaaaaaaaaan of constant sorrrrrrowwwwwwww.... I've seen trouuuuuuble all my daaaaaaays    
    
    
    Photo: This is Molly’s, “I need it to stop being so hot" face. #dogstagram #lab http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yoR9vi8     
    
    
    Photo: View from the road. Today’s 100 mile ride was gorgeous. #cycling #seabikes #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yoW5ADc     
    
    
    Photo: I wouldn’t have made it the full 100 if it wasn’t for Heidi. Tragically one of her tires exploded... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yoW6OLV     
    
    
    Photo: So. Yeah. Now I know how THAT feels. #cycling #seabikes #Century #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yoWD0jM     
    
    
    Just finished my first century. Now settling in and watching the pros. http://bit.ly/18nNn85  #GetGlue @letour    
    
    
    Photo: Feeling spoiled. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yoeiC-2     
    
    
    @jfouts thank you :) I'm trying for STP which is 200+    
    
    
    @jfouts it's a lot of hard work and training hours :-)    
    
    
    Photo: Got to visit @cascadebicycle after our last CTS ride of the season today. Learned these bad boys are... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yp1ZmvM     
    
    
    Photo: Last CTS ride of the season. Met some truly wonderful people. A little sad it’s over. #seabikes... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yp1d24D     
    
    
    Photo: Happy Birthday Mama (@CJPalfreyEhlers)! #croquet #family http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yp2alyV     
    
    
    Photo: Sometimes making a decision is the hardest part. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yp6RQvP     
    
    
    Bank of America Bot Cares About You http://bit.ly/12kX66z     
    
    
    I love this >> Dustin Hoffman Breaks Down Crying Explaining Something That Every Woman Knows http://bit.ly/1aWHtvy     
    
    
    Confirming my hotel/motel reservations for #bikestp --> SO NERVOUS!    
    
    
    @ppatulot that was all the training you've done?    
    
    
    Updated my Seattle to Portland 2013 Story. Ridiculously nervous. http://sfy.co/bEfk  #storify #epic    
    
    
    Wow, yeah. #Accurate RT @starfocus: This is so true... http://www.buzzfeed.com/jessicamisener/30-signs-youre-almost-30 …    
    
    
    @thienkim that sounds amazing!    
    
    
    This.  RT @AmberCadabra: The first time someone shows you who they are, believe them. - Maya Angelou    
    
    
    @ppatulot good luck!    
    
    
    Photo: Exhibit A: My “side" of the bed. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypTnPtn     
    
    
    Photo: 12 hours to go…… #bikestp #epic #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypW1adn     
    
    
    Still in #bikestp traffic. What a way to start. So nervous!    
    
    
    @bikemyway good luck!    
    
    
    @lilburnside43 good luck!    
    
    
    70 miles in! #bikestp    
    
    
    @YarnHarlot thank you!    
    
    
    Pedal pedal pedal pedal #bikestp    
    
    
    Made it to the midway point! Exhausted...... #bikestp    
    
    
    Photo: Icing my knees, ankles, and sore legs. Hopefully it will help day 2. #bikestp #cycling #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypbglxe     
    
    
    @anthonyrstevens thank you!    
    
    
    Maybe one day - - > "@CampyOnlyGuy: Official Seattle to Portland One-day finishers patch. #BikeSTP #stp2013 pic.twitter.com/sJ7od7nZA9"    
    
    
    @RollerEclipse we think we are rolling in around 6    
    
    
    @RollerEclipse more like 7    
    
    
    Photo: I’m officially an STP finisher. It was the most challenging thing I’ve ever done emotionally,... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypj-aat     
    
    
    Thanks ladies! Naturally, I had wine and champagne afterwards  ;)  "@winesisterhood: @shellimartineau Awesome achievement. Congrats Shelli!"    
    
    
    Spoiling my support team! (at @VoodooDoughnut Too w/ 3 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/12Bm9ak     
    
    
    Photo: For the record. #bikestp #cycling #seabikes #finisher http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypkKsJJ     
    
    
    Thank you! It was my first :-)  "@bikemyway: @ShelliMartineau Congratulations on finishing STP!"    
    
    
    @ghdurham very cool. Congrats!    
    
    
    Trying out Birchbox!  http://fbuy.me/dRYk     
    
    
    100% accurate. Replace running with cycling and that's what I've been doing in a nutshell. ;) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ypovhy7     
    
    
    “If it’s both terrifying and amazing then you should definitely pursue it.” - Erada #BikeSTP pic.twitter.com/R9m4cCH9pE    
    
    
    "My goal is no longer to get more done, but rather to have less to do." —Francine Jay    
    
    
    “Whatever you are not changing, you are choosing.” —Laurie Buchanan    
    
    
    Life is in the details. Pay attention to them.    
    
    
    The New Facebook Insights: What's New, What's Awesome and What Sucks via Jon Loomer Digital http://bit.ly/15Ioq21     
    
    
    Everyone saw the biracial Cheerios commercial, but kids saw it differently http://bit.ly/1bsxEWo     
    
    
    Urban Bicycling Is For Lazy People --- Love this post by @jamesschwartz http://bit.ly/12PoF8z  via @theurbancountry    
    
    
    Congrats to @ChatWork_En for reaching 200k users with their IM product for businesses --> http://bit.ly/12SEMSA  #client #socool    
    
    
    I have to say, I'm loving the new Facebook insights. Do you have them yet? What do you think?    
    
    
    Benefits of the New Facebook Ad Reports http://bit.ly/1bwzvcR     
    
    
    Photo: Gave my #yogamat a bath and now she’s hanging up to dry. Can’t wait to start at my potential new... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yq4IOBY     
    
    
    Hee Hee >> Either Chipotle Doesn't Know How To Use Twitter, Or They Know Exactly How To Use Twitter http://bit.ly/1dOfLxX     
    
    
    Walking Group! (@ Celebration Park w/ @cjmartineau) [pic]: http://4sq.com/160Bnqa     
    
    
    The key to good marketing? Notice. http://bit.ly/18ASfrr     
    
    
    Giving OneFeed a try. I like when things are organized.... http://bit.ly/132oLOO     
    
    
    Excellent tips. Worth the read --> 6 Tips for Creating Amazing Content http://bit.ly/132oTh9     
    
    
    Photo: Roasted Vegetable Amazingness. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yqR4V9Y     
    
    
    Photo: Self Care 101: Monthly Presents! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yqVZM18     
    
    
    Neat! -->  Google Launches The $35 Chromecast Streaming Device To Bring Chrome To The Living Room http://tcrn.ch/169OpQf     
    
    
    SO WEIRD --> Chipotle Faked Its Twitter Hack http://on.mash.to/18DAwzC     
    
    
    @KJWines thanks for the follow!!    
    
    
    Whoa --> The Scary, Passenger's Eye View From Inside the Crashed Southwest Plane http://bit.ly/16kh8Ss     
    
    
    @DJChairmanMoe right?!    
    
    
    “ The sweetest of all sounds is praise. ”— Xenophon    
    
    
    @kirbycuse yikes! I had a weird elbow issue for awhile after too    
    
    
    @gingerpally good luck!    
    
    
    @autumnthing that sounds wonderful :)    
    
    
    Too cool! RT @bikewa: RT pls to help #womenbike writer fund WA bicycle tour book  http://ow.ly/np8Jr  @amrook @bikegrrl @cmg_shift_blog    
    
    
    Dreaming about taking a cycling trip to Lopez Island. Swoon.    
    
    
    @bethsjourneytt congrats!    
    
    
    I am *so* addicted. I should do this T @alivincent: Addicted to @Starbucks?  WATCH THIS and save calories!  http://livewelln.co/1aKR8Ta  #LiveBig    
    
    
    @familyride @totcycle brilliant!    
    
    
    NW Cyclist: 10 Classic rides in the Northwest  http://bit.ly/16v374g  #seabikes    
    
    
    Photo: GPOY. Took a Gentle Yoga class today. It was a little too Gentle/Slow for me, but I enjoyed myself. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yqwMG5k     
    
    
    "Be miserable. Or motivate yourself. Whatever has to be done, it’s always your choice." - Wayne Dyer (via... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yqyCF1c     
    
    
    26 Tips to Enhance Your Social Media Profiles  http://bit.ly/16AkvVn     
    
    
    3 Ways Brands Are Destroying Social Media http://bit.ly/1e9dvSa     
    
    
    Just signed up to be a volunteer at @GeekGirlCon . This should be interesting!!    
    
    
    Does anyone know a good, environmentally friendly way to get rid of/sell books? #AspiringMinimalist    
    
    
    @lamiki where would you sell them? Ebay? Hmmm.    
    
    
    @haleykilgour that looks like fun :)    
    
    
    @briancjohnson leaving so soon? Where is the SDL position?    
    
    
    @lamiki I was thinking of selling them in bulk, but I will check out HPB's thank you for the tip :)    
    
    
    "You probably don’t need as much of the stuff you think you do" - @IAmMarkManson http://bit.ly/16EF5Ee     
    
    
    Neat. Facebook just launched embedded posts --> http://allfacebook.com/embedded-posts_b122838 …    
    
    
    @iReadAndSing gonna flash my ignorance here. Why 'Bushwick'? Isn't that in NY?    
    
    
    @iReadAndSing that makes sense then! ^__^    
    
    
    Can’t Keep Up? 11 Ways to Instantly Simplify Your Life http://bit.ly/1ebC2WW  via @prolificliving    
    
    
    "Give what you have. To someone, it may be better than you dare to think.” ―Henry Longfellow" http://bit.ly/1ebBU9F     
    
    
    Photo: My favorite girl. :-) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yr7ma4E     
    
    
    Photo: Lately I’ve been dreaming of camping quite a bit. Thinking of a trip to Ruby beach or possibly hiking... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yr9rXue     
    
    
    How to Create a Week’s Worth of EPIC Content From One Blog Post!  http://bit.ly/19zW7bE  via @socialmouths    
    
    
    This looks like fun --> Ditch the Poles: 10 Places to Go Yurt Camping in Washington http://bit.ly/1egLvw9     
    
    
    #Spoiled myself with a new purse from @ModCloth! Now I'm sharing the love: Use this link at get $15 off http://sharethelove.modcloth.com/a/clk/vw5nT     
    
    
    Facebook Announces ‘Story Bumping,’ And Other Small Changes To News Feed Algorithm http://bit.ly/172KyF0     
    
    
    News Feed FYI: A Window Into News Feed http://on.fb.me/172KCEP     
    
    
    Great ideas to get you thinking about your own content > 40 Free Titles For Blogs http://bit.ly/175tM89  from @heidicohen    
    
    
    This. >> 'Homeless' man surprises train commuters by bragging instead of begging in College Humor prank http://bit.ly/175z0Rn     
    
    
    "Starting today you can upload videos from your phone’s media library and share those moments to Instagram" http://bit.ly/19b48oj     
    
    
    More on the Facebook News Feed Update: Story Bumping, Last Actor, Chronological by Actor http://bit.ly/19b5yiv     
    
    
    http://fbuy.me/fD5U  @NatureBox    
    
    
    Photo: Happy Throwback Thursday! This was me circa 2009 (about 70lbs ago…..) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yrmGW8L     
    
    
    Officially adding to my bucket list! (Going to convince my brother in law to take me) --> http://bit.ly/136loZ6     
    
    
    Video: Why is it okay to be fat? Because the alternative: Scale-dependent self esteem, yo-yo dieting and... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yrrwm27     
    
    
    @bbangie it's so hard. We're taught body hate at a young age. I hope it helps her :-(    
    
    
    Video: The men folk swear they can get a fire started this way. #bbq #funnymen http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ys2BLDA     
    
    
    Photo: It’s all gone now. All gone. #gingerbeer #yummy http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ys2duff     
    
    
    Photo: brooklynmutt: "We did it guys! We killed English!" - @magnus72 Define, “literally” http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsARUnu     
    
    
    Honestly, I don't care why 13 year olds are rejecting Facebook.....    
    
    
    @OhhSuzannah yeah, huge eye roll!    
    
    
    @OhhSuzannah further, it's not realistic for them to ALL migrate to 1 alt platform.. it's silly to assume ppl can't use multiple networks    
    
    
    @OhhSuzannah yes!!    
    
    
    @OhhSuzannah its a sign of lazy marketing to simply rely on Facebook as the "go to" network.    
    
    
    "People will love you. People will hate you. And none of it will have anything to do with you." - (via... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsFtaga     
    
    
    Video: nprmusic: New Zealand native Ella Yelich-O’Connor is just 16, but she’s already notched one of the... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsGpL-2     
    
    
    I like this --> Simplify Your Tech Life, Thoreau-Style http://on.wsj.com/1eK9XpX     
    
    
    Stuff We Don’t Need: 5 Reasons Why It Doesn’t Lead to Happiness http://bit.ly/1d7FrIx     
    
    
    Photo: 3 guesses…. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysIN8t9     
    
    
    This looks like a really fun Kickstarter --> Pursuing Happiness - A Documentary Film by Adam Shell & Nicholas Kraft http://kck.st/16bWeq6     
    
    
    Declutter Your Life http://bit.ly/16bWk0Y     
    
    
    Photo: Feeling proud of myself for being extra health conscious and brave this week. I even tried sushi for... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysL8_VU     
    
    
    Photo: If other professions were paid like artists freelancers. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsLdVuA     
    
    
    Photo: I love this. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysQhcqx     
    
    
    Video: Hiking with the girls. (at Dash Point State Park) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysX911K     
    
    
    Photo: We are giving @NatureBox a try. Just received a ton of snacks: Almonds, sunflower seeds, granola, tea... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysY9Vgs     
    
    
    Go Kaleo Condensed http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yscflnr     
    
    
    Some ppl are convinced that shame & guilt are effective ways to motivate someone to address their weight...  http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yshOEv9     
    
    
    An amazing Open Apology by a former weight loss consultant:  http://huff.to/1bN8G1v     
    
    
    Photo: Yoga at the beach! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ysjSTim     
    
    
    Photo: runswithpoodles: Life motto. This is going around everywhere. Love it. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsk6DX7     
    
    
    Great tips for stimulating new ideas --> http://bit.ly/14Yw5y0     
    
    
    I missed the @GelaSkins 20% off sale because I took too long deciding :( :( :(    
    
    
    Clever Ways to Get Some Exercise at the Office (or Any Small Space) http://bit.ly/14Ywfpb     
    
    
    Do You Really Need Willpower to Lose Weight? http://bit.ly/1bQkro6     
    
    
    .@HelloFresh looks cool. Would love notification when you come to Seattle.    
    
    
    I have to disagree w @YayaHan. Cosplay isn't abt only choosing parts you "fit." It's about being the character you wanna be. #cosplayheros    
    
    
    @YayaHan thanks for clarifying... I was disappointed as those comments just didn't make sense.    
    
    
    Photo: Werd. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsu2sSN     
    
    
    This is bril..... (but hardly a secret) ;) --> The Secret Process to Increasing Facebook Likes  http://bit.ly/16cVHRe     
    
    
    My @Modcloth wishlist is growing..... http://www.modcloth.com/storefront/wishlists/2444755 …    
    
    
    Embedded Posts now available for everyone on Facebook http://bit.ly/151fsBP     
    
    
    This is one of my favorite art pieces by my husband. No, you can't buy it. it's MINE ALL MINE. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yswtK8h     
    
    
    Photoset: thecureforitscrimes: Through the years We get to see them at Bumbershoot! http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsxClNn     
    
    
    Photoset: When was the last time you cried? It’s on my bookshelf. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxsxD0Lg     
    
    
    Photoset: buzzfeed: A Chinese zoo was trying to pass off this incredibly fluffy dog as a lion. The zoo was... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxszhecY     
    
    
    moxie-hart asked: Sometime in March I decided to stop putting silly restrictions on my food, that included... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yszv9fu     
    
    
    moxie-hart asked: So all of that to say that I'm proud of you and if I can do it, you can do. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yszvJVe     
    
    
    Photo: One of the trays I made in pottery. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yt03W2p     
    
    
    Video: … aaaand some more things I made in pottery. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yt0553a     
    
    
    Photo: #me ;) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytA4oZQ     
    
    
    Photo: Last weekend my husband taught me how to make an omelet. This weekend I decided to try myself. I... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytFSrsW     
    
    
    Photoset: thatcrazywhoviangirl: Oh my gosh. He looks so shocked in the second picture. Hee hee. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxtKeFQP     
    
    
    Photo: Be brave. Be ruthless. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytRMgwK     
    
    
    @jillwillrun Joshua is so annoying!    
    
    
    It's tacky, unimaginative, and downright not okay for brands to piggyback off of many holidays and celebrations http://bit.ly/1dPXNOv     
    
    
    @jillwillrun really?! Ugh.... every time he talks I cringe....    
    
    
    @Kaela907 yeah.... you would *think* people would have learned by now....    
    
    
    "It was a day better lived slowly, and it was a good day." http://bit.ly/1chaGPR     
    
    
    Did you hear the news? What do you think? Facebook Timeline Promotions Are Now Legal http://bit.ly/16Rlr9z     
    
    
    "To be content doesn't mean you don't desire more, it means you're thankful for what you have and patient for what's to come." ~Tony Gaskins    
    
    
    "When we stop chasing society's definition of happiness, we can see the simple decision to be happy has been available all along." —Becker    
    
    
    Job title and salary are not the sole measures of human worth. LOVE this @ZenPencils cartoon --> http://bit.ly/153ZFwi     
    
    
    Video: fatbodypolitics: Sara Bareilles - Brave This is a really good example of fat positivity. That. Was.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytZ4C3N     
    
    
    @haleykilgour my sister just went into labor!    
    
    
    "When we give up dieting, we take back something we were often too young to know we had given away: our..." http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytbRaLz     
    
    
    @haleykilgour hee hee.    
    
    
    @haleykilgour when are we getting together? I had it in my cal, but somehow it fell off....? Tomorrow afternoonish??    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytnB8yO     
    
    
    Photo: My baby nephew Jaden is 3 days old! I’m completely smitten. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ytpz3At     
    
    
    In line for Tegan and Sara. P.S. #zooelephantssuffer (at @Bumbershoot 2013 w/ 81 others) http://4sq.com/18iLzcv     
    
    
    "If opening your eyes, or getting out of bed, or holding a spoon, or combing your hair is the daunting..." http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yu8_R0C     
    
    
    Photoset: zenpencils: WHAT TEACHERS MAKE by Taylor Mali Yes! Love that @zenpencils did this one! Taylor... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxuH8Npp     
    
    
    Photo: Love. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yuJJgOz     
    
    
    Photo: #sealife #kelp #pnwpride #upperleft http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yuPt9v1     
    
    
    "It's 5 o'clock in Florida....." #LastVegas #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/15MT5Au     
    
    
    Photoset:  http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxuf2yXn     
    
    
    Photo: My new “un-gym” is a “fitness boutique” which means, in addition to kicking my ass and making me... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yuhW6Bk     
    
    
    Amazing @ZENPENCILS cartoon on the social media generation as seen by Marc Maron http://bit.ly/15U65h5     
    
    
    @ReembodyMe great post!    
    
    
    Great post from @Reembodyme --> The 6 Most Shockingly Irresponsible “Fitspiration” Photos http://bit.ly/15UBv6S     
    
    
        
    
    
    "25 'Boring' Companies With Brilliant Social Media Cover Photos" http://bit.ly/181l8pL     
    
    
    We've been hearing about this for awhile now --> New Facebook Link Thumbnail Image Dimensions http://bit.ly/15S40ZD     
    
    
    Photo: ilovecharts: No. This. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxupOpY8     
    
    
    Had an amazing workout this morning at Victory Fit Club. Left feeling proud of myself. :) (Victory Get Fit Club)    
    
    
    6 Ways to Maximize Your Google+ Engagement http://bit.ly/18TCKGv     
    
    
    Loving this visual map of reddit and guide to smaller subreddits worth a visit http://bit.ly/1e9QdQC     
    
    
    7 Things You Didn't Know Bitly Could Do http://on.mash.to/14d6ajk     
    
    
    Realtime is a really cool discovery tool! It tells you which links are most trending on any given topic. Nifty! http://bit.ly/17HeDMb     
    
    
    This looks seriously amazing. *drool* --> "The Best Way to Cook Zucchini and Carrots" http://bit.ly/17Hu1rW     
    
    
    Kinda don't care that summer is nearly over. These look YUM  --> The Best #Healthy Burger Recipes http://bit.ly/17Hu9rq     
    
    
    Photo: No. I’m not desperately clinging to summer. No. Those aren’t raindrops I feel. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yvKaJq5     
    
    
    Photo: Bright sun and rain. Welcome to Seattle in the Fall. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yvmZya6     
    
    
        
    
    
    7 Tools For Monitoring The Effectiveness Of Your Tweets http://bit.ly/18lhD1R     
    
    
    Photo: Our version of French Fries: Roast carrots, zucchini, and potatoes (seasoned as desired) at 450 for... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yvrrY-y     
    
    
    This is great..... Louis C.K. on Cell Phones  http://bit.ly/18pMCtF     
    
    
    Justin Timberlake Shows Us How Dumb We Sound When We Use Hashtags http://bit.ly/15tPr8W     
    
    
    @nikhewitt I have not been on sl in ages! You?    
    
    
    Anyone out there having problems with Power Editor this morning?    
    
    
    Photo: He’s so big! #milkyface #worldscutestnephew http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ywGv5Ei     
    
    
    Who will be the next Park Pals Cover Dog? Vote Now! http://ow.ly/plPCG  #FederalWay #DogPark    
    
    
    Photoset: runloveyogi: healthiswealthx3: thealpha—and—theomega: thegoddamazon: ancestryinprogress:... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxwUF0s_     
    
    
    Photo: Bought myself some new #yogaswag cause I deserve it. #yoga #nsv #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ywcl-Qm     
    
    
    Photo: Fact: You are ill-equipped to handle the cuteness that is my baby nephew. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2ywe5fzG     
    
    
    Hmmmm. I'm thinking someone *might* want me to show up to this? ;-) http://instagram.com/p/fBlVqoLKW0/     
    
    
    Photo: mothernaturenetwork: Here are some of the most remarkable book shops from all around the globe, each... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxxB5pei     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxxCcc65     
    
    
    Facebook is updating ad creation design for more of an objective focus. http://on.fb.me/GOvGSZ     
    
    
    "Measure wealth not by the things you have, but by the things you have for which you would not take money." —Unknown    
    
    
    Photo: Lunch: Baked Apple and Spinach Smoothie. Yum! #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yxIrg9K     
    
    
    Photo: Werd. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxxIrtzR     
    
    
    Amazing --> How Malala, Teen Activist Shot By Taliban, Made Jon Stewart's Jaw Drop (VIDEO) http://huff.to/1gui7X0     
    
    
    Photo: 260/365: (that says improvement. next time i’ll write better) This. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yxN_R4w     
    
    
    Photo: I love this! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yxUH94Q     
    
    
    .@FullScreenMario makes me ridiculously happy.    
    
    
    6 Amazing Social Media Productivity Tools http://bit.ly/1gI1Y09     
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yxkpmpR     
    
    
    Photo: Giving banana nut #overnightoats a whirl. Got the idea from my awesome trainer @victoryfit :-) #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yxsxpFB     
    
    
    @VictoryFit It went well but I think next time I'll try a different recipe :)    
    
    
    How to #Declutter Your Life http://bit.ly/171MHUr     
    
    
    Quit trying so hard #Yahoo. Ur killing me. You don't need to encourage people to use #tumblr it does that on it's own pic.twitter.com/wbvtrOoGXc    
    
    
    Genius! Collect Accomplishments, Not Stuff http://bit.ly/19lhmvq     
    
    
    Simple, easy-to-implement tips: Building a Professional Online Presence http://bit.ly/19lhJ9n     
    
    
    A Crystal Clear Explanation of How Social Media Influences SEO http://bit.ly/171NxAA  (aaaaaand what you should do about it!)    
    
    
    How To Strategically Use Your Website's "About Us" Page To Win More Customers  http://bit.ly/19liLSQ     
    
    
    Handy for #B2B --> 26 Actionable Content Marketing Options and Tips http://bit.ly/19ljALr     
    
    
    It's all about the biggest stick she can find. Every. Single. Time. #sp http://instagram.com/p/fvfMnOLKc5/     
    
    
    Overwhelmingly helpful --> Social Media Tools and Technology-101 magic tools and technology tips http://bit.ly/19lkuaT     
    
    
    6 Simple Rituals To Reach Your Potential Every Day http://bit.ly/171QP6V     
    
    
    @alielombardi <3    
    
    
    Photo: I bought myself a gift for #crocktober cause I’m working so hard on mindful eating and trying new... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yyJ2yp6     
    
    
    “If your love is only a will to possess, it's not love.” ―Thích Nhất Hạnh    
    
    
    Photo: Whoever said “No food tastes as good as skinny feels” never had a healthy, hearty soup on a cold,... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yyRYD8d     
    
    
    "Work to become, not to acquire." —Elbert Hubbard    
    
    
    Love, Love, Love this advice from @SlowYourHome --> Don’t Save Your Stickers http://bit.ly/1h8zIEd     
    
    
    Why Your Brain Needs More Downtime http://bit.ly/1a9Ixsl     
    
    
    The film is funny too! >> @CBSFilms ’ Official Twitter Account for ‘Last Vegas’ Might Be Funnier Than the Film http://bit.ly/1ae3thS     
    
    
    "If this doesn't go viral I'm coming for you" -- Morgan Freeman. Freeman Reads 'The Fox' http://huff.to/1c1oDBa  #LastVegas    
    
    
    Very similar to what Tumblr tried --> Instagram to debut ads next week http://cnet.co/1c4gTOL     
    
    
    Viraltag allows you to schedule pins, track metrics and manage multiple accounts on Pinterest. Try it out - https://www.viraltag.com     
    
    
    Photo: Weeeeeeekend. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yyjZJLJ     
    
    
    Photo: I’m going to call this a “balanced snack.” #epic #pumpkincookie http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yyuJ4tG     
    
    
    @OhhSuzannah hee hee.    
    
    
        
    
    
    See Why We Have An Absolutely Ridiculous Standard Of Beauty In Just 37 Seconds http://bit.ly/HsoZHM     
    
    
        
    
    
    Need to come up with a name for your new biz? Wordoid might help (I'm now addicted to this site): http://bit.ly/HsCNC3     
    
    
    Gonna try @PlantoEat 's 30 day free trial --> Plan to Eat Saves Recipes, Builds Grocery Lists and Meal Plans For You http://bit.ly/HsH48x     
    
    
    @PlanToEat Actually you can help. Do you have a droid app?    
    
    
    @PlanToEat will do    
    
    
    @davidhoang sorry for your loss :(    
    
    
    @davidhoang oh! I missed the word travel! Glad your cat is ok. Lol. *facepalm*    
    
    
    @nikhewitt @tankpr 'grats Nik!    
    
    
    @moxie_hart smart!    
    
    
    @moxie_hart not bad at all!    
    
    
    Photo: Freckles + Puppy Eyes. We get away with everything. #spoiled #sp http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yzImLaB     
    
    
    Love that Lane Bryant has plus size active wear (at @LaneBryant - Southcenter Square) http://4sq.com/16X2dml     
    
    
    Photo: Used my free trial of @PlanToEat to plan my meals for the week. The best part was how EASY it was to... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yzQBk00     
    
    
    Photo: I work out for inner peace and for my sanity. But, on occasion, its nice to notice I’m getting... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yzUOFfF     
    
    
    Reverie BBQ is a biz that's close to my heart. Will you help by giving them a vote? They are trying to win a grant: https://www.missionmainstreetgrants.com/business/detail/121833 …    
    
    
    I'm still on the fence about Twitters expanded image feature, but apparently lots of people don't like it! http://bit.ly/1aYEhOF     
    
    
    Watching @Schmittastic. Wow this girl is a little terrifying > The Question You MUST Ask at Every Coffee Meeting  http://bit.ly/1iN3hJx     
    
    
    @Schmittastic terrifying in the best way! A fierce and fearless networker. I need to channel that. :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Schmittastic Seattle is the best! Hope you had some worthwhile coffee dates :)    
    
    
    @Rachel_Hickel just remember to keep it real and don't spam people!!    
    
    
    @SavvySexySocial thanks for the follow btw!    
    
    
    @vasaart @yogadork agreed. Making sub par clothes and then blaming your customer is pretty messed up    
    
    
    @nikhewitt I like em!    
    
    
    @MoniqueElwell congrats on the baby!    
    
    
    Seth's Blog: What "no" means http://bit.ly/1babKpD     
    
    
    Photo: dontneedanexcuse: “I was put on my first diet at age 12 and Developed an eating disorder due to body... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yzm2bdq     
    
    
    Photo: Today I noticed someone had the goal, “Eat [insert healthy thing] when I’m bored.” Don’t get me... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y_8A2Ok     
    
    
    This @thingCHARGER thing looks amazing! I want one. I may have to contribute to this @Indiegogo fundraising campaign http://bit.ly/HQuMqy     
    
    
    Photo: Apple slices + cinnamon = Baked Apple Smoothie #nom #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y_9aDqk     
    
    
    Fascinating! --> Why Creative People Sometimes Make No Sense http://bit.ly/18mONLx     
    
    
        
    
    
    Saw this on Reddit. Faith in humanity restored --> Social media brings 100s to funeral of British WWII soldier http://nydn.us/1eJajSj     
    
    
    Read a more technical explaination of Twitter's Custom Timelines: http://bit.ly/1cowacE     
    
    
    Just purchased a book my nutritionist recommended. Anyone want to read it with me? --> The Slow Down Diet  http://ow.ly/qN1rq     
    
    
    For those in #WA interested/confused/scared about Obamacare (especially you self employed people out there!) ---> http://ow.ly/qN1E6     
    
    
    Hilarious --> 12 Days of Holiday Bullshit by Cards Against Humanity http://bit.ly/1apMiv5     
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo: I’ve discovered a new app! #textcutie #bravery #quote #unicorn http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y_MLqI7     
    
    
    @comcastwill Hi. Karen says you can help me with my broken Internet. Help.    
    
    
    I'm on the social media equivalent of hold......    
    
    
    Photo:  http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y_Pd1Oy     
    
    
    @ComcastPete it got resolved. I had to call. Lame.    
    
    
    I'm at Pioneer Square - @seattleparks (Seattle, WA) http://4sq.com/I4IyFq     
    
    
    Yaaaay for the weekend (@ Remedy Teas) http://4sq.com/1eWUIPg     
    
    
    Brunch! (at @CoastalKitchen) http://4sq.com/1dEfJdI     
    
    
    Photo: My next read. #epic http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y_hg3at     
    
    
    Laughed out loud watching the Inside Llewyn Davis Trailer "He jumped off the George WA Bridge? Who does that?" http://bit.ly/18Ks501     
    
    
    Looove --> GoldieBlox commercial rewrites the Beastie Boys, urges young girls to pursue engineering http://slate.me/1h1svHv  cc: @AlizaSherman    
    
    
    @GrowMarketing right?!    
    
    
    @missbritt @alizasherman perfect timing!    
    
    
    @missbritt link?    
    
    
    @missbritt thanks!    
    
    
    @emilybratkovich not wine, but if you're going out tonight Bai Tong is giving ALL their proceeds to Typhoon Victims http://www.baitongrestaurant.com/     
    
    
    Watching Zach's story made me cryyyyyy --> My Last Days: Zach Sobiech "Clouds" Celebrity Music Video http://bit.ly/18p0o0x     
    
    
    Happy Thursday! Watch when you need a giggle --> Narration of what goes on inside a cat's head all day http://bit.ly/18bhT6z     
    
    
    Only an hour left! #DoctorWho #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1c0HVIv     
    
    
    Watching #DoctorWho50thLive #DoctorWho #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/1c0HVIv     
    
    
    @fedwaybuzz what's happening by Fed Way high school? Police and helicopters?!    
    
    
    @FedWayPD what's happening by federal way hs? We are hearing sirens and helicopters    
    
    
    @FalynGarner @TaneaJanine we hear it too.    
    
    
    Pinterest now allows you to pin places. Check out these examples --> http://bit.ly/1i9oAtQ     
    
    
    Just purchased @thesweetstrap for a photog friend. Hopefully she likes it. I know NOTHING abt photography but Liz seems to have a passion    
    
    
    Apparently Brits think Oregon is Washington and Washington is actually a part of Canada http://some.ly/18F3wFH     
    
    
    This is a really great list of Netflix US Documentary Suggestions via @Reddit http://bit.ly/1cvOMrD     
    
    
    Photo: amandapalmer: i broke a lightbulb on the kitchen floor on thanksgiving day. miriam was 6 and... http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wx101dcDe     
    
    
    You stay classy, Ron..... >> Will Ferrell Anchored Local News as Ron Burgundy and It Was Perfect http://bit.ly/186rhbk     
    
    
    Reading #Bossypants. It's hysterical. Tiny Fey's description of getting ready for a photo shoot sounds like something fm the Hunger Games.    
    
    
    I'm at @KeyArenaSeattle for Vampire Weekend, Phoenix, The Head and the Heart, Alt-J and 4 more (Seattle, WA) http://4sq.com/1eMMTbD     
    
    
    Photo: Oldest on the floor? #quitepossibly #nomatter #dthb http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y10Brh5-     
    
    
    Very Powerful ▶ WATCH: How the Media Failed Women in 2013    
    
    
    "Everyone wants to save the world, but no one wants to help mom do the dishes." —P.J. O'Rourke    
    
    
    Checking out @CrowdAlbum the tool used to showcase the massive amount of photos taken at #DTHB . Pretty cool tool. http://alpha.crowdalbum.com/gallery/529d8fd5992cc62a8b000014/Deck-the-Hall-Ball-2013-with-Vampire-Weekend--Phoenix--The-Head-and-the-Heart--Alt-J--Arctic-Monkeys--Lorde--Foals--Tame-Impala_20131203 …    
    
    
    "He who dies with the least toys wins. Because the more you know, the less you need." —Yvon Chouinard    
    
    
    I'm already overwhelmed >> A Simple Year: 12 Months of Guided Simplicity http://bit.ly/18ibd3Y     
    
    
    “Maybe Christmas doesn’t come from a store, maybe Christmas perhaps means a little bit more.” —Dr. Seuss    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @bunnybuddhism when is your book coming out? I really wanna give it to a friend!!    
    
    
    @theangelah yeah, I need to win that    
    
    
    @charleskoh @netflix This is a really great list of Netflix US Documentary Suggestions via @Reddit http://bit.ly/1cvOMrD     
    
    
    @loveourbodies thanks will do!    
    
    
    "What would happen if we all blew this joint? What would the world look like if we all just ate food?..." http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y10kntIh     
    
    
    Photo: Normally I’m a #teasnob but I thought I’d give this #chai a go. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y10lzNrF     
    
    
    Photo: First #satsuma of the season. Hoping it’s yummy… http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y10nTIE5     
    
    
    @JJStrength thanks for the follow, Jake!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Excellent tips on finding people to help via Twitter. Well worth the read: http://bit.ly/1iX3eAb     
    
    
    Anyone know how to get a @Facebook Vanity URL that isn't currently in use, but is "Not Available" none the less?    
    
    
    Nice! --> Gmail Will Never Ask You to 'Display Images Below' Again http://on.mash.to/18GoKmh     
    
    
    Finally signed up for a year's subscription to @PlanToEat . It's a great tool, extremely handy, and their customer service is awesome too.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kristiNseattle thanks!    
    
    
    This is adorable and just what I needed this afteroon: The 25 Most #British Things That Have Ever Been Knitted http://bzfd.it/1dyaoV0  #knit    
    
    
    Movie time! I'm watching #TheHobbitMovie. Join the conversation on #GetGlue http://gtg.lu/Jp4oVI     
    
    
    Photo: The latest in my #tea experiments. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y11BbI3D     
    
    
    @iamron pretty good!    
    
    
    Photo: A recent gift all the way from Burkina Faso in Africa where women go to collect and bring home water... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y11F5xAZ     
    
    
    @moxie_hart Yay! You're going to LOVE it. Promise!    
    
    
    @moxie_hart we all do. The point is to improve and not compare. You'll be surprised at how much you can do    
    
    
    @moxie_hart I was always the slowest.... And the very last to finish. Don't worry, if that happens to you (I doubt it) you'll have support    
    
    
    Watching @Andrew_Solomon 's TED Talk: Depression, the secret we share http://bit.ly/1fpNtMA  . Very insightful. Very uplifting :)    
    
    
    @moxie_hart did you already go?!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @moxie_hart I never got into spin. So painful!    
    
    
    This is pretty handy! >> Is It Better to Buy or Rent? - Interactive Graphic http://nyti.ms/1c4u5Fo     
    
    
    When you tell yourself..... - "I’ll be happy when I’m thin" "I’ll be happy when I eat perfectly" "I’ll be... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y11hG4BG     
    
    
    Reading more about Custom #timelines in TweetDeck http://bit.ly/1fsj0O2     
    
    
    Rumor has it that  @vineapp is going to let its users register a profile URL  in the form of:  http://vine.co/[chosen_name ]    
    
    
    Are you serious?? What Organic Reach?? --> Brands Soon To See Organic Reach Decline on Facebook http://bit.ly/1fMjD60     
    
    
    My first visit. Here for the music. (@ Sorrento Hotel) http://4sq.com/1ftqpwI     
    
    
    It works! --> Grab Photoshop and CS2 For Absolutely Free Right Here http://bit.ly/1ciFdP2     
    
    
    Yuuuuuuuummy (@ Bai Tong Thai Restaurant) http://4sq.com/1gThkks     
    
    
    I'm at Regal Meridian 16 - @regalmovies for The Secret Life of Walter Mitty (2013) (Seattle, WA) w/ 15 others http://4sq.com/JvDria     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    This creative writing workshop in Paris sounds amazzzzzing. ---> http://bit.ly/19NkW3b     
    
    
    Photo: Beachwalk with my pup. Just what I needed. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2y13IgDyJ     
    
    
    I can not live without coffee.    
    
    
    5 Typography Devices to Help Increase Readership by David Ogilvy http://pinterest.com/pin/268316090271631412/ …    
    
    
    @thienkim scoundrels!    
    
    
    @thienkim I need to get a back up for such an emergency. I'm doing good. Just starting off my Monday trying to organize my week :)    
    
    
    Photo: Step 7: Plan ahead for a healthy tomorrow One big barrier to treating oneself well is lack of... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfVSOOD     
    
    
    Rep Orcutt Responds to his INSANE claim that biking is bad for the environment http://sco.lt/7s2vc9  #seabikes    
    
    
    16 Ways Businesses Are Using Twitter Vine  http://sco.lt/7tBK8P     
    
    
    @LoudSeahawksFan yeah, I'm wondering what a realistic solution might be.    
    
    
    @CEM_Social you're welcome! I have here and there. It's a fun tool and I love seeing what brands and businesses have been doing with it.    
    
    
    @CEM_Social I am waiting patiently for it to come out on Droid :)    
    
    
    Carrot Cake Oatmeal - yum! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfVjtP7     
    
    
    @adamholdenbache I noticed 1 of your @socialfresh posts was taken down (22 Social Media Alerts Your Biz Should use) is it posted elsewhere?    
    
    
    Amanda Palmer is a goddess. Watch her TED Talk on: The art of asking http://bit.ly/13C9pSb  (I nearly cried)    
    
    
    Happy Monday everyone! I'm listening to Lily Allen today. It's a Lily Allen day for sure. Yup. #musicmonday    
    
    
    @LoudSeahawksFan I actually fell asleep last night trying to puzzle it out. lol    
    
    
    Photoset: How to properly treat deadlines…… http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxfW60h4     
    
    
    @AdamHoldenBache oh, duh, I didn't check to see if the entire site was working. Sorry if I caused a mini-panic :)    
    
    
    Photo: My neighbor’s homemade ranch dressing and @metmarket croutons made salad the easy choice today.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfWB75J     
    
    
    @MetMarket thank you! Your croutons are like crack.    
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ actually, those are black beans. #nom    
    
    
    @socialfresh @AdamHoldenBache thanks for letting me know. I wanted to link to that article in a blog post. Will wait patiently :)    
    
    
    18 Social & Local Marketing Ideas Based on the Consumer Journey  http://bit.ly/14l7v3U     
    
    
    Photo: Pre-Body Pump. Taking it easy. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfYE80y     
    
    
    Photo: Getting excited for Seattle Bike Expo. Yoga for cyclists sounds awesome. #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfYF2SY     
    
    
    Loving this show. I'm such a geek. http://is.gd/1Z1H7e  #GetGlue @HistoryVikings    
    
    
    Photo: I miss yoga!! I need to get it back into my exercise routine. http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfaPe-P     
    
    
    lol. This is awesome. RT @buzzfeed: This mashup of Nine Inch Nails and "Call Me Maybe" is perfect http://bzfd.it/XKNqmG     
    
    
    @donpower I can help!    
    
    
    @seattleweekly that's more than a slip up! That's stupidity at it's best    
    
    
    @captainchunk I know what you mean. I kept wishing I could rewind time just a bit.    
    
    
    @charlesredell it's a crowded place, maybe they felt bike racks would cause more congestion?    
    
    
    @cascadebicycle I look forward to it. I was just telling @yogaforbikers how much I miss yoga. I need to work it back into my schedule.    
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ it's funny you say that. I planned on adding it and forgot last minute.    
    
    
    How I often feel on my bike ;) -- It's like learning my city all over again #seabikes http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfbgLZm     
    
    
    @Social_Freedom_ @EarlsBellevue I will have to check them out!    
    
    
    @CharlesRedell it's been awhile since I was last at Pike Place. I don't remember car parking either? lol    
    
    
    @CharlesRedell I didn't even realize there was parking there. I thought the cobbled street was just for thru traffic/vendors.    
    
    
    Facebook Is Making The Most Critical Update To News Feed In 7 Years Tomorrow! http://read.bi/14tDgId     
    
    
    @downwarddog agreed. It will be interesting to see how this effects Pages. Prepare for the complaints!    
    
    
    Congrats!! RT @iamqdot: Announcement: BET selected me to perform at their #MusicMatters showcase in NYC May 14th! =) mmmhhhmmm.    
    
    
    Heading out for a 20 mile bike ride. Anyone in #Auburn wanna join me? ;)    
    
    
    Photo: Things that suck: Freezing rain, helmet hair, knee pain. Things that rock: husbands, t-bone steaks,... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfhjwiC     
    
    
    Finished my ride for the day. Freezing rain and wind suuuuck!  #strava #seabikes http://app.strava.com/activities/43446725 …    
    
    
    Photoset: sassypantzz: Wall Piece With 200 Letters, Mikko Kuorinki  Love this. http://tmblr.co/ZRI6wxfjjgzZ     
    
    
    Going to be watching Facebook Livestream Announcement in a few mins... --> http://bit.ly/14yqh82     
    
    
    Waiting to watch this announcement >> Facebook’s Redesign Hopes to Keep Users Engaged - http://nyti.ms/14ytdBt     
    
    
    @iamqdot have you seen this? http://youtu.be/IGH2HEgWppc     
    
    
    So far nothing surprising >> UI consistent with mobile, bigger pictures, richer links, emphasis on visuals etc. #FacebookUpdate    
    
    
    See The New Facebook News Feed http://bit.ly/14yF02M     
    
    
    Google Plus update info complete with photoshop template (nice) http://bit.ly/14yqrMy     
    
    
    How NOT to Have Your Social Media Accounts Hacked http://linkd.in/13J8RKc     
    
    
    @bbangie @howiecohen @evonnebenedict @Martha_Kang you're welcome! I try to stalk as many awesome ppl as possible!    
    
    
    5 Tips to Enhance Your Facebook Graph Search Ranking http://bit.ly/14yA0Lz     
    
    
    Know. Your. Audience >>> Sephora: Our Pinterest followers spend 15X more than our Facebook fans  http://bit.ly/13JyOt1     
    
    
    "Most of all, people matter. Individual human beings with names and wants and interests." http://bit.ly/13L913Q     
    
    
    Photo: Feeling like a bit of a badass! 26.7 miles on a gorgeous day. I may even have a bit of a sunburn.... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfv2mLD     
    
    
    Photo: This is actually a thing. #bikeexpo (at Pier 91 - Smith Cove Terminal) http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfyZzIo     
    
    
    Photo: For big kids. Want. #bikeexpo http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yfyqNU2     
    
    
    Well. Have you? #funnysign http://instagr.am/p/Wsn98yrKVa/     
    
    
    Photo: Well. Have you? #funnysign http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_QbeR     
    
    
    Photo: I love the Burke-Gilman trail! Fun houses and beautiful views. Also, day #2 on a bike is much harder... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_SBig     
    
    
    Photo: My baby. Hoping she’ll take me from Seattle to Portland and back. She still needs a name! http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yf_nl7-     
    
    
    10 Minutes of Prep: 10 Amazing Meals http://pinterest.com/pin/268316090271674550/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Step 8: Eat more fruits and vegetables It’s no surprise that there are many benefits to eating fruits... http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yg1Dwx-     
    
    
    @gigharborlive I'd love to help if you're still looking for a community manager!    
    
    
    @outdoorsnwmag hope I win it! My hubs needs one :)    
    
    
    @cyu888 that explains so much!    
    
    
    @yogadork *sigh* I just HAD to click that. Didn't I? lol    
    
    
    This is cool! RT @bikewa: They're all the buzz at #SXSW: Bikes made out of junked cars http://ow.ly/iL7Pr . 3K preordered #bicycledbikes    
    
    
    @bikewa absolutely the best. Very cool.    
    
    
    Pinterest quietly pops out a fantastic new layout http://bit.ly/ZB8mhC     
    
    
    Photo: Inhaled! #fitfoodie http://tmblr.co/ZkYD2yg3WAx1     
    
    
    I'm watching Vikings (150 others checked-in) http://is.gd/1Z1H7e  #GetGlue @HistoryVikings    
    
    
    