learning actionscript 3... :)    
    
    
    cant believe there was an earthquake in copenhagen    
    
    
    designing games    
    
    
    the first morning cycle and coffee of the day is so good!    
    
    
    is about to start reactivision...    
    
    
    is laughing while still working :)    
    
    
    setting up an exhibition...    
    
    
    enjoying a post exhibition beer with my legendary CIID classmates    
    
    
    leaving copenhagen    
    
    
    looking at the beautiful clear blue skys in scotland    
    
    
    looking froward to meeting durrell bishop    
    
    
    bringing new meaning to everyday objects....hmmmm    
    
    
    @choosenick steve jobs in a an absolute genius!    
    
    
    drinking tea    
    
    
    can networked objects be used for social awareness    
    
    
    storyboarding...    
    
    
    @TessyBritton you may already have it, but there is also an app to use it as a remote control for your itunes music if you have a mac!    
    
    
    reflecting  on today's very useful feedback....    
    
    
    more coffee drinking and concept developing    
    
    
    writing up elderly people project for ciid.dkds.dk    
    
    
    listening to old intersections podcats    
    
    
    heading to bed with a ted talk    
    
    
    designing a science museum exhibit to teach children about environmental responsibility....any advice?    
    
    
    @jbaldwin no its a project at CIID, but out idea is targeted to be a playful exploration/learning tool/installation for children    
    
    
    @jbaldwin i love it!    
    
    
    refreshed after a 15mile cycle and ready to work!    
    
    
    now CIID website is live! http://ciid.dk    
    
    
    Application for next years CIID are open! http://ciid.dk/education/admissions/    
    
    
    trying to find a link between pollution from produce transport and dieing trees    
    
    
    thinking who are my design hero's    
    
    
    trying to get electronics to work    
    
    
    baking shortbread for CIID buddies    
    
    
    @hogsonmaman are you a good old IPD student by any chance?    
    
    
    @hogsonmaman thats crazy! IPD was the best name, i was actually emailing jon the other day,cause i just did a project for the elderly    
    
    
    three hours sleep and back to final prototype    
    
    
    @jbaldwin yes you are completely right, i don't think it sounds hugely inviting initially to undergrads students,IPD had such a ring to it!    
    
    
    preparing for TUI exhibition 2mrw    
    
    
    TUI over. not sleeping for two days..so worth it.    
    
    
    reading up about sustainable design comp in india    
    
    
    thinking about a thesis topic    
    
    
    CIID pilot year microsites are live. check them out http://dkds.ciid.dk    
    
    
    @shawnbot they look awesome don't they! alie and mellis did a great job!    
    
    
    thinking about specific user groups    
    
    
    wondering what tools teachers have to help children read these days...    
    
    
    how do you choose a user group to work with when it is wide open?    
    
    
    @mimi_son this is the story of my life :)    
    
    
    getting confused....do i start with a user group or a broader known problem area.    
    
    
    writing about products V's services    
    
    
    first tiny step towards thesis is over    
    
    
    @Redjotter i've a lot of research around this, but it is specific to people living in elderly homes in cph, not sure if it would be helpful?    
    
    
    how do you talk about 6months of learning in 15minutes    
    
    
    what are the best ways to show what you have learned?!so stuck    
    
    
    up bright and early for a productive day :)    
    
    
    the most beautiful day in Copenhagen...wow!    
    
    
    beautiful cycle to uni today    
    
    
    @jbaldwin it is one of the bonus's of living in copenhagen, the best cycling ever!    
    
    
    about to do work again after a lovely afternoon outdoors    
    
    
    needs to focus on work    
    
    
    check this out. A brilliant organization based in scotland!! http://www.distancelab.org    
    
    
    cylcling in the snow -not as fun as expected    
    
    
    waiting for my review :/    
    
    
    making a Lego USB drive..some might say procrastinating    
    
    
    editing film    
    
    
    @daveIxD Its great to have your support :)    
    
    
    in preparation for day 2......    
    
    
    very excited about exhibiting at NEXT conference    
    
    
    @daveIxD Bill Verplank, taught us design theory at CIID. He was awesome!    
    
    
    exams over and great news about the innovation lab :)    
    
    
    @askrom he was with us for a week, on our panel for our physical comp. review then taught us for 3 full days. he was an amazing inspiration!    
    
    
    annoyed with imovie    
    
    
    looking forward to the DSB/live|work project starting on monday :)    
    
    
    back from mammoth cycle to try clear mammoth hangover    
    
    
    18 miles to be exact!    
    
    
    really enjoying the first day with the Oslo live|work team and DSB    
    
    
    needs an idea for how to encourage sustainability around public transport    
    
    
    designing a service to help educate children on sustainable travel    
    
    
    @everythingiknow that lynsey better be behaving herself!    
    
    
    about to start experience prototyping    
    
    
    @Redjotter i'll collect them together this weekend for you    
    
    
    having a beer whilst refining our user journey :)    
    
    
    is trying not to be tempted to work    
    
    
    very content after lovely Italian risotto watching the snow fall outside    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove ah yeas, i love action script 3, i had the joy of learning it a few weeks back :)    
    
    
    going to go and do work somewhere relaxing and drink coffee while doing so :)    
    
    
    car crash outside our house. its gone mad in fredriksberg    
    
    
    designing a service for children to teach them about sustainable mobility in a school, and it will have a link to parents is a challenge!    
    
    
    anyone done any engaging children projects?    
    
    
    @joshlegend 0-3 yeas that's tough! we are trying to teach them about traveling by more sustainable transport!    
    
    
    @jbaldwin no really engages them, we're designing a toolkit for teachers to educate children on sustainability    
    
    
    @jbaldwin well funny you should say that our idea is to teach children in a way to get them to raise questions with their parents and make.    
    
    
    @jbaldwin then consider the way they change. Create a platform for action, between teacher-children-parents    
    
    
    @jbaldwin the client crit is on fri, so il send you the final presentation once it is over!    
    
    
    @joshlegend yes i remember those days, don't worry it only gets better!tell jon eilidh says organize an IPD to Copenhagen!    
    
    
    @thinkpublic your animation is amazing! :) so beautiful!    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove you can download the old version imovie HD for free, give you more flexibility, its less like a home movie tool!    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove final cut express or adobe premier is pretty easy to get a handle of and can do so much much, great titles, split screens etc    
    
    
    back to being a graphic design sweatshop  monkey for another day    
    
    
    @marcfonteijn a huge amount! we were told at uni by someone from nokia but cant remember now!    
    
    
    my graphic design days are almost over for this project! woo hoo! the end is in sight, just one massive blueprint to  make!    
    
    
    blueprint finished, i'm sure many alterations to make!    
    
    
    live|works guy brought us beer as we work late for presentations. lovely chaps! :)    
    
    
    not long till presentations :)    
    
    
    wow amazing day of presentations and CIID are launching new applications http://ciid.dkds.dk/admissions/    
    
    
    reading article on jaime lerner    
    
    
    blogging about last weeks project    
    
    
    @vanderbeeken I may be a little bias but the course is amazing!    
    
    
    meeting at 8.40 for a surprise visit somewhere    
    
    
    started 5 week service design block today....need to choose between libraries or health care?    
    
    
    @nonlocal nice post :)    
    
    
    writing my first article for http://johnnyholland.org/    
    
    
    @thinkpublic there are many on the course i am on now!some crazy fantastic programmers,but also good designers.    
    
    
    installing twitter widget on my dashboard    
    
    
    @eilidhdickson    
    
    
    watching lift09 presentations    
    
    
    ordered mini moo cards for NEXT exhibition/conference    
    
    
    what do people think about libraries? let me know!    
    
    
    @jbaldwin thats super interesting we were talking about how amazon gives you a very personal service, recommending what you might like..    
    
    
    libraries libraries.....what do people perceive them to be?    
    
    
    freitag bar :)    
    
    
    going to look at flowers at the botanic garden, maybe get some inspiration    
    
    
    blogging about out ezio manzini lecture at ciid    
    
    
    heading to the jungle for some user research    
    
    
    writing up research findings    
    
    
    starting to edit film at ten to ten, not good practice    
    
    
    off to the airport for research in people coming to copenhagen    
    
    
    had a productive day synthesizing insights and writing "how might we statements"about to make service frame work    
    
    
    having to write a design challenge with a fried brain..not easy    
    
    
    finished design challenges....now blogging about them :)    
    
    
    feels privileged, Brian Rink= all time super star inspiration http://tinyurl.com/bpospy he is just incredible!    
    
    
    baking... :)    
    
    
    ready for a day of brainstorming...    
    
    
    brainstorming facilitation...check    
    
    
    blogging about brainstorming festival...http://lovelearn.wordpress.com    
    
    
    meet the food you eat.....
http://tinyurl.com/btazsc    
    
    
    more publicity...http://tinyurl.com/dyf3jv    
    
    
    about to do Meet the food you eat press pack for NEXT...http://www.innovationlab.net/da/next    
    
    
    beautiful day outside...excited about my morning cycle to the studio,after my lovely coffee im drinking    
    
    
    need coffee....    
    
    
    drinking tea and updating blog...mentally preparing for more scenario building 2mrw.    
    
    
    @jbaldwin it is very good isn't it!i'm hopefully meeting the founder in a couple of weeks at NEXT conference, so will report back!    
    
    
    MTFYE on pervasive shopping :)http://pervasiveshopping.wordpress.com/    
    
    
    @ileddigital i must book my flights for this :)    
    
    
    school on a sunday...fun times :)    
    
    
    @wildwoman your going to dundee! im so jealous :(    
    
    
    @designthinkers you should look up samsø island in Copenhagen, it is a sustainable island that has been co-created by its residents    
    
    
    14 hour day...nice    
    
    
    experience prototyping new library services has begun    
    
    
    reflecting on jennie winhall's talk she gave at CIID today    
    
    
    preparing for a rainy cycle home from the designskole    
    
    
    @chrismonnier the answer is no i'm afraid :( but it is an awesome city!    
    
    
    filming library video    
    
    
    so much so do, so little time    
    
    
    meet the food you eat is going to be on TV2! good morning Denmark here we come!    
    
    
    last week of service design course, presentation tues, thurs and fri.....last push!    
    
    
    if only you could CRTL S electronics! long night ahead preparing for good morning denmark,  http://tinyurl.com/cz3wfe    
    
    
    tv2 studio was great fun, and the scale performed brilliantly!    
    
    
    back in Scotland for a few days after anothere amazing 3 months at CIID    
    
    
    working on portfolio    
    
    
    can't move after family meal    
    
    
    finally written an article for johnny holland    
    
    
    @multikev its on personal informatics,i supposed to do it about three months ago!when you were doing the one on our data viz class!    
    
    
    off out into the sun!    
    
    
    preparing to go back to Copenhagen tomorrow, then its thesis time.......    
    
    
    @vorgitsu what is this??!!    
    
    
    back in the sun in copenhagen    
    
    
    going to the beach...    
    
    
    editing..    
    
    
    @sicamp is it a bar you want for it?    
    
    
    thinking about after CIID    
    
    
    reboot meeting    
    
    
    creating personal profiles    
    
    
    brilliant talk by Robert Fabricant http://vimeo.com/3730382 starting point for my thesis.    
    
    
    2 bike punctures, big picnic, one bike crash, lots of frisbie, danish countryside and amazing people :)    
    
    
    updating blog.    
    
    
    @Redjotter me too!    
    
    
    started thesis    
    
    
    nap time was not sufficient enough    
    
    
    @wildwoman i'm sure Alie would have a few stories to tell..    
    
    
    writing up notes from first research session    
    
    
    After a 2 year break it's time to reunite with twitter    
    
    
    planning for parents arriving in copenhagen    
    
    
    up early...parents arriving soon :)    
    
    
    does anyone know of any diabetes initiatives in Boston?    
    
    
    Looking forward to @hxdconf with @hellerohdea    
    
    
    Switch to teaching mode for 3 days with @ishacbertran #carboncopy #CIID    
    
    
    @hxdconf does anyone know someone working at #the full yield. Would love to talk to them about their work    
    
    
    @adrane that would be great. Thank you! My email Is e.dickson@ciid.dk    
    
    
    on top secret industry project so no blogging for the next 2 weeks    
    
    
    re-design portfolio http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk let me know any feedback/mistakes/errors/typo's you find!    
    
    
    @mayonissen not yet, soon though :-)    
    
    
    building storyboards    
    
    
    presentation 2 of industry project, 2 to go!    
    
    
    #CIID is hiring a project and research manager. http://ciid.dk/about/jobs/project-and-research-manager/ …    
    
    
    "The NHS is full of brilliant people with brilliant ideas" #NHS #Bottomupinnovation #thewayitshouldbe http://www.challengeprizes.institute.nhs.uk/     
    
    
    awesome graphic notes by @cassiemc from #hxdconf. http://bit.ly/HjE8sH . @hellerohdea you should check it out    
    
    
    http://soundcloud.com/aretive/deadsynth …    
    
    
    @nonlocal great find!    
    
    
    @mayonissen I feel that pain    
    
    
    Could get very used to this    
    
    
    “@FastCoDesign: The World’s First Commercial #3D Chocolate Printer Is On Sale http://bit.ly/JpEyt6 ” this ones for you @hellerohdea    
    
    
    @mayonissen its the best course in the world!    
    
    
    amazing video for 2012 olympics http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FMunV1Y4X2o&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    @mayonissen well just drop me an email if you need any help or questions answered, my email is on eilidhdickson.co.uk    
    
    
    @emeasee .....Urbbi?? http://www.fastcodesign.com/1669604/talk-to-your-plants-for-dummy-proof-gardening-using-a-sensor-and-an-iphone-app …    
    
    
    “@designboom: pantone unveils 336 new colors http://dlvr.it/1Tf2n0  - #design” #patonelove    
    
    
    deadline 4hrs 40 mins...no sleep    
    
    
    @johnlync you are my hero    
    
    
    CIID wins Knowledge Relay (Videnstafet) for Denmark's most innovative and ambitious knowledge enterprise. http://ciid.dk/?p=13846  #CIID    
    
    
    looking back over old twitter/blog/website posts - I was much more proactive when i was a student #thismustchange    
    
    
    Does anyone in London want to try and buy me a Nike Fuel band tomorrow?    
    
    
    @krissus amazing find!!!!!!    
    
    
    @johnlync i'm sending you a direct contact for SF    
    
    
    @ishacbertran on @FastCoDesign http://www.fastcodesign.com/1669665/watch-this-ingenious-ui-idea-for-dragging-files-from-your-phone-to-computer …    
    
    
    @johnlync now you have me thinking....    
    
    
    Back to thesis work    
    
    
    looking forward to going to see the K3 Interaction Design end of year show    
    
    
    catching up on very overdue blogging    
    
    
    sweden tomorrow :)    
    
    
    IDEO considers the future of news.....http://bit.ly/AZWqD    
    
    
    @jeroenvangeel unfortunately not,i would have love to.Dave Malouf is giving us a lecture though,you should come visit the CIID studio!    
    
    
    @designthinkers you should come to this! CIID are going to be there acting as "consultants" to help people develop & prototype their ideas!    
    
    
    writing "how might we statements" idea time soon!    
    
    
    @daveixd looking forward to it :)    
    
    
    http://reflectionaction.com  => a side project I've been working on with @hellerohdea  Check it out! Any feedback is welcomed #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    Amazing first day with Brian Rink as head of consulting #CIID #Consulting    
    
    
    @emeasee Thanks Mac!!!    
    
    
    Marker Happiness - a tribute to our amazing drawing utensils: http://reflectionaction.com/?p=364  #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    @DesignThinkers Thanks for the mention Arne! @hellerohdea @reflectioninact    
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaD9jcrbnN/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaJkaErbo_/     
    
    
    Step 2 - digital #reflectioninaction http://instagr.am/p/LaS0rMrbr7/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaWk2nrbs1/     
    
    
    Making a feeling tangible  http://instagr.am/p/Lag5Marbgv/     
    
    
    @richardshed I just saw this now!!! Anyway looking forward to seeing you at CIID tomorrow!    
    
    
    A new post by @ReflectionInAct. Can you bottle motivation? - a design provocation. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=465  #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    @johnlync nice find!! @ReflectionInAct    
    
    
    Free Keynote mockup templates for prototyping iPhone, iPad, Android and Web apps #design #UX #mockups http://keynotopia.com/keynote-mockups-templates/ … via @keynotopia    
    
    
    Interviewing for Interaction Design Programme 2013. How time flies! #CIID @CIIDnews    
    
    
    @everythingiknow thank you rory!!!!! @ReflectionInAct @hellerohdea    
    
    
    tracking behaviour to understand communication with family    
    
    
    @wildwoman what sort of charts, project planning?    
    
    
    @wildwoman we might have some good ones at CIID    
    
    
    CIID student project featured on @FastCoDesign: Machine Scans Twitter For Mentions Of Fruit&turns them to smoothies http://bit.ly/Kdwzzy ”    
    
    
    Great lecture from Matt Jones today    
    
    
    @marcinignac sketch up?    
    
    
    brainstorming festival commences in 30 minutes, armed with markers, post-its and goodies :)    
    
    
    @daveixd so well said!    
    
    
    “@daveixd: Stop designing for clients & start creating with partners.” ... The way it should be.    
    
    
    NEW POST @ReflectionInAct --> Digital Materiality - An Exploration: http://reflectionaction.com/?p=558     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/MiZ-x0Lbim/     
    
    
    time to start concept scenarios after brainstorming    
    
    
    New inspiration on @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?page_id=114  #nonintentionaldesign #relfectioninaction    
    
    
    @tommetcalfe I'm sure if I remember correctly there will be a lot of nice 3d renders of cars, bikes and home gadgets ;) #noinvention    
    
    
    Off for an injection of music for the day at roskilde @orangefeeling    
    
    
    @tommetcalfe yes you should come... Visit CIID!    
    
    
    presentation on monday with external faculty....looking forward to a fresh perspective    
    
    
    New post on @ReflectionInAct about low tech tracking tools. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=599  #reflectioninaction #personalinformatics #trackingtools    
    
    
    Sorry for an spam people are getting from me. My account has been hacked. Trying to sort it out now.    
    
    
    @dianakeeling what do we run on saturday??! So i know what to do during the week :-)    
    
    
    excited to hear the @Core77Awards results for the speculative category. Come on @CIIDnews!!!!!!!!!! #CIID #windowtotheworld #toyota    
    
    
    @dianakeeling neither am I just now :-) trying to get back into after a lazy period! but that sounds lovely! excited for friday!!!    
    
    
    @dianakeeling do you want anything Danish brought to you?! :-) (apart from tobias)    
    
    
    Congratulations to @yufangised for coming runner up in the student interaction category in the @Core77Awards    
    
    
    just watched matt jones at fbtb..AMAZING! http://johnnyholland.tv/    
    
    
    presentation making for review tomorrow: feeling very inspired after watching matt jones at from business to buttons    
    
    
    Some new urban inspiration on @ReflectionInAct from our travels in Pittsburgh http://reflectionaction.com/?page_id=114  #reflectioninaction    
    
    
    New Urban Inspiration: DIY bike repair station in wholefoods @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?p=658 
#relfectioninaction #pittsburgh    
    
    
    New Urban Inspiration: Well informed or too elaborate road signage? @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?p=655 
#relfectioninaction #pittsburgh    
    
    
    Doing Finishing touches to presentation for final project review http://twitpic.com/833gu    
    
    
    It’s easy to believe our own excuses, particularly if they’re good ones. #motivationishard    
    
    
    Interesting.....What do the most successful people accomplish before breakfast? @FastCompany http://bit.ly/MzFIDq     
    
    
    "Turning a desire into a ritual requires willpower" #sotrue    
    
    
    co creation event in copenhagen on thursday http://copenhagencocreation.com/    
    
    
    2 days to go!! http://www.reboot.dk/    
    
    
    CIID Consulting is proud to announce the launch of a new section of our website devoted to sharing the methods & tools 
http://ciid.dk/tools_workshops/ …    
    
    
    @paulmmay Thanks Pau! Please share it with anyone who you think will find it useful    
    
    
    'super shuttle' more like 'disaster shuttle'    
    
    
    @mayonissen @hellerohdea    
    
    
    @mayonissen @hellerohdea yes... Minor travel hiccup - we leave again in a few hours...    
    
    
    Back home in CPH after my first missed flight of my life - exhausted but inspired to come up with some new travel service ideas.    
    
    
    I love jetlag #nocturnal    
    
    
    first day at #reboot11=awesome!    
    
    
    day 1@reboot: Write up for the CIID Open Lab
http://bit.ly/NWOYE    
    
    
    can't believe about michael jackson
http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/americas/8119951.stm    
    
    
    reboot day 2 write up for CIID......
http://bit.ly/5SNNI    
    
    
    #Reboot11 write up for CIID
http://bit.ly/ne1yX    
    
    
    CIID Industry trip tomorrow, Bang & Oulfsen, Lego and Danfoss    
    
    
    on the way to legoland avec CIID    
    
    
    Looking for a good recruitment company that can help getting research respondents in Savannah, GA. Any tips welcomed!    
    
    
    New post on @ReflectionInAct. Urban Play. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=673  #reflectioninaction #exercise #urban #babysteps    
    
    
    @mayonissen his presentation at Reboot was amazing!    
    
    
    Presenting with @hellerohdea  to @DesignDundeeabout CIID Consulting on the 21st Sep. Come along ! http://bit.ly/Q6tfdQ     
    
    
    @TessyBritton I will be in London next wk with @hellerohdea (23-28th Sept) Let know if you have time for a coffee    
    
    
    @TessyBritton @hellerohdea I leave on the 28th to go o Scotland.Will email you once i know my definite travel plans. Enjoy France!    
    
    
    I'll see you tomorrow Scotland. In the mean time some inspiration - EPIC must see video. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cj6ho1-G6tw …    
    
    
    Nice write up on @hellerohdea and my talk at @DesignDundee http://masterofdesignforservices.com/2012/09/21/ciid-consulting/ …    
    
    
    @DesignDundee Thank for having us, it was a pleasure!    
    
    
    @DesignDundee some of you were asking @hellerohdea and I about personal projects we do. Here you go @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/     
    
    
    CIID got the funding for year 2....woo hoo!    
    
    
    @wildwoman everyone is over the moon!end of yr exhibition 27th Aug-6th sept :)    
    
    
    A week of prototyping in the UK with @hellerohdea done. Next up Scotland - Copenhagen - New York - North Carolina - Georgia.    
    
    
    @katerishka @hellerohdea the most fun part will be the reunion in Copenhagen next weekend :-)    
    
    
    Scottish wedding :-) http://instagr.am/p/QMr2x3JBpK/     
    
    
    @mayonissen will you be in NY on the 7th and 8th (this month) thats when @hellerohdea and I will be there    
    
    
    @mayonissen there will be a forum opening up soon for you :)    
    
    
    @CIIDnews first official reunion for the Interaction Design Programme! Come on the PILOT YEAR!!!!!!!    
    
    
    butterflies #ciidreunion #pilotyear    
    
    
    pleased our project is on http://www.servicedesigntools.org/tools/24    
    
    
    New York complete. Now Charlotte, NC    
    
    
    Missing my playground http://www.nike.com/us/en_us/c/running/nike-running-lunarglide-plus …
#running #Copenhagen #builtupenergy    
    
    
    Last day in Charlotte. Tomorrow Savannah, GA #EPIC2012    
    
    
    eilidh likes @mimi's graphic design advice :)    
    
    
    Savannah.    
    
    
    A new start up by the very talented @emeasee http://ajoto.com/     
    
    
    @epiconference what pace are you planning to run at?! :-) #epiconference    
    
    
    Awesome inspiring keynote by Emily Pilloton #epiconference http://instagr.am/p/QzmQKtrbn4/     
    
    
    EPIC 2012@thelucas theatre #epiconference   @ Lucas Theatre for the Arts http://instagr.am/p/Q0Mn3jLbhZ/     
    
    
    @daveixd yes! CIIDconsulting are presenting an artifact, we are working on client work on wed but keep me posted if your around tomorrow    
    
    
    EPIC2012 are rocking the word clouds #epiconference   @ Lucas Theatre for the Arts http://instagr.am/p/Q0QuE2Lbkn/     
    
    
    A cool new online photobooth project by my friend Sid who works at LEGO. Still in Beta Version, but try it out...
http://www.snippic.com     
    
    
    Buddy - a digital tool to support therapy services, created by @sidekickstudios http://www.buddyapp.co.uk/     
    
    
    The average American physician interrupt their patient in 14 seconds  http://instagr.am/p/Q2qo5jLbtA/     
    
    
    From the awesome @daimyoon: project SONIVIVI has been selected for @IxDAwards 2013 shortlist!.”    
    
    
    shortlist for 2013 @IxDAwards Announced! http://ow.ly/eCihX ... and there are 8 @CIIDnews student entries!!    
    
    
    @Redjotter you are definitely in Scandinavia somewhere :)    
    
    
    2 days. 8 hours sleep. Tiered. #jetlag #deadlines    
    
    
    paper to pixels    
    
    
    "This is why I love working with you on this project... Because it makes me think outside of my normal......" #toughweekmadebetter #client    
    
    
    @stephfulke I'm actually going to be in Ireland for a wedding! How long you in town for?    
    
    
    Impressed by @CIIDnews IDP industry presentations for Novo Nordisk. Great thinking happening in the house.    
    
    
    @stephfulke ah I though you meant November. I should be around then :)    
    
    
    @ileddigital this is awesome :)    
    
    
    Bye bye @ishacbertran I'm going to miss you and our geeky design chats.  @ alie's house http://instagr.am/p/RuCIGsrbob/     
    
    
    @ishacbertran @elaineygianni new documentaries screening over the next few days in NYC at @DOCNYCfest http://www.docnyc.net/films-events/#all …”    
    
    
    Go go CIID! “@IxDAwards: And so it begins! The jurors are gathered in NYC to determine the winners for the 2013 Interaction Awards!...”    
    
    
    A lot of runners #geek #training #earlysundaymorning http://instagr.am/p/R4dc7BLbu3/     
    
    
    great work by @ishacbertran “Flaps, fast and contextual web browsing: http://ishback.com/lab/flaps/flaps.html …”    
    
    
    'Vision, blueprint, strategy' #lifeasadesignconsultant    
    
    
    At last! A tracking device for non super users  http://trib.al/bNIHaI ”    
    
    
    “@odannyboy: Intriguing product in a crowded space: Shine http://www.indiegogo.com/misfitshine  Watch how it syncs data! #microinteractions”    
    
    
    Amazing! 
“@novonordisktbl: A beautiful #blue as night falls on #WDD. Copenhagen Opera House shines for #WDD2012 pic.twitter.com/UlNllf3S”    
    
    
    back to learning flash for the day    
    
    
    Quite proud of myself that I ran 190km in November. #backinthegame    
    
    
    A winter morning http://instagr.am/p/SzjsVGLbrK/     
    
    
    Massive congratulations to @daimyoon for being announced as a winner in the 'empowering' category for this years IxDA Awards!    
    
    
    Archiving my design life    
    
    
    “@IxDA: 2013 @IxDAwards Winners Announced! http://goo.gl/vkdBk ” and CIID's @daimyoon is a winner!!!!!!    
    
    
    Good luck to all the #IDP2012 students with their final presentations this week!    
    
    
    @DesignDundee a big Happy Holiday to you all from @hellerohdea and @eilidhdickson from CIID Consulting http://ciid.dk/holidays2012/     
    
    
    Very Happy to be speaking about 'Understanding Networks of Diabetes Care' @hxdconf this year with @hellerohdea #CIID #HXDconf    
    
    
    @HolidayCollider tis the season for #bows and #snow http://tellart.com/holiday/2012  (via @tellart)    
    
    
    Thanks to @MiniPagura and @johnlync an afternoon of brainstorming is complete #ciidconsulting    
    
    
    Craving America. Roll on @hxdconf in march #HXDconf    
    
    
    -6 degrees, piercing blue sky, 21k run - good Sunday morning #takethatcold    
    
    
    CIID website temporarily down    
    
    
    @mayonissen not too sure what the problem is..in the process of being sorted though!how was thinkpublic?    
    
    
    Preparing presentation for @hxdconf 'understanding networks of diabetes care' #HxD2013 #ciidconsulting pic.twitter.com/DeDUvnI7    
    
    
    Progressing... #HxD2013 pic.twitter.com/pJSrVXxH    
    
    
    The moment you want to quit is the moment you need to keep pushing #marathontraining    
    
    
    Via @novonordisk: First-Ever Guidelines for Children With Type 2 Diabetes. Scary but interesting. http://diabetes.webmd.com/news/20130125/guidelines-kids-diabetes ….    
    
    
    @mrettig just read your thoughts on the 'connecting' film. I am with you 100% of the way! http://www.ixda.org/node/33654     
    
    
    I would love some advice on good running routes in boston from any locals attending @hxdconf this year #boston #running #HxD2013    
    
    
    Will be in New York from the 26-28th of March. Let me know if are around and want to have a coffee/beer etc..    
    
    
    CV overhall #longoverdue    
    
    
    There are over 47000 products and no seasons in an average American supermarket #sigh #    
    
    
    New York next Monday to Friday. Message me if your around    
    
    
    A weekend of presentation building begins    
    
    
    2 week travel Itinerary starting tomorrow. New York - Copenhagen - Boston - New York - Copenhagen    
    
    
    AMAZING to see you @mayonissen @ishacbertran @elaineygianni. Now a few days in CPH then to Boston to present @hxdconf with @hellerohdea    
    
    
    Question to the world… What is the most innovative, self sustaining business model you have ever encountered/heard of?    
    
    
    Arrived in Boston with @hellerohdea for @hxdconf #hxdconf #hxd13    
    
    
    Hear how research builds empathy in organizations come to 'understanding networks of diabetes care' at 3.40 @hxdconf #hxd2013 #HXDconf    
    
    
    @skrugman where are you?    
    
    
    @skrugman ballroom a with Dustin    
    
    
    @sean__burke nice to connect! Hope your enjoying the conference    
    
    
    Missing New York's charm already #takemeback    
    
    
    @avantgame I saw ur talk at HxD + wanted to say it was AMAZING! The highlight of the conference & such an inspiration for a fellow designer.    
    
    
    Must see TED Talk. Jane McGonigal: The game that can give you 10 extra years of life. http://www.ted.com/talks/jane_mcgonigal_the_game_that_can_give_you_10_extra_years_of_life.html …    
    
    
    @chrisallick I just realized I wasn't following yo.How could that be?! I've been missing out! PS. When you coming to CPH?    
    
    
    CIID Final Year Exhibition
http://bit.ly/YClaV    
    
    
    YouTube's ready to select a winner #aprilfool http://youtu.be/H542nLTTbu0 ”    
    
    
    Homework to do…1) Bring an object that represents CIID 2) Think of one anecdote that to you summarizes the spirit of CIID #CIID #rebranding    
    
    
    CIID future strategy meeting #rebranding http://instagram.com/p/Xo2sVSrbvt/     
    
    
    @cbehrlich    
    
    
    @hellerohdea and I talking about “Understanding Networks of Diabetes Care” @hxdconf http://vimeo.com/63539162     
    
    
    @mayonissen i haven't seen a segway here in 11 months!    
    
    
    @mayonissen Copenhagen Bliss    
    
    
    starting final presentation....the end is in sight!    
    
    
    has has finished her final  CIID exam, presenting to bill moggridge! feels good!    
    
    
    @wildwoman it was great, i cant believe its over! we will see what the jury  have to say tomorrow!    
    
    
    @mayonissen i think it went well! we will see what the verdict is tomorrow though! and then to party!    
    
    
    what is a good software i can download to compress videos?    
    
    
    @mivesto  thanks for the mention    
    
    
    @mayonissen theres a cool cafe in vesterø called bang and jensons with free wi fi :) 130 Istedgade    
    
    
    @mayonissen im still in recovery mode...but will keep you posted with any plans :)    
    
    
    last day of the CIID Pilot Year exhibition tomorrow!    
    
    
    @mayonissen i think you need to get some our addresses :)    
    
    
    @mayonissen we have to take down the exhibition at 5 im afraid    
    
    
    Toronto Next week for 4 weeks with @johnlynch. Any tips? Running Routes? Design meet ups?    
    
    
    New York from the 16th-20th of October. Who's around?    
    
    
    @mayonissen the laundromat cafe of course!    
    
    
    1 interview away from being with @elaineygianni and @ishacbertran    
    
    
    where are the hipster shops in toronto. @johnlync and I need sneakers    
    
    
    Sync your files online and across computers with @Dropbox. 2GB account is free! http://bit.ly/p0oUr    
    
    
    updating website....http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk/thesis.html    
    
    
    @CarolineArvids1 Welcome Back!    
    
    
    @CarolineArvids1 have a good day at the conference representing @CIIDnews #ciidconsulting    
    
    
    presentation preparation..    
    
    
    #CIID students rocking the @IxDAwards once again with 6 short listed entries!
http://www.ixda.org/awards     
    
    
    Jawbone talking about "the internet of me" http://www.fastcodesign.com/homepage/2013/11/12 …    
    
    
    Come see the hottest interaction design talent around at the #CIID end of year exhibition. http://ciid.dk/2013/12/12/end-of-year-exhibition-2013/ …    
    
    
    “@CIIDnews: 20 Students - 13 Countries. CIID invites you to join us for the end-of-year exhibition: http://ciid.dk/?p=25441 ”    
    
    
    Experimenting with AMAZING CIID students! #ciid http://instagram.com/p/g_d2cNrbpJ/     
    
    
    A hugely inspirational video about interviewing people while they run. by @goodgym #theunners
http://goodgym.org/therunners/     
    
    
    long awaited news update on http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk    
    
    
    Worst. Idea. Ever http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-scotland-politics-25088251 …    
    
    
    Big discussions at CIID Consulting #rebranding @ CIID http://instagram.com/p/hNvF-zrbpG/     
    
    
    November is over. December challenge begins: Run.every.day.    
    
    
    "We bring novelty in the way we do things" #simonamaschi #ciid @CIIDnews    
    
    
    Good food for thought at the CIID exams "What's an emotional or behavioral prototype" @mrettig    
    
    
    final project on servicedesigntools http://servicedesigntools.org/tools/35    
    
    
    @PaddyStevenson we think, by charles leadbeater or the classic....one of don normans books.    
    
    
    updating portfolio with Novo project    
    
    
    Off to madrid to help teach design processes/methods/prototyping :)    
    
    
    house hunting...for the first time in 15 months in Copenhagen..I obviously been too lucky before    
    
    
    India for 16 days, see you soon copenhagen    
    
    
    learning actionscript 3... :)    
    
    
    cant believe there was an earthquake in copenhagen    
    
    
    designing games    
    
    
    the first morning cycle and coffee of the day is so good!    
    
    
    is about to start reactivision...    
    
    
    is laughing while still working :)    
    
    
    setting up an exhibition...    
    
    
    enjoying a post exhibition beer with my legendary CIID classmates    
    
    
    leaving copenhagen    
    
    
    looking at the beautiful clear blue skys in scotland    
    
    
    looking froward to meeting durrell bishop    
    
    
    bringing new meaning to everyday objects....hmmmm    
    
    
    @choosenick steve jobs in a an absolute genius!    
    
    
    drinking tea    
    
    
    can networked objects be used for social awareness    
    
    
    storyboarding...    
    
    
    @TessyBritton you may already have it, but there is also an app to use it as a remote control for your itunes music if you have a mac!    
    
    
    reflecting  on today's very useful feedback....    
    
    
    more coffee drinking and concept developing    
    
    
    writing up elderly people project for ciid.dkds.dk    
    
    
    listening to old intersections podcats    
    
    
    heading to bed with a ted talk    
    
    
    designing a science museum exhibit to teach children about environmental responsibility....any advice?    
    
    
    @jbaldwin no its a project at CIID, but out idea is targeted to be a playful exploration/learning tool/installation for children    
    
    
    @jbaldwin i love it!    
    
    
    refreshed after a 15mile cycle and ready to work!    
    
    
    now CIID website is live! http://ciid.dk    
    
    
    Application for next years CIID are open! http://ciid.dk/education/admissions/    
    
    
    trying to find a link between pollution from produce transport and dieing trees    
    
    
    thinking who are my design hero's    
    
    
    trying to get electronics to work    
    
    
    baking shortbread for CIID buddies    
    
    
    @hogsonmaman are you a good old IPD student by any chance?    
    
    
    @hogsonmaman thats crazy! IPD was the best name, i was actually emailing jon the other day,cause i just did a project for the elderly    
    
    
    three hours sleep and back to final prototype    
    
    
    @jbaldwin yes you are completely right, i don't think it sounds hugely inviting initially to undergrads students,IPD had such a ring to it!    
    
    
    preparing for TUI exhibition 2mrw    
    
    
    TUI over. not sleeping for two days..so worth it.    
    
    
    reading up about sustainable design comp in india    
    
    
    thinking about a thesis topic    
    
    
    CIID pilot year microsites are live. check them out http://dkds.ciid.dk    
    
    
    @shawnbot they look awesome don't they! alie and mellis did a great job!    
    
    
    thinking about specific user groups    
    
    
    wondering what tools teachers have to help children read these days...    
    
    
    how do you choose a user group to work with when it is wide open?    
    
    
    @mimi_son this is the story of my life :)    
    
    
    getting confused....do i start with a user group or a broader known problem area.    
    
    
    writing about products V's services    
    
    
    first tiny step towards thesis is over    
    
    
    @Redjotter i've a lot of research around this, but it is specific to people living in elderly homes in cph, not sure if it would be helpful?    
    
    
    how do you talk about 6months of learning in 15minutes    
    
    
    what are the best ways to show what you have learned?!so stuck    
    
    
    up bright and early for a productive day :)    
    
    
    the most beautiful day in Copenhagen...wow!    
    
    
    beautiful cycle to uni today    
    
    
    @jbaldwin it is one of the bonus's of living in copenhagen, the best cycling ever!    
    
    
    about to do work again after a lovely afternoon outdoors    
    
    
    needs to focus on work    
    
    
    check this out. A brilliant organization based in scotland!! http://www.distancelab.org    
    
    
    cylcling in the snow -not as fun as expected    
    
    
    waiting for my review :/    
    
    
    making a Lego USB drive..some might say procrastinating    
    
    
    editing film    
    
    
    @daveIxD Its great to have your support :)    
    
    
    in preparation for day 2......    
    
    
    very excited about exhibiting at NEXT conference    
    
    
    @daveIxD Bill Verplank, taught us design theory at CIID. He was awesome!    
    
    
    exams over and great news about the innovation lab :)    
    
    
    @askrom he was with us for a week, on our panel for our physical comp. review then taught us for 3 full days. he was an amazing inspiration!    
    
    
    annoyed with imovie    
    
    
    looking forward to the DSB/live|work project starting on monday :)    
    
    
    back from mammoth cycle to try clear mammoth hangover    
    
    
    18 miles to be exact!    
    
    
    really enjoying the first day with the Oslo live|work team and DSB    
    
    
    needs an idea for how to encourage sustainability around public transport    
    
    
    designing a service to help educate children on sustainable travel    
    
    
    @everythingiknow that lynsey better be behaving herself!    
    
    
    about to start experience prototyping    
    
    
    @Redjotter i'll collect them together this weekend for you    
    
    
    having a beer whilst refining our user journey :)    
    
    
    is trying not to be tempted to work    
    
    
    very content after lovely Italian risotto watching the snow fall outside    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove ah yeas, i love action script 3, i had the joy of learning it a few weeks back :)    
    
    
    going to go and do work somewhere relaxing and drink coffee while doing so :)    
    
    
    car crash outside our house. its gone mad in fredriksberg    
    
    
    designing a service for children to teach them about sustainable mobility in a school, and it will have a link to parents is a challenge!    
    
    
    anyone done any engaging children projects?    
    
    
    @joshlegend 0-3 yeas that's tough! we are trying to teach them about traveling by more sustainable transport!    
    
    
    @jbaldwin no really engages them, we're designing a toolkit for teachers to educate children on sustainability    
    
    
    @jbaldwin well funny you should say that our idea is to teach children in a way to get them to raise questions with their parents and make.    
    
    
    @jbaldwin then consider the way they change. Create a platform for action, between teacher-children-parents    
    
    
    @jbaldwin the client crit is on fri, so il send you the final presentation once it is over!    
    
    
    @joshlegend yes i remember those days, don't worry it only gets better!tell jon eilidh says organize an IPD to Copenhagen!    
    
    
    @thinkpublic your animation is amazing! :) so beautiful!    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove you can download the old version imovie HD for free, give you more flexibility, its less like a home movie tool!    
    
    
    @giorgio_giove final cut express or adobe premier is pretty easy to get a handle of and can do so much much, great titles, split screens etc    
    
    
    back to being a graphic design sweatshop  monkey for another day    
    
    
    @marcfonteijn a huge amount! we were told at uni by someone from nokia but cant remember now!    
    
    
    my graphic design days are almost over for this project! woo hoo! the end is in sight, just one massive blueprint to  make!    
    
    
    blueprint finished, i'm sure many alterations to make!    
    
    
    live|works guy brought us beer as we work late for presentations. lovely chaps! :)    
    
    
    not long till presentations :)    
    
    
    wow amazing day of presentations and CIID are launching new applications http://ciid.dkds.dk/admissions/    
    
    
    reading article on jaime lerner    
    
    
    blogging about last weeks project    
    
    
    @vanderbeeken I may be a little bias but the course is amazing!    
    
    
    meeting at 8.40 for a surprise visit somewhere    
    
    
    started 5 week service design block today....need to choose between libraries or health care?    
    
    
    @nonlocal nice post :)    
    
    
    writing my first article for http://johnnyholland.org/    
    
    
    @thinkpublic there are many on the course i am on now!some crazy fantastic programmers,but also good designers.    
    
    
    installing twitter widget on my dashboard    
    
    
    @eilidhdickson    
    
    
    watching lift09 presentations    
    
    
    ordered mini moo cards for NEXT exhibition/conference    
    
    
    what do people think about libraries? let me know!    
    
    
    @jbaldwin thats super interesting we were talking about how amazon gives you a very personal service, recommending what you might like..    
    
    
    libraries libraries.....what do people perceive them to be?    
    
    
    freitag bar :)    
    
    
    going to look at flowers at the botanic garden, maybe get some inspiration    
    
    
    blogging about out ezio manzini lecture at ciid    
    
    
    heading to the jungle for some user research    
    
    
    writing up research findings    
    
    
    starting to edit film at ten to ten, not good practice    
    
    
    off to the airport for research in people coming to copenhagen    
    
    
    had a productive day synthesizing insights and writing "how might we statements"about to make service frame work    
    
    
    having to write a design challenge with a fried brain..not easy    
    
    
    finished design challenges....now blogging about them :)    
    
    
    feels privileged, Brian Rink= all time super star inspiration http://tinyurl.com/bpospy he is just incredible!    
    
    
    baking... :)    
    
    
    ready for a day of brainstorming...    
    
    
    brainstorming facilitation...check    
    
    
    blogging about brainstorming festival...http://lovelearn.wordpress.com    
    
    
    meet the food you eat.....
http://tinyurl.com/btazsc    
    
    
    more publicity...http://tinyurl.com/dyf3jv    
    
    
    about to do Meet the food you eat press pack for NEXT...http://www.innovationlab.net/da/next    
    
    
    beautiful day outside...excited about my morning cycle to the studio,after my lovely coffee im drinking    
    
    
    need coffee....    
    
    
    drinking tea and updating blog...mentally preparing for more scenario building 2mrw.    
    
    
    @jbaldwin it is very good isn't it!i'm hopefully meeting the founder in a couple of weeks at NEXT conference, so will report back!    
    
    
    MTFYE on pervasive shopping :)http://pervasiveshopping.wordpress.com/    
    
    
    @ileddigital i must book my flights for this :)    
    
    
    school on a sunday...fun times :)    
    
    
    @wildwoman your going to dundee! im so jealous :(    
    
    
    @designthinkers you should look up samsø island in Copenhagen, it is a sustainable island that has been co-created by its residents    
    
    
    14 hour day...nice    
    
    
    experience prototyping new library services has begun    
    
    
    reflecting on jennie winhall's talk she gave at CIID today    
    
    
    preparing for a rainy cycle home from the designskole    
    
    
    @chrismonnier the answer is no i'm afraid :( but it is an awesome city!    
    
    
    filming library video    
    
    
    so much so do, so little time    
    
    
    meet the food you eat is going to be on TV2! good morning Denmark here we come!    
    
    
    last week of service design course, presentation tues, thurs and fri.....last push!    
    
    
    if only you could CRTL S electronics! long night ahead preparing for good morning denmark,  http://tinyurl.com/cz3wfe    
    
    
    tv2 studio was great fun, and the scale performed brilliantly!    
    
    
    back in Scotland for a few days after anothere amazing 3 months at CIID    
    
    
    working on portfolio    
    
    
    can't move after family meal    
    
    
    finally written an article for johnny holland    
    
    
    @multikev its on personal informatics,i supposed to do it about three months ago!when you were doing the one on our data viz class!    
    
    
    off out into the sun!    
    
    
    preparing to go back to Copenhagen tomorrow, then its thesis time.......    
    
    
    @vorgitsu what is this??!!    
    
    
    back in the sun in copenhagen    
    
    
    going to the beach...    
    
    
    editing..    
    
    
    @sicamp is it a bar you want for it?    
    
    
    thinking about after CIID    
    
    
    reboot meeting    
    
    
    creating personal profiles    
    
    
    brilliant talk by Robert Fabricant http://vimeo.com/3730382 starting point for my thesis.    
    
    
    2 bike punctures, big picnic, one bike crash, lots of frisbie, danish countryside and amazing people :)    
    
    
    updating blog.    
    
    
    @Redjotter me too!    
    
    
    started thesis    
    
    
    nap time was not sufficient enough    
    
    
    @wildwoman i'm sure Alie would have a few stories to tell..    
    
    
    writing up notes from first research session    
    
    
    After a 2 year break it's time to reunite with twitter    
    
    
    planning for parents arriving in copenhagen    
    
    
    up early...parents arriving soon :)    
    
    
    does anyone know of any diabetes initiatives in Boston?    
    
    
    Looking forward to @hxdconf with @hellerohdea    
    
    
    Switch to teaching mode for 3 days with @ishacbertran #carboncopy #CIID    
    
    
    @hxdconf does anyone know someone working at #the full yield. Would love to talk to them about their work    
    
    
    @adrane that would be great. Thank you! My email Is e.dickson@ciid.dk    
    
    
    on top secret industry project so no blogging for the next 2 weeks    
    
    
    re-design portfolio http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk let me know any feedback/mistakes/errors/typo's you find!    
    
    
    @mayonissen not yet, soon though :-)    
    
    
    building storyboards    
    
    
    presentation 2 of industry project, 2 to go!    
    
    
    #CIID is hiring a project and research manager. http://ciid.dk/about/jobs/project-and-research-manager/ …    
    
    
    "The NHS is full of brilliant people with brilliant ideas" #NHS #Bottomupinnovation #thewayitshouldbe http://www.challengeprizes.institute.nhs.uk/     
    
    
    awesome graphic notes by @cassiemc from #hxdconf. http://bit.ly/HjE8sH . @hellerohdea you should check it out    
    
    
    http://soundcloud.com/aretive/deadsynth …    
    
    
    @nonlocal great find!    
    
    
    @mayonissen I feel that pain    
    
    
    Could get very used to this    
    
    
    “@FastCoDesign: The World’s First Commercial #3D Chocolate Printer Is On Sale http://bit.ly/JpEyt6 ” this ones for you @hellerohdea    
    
    
    @mayonissen its the best course in the world!    
    
    
    amazing video for 2012 olympics http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=FMunV1Y4X2o&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    @mayonissen well just drop me an email if you need any help or questions answered, my email is on eilidhdickson.co.uk    
    
    
    @emeasee .....Urbbi?? http://www.fastcodesign.com/1669604/talk-to-your-plants-for-dummy-proof-gardening-using-a-sensor-and-an-iphone-app …    
    
    
    “@designboom: pantone unveils 336 new colors http://dlvr.it/1Tf2n0  - #design” #patonelove    
    
    
    deadline 4hrs 40 mins...no sleep    
    
    
    @johnlync you are my hero    
    
    
    CIID wins Knowledge Relay (Videnstafet) for Denmark's most innovative and ambitious knowledge enterprise. http://ciid.dk/?p=13846  #CIID    
    
    
    looking back over old twitter/blog/website posts - I was much more proactive when i was a student #thismustchange    
    
    
    Does anyone in London want to try and buy me a Nike Fuel band tomorrow?    
    
    
    @krissus amazing find!!!!!!    
    
    
    @johnlync i'm sending you a direct contact for SF    
    
    
    @ishacbertran on @FastCoDesign http://www.fastcodesign.com/1669665/watch-this-ingenious-ui-idea-for-dragging-files-from-your-phone-to-computer …    
    
    
    @johnlync now you have me thinking....    
    
    
    Back to thesis work    
    
    
    looking forward to going to see the K3 Interaction Design end of year show    
    
    
    catching up on very overdue blogging    
    
    
    sweden tomorrow :)    
    
    
    IDEO considers the future of news.....http://bit.ly/AZWqD    
    
    
    @jeroenvangeel unfortunately not,i would have love to.Dave Malouf is giving us a lecture though,you should come visit the CIID studio!    
    
    
    @designthinkers you should come to this! CIID are going to be there acting as "consultants" to help people develop & prototype their ideas!    
    
    
    writing "how might we statements" idea time soon!    
    
    
    @daveixd looking forward to it :)    
    
    
    http://reflectionaction.com  => a side project I've been working on with @hellerohdea  Check it out! Any feedback is welcomed #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    Amazing first day with Brian Rink as head of consulting #CIID #Consulting    
    
    
    @emeasee Thanks Mac!!!    
    
    
    Marker Happiness - a tribute to our amazing drawing utensils: http://reflectionaction.com/?p=364  #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    @DesignThinkers Thanks for the mention Arne! @hellerohdea @reflectioninact    
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaD9jcrbnN/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaJkaErbo_/     
    
    
    Step 2 - digital #reflectioninaction http://instagr.am/p/LaS0rMrbr7/     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/LaWk2nrbs1/     
    
    
    Making a feeling tangible  http://instagr.am/p/Lag5Marbgv/     
    
    
    @richardshed I just saw this now!!! Anyway looking forward to seeing you at CIID tomorrow!    
    
    
    A new post by @ReflectionInAct. Can you bottle motivation? - a design provocation. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=465  #ReflectionInAction    
    
    
    @johnlync nice find!! @ReflectionInAct    
    
    
    Free Keynote mockup templates for prototyping iPhone, iPad, Android and Web apps #design #UX #mockups http://keynotopia.com/keynote-mockups-templates/ … via @keynotopia    
    
    
    Interviewing for Interaction Design Programme 2013. How time flies! #CIID @CIIDnews    
    
    
    @everythingiknow thank you rory!!!!! @ReflectionInAct @hellerohdea    
    
    
    tracking behaviour to understand communication with family    
    
    
    @wildwoman what sort of charts, project planning?    
    
    
    @wildwoman we might have some good ones at CIID    
    
    
    CIID student project featured on @FastCoDesign: Machine Scans Twitter For Mentions Of Fruit&turns them to smoothies http://bit.ly/Kdwzzy ”    
    
    
    Great lecture from Matt Jones today    
    
    
    @marcinignac sketch up?    
    
    
    brainstorming festival commences in 30 minutes, armed with markers, post-its and goodies :)    
    
    
    @daveixd so well said!    
    
    
    “@daveixd: Stop designing for clients & start creating with partners.” ... The way it should be.    
    
    
    NEW POST @ReflectionInAct --> Digital Materiality - An Exploration: http://reflectionaction.com/?p=558     
    
    
    http://instagr.am/p/MiZ-x0Lbim/     
    
    
    time to start concept scenarios after brainstorming    
    
    
    New inspiration on @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?page_id=114  #nonintentionaldesign #relfectioninaction    
    
    
    @tommetcalfe I'm sure if I remember correctly there will be a lot of nice 3d renders of cars, bikes and home gadgets ;) #noinvention    
    
    
    Off for an injection of music for the day at roskilde @orangefeeling    
    
    
    @tommetcalfe yes you should come... Visit CIID!    
    
    
    presentation on monday with external faculty....looking forward to a fresh perspective    
    
    
    New post on @ReflectionInAct about low tech tracking tools. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=599  #reflectioninaction #personalinformatics #trackingtools    
    
    
    Sorry for an spam people are getting from me. My account has been hacked. Trying to sort it out now.    
    
    
    @dianakeeling what do we run on saturday??! So i know what to do during the week :-)    
    
    
    excited to hear the @Core77Awards results for the speculative category. Come on @CIIDnews!!!!!!!!!! #CIID #windowtotheworld #toyota    
    
    
    @dianakeeling neither am I just now :-) trying to get back into after a lazy period! but that sounds lovely! excited for friday!!!    
    
    
    @dianakeeling do you want anything Danish brought to you?! :-) (apart from tobias)    
    
    
    Congratulations to @yufangised for coming runner up in the student interaction category in the @Core77Awards    
    
    
    just watched matt jones at fbtb..AMAZING! http://johnnyholland.tv/    
    
    
    presentation making for review tomorrow: feeling very inspired after watching matt jones at from business to buttons    
    
    
    Some new urban inspiration on @ReflectionInAct from our travels in Pittsburgh http://reflectionaction.com/?page_id=114  #reflectioninaction    
    
    
    New Urban Inspiration: DIY bike repair station in wholefoods @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?p=658 
#relfectioninaction #pittsburgh    
    
    
    New Urban Inspiration: Well informed or too elaborate road signage? @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/?p=655 
#relfectioninaction #pittsburgh    
    
    
    Doing Finishing touches to presentation for final project review http://twitpic.com/833gu    
    
    
    It’s easy to believe our own excuses, particularly if they’re good ones. #motivationishard    
    
    
    Interesting.....What do the most successful people accomplish before breakfast? @FastCompany http://bit.ly/MzFIDq     
    
    
    "Turning a desire into a ritual requires willpower" #sotrue    
    
    
    co creation event in copenhagen on thursday http://copenhagencocreation.com/    
    
    
    2 days to go!! http://www.reboot.dk/    
    
    
    CIID Consulting is proud to announce the launch of a new section of our website devoted to sharing the methods & tools 
http://ciid.dk/tools_workshops/ …    
    
    
    @paulmmay Thanks Pau! Please share it with anyone who you think will find it useful    
    
    
    'super shuttle' more like 'disaster shuttle'    
    
    
    @mayonissen @hellerohdea    
    
    
    @mayonissen @hellerohdea yes... Minor travel hiccup - we leave again in a few hours...    
    
    
    Back home in CPH after my first missed flight of my life - exhausted but inspired to come up with some new travel service ideas.    
    
    
    I love jetlag #nocturnal    
    
    
    first day at #reboot11=awesome!    
    
    
    day 1@reboot: Write up for the CIID Open Lab
http://bit.ly/NWOYE    
    
    
    can't believe about michael jackson
http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/americas/8119951.stm    
    
    
    reboot day 2 write up for CIID......
http://bit.ly/5SNNI    
    
    
    #Reboot11 write up for CIID
http://bit.ly/ne1yX    
    
    
    CIID Industry trip tomorrow, Bang & Oulfsen, Lego and Danfoss    
    
    
    on the way to legoland avec CIID    
    
    
    Looking for a good recruitment company that can help getting research respondents in Savannah, GA. Any tips welcomed!    
    
    
    New post on @ReflectionInAct. Urban Play. http://reflectionaction.com/?p=673  #reflectioninaction #exercise #urban #babysteps    
    
    
    @mayonissen his presentation at Reboot was amazing!    
    
    
    Presenting with @hellerohdea  to @DesignDundeeabout CIID Consulting on the 21st Sep. Come along ! http://bit.ly/Q6tfdQ     
    
    
    @TessyBritton I will be in London next wk with @hellerohdea (23-28th Sept) Let know if you have time for a coffee    
    
    
    @TessyBritton @hellerohdea I leave on the 28th to go o Scotland.Will email you once i know my definite travel plans. Enjoy France!    
    
    
    I'll see you tomorrow Scotland. In the mean time some inspiration - EPIC must see video. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Cj6ho1-G6tw …    
    
    
    Nice write up on @hellerohdea and my talk at @DesignDundee http://masterofdesignforservices.com/2012/09/21/ciid-consulting/ …    
    
    
    @DesignDundee Thank for having us, it was a pleasure!    
    
    
    @DesignDundee some of you were asking @hellerohdea and I about personal projects we do. Here you go @ReflectionInAct http://reflectionaction.com/     
    
    
    CIID got the funding for year 2....woo hoo!    
    
    
    @wildwoman everyone is over the moon!end of yr exhibition 27th Aug-6th sept :)    
    
    
    A week of prototyping in the UK with @hellerohdea done. Next up Scotland - Copenhagen - New York - North Carolina - Georgia.    
    
    
    @katerishka @hellerohdea the most fun part will be the reunion in Copenhagen next weekend :-)    
    
    
    Scottish wedding :-) http://instagr.am/p/QMr2x3JBpK/     
    
    
    @mayonissen will you be in NY on the 7th and 8th (this month) thats when @hellerohdea and I will be there    
    
    
    @mayonissen there will be a forum opening up soon for you :)    
    
    
    @CIIDnews first official reunion for the Interaction Design Programme! Come on the PILOT YEAR!!!!!!!    
    
    
    butterflies #ciidreunion #pilotyear    
    
    
    pleased our project is on http://www.servicedesigntools.org/tools/24    
    
    
    New York complete. Now Charlotte, NC    
    
    
    Missing my playground http://www.nike.com/us/en_us/c/running/nike-running-lunarglide-plus …
#running #Copenhagen #builtupenergy    
    
    
    Last day in Charlotte. Tomorrow Savannah, GA #EPIC2012    
    
    
    eilidh likes @mimi's graphic design advice :)    
    
    
    Savannah.    
    
    
    A new start up by the very talented @emeasee http://ajoto.com/     
    
    
    @epiconference what pace are you planning to run at?! :-) #epiconference    
    
    
    Awesome inspiring keynote by Emily Pilloton #epiconference http://instagr.am/p/QzmQKtrbn4/     
    
    
    EPIC 2012@thelucas theatre #epiconference   @ Lucas Theatre for the Arts http://instagr.am/p/Q0Mn3jLbhZ/     
    
    
    @daveixd yes! CIIDconsulting are presenting an artifact, we are working on client work on wed but keep me posted if your around tomorrow    
    
    
    EPIC2012 are rocking the word clouds #epiconference   @ Lucas Theatre for the Arts http://instagr.am/p/Q0QuE2Lbkn/     
    
    
    A cool new online photobooth project by my friend Sid who works at LEGO. Still in Beta Version, but try it out...
http://www.snippic.com     
    
    
    Buddy - a digital tool to support therapy services, created by @sidekickstudios http://www.buddyapp.co.uk/     
    
    
    The average American physician interrupt their patient in 14 seconds  http://instagr.am/p/Q2qo5jLbtA/     
    
    
    From the awesome @daimyoon: project SONIVIVI has been selected for @IxDAwards 2013 shortlist!.”    
    
    
    shortlist for 2013 @IxDAwards Announced! http://ow.ly/eCihX ... and there are 8 @CIIDnews student entries!!    
    
    
    @Redjotter you are definitely in Scandinavia somewhere :)    
    
    
    2 days. 8 hours sleep. Tiered. #jetlag #deadlines    
    
    
    paper to pixels    
    
    
    "This is why I love working with you on this project... Because it makes me think outside of my normal......" #toughweekmadebetter #client    
    
    
    @stephfulke I'm actually going to be in Ireland for a wedding! How long you in town for?    
    
    
    Impressed by @CIIDnews IDP industry presentations for Novo Nordisk. Great thinking happening in the house.    
    
    
    @stephfulke ah I though you meant November. I should be around then :)    
    
    
    @ileddigital this is awesome :)    
    
    
    Bye bye @ishacbertran I'm going to miss you and our geeky design chats.  @ alie's house http://instagr.am/p/RuCIGsrbob/     
    
    
    @ishacbertran @elaineygianni new documentaries screening over the next few days in NYC at @DOCNYCfest http://www.docnyc.net/films-events/#all …”    
    
    
    Go go CIID! “@IxDAwards: And so it begins! The jurors are gathered in NYC to determine the winners for the 2013 Interaction Awards!...”    
    
    
    A lot of runners #geek #training #earlysundaymorning http://instagr.am/p/R4dc7BLbu3/     
    
    
    great work by @ishacbertran “Flaps, fast and contextual web browsing: http://ishback.com/lab/flaps/flaps.html …”    
    
    
    'Vision, blueprint, strategy' #lifeasadesignconsultant    
    
    
    At last! A tracking device for non super users  http://trib.al/bNIHaI ”    
    
    
    “@odannyboy: Intriguing product in a crowded space: Shine http://www.indiegogo.com/misfitshine  Watch how it syncs data! #microinteractions”    
    
    
    Amazing! 
“@novonordisktbl: A beautiful #blue as night falls on #WDD. Copenhagen Opera House shines for #WDD2012 pic.twitter.com/UlNllf3S”    
    
    
    back to learning flash for the day    
    
    
    Quite proud of myself that I ran 190km in November. #backinthegame    
    
    
    A winter morning http://instagr.am/p/SzjsVGLbrK/     
    
    
    Massive congratulations to @daimyoon for being announced as a winner in the 'empowering' category for this years IxDA Awards!    
    
    
    Archiving my design life    
    
    
    “@IxDA: 2013 @IxDAwards Winners Announced! http://goo.gl/vkdBk ” and CIID's @daimyoon is a winner!!!!!!    
    
    
    Good luck to all the #IDP2012 students with their final presentations this week!    
    
    
    @DesignDundee a big Happy Holiday to you all from @hellerohdea and @eilidhdickson from CIID Consulting http://ciid.dk/holidays2012/     
    
    
    Very Happy to be speaking about 'Understanding Networks of Diabetes Care' @hxdconf this year with @hellerohdea #CIID #HXDconf    
    
    
    @HolidayCollider tis the season for #bows and #snow http://tellart.com/holiday/2012  (via @tellart)    
    
    
    Thanks to @MiniPagura and @johnlync an afternoon of brainstorming is complete #ciidconsulting    
    
    
    Craving America. Roll on @hxdconf in march #HXDconf    
    
    
    -6 degrees, piercing blue sky, 21k run - good Sunday morning #takethatcold    
    
    
    CIID website temporarily down    
    
    
    @mayonissen not too sure what the problem is..in the process of being sorted though!how was thinkpublic?    
    
    
    Preparing presentation for @hxdconf 'understanding networks of diabetes care' #HxD2013 #ciidconsulting pic.twitter.com/DeDUvnI7    
    
    
    Progressing... #HxD2013 pic.twitter.com/pJSrVXxH    
    
    
    The moment you want to quit is the moment you need to keep pushing #marathontraining    
    
    
    Via @novonordisk: First-Ever Guidelines for Children With Type 2 Diabetes. Scary but interesting. http://diabetes.webmd.com/news/20130125/guidelines-kids-diabetes ….    
    
    
    @mrettig just read your thoughts on the 'connecting' film. I am with you 100% of the way! http://www.ixda.org/node/33654     
    
    
    I would love some advice on good running routes in boston from any locals attending @hxdconf this year #boston #running #HxD2013    
    
    
    Will be in New York from the 26-28th of March. Let me know if are around and want to have a coffee/beer etc..    
    
    
    CV overhall #longoverdue    
    
    
    There are over 47000 products and no seasons in an average American supermarket #sigh #    
    
    
    New York next Monday to Friday. Message me if your around    
    
    
    A weekend of presentation building begins    
    
    
    2 week travel Itinerary starting tomorrow. New York - Copenhagen - Boston - New York - Copenhagen    
    
    
    AMAZING to see you @mayonissen @ishacbertran @elaineygianni. Now a few days in CPH then to Boston to present @hxdconf with @hellerohdea    
    
    
    Question to the world… What is the most innovative, self sustaining business model you have ever encountered/heard of?    
    
    
    Arrived in Boston with @hellerohdea for @hxdconf #hxdconf #hxd13    
    
    
    Hear how research builds empathy in organizations come to 'understanding networks of diabetes care' at 3.40 @hxdconf #hxd2013 #HXDconf    
    
    
    @skrugman where are you?    
    
    
    @skrugman ballroom a with Dustin    
    
    
    @sean__burke nice to connect! Hope your enjoying the conference    
    
    
    Missing New York's charm already #takemeback    
    
    
    @avantgame I saw ur talk at HxD + wanted to say it was AMAZING! The highlight of the conference & such an inspiration for a fellow designer.    
    
    
    Must see TED Talk. Jane McGonigal: The game that can give you 10 extra years of life. http://www.ted.com/talks/jane_mcgonigal_the_game_that_can_give_you_10_extra_years_of_life.html …    
    
    
    @chrisallick I just realized I wasn't following yo.How could that be?! I've been missing out! PS. When you coming to CPH?    
    
    
    CIID Final Year Exhibition
http://bit.ly/YClaV    
    
    
    YouTube's ready to select a winner #aprilfool http://youtu.be/H542nLTTbu0 ”    
    
    
    Homework to do…1) Bring an object that represents CIID 2) Think of one anecdote that to you summarizes the spirit of CIID #CIID #rebranding    
    
    
    CIID future strategy meeting #rebranding http://instagram.com/p/Xo2sVSrbvt/     
    
    
    @cbehrlich    
    
    
    @hellerohdea and I talking about “Understanding Networks of Diabetes Care” @hxdconf http://vimeo.com/63539162     
    
    
    @mayonissen i haven't seen a segway here in 11 months!    
    
    
    @mayonissen Copenhagen Bliss    
    
    
    starting final presentation....the end is in sight!    
    
    
    has has finished her final  CIID exam, presenting to bill moggridge! feels good!    
    
    
    @wildwoman it was great, i cant believe its over! we will see what the jury  have to say tomorrow!    
    
    
    @mayonissen i think it went well! we will see what the verdict is tomorrow though! and then to party!    
    
    
    what is a good software i can download to compress videos?    
    
    
    @mivesto  thanks for the mention    
    
    
    @mayonissen theres a cool cafe in vesterø called bang and jensons with free wi fi :) 130 Istedgade    
    
    
    @mayonissen im still in recovery mode...but will keep you posted with any plans :)    
    
    
    last day of the CIID Pilot Year exhibition tomorrow!    
    
    
    @mayonissen i think you need to get some our addresses :)    
    
    
    @mayonissen we have to take down the exhibition at 5 im afraid    
    
    
    Toronto Next week for 4 weeks with @johnlynch. Any tips? Running Routes? Design meet ups?    
    
    
    New York from the 16th-20th of October. Who's around?    
    
    
    @mayonissen the laundromat cafe of course!    
    
    
    1 interview away from being with @elaineygianni and @ishacbertran    
    
    
    where are the hipster shops in toronto. @johnlync and I need sneakers    
    
    
    Sync your files online and across computers with @Dropbox. 2GB account is free! http://bit.ly/p0oUr    
    
    
    updating website....http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk/thesis.html    
    
    
    @CarolineArvids1 Welcome Back!    
    
    
    @CarolineArvids1 have a good day at the conference representing @CIIDnews #ciidconsulting    
    
    
    presentation preparation..    
    
    
    #CIID students rocking the @IxDAwards once again with 6 short listed entries!
http://www.ixda.org/awards     
    
    
    Jawbone talking about "the internet of me" http://www.fastcodesign.com/homepage/2013/11/12 …    
    
    
    Come see the hottest interaction design talent around at the #CIID end of year exhibition. http://ciid.dk/2013/12/12/end-of-year-exhibition-2013/ …    
    
    
    “@CIIDnews: 20 Students - 13 Countries. CIID invites you to join us for the end-of-year exhibition: http://ciid.dk/?p=25441 ”    
    
    
    Experimenting with AMAZING CIID students! #ciid http://instagram.com/p/g_d2cNrbpJ/     
    
    
    A hugely inspirational video about interviewing people while they run. by @goodgym #theunners
http://goodgym.org/therunners/     
    
    
    long awaited news update on http://www.eilidhdickson.co.uk    
    
    
    Worst. Idea. Ever http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-scotland-politics-25088251 …    
    
    
    Big discussions at CIID Consulting #rebranding @ CIID http://instagram.com/p/hNvF-zrbpG/     
    
    
    November is over. December challenge begins: Run.every.day.    
    
    
    "We bring novelty in the way we do things" #simonamaschi #ciid @CIIDnews    
    
    
    Good food for thought at the CIID exams "What's an emotional or behavioral prototype" @mrettig    
    
    
    final project on servicedesigntools http://servicedesigntools.org/tools/35    
    
    
    @PaddyStevenson we think, by charles leadbeater or the classic....one of don normans books.    
    
    
    updating portfolio with Novo project    
    
    
    Off to madrid to help teach design processes/methods/prototyping :)    
    
    
    house hunting...for the first time in 15 months in Copenhagen..I obviously been too lucky before    
    
    
    India for 16 days, see you soon copenhagen    
    
    
    