"Young people need to be able to communicate and socialize insights with each other." @changeist: http://is.gd/educationfutures …    
    
    
    "The future isn’t won just because a few students can build a robot or print a simple plastic model" - @changeist: http://is.gd/educationfutures …    
    
    
    We're unveiling new work by @jeffnoon & @tom_armitage: http://is.gd/noonarmitage  at the Digital Late next week: http://is.gd/digitallate  #BDF2013    
    
    
    Plans within plans ....    
    
    
    Inspirational speech by our great MP @CarolineLucas on the societal value of arts, quoting everyone from Jeanette Winterson to Steve Jobs.    
    
    
    "A civilised society should not be neglecting its most vulnerable people but nor should it neglect its cultural heritage." @CarolineLucas    
    
    
    "The language of the market has seeped into everything. I want to be a citizen, not a customer." @CarolineLucas    
    
    
    This Friday eve come to the Cube Cola Trading Post at ONCA. We'll be mixing up drinks & hacking carbonation: http://is.gd/cubecola  #BDF2013    
    
    
    There'll be a talk & cocktail tastings from Francisco Fernández Gallardo, an imaginative environmental technologist: http://is.gd/cubecola     
    
    
    Explore the interconnections b/w cocktails, urban ecosystems, plant/animal interactions & taste this Friday: http://is.gd/cubecola  #BDF2013    
    
    
    @SheSaysBrighton @LighthouseArts You are very welcome.  We are proud to support you.    
    
    
    @juhavantzelfde There must be a specialist curatorial agency who can help with something like that? ;> cc @jldevicente    
    
    
    @adamhrv I think i might try and come over for this ....    
    
    
    One race away ...    
    
    
    The untold story of Korolev's role in the space race & then a frank analysis of the ethics of sex work. @BBCRadio4 being refreshingly brave.    
    
    
    An affirmation of citizenry, wildcrafting, optimal learning structures, serendipitous collisions, debates about writing. Brighton, tonight.    
    
    
    I might be irrationally plotting something about something New York, something something something October.    
    
    
    Emergent culture: quantum gravity explored fairly coherently in the form of song (!) + research refs: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2rjbtsX7twc … (via @REasther)    
    
    
    @tobias_revell @changeist And that would be a problem .... *because* ...  ?    
    
    
    @bobbie I think you may be on to something there ... replete with the capacity of separating body from soul at strategic moments.    
    
    
    @tobias_revell Just a wee heads up. You did say that out loud.  cc @changeist    
    
    
    Reminder: we're putting on a cocktail party with a difference this Friday at the Cube Cola Trading Post at ONCA: http://is.gd/cubecola     
    
    
    @LydNicholas I can relate. And I send sympathies. And if it helps, I'm suspecting @tobias_revell was referring to weasels.  cc @changeist    
    
    
    . @soozaphone It most certainly is! So on Friday, were combining Cube Cola -their open source cola- with DIY cocktail science. Want to come?    
    
    
    @LydNicholas Right you are about the civets. Now unsure which two letters to follow this with so I'll point -> @changeist @tobias_revell    
    
    
    @tobias_revell @changeist So now we've moved this into historical Crime Fiction? One for the crowdfunded anthology, @LydNicholas?    
    
    
    Architects behind the world's first invisible skyscraper begin construction of "Tower Infinity" http://mashable.com/2013/09/16/invisible-skyscraper/ … (via @tobias_revell)!    
    
    
    OH: "The garden will need some work, as soon the airstrikes abate and peace returns to this troubled region."    
    
    
    As Peter Kirk once intoned: "being brought to hysterics as only @julian0liver could inspire."    
    
    
    @ntlk We now have an Artfefact card (cf @willsh) which includes a diagram of the chasm left by your departure.    
    
    
    At Linuxcon, Linus Torvalds admitted that the #NSA approached him to put a backdoor into #Linux! http://goo.gl/qxuKW8  (via @danmcquillan)    
    
    
    Why would that be so? Open isn't synonymous with virtuous. MT @Jon_Christian. Isn't malicious open source code an oxymoron    
    
    
    @Jon_Christian Android is theoretically open. Here's today's news: http://pastebin.com/Hg9aeHEd     
    
    
    The "NSA are committing code to the Android security stack. Here's a call to audit their contributions" @julian0liver http://pastebin.com/Hg9aeHEd     
    
    
    Hello London.    
    
    
    Somewhat irrationally excited to be at Imperial College. Ahead of the MediaSpace opening at the @sciencemuseum tonight.    
    
    
    Huge congratulations to @sciencemuseum on the launch of MediaSpace. Its an important new space for London. Thanks to Dave, Hannah & the team    
    
    
    Breakfast between the Energy Futures Lab & the Climate Change Institute.    
    
    
    Possibly the most important piece you'll read all day -the UK's response to the Snowden revelations: http://is.gd/themonster  (via @erocdrahs)    
    
    
    "[the digital revolution] has shrunk the globe & vastly increased transparency ..." http://is.gd/themonster  (1/3)    
    
    
    "but it is poised to corrupt the very freedoms it professes to advance." http://is.gd/themonster  (2/3)    
    
    
    "The market is no guard against it, only democratic oversight. If that fails, as it has, everything is at risk" http://is.gd/themonster  (3/3)    
    
    
    Multiversality ...    
    
    
    Dual Elliptic Curve Deterministic Random Bit Generation ...    
    
    
    "Found Infrastructure Fictions (@PaulGrahamRaven)    
    
    
    (there's a play on musique concrete in there somewhere, but I'll leave that to the synthetic neologists.) cc @changeist    
    
    
    Oh very good. MT @justinpickard:  Musique reinforced concrete: http://www.sjef.nu/concrete-immaculate/ …    
    
    
    Tonight - open source wildcrafted cocktails & food design at the #CubeCola DIY party: http://is.gd/cubecola  - 7-9pm at Onca Gallery.    
    
    
    Being quizzed on exactly how *present* I intend to be at tonight's event. #eventontologies #mindfulness    
    
    
    The #CubeCola DIY Party kicks off with a talk of biodiversity & Cola cocktails. pic.twitter.com/xz55k2mNhI    
    
    
    "What he was interested in doing is setting fire to diamonds." - so far, so brilliant.    
    
    
    "Making visible material out of technological infrastructure is the 1st step towards understanding them" @timoarnall: http://is.gd/immaterials     
    
    
    "Mining for Spatially-Near Communities in Geo-Located Social Networks": http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.2900  - definitely one for @theeuronomad    
    
    
    Boston Dynamics begins production on 'Big Mule' (aka 'LS3') - "a donkey-sized 4-legged robot": http://is.gd/bigmule     
    
    
    "Using Cosmology to Establish the Quantization of Gravity"  - @LKrauss1 & @FrankWilczek's new paper on gravitons: http://frankwilczek.com/2013/gravitons3.pdf …    
    
    
    "one might wonder whether we can ever directly validate any quantum effects associated with the gravitational field." http://is.gd/gravitons     
    
    
    "cosmology provides a realistic observable that is directly tied to the quantization of gravity.": http://is.gd/gravitons     
    
    
    Observing "a cosmological gravitational wave background associated with an inflationary phase would provide evidence" http://is.gd/gravitons     
    
    
    "It does so in a way which is heuristically equivalent to all laboratory experiments that probe quantum phenomena.": http://is.gd/gravitons     
    
    
    "it couples quantum mechanical phenomena to a classical detector ... " http://is.gd/gravitons  (1/2)    
    
    
    "... effectively amplifying quantum mechanical effects so that they are classically measurable." http://is.gd/gravitons  (2/2)    
    
    
    "The classical detector, in this case, is the expanding Universe." @LKrauss1 & @FrankWilczek: http://is.gd/gravitons     
    
    
    "Is concealment a solution or rather a retreat?" - artists & hackers shed light on data & darknets in 'Going Dark': http://arthackday.net/berlin/     
    
    
    I would very much like to tell you about the story that @julian0liver just sent me.  But I genuinely don't know how I'd begin to try ...    
    
    
    "Despite his tragic sartorial collaborations with the avian world John still believed that somehow he could to make his transistors smaller"    
    
    
    "John’s coworkers eventually understood his wisdom, and their need to wear coffee-resistant indoor ponchos lessened with time."    
    
    
    "John’s massive parallelism strategy assumed that lay people use their computers to simulate hurricanes, decode monkey genomes and ..."(1/2)    
    
    
    "... multiply vast dimensioned matrices in an attempt to unlock eigenvectors whose desolate grandeur could only be imagined by Poe" (2/2)    
    
    
    "even though you’ve been sued by several pedestrians who suddenly acquired rare paintings as hats, you go out the master of your domain."    
    
    
    "As the transistors became increasingly unpredictable, the foundations of John’s world began to crumble."    
    
    
    "So, John did what any reasonable person would do: he cloaked himself in a wall of denial and acted like nothing had happened."    
    
    
    "The point is that flying in airplanes used to be fun, but now it resembles a dystopian bin-packing problem"    
    
    
    Can the internet give James Mickens a round of applause, please, for this superb hypnogogically indescribable text: http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    "Thus, when John said 'imagine a world in which you’re constantly executing millions of parallel tasks,' ..." (1/2): http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    "… it was equivalent to saying 'imagine a world that you do not and will never live in'.” (2/2):  http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    "John learned about the new hyperthreaded processor that ran so hot that it burned a hole to the center of the earth" http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    "Whenever someone proposed a new hardware feature, John would yell 'THE MAGMA PEOPLE ARE WAITING FOR OUR MISTAKES'.” http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    @futureidentity Cunningly disguised as a piece on air travel, the piece is really about the breakdown of Moore's Law: http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    @AndrewJanke An article about the breakdown of Moore's Law in CPU management disguised as a piece on airline travel: http://is.gd/slowwinter     
    
    
    Mistaken for a well-programmed spambot. Achievement unlocked.    
    
    
    Tomorrow on @BBCRadio4 Improving Reality speaker, @Flygirltwo will be talking tech with Beeban Kidron & @adrianhon: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03bdbpt …    
    
    
    Start the Week contextualises & challenges Beeban Kidron's controversial new documentary on young people & technology http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03bdbpt …    
    
    
    Last chance to see Kate Rich & Kayle Brandon's Trading Post. They've been making open source cola with young people: http://is.gd/cubecola     
    
    
    Radio & television? MT @booksprint: @accessjames yes, powerful electromagnetic spectrum weapons have been employed on the masses for decades    
    
    
    Speechless. "If the girl starts saving, she can buy back some of her father’s time spent at work" http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=PakIPqMl25U … (via @anabjain)    
    
    
    "We need an Arts Strategy Board like the Technology Strategy Board, to fund R&D for creative industries." @dougrichard via @CreativeSoc    
    
    
    Sad & chilling. Ladar Levison, founder of Lavabit, turns off phones & avoids areas reachable by mics: http://www.geekwire.com/2013/scared-tech-startups-debate-business-opportunities-privacy/ … (via @adamhrv)    
    
    
    The whole of New Zealand on tenterhooks ...    
    
    
    Somewhat surreally, a nation collectively prays for the spontaneous appearance of whales.    
    
    
    Watching a film made by @deepspeedmedia. One I feel very close to.  I can't wait till you get to see it. Because it's *utterly beautiful*.    
    
    
    That moment where you see a star ascending ....    
    
    
    In an hour, Start the Week with #ireality speaker, @Flygirltwo, Guiding Lights mentor, Beeban Kidron & @adrianhon: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03bdbpt …    
    
    
    Expect a nuanced discussion on the myth of the digital native, algorithms & technological futures on #StartTheWeek: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03bdbpt …    
    
    
    "Showing the cables, the data centres, is about showing the viscerality of the internet" - Beeban Kidron #StartTheWeek    
    
    
    "How can we make the cloud tangible, so that we can critically approach it?" - @Flygirltwo #StartTheWeek #Immaterials    
    
    
    "What are we making visible, and what are we imagining?"- @Flygirltwo #StartTheWeek #Immaterials    
    
    
    Farida Vis (@Flygirltwo) brings up the spying bins on #StartTheWeek.  Worlds colliding ...    
    
    
    Farida Vis (@Flygirltwo) analysing the algorithms that made up our world #StartTheWeek - See http://is.gd/slavinted  for the primer.    
    
    
    Wonder if this is the first time Klout scores have been discussed on #StartTheWeek? @Flygirltwo paraphrases her #ireality talk ...    
    
    
    "We can't have 10 million programmers in the UK. That obviously doesn't make any sense at all" - @adrianhon #StartTheWeek #FutureJobs    
    
    
    "One of the new norms is meeting strangers online" Beeban Kidron. Well, that's kind of been the case since 1993 … #StartTheWeek    
    
    
    Nuanced discussion on #StartTheWeek about online behaviour, the dangers of invisibility & complex futures from @Flygirltwo, @adrianhon & co.    
    
    
    It's an *excellent* talk. & there's cricket MT  @Flygirltwo More on those spying bins in this talk by @jamesbridle: http://bambuser.com/v/3836761     
    
    
    "Many universities are still not paying enough attention to the world of work that their students will be entering" https://medium.com/futures-exchange/a2d03a433230 …”    
    
    
    We have some news ...    
    
    
    Thrilled to announce that one of our BFI Short films, @OrbitEverAfter, has won the main prize at @EncountersSFF: http://is.gd/orbitwinsaward     
    
    
    "A system that gives white men greater visibility also favors them financially."  @jomc on tech conferences: https://medium.com/p/a1bd497a16c2     
    
    
    Experimenting with going dark for a bit. If we've met I'll be over at @metanautic.    
    
    
    On Thursday at Digital Late (http://is.gd/digitallate ), we're unveiling this new project by @tom_armitage & @jeffnoon: http://literaryoperator.com     
    
    
    Glad you like it Kars :) MT @kaeru: The Literary Operator. Lovely work by @tom_armitage and @jeffnoon: http://bit.ly/1ffJplL     
    
    
    Some seriously valuable insights in this piece by @fchimero: http://is.gd/frankch  - recommend watching with @bruces' Next talk in mind.    
    
    
    I'd go so far as to say that if the only thing that came out of #xoxofest was this http://is.gd/frankch  it would be worth it just for that    
    
    
    @fchimero @xoxo this is one of the most poignant & important pieces I've read in a while. I'm going to reread & share widely. Thank you.    
    
    
    "digital culture has co-opted the language of revolution and magic without the ethics, conviction, or imagination." http://is.gd/frankch     
    
    
    For those that missed it last night -"It’s nearly impossible to organize to change things if everyone is moving fast" http://is.gd/frankch     
    
    
    "A mythology of speed is one of willful ignorance to the small details that hold the whole arrangement together." http://is.gd/frankch     
    
    
    "Your thing becomes *our* thing. This is deeply unsettling, but it is also a beautiful situation that binds us to one another." @fchimero    
    
    
    Can we all please give @zenbullets a massive around of applause, please, for his stunning new video for @65dos: http://vimeo.com/75299268     
    
    
    "I just wrote a computer algorithm, and the computer did it all." - @zenbullets on the aptly named PRISMS by @65dos: http://vimeo.com/75299268     
    
    
    . @SciencePunk @zenbullets, who made it is also from Brighton (as are Semiconductor). The emerging Algo-Culture centre of Europe? ;)    
    
    
    Tickets selling fast for Digital Late (http://is.gd/digitallate ). @jeffnoon is giving a reading & we're unveiling this http://is.gd/theoperator     
    
    
    At the Digital Late, @hidingandseeking will show new games & there is music & stories from @christt & @Therematrix: http://is.gd/digitallate     
    
    
    And if that's not enough, DJ @AlabasterC of Audiosyncracy will be playing tunes at the Digital Late throughout: http://is.gd/digitallate     
    
    
    Super to see the brilliant @juliaxgulia on the "50 people in NYC’s tech scene that you need to know" list: 
http://thenextweb.com/us/2013/09/25/50-people-in-nycs-tech-scene-that-you-need-to-know/5/ …    
    
    
    Some words by @adactio on The Literary Operator by @tom_armitage & @jeffnoon premiering tomorrow at the Digital Late: http://adactio.com/journal/6508/     
    
    
    All assembled at @dukesatkomedia for the second of @LighthouseArts' conferences this month, reFramed: http://is.gd/storyscape  #BDF2013    
    
    
    Emily from @LighthouseArts' stresses Brighton's role within the film industry, hosting a Creative England Talent Centre & a BFI Audience Hub    
    
    
    Moderator, Chris Smith, gives OpenGL and OpenFrameworks a shout-out at #reFramedfilm #BDF2013    
    
    
    Hilary Perkins on attention patterns (hi @matlock!) & the limits of the audience data BARB (http://www.barb.co.uk/ ) collects #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    . @cowbite stresses the importance of the audiences - the fans - in worldbuilding. Echoing @BaconMeteor talk at #dConstruct #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    @paulrobertlloyd Norman Kirk is a revelation isn't he?    
    
    
    "Producers & commissioners *do* watch Twitter when programmes go out. It's already having an effect on scheduling." @cowbite #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Been looking forward to this. @cfonnes introducing the online mystery, Cloud Chamber: https://www.facebook.com/CloudChamberMystery … #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "I've been haunted by this question: what is the narrative form for the internet" @cfonnes #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Honestly, Cloud Chamber Mystery by @cfonnes looks awesome. Site goes live on 4 October. Trailer here: http://vimeo.com/72414275  #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "I wanted to figure out the Universe. So, Cloud Chamber is about that." @cfonnes on making astrophysics-based online drama #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "It's like a 3D Wikileaks" @cfonnes on the Cloud Chamber Mystery. Yes, it is that good. #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    So @cfonnes & his team have literally build the geology of T'Rain in the Cloud Chamber Mystery. Landscapes based on real data. #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "We're applying the principles of Dogme 95 to transmedia storytelling" @cfonnes #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "Any sufficiently advanced technology would be indistinguishable from *Nature*." @cfonnes reframing the Arthur C. Clarke quote #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "We're telling a story that combines astrophysics and teenage rebellion." @cfonnes #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Quite difficult to articulate just how extraordinary the Cloud Chamber Mystery by @cfonnes & team is: http://investigatenorth.com/production/cloud-chamber/ … #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Philo van Kemenade (@phivk) has put his slides on web-native storytelling online: http://slid.es/phivk/born-on-the-web … #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    The Cosmonaut (http://en.cosmonautexperience.com/ ) shown by @phivk, a successor to A Swarn of Angels, the first crowdcsourced film #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "Put story first and technology second" - Philo van Kemenade (@phivk) #reFramedfilm. Stellar conference so far. Wish @matlock was here.    
    
    
    "Any sufficiently advanced technology would be indistinguishable from *Nature*" @cfonnes articulates the challenge that SETI face every day.    
    
    
    cf @cfonnes' "any sufficiently advanced technology would be indistinguishable from Nature" reference: http://www.nextnature.net/2012/02/any-sufficiently-advanced-civilization-is-indistinguishable-from-nature/ … (via @gerwitz)    
    
    
    Luke Ritchie showing Forms by @quayola (http://www.quayola.com/forms/ ) at #reFramed. Always looks so good on the big screen.    
    
    
    @cfonnes Or possibly from this general vector (http://www.warrenellis.com/?p=13752 ) or (http://is.gd/kschroeder )? Which is more how you meant it ...    
    
    
    @cfonnes But that article goes include the @bruces variation: “Any sufficiently advanced technology is indistinguishable from its garbage.”    
    
    
    "Websites are written on water." - Simon Pummell on the difficulty of maintaining the 10-year old Bodysong website #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Brand New U, the new SF feature by Simon Pummell looks amazing: http://www.pictureville.net/2013/04/shooting-starts-on-simon-pummells-brand.html … #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    Very happy to hear the @BFI's Lizzie Francke acknowledging the pioneering & ever brilliant work of @blasttheory at #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    "Future scenarios should be thought of as being in perpetual draft form; they should be rewritten constantly": http://is.gd/criticalfutures     
    
    
    "What is exciting about Brighton is that all the BFI's talent development work is being devolved to here & Sheffield" Francke #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    . @blasttheory I should start counting the number of conferences you guys get a shout-out. I'd say is roughly ever third one I go to @BFI    
    
    
    Encouraging to hear Lizzie Francke speaking about the strength artists' moving image & bemoaning the closure of @BFI's gallery #reFramedfilm    
    
    
    So, the director who shot the film sequences for Cloud Chamber directed The Killing. http://investigatenorth.com/production/cloud-chamber/ … #reFramedFilm    
    
    
    "There is no town square for Google" - *excellent* piece on critical design & conflict territories by @tobias_revell: http://is.gd/ConflictTerritories …    
    
    
    "The entities constructing & steering our futures aren't states & they work on a completely different geopolitical strata" @tobias_revell    
    
    
    "Snowden issued a call for action & the world failed to respond. I have a term for this reaction - shocked acquiescence." @tobias_revell    
    
    
    If you missed it at the Digital Late, watch the film of The Literary Operator by @jeffnoon & @tom_armitage here: http://is.gd/theoperator     
    
    
    Are you a curator fascinated by data and art? Then @LighthouseArts @UKODI & @FuturEverythin want to hear from you: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/about/opportunities …    
    
    
    Data as Culture makes the point that open data is a cultural concern, not just a technological issue: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/about/opportunities … cc @UKODI    
    
    
    "globally connected networks, tools for unknown futures & physical manifestations of digital worlds": http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/about/opportunities … #dataasculture    
    
    
    @tobias_revell Agreed. And I think your notion of 'shocked acquiescence' is a good description of that bit of the population cc @Dymaxion    
    
    
    Open data is a cultural concern, not just a technological matter. Happy to be working with @UKODI on #dataasculture: http://is.gd/dataasculture     
    
    
    Wishing our friends at @clearleft all the best wishes as they move into their new space. We're going to miss them.    
    
    
    Nature pick up on @FrankWilczek  & @LKrauss1's beautiful quantum gravity paper: http://is.gd/gravitonnature  (paper here: http://is.gd/gravitons )    
    
    
    Japanese space agency plans a power station in space to capture sunlight & beam the energy down: http://is.gd/solarprog  (@via @Dr_Lucie)    
    
    
    Here's @imperialigem's latest creation -  enhanced plastic producing E.coli. See:  http://2013.igem.org/Team:Imperial_College/PHB_production … & pic.twitter.com/DZqpPyj4wm #iGEM13    
    
    
    @wonderlandblog it's quite good.    
    
    
    "This paper proposes a context-aware sensor search, selection & ranking model" http://arxiv.org/abs/1309.3618  - the coming era of IoT sensor search.    
    
    
    @gileslane This looks amazing.  Thanks, Giles.  cc @leashless @njeremijenko    
    
    
    Saturn's moons deliver up yet more surprises: http://is.gd/propylene  - propylene, an ingredient in plastic, has been found on Titan.    
    
    
    A primer on our new now - "Reality as failed state; its interior collapsing into permanent conflict" http://is.gd/realityfail  (via @changeist)    
    
    
    Someday Somewhere Beyond by @deepspeedmedia is premiering at @imaginescience on 13 October: http://is.gd/somedaysomewhere … - I urge you to *go*.    
    
    
    "our lives are influenced by technologies not simply as objects but invisible systems that surround us" @SciencePunk https://medium.com/futures-exchange/4bc7c8dcd5 …    
    
    
    Are you a curator interested in data? There's just over a week to get your proposals in for #dataasculture http://is.gd/dataasculture  cc @UKODI    
    
    
    *Hugely* important piece by novelist, John Lanchester, on why the Snowden revelations concern us all: http://is.gd/lanchester  - a must-read.    
    
    
    "Take a hypothetical ... ability to eavesdrop on any room via an electrical socket." http://is.gd/lanchester  -paging @julian0liver #newstweek    
    
    
    "Snowden's revelations are not just interesting or important but vital, because the state is about to get powers that no state has ever had"    
    
    
    potential game-changer ... "Ikea has announced plans to sell flat-packed solar panels." http://www.dezeen.com/2013/10/01/ikea-to-sell-flat-pack-solar-panels/ … (via @cityofsound)    
    
    
    Beautiful work from @Loop.pH (Rachel Wingfield & Mathias Gmachl) - a dome based on bonds between carbon atoms: http://is.gd/loopPH     
    
    
    A taste of things to come perhaps. @NASA's website is now down, presumably due to the #shutdown. pic.twitter.com/rbHgMPvokM    
    
    
    A world without @NASA. #shutdown pic.twitter.com/WwsAAmjbFN    
    
    
    Excited to see @rhizome's Seven on Seven line-up of artists & technologists. Happy to be on the honorary committee: http://is.gd/sevenonseven     
    
    
    Seven on Seven teams up major artists like Susan Philipsz & Haroon Mirza with technologists like @iamdanw & @smarimc: http://is.gd/sevenonseven     
    
    
    Just when you thought @monamuseum couldn't get any more awesome: http://is.gd/mona_  - Art & science team up for environmental clean-up.    
    
    
    Cloud Chamber - the most ambitious transmedia project I've seen, has launched! http://cloudchambermystery.com/  - *Highly* recommended. #cloudchamber    
    
    
    Is an 'ethics', or at least a 'code of conduct' for design-fiction necessary?    
    
    
    Jawdropping - NASA have actually banned Chinese researchers (including those based in the States!) from a conference: http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/05/us-scientists-boycott-nasa-china-ban …    
    
    
    "Nasa officials rejected applications from Chinese nationals citing a law which prohibits anyone from China setting foot in a Nasa building"    
    
    
    "Science is supposed to be open to all and restricting those who can attend by nationality goes against years of practice" @chrislintott    
    
    
    @paulmison I respectfully disagree. It could have been shifted to a different venue. Indefensible to ban scientists for political reasons.    
    
    
    @paulmison I can't believe that venue expenses would trump the principles of open science, which remained in place even during the Cold War.    
    
    
    You're all deep in the Cloud Chamber, right? http://cloudchambermystery.com/game/  #cloudchamber #radioastronomy #neutrinos #helioseismology    
    
    
    The #cloudchamber is "the most ambitious attempt yet at creating a new form of fiction for the internet" http://cloudchambermystery.com/game/     
    
    
    @mildlydiverting Part ARG, part interactive film. It's genuinely amazing. It's seriously worth checking out. Have raved to @matlock about it    
    
    
    @mildlydiverting @matlock Its shot by the people who filmed The Killing. So part Nordic Noir, part Wonders of the Universe. 'Science Noir'.    
    
    
    @cityofsound but Joi Ito's point is that this is not the case. He's arguing for a skillset that includes all four. & I'd agree with that.    
    
    
    @cityofsound surely we've moved beyond making the traditional art-science v design-engineering distinctions. Reality is more intertwingled.    
    
    
    "The most essential challenge we face today is related to the real effect of the Internet.": http://tmblr.co/ZdGpWxwxSJU2  cc @danmcquillan    
    
    
    @cityofsound yes, there's an element of truth in that, for sure. But I'd suggest that's more nurture than nature, if you know what I mean?    
    
    
    @cityofsound indeed you are. Which I'm very happy about. :)    
    
    
    Seeking an alternative venue for the Kepler Science Conference: http://tangledfields.com/2013/10/06/seeking-alternate-venue-for-the-kepler-science-conference/ … - a vital plea from @shaka_lulu. Cc @chrislintott    
    
    
    @tcross81 @AstroKatie @EconSciTech many of the leading Kepler scientists are trying to arrange an alternative venue: http://tangledfields.com/2013/10/06/seeking-alternate-venue-for-the-kepler-science-conference/ …    
    
    
    San Francisco tweeps, the Kepler Conference needs an alternative venue: Can you help? http://tangledfields.com/2013/10/06/seeking-alternate-venue-for-the-kepler-science-conference/ … cc @arielwaldman @adactio    
    
    
    The Kepler conference organisers do not want scientists banned because of where they come from & need another venue: http://is.gd/saveopenscience     
    
    
    Conference on exoplanets seeks a new home, after controversy about Chinese scientists being excluded: http://is.gd/keplerconference …    
    
    
    In case you missed it, the Kepler exoplanets conference may need a new venue, so Chinese scientists aren't excluded: http://is.gd/keplerconference …    
    
    
    Two amazing opportunities for artists: BeamTime, an artist residency in a laser facility: http://is.gd/laserart  (1/2) via @TheArtsCatalyst.    
    
    
    Calling for proposals from artists who've worked on space-based solar power for a big exhibition: http://is.gd/solarart  (2/2) #solarbaroque    
    
    
    Big news from @CERN: the CLOUD experiment makes a major advance in solving a long-standing enigma in climate science: http://is.gd/cloudexperiment     
    
    
    This October the space telescope Planck "will end its days making a slow turn around the Sun." http://is.gd/goodbyePlanck     
    
    
    OK, we're on!    
    
    
    Francois Englert & Peter W. Higgs have been awarded 2013 #NobelPrize in #Physics. Just the two. No CERN.    
    
    
    Spare a thought for Guralnik, Hagen and Kibble. #NobelPrize    
    
    
    This is a great photo. Jubilation for @ATLASexperiment & @CMSexperiment physicists @CERN for the #NobelPrize result pic.twitter.com/a3eSdP6LiL    
    
    
    "Apparently Peter Higgs has gone on holiday without a phone. Seriously. Brilliant." - @malcfairbairn (via @AstroKatie) #Higgs #NobelPrize    
    
    
    Can't help thinking that 4 July 2012 was a more important day for Peter Higgs than today. #NobelPrize    
    
    
    Here at last … the physics community reacts to the nobel prize for Francois Englert & Peter Higgs: http://is.gd/hereatlast     
    
    
    "Nobel prizes are for discovery, Higgs & Englert discovered the theory, Cern discovered the reality" @jonmbutterworth http://is.gd/hereatlast     
    
    
    The "history of science ... is always vastly more complex than the simple stories we tell ourselves" @MattStrassler: http://is.gd/hereatlast     
    
    
    @GdnCulturePros Really?! Wow, that's a complete surprise. Thanks for letting me know.    
    
    
    Very humbled to be nominated by readers of @GdnCulturePros for the @TheHospitalClub's 100 top creative professionals: http://is.gd/thc100     
    
    
    Astronauts reflect on the Overview Effect: http://vimeo.com/55073825  cc @deepspeedmedia    
    
    
    @justinpickard I think that's probably what @deepspeedmedia's would say too: http://www.imaginesciencefilms.org/2013/09/30/someday-somewhere-beyond/ …    
    
    
    @erocdrahs Thank very much, kind sir. That's a very lovely thing to say.    
    
    
    @TomNullpointer I think that' the first time anyone's sung me a song on Twitter, Tom. So thank you for, once again, being a pioneer.    
    
    
    @matlock Thanks Matt!    
    
    
    @SciencePunk @RadioKate Some of us literally: http://vimeo.com/55073825#     
    
    
    “This year’s prize is about taking the chemical experiment to cyberspace” - Karplus, Levitt & Warshel receive #Nobel: http://blogs.nature.com/news/2013/10/nobels-2013-chemistry-prize-goes-to-computer-modelers.html …    
    
    
    And for those who follow such things, Thomson Reuters are 1 for 3. Not their best year: http://thomsonreuters.com/press-releases/092013/nobel-laureates … #Nobel #Futurism    
    
    
    @cvansoutheast Thank you very much for this. That's incredibly kind.    
    
    
    @thejaymo @m1k3y @justinpickard @ar7w1n And leave them there? A sort-of reverse-Elysium-meets-Gravity kind of scenario?    
    
    
    @m1k3y @thejaymo @justinpickard @ar7w1n So a kind-of "Overview Effect Enforcement Unit"? Presumably best experienced untethered & terrified?    
    
    
    The Curious Link Between Online Gaming and Chinese Regional Culture: https://medium.com/the-physics-arxiv-blog/f482a7946e50 … (via @arxivblog)    
    
    
    @nraford But that misses out the Overview Effect Enforcement Unit. (PS. I *love The Similarity) cc @thejaymo @m1k3y @justinpickard @ar7w1n    
    
    
    Very happy to announce that HELIX by @davidblandy @AdamRutherford & @DanielULocke opens at @GV_Art on 24 October: http://is.gd/helixgvart     
    
    
    @katybeale Right you are! I'll correct that now. Thanks!    
    
    
    Open data is a cultural concern, not just a technological matter: http://is.gd/dataasculture  - proposals for #dataasculture are due this Sunday.    
    
    
    @heathercorc @eyebeamnyc ! Did I miss an announcement??    
    
    
    Big news for New York - the fabulous @eyebeamnyc are moving from Chelsea to downtown Brooklyn: http://us4.campaign-archive1.com/?u=c72c271895f3f76b36105229c&id=144f66ff5f …    
    
    
    Infrastructure Friction, anyone? Should we fear hackers in the electricity grid?: http://is.gd/infrastructurefriction …    
    
    
    Very. Interesting. @eyebeamnyc "also expect to collaborate with Science Gallery International on exhibitions." http://us4.campaign-archive1.com/?u=c72c271895f3f76b36105229c&id=144f66ff5f …    
    
    
    @justinpickard @christt @marcosgcm @anabjain @carabelljones @ablerism @changeist @AlabasterC thank you all, so much for the birthday wishes!    
    
    
    Diamond rain in the skies of Jupiter & Saturn: http://www.space.com/23135-diamond-rain-jupiter-saturn.html … (via @UnlikelyWorlds)    
    
    
    Sailing The Seas Of Superdensity - @changeist calls for a shipping forecast for weird, new normal futures: http://www.superflux.in/blog/superdensity …    
    
    
    I think @willsh, especially, will understand the deep resonance of @changeist's call for a futures shipping forecast: http://www.superflux.in/blog/superdensity …    
    
    
    Huge! The law banning Chinese scientists from the Kepler conference may've been misinterpreted: http://phys.org/news/2013-10-nasa-chinese-scientists-boycott.html … (via @deepspeedmedia)    
    
    
    Congressman Wolf's letter to NASA correcting the record on restrictions for Chinese nationals: http://wolf.house.gov/press-releases/wolf-letter-to-nasas-bolden-correcting-record-on-restrictions-involving-chinese-nationals/ … via @deepspeedmedia    
    
    
    @deepspeedmedia WHAT?!    
    
    
    "for all the points of the compass, there is only one direction, and time is its only measure." Tom Stoppard. for Julian.    
    
    
    Last hour to respond to the call for proposals for #dataasculture: http://is.gd/dataasculture  - Curators' proposals are due by midnight.    
    
    
    Thinking of some of the amazing scientists & technologists who inspire me this #AdaLovelaceDay. Will call a few out … #ALD13    
    
    
    After the Nobels, I'm thinking of Fabiola Gianotti who helped make this the most unforgettable day of 2012: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Tnd8bxDYOs … #ALD13    
    
    
    A shout-out to @JannaLevin for articulating the sonic dimensions of space so beautifully & for being the ultimate renaissance woman #ALD13    
    
    
    To @lirarandall for having a brilliant idea whilst climbing rocks a few years ago, and having a whole plethora of them since. #ALD13    
    
    
    To Laura Mersini-Houghton for her lucid formula of how to locate a multiverse: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OAL1-vzMvmA … #ALD13    
    
    
    And a bit closer to home, shout-outs to two people who help me think about the world differently, most days: @alicebell & @gsvoss #ALD13    
    
    
    I have a few artists to do #AdaLovelaceDay shout-outs to. They are some of the most rigorous thinkers about science I know. #ALD13    
    
    
    Firstly, please follow @AnnaDumitriu who does pioneering work with bacterial communication & microbiology; http://annadumitriu.tumblr.com/  #ALD13    
    
    
    For biologically-inspired art, follow Julie Freeman (@misslake) http://www.translatingnature.org/ , who also pioneered the @ODI's #dataasnature #ALD13    
    
    
    Follow Lucianne Walkowicz (@shaka_lulu), an astrophysicist specialising in exoplanets & an artist working with data sonification. #ALD13    
    
    
    This #AdaLovelaceDay, check out the visionary @anabjain, speaking about the future of health & genomics: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4PTjUczp6mI … #ALD13    
    
    
    This #ALD13 get following these amazing #SciFoo folks: @soozaphone @ablerism @portablebrain @Magda_Skipper @catallman @helenczerski @flimsin    
    
    
    Jeremy Keith (@adactio) on the pioneering radio astronomer, Jocelyn Bell Burnell: http://adactio.com/journal/6531/  #LGM-1 #unknownpleasures #ADL13    
    
    
    Oh! New Zealand's @EleanorCatton has won the #ManBookerPrize for 'The Luminaries'.  Huge congratulations!    
    
    
    A US #1 and now a #ManBooker prize. Aotearoa culture is having quite a week. Ka pai kē.    
    
    
    Seven on Seven, @rhizome's programme of artists working with technologists, ends with this conference. Come join us: http://rhizome.org/sevenonseven/     
    
    
    “This new space settlement documentary by @deepspeedmedia will make you homesick for a future that has yet to arrive" http://shar.es/EADhn     
    
    
    Someday Somewhere Beyond - the new film by @deepspeedmedia about the future of space colonies. I urge you to watch it http://vimeo.com/75096784     
    
    
    Delighted to be speaking at the Open Data Instutite's Summit on 29 October, with @timberners_lee & other luminaries: http://summit.theodi.org/     
    
    
    @tomhigham I'll see if i can bottle the magic and export it back to the provinces. cc @Macroscopist    
    
    
    If you've ever wondered what the #LHC actually looks like, you might want to be following @TaraShears right about now ...    
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing Covariance by Lyndall Phelps & @benstill today: http://www.physics.org/Superposition/  - artwork inspired by particle detectors.    
    
    
    @Macroscopist Awww, thank you. You've done the same for me *many* *many* times.    
    
    
    Visibility Machines - a new exhibition by Trevor Paglen and Harun Farocki: http://www.umbc.edu/cadvc/exhibitions/VisibilityMachines.php … (via @Macroscopist cc @stml)    
    
    
    "Visibility Machines explores the roles Farocki & Paglen play as meticulous observers of the global military industrial complex."    
    
    
    "Visibility Machines" also includes a panel with the artists & Marko Peljhan. On drones. I think I better go: http://www.umbc.edu/cadvc/exhibitions/VisibilityMachines.php …    
    
    
    It is a huge privilege to be included in the @FTMag's physics special this weekend, alongside many brilliant people: http://is.gd/honorft     
    
    
    Hats off to the @FT for the comprehensive physics edition. Antimatter, a dark energy camera, sounds of space & more. pic.twitter.com/mkJ9me23Ao    
    
    
    @iotwatch @twitter Agreed. It's completely moronic.    
    
    
    @paulmison @iotwatch @twitter It is a massive compromise on core functionality. And a disincentive to use the service.    
    
    
    This week @LighthouseArts is excited to launch HELIX, a story about DNA by @davidblandy, @AdamRutherford & co: http://is.gd/helixgvart     
    
    
        
    
    
    Helix by @davidblandy @AdamRutherford & @DanielULocke, commissioned by @LighthouseArts, is featured in @WIRED: http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2013-10/21/helix-graphic-novel …    
    
    
    @andyhume @nd_kane @LighthouseArts RIght back at you. And we miss you too! (sent from Tweetdeck)    
    
    
    The BBC visit ZKM to find out how iconic media art works by Nam June Paik, Jeffrey Shaw & co are being preserved; http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-24585267 …    
    
    
    Just had a meeting about Helix. There were squeals of excitement. Come see it http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/david-blandy-adam-rutherford-and-daniel-locke-helix … cc @AdamRutherford @davidblandy @GV_Art    
    
    
    "These biological remixes were what we became fixated on whilst discussing the shape of [...] Helix" @AdamRutherford: http://blog.wellcome.ac.uk/2013/10/22/helix-a-different-way-of-looking-at-dna/ …    
    
    
    "Genetic Modification began in 1973, the same year as the birth of hip-hop, & has come to dominate ... biological research" @AdamRutherford    
    
    
    We "found ourselves drawn to the 40,000-year obsession that we have had with swapping biological traits & acquiring non-human ones."    
    
    
    London, @AdamRutherford will give a talk on synthetic biology, copyright & hiphop at the opening of Helix tomorrow: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/david-blandy-adam-rutherford-and-daniel-locke-helix …    
    
    
    @benstill Seriously?    
    
    
    @benstill Even by physics standards, that's a doozy. IMHO, the acronyms are serious proof of the presence of creativity in the field ;)    
    
    
    @benstill Who named the Gadolinium Antineutrino Detector Zealously Outperforming Old Kamiokande experiment (GADZOOK)??    
    
    
    @benstill The paper was written at One Shields Ave, one of the experiments is called WATCHMEN, another is EGADS & GADZOOK …?? Riiiiight.    
    
    
    @timoarnall What? So first @Twitter remove links in DMs, and now this? Is this Make Technology More Dysfunctional Week or something?    
    
    
    "We call it a Digital Biological Converter. And we have the prototype." - Craig Venter on "doing the future": http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/13/craig-ventner-mars …    
    
    
    @peterbihr @alper @kaeru Absolutely! The more the merrier. Plus Adam Rutherford is going to be speaking about synthetic biology & hiphop.    
    
    
    Ahead of his talk at the opening of #Helix tomorrow @AdamRutherford, writes about genetics, hiphop & remixing: http://is.gd/adamhelix     
    
    
    @kaeru Indeed! Plus copyright & genetics. And mutant creatures & chimeras. It will be great to see you, Kars. You too, @alper & @peterbihr.    
    
    
    In town for #playful13? Looking for something to do? Like synbio, hiphop & mutant creatures? We have just the thing! http://is.gd/helixpreview     
    
    
    @alper @peterbihr @kaeru It's at @GV_Art gallery (49 Chiltern Street, London W1U 6LY), 6-9pm: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/david-blandy-adam-rutherford-and-daniel-locke-helix … - talk & drinks at 7pm.    
    
    
    The Large Underground Xenon experiment releases *highly* anticipated #darkmatter results on 30.10: http://www.scientificamerican.com/article.cfm?id=highly-anticipated-dark-matter-update-expected-next-week … (via @caleb_scarf)    
    
    
    @matlock Just heard you on Radio 4. You were great! :-)    
    
    
    Empires of Attention by @matlock: http://wp.me/p5YBr-ce 
- the transcript from Matt's excellent piece for @bbcradio4's Four Thought show.    
    
    
    Highly targeted residencies at @CERN now available RT @benstill: Are you a Swiss web artist or Greek visual artist?: http://press.web.cern.ch/press-releases/2013/10/cern-announces-acceleratecern-programme …    
    
    
    "Open-Access Harassment: Science, technology and women" - an excellent piece of analysis by @alicebell & @gsvoss:  http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/24/open-access-harassment-science-technology-and-women …?    
    
    
    "Bugger Google Glass: build the spectacles which render visible the invisible inequalities of power" - @gsvoss: http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/24/open-access-harassment-science-technology-and-women …?    
    
    
    @LondonCritical Indeed :) & perhaps even more relevantly, The Artvertiser by @julian0liver: http://theartvertiser.com  cc @gsvoss @danmcquillan    
    
    
    Lovely to have @FinalBullet at @LighthouseArts, checking out the prototype of our new studio with @nd_kane, @andrewsleigh & @cataspanglish.    
    
    
    Londoners, come along to the opening of the #Helix show tonight & hear @AdamRutherford speak about genetics & hiphop: http://is.gd/adamhelix     
    
    
    RIP Anthony Caro (1924-2013). He will be dearly missed. http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/entertainment-arts-24654484 …    
    
    
    Helix by @davidblandy @DanielULocke & @AdamRutherford is opening at @GV_Art in 2 minutes. Come along and join us: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/david-blandy-adam-rutherford-and-daniel-locke-helix …    
    
    
    So many people to thank ...    
    
    
    @Kevin_Fong no problem at all. You were with us in spirit. Hope all is well.    
    
    
    @giagia So lovely to see you again. Thanks so much for coming along tonight.    
    
    
    @jonmbutterworth we missed you tonight! But the show's on for a week if you have time to drop by? Cc @giagia @AdamRutherford @m000sh    
    
    
    @easternblot we missed you Eva. But drop by & let me know what you think.    
    
    
    @annabelhuxley @meroec @bnglaser @wynnabbott thank you so much for coming along tonight. It was a wonderful to have you with us.    
    
    
    Huge thanks to @davidblandy @adamrutherford & @DanielULocke for making such a beautiful project. Big thanks too to @storythings & @GV_Art.    
    
    
    @kaeru @alper @peterbihr @iamdanw @justinpickard @tobias_revell Great to see you all this evening at the Helix launch. Thank you for coming.    
    
    
    @easternblot Hi Eva, it's on until the 30 October. There's a talk on Saturday at 3pm too.    
    
    
    Morning all you #playful13 folks. Hope you have an amazing day. Wish I could be with you, but Amsterdam & the #Dread symposium await.    
    
    
    @DigitalanUK Thank you Al. Was awesome to see you & @timohannay last night.    
    
    
    @marksimpkins a symposium on anxiety & technology, post-PRISM: https://www.facebook.com/events/1427812167435274/ …    
    
    
    Sending lots of good luck wishes to @natalie_l_lloyd for #TEDxBrighton today. The @LighthouseArts team will be there in force.    
    
    
    Off to see the @dread exhibition. & then keynoting at the symposium tomorrow: http://www.dehallen.nl/en/activities/  - if you're in Amsterdam, come along.    
    
    
    Who authors our futures? Great piece on the dangers of technological hype in today's @guardian by @justinpickard:  http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/25/dont-believe-the-hype-who-authors-our-futures …    
    
    
    "we are ... living in a world of high-frequency trading algorithms, remotely-piloted drones, and 'normal accidents'" http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/oct/25/dont-believe-the …    
    
    
    "Dread is ineffable, a bad sublime, a dark awe. It's the surplus value of fear" China Mieville in the #dread. pic.twitter.com/PlEwKIcx41    
    
    
    Like emissaries from the Lighthouse past & present, They Watch the Moon by @trevorpaglen & Satellite Lamps. #dread pic.twitter.com/Yb5WVNLPQ2    
    
    
    Here is the sublime Robot Readable World by @timoarnall, surrounded by dystopic lithographs by Constant. #dread pic.twitter.com/R8P9WeDZV8    
    
    
    Sounds like @anabjain rocked #poptech  the inexorable march of The New Normal continues ...    
    
    
    The Light of God by @jamesbridle  (after Omer Fast) - made real & hanging in a gallery. #dread pic.twitter.com/PzEGEeO4SE    
    
    
    Around 15 years after the fact, the @guardian discovers glitch: http://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2013/oct/25/rise-of-glitch-art … (via @juliaxgulia)    
    
    
    The article, as the comments point out, largely confuses pixelation for glitch art. But hey, it;'s a start: http://www.theguardian.com/artanddesign/2013/oct/25/rise-of-glitch-art …    
    
    
    I'm speaking about invisibility in the post_PRISM Age at the @dreadexhibition symposium in Amsterdam today: http://www.eyefilm.nl/en/dread-fear-in-the-age-of-technological-acceleration …    
    
    
    The view from the conference room at the EYE museum, where we are about to start talking about technological Dread. pic.twitter.com/36KfmVi2dl    
    
    
    @caleb_k more about mechanised surveillance, The Cloud, misapplied metaphor, clandestine satellites, drones & conceptual insurgency. :)    
    
    
    "The invention of the ship was also the invention of the shipwreck" @juhavantzelfde quoting Virilio kicks off #Dread pic.twitter.com/7TdLSK62GE    
    
    
    "The Devils Gate" by Mark Bain - one of the most powerful works in #Dread - is a continuous drone chord. pic.twitter.com/wkYzxM9VCF    
    
    
    Roger Hiorns' stunning atomized jet engine, displayed on the floor of #Dread, almost like a dislocated moonscape. pic.twitter.com/YS4sUcgVDx    
    
    
    "The obscene is what does away with every mirror, every image" - Mark Fisher quoting Baudrillard at #dread: (PDF)
http://www.conductiveoutfit.com/mta/technologyandmen/readings/Baudrillard%20-%20The%20Ecstacy%20of%20Communication.pdf …    
    
    
    The notes for my #dread talk - "Invisibility in the Post-PRISM Era" - are online here: http://is.gd/postprism     
    
    
    Fisher on Dick "Some of [his] most powerful passages are those in which there is an ontological interregnum": http://k-punk.abstractdynamics.org/archives/011246.html … #dread    
    
    
    Seeing correlations with Fisher's Capitalist Realism: http://is.gd/nimuvi  & @jamesbridle's Network Realism: http://booktwo.org/notebook/network-realism … #dread    
    
    
    "I have no time to recharge my own batteries, because I'm constantly recharging the batteries of my devices." - Mark Fisher #dread    
    
    
    "Asking if there's a payphone in the UK today is like asking if there's a gramophone available to use." - Mark Fisher #dread    
    
    
    "Being on Twitter is consenting to being in a constant state of panic." - Mark Fisher #dread    
    
    
    "Twitter is the leading edge of the screaming panic of technology. This sense of being constantly, structurally late." @kpunk99 #dread    
    
    
    "Twitter, like free newspapers, leads you to be curious about things you're not even interested in." @kpunk99 #dread    
    
    
    "We're seeing the micro-level engineering of human behaviour on a marco-scale". Mark Fisher (@kpunk99) #dread    
    
    
    "We all now accept that life is simply the thing you do in between being online. You have to have something to tweet about." @kpunk99 #dread    
    
    
    Mark Fisher (@kpunk99) speaking eloquently about the tactile power of The Otolith Group's film, Anathema: http://lux.org.uk/collection/works/anathema … #dread    
    
    
    "'Join the debate!' - corporations constantly entreat us to do that. Why would anyone go to the l'Oreal website to debate?" @kpunk99 #dread    
    
    
    "Whilst we might be in a world of technological acceleration, we're also in a world of cultural stagnation" @kpunk99 #dread (really??!)    
    
    
    Suspect Mark Fisher might be mistaking correlation for causation with that last statement. & don't agree we're culturally stagnating #dread    
    
    
    "We are experiencing the effect of the crazed decoupling of communications from function; it has become a telos in itself" @kpunk99 #dread    
    
    
    Next up at the #dreadsymposium, we are seeing the Dutch premiere of Blind Data, a new piece by Silvia Maglioni and Graeme Thomson on drones.    
    
    
    Trying to work out if Terminal Beach's deliberate juxtaposition of drones and drone music is a first. Certainly very welcome #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    "There is a need for a deceleration of perception. What we have right now is blurred vision." Graeme Thompson #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    It's the future. Take it? MT @KatrionaBeales: why not practice over-identifying instead? Embrace overload! Resisting the flow is pointless?    
    
    
    And now to close the #dreadsymposium @mthvn will speak about failed states & how surveillance watermarks reality pic.twitter.com/MQAqVqeSDJ    
    
    
    Unsettling stuff by @mthvn, showing the hypocrisy of the Head of the NSA, General Keith Alexander. #dreadsymposium pic.twitter.com/dfga2JEqQY    
    
    
    "The NSA has become the overly attached girlfriend [or boyfriend] of the world" -  @mthvn at #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    "Every society gets the drone it deserves." - @mthvn #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    Metahaven (@mthvn) bringing @smarimc  to the #dreadsymposium to talk about code, law & infrastructure. pic.twitter.com/RDqlsw94HL    
    
    
    "Law is the software upon which society is run. And it has a lot of bugs." - @smarimc, as seen in @mthvn's talk in the #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    Anthropomorphising submarine cables to make internet infrastructure more legible. @mthvn #dreadsymposium pic.twitter.com/Z24lAVeWCE    
    
    
    Metahaven calls for a Large Data Collider, operating on the Russian-Norwegian border. #dreadsymposium pic.twitter.com/Lbw0BI3PpO    
    
    
    @attikusf It's a reference from my talk, "Invisibility in the Post-Prism Era" : http://is.gd/postprism  cc @dreadexhibition @GreatDismal    
    
    
    "Pattern recognition & algorithms  replace decision making." @mthvn in the film Black Transparency. #dreadsymposium pic.twitter.com/FhRWiyqhVm    
    
    
    @brakemitchell Spook Country.    
    
    
    Seriously brilliant, and somewhat devastating, presentation by the amazing @mthvn at the #dreadsymposium. Worth the admission price alone.    
    
    
    "One of the problems of the militant left is that it does not have a visual sensibility. We want to help with this." @mthvn #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    Thank you so much to @dehallenhaarlem & @juhavantzelfde for a inspiring & unrelenting day at the #dreadsymposium.    
    
    
    Just you wait till @mthvn release the Black Transparency film online. Just wait. It's the very embodiment of the zeitgeist. #dreadsymposium    
    
    
    A Mobile Robotic Personal Nightstand with Integrated Perceptual Processes: http://arxiv.org/abs/1310.4168  cc @iotwatch !    
    
    
    @DanielULocke Dan, thanks so much for this. It makes everything we do worthwhile. It's the reason why we do what we do. cc @timohannay    
    
    
    @jkleske yep.    
    
    
    So who is going to be at @rhizome's Seven on Seven conference today? http://is.gd/sevenonseven     
    
    
    The brilliant Graham Harwood takes the stage at #7xLDN - Looking forward to see what he came up with. pic.twitter.com/LjaiSEvtp7    
    
    
    "Databases are truth machines. They create a kind of governance." Graham Harwood on relationships between knowledge & power. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Voter turnout is 35.9% in Lithuania. A sad reflection on the collapse of trust in political parties. cf. Alberto Nardelli's talk at #7xLDN    
    
    
    "Harwood asks, "Why make numbers visible? What you are trying to is change conduct" - becoming visible is *the* theme of the year. @#7xLDN    
    
    
    "We abstract something to process it, creating remote control over its materiality" Graham Harwood being particularly astute at #7xLDN    
    
    
    "There's a dark futurist machine constantly at work trying to plot your data" - Harwood on how medical records shape cities #7xLDN    
    
    
    "This is what these numbers are about. This data is about the contingencies of the now" - Harwood at #7xLDN    
    
    
    "We have entire systems built around not reality, but *perceptions* of reality." - Alberto Nardelli at #7xLDN    
    
    
    Actually quite glad to see Harwood & Alberto Nardelli discuss motivations & politics rather "creative trinkets" made in a day. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Mark Leckey & @iamdanw take the stage at #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/8g965Uj97a    
    
    
    Mark Leckey makes the important point that its difficult to create anything meaningful in one day. Collaboration takes time. #7xLDN    
    
    
    "Flip flopping is a term by Robin Sloan that describes making something digital physical and then making it digital again" @iamdanw #7xLDN    
    
    
    "One of my interests is making the infrastructures of technology legible" - @iamdanw channeling Bridle & Arnall at #7xLDN    
    
    
    It's fast becoming apparent that the real value of 7on7 has been the conversations between the participants. Which is no bad thing. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Mark Leckey made a work about the inner thoughts of an Internet fridge. Deeply wonderful. #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/LcjCdzioPH    
    
    
    Excellent. @iamdanw presenting @HardSciFiMovies & @DroneInsertion at #7xLDN    
    
    
    Fascinating analysis of the animistic qualities of the Internet of Things by @iamdanw & Leckey. With the obligatory reference to OOO #7xLDN    
    
    
    "It's like the machines have got a discoball that we can't see" @iamdanw showing a Kinect field in infrared. #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/0ZZVURLKUT    
    
    
    The Internet of Dreams - where the real and the fictional happily coexist. As described by @iamdanw. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Important point there by Mark Leckey "Dan was too sympathetic". That's because @iamdanw has a creative practice of his own. #7xLDN    
    
    
    "Once you put something in a gallery, you cut of its media-cyborg dimension" - massively important point there by @iamdanw #7xLDN    
    
    
    Susan Phillipsz & Naveen Selvaduri showing Eames' Powers of Ten at #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/9UeFNeSS9E    
    
    
    Susan Phillipsz speaking of sonifying radio & Marconi's notion of the permanent resonance of soundwaves. That makes me feel at home #7xLDN    
    
    
    Aleksandra Domanovic & @smarimc take the stage at #7xLDN. This feels like a very good pairing. pic.twitter.com/XYP2KTRPX7    
    
    
    "The first outcome of our collaboration was that @smarimc made me encrypt my email." - Aleksandra Domanovic. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Aleksandra Domanovic presenting "The Philosopher's Hand". "It's indecipherable unless you're an alchemist".  #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/0QUDjVruO0    
    
    
    Interesting analysis by @smarimc about the iconography of privacy - the prevalence of the metaphor of the lock & key.  #7xLDN    
    
    
    Domanovic & @smarimc present their ideas for how to better visualise the semiotics of privacy & security. #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/KRbFrq7rKs    
    
    
    The only good thing about the horrendous NSA Powerpoint presentations is that they've taken the heat off particle physics Powerpoints #7xLDN    
    
    
    If you liked that work on visual semiotics, you might like to check out Occupy the Cloud by @jamesbridle: http://www.themovingmuseum.com/index.php/exhibitions/view/open-heart-surgery … #7xLDN    
    
    
    Cecile B. Evans & Alice Bartlett take the stage to talk about spambots. #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/4xwIpKxHWD    
    
    
    Dust by Greg Egan gets a somewhat unlikely name check by Cecile Evans at #7xLDN    
    
    
    @mildlydiverting To be fair, many of her (former) colleagues from Atlas tease Fabiola about Comic Sans too ...    
    
    
    "How do we make these algorithmic systems more visible?" @alicebartlett continues on this year's big theme. #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/pcQfz7Qc7d    
    
    
    Here are the notes from the 7on7 collaboration between Dan Williams (@iamdanw) and Mark Leckey: http://www.iamdanw.com/wrote/seven-on-seven/ … #7xLDN    
    
    
    Here's the 7on7 project by @cecilebevans & @alicebartlett: http://sevenonseven.herokuapp.com  #7xLDN    
    
    
    And @ryder_ripps just won the conference. #7xLDN    
    
    
    So @ryder_ripps & Haroon Mirza made this: http://aboutwhateveritis.com  & then performed it live. You sort of had to be there. #7xLDN    
    
    
    Ok. This is brilliant. Eeeeemail (http://eeeeemail.com ) by Jonas Lund & Michelle You. Disturbing & playful #7xLDN pic.twitter.com/IICZo5YwQp    
    
    
    Lou Reed. Really??    
    
    
    Oh no. It's true. Farewell Lou Reed. http://m.rollingstone.com/music/news/lou-reed-velvet-underground-leader-and-rock-pioneer-dead-at-71-20131027 …    
    
    
    So we are all officially stranded due to The Storm Coming. And Lou Reed is dead. Suddenly it all gets a bit apocalyptic.    
    
    
    @skry Hiya. The talks weren't recorded, unfortunately. I will see if I can write it up at some point though ...    
    
    
    @ryder_ripps @bitpshr Very good to know. Thanks Ryder. The presentation yesterday was brilliant. Thank you.    
    
    
    Morning all. We've got 2 exhibition on this week: Helix in London (http://is.gd/helixgvart ) & Immaterials in Brighton: http://is.gd/immaterials     
    
    
    This week I'm speaking at the @UKODI Summit in London: http://summit.theodi.org/speakers/  & at the Cambridge Festival of Ideas: http://www.anglia.ac.uk/ruskin/en/home/microsites/code/code_events.html# …    
    
    
    Simultaneous announcements from @BERGLONDON's re their connected products focus & @uah re @umbrellium. London - the IoT capital of the world    
    
    
    Incredible documentary on Māori astronomy & Māori science more broadly: http://www.maoritelevision.com/tv/shows/project-matauranga/S02E008/project-matauranga-series-2-episode-8 … - huge thanks to @astrokiwi for the link.    
    
    
    I'm speaking at the #ODIsummit today, with @timberners_lee & co. Stay tuned for a big announcement from the @UKODI @LighthouseArts later on.    
    
    
    Pleased to announce that @LighthouseArts has joined the @UKODI international network as its Brighton node: http://is.gd/ODInode  #opendata    
    
    
    As well as working with @UKODI on Data as Culture, which we'll be talking about at #odisummit, @LighthouseArts is also a node in the network    
    
    
    At the #ODIsummit. Shortly @agentGav & @timberners_lee will call the new ODI nodes on stage to signup to the network pic.twitter.com/WdV2N82qRb    
    
    
    Gavin Starks (@agentGav) kicks off the inaugural #ODIsummit in London. pic.twitter.com/KmR63fyE3T    
    
    
    "There is a real buzz around open government data at the moment" - Tim Berners-Lee (@timberners_lee) #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/zs2krXJQkj    
    
    
    "These are our beautiful data sets" @billt channeling Talking Heads with @timberners_lee @bethnovak & Co #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/zS4v9xN18B    
    
    
    "There was a nifty moment with Gordan Brown where he asked what we should do. I said put your data online. He said "Yes"!" @timberners_lee    
    
    
    "We have hundreds of thousands of open datasets around the world. We have a culture & an infrastructure of open data" @bethnovak #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "This community is driven by passion." @Nigel_Shadbolt speaking eloquently about the collective spirit of the #opendata movement #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "There is nothing like a default for open yet. There is a long way to go. We need better egs of open innovation" @Nigel_Shadbolt #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "Everybody is somebody's tech support" @Nigel_Shadbolt quips as @timberners_lee helps out with his mic #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/kskdmE5kPp    
    
    
    "We need to know who within the future political class we need to infect with a passion for #opendata" @Nigel_Shadbolt #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "This week the National Infrastructure Report comes out. It will say data is as valuable as the electrical grid" @Nigel_Shadbolt #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "There could be an open data Winter" - @Nigel_Shadbolt urges persistence and caution at #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/0oxjADJPyA    
    
    
    Our fellow #ODInode member, @toodrew from @FuturEverythin,g introduces their work with data & culture #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/Ju0qKNW3QQ    
    
    
    And now @obviousjim joins the #ODIsummit via @toodrew. This his work, Clouds by James George & @deepspeedmedia. pic.twitter.com/CF6T9Qe4GF    
    
    
    "This is our culture. Openness is our culture." @toodrew at the #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/qWWMhkBQEn    
    
    
        
    
    
    "We need to be relevant to the streets of Istanbul, just as much as the High Street in the UK." Tisne #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/qm5uIBSunC    
    
    
    Excellent intervention by @martintisne about activism, human rights, "open-washing" & representation. #ODIsummit pic.twitter.com/T4cWnehS0g    
    
    
    “#Openwashing - When states use rhetoric of 'open data' to obfuscate their repressive practices" @martintisne (via @markcote) #odisummit    
    
    
    @alastairdunning we'll address that point at the #DataAsCulture panel at the #ODIsummit this afternoon. Data is a social & cultural concern.    
    
    
    "There's a clear correlation between openness & public approval" - #ODISummit pic.twitter.com/IKjH3zVbGk    
    
    
    "We're having a bit of dialogue about privacy in the US. In case you haven't noticed" - cue laughter & ironic applause. #ODISummit    
    
    
    "Where are the people taking the amazing artworks you have in the @UKODI & putting them in the public realm?" @Marthalanefox #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "Anyone who doubts the Millennial Generation should come to my office. I have tremendous respect for young people" Mike Flowers #ODIsummit    
    
    
    "Government is a data business" - @liammax discussing the value of #opendata to the Government Digital Service (@GOVUK). #ODIsummit    
    
    
    @paulrobertlloyd I'd heard rumours, but didn't realize it was true. You'll be a huge loss for @clearleft. @guardian are lucky to have you.    
    
    
    @paulrobertlloyd oh and I'm really glad you're staying in Brighton! Cc @clearleft @guardian    
    
    
    It was a huge pleasure to speak about #dataasculture with @tonyageh @misslake @hannah_redler & @alastairdunning at the #odisummit    
    
    
    I'm in Cambridge later today to debate smart cities with @uah, @andrewnairne & other luminaries: https://www.cambridge.gov.uk/is-cambridge-a-smart-city-the-potential-for-creative-collaboration-betwen-silicon-fen-and-the-arts …    
    
    
    An definite must-watch stream MT @luxdarkmatter LUX announcing first results tomorrow. Live webcast here: http://sanfordlab.org  #darkmatter    
    
    
    I'll be getting read to talk about the #smartcity as the @luxdarkmatter results come in at 3pm, so can someone let me know what they found?    
    
    
    "I'm interested in a form of smartness which emerges from people rather technology" - Usman Haque (@uah) #smartcam pic.twitter.com/lWoyMlTAUD    
    
    
    "Technology companies are selling us a view of the future where connected technology delivers a kind of homogeneous boredom" @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    "Arts, culture and well being are difficult to measure on a computer" @ClaireMookerjee from the Future City Catapult #smartcam    
    
    
    This. Is. Brilliant.  @jomc and @nimbu can help the Men of the Internet Learn to Search: http://learn-to-search.com/  (via @debcha)    
    
    
    "What is a city? A city is not its buildings or infrastructure. It's the interactions between people and ideas." @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    "Security, predictability & convenience are things that make cities bearable. Not smart." @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    "The people who benefit from efficiency, predictability & convenience are the city managers. Not the citizens" - @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    "When you start seeing the city as a problem to be solved, you lose the capacity to value mess & complexity." - @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    "A better vision of a smart city is one full of smart citizens, not just smart technological infrastructure." - @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    A brilliant vision of what a properly smart city could be by @andrewnairne, highlighting the current absence of smartness #smartcam    
    
    
    "Can a city be smart if so many people can not afford to live here?" @Puffles2010  raises an important sociological question at #smartcam    
    
    
    "A smart city is one that gauges the welfare of all its citizens." @jonpratty underscoring that smartness if not just about tech #smartcam    
    
    
    Seamfulness enters the debate in a discussion about the dystopic dark side of the traditional technological smart city. #smartcam    
    
    
    Seems like there's a massive gap in the market for some kind of art-science-technology agency in Cambridge. #smartcam    
    
    
    "Talking about open data is a bit trendy right now. There's a danger of data spectatorship. Its interpretation that matters" @uah #smartcam    
    
    
    The excellent @MattStrassler on the #LuxDM #darkmatter results and why they matter (excuse the pun): http://wp.me/p1Fmmu-1M8     
    
    
    The 2013 Improving Reality talks are now online at the @LighthouseArts website: http://is.gd/irealityfilms  #ireality    
    
    
    Talks by @timoarnall, Keller Easterling & @SciencePunk show how to make invisible infrastructures visible: http://is.gd/irealityfilms  #ireality    
    
    
    Talks by @PaulGrahamRaven @deziluzija @alexandradaisy & @tobias_revell show how artists & writers are designing new realities. #ireality    
    
    
    And @Flygirltwo @archiville @gsvoss & @justinpickard ask just whose reality we are trying to improve?  http://is.gd/irealityfilms  #ireality    
    
    
    Occupy the Cloud by @jamesbridle: http://booktwo.org/notebook/occupy-the-cloud/ … - moving the debate about data from the physical sphere to the digital & back again    
    
    
    Good to see the Improving Reality talks finding their way through the interwebs. Hope you like them. http://is.gd/irealityfilms  #ireality    
    
    
    @anabjain @matthewward Thank you both, so much.    
    
    
    Black worlds, art for oligarchs, sarcastic drones, camouflaged slides, dream states & devastating illustrations. Thanks Suzanne Treister.    
    
    
    Today is the last day to see Immaterials by @timoarnall @snve @jorngeorg @moleitau & Jack Schulze at @LighthouseArts: http://is.gd/immaterials     
    
    
    You always have tremendous affection for the shows you curate, but I have a special soft spot for #Immaterials by @timoarnall & co.    
    
    
    Fancy some firework *inside* this November? @seb_ly is staging Brighton's only *indoor* fireworks show this month: http://pixelpyros.org/blog/post.php?s=2013-11-01-brighton-event-rescheduled …    
    
    
    There's a theory doing the rounds -mostly propagated by @Benjam8n it should be said -that LinkedIn has suddenly become interesting. Reckons?    
    
    
    Art "is like the large hadron supercollider of the soul" - @Tim_Etchells on the value of art: http://is.gd/whatcanartdo  (via @site_gallery)    
    
    
    Astonishing aerial views of the "strange new human-made landscapes" created by fracking. By @amy_youngs: http://www.flickr.com/photos/amymyou/9431314171/ …    
    
    
    "Sound the pre-crime klaxon - algorithms are intent on passing the bar." -  @quadrophobiac on the CAPTCHA furore: http://www.dazeddigital.com/artsandculture/article/17749/1/through-the-looking-glass-bot …    
    
    
    Ah Brighton. Wild winds, synchronicities, random encounters, autumn light & beautiful people. As always, you'll do.    
    
    
    @changeist @matlock should I arrange some kind of dinner?    
    
    
    @SciencePunk @tobias_revell Ah yes. The Exterminating Angel then?    
    
    
    “We find absolutely no events consistent with any kind of dark matter” - why the LUX results are so important: http://www.nature.com/news/no-sign-of-dark-matter-in-underground-experiment-1.14057 …    
    
    
    Today, I might be pointing you to worlds that artists are growing rather than making, and critical revelations of infrastructures. #ireality    
    
    
    "Our inability to see invisible technological systems thwarts our ability to understand their importance" @timoarnall http://is.gd/revealingreality …    
    
    
    Keller Easterling presents the "retinal afterglow of the soupy matrix, [the] formulas that make space in the world" http://is.gd/revealingreality …    
    
    
    "Infrastructure space is a wilder mongrel than any of our leviathans" - Keller Easterling: http://is.gd/revealingreality … #ireality    
    
    
        
    
    
    As if stocking up on conceptual firewood for Winter, I felt the need to acquire the classic texts by Marx, Benjamin, Emerson, & Kuhn today.    
    
    
    As well as some nice primers by @lirarandall @closefrank, Neil Turok & David Wade. Long nights of reading ahead ...    
    
    
    China Miéville making somewhat unexpected links between Hugo Chávez, witches and Halloween capitalism: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=paCqiY1jwqc&feature=youtu.be … (via @iamdanw)    
    
    
    If ever there was an argument for in-line images, it's this: the Solar Eclipse and Milky Way seen from the ISS: pic.twitter.com/IN1Oa1RJZY    
    
    
    *But* as @BadAstronomer has pointed out, that show-stopping image isn't real. It's an artwork by A4size-ska: http://is.gd/fakeeclipse     
    
    
    Here's one for fans of *reality*. Here's what the eclipse *really* looked like from the ISS: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJ25zCJlUm0 … (via @BadAstronomer)    
    
    
    @w_stanley @benhammersley Indeed. Here's what the eclipse really looked like from on-board the ISS: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QJ25zCJlUm0 …    
    
    
    @BadAstronomer Right you are. But at least it's real.    
    
    
    On Friday's episode of @BBC's Newsnight, @jamesbridle, Oren Yakobovich & co discussed wearable technology & politics: http://is.gd/newsnighttech     
    
    
    "I think it's going to take some kind of Privacy Crash for people to understand what they're giving up" @jamesbridle: http://is.gd/newsnighttech     
    
    
    {Blinks} "no rehearsal, no retakes, trying to collaborate with and accompany, myself.": Russell Davies does In C: http://russelldavies.typepad.com/planning/2013/11/31-days-in-c-a-one-man-portsmouth.html …    
    
    
    What happens to our data is big topic right now & one @aral will be tackling in his Monthly Talk at @LighthouseArts: http://is.gd/araltalk     
    
    
    Thanks to @ChrisUnitt for this analysis of the treatment of digital within @ace_national's new strategic framework: http://www.chrisunitt.co.uk/2013/11/digital-aspects-arts-council-englands-strategic-framework/ …    
    
    
    @matlock care to list?    
    
    
    @AdamRutherford Great news! But what happened to Slovenia?! #IDEAN2013WCJ    
    
    
    @AdamRutherford Ahh, gotcha! So they're even-numbered years?    
    
    
    Timely question given the Kepler conference. @shaka_lulu, want to take a stab? MT @AdamRutherford: Number of exoplanets as of this moment?    
    
    
    @shaka_lulu Thanks Lucianne. I knew you'd be able to help. Suspect @AdamRutherford would prefer confirmed. Would that be right, Adam?    
    
    
    @AdamRutherford Not the optimal moment to ask them to stop, since all the exoplanet hunters are at #Kepler2. Counting. cc @shaka_lulu    
    
    
    @AdamRutherford It is *the* exoplanet conference: http://nexsci.caltech.edu/conferences/KeplerII/ … - You know. The one that generated a fair bit of, err, controversy.    
    
    
    One for @AdamRutherford RT @viXra: Two billion planets in our galaxy may be suitable for life... http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/nov/04/planets-galaxy-life-kepler?CMP=twt_fd …    
    
    
    "Net neutrality is a dead man walking." http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/11/so-the-internets-about-to-lose-its-net-neutrality/ … - a very chilling read about fresh threats to net neutrality (via @erocdrahs)    
    
    
    Disruption Tolerant Networking, a new architecture designed for vast distances. Basically the Internet of Space: http://is.gd/internetofspace     
    
    
    @uah I haven't seen him in a long time either. Will send the scouts. I miss him.  cc @matthewward @agpublic    
    
    
    The historic Mars Orbiter Mission took off at 09:08 GMT this morning. Here's @changeist's take on it: http://qz.com/138940/indias-upcoming-mission-to-mars-is-a-chance-to-best-russia-and-china/ …    
    
    
    @philgyford Saw that one yesterday. Was hoping you'd spotted it. cc  @hondanhon    
    
    
    Very excited to announce that we're prototyping a major new interdisciplinary studio at @LighthouseArts in Brighton: http://is.gd/lighthousestudio …    
    
    
    We are prototyping a new studio at @LighthouseArts. The theme of our first phase of work is our post-PRISM world: http://is.gd/lighthousestudio …    
    
    
    I'm speaking Meaning tomorrow, alongside @falkvinge @umairh and lots of other brilliant people: http://2013.meaningconference.co.uk/  #meaningconf    
    
    
    The first event coming out the @LighthouseArts Studio, kicks off with @aral's talk about digital feudalism. pic.twitter.com/gTCFKdZlbI    
    
    
    This might be the first ever non-dystopian mention of Glass at @lighthousearts. Heres @aral giving our Monthly Talk. pic.twitter.com/WLJgCKTC3A    
    
    
    "The Experience Machine knows everything about the world, everything about you, and it can read your mind" - @Aral. Ie The Machine from POI.    
    
    
    "We need to support open data initiatives. Lighthouse has become a node in the Open Data Institute's international network." @aral    
    
    
    "We have to design the organisation, before we can design the product. The vision must come from the top." @aral pic.twitter.com/IMplrxDbCT    
    
    
    "We need a new category of open technology. Experience-driven open." @aral on "the missing quadrant". pic.twitter.com/JWp0nGx0Jg    
    
    
    @damienmulley @alexkjerulf Lovely to meet you & debate the relativities of Gibson & Stephenson. & Thank you too, @willmcinnes & @tomnixon.    
    
    
    Today, I'll be at the Meaning conference: http://2013.meaningconference.co.uk  Speaking a bit later on & looking forward to everyone's talks #meaningconf    
    
    
    Here's all 3538 known & candidate exoplanets that Kepler has helped us discover so far: pic.twitter.com/LV69pjrdbO (for the #meaningconf crowd)    
    
    
    If you're not at @MeaningConf you can still watch the talks. The live stream is here: http://youtu.be/5YGEhCaT47w  #MeaningConf    
    
    
    Rick @Falkvinge kicks off #MeaningConf with a call to start a revolution. pic.twitter.com/iN2AA6MfML    
    
    
    "If an invasion of privacy wasn't OK in the age of the letter, it's not OK in the age of the net." @Falkvinge #meaningconf    
    
    
    The Pirate Party uses the 3 person rule. If 3 people  think something should happen they have authority to do it. @Falkvinge #meaningconf    
    
    
    Introducing the notion of "intentional nomadism", @MAmusing takes the stage at #meaningconf pic.twitter.com/Nxd2Aw1bVH    
    
    
    "Where is the homefullness in work?" - @MAmusing giving a simply amazing talk at #meaningconf pic.twitter.com/wDDmO1SOLp    
    
    
    "The centre is tired." @MAmusing at #MeaningConf beautifully echoing an ongoing with conversation with @justinpickard #meaningconf    
    
    
    @PhilDyson @PaulGrahamRaven I'm not doing the orchestration. But it's definitely happening. Two NZers speaking at the conference I'm at.    
    
    
    @PhilDyson @PaulGrahamRaven oh and yes, I'm sure Paul knows the obvious stuff from Dunedin. But maybe not Xpressway.    
    
    
    Yimby by @JustGiving - a new crowdfunding community for social good, launching next week, looks great #MeaningConf pic.twitter.com/2xHsgIFIYt    
    
    
    The credits & references from my Meaning talk are online here: http://is.gd/meaningtalk  #MeaningConf    
    
    
    @janefinnis @LighthouseArts aww, thanks, Jane :-)    
    
    
    Happy to hear @dgwbirch speak again. Such a great speaker. He's about to speak about "money hacking". #MeaningConf pic.twitter.com/qvs7KizDzw    
    
    
    Waiting for the bitcoin klaxon. Figuring @dgwbirch will oblige. #MeaningConf    
    
    
    @justinpickard He's being typically witty. Think you would have really enjoyed #MeaningConf. That chat earlier this week was a good primer.    
    
    
    "The paperless office is about as likely as the paperless bathroom" - @dgwbirch is being even more witty than usual at  #MeaningConf    
    
    
    "I have a petition into the government right now to change the police sirens to the Benny Hill theme tune." @dgwbirch #MeaningConf    
    
    
    A big thank you to @tomnixon & @willmcinnes for getting @dgwbirch to #meaningconf. Very funny & highly  illuminating as always.    
    
    
    And there we go - the obligatory bitcoin klaxon. #meaningconf    
    
    
    "Meaning should be eudaimonic" - @umairh at #meaningconf (cc @justinpickard)    
    
    
    "Are we entering a dark age?" - @umairh introducing Jane Jacobs into the discussion. #MeaningConf    
    
    
    "51% of Americans support the NSA's spying program em" - @umairh quoting this poll: http://techcrunch.com/2013/11/05/poll-public-supports-nsa-spying-on-their-email-neighbors-and-foreign-leaders/ … #meaningconf - really not sure :/    
    
    
    "Places like Australia have resisted the draw of billionairism" - @umairh #MeaningConf - what on *Earth* is the evidence base for that?    
    
    
    @gsvoss Sigh. Don't get me started. Ranting on the back-channel. Mining. Letting refugees drown at sea. Genocide. Concentration camps.    
    
    
    "Save business from the businessmen." @leebryant pointing out how profoundly broken traditional company structure is. #MeaningConf    
    
    
    "Are start-ups just a new financial product?" - @leebryant echoing @philgyford's "Our Incredible Journey" tumblr. #meaningconf    
    
    
    "Why is there so little innovation around organisational design?" @leebryant is making a huge amount of sense at #MeaningConf    
    
    
    "More interesting than the technology are the affordances it brings into play" - @leebryant #MeaningConf    
    
    
    The Valve Employees Handbook:  http://newcdn.flamehaus.com/Valve_Handbook_LowRes.pdf … - as quoted in @leebryant's brilliant talk at #MeaningConf    
    
    
    "Institutions codify and give longevity to ideas" - @leebryant on why we need to create new types of institutions.  #MeaningConf    
    
    
    Obligatory reference to the "miraculous GDS" by @leebryant, who emphasises the value of their notion of the "protected space". #MeaningConf    
    
    
    Pretty awesome hearing stories about Paua and Tangaroa at a UK conference. Thanks @MAmusing. #MeaningConf pic.twitter.com/YuAv9TJ7dI    
    
    
    Thoroughly inspiring day at #MeaningConf today. My sincere thanks to @tomnixon & @willmcinnes for curating such a wonderful day of talks.    
    
    
    And lovely, as always, to see @boxman @paulrobertlloyd @clagnut @adactio & the rest of the @clearleft gang today. Now pondering obliquity...    
    
    
    @clagnut @boxman more on ANTARES & neutrino astronomy here : http://is.gd/skybelow  :-)    
    
    
    Wow. Huge. IceCube has discovered two extraterrestrial neutrinos with energies higher than any neutrino detected yet: http://www.symmetrymagazine.org/article/november-2013/ultra-high-energy-neutrinos …    
    
    
    @MAmusing Thank you for your talk. For the notions of eldership & homefulness. For "the centre is tired". & for bringing Tangaroa to Meaning    
    
    
    @thesjef That would be the best neutrino documentary ever! Ice Cube travelling to Antarctica to report on the IceCube results. Genius.    
    
    
    At St Pancras, about to take the train to #ICTArt2013, where I'm speaking tomorrow: http://www.ict-art-connect.eu/event/ictart-connect-2013/ … - see you soon, @AnnaDumitriu.    
    
    
    @changeist Sad to be missing you & @tobias_revell this weekend. Have fun with fellow contra-panglossians, @justinpickard @gsvoss & @nd_kane    
    
    
    Have made it to day 1 of @ICTArt. Artists & technologists are making a permanent online sunrise, mapping data onto cities & more #ICTArt2013    
    
    
    Just gave a talk at @ICTArt called, New Narratives, New Territories. My notes are here: http://is.gd/articttalk  #ICTArt2013    
    
    
    Tonight at #ICTArt2013, @seb_ly presents Lunar Trails. Watch the timelapse of him installing it at Bozar here: http://www.flickr.com/photos/sebleedelisle/10776778654/ …    
    
    
    @lukemunn Thanks Luke! I knew this reminded me of something, & I couldn't put my finger on it. Will pass that link to the group. cc @ICTArt    
    
    
    Met some amazing new open data allies & fellow journeymen at #ICTArt2013. And learned that @AnnaDumitriu's social judgement is *impeccable*.    
    
    
    Leaving the Data Ethics Working Group with @thickear & @josperello who'll present Terms & Conditions to the EU Parliament today #ICTArt2013    
    
    
    @jackaftersound @josperello @thickear Good luck. You'll be amazing. Send updates.    
    
    
    Thoughts with my Data Ethics Working Group comrades. MT @jackaftersound: Getting ready to address the European Parliament on Data & Ethics.    
    
    
    @jackaftersound Good to hear. @atautanaka is always good in that kind of context. You all set? cc @josperello @thickear    
    
    
    @jackaftersound Nervous?    
    
    
    @jackaftersound You'll be great. You know this material really well. And the bit about the potential energy is beautiful.    
    
    
    Astronomers observe a “ring rain” falling on Saturn: https://medium.com/the-physics-arxiv-blog/909f9767a518 … (via @arxivblog)    
    
    
    @jackaftersound That's great to hear!  Congratulations.  Now you can go and relax.    
    
    
    Our fellow shipping forecaster @changeist has arrived at @LighthouseArts for the afternoon, ahead of tomorrow's high-seas adventure.    
    
    
    One for @thickear @josperello & @jackaftersound. Thanks Dan. RT @danmcquillan: Methodolatry and the Art of Measure: http://places.designobserver.com/feature/methodolatry-in-urban-data-science/38174/ …    
    
    
    Today we're welcoming @willsh @changeist @justinpickard @tobias_revell & @gsvoss to @LighthouseArts for a workshop on critical forecasting.    
    
    
    Here's is a Lidar Elephant by @tobias_revell on one of @willsh's artifact cards. Cc @iamdanw @justinpickard pic.twitter.com/wB61kyUncX    
    
    
    Critical foresight bootcamp at @LighthouseArts with @changeist @justinpickard @gsvoss @nd_kane @tobias_revell et al. pic.twitter.com/YYBmudscGO    
    
    
    This is me and @tobias_revell defining Time and Space at @LighthouseArts. pic.twitter.com/DUjA3d84Iu    
    
    
    Shipping forecasters at @LighthouseArts @tobias_revell @justinpickard @gsvoss @nd_kane @willsh @changeist: ttp://t.co/YnR4Pp7hIa    
    
    
    Some very sharp synthesis goug on here by @justinpickard & @nd_kane at the Shipping Forecast workshop. pic.twitter.com/y0kTuzOU9v    
    
    
    Massive thanks to @willsh and @changeist for leading an inspiring Shipping Forecast workshop at @LighthouseArts today.    
    
    
    Mind full of nautical metaphors, territory vs geography, temporal horizons & weather patterns; plus the many faces of Lidar Elephant.    
    
    
    In case you missed it here's @tobias_revell's Lidar Elephant from the critical foresight workshop at @LighthouseArts pic.twitter.com/rPWzxyQJ94    
    
    
    Really sad to have missed the #smCollider exhibition opening at the @sciencemuseum yesterday. By all accounts it's amazing. Who can verify?    
    
    
    @sciencemuseum Great. Can't wait to see it. Been looking forward to it for ages. What did you think @jonmbutterworth, @benstill? #smcollider    
    
    
    @jonmbutterworth "Authentic and accurate" is high praise indeed form you. cc  @sciencemuseum @benstill    
    
    
    @benstill @sciencemuseum @jonmbutterworth Wow. That's some curating from @harryvcliff. I'll get up to see it ASAP.    
    
    
    @harryvcliff @ali_boyle @rupertpelham congrats to you all! I'll try & get up to see / review it this weekend. Really looking forward to it.    
    
    
    Congratulations to @adrianhon on the launch of "A History of the World in 100 Objects". Great to be there for the launch      .    
    
    
    En route to Laboral in Gijon. With a stopover in Barcelona.    
    
    
    Calling all Shipping Forecasters. This was found in @changeist's apparently randomly assigned apartment today: pic.twitter.com/hIVs4yLZmY    
    
    
    Here's a thing I helped (in a very minor way) make, last weekend with @thickear @jackaftersound @josperello & co: pic.twitter.com/kcCxPqKZUt    
    
    
    For @nd_kane MT @jamesbridle: I went to New Mexico in search of Render Ghosts, and wrote about it for @_EVP: http://www.electronicvoicephenomena.net/index.php/the-render-ghosts-james-bridle/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @julian0liver @k0a1a @transmediale Glad to hear this.    
    
    
    At LABoral today, where they have just announced this - NEXT THINGS 2014 – the global art & technology challenge: http://www.laboralcentrodearte.org/en/r/convocatorias/next-things-2014-2013-personal …    
    
    
    Amongst other things, the Art & Technology challenge is looking for IoT projects which address the post-PRISM moment: http://www.laboralcentrodearte.org/en/r/convocatorias/next-things-2014-2013-personal …    
    
    
    "broken & scattered, still, alone, more fragile, but with more vitality, more unsubstantial, more persistent, more faithful." marcel proust    
    
    
    DARPA's 'smart dust' heralds the era of the Internet of Molecules: http://is.gd/smartdust  (complete with Pynchonian introduction)    
    
    
    "Smart Dust is made of “motes” - tiny sensors that can perform a variety of functions": http://is.gd/smartdust  (for all you Revolution fans)    
    
    
    "The world may soon be quantified by sensors, floating on the winds to everywhere." http://is.gd/smartdust  #whatcouldpossiblygowrong?    
    
    
    Beautiful work by @jamesbridle on GPS, the "vast … celestial superstructure that we are all living inside.": http://www.where-you-are.com/james-bridle     
    
    
    "a grand asymmetric architecture composed of space-hardened signallers and radio waves, and us, no longer lost...": http://www.where-you-are.com/james-bridle     
    
    
    "defamiliarization encourages users to scrutinize their role in a given system. Seamless experiences are suspect.": http://slowerinternet.com/principles.html     
    
    
    Illegible Infrastructure (in Guangzhou, China): pic.twitter.com/jZ9OTwx3m7 (via @julian0liver)    
    
    
    @agentGav Looks a bit more permanent than warchalking, wouldn't you say?. Warbranding. Or warwelding, maybe?    
    
    
    For all you #CloudChamber fans, @esa's SWARM satellite is preparing for launch: http://is.gd/swarmlaunch  (via @Mario_Livio cc @cfonnes)    
    
    
    Extreme astronomy: an asteroid encounters a pulsar: (abstract: http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.3541v1  - full paper: http://arxiv.org/pdf/1311.3541v1.pdf …)    
    
    
    Interesting musings on the plausibility of 'warm dark matter' (WDM), derived from the Planck findings. Worth a read: http://arxiv.org/pdf/1311.3419v1.pdf …    
    
    
    @jastilley There's announcements about the plans here: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/news/lighthouse-announced-as-open-data-institute-node … & here: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/news/data-as-culture-a-partnership-with-the-open-data-institute … - drop us a line for more :-)    
    
    
    Machine synaesthesia - "a connection to pretty much everything with some kind of mechanically-powered moving part": http://is.gd/sensingmachines     
    
    
    I met the Girl with Machine Synaesthesia via @newaestheticbot & can't get her out of my head. Surely someone has written a novel about this?    
    
    
    "The best analogy I can use is a radio. My senses are my radio, picking up stimulus and playing it back in my brain": http://is.gd/sensingmachines     
    
    
    "It's as if the machine & I are connected & I can feel what it feels through that lens without actually becoming it." http://is.gd/sensingmachines     
    
    
    "My synesthesia […] also gives me a better understanding of physics and mechanical designs.": http://is.gd/sensingmachines     
    
    
    "From time to time the emotional lightning flashed & showed a landscape of private misery, & then -we went on dancing." R.I.P. Doris Lessing    
    
    
    "We're like meridians, all beginning and ending in the same place." - Neal Stephenson: http://is.gd/meridians     
    
    
    "There really are no words to describe the devastation of Typhoon Haiyan. It is total, it is complete.": http://www.stuff.co.nz/world/asia/9413142/Typhoon-survivors-will-you-tell-them-about-us … <- read this    
    
    
    @matlock Ummm, yes.  Come and talk to us.    
    
    
    . @gsvoss @justinpickard & @changeist need to know of the Centre for Innovation & Radical Fishmongery: http://scurtis.co.uk/fscirf.html  (via @centgg)    
    
    
    @willsh Send details. cc @changeist    
    
    
    @julian0liver There have been some updates to the laws of physics whilst you were away too.  I'll fill you in on Friday.    
    
    
    @julian0liver @changeist There's also been changes to voting regulations. You are now required to commit to a physics model, before voting.    
    
    
    "what do these bots tell us about ourselves, and our digital presences?":  https://medium.com/futures-exchange/e93c54c2cd00 … - great piece of writing by @nd_kane.    
    
    
    "this is where the ugly parts lie, a hastily written email, a frank conversation, a broken heart digitised" @nd_kane https://medium.com/futures-exchange/e93c54c2cd00 …    
    
    
    @GarethM @imperialcollege See also Immaterials Wifi by @timoarnall @snve & @jorngeorg which you saw in Brighton :) http://www.nearfield.org/2011/02/wifi-light-painting …    
    
    
    Five reasons why post-Higgs-boson physics is interesting. Reason 1. "We cannot explain why we are here at all." http://m.phys.org/news/2013-11-higgs-boson-physics.html …    
    
    
    Scientists starting to use the language of triage: who can we save? which parts of the world? http://elizabethmaymp.ca/news/blogs/2013/11/17/warsaw-cop19-daily-blog/ … (via @SMEasterbrook)    
    
    
    Devastated to hear of the passing of Peter Wintonick. The world has lost one of the great ones. Go well, dear Peter. http://realscreen.com/2013/11/18/ridm-13-industry-rallies-behind-peter-wintonick/ …    
    
    
    @nearnow @TheHospitalClub Thank you!    
    
    
    @katybeale Thanks Katy!    
    
    
    Thank you to @TheHospitalClub for the award last night (pic.twitter.com/OOgGTsEoOI) & for including me in #hClub100: http://is.gd/h_club     
    
    
    @justinpickard it's between Under the Shadow of the Drone and Data as Culture for the time being. pic.twitter.com/yIkQTCAi5J    
    
    
    @matlock @tobias_revell Thanks heaps. It's all a bit surreal, I tell you.    
    
    
    @tobias_revell @matlock I suspect our friend @justinpickard might question the use of the term, "deserved" in this context ;-)    
    
    
    @tobias_revell @matlock @justinpickard yes, 'appropriate' might be appropriate.    
    
    
    "In a world without hope, snake throwing is a reasonable way to resolve disputes." - more genius from James Mickens: https://research.microsoft.com/en-us/people/mickens/thenightwatch.pdf …    
    
    
    Adam isn't kidding. RT @AdamRutherford: There's really no point in doing anything else now. Ever. Well done everybody http://bit.ly/1bASnmd     
    
    
    @arielwaldman @AdamRutherford I know right?  What about the tennis channel? Diovesky vs Plotnivich. EPSN meets Dostoevsky.    
    
    
    "Reason and the rule of law are important things. And they're worth taking some trouble over." - Norman Kirk: http://www.nzonscreen.com/title/frost-over-new-zealand-the-leaders-1973 …    
    
    
    Awww, Gemma, thanks so much! MT @gemmagracewood: Hey look! Another NZ woman on top of the world. http://www.theguardian.com/culture-professionals-network/culture-professionals-blog/2013/nov/19/hospital-club-100-list-2013 …    
    
    
    @nraford & with you, Noah. Our mutual critical futures colleagues regularly sing your praises. Would be great to meet. cc @changeist    
    
    
    The @BFI with us today at @LighthouseArts today & tonight we are celebrating our Guiding Lights filmmakers at @BAFTA: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/guiding-lights-5 …    
    
    
    Our good friends at @FuturEverything have announced that the 2014 festival theme is "Tools for Unknown Futures": http://futureeverything.org/festival/tools-for-unknown-futures/ …    
    
    
    . @FuturEverything "will debate our fascination with tools as the most natural path towards social change" http://futureeverything.org/festival/tools-for-unknown-futures/ …    
    
    
    . @FuturEverything "will open up new ways to question, imagine & make the strange, troubled thing called the future" http://futureeverything.org/festival/tools-for-unknown-futures/ …    
    
    
    Um. Wow. MT @Macroscopist: First speakers: @anabjain @jamesbridle @Golan @tom_armitage @sebchan & Antony Dunne: http://futureeverything.org/festival/conference/ …    
    
    
    "We challenge YOU to detect the most elusive, mysterious and yet most abundant matter in all existence.": http://www.kaggle.com/c/DarkWorlds  #darkmatter    
    
    
    "Observing dark worlds" is a citizen science project engaging the public in the search for #darkmatter: http://www.kaggle.com/c/DarkWorlds     
    
    
    "Today, the tool as a conversation piece is one of the most relevant forms of production of discourse around futures" http://futureeverything.org/festival/tools-for-unknown-futures/ …    
    
    
    As predicted by @AnnaDumitriu, we're delighted to be presenting a talk by the artists, @thickear, at @LighthouseArts: http://is.gd/thickear     
    
    
    The artists in the @thickear collective explore the ethics of data collection & measurement via sound & performance: http://is.gd/thickear     
    
    
    En route to @BAFTA to toast the success of the filmmakers who have taken part in this year's Guiding Lights programme http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/guiding-lights-5 …    
    
    
    @CrAaronHawkins @RadioOne91FM you're going to be missed, Aaron.    
    
    
    @CrAaronHawkins I know. Dunedin is super lucky to have you. But the @RadioOne91FM faithful - home & away- will miss you.    
    
    
    @jonmbutterworth happy birthday Jon.    
    
    
    We're investigating the post-PRISM world at @LighthouseArts this month. Come along to our screening next Tuesday: http://is.gd/tandc     
    
    
    Cosmic neutrinos have been detected by Antarctic detector, IceCube, at the South Pole: http://is.gd/ice_cube     
    
    
    @PatrickRiot @LegacyRussell Slightly different method, but Cherenkov radiation is still in play. It's explained here: http://icecube.wisc.edu/about/explained     
    
    
    The data IceCube used to detect cosmic neutrinos contained 2 collisions, named Bert & Ernie: http://is.gd/ice_cube  pic.twitter.com/ZLlX5FwqXn    
    
    
    "The era of neutrino astronomy has begun" Gregory Sullivan of IceCube: http://is.gd/ice_cube  (for more on the field http://is.gd/skybelow )    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Neutrinos allow us to stare deeper into the cosmos, and this is the first step in a long journey of new discovery." @benstill #IceCube    
    
    
    Listen to Olga Botner, speaking about why those cosmic neutrinos IceCube has detected are so special: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1L3xEgPslEM …    
    
    
    The #SWARM mission has launched, promising to unveil some of the mysteries of magnetism: http://spaceflightnow.com/rockot/swarm/status.html … (#cloudchamber) cc @cfonnes    
    
    
    Cosmic Neutrinos: You've read the story, met Bert & Ernie, seen the movie, now read the #IceCube paper: http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.5238     
    
    
    Quantum computing, structural engineering-fiction, velocities, geofencing, real real prisms & the invention of the MyFive. Berlin, you'll do    
    
    
    TEMPEST aura by Bengt Sjölén - stunning work that "literally visualises the 'ghosts' of electronic machines": http://wiki.ljudmila.org/Artist-in-Residence:_Bengt_Sjolen_(en) …    
    
    
    Indeed. Adam won Saturday MT @julian0liver @datatheism made My-5 a thing. Reach out to classic High-5, no one's there? High-5 with yourself.    
    
    
    Things I'll be thinking hard about after a weekend at Weise7: Operation Igloo White, Beacon, Prism, Engineering-fiction, airlines, language.    
    
    
    Robot Listenable World - "how to detect & localize people that are both seen & heard by a robot": http://arxiv.org/abs/1311.2460  cc @julian0liver    
    
    
    The coming age of robots "performing the labours of love without ever loving.":  http://www.3quarksdaily.com/3quarksdaily/2013/11/love-in-the-time-of-robots.html …    
    
    
    Very interesting. Biology finally gets a pre-print service, http://biorxiv.org/  & http://www.nature.com/news/preprints-come-to-life-1.14140 … (Via @viXra)    
    
    
    Thank you to @julian0liver @k0a1a @bengtsjolen @datatheism (& all the non-connected) for the dizzying conceptual calisthenics. & now, home.    
    
    
    @k0a1a iI was so great to see you. And I'll email about The Proposition.    
    
    
    Aningaaq. Oh my. Thank you @julian0liver & @changeist.    
    
    
    "finding connections between things and other things [and] pointing out these parallels": http://www.theonion.com/articles/professor-sees-parallels-between-things-other-thin,5692/ … (via @matthewward)    
    
    
    @changeist @LIFTconference Excellent news. Nice programming @sylviereinhard & @nicolasnova.    
    
    
    Very sad to hear that our good friends @hidingseeking are closing: http://hideandseek.net/2013/11/26/hideseek-is-closing/ … - their inspiring work will be deeply missed.    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Somehow, the best and more singular bits of Silicon Roundabout are proving unsustainable. Something's being done wrong." @Macroscopist    
    
    
    The Terms & Conditions May Apply screening is kicking off at @LighthouseArts introduced by @andrewsleigh. pic.twitter.com/JB69Phawpl    
    
    
    "There's a value, in not knowing what the future will bring & a truth in not pretending to" @slavin http://vimeo.com/78829799  for @Macroscopist    
    
    
    A huge HAPPY BIRTHDAY to @Macroscopist (aka @jldevicente) who begins charting a new decade today.    
    
    
    @thejaymo Agreed. I'm sure you can work out what that is, @julian0liver. Basically Gravity on Rift. Without tethers. For political leaders.    
    
    
    @benvickers_ @thejaymo @julian0liver The potential of the Overview Effect Enforcement Agency? I think it's best explained in person.    
    
    
    @Macroscopist hear hear!    
    
    
    The new music video by Eminem uses the open source #RGBDToolkit developed by artist, James George (@obviousjim) & co: http://www.animalnewyork.com/2013/eminems-new-video-uses-free-open-source-rgbdtoolkit/ …    
    
    
    @DEBUTContemp Thank you so much!    
    
    
    This is excellent & informative. Pithy explanation of why the 23andMe / FDA furore matters: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VZXDtTNqDuQ#t=110 … (via @BoingBoing)    
    
    
    Four words you never expected to read: Wales Joins Space Race: http://www.wired.co.uk/magazine/archive/2013/11/play/liftoff … (via @changeist)    
    
    
    This is so brilliant. @hellohefin's "recontextualisation of Welsh culture and skills into a cosmic context.": http://www.hefinjones.co.uk/The-Welsh-Space-Campaign …    
    
    
    So happy to see our BFI Shorts continuing to pick up awards: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/news/bfi-shorts-festival-awards-and-nominations … - Congrats to the SeaView, SLR & @OrbitEverAfter teams!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Macroscopist @juliaxgulia can we make this happen? I think it's important.    
    
    
    @hellohefin thank you for this. And for the work. I've dropped you a line.    
    
    
    @Dymaxion Really? That's fantastic news! When are you getting in? We're having a privacy show&tell over lunch at Lighthouse. Want to come?    
    
    
    London finally gets the drone it deserves. MT @jamesbridle: Today we are drawing a drone in Windrush Square, Brixton: pic.twitter.com/ggUgkLJhqB    
    
    
    Today at @LighthouseArts at 1pm, @@cataspanglish is giving a Show&Tell on privacy for the team & a few invited guests. Ahoy there @Dymaxion.    
    
    
    Here's @cataspanglish talking about his CCTV map of Brighton at the Privacy Show&Tell at @LighthouseArts pic.twitter.com/L0f8zWbNTP    
    
    
    We are very happy to have @sfingali, director of SLR, one of our BFI Shorts (http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/bfi-shorts-2012/slr …), with us for the Privacy Show&Tell.    
    
    
    Chris (@cataspanglish) just made us feel deeply uncomfortable by asking everyone to give their phone & wallet to the person next to them.    
    
    
    "The word idiot stems from the Ancient Greek term for privacy. An idiot was a private person." - the Privacy Show&Tell at @LighthouseArts    
    
    
    "One of the reasons we continue to give our data to large tech corporations is because we lack good alternatives" @seb_ly, Privacy Show&Tell    
    
    
    The Privacy Show&Tell at @LighthouseArts by @cataspanglish is perfect preparation for the #cryptofestival in London & Brighton this weekend.    
    
    
    Pioneering journalist, Duncan Campbell, the man who exposed #Echelon is speaking at the Brighton #cryptofestival: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/brighton-cryptofestival …    
    
    
    If you missed #Echelon first time round, it was the hardware layer to PRISM's software layer: http://www.duncancampbell.org/content/echelon  #cryptofestival    
    
    
    @Macroscopist More of a metaphor. But a not-terrible one, I think.    
    
    
    Getting deja vu with @LighthouseArts' #crypto events. Here's the last time I curated Duncan Campbell into an event: http://www.tate.org.uk/context-comment/video/surveillane-control-symposium-video-coverage#open239887 …    
    
    
    Seriously weighty & deep discussions about world-building, ethics, realism & responsibility with @Dymaxion & @sfingali. Thank you both.    
    
    
    @stevecrossan Steve, it's a long conversation. And one best done in person.  How are you? cc @Dymaxion @sfingali    
    
    
    One of those days where the effects of the @LighthouseArts studio, & its open & interdisciplinary effect, starts becoming starkly apparent.    
    
    
    Tonight: force multiplication factors, networks, unthinkable modelling, variables vs individuals, designing ethical systems. Atrocities.    
    
    
    "nothing locally exceeds the speed of light, but space can expand & contract at any speed": http://io9.com/5963263/how-nasa-will-build-its-very-first-warp-drive … (via @deepspeedmedia)    
    
    
    "Existence proof is important." - the amazing Harold White explains how he's testing the Alcubierre Drive: http://io9.com/5963263/how-nasa-will-build-its-very-first-warp-drive …    
    
    
    "This loophole in general relativity would allow us to go places really fast as measured by both Earth observers & observers on the ship."    
    
    
    Long long way back for the #Kiwis now.    
    
    
    Hard to remember a more clinical & efficient performance than this by any team in either code. Not spectacular, but astonishingly effective.    
    
    
    The Brighton #Cryptofestival is kicking off at @LighthouseArts. Drop by to learn how to be more secure online: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/brighton-cryptofestival …    
    
    
    Dialogue needed between underwater archaeologists & particle physicists over use of  artefacts: http://www.agenciasinc.es/en/News/Controversy-over-the-use-of-Roman-ingots-to-investigate-dark-matter-and-neutrinos … (via @rwchambliss)    
    
    
    For two decades the launch code at every nuclear silo in the US was 00000000: http://gizmodo.com/for-20-years-the-nuclear-launch-code-at-us-minuteman-si-1473483587 … (via @benadida) #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    Great historical primer on the development of NSA surveillance at  #cryptofestbtn. pic.twitter.com/6fMvdjBWE3    
    
    
    Obligatory jokes about the hideousness of the PRISM PowerPoint slides at #cryptofestbtn pic.twitter.com/kCsVACSsQM    
    
    
    @marksimpkins plus a comparative analysis with particle physicists' font use.    
    
    
        
    
    
    The realities of breaking encryption: http://xkcd.com/538/  - as seen at #cryptofestbtn #cryptofestival    
    
    
    Here's @cataspanglish introducing "professional troublemaker",
@smarimc at #cryptofestbtn at @LighthouseArts pic.twitter.com/BP8Ja2JbIO    
    
    
    "When the State has the ability to see all of the cards all of the time, it becomes difficult to defend yourself." @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "The Director of National Intelligence in the US has a budget of US$56 billion." - @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "The Internet currently has 2.5 billion users. The total surveillance budget available equates to 13c per user" @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "Let's decentralize. Lets take data away from the big silos - Google, Outlook etc. Distribute the targets." @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "Let's raise the cost of surevillance from 13c per user per day to much, much more." @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "If we make the cost of surveillance prohibitive, we starting solving the problem." @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    "The problem with clouds is that they rain. A Cloud on the Internet is going to rain data. Your data." @smarimc #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    Hugely privileged to have Duncan Campbell at @LighthouseArts speaking about surveillance at #cryptofestbtn pic.twitter.com/qZfb1pixpK    
    
    
    Devastating presentation from Duncan Campbell, now unpacking some of the latest Snowden revelations. #cryptofestbtn pic.twitter.com/n9E6gqOE0m    
    
    
    Mind-blowing talk by Duncan Campbell exposing the true scope of surveillance infrastructure. Hugely upsetting & important. #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    Duncan Campbell warns of forthcoming  highly troubling revelations about the compromise of core Internet hardware. #cryptofestbtn    
    
    
    @cataspanglish Doing very well!  Thank you so much for #cryptofestBTN. It was a triumph. And so good to have you with us, @smarimc.    
    
    
    Still reeling from a chilling talk by @dcampbell_iptv at #cryptofestBTN yesterday. Expect some terrifying revelations in the coming weeks.    
    
    
    Unconventional computing items in the bagging area: http://charlesmartinreid.com/wordpress/2012/07/solarpunk-no-powerlow-power-lono-computing-organic-computing/ … http://uncomp.uwe.ac.uk/  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2Ckytxq0OWc … via @justinpickard    
    
    
    Strong work here by @jamesbridle, "using the tools of the network against its darkest masters": http://booktwo.org/notebook/anatomy-failed-rendition-ifa-muaza/ …    
    
    
    Another excellent example, along with the work of @trevorpaglen, of the artist as investigative journalist: http://booktwo.org/notebook/anatomy-failed-rendition-ifa-muaza/ …    
    
    
    "the shadowy technological aspects of these abominations [reveal]the underlying moral bankruptcy of the perpetrators" http://booktwo.org/notebook/anatomy-failed-rendition-ifa-muaza …    
    
    
    Nestled within that piece by @jamesbridle is an incisive take on what it means "to render" in our technological times http://is.gd/torender     
    
    
    "There is no 'the' future. There's just a bubbling & propagating mess of technologies & hopes & fears" @tobias_revell http://blog.tobiasrevell.com/2013/12/critical-design-design-fiction-lecture.html …    
    
    
    "Children of Men is one of the greatest diegetic design fictions of all time." @tobias_revell: http://blog.tobiasrevell.com/2013/12/critical-design-design-fiction-lecture.html …    
    
    
    Congratulations, @golan. Great news. They are lucky to have you. The Emerging Media programme (http://code.arc.cmu.edu/about/ ) looks amazing.    
    
    
    Take a look at the amazing work that @obviousjim did whilst being Microsoft Research's first artist in residence: http://is.gd/jamesatmicrosoft …    
    
    
    "He’s revealed a way for them to look at their work through a new lens” - Asta Roseway on what @obviousjim did for Microsoft researchers.    
    
    
    @mimrandall Thanks for this Miriam. My favourite song off that album (for obvious & non-obvious reasons). & @iainandjane, stunning work.    
    
    
    "Rather like James Watt complaining that he can't find any takers for his new steam engine": http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/dec/03/graphene-wonder-substance-uk-economy …    
    
    
    Andre Geim "1 of the world's great scientists, pointing out that British businesses are either incapable or unwilling to use his inventions"    
    
    
    "It breaks my heart to say this, but the nearest company that would take what we could offer was in the Far East." http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/dec/03/graphene-wonder-substance-uk-economy …    
    
    
    The post graphene blues, as sung by its discoverers, Kostya Novoselov and Andre Geim: http://www.theguardian.com/science/2013/dec/03/graphene-wonder-substance-uk-economy … (via @jonmbutterworth)    
    
    
    @ProfBrianCox @bisgovuk Pretty depressing reading, especially right after Alexander announcing cuts to funding for solar & wind energy.    
    
    
    You have to love physicists' acronyms. Here's a beauty: "ARRAKIS" (Atlas of Resonance Rings As Known In the S4G): http://arxiv.org/abs/1312.0866     
    
    
    New writing by Paul Steinhardt & Neil Turok on their explanation of the big crunch - big bang transition: http://arxiv.org/pdf/1312.0739v1.pdf …    
    
    
    @Stephen_Curry Thanks for the link Stephen. I'll sign & circulate. I presume, @profbriancox already has?    
    
    
    If you found that piece on graphene as depressing as I did, then you might want to sign this: http://scienceisvital.org.uk/2013/11/29/open-letter-to-vincent-cable-secretary-of-state/ … (via @Stephen_Curry)    
    
    
    "These are generic geodesically complete solutions that can naturally incorporate the cyclic theory of the universe." http://metanautics.tumblr.com/post/68966935520/sailing-through-the-big-crunch-big-bang-transition …    
    
    
    @astrolitterbox Thank you very much.  I'll read with interest.    
    
    
    @julian0liver Excellent.  Glad you liked it.    
    
    
    Big Bang Data - a new exhibition curated by @jldevicente - will open in Barcelona next year. & it will be *amazing*: http://blogs.cccb.org/lab/en/article_big-bang-data/ …    
    
    
    @AquilaRift Cosmologists everywhere are looking to one another and saying, "I told you so."    
    
    
    Massive congratulations to @juliaxgulia, who will be leading the @newmuseum's new incubator for art & technology: http://on.wsj.com/1kaEIHe     
    
    
    Happy to see that The New Statesman has republished @jamesbridle's important piece on rendition: http://www.newstatesman.com/politics/2013/12/ifa-muaza-anatomy-failed-rendition …    
    
    
    Happy to have @thickear with us at @lighthouseArts today, ahead of their talk. Doors at 6.30pm if you want to come. http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/programme/monthly-talk-thickear …    
    
    
    Thickear begin their talk at @LighthouseArts by lovingly discombobulating everyone. pic.twitter.com/fY4ODjngtS    
    
    
    Here's @jackaftersound presenting the work of the artists, @thickear at @LighthouseArts. pic.twitter.com/7syWMgGMxz    
    
    
    Extremely interesting points from @jackaftersound about sonification, rules, representation & authenticity. pic.twitter.com/fNKZYzEFBY    
    
    
    "What we have created here is a sonification of the idea of sonification" - @jackaftersound at @LighthouseArts.    
    
    
    Here's Geoff Howse from @thickear speaking about the subjectivity of measurement and the Dichotomy Paradox. pic.twitter.com/o4QBklHLBl    
    
    
    Geoff Howse discussing the @ICTArt programme, which @thickear's Ministry of Measurement was part of Cc @AnnaDumitriu pic.twitter.com/cfKPCehwFz    
    
    
    Performative form-filing as a cathartic act. As described by @jackaftersound at @LighthouseArts. pic.twitter.com/HnaX0qGmDo    
    
    
    Here's a copy of the "unique pieces of data" that @thickear are now issuing to the audience at @LighthouseArts. pic.twitter.com/DFFsFGjIAd    
    
    
    Home after a beautiful evening. But the news is still real. And the world is a poorer place.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @paulsq Kind of. That's how I met @jackaftersound & @thickear.    
    
    
    @jackaftersound That's good to hear. We were too. Come back soon. cc @nd_kane @LighthouseArts @thickear    
    
    
    London-in-the-dark.    
    
    
    @Erica_Scourti *waves from down the road*    
    
    
    Strong evidence for the Peak Strangeness of Reality (vs fiction): http://qz.com/155130/americas-outer-space-spy-program-has-a-new-mascot-a-world-eating-octopus/ … (via @changeist)    
    
    
    So, who is in London today and tomorrow?  Consider this an impromptu census.    
    
    
    @LydNicholas Damn. You've rumbled me!    
    
    
    Well well well MT @OxfordQuantum: Chancellor confirms £270 million investment in Quantum technology http://royalsociety.org/news/2013/chancellor-investment-quantum-technology/ …    
    
    
    Who's coming to hear Evgeny Morozov speak in London this evening? http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/cybersalon-digital-futures-evgeny-morozov-9-dec-tickets-9438397501 …    
    
    
    @thejaymo I know @tobias_revell is, but didn't know @benvickers_ was too. Excellent. See you all there.    
    
    
    Bit of an emotional day. Some news. I'm going to be leaving @LighthouseArts in the new year: http://lighthouse.org.uk/news/honor-harger-to-take-new-international-position …    
    
    
    Thanks so much, @dougiegyro @Macroscopist @nicolasnova @willsh @jon_pratty @polinski @mattsheret @antimega @SciencePunk for the kind words.    
    
    
    So that means one of the most interesting organisations in the country needs a visionary Artistic Director: http://is.gd/hhlighthouse     
    
    
    @leebryant Great to see you too.  What did you think of the film?    
    
    
    @leebryant Yep, agreed. I felt a bit emotionally devastated. But it's an amazing piece of work. And I agree, the Q&A was excellent.    
    
    
    Thank you very much to @MarkTreagus @VIVID_ @badgermind @gerwitz @Cekent @sophystar for the good wishes.    
    
    
    @VIVID_ Thank you so much for this.  Those are very kind words indeed.    
    
    
    @matlock thank you so much Matt. I'm going to miss you & everyone in Brighton, hugely.    
    
    
    "The project seeks to remake the roots of Ecuador’s economy [based on] free and open knowledge.”: http://bollier.org/blog/bauwens-joins-ecuador-planning-commons-based-peer-production-economy … (via @cityofsound)    
    
    
    Thank you so much to @nialljthompson @mattcaines @alisoncj @AndrewChetty @honeyinmyveins and everyone else who has sent kind words my way.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Evgeny Morozov kicking off his talk at the Cybersalon. The Internet is here. pic.twitter.com/9ovMbtE4dU    
    
    
    Lots of discussion about climate change, health & quantified self by @evgenymorozov at #Cybersalon. {waves at @justinpickard}.    
    
    
    @justinpickard it's more behavioral economics, drones & big data so far. No solutionism klaxon yet. We will let you know. #Cybersalon    
    
    
    @PatrickRiot {waves!}    
    
    
    "I don't know what technology is." Evgeny Morozov drops a bit of a bombshell. Don't tell his publisher. #Cybersalon    
    
    
    "The financial institutions are a packet switching network" - Richard Barbrook. #cybersalon    
    
    
    @benvickers_ @Dymaxion We are partying like its 1999.    
    
    
    @Dymaxion @benvickers_Hang on we're back to the loom now. So correction: 1993.    
    
    
    "I care if democracy survives. I don't care if the Internet survives." - Evgeny Morozov #Cybersalon    
    
    
    "People think that they are doing politics by building tools, without building the institutions & infrastructures too." Morozov #Cybersalon    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Everything revolves around infrastructure and identity these days" - Evgeny Morozov #Cybersalon    
    
    
    I think Evgeny's basic point is: "don't mistake the tools for the purpose" (P. Kirk). Hard to disagree. But .... #Cybersalon    
    
    
    "I don't believe in agents." Evgeny Morozov. #Cybersalon    
    
    
    Grand indeed to spend some time with the People of the Internet, @thejaymo @benvickers_ @Dymaxion @uah @tobias_revell @iamdanw @aral & co.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @cerigorton That's incredibly kind of you to say. Thank you so much.    
    
    
    Last month I gave a talk at @MeaningConf, on art in the post-PRISM age, called Seeing in the Dark: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PK2hy-e2zfk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    I'm indebted to @julian0liver @k0a1a @jamesbridle @trevorpaglen @timoarnall & others for making the brilliant work that inspired the talk.    
    
    
    On days like this @LighthouseArts officially misses @ntlk.    
    
    
    Official visit to @clearleft towers.    
    
    
        
    
    
    . @juliaxgulia is saying nice things to New Zealanders. The entire country is looking awkwardly at our shoes whilst smiling inwardly.    
    
    
    @Emma_J_Davis Thank you! Don't mean to be cryptic. It's just not public yet, but we had to begin recruiting at Lighthouse immediately.    
    
    
    Routing gas using the same decentralised control techniques developed for the internet could improve energy security: http://www.technologyreview.com/view/522471/how-internet-style-routing-for-gas-could-dramatically-improve-europes-energy-security/ …    
    
    
    New work responding to the post-PRISM hyper-surveillance moment by @superflux: http://superflux.in/work/openinformant … & @jamesbridle: http://booktwo.org/notebook/surveillance-spaulder/ …    
    
    
    Essentially (as someone has already said) @stml made himself a spidey-sense: http://booktwo.org/notebook/surveillance-spaulder/ …    
    
    
    Having being press-ganged by just about everyone, am finally plotting a recon to the Drowned Man: http://punchdrunk.com/current-shows  - show of hands?    
    
    
    Robots convincing people they are not robots: http://io9.com/freakishly-realistic-telemarketing-robots-are-denying-t-1481050295 … - not recommended reading for those with a fragile sense of reality.    
    
    
    So @ScienceGallery in Dublin actually have a talk by @cmdr_Hadfield. I didn't think their programme could get any better. cc @michaeljohng    
    
    
    Looking forward to @marksimpkins' Show&Tell at @LighthouseArts today & welcoming vistors, including @tobias_revell & @seb_ly. & Flags.    
    
    
    There's a drone droning quietly in the background at our Show&Tell. It's made by Cathal Coughlan & @marksimpkins. This makes me so happy.    
    
    
    "Do you feel watched?" @marksimpkins at his Show&Tell at @lighthousearts. pic.twitter.com/RVnKr3Kuae    
    
    
        
    
    
    "CCTV - the fifth public utility". - Stephen Graham quoted by @marksimpkins at @LighthouseArts. pic.twitter.com/iwAgEY4hVT    
    
    
    The Surveillance Diaries by @marksimpkins are an extension of 'the cultural probe' developed by Anthony Dunne & co. pic.twitter.com/u3Im7eCSpm    
    
    
        
    
    
    . @marksimpkins is repatrioting the term "drone" back into the context of sound & music whilst making a statement about drones.    
    
    
    Really happy that @marksimpkins created this work. We first brainstormed this at the last @LighthouseArts Show&Tell with @cataspanglish.    
    
    
    Very sad to hear of the passing of the great Zbigniew Karkowski. An amazing artist & a wonderful person. R.I.P. http://pitchfork.com/news/53342-rip-electronic-composer-zbigniew-karkowski/ …    
    
    
    "we are composed of sound and all manifestations of forms in the universe are nothing else but sounds" - Zbigniew Karkowski. (R.I.P.)    
    
    
    For @julian0liver @nat @gemmagracewood @CrAaronHawkins @vickytnz @thesjef @Benjam8n & fellow Kiwis: pic.twitter.com/pNjTp8QFMc (@CitizenBomber)    
    
    
    A lament for a declining empire: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nyc6RJEEe0U&feature=youtu.be … - first glimpse of Christopher Nolan's 'Interstellar'. (via @Cekent)    
    
    
    “Anti-resolution” beam bathes objects in darkness: https://medium.com/p/fd5386e20aee  - the era of the darkness ray begins in Singapore.    
    
    
    The suggested applications for the Darkness Beam are somewhat … illuminating: http://is.gd/darknessbeam  ("superb surveillance", "military use")    
    
    
    @changeist There's links to a few here: http://is.gd/darknessbeam  - prototypes come out a dime a dozen these days. Mostly using metamaterials.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Posting the darkness beam again for those who missed it yesterday ...    
    
    
    “Anti-resolution” beam bathes objects in darkness: http://is.gd/darknessbeam  - the era of invisibility through darkness begins in Singapore.    
    
    
    Disturbing. "Cameron admitting ISPs will be required to block whatever the government deems necessary" @SciencePunk: http://twitter.com/SciencePunk/status/412514346598531072/photo/1pic.twitter.com/eRKGPBXrHy     
    
    
    "We're at a tipping point where human behaviour can be inferred from data" Josie Rourke on the Donmar's privacy play: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03lnvx1 …    
    
    
    Great work Katy Hickman. That Start the Week on Strategy was one of the best of the year. & it's been a good year: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03lnvx1 …    
    
    
    Official definition of "extremism" & what measures - including online censorship - will stop it: https://www.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/263181/ETF_FINAL.pdf … (via @jamesbridle)    
    
    
    Post Western Cultures: http://www.idpure.ch/flip/postwestern/index.html?reload … - a new publication by Joel Vacheron & ID Pure (via @nicolasnova: http://nearfuturelaboratory.com/pasta-and-vinegar/2013/12/15/post-western-cultures/ …)    
    
    
    @toodlepip @meaningconf That was the Men In Grey. Website and details here:  http://meningrey.net/video/     
    
    
    Great to see @adamhrv in the New York Times with his fantastic CV Dazzle project: http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2013/12/14/opinion/sunday/20121215_ANTIFACE_OPART.html?_r=2& …    
    
    
    That last link is how to make a literal compilation from compilation. @julian0liver may wish to elaborate.    
    
    
    If you're at home, I highly recommend tuning into @BBCRadio4. The Start the Week on strategic thinking is a classic: http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/b03lnvx1 …    
    
    
    On the historical Polynesian use of binary notation: http://motherboard.vice.com/blog/polynesian-tribes-used-binary-long-before-europeans … (via @JenLucPiquant. Cc @julian0liver)    
    
    
    The already stellar @FuturEverything line-up just got starrier: @Dymaxion @iamdanw @adamhrv @PaulGrahamRaven @alexandradaisy all speaking.    
    
    
    The full @FuturEverything line-up, which also includes @anabjain @iotwatch @jamesbridle @liam_young & @golan is here: http://futureeverything.org/festival/conference/ …    
    
    
    @PhilDyson @PaulGrahamRaven The Next talk has to be the talk of the year.    
    
    
    @PhilDyson @PaulGrahamRaven I think it was the context in which he articulated it, and the alarmed expressions of the attendees that did it.    
    
    
    Plotting exciting things for the New Year at @LighthouseArts, with @julian0liver @k0a1a @cataspanglish @tobias_revell @marksimpkins & co.    
    
    
        
    
    
    We are seeking a new Artistic Director to bring visionary creative leadership to @LighthouseArts: http://www.lighthouse.org.uk/about/opportunities … - deadline 20.1.14    
    
    
        
    
    
    Very very lovely evening with @jackaftersound & then @simonings & @LydNicholas. Reality matrix reinstalled and solid.    
    
    
    This is upsetting -but essential- reading. @jamesbridle's first hand account of a deportation flight leaving the UK: http://booktwo.org/notebook/planespotting/ …    
    
    
    'The ongoing deportation of Nigerians on charter flights is called “Operation Majestic”' - @jamesbridle: http://booktwo.org/notebook/planespotting/ …    
    
    
    Extreme acoustic cryptanalysis. Security researchers have broken a highly secure encryption algorithm by *listening*: http://is.gd/acousticcryptanalysis …    
    
    
    Today, in which I join The Cult of The Drowned Man.    
    
    
    Call for proposals for a new artist commission for @LighthouseArts at  @HOUSE_festival & @brightfest 2014: http://is.gd/house2014     
    
    
        
    
    
    @hellohefin Lovely to meet you! Conversations about space, rugby & future speculations are the best conversations.    
    
    
    And now. For The Drowned Man.    
    
    
    Dreamt of the Dust Witch, Miguel and a world of sand.  cc @alderfield @antimedia @gsvoss @iFlicks    
    
    
    Today is a good day because there's a new James Mickens piece. This time he aims his scythe at art http://research.microsoft.com/en-us/groups/studio99/preparetobedevastated.aspx … (via @obviousjim)    
    
    
    "I had also inadvertently invented an algorithmic story-generator." - great piece by @REasther on N-body dynamics: http://excursionset.com/blog/2013/11/26/a-romantic-comedy-as-told-by-newton …    
    
    
    Archetypal film stories translated into an N-body physics model by cosmologist, @REasther - your link of the day: http://excursionset.com/blog/2013/11/26/a-romantic-comedy-as-told-by-newton …    
    
    
    Wonder if the online launch of SLR, the film @LighthouseArts has exec produced (http://is.gd/slrselfie ) will make it past the pr0n filter?    
    
    
    Since you know, *Mailpile* is blocked. MT @MailpileTeam Following Mailpile's progress just became more difficult. Our website blocked by @O2    
    
    
    “Everything that isn't explicitly allowed is banned, it seems. Because that's how censorship works. Thanks, UK" @smarimc #ukcensorship    
    
    
    “Now that generalized censorship exists in the UK, perhaps people will want the proposers of the censorship to resign?" @smarimc    
    
    
    “All websites of Dutch politcal parties are blocked by @O2 as well. So is my blog but that's besides the point.” @petrakramer    
    
    
        
    
    
    Three of the best days of the year.    
    
    
    In London this weekend, a-Drowning. Who's about?    
    
    
    Without a doubt, the 2013 Image of the Year: http://is.gd/2013planck  - the Cosmic Background Microwave Radiation, as observed by Planck.    
    
    
    Hello London.    
    
    
        
    
    
    It's a rare skill being able to cultivate a parallel universe. And yet there is one, existing in the heart of London. Resplendent.    
    
    
    A day of serendipity, conversational remakings of the universe, fine company & conviviality. With @agentGav @josefoconnor @LaDeDara et al.    
    
    
    Cosmology paper of the day:  "Cosmology in ghost-free bigravity theory ... The origin of dark matter": http://wp.me/p3ZmZy-42M  (via @arXiver)    
    
    
    @matlock Excellent. See you there! Come down, @wonderlandblog!    
    
    
    Another round of applause please for @gemmagracewood for taking the candid photo of 2013: http://static2.stuff.co.nz/1388106490/526/9557526.jpg … - thanks mate. #NZNYOnyas    
    
    
    @gemmagracewood Art direction is vital! The whole set of photos are priceless. Thanks for making it happen.    
    
    
    One of 2013's sobering offhand remarks, uttered by the remarkable @dcampbell_iptv: "2.5 million people have access to XKeyscore" #postPRISM    
    
    
    Nearly 96% of the Universe is dark. There, but invisible: http://is.gd/butinvisible  So, what an extraordinary time to be alive. Happy New Year!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Acoustic levitation: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=odJxJRAxdFU … - Japanese scientists levitate particles using an ultrasound standing wave (ignore the music.)    
    
    
    Thanks to @stml for the New Year's Day hospitality. & to @anneholiday @antimega @prehensile @cohenvanbalen @gsvoss & co for the discussions.    
    
    
    @anneholiday It was lovely to talk to you too! Check out @deepspeedmedia's beautiful film, Someday Somewhere Beyond: http://vimeo.com/m/75096784     
    
    
    @M_PF We would love to have you visit us at @LighthouseArts on the 18th. Details about the event will be online soon. We'll be in touch.    
    
    
    Out of Office: due to illness.    
    
    
    "Searching the Internet for evidence of time travellers" - an actual study by actual physicists: http://arxiv.org/abs/1312.7128  (via @doingitwrong)    
    
    
    "three implementations of Internet searches for time travellers are described, all seeking [prescient information]" http://arxiv.org/abs/1312.7128     
    
    
    “Maybe social media doesn’t persist in the far future, so time travellers don’t know how to tweet.”: @bgreene on http://is.gd/timetravellers     
    
    
    "Stephen Hawking held a party for time travellers from the future, announcing the party only after its completion." http://is.gd/timetravellers     
    
    
    "No one showed up.": http://is.gd/timetravellers     
    
    
    "this search might be considered the most sensitive and comprehensive search yet for time travel from the future." http://arxiv.org/pdf/1312.7128v1.pdf …    
    
    
    #HawkingParty: a gathering to which no one comes, which is later described as a "time travellers'" party. Attribution: S.Hawking & @Cekent.    
    
    
    The olden days were indeed simpler. This was how you wrote a research grant application in 1921: http://drtomcrick.com/2013/12/15/grant-applications-early-20th-century-style … (via @mikraemer)    
    
    
    