Looking forward to the #blogchatie this evening. Here's what it's about http://www.writeontrack.ie/blogging-for-success/blogchatie/# …    
    
    
    @Blogshane Thanks for the RT    
    
    
    .@JBBC Hi Marie and everyone on #blogchatie    
    
    
    Re introductions: I'm Beatrice and I am editor of the Sage.ie blog and I also guest blog for a number of sites  #blogchatie    
    
    
    My goal would be to find the time to blog more often and to comment on more blogs #Blogchatie    
    
    
    Making blogging resolutions is one thing but keeping them is another, a blogging calendar is helpful for this #blogchaite    
    
    
    @ConallOM @mediahqnews or bloggers anonymous! #blogchattie    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L @thereluctantsc also depends on how much discussion you're getting on other ones you've posted #blogchatie    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L @thereluctantsc some LinkedIn groups are just saturated with spammy links to blog posts, don't you think? #blogchatIE    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC I've been guilty of it myself, it's easy to get carried away when trying to increase an audience #blogchatie    
    
    
    @paulinesargent yeah #blogchatIE is a great idea of @WriteOnTrack_L  and @JBBC    
    
    
    @mindfulproduct yeah long posts can be broken into two parts, better way of using the content I think #blogchatIE    
    
    
    @gettapsandsinks you can unsubscribe to the email updates, otherwise it is too much I agree    
    
    
    @kevinmarkham you'll have to take a photo of me as I dodge golf balls, power walking the track around the golf course in Heritage, Killenard    
    
    
    @DrivingForWork @gettapsandsinks @kevinmarkham @mindfulproduct I tried putting quotes from each section post in as an image #blogchaite    
    
    
    @DrivingForWork @gettapsandsinks @kevinmarkham @mindfulproduct got that idea from @Hamperlady, then posted one of the images to our FB page    
    
    
    @3keyscoach @jbbc @writeontrack_l agree #blogchaite was great and for some reason I couldn't even see the spammers, feel like I missed out!    
    
    
    I'm at #KLCK bloggers network, discussing bloggers block and other topics    
    
    
    Americans comment on blogs more than we do in Ireland, why is that? #KLCK    
    
    
    Increase readership by including your blog posts in your email newsletter #klck    
    
    
    Anyone use Weebly as their blogging platform? We're discussing it at #KLCK    
    
    
    FREE Ebook: How To Manage The Cash Flow In Your Business #smecommunity #irishbiz http://ow.ly/gNMIJ     
    
    
    @Spiderworking thanks Amanda    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L I just manually take a sentence from the post and make it look nice in photoshop, then embed the image in the post    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L yeah but I'm sure you could do the same in gimp    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L thanks yeah some great tips in there by @avrilmcardle    
    
    
    @auntyamo @writeontrack_l nah I like to keep things nice and easy :)    
    
    
    Feeling a bit jealous of the Kevin Abosch portraits in my twitter stream, remember them from the websummit. He makes geeks look good.    
    
    
    @susan_whyte yes I can help, used it before. Here is my @prezi on Blogging For SEO http://prezi.com/msd4wrcm7_rv/blogging-for-seo-success/ …    
    
    
    FREE Ebook: How To Start A Business via @sageireland http://ow.ly/gNO1R  #startups    
    
    
    Seven Marketing Tips For Small Businesses by @avrilmcardle http://ow.ly/gG9nM     
    
    
    @RitaTobin thanks a mill for the share, more free ebooks coming today    
    
    
    @elainerogers thanks for the RT, how are you keeping?    
    
    
    @shane_burroughs about 40 members I'd say, we're in Laois next month if you want to come along #KLCK    
    
    
    What Type Of Business Owner Are You?  http://ow.ly/gHcNM     
    
    
    @armelleskitchen Just found your site via a tweet from your hubby to @sageireland - in heaven looking at Macarons  & you're in Kildare too!!    
    
    
    @elainerogers thanks already planning next years    
    
    
    FREE Ebook: How To Start A Business http://ow.ly/gNOUl  #startups #startupinspiration    
    
    
    @SunzuSam congrats on your new job, here's to a great 2013    
    
    
    @SunzuSam great thanks, busy with the usual stuff but all good    
    
    
    @SunzuSam thanks for the invite, will def check that out on Monday, in movie and wine mode now :)    
    
    
    Connecting With Your Customers, A Free Guide To Social Media http://ow.ly/h3qku     
    
    
    Five Simple Steps To Run Successful Competitions On Facebook http://bit.ly/VXkR6n  by @aoiferigney on @TweakYourBiz    
    
    
    @JeniPim I like the desk calendar so much I robbed it from Rob pic.twitter.com/IIF66SCo    
    
    
    @JeniPim yes love it, have you seen our little eggs? Let's swap eggs! pic.twitter.com/nV54YFSj    
    
    
    Connecting With Your Customers, A Free Guide To Social Media http://ow.ly/h3qku     
    
    
    Off to Ardnacrusha for a tour of the power station with the other ecar ambassadors    
    
    
    Ardnacrusha http://vine.co/v/b5LM1Y79VEt     
    
    
    @pauldonno surely one Guinness wouldn't do any harm ;)    
    
    
    @pauldonno won't get to hear your talk in person but I'll be watching on Twitter #FutureOfAccounting    
    
    
    Speaking at day 2 of the @FingalCEB Bootcamp @CartonHouse tmrw. Will be discussing how online can change your business model. #fceb2013    
    
    
    @pauldonno great example of a scheduled tweet and I'm even more sorry I'm missing your talk now    
    
    
    How time flies around again, preparations for the 2013 Blog Awards Ireland now underway.    
    
    
    @avonfromfiona sorry thought I was :)    
    
    
    @avonfromfiona following there now    
    
    
    Sounds like @BookMarkLee is giving a really good talk on social media for accountants at #FutureOfAccounting. Cutting through the hype.    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen could we be more unlucky?    
    
    
    Okay twitter give me a number between 2 and 6    
    
    
    @Ross_McConnell has to be a full number, at the dogs!    
    
    
    @DMcAPhotography okay going for 4    
    
    
    @Paullyie 3 it is you've just decided my faith    
    
    
    @Ross_McConnell yeah it's on 4    
    
    
    @DMcAPhotography no it didn't, ah well    
    
    
    @Paullyie and 4 went the wrong way!    
    
    
    Looking forward to hearing Dee @greensideupveg talking all about her blog and Blogger vs Wordpress at #KLCK tonight    
    
    
    Dee started her blog in 2009, it's all Lorna Sixsmith's fault #KLCK    
    
    
    Wordpress vs Blogger which do you prefer? #KLCK    
    
    
    Control seems to be a major benefit of having blog site vs a traditional website, update it yourself instead of asking web developer #KLCK    
    
    
    Dee blogs for her existing customers, to give them info they need, why do you blog? #KLCK    
    
    
    Dee says for a personal blog, blogger is good as its very easy to change the themes #KLCK    
    
    
    Google loves frequently updated sites so blogs tend to rank well #KLCK    
    
    
    Both Blogger and http://WordPress.com  have very good mobile versions that come as standard #KLCK    
    
    
    Commenting facility on Blogger is not great, often prevents people from commenting  #KLCK    
    
    
    @cdynamics We're discussing your blogger blog at #KLCK bloggers network, we like how your readers can choose their theme    
    
    
    Dee @greensideupveg sells these seeds, I love her packaging #KLCK pic.twitter.com/dPwxEe7G    
    
    
    Better get some shut eye, off to @measurementconf tomorrow, up at the crack of dawn but looking forward to it #donedealsocial    
    
    
    .@itsrealTED: 'If you try to wake me up by pulling my blankets off, I'll probably kill you.' That was so my 3 year old this morning,    
    
    
    Terrible stressful evening as two charge points not working, eventually got home after pissing off all motorway drivers by driving 50kmph    
    
    
    That's never happened before I've been really lucky with charge points up to now, resulting stress was not good though, bring on the carbs    
    
    
    Esp for Chinese New Year Here's a game of business snakes and ladders http://ow.ly/hy4IB  #yearofthesnake    
    
    
    @Spiderworking waves back to ya    
    
    
    Has it started yet? I'm running late #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC are you going Eamonn?    
    
    
    @cianodriscoll slow them down for me, create a diversion when I walk in late    
    
    
    @cianodriscoll oh mouse under chair is always good, will keep everyone on their toes    
    
    
    @rickoshea delighted to hear as I'm running late, they're all decoys I asked to buy me some time #donedealsocial #waitforme    
    
    
    @aoifep great, lots to catch up on, feeling very old when I added up the years    
    
    
    Brian Harte from Tourism Ireland talks about using social to create consideration for Ireland as a place to visit #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @PaulMDonovan I'd recommend http://prezi.com     
    
    
    Tourism Ireland have 18 Facebook pages, needed as cultural differences require a separate page for each target market #donedealsocial    
    
    
    Engagement is relevant as it happens prior to the state change, it's not ultimate goal of social but it contributes to it #donedealsocial    
    
    
    By 2015 we will reach 'peak desktop' - after then the number of people that view our site on desktop will decline #donedealsocial    
    
    
    '7% of people go to a store to look at the product and then go home and buy it online' #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @donald_richard sure, will have a goo at it later, no speakers from Sage #tuttut    
    
    
    Using a sentiment and social media monitoring tool  you could automatically filter out the mentions that don't apply #donedealsocial    
    
    
    A website is for life, not just for Christmas! #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @aoifep coming to seek you out for coffee    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC I'm blind so can you find me so we can grab a coffee?    
    
    
    Goodie bags yipeeeeee #donedealsocial pic.twitter.com/6ZKyazQz    
    
    
    @donald_richard will certainly have a look and see if I can make it, thanks for the invite    
    
    
    @cianodriscoll Was going to walk in and shout 'Mark Zuckerberg is in the lobby looking for a social media specialist' but decided against it    
    
    
    Being entertained by the creator of Condescending Corporate Brand Page @JonMorter, 'i'ts all bollocks' #donedealsocial    
    
    
    . @jonmorter is giving the most entertaining talk I've ever been to at #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L @jonmorter yeah and it's very funny    
    
    
    Barry Hand brining us through 'How to track value of Social using Google Analytics' at #donedealsocial pic.twitter.com/CKCLhiJT    
    
    
    @CadburyIreland You here at measurement conf? Want to thank you in person for choc you gave for goodie bags for an event last year    
    
    
    Barry Hand advises that Google Analytics 'won't give you all the numbers you want, it's not like Sage software' love that! #donedealsocial    
    
    
    Traveling to the dark side of social media with @GinaBo #donedealsocial pic.twitter.com/I6JeXKXz    
    
    
    'Does your company expect you to be the social media superhero for the organization?' @GinaBo at #donedealsocial pic.twitter.com/HvYXkdlI    
    
    
    Don't alienate yourself from the rest of the business, up skill the people you work with so they can do social too #donedealsocial    
    
    
    @aoifep yeah great seeing you, next time I'm down in Sligo I'll organise to drop in and you do the same when you're up in Dublin    
    
    
    I'm writing an ebook about Business Networking In Ireland, if your networking group wants to be included get in touch.    
    
    
    I'm writing an ebook about Business Networking In Ire, if your networking group wants to be included get in touch.    
    
    
    @eugryan Hi Eugene, thanks for your tweet.  What's your network group?    
    
    
    @GayeMoore sounds good can you email me some details Beatrice.whelan@sage.com    
    
    
    @safetysam66 thanks Liam, I've sent Sandra a LinkedIn message    
    
    
    @OlwenIBI thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @eugryan thanks yeah will def be including BNI if I can get the info    
    
    
    @eoink I'm going to the PRII talk today so if your around for a quick chat afterwards I'll catch you there?    
    
    
    First Google and then PRII - lots of learning to be done today    
    
    
    All parked up at the luas red cow for a free charge #ecar pic.twitter.com/1iO4cFjs    
    
    
    @SandraHartBNI @eugryan thanks Sandra will do    
    
    
    One week to go to enter the Business Achiever Awards http://ow.ly/hULVB  @SmallBC    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC thanks Eamonn    
    
    
    @themarkerhotel it looks amazing, congrats    
    
    
    @sageireland good luck Leila    
    
    
    I’m following the @AhainGroup to win 2 #SMWF Europe passes worth £1990 #pickme    
    
    
    ’m following the @AhainGroup to win 2 #SMWF Europe passes worth £1990 #pickme    
    
    
    Everyone say hello to Shauana, she's manning the @sageireland Twitter account today, hi Shauna you're doing a great job    
    
    
    It's employee appreciation day. Reduce employee attrition in your company, here's how http://ow.ly/iafL1  #employeeappreciationday    
    
    
    @paulinesargent @aoiferigney @spiderworking @jilloherlihy great idea, will get snapping    
    
    
    http://vine.co/v/bHIILWDlrEH     
    
    
    Meet some of the digiwomen at Sage http://vine.co/v/bHIILWDlrEH  #digiwoman @lornamkeogh @KarinaWT1983 @avrilmcardle @shauna_crawley @aislingwhite    
    
    
    Anyone else going to #digital_summit tomorrow? For me the speakers from @elementtechware and @stephenoleary  will be the ones I can't miss    
    
    
    @ElementTechWare thanks, will do    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital of course not, was saving my tweets for you for tomorrow, remember to give us some killer one liners to tweet!    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital 'What does BLOG stand for? A Better Listing On Google.' For this and more cheesy one liners, keep following :)    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital Glad I could be of service :)    
    
    
    @paulinesargent thanks Pauline    
    
    
    Just 2 requests for today's speakers, pls don't tell us digital is the future or that we need a mobile site #wealreadyknow #digital_summit    
    
    
    Google has a 94% market share in Ireland #digital_summit    
    
    
    In 2012 Technological Singularity occurred in the world of SEO, machines got smarter than humans with the Penguin update #digital_summit    
    
    
    The 4 new rules of SEO: growing site, natural inbound links, social signals and  authorship #digital_summit    
    
    
    Infographics are so hot right now! #digital_summit    
    
    
    Content marketing engages customers at every stage of the purchase funnel and ultimately increases conversion rate #digital_summit    
    
    
    @Spiderworking @jilloherlihy @paulinesargent @aoiferigney here's my vine http://vine.co/v/bHIILWDlrEH     
    
    
    Are any of the #digiwomen at 
#digital_summit ? #digiwoman convention during the break, yeah?    
    
    
    There's @WolfgangDigital jetting off to the US for another conference, ahh the life of an SEO expert #takemewithyou    
    
    
    @Spiderworking @jilloherlihy @paulinesargent @aoiferigney was trying to get one of the guys in the office to do #digidrag but none would :(    
    
    
    Regulation smegulation...only kidding I'm totally compliant! #digital_summit    
    
    
    @BrianHonan great talk, nicely balanced, useful info, good examples    
    
    
    In this world of digital and social we actually don't share what were working on with each other #digital_summit    
    
    
    Day of the app is challenged, as people move to their 2nd smart phone they will only download 5 apps they will actually use #digital_summit    
    
    
    @Spiderworking ah bugger    
    
    
    Death to the desktop website by @Brando_Digital at #digital_summit Desktop websites will behave like mobile websites    
    
    
    By 2015 we will reach peak desktop,num of people looking at website on desktop will decline as mobile takes over #digital_summit @iqcontent    
    
    
    @OlwenIBI it was great, so sorry for not getting back to you, up to my eyes but your top of my list when back in office tomorrow    
    
    
    @OlwenIBI was talking to someone about you yesterday that said you're great, but sur I knew that    
    
    
    @OlwenIBI ah now, all will be revealed in good time    
    
    
    @PierceComms @digital_summit @firstpageie @niallmckeown you are #digiflirts    
    
    
    @dmigroup @piercecomms @digital_summit @firstpageie @niallmckeown no body parts please! #digiflirts    
    
    
    @niallmckeown @piercecomms @digital_summit @firstpageie an app for the #digiflirts yeaaah!    
    
    
    .@stephenoleary I wonder what @irishmammies would make of tea patches    
    
    
    The carwings app allows me to defrost my car from bed, handy on a cold morning and no kettles needed #digital_summit    
    
    
    @badams the #digiwoman initiative will like that post  http://www.stateofsearch.com/fighting-sexism-a-digital-conferences/ … /cc @digital_summit    
    
    
    @badams good points there, the @BlogAwardsIE are organized by three women and at last years event we had a female MC too    
    
    
    @badams yeah sur it's always the same, for me I don't mind if the speakers are make or female once they give a good presentation    
    
    
    I think 4 FB posts from a brand a day is way too much, people will just hide your posts from their newsfeed #digital_summit    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital yeah you could do lots of tweets a day if they are well spaced out and provide value    
    
    
    @PierceComms @digital_summit @ncirldigital thanks, I try to provide light amusement wherever I go!    
    
    
    MT @sageireland: Paul here from the Sage webstore on Twitter today. pic.twitter.com/IgHnGTs6k6 > love the pic    
    
    
    @behanval yeah drop in for tea and we can compare our range!    
    
    
    A record day for Twitter hacking I see, getting lots of DMs from people that have clearly been hacked.    
    
    
    @O2IRL realized you've been charging me an extra 20 eur a month for UK roaming even though I only requested it for one month, months ago    
    
    
    @JeniPim @o2irl I know but I had to vent, so annoyed    
    
    
    O2IRL thanks but I've already spoken to someone in the call centre, want to change my plan too so waiting for a call back about that tmrw    
    
    
    @O2IRL on a plan that well exceeds my needs, been charged for roaming and text add ons that I don't use    
    
    
    @noel_davidson yes, am considering my options as they say. I'm well but not as well as those peeps that get a full page in the SBP ;)    
    
    
    @noel_davidson how could I miss it?;) Alas, I am not a media darling but who knows what the future may hold    
    
    
    @noel_davidson yeah, just sent you a DM about something I noticed, chat soon    
    
    
    Strategy is not just a buzz word. Discover the real meaning of strategy for your business via @olwenIBI http://ow.ly/jdkmd     
    
    
    @OlwenIBI you're very welcome, how are things in the west?    
    
    
    @OlwenIBI the same, snowing most of the day, need some sunshine badly    
    
    
    Dose goin' around #Irelandin3words    
    
    
    Read my interview w/ @Nic_Mc_Nally from @boards_ie about how businesses can get the most from engaging on boards http://ow.ly/jH7sA     
    
    
    @dmigroup thanks, really interesting answers from @boards_ie    
    
    
    @RadicalDublin Trying to contact you via email but it keeps bouncing back, can you DM me re an analytics project    
    
    
    @RadicalDublin thanks @jpmca will be in touch    
    
    
    Hello to all at #klck tonight, sorry to be missing the panelists and the conversation    
    
    
    @sageireland Hi Karina,I  see you tweetin', you tweet good!    
    
    
    Monkey https://vine.co/v/bt9vzbwEKAB     
    
    
    @dublingunner Vine videos are only 6 seconds, try Vine, it's cool    
    
    
    @dublingunner love the Sage picture    
    
    
    @WebSummitHQ founder of WordPress, Yes! - I call first dibs on interview    
    
    
    @WebSummitHQ just an idea, show how genuine your apology is and give free tickets to the #digiwomen    
    
    
    @WebSummitHQ also last years leaders lunch was an insult to the equality of women so I wouldn't be mentioning that in your apology    
    
    
    74% of Irish SMEs say Government should do more to support businesses http://bit.ly/13kHiDy  via @sageireland    
    
    
    @EI_EUPresidency how much are the tickets to EuroSME2013?    
    
    
    @EI_EUPresidency that's great, thanks    
    
    
    Back to work tomorrow after 3 weeks off, exams over and normal life resumes    
    
    
    For those of you curious about my ecar driving experience here is my post about the last six months #ecar http://www.esbecarsblog.ie/six-months-as-an-ecar-ambassador/ …    
    
    
    Do you do business with govt or local authorities? Read: Benefits Of Using A Purchase Order System http://www.sage.ie/blog/index.php/benefits-purchase-order-system/ … via @sageireland    
    
    
    The National Software Campus is offering 10% off a virtual office when you sign up in May http://ow.ly/kRukA  @NSCCampusCork    
    
    
    How to turn your Pinterest boards into a PDF or JPEG image so you can refer to them off line http://krishnade.com/2013/save-your-pinterest-boards-as-a-pdf/ … by @KrishnaDe    
    
    
    .@Glenisk pop up store on Dawson street #yumandfab pic.twitter.com/T5tuaFPOOX    
    
    
    Sad white babies with mean feminist mommies http://jessicavalenti.tumblr.com/post/25465502300/sad-white-babies-with-mean-feminist-mommies-the …    
    
    
    On my way into @iia conf on inbound marketing - content is king    
    
    
    Here at the @iia seminar in the digital hub. Coming up are talks from @WolfgangDigital and @HubSpot #contentisking    
    
    
    Here is the inbound marketing methodology Hubspot use via @searchbrat speaking at #contentdd pic.twitter.com/FclYJT3LtS    
    
    
    Think like a media company, what would a publisher do? #contentdd    
    
    
    Don't forget about context in your content marketing, tailor content to what your customers are interested in, use customer data #contentdd    
    
    
    Personalise email content based on what content each person previously downloaded #contentdd    
    
    
    First step of content marketing, build buyer personas. #contentdd pic.twitter.com/oVi85M8wEQ    
    
    
    Measure like a boss #contentdd pic.twitter.com/FNkBVnpczw    
    
    
    .@hlinehan is up next to tell us what media and publishing companies think about content marketing #contentdd    
    
    
    Porus Paywalls: the future of online newspapers? #contentdd    
    
    
    Display advertising is dead, long live content sponsorship! #contentdd    
    
    
    Content sponsorship only works if the content fits with the brand and audience of the publisher #contentdd    
    
    
    Create content that is so good people would pay for it and then give it for free - that is my biggest content marketing tip #contentdd    
    
    
    @hlinehan really enjoyed that, thanks    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital arts graduates with marketing postgrads also make great content marketers ;)    
    
    
    @TitanicBelfast planning my ecar charging route so I can make it up to Game of Thrones exhibit    
    
    
    Understand the difference between real time and evergreen content #contentdd    
    
    
    Siobhan from @WolfgangDigital giving lots of great practical examples of content marketing at #contentdd    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital I've gone all shy and blushing    
    
    
    I like this type of content calendar #contentdd pic.twitter.com/QWUmPUZHKW    
    
    
    COPE - create once publish everywhere - create your content then repurpose for newsletters, brochures, blogs, tweets etc. #contentdd    
    
    
    Here's the link to that 50 Business Tips Ebook that we did last year in Sage http://www.sage.ie/general-information/free_ebook_50_ways_to_help_your_business_prosper.html … #contentdd    
    
    
    @mychefathome thanks Wendy    
    
    
    @robgerard thanks for your RT    
    
    
    #IrishFoodTours launched http://www.irishfoodtours.ie/p/weekend-tours.html … via @mychefathome    
    
    
    #ictawards tough crowd    
    
    
    @niallkitson on my way :)    
    
    
    @martinjcasey @Arekibo best of luck from a long time fan, Bea    
    
    
    https://vine.co/v/bEgBTMX9Iul     
    
    
    The ICT Awards, a Vine https://vine.co/v/bEgBTMX9Iul  #ictawards    
    
    
    https://vine.co/v/bEgzTO10gJh     
    
    
    Lovin the 80s music  at the #ictawards more of this please    
    
    
    Have you tried turning it off and turning it back on again? #ictawards #theitcrowd    
    
    
    Just won the marketing excellence awards at the #ictawards #goteam @sageireland pic.twitter.com/vIhEh84uGW    
    
    
    Award on ice #ictawards pic.twitter.com/q5trOSo67R    
    
    
    Mexican wave at the Sage table #ictawards https://vine.co/v/bEgEqqmKFHE     
    
    
    Connecting With Your Customers, A Free Guide To Social Media http://ow.ly/k0vap  #socialmedia    
    
    
    @SenJohnWhelan Thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @RedCert the heads up?    
    
    
    @RedCert oh thanks, your kind and I'm sleepy    
    
    
    Twitter magnets pic.twitter.com/Zmjcs90xBQ    
    
    
    Grand Canal Theatre pre Loin King https://vine.co/v/b9X3ArY6tYT     
    
    
    Citywest on a sunny day https://vine.co/v/b9X35qBJIQe     
    
    
    @dublingunner hakuna matata!    
    
    
    So what did you do when Google was down?    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen yeah and I couldn't find anything, it was very strange    
    
    
    Nutella, with this social media debacle you are really spoiling us    
    
    
    @sageireland hi Aisling, you be doin' great on the twitter machine    
    
    
    Priest leads his sermon for fist holy communion mass talking about One Direction, went down a treat with the kids #trendypriest    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC I am Eamonn I'm at a communion dinner, enjoying a few    
    
    
    Just downloaded the Waze app, with Google and Facebook in a bidding war for it thought it would be worth a go    
    
    
    @Intel_IRL I'm liking your tweets, who mans your Twitter machine?    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel @BillGates there are many things I would do if I were 20, now what would you do if you were closer to 40? #justasking    
    
    
    @waze well just downloaded so will try it out properly tomorrow, in my ecar don't ya know! Nice social media monitoring btw    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel send a plane to collect me won't you    
    
    
    MT @_Sians: 7 Steps to Facebook Success http://bit.ly/YFcUnh  FREE webinar, with @MariSmith June 4th. Save your seat!    
    
    
    @elainelarkin I find it great, don't you like it?    
    
    
    @elainelarkin interesting, works fine for us in house but have never tried it outside. So handy though.    
    
    
    @WazeIreland @waze any chance of adding ecar charge points to the Waze app?    
    
    
    @Intel_IRL Nice one Sarah, liked the pic of Katie Taylor and the bunny man too    
    
    
    @WazeIreland super, thanks, if you need to discuss with Ireland charge point admins let me know and I can connect you with ESB ecars peeps    
    
    
    @WazeIreland yeah all ecar charge points are done by ESB ecars as far as I know, they have an app too ESBecars.ie    
    
    
    @WazeIreland great thanks    
    
    
    @pdscott no one told me either, outrageous!    
    
    
    @pdscott and I was just looking at a video about orbits of the sun, someone invent an app...    
    
    
    @pdscott ... that tells me about upcoming events depending on content I view or read    
    
    
    @susan_whyte @pdscott no I'm selling it to Google for one hundred billion euros, muhaha!    
    
    
    @susan_whyte @pdscott whats 100 million among friends, sur Nama write off that amount in an afternoon    
    
    
    @pdscott @susan_whyte 4 and 29    
    
    
    @susan_whyte @pdscott ticket tomorrow and tweet me the pic (and that was the last she ever heard of them...they were spotted in Vegas)    
    
    
    @susan_whyte @pdscott you going to social media awards on Thursday?    
    
    
    @susan_whyte @pdscott pity, we could have had a natter    
    
    
    If there's no chocolate, I'll be going to bed then    
    
    
    @waze @WazeIreland I see Waze will be at the Dublin Web Summit, I call dibs on an interview    
    
    
    10 On-Page SEO Tips For Beginners by @trevorkoen on the @sageoneireland blog http://www.sageone.ie/2013/05/28/seo_tips_for_beginners/ …    
    
    
    Big shout out to my wonderful nephew @RickyWhelan . We are with you Ricky.    
    
    
    @IrishSmiley hi Frederique that is brilliant, thanks so much    
    
    
    @IrishSmiley questions for interview to you early next week    
    
    
    At #sockies13 with @TrevorKoen here we go...    
    
    
    @ChMurphy hey yeah you too!    
    
    
    Lots of Twitter birds about #sockies13    
    
    
    @avrilmcardle @TrevorKoen we won, totally chuffed! pic.twitter.com/v5xohxL7Ru    
    
    
    Delighted we won best inbound marketing campaign at the #sockies13 tonight. Thanks @socmediaawards @HubSpot and team @sageireland    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 thanks *blushes*    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen thanks Trevor, couldn't have got up there without you    
    
    
    @elainelarkin thanks Elaine :)    
    
    
    @thesociable thanks guys    
    
    
    @Shauna_Crawley thanks #winning    
    
    
    Charging up at Dublin airport #ecar pic.twitter.com/DsH0ykpXpc    
    
    
    @davidhall75 yeah that's me :)    
    
    
    @sageireland congrats Lorna, well deserved, have a great night, cake tomorrow yeeeah!    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @Shauna_Crawley @aislingwhite @sageireland trophy cabinet required if this keeps up!    
    
    
    @LornaMKeogh you look fab, no one deserves it more than you Lorna, have a great night    
    
    
    @LornaMKeogh ah that's great, what a great story to share with others in work and post on the blog too, I feel a blog post coming on!    
    
    
    @ireland @MetEireann it's scientific name is 'The Leaving Cert phenomenon'    
    
    
    @markcahill worse it's getting    
    
    
    Social CRM is changing the way we do business. Good slideshare here by @wwwSageCRMcom http://slidesha.re/12J8qez     
    
    
    Road Trip ecar style!http://www.esbecarsblog.ie/road-trip-ecar-style/ …    
    
    
    What is RSS? And Is It Still Important? http://sbt.me/2k   By @anitacampbell    
    
    
    Changing my profile to 'available for BBQs'    
    
    
    @MTVIreland do you have an email address I can use?    
    
    
    About to deep dive into some CSS after a  six month break, this should be fun.    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel cross browser compatibility is my nemesis but I shall be victorious    
    
    
    Looking forward to #tasteofdublin13 next weekend, if the weather stays it will be brill    
    
    
    Good mobile site @MetEireann    
    
    
    I'll be speaking at the IIA Digital Marketing Mix Deep Dive on June 26th, tickets available here http://www.iia.ie/events/event/405/digital-marketing-mix/ …    
    
    
    @nickgoode thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @nickgoode will do    
    
    
    Managing Your Social Media While On Holiday http://ow.ly/lWNJh  by @sageireland on @TweakYourBiz    
    
    
    @AllogenBiotech congrats on your win #startupawards    
    
    
    I'll be speaking at the IIA Digital Marketing Mix Deep Dive on June 26th, tickets available here http://www.iia.ie/events/event/405/digital-marketing-mix/ …    
    
    
    @martina_skelly congrats, enjoy    
    
    
    @ireland snoop snoop    
    
    
    Many thanks to @groovyspoon and @CG_OnlineM for their amazing work on the new @BlogAwardsIE website http://blogawardsireland.com  #blogawardsIE    
    
    
    Which bloggers on #irishblogs will be entering Blog Awards Ireland 2013 http://www.blogawardsireland.com/nominations-open/ … #blogawardsIE    
    
    
    We've opened nominations for Blog Awards Ireland 2013  http://www.blogawardsireland.com/nominations-open/ … #blogawardsIE    
    
    
    Gorgeous day at @TasteDublin pic.twitter.com/Je46nAe5YC    
    
    
    @Glenisk are you at Taste of Dublin ?    
    
    
    @conorbyrne thanks Conor it was designed by @groovyspoon    
    
    
    @GingerTT @keithbohanna @mark_breen  thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @tbake thanks for your share and mention    
    
    
    @YesYesStephen @mudpuds thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @nialldevitt @AhainGroup thanks for your support and RT    
    
    
    @RickyWhelan that would be great news, fingers crossed for ya here    
    
    
    @noel_davidson hardly famous but thanks all the same :)    
    
    
    @noel_davidson No avoiding me at the moment I'm afraid :)    
    
    
    There's @Tracey2103 and @Cute_Honey_  in Irish Tatler, providing good advice and doing it with style    
    
    
    @worldirish a good bargain #whatmakesirishpeoplehappy    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital @Spiderworking hard to get good content peeps. One recruiter said to me 'they're all in Hubspot or Sage' ;)    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital @Spiderworking Will get the thinking caps on    
    
    
    @frogmahon ha, there goes my 15 mins!    
    
    
    At the @iia Deep Dive, presenting about how Sage use social media. Any questions for me? pic.twitter.com/CCS4hKg8oF    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital Howya!    
    
    
    Live from #deepdive3 Top Tops for posting to your FB page: Keep it short, use photos, promote special offers pic.twitter.com/K9rQeLalNY    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital thanks!    
    
    
    Brave and innovative use of social media by @Burritosblues #deepdive3 pic.twitter.com/jBEvFC4kWw    
    
    
    . @Burritosblues How can you say Burrito this many times and not give us burritos, #burritocrave #deepdive3    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen I'm expecting to see a mega interface when I get into work in the morning, here wondering what you have made #makeymakey    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 I'm coming in early just for that    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph hi yeah no problem, ill send it on, the pres itself is just pics, no text in it I'm afraid so not sure how useful it will be    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph yeah sure drop me an email Beatrice.whelan@sage.com    
    
    
    80 rules of social media via @jeremywaite http://jeremywaite.tumblr.com/post/51674205690/the-80-rules-of-social-media …    
    
    
    @jeremywaite I've just emailed it to the whole marketing team :)    
    
    
    Tasting fab chocolate and lemon desert @Glenisk pop up shop pic.twitter.com/cUwfapibkP    
    
    
    @RuthBurnside o what is it? Send me a pic    
    
    
    @RuthBurnside oh yeah thanks yeah that's great that there are more charge points    
    
    
    Free tickets left for this special event on 17th July in the Shelbourne. Speakers from Google and Facebook. Register http://ow.ly/mS6cm     
    
    
    Child of Prague is up to keep the good weather for Paul's wedding pic.twitter.com/jkP3fLZ3t3    
    
    
    @darraghdoyle thanks Darragh    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel sorry Conor should have dropped you an invite, do ya wanna come?    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel thanks Conor will do    
    
    
    Séadna Dervan from Facebook giving some great tips on using Facebook for business at #bizchatirl pic.twitter.com/Sb3I9oH2Ac    
    
    
    What would you do if you weren't afraid #Bizchatirl pic.twitter.com/EySy57vMMh    
    
    
    @cianodriscoll @rickoshea @SageOneIreland thanks Cian, it was tempting wasn't it    
    
    
    @rickoshea @SageOneIreland thanks for coming Rick, you were a great host for our party    
    
    
    @FionaFKearns @SageOneIreland Thanks for coming :)    
    
    
    @Spiderworking thanks for coming :)    
    
    
    @SherylThompson @TrendsIreland whoop whoop    
    
    
    @SageOneIreland blushing now    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Spiderworking come over for some lemonade    
    
    
    @Irishcooking @IrishFarmerette I think you might have @sageireland confused with a different business, the Sage restaurant I'm thinking?    
    
    
    @mediaflash you are indeed #whoopwhoop    
    
    
    @mark_breen I love this, can I share it out?    
    
    
    @mark_breen I think it's brilliant, really good graphics    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 I love it!    
    
    
    "@KarinaWT1983 Thought you might like this @beatricewhelan #bearocks pic.twitter.com/AbF0CXK6J4" > I love it!    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph done :)    
    
    
    Looking forward to the Blog awards launch tomorrow night in the @Glenisk pop up shop on Dawson street    
    
    
    For anyone attending or virtually watching the launch of @BlogAwardsIE this evening the hashtag is  #blogawardsIE    
    
    
    @PatCarrollTouch you going to the launch tonight?    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @BlogAwardsIE thanks so much, wish you were here but not to worry the big event is in October :)    
    
    
    @aoifep yeah looking forward to it, we'll have to set aside some time for a decent chat    
    
    
    If you're heading into the #blogawardsIE launch you're in for a real treat, @Glenisk food is amazing so make sure to grab some @TrevorKoen    
    
    
    @Con_Keppel @PatCarrollTouch perhaps :) sur they let me tag along :)    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph @MediaBoxPR thank you soooo much, and for the other thing too, delighted!    
    
    
    @PatCarrollTouch no worries Pat, hope all is well with you, see you later @LorGMedia    
    
    
    #blogawardsie loving the branded menus pic.twitter.com/ubfzgYYpvl    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @Glenisk we'll save you a space and some Glenisk treats    
    
    
    Tweet wall old school #blogawardsie pic.twitter.com/xXW3aR1OHk    
    
    
    Yummy Glenisk Eton mess #blogawardsie pic.twitter.com/NFoFEFGjSY    
    
    
    .@Corcradee with the tweet wall #blogawardsie pic.twitter.com/1CDvRKUSCi    
    
    
    @LorGMedia great to meet you too :)    
    
    
    @digital_times Thanks for coming Stephen :)    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital Missed you guys last night, where were ye hiding?    
    
    
    @unakavanagh thanks for coming, sorry I didn't get to meet you in person    
    
    
    @AgrilandIreland great to meet you last night    
    
    
    @unakavanagh we will indeed :)    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital ha! I was on the ground floor chatting all evening, it was fun wasn't it?    
    
    
    @WolfgangDigital I know, delish!    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph I did indeed, sorry was a very busy few days with the long list announced. Reply coming to you this morning :)    
    
    
    @themarkerhotel nom nom nom    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen had to share this with @KarinaWT1983 she loves that song http://youtu.be/YOZjaqHioro?a )    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 we can totally replicate that in the office, ill bring the kids instruments, you bring the banana    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 totally!    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen oh god what have I started! We can totally go viral with Karinas maracas alone!    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen nice choice of words Karina, never heard it called that before ;)    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 i feel a debut at the ploughing championships coming on    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen I kinda need to practice, it's a complex song, who's lead vocals?    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 well @jpmca can you be front man?    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @KarinaWT1983 @jpmca we might need to speak to his agent    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen @jpmca more cowbell :)    
    
    
    @RachelArgyle @irishtatler @dmigroup thanks Rachel and no probs :)    
    
    
    @aoifep @PerfecPlan4Life @Shaneymac yeah same here, see you all there    
    
    
    @SageOneIreland @nicklevine Hi Nick, can I email you their details? DM me your email.    
    
    
    @nicklevine thanks, yeah got the DM, perhaps it was just slow    
    
    
    @aoifeban @ashleyaagrey @mashob we already danced beside that piano!    
    
    
    @mashob @aoifeban @ashleyaagrey famous last words :) I need to see those pics    
    
    
    @ashleyaagrey @mashob @aoifeban same here, milkshake from supermacs, best cure ever    
    
    
    @mashob @ashleyaagrey @aoifeban no town, I was all danced out :)    
    
    
    @mashob @ashleyaagrey @aoifeban I trust you're selecting only the most innocent of pics :)    
    
    
    @ashleyaagrey oh yeah it's Short Stack from the folks at @ShortStackLab    
    
    
    @ShortStackLab done :)    
    
    
    @ashleyaagrey FB comp rules just changed, more info here http://allfacebook.com/updated-promotions-guidelines_b124179 …    
    
    
    At the #tg4fomhar event with @aislingwhite. I need some help with the Gaeilge    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen I have dibs on the xylophone    
    
    
    @ashleyaagrey no probs at all :)    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @aislingwhite @avrilmcardle @CadburyIreland OMG I'm so healthy so!    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L @whitecupeoin @JBBC  yeah I've done some, tip would be to find a good template and then change it to suit what you want    
    
    
    @nickgoode @simondbell @TrevorKoen well if they have good social media monitoring they should pick that right up ;)    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen @nickgoode @simondbell indeed :)    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen just saw this tweet, how very relevant    
    
    
    @NiamhPedreschi no I don't think so, unless they shared a commonality, then you might be able to do some sort if search on the folder...    
    
    
    @NiamhPedreschi ...search that would find them all and then you could delete    
    
    
    @NiamhPedreschi soz    
    
    
    @NiamhPedreschi no probs, we need to do that lunch soon, I miss our chats    
    
    
    @NiamhPedreschi yeah sounds good    
    
    
    @themarkerhotel seeking cronuts, I'll be there tomorrow, can I buy a box?    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @themarkerhotel it was meant to be a surprise for all of you #caughtme    
    
    
    @KarinaWT1983 @themarkerhotel it can be our little secret ;)    
    
    
    In Utero is 20 years old, I feel old #Nirvana    
    
    
    7 secret website functions you probably don't know about (via @dailyedge) http://jrnl.ie/1089484     
    
    
    Bitcoin and the homeless, interesting read via @jpmca http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/09/bitcoin-homeless/2/ …    
    
    
    Industry Report: Social Customer Service, Care & Support by @AhainGroup http://ow.ly/p16fu  #custserv #custexp    
    
    
    Oldie but a goodie. Great People Doing The Right Things http://www.ceotoceo.biz/publications/best-practices-illustrations/item/278-great-people-doing-the-right-things-network-appliance.html …    
    
    
    Well worth a read if you have a few minutes. From Dot Com Zero to Hero http://www.fourhourworkweek.com/blog/2013/09/17/alexis-ohanian-reddit/#more-9989 …    
    
    
    @AhainGroup very welcome :)    
    
    
    Google tries to solve death  http://www.technologyreview.com/view/519456/google-to-try-to-solve-death-lol/ …    
    
    
    Google to Encrypt ALL Keyword Searches: Say Goodbye to Keyword Data  http://blog.hubspot.com/google-encrypting-all-searches-nj …    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph @WolfgangDigital Yeaaah congrats David    
    
    
    The second coming of Java. Bye Ruby on Rails, hello Scala http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/09/the-second-coming-of-java/ …    
    
    
    Google Has Unveiled A New Search Algorithm http://po.st/DCkafa  via @popsci    
    
    
    @EamoGrant @google @iia @smockalley yes big day ahead tomorrow, two really good events #spoiled    
    
    
    At the @iia #netvis13 awards with @jpmca wish us luck pic.twitter.com/gEYaCntu28    
    
    
    #nerdroast has begun! #netvis13    
    
    
    Room looks great  #netvis13 #nerdfest pic.twitter.com/8kaBhKdT0S    
    
    
    @aoifep are you here? Shirley is here #reunion    
    
    
    @aoifep I'll tell her you said hi, see you in October    
    
    
    @jpmca John Casey lifetime achievement award pic.twitter.com/VbvEZrFJVd    
    
    
    @yoga_with_emma no prob I'm good thanks    
    
    
    @yoga_with_emma can I send you a DM    
    
    
    @theianfella for sure, send on the link or the doc    
    
    
    @theianfella is that you in the finals of the blog awards BTW?    
    
    
    @theianfella #wow    
    
    
    @theianfella great post, rich with information, tells a story, love it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @theianfella that's if you're willing?    
    
    
    @theianfella but won't the Google gods frown upon that sort of thing? :)    
    
    
    @theianfella plus don't want to be stealing your traffic, maybe could take it in a few weeks and tag it up so you get the SEO juice not us    
    
    
    @theianfella you still knocking around city west?    
    
    
    @theianfella oh go on then, I'll have some of that then!    
    
    
    @theianfella will have to bring you for a spin before I give back this ecar    
    
    
    @theianfella yeah let's do that and then we can link back to part 1 on your blog, we'll inbound the hell out if it!    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen love it!    
    
    
    @SageOneIreland save me a tweetie pie #fomo    
    
    
    @Shauna_Crawley @TrevorKoen I want to see video footage!    
    
    
    @stephenjatdell why not go fully electric and try a Nissan Leaf. Lots of charge points around.    
    
    
    @stephenjatdell yeah here you go http://www.esb.ie/electric-cars/electric-car-charging/electric-car-charge-point-map.jsp …    
    
    
    @stephenjatdell you also get a charge point installed at home for free when you buy an ecar. I have one at home and one in work.    
    
    
    Tickets for next weeks blog awards available here http://www.blogawardsireland.com/blog-awards-tickets/ …    
    
    
    @stephenjatdell no probs if you need any more info just let me know, happy driving!    
    
    
    Morning, this is good: Instrumental Cover of Daft Punk's 'Get Lucky' via @marklittlenews http://screen.yahoo.com/popular/daft-punks-lucky-gets-folked-100044382 …    
    
    
    @marklittlenews very good, it sounds Cuban when played like that    
    
    
    Kettle is on    
    
    
        
    
    
    Love this: Visual Content: The Potential and Pitfalls of Parallax Design from @cmicontent http://contentmarketinginstitute.com/2013/10/visual-content-potential-pitfalls-parallax-design/ …    
    
    
    @aoifep hey haven't even looked at it yet, Blog Awards this weekend, call you Monday?    
    
    
    @miss_susanboyle absolutely LOVED your show tonight, want to see it again, next time with friends and not on a school night ;)    
    
    
    @aoifep thanks :)    
    
    
    @aoifep yeah we speaking Wednesday or Thursday?    
    
    
    @aoifep I've not prepared anything, will be working this Sunday so!    
    
    
    There is at least one camel on the loose in Finglas (via @thejournal_ie) http://jrnl.ie/1122957     
    
    
    @simondata looks like it was a good event    
    
    
        
    
    
    @derekgreene would like to hear your interpretation of the graphs, we must arrange for us to meet up with you, you going Saturday night?    
    
    
    @derekgreene great, will organise something, wouldn't be feedback, would be us learning from you, looks really interesting    
    
    
    Birdy is on the Late Late singing Wings #whatatreat    
    
    
    It's not your average Saturday ya know, it's Blog Awards Saturday! Expect lots of tweets to fill up your feed. Soz in advance!    
    
    
    @theianfella they are like gold dust, I nearly had to give up my seat, we need a bigger boat!    
    
    
    @armelleskitchen yum!    
    
    
    @sarahryantweets @BlogAwardsIE thanks for all your help Sarah, looking forward to catching up later    
    
    
    For anyone coming to the Blog Awards tonight, we have an abundance of Oreo cookies @CadburyIreland #sugarrush #yum pic.twitter.com/JRhI11tfSk    
    
    
    @WriteOnTrack_L @Spiderworking yeah in the bar    
    
    
    @TrevorKoen we have a similar abundance of TK red lemonade, you've not experienced Ireland until you have red lemonade    
    
    
    Here we go #blogawardsie    
    
    
    @Shauna_Crawley @groovyspoon @TrevorKoen and me!    
    
    
    @simondbell thanks Simon    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph @sarahryantweets brilliant, that's how we do it!    
    
    
    #theinternetisforporn may yet trend #blogawardsie pic.twitter.com/WelFXutLjk    
    
    
    @IrishFarmerette @cearbhuil @Spiderworking thanks Damien for your help again this year    
    
    
    @avrilmcardle thanks Avril, it did and there was some great dancing from @Shauna_Crawley and @TrevorKoen    
    
    
    @PatCarrollTouch thanks Pat for your support again, couldn't do it without the sponsors    
    
    
    @thesociable @BlogAwardsIE @Spiderworking @WriteOnTrack_L thanks for coming and big congrats on your win    
    
    
    From the #blogawardsie goodie bag, my fave new mug pic.twitter.com/l6Zk8u0zK2    
    
    
    The full list of winners from #blogawardsie http://www.blogawardsireland.com/and-the-winners-are/ … @BlogAwardsIE    
    
    
    @JBBC thanks Marie and congrats on your win, well deserved    
    
    
    @groovyspoon great to finally meet you in person last night, thanks for making the trip down    
    
    
    Craving Hawaiian pizza    
    
    
    @PatCarrollTouch all I know is that a cure is badly needed ;)    
    
    
    @DavidCorscadden @IrishFarmerette @Spiderworking thanks David, glad you enjoyed it    
    
    
    @Eco__Evolution @IrishFarmerette @Spiderworking thanks Mary, we had great fun doing it    
    
    
    @trickearney @IrishFarmerette @Spiderworking thanks, it was great to meet so many bloggers that I follow    
    
    
    If you loved the entertainment at #blogawardsie as much as I did, follow @underCURRENTdub    
    
    
    @LorGMedia @PatCarrollTouch @IrishFarmerette @Spiderworking I had forgotten it was Pat that connected us, thanks Pat!    
    
    
    @LorGMedia I mangled those Irish blog names last night, should have asked you up on stage to announce them    
    
    
    From @sageireland Win a #WebSummit ticket with Sage http://ow.ly/pN8he     
    
    
    @aoifep can you DM your number and I call you in the morning at 10.15 if that suits?    
    
    
    @thesociable @WriteOnTrack_L @Spiderworking still getting over this year! Feel like hibernating for the winter!    
    
    
    @thesociable @TheClotheslines ah ha! Now I know who to keep an eye on!    
    
    
    @LouisFitzHotel 'Congrats @beatricewhelan Winner of @Joelsrestaurant Business Bowl competition of overnight stay and Dinner B&B for 2'  :)    
    
    
    Eleanor Catton becomes the youngest ever winner of the Booker Prize http://jrnl.ie/1131772     
    
    
    Today I'm  at #NWED in Laois where I'll be speaking about business blogging. Tweet me your questions.    
    
    
    @aoifep @PerfecPlan4Life @Shaneymac see you all soon    
    
    
        
    
    
    Looking forward to some good questions about business blogging at @nwed #nwed    
    
    
    Big crowd for the #NWED social media workshop pic.twitter.com/wrKooJGNpd    
    
    
    .@Shaneymac we are all on our phones, tweeting your talk about phones, that's so meta right now! #nwed    
    
    
    My phone is ringing, wouldn't it be ironic to talk on the phone now #nwed #hellooo!    
    
    
    @aoifep no that's just what I picked up on the inter web ;) they don't teach that in school!    
    
    
    80% of all social media conversations are happening on a mobile device #nwed    
    
    
    @carolokelly Thanks Carol, it's great to get feedback like that    
    
    
    Next up at #nwed is @aoifep - a web developer who actually gets SEO, this is more rare than you would think    
    
    
    SEO is for life, not just for Christmas! #nwed @aoifep    
    
    
    @nwed thanks, really enjoyed it    
    
    
    @ISLEmagazine sorry I had to leave after the social media workshop, little girl at home who needed her mam    
    
    
    @ISLEmagazine @BlogAwardsIE thanks, no, back in the office #missingout    
    
    
    @sewingconcepts very welcome, hope it was helpful    
    
    
    Via @TheOneImage: 'Stunning new Blade Runner trailer styled to look like a sepia-toned 1940's film noir http://www.theverge.com/2013/10/16/4846140/blade-runner-goes-from-cyberpunk-to-classic-noir-in-a-recut-trailer …' really nice    
    
    
    @TheOneImage both :) yeah looks good, never read the books but I hear it's really good    
    
    
    Win a #WebSummit ticket with Sage http://ow.ly/pN8he     
    
    
    Where are all the tech women? http://www.irishtimes.com/life-and-style/where-are-all-the-tech-women-1.1565824#.UmQReiHTc7w.twitter … via @IrishTimes #websummit    
    
    
    Win a #WebSummit ticket with Sage http://ow.ly/pN8he     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Omaniblog I'll be there and so will @sageireland and @SageOneIreland    
    
    
    @Omaniblog yaaay! Thank you, thanks for the podcast you did with us last year. Hope you're going to come visit us again this year?    
    
    
    @EmmaZgo love the pics you're posting to the Irish architecture FB page, great quality and the perfect amount of info in the captions.    
    
    
    Via @lifehacker The "personal brand" myth: http://lifehac.kr/6CWr4Vt     
    
    
    World War Z #brilliant    
    
    
    Here's a list of essential things you need to know for Dublin Web Summit - http://list.ly/list/9tw-dublin-web-summit … #websummit via @IanCleary    
    
    
    When art is successful it unavoidably becomes a business    
    
    
    Via @SpotifyIreland 'Here's a playlist that gets us through any run. http://spoti.fi/19FayZO  ' Handy    
    
    
    @donal_cahalane @Burritosblues yum! Good idea, where is the nearest one to Web Summit?    
    
    
    @Burritosblues @donal_cahalane RDS on Wednesday and Thursday, stand set up on Tuesday eve, 10,000 hungry ones to be fed!    
    
    
        
    
    
    For those attending #WebSummit tomorrow here is a handy schedule and floor plan http://ow.ly/qhUqh  via @sageireland    
    
    
    @TheReluctantSC Thanks Eamonn, you going tomorrow?    
    
    
    @eoink trying to DM you back but can't, drop me an email?    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph I will indeed, be sure to pop by for a coffee and a chat    
    
    
    #WebSummit is giving everyone the full Irish experience in Market Bar pic.twitter.com/CzhQO2wtlv    
    
    
    .@amandajobbins you rocked the Digital Stage #websummit pic.twitter.com/WHO0q83fsQ    
    
    
    @pdrox was just about to send you a DM but you don't follow me, you crazy?    
    
    
    @pdscott I was wondering why you always look so scared when we meet at web summit :)    
    
    
    #nightsummit pic.twitter.com/iWCnC6L5ER    
    
    
    Anyone know what time and which stage Matt Mullenweg is on today #WebSummit #WebSummit2013    
    
    
    @carolineblang @paulinesargent thanks    
    
    
    This way to the cloud #websummit pic.twitter.com/vDIeQtcnpC    
    
    
    @EcoAppz thanks, you should check out the live stream    
    
    
    @Spiderworking yeah I'm at the digital stage, wanna do coffee in a few mins?    
    
    
    Vine cafe @spiderworking pic.twitter.com/zQr6D6JLJP    
    
    
    @eoink email on its way    
    
    
    Congregation.ie is a social media conf on in Cong, Mayo on November 30th. More here @congregation13 http://www.congregation.ie/blog/LearningNeedsFacetoFace.html …    
    
    
    This week's #SageOne draw for 300 eur closes at midnight. Enter here http://uk.sageone.com/plus-one/  @SageOneIreland    
    
    
    ''@moranstheweir: We are delighted to be named again in the Michelin Good Food Pub Guide 2014 #pubs #michelinguide2014'' well deserved    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph yeah it was great, you going to @congregation13 ?    
    
    
    @mcwilliamph @congregation13 @eoink trying to see if it is possible as will be just back from a trip to the UK    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @brandalisms agree, kinda cool isn't it    
    
    
    Is it better to walk or run in the rain  http://m.youtube.com/watch?v=3MqYE2UuN24 …    
    
    
    @xcelbusiness np, these are the important things in life :)    
    
    
    Thanks Karen from Karen's Kupcakes for this beautiful cake she made for Sophie's 4th birthday. http://instagram.com/p/gQBCkLRE7_/     
    
    
    @miss_susanboyle had it last year, could not stop coughing, up all night, fever too, it feels different to a cold, get thee to a doctor    
    
    
    Thinking of hiring an app developer on Elance, read this first http://tnw.to/p9DM  by @mikelemovitz on @TheNextWeb    
    
    
    I'm trying out @path Anyone else tried it, thoughts?    
    
    
    Want to be inspired? Check out this video of @garyvee at #websummit http://new.livestream.com/websummit/MainStage2013/videos/33533712 …    
    
    
    @fleurman thanks Jim    
    
    
    @Omaniblog @listly a Thanks Paul it was great to meet you    
    
    
        
    
    
    All of this has happened before and it will all happen again.    
    
    
    Going to @Inbounddublin this evening to see @iPullRank @iacquire at @HarrysotGreen    
    
    
    #inbounddublin kicks off pic.twitter.com/GVoCX6c1f0    
    
    
    Big Dublin welcome to Michael King @iPullRank #inbounddublin pic.twitter.com/ZdeYeARkxs    
    
    
    12 Days of linkmas #loveit #inbounddublin    
    
    
    @brandalisms you here at Inbound Dublin? If so hello, I'm the girl in the blue coat :)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @brandalisms same here, yes please do that would be great    
    
    
    @_LouisGrenier sounds good, you want to do a call or a coffee?    
    
    
    @_LouisGrenier eh since you asked for the catch up why would I come to you ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Day started rough and got a whole lot better when I got biscuits shaped as shoes from my work colleagues, yum! pic.twitter.com/sCtsNWGlh9    
    
    
    @_LouisGrenier sure does    
    
    
    Nice Twitter promo by @OpiumDublin using the #GoodThingsComeInPairs hashtag    
    
    
    Ireland gets a new computer, isn't that good  http://www.rte.ie/news/2013/1113/486469-supercomputer-fionn/ …    
    
    
    Love this - couple convince their kids that their toy dinosaurs come to life every night  https://medium.com/thoughts-on-creativity/6f4cb1886d41 …    
    
    
    @RCHunt92 Enterprise Ireland or IDA might have some reports or ebooks, check their website    
    
    
    @brandalisms you got any info on the Xmas thing?    
    
    
    @brandalisms sounds exciting! Thanks chat later    
    
    
    Not just one cornetto then ;) RT '@rtenews: Ice cream cone recall on after pain relief tablet found in two cones' pic.twitter.com/cApMbRczbd    
    
    
    @noel_davidson I try ;)    
    
    
    @simonhodgkins getting it done early then    
    
    
    @simonhodgkins it's beginning to look a lot like ...    
    
    
    Best of luck to Michael Thompson @mickthompson83 and the team from Sage @sageireland at the CCMA awards tonight #ccmalive    
    
    
    @robmacgalway oh very handsome, have a great night, ye deserve it    
    
    
    @mickthompson83 @sageireland congrats that is great news, well done!    
    
    
    @robmacgalway tell them to keep those suits for the Christmas party    
    
    
    @aislingwhite rocky my vintage, you gonna get yourself a little something?    
    
    
        
    
    
    #alien http://instagram.com/p/g86gHcRE8p/     
    
    
    .@siliconrepublic are hiring http://www.siliconrepublic.com/careers/item/34921-were-hiring-online-news-e …    
    
    
    7 Irish duos that work better together by @Sageoneireland on @dailyedge http://jrnl.ie/1181172     
    
    
    @simondbell thanks Simon, will do!    
    
    
    Tyneside http://instagram.com/p/hQjYxIREwv/     
    
    
    Tyneside http://instagram.com/p/hQjl2KREw-/     
    
    
    #rudolf http://instagram.com/p/hRcz5TxE3u/     
    
    
    All you need to know about US Visa Options for Business in @USVisaExpert #Slideshare: http://slideshare.net/DeirdreOBrien/ … pic.twitter.com/65H1FY1zln    
    
    
        
    
    
    Perfect for December 1st, listen at 5.45 secs in for a little surprise #bellx1 http://open.spotify.com/track/0G1eTYQa7JMqMmFN2B9iDv …    
    
    
    #purpletree http://instagram.com/p/hgy1LgxE7P/     
    
    
    @dublingunner thanks, that could be arranged. I had a little help from a 4 year old elf!    
    
    
    @simondbell @KarinaWT1983 @TrevorKoen thanks Simon, I really enjoyed it too, loads of water today ;)    
    
    
    #lacuciucina #kildarevillage http://instagram.com/p/hoGsmlxE0q/     
    
    
    The perfect recovery aid #tiramisu http://instagram.com/p/hoJ2_ORE6z/     
    
    
    #festive http://instagram.com/p/hoLMnQRE9K/     
    
    
    @mcwilliamph will do, although it may be Feb at this stage, always head to Galway for birthday treats    
    
    
    Don’t panic: How to undo a sent email in Gmail (via @thejournal_ie) http://jrnl.ie/1206559     
    
    
    Mrs Claus tells us a story at #Rathwood http://instagram.com/p/hqw3ewRE3e/     
    
    
    The moderation glitch http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/12/the-moderation-glitch.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+typepad%2Fsethsmainblog+%28Seth%27s+Blog%29&utm_content=FaceBook …    
    
    
    Council rejects ‘premature’ motion to accept Bitcoin payments (via @thejournal_ie) http://jrnl.ie/1222314     
    
    
    Top 10 things to do in Dublin This Christmas  http://www.visitdublin.com/InsideDublin/Dublins_Top_10s/Top_10_This_Christmas …    
    
    
    @BrianHonan thanks for the RT    
    
    
    @RickyWhelan is that really heading our way?    
    
    
        
    
    
    The IT Crowd Special: 'The Internet Is Coming', Christmas Eve on Channel 4. YES!    
    
    
    Good micro site from entertainment.ie listing all the Xmas movies http://entertainment.ie/microsite/christmas-guide/movies.asp …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @faithwhelan I gots them!    
    
    
    Facebook now tracking what you decide not to post.  http://socialmediatoday.com/jillian-ryan/2021176/you-are-what-you-type-facebook-tracks-what-you-decide-not-post …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Kindle in hand, book recommendations please, tweet me your top 3    
    
    
    @BrendaDrumm thanks will check them out, Happy Christmas    
    
    
    @PatCarrollTouch thanks Pat, Transatlantic is def on the list, Merry Christmas    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @pdscott I thought as much    
    
    
    Perfect night for watching Fargo #Netflix    
    
    
    That awkward moment when you can't let visitors into a room as it's just too messy    
    
    
    @groovyspoon haha keepin' it real then, how was your Christmas?    
    
    
    @groovyspoon well in that case, here's to a happy and *healthy* new year to you all    
    
    
    'I can't believe it's not pleather' cc @Shauna_Crawley    
    
    
    