    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 Congrats on getting the internship!! That is so exciting!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Oh! @Lisaka please do!! Where are you going??    
    
    
    YES, Sandra Bullock! So classy! So elegant! #Oscars    
    
    
    @eolson5 Very emotional! She's so gracious!    
    
    
    @kmatthews I like 1 and 2!    
    
    
    @Lisaka I've never been to Latin America, although I've heard some amazing things about it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @eolson5 Thank you! :)    
    
    
    Last day of classes at the University of Oregon!!    
    
    
    YES! Drinks at Rennies! RT @sarahannelilly well...yes it is always fun! But @krhodey and I are hoping for drinks at Rennies :)    
    
    
    @ConanOBrien starting tour in #Eugene on April 12!! I wish I wasn't moving!! http://bit.ly/bNTd3U    
    
    
    Working with @andrewmphillips on finishing our final PR plan for @EugRec Outdoor Program!    
    
    
    So happy to be done with school! Thank you @derville and @kmatthews for teaching me about PR!    
    
    
    Back to California! Goodbye #Eugene!    
    
    
    @alexknott Thanks, Alex! I can't wait to come visit you and @jsoriano21 in LA!    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 Hi! How are you liking LA? How's the new job treating you?    
    
    
    Plane tickets officially booked. Destination: Hanoi, Vietnam.    
    
    
    @eolson5 I leave in a month! I'm so excited! How are you doing?    
    
    
    Sad news. Vietnam postponed for later... South Korea here I come!    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 Hey, John! I've been working for my dad while waiting to go to SD. What about you? Are you still liking LA??    
    
    
    @andrewmphillips What's up Drew? How is the @EugRec internship going??    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 I'm moving to SD in July! I can't wait! We should meet up when I come down!    
    
    
    I'm finding I like using Wordpress much better than Blogger... Or maybe I'm still in the learning curve.    
    
    
    Just created a new travel blog! Check it out! http://bit.ly/besS4A    
    
    
    Just updated my travel blog! http://bit.ly/besS4A  Leaving for #Seoul in ten days!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hello from Busan, South Korea!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jsoriano21 You are going to the Dancing with the Stars finale??? So jealous!! Say hi to Evan Lysacek for me!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    The new Harry Potter trailer is such a tease! Can't wait for the movie! http://bit.ly/9M3TpJ    
    
    
    Just found out the new AP Styleguide 2010 now spells "Web site" as "website." Good to know! http://bit.ly/EZr1O    
    
    
    Just read some awesome posts on @EpicAsia's blog! http://bit.ly/aEEifv    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 I'm moving beginning of August! Can we please have a reunion!? I want to hear all about the new job too!    
    
    
    Someone in San Francisco turned an old church into a huge family home! Take a look! http://bit.ly/9WJwuS    
    
    
    Go go go Japan!!! #jpn    
    
    
    Now officially living in #SanDiego!    
    
    
    @nikimae Nope nope. I'm permanently in San Diego now. What are you up to these days? :)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Pictures that will restore your faith in humanity http://bit.ly/LCi1jj  #actsofkindness    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ann Curry announces new role at NBC News http://bit.ly/L4fnn1  via @todayshow    
    
    
    This is crazy! Tiger Wood's ex-wife is getting 100 million in a divorce settlement. http://bit.ly/aVUHlE    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @nikimae Hehe! Sorry! Even though SD is nice, I do miss #Eugene a lot! Especially the summers. :)    
    
    
    Uh oh! Dropbox Admits Hack, Adds More Security Features http://twb.io/QpYXob  @informationweek    
    
    
    @JSanger13 It's support group time!    
    
    
    @JSanger13 that's why I moved them all close to you!    
    
    
    @JSanger13 Don't leaaaavvve meeeee!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Japanese goody day at work! With @JSanger13 #asianfood #yumm pic.twitter.com/creH33t7    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @dos_dedos I love using Mpme! RT: Nominate MPme for the Best Overall Startup of 2012 2012 Crunchie! http://is.gd/vf75CB  #crunchies    
    
    
    @IrenaBoostani can't wait for lunch to get here! #sohungry @urbanplates    
    
    
    Congrats @IrenaBoostani! Just more evidence that you are #awesome! @comunicanonews    
    
    
    Great #tech article! RT: @irenaboostani New tech promises on-the-spot mobile engagement http://bit.ly/SoFZNn  … via @fastcasual    
    
    
    Just got my #nutcracker tickets. Can't wait to see it! @sfballet    
    
    
    This video really makes me miss #Hanoi! RT:  @lonelyplanet 5mil scooters & no traffic light in sight. Welcome to Hanoi http://bit.ly/RYzkfZ     
    
    
    SO BUMMED. But I still love my ducks. #Oregon #GoDucks    
    
    
    I'll be looking forward to these this week! 10 Things a PR Girl Can Expect on Thanksgiving http://bit.ly/rYWT8x  @nycPRgirls #thanksgiving    
    
    
    Good read for people in the #PR industry RT: @DaniERoss 5 Steps for Finding a Balance in PR Work and Life http://shar.es/6tZcd  #PRPros    
    
    
    Interesting market perspective for online #coupons -- LivingSocial: Things are going to get worse http://bit.ly/U5d5kM  via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    @ctlncmbr Not caffeinated enough! #sleepy #toomuchtodo    
    
    
    Voice commands in #mobileapps are awesome! Nominate OneTok for the Best Bootstrapped Startup 2012! #crunchies http://buff.ly/Rona1R     
    
    
    Is it Worth it to Build an #NFC App Right Now? Read an expert opinion from Stefan Rust of @exicon http://mashable.com/2012/12/12/build-nfc-app/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Such #heartwarming moments! Moments that Restored Our Faith in #Humanity in 2012 http://po.st/Dq5DUv  via @ebaumsworld    
    
    
    Another way to get into the #holiday spirit! Enjoy a holiday-themed keyboard on your #Android #smartphone http://zd.net/UfEoy6  @adaptxt    
    
    
    #GoDucks!! WTD!!    
    
    
    WOW! Allen Hall, you look AMAZING! #SOJC #UO @UOsojc http://bit.ly/10fSlR0     
    
    
    I've voted http://adaptxt.com  as "Best mobile app" in the TNW UK Startup Awards #UKSA http://tnw.to/ukawards     
    
    
    Very true! RT @Hoojobs 7 myths about working from home http://ow.ly/klDrM  #workplace #worklifebalance    
    
    
    Yikes!! 'World's oldest hamburger' bought in 1999 looks exactly the same today   http://soa.li/0Wsyu8U  #disgusting    
    
    
    THIS IS AMAZING!! RT @EW @'Arrested Development' sneak peek: Buster and Lucille get closer than ever - EXCLUSIVE CLIP http://bit.ly/14S3SZf     
    
    
    RI becomes 10th state to legalize gay marriage - hoping my home state CA will follow suit! http://nbcnews.to/165TTiB  #marriageequality    
    
    
    Watching the #DalaiLama speaking at my alma mater online! http://uoregon.edu/dalai-lama  #UO #GoDucks    
    
    
    Very sad and interesting story - Orphaned and homeless: Surviving the streets of North Korea http://bit.ly/17YN1BN     
    
    
    6 AP Style rules for press releases http://bit.ly/14O5PDu  #APTips #PressReleases    
    
    
    These were quite funny! RT 10 More Things PR Professionals ‘Love’ http://bit.ly/1gGvkha  @PRAssociation    
    
    
    This is so incredible and inspiring! SF Morphs Into Gotham City for Kid Battling Leukemia http://www.nbcbayarea.com/news/local/SF-Morphs-Into-Gotham-City-for-Batkid-Battling-Leukemia-232054521.html … #SFBatKid    
    
    
    is learning about hashtags in #J452    
    
    
    Hello, #J452 classmates! Feel free to add my blog to your aggregator. http://jonizuka.wordpress.com    
    
    
    Looking forward to doing social media projects for Ballet Fantastique!    
    
    
    Thank you for letting me use three Spanish Lit classes, J school! My last term at UO is going to be a lot easier now!    
    
    
        
    
    
    just went to the Ducks basketball game!    
    
    
    @iamlyddy Oh no! I get back to Cali on the 18th! Sad story.    
    
    
    @iamlyddy Yeah, I leave the 28th... but I'm moving back to Cali in March! Sad, this does happen like EVERY year!    
    
    
    Feeling under the weather, but going to get some homework done before work.    
    
    
    Oprah's interview with Sarah Palin is making me feel awkward...    
    
    
    @innabinna I felt kind of bad for her... lol! Inna, how are you?!    
    
    
    Can't wait to register for my last term at UO!    
    
    
    @innabinna I'm good! I'll be moving back to Cali in March! We should have a reunion dinner party!    
    
    
    @innabinna ...and spicy potatoes!! mmm...    
    
    
    The weather is freaking me out!    
    
    
    @TopherV Congratulations on getting into the Peace Corps! Dominican Republic sounds amazing!    
    
    
    Wow... I sure learned a lot about editing in #J452! My old assignments don't look very good anymore...    
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!    
    
    
    Parents just left to go back to California. Back to work...    
    
    
    Didn't get a ticket to the Civil War game.... and I'm very upset about it.    
    
    
    Practicing my #J452 speech on good employee management! Hopefully it will turn out ok!    
    
    
    Got into the game without a ticket! Yes! Rose Bowl!!    
    
    
    The Blind Side was such a good movie!!    
    
    
    @sfballet The Nutcracker was beautiful as always! This was my tenth consecutive year seeing it!    
    
    
    Back to school tomorrow. Last term as an undergrad!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I wish I could play the piano like Chris Martin. :)    
    
    
    Watching the Lion King with my roommate! New Disney movies are just not the same.    
    
    
    My computer dies at such inopportune times... This means I should get a MacBook!    
    
    
    @EugRec I love the programs you offer! You guys are awesome!    
    
    
    People are so creative. Watch this Face Off spoof with The Office clips. So funny! http://bit.ly/DRrbu    
    
    
    Today's Oprah is so inspiring! A girl had five types of cancer before she was 25!    
    
    
    Who let me start reading The Lovely Bones during midterms? Too hard to put down...    
    
    
    @kmatthews Thanks, Kelli! Drew has really taken off with SEO! It's pretty complicated.    
    
    
    Wow, Southwest. Way to be sensitive. http://bit.ly/aw5UGK    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just had the most frustrating experience with Target. Not happy.    
    
    
    Lunch today with @LeahROlson makes me want to go to Asia! Can't wait to go snowboarding with Eug. Outdoor Program on Sunday @EugRec    
    
    
    @johnsoriano21 Thanks, John! Did you see this apology from John Mayer? http://bit.ly/aQyZTu How effective do you think that is? Hmm....    
    
    
    Went snowboarding for the first time today @HoodooRec! It was sunny but the snow was like cement!!    
    
    
    I'm on a casserole craze... anyone know a good recipe??    
    
    
    Should hot dogs come with warning labels? This is crazy. Perhaps chewing lessons are in order. http://bit.ly/dsCqkA    
    
    
    Really tempted to buy a plane ticket to Thailand. Must...hold... off...    
    
    
    A somewhat happy ending for two victims of Argentina's Dirty War. http://bit.ly/a6GBwM    
    
    
    @jsoriano21 Good luck!! You're going to do great!! Say hi to Alex for me! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Yay for Kim Yu-na, Mao Asada and Joannie Rochette!!!    
    
    
    Mis pensamientos están con las personas que viven en Chile. My thoughts are with Hawaii as well.    
    
    
    @iamlyddy My sister-in-law always went to Lana's Nails on Fourth St. Her nails were always very pretty! They also do good pedicures!    
    
    
    #Chile Some impacting photojournalism from Chilean disaster. http://bit.ly/dAoLKP    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sochi 2014 Olympics look very promising!! Can't wait!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TopherV Have fun in la Republica Dominicana!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Erg! That pole came out of nowhere...    
    
    
    