"A Probabilistic Method for Inferring Preferences from Clicks" with Shimon Whiteson and Maarten de Rijke #cikm2011 http://bit.ly/ooA5fR     
    
    
    “@ggdupont: machine learning for IR session in #cikm2011 : first paper was great” -- Thanks! :-)    
    
    
    Just closed the #dir2011 demo submission. 7 demos were submitted.    
    
    
    This week's folia (UvA magazine) has a short piece about my research (under TECH-SHIRTS): http://issuu.com/foliacivitatis/docs/folia15_64/18    
    
    
        
    
    
    Nice! One full paper and one poster accepted at #cikm2012.    
    
    
    @tomas_matousek things are pretty good, although not as adventurous as for you, apparently - those pics are awesome! :-)    
    
    
    Am I really supposed to pay twice the registration fee to present two papers at #cikm2012?    
    
    
    @adambermingham @breyten thanks! let's see if I can actually afford to present both the full paper and the poster ... :)    
    
    
    @krisztianbalog you can use \raggedright (before \bibliography...)    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Nice! "Reusing Historical Interaction Data for Faster Online Learning to Rank for IR" \w @anneschuth, @shimon8282 & @mdr accepted #wsdm2013    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @mariahendrike why should the looks matter?    
    
    
    @dvdgrs @mariahendrike... Can only speak for myself, but I pick role models by what they say and do (and how they do it).    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Fidelity, Soundness, and Efficiency of Interleaved Comparison Methods" (Hofmann, Whiteson, de Rijke) accepted \w minor revs. in ACM TOIS :)    
    
    
    @firadl is making some last minute changes on our tutorial slides. Looking forward to the tutorial this afternoon #ECIR2013    
    
    
    Posted slides and additional material for our #ECIR2013 tutorial on Practical Online Retrieval Evaluation http://wp.me/p2tKD7-15  (w @firadl)    
    
    
    Mark Najork about social search: 10% of bing searches are for people #ecir2013    
    
    
    @leifos I think i will be crucial in the future - when all our data is online. We'll search the web, personal photos, docs from one point.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Paul Ogilvie explains biases that make evaluation on LinkedIn hard: repetition, time of day, referrer... #ecir2013    
    
    
    Antonio Gulli about Bing: 110m unique users in the US #ecir2013    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Karen Church: mobile search is unique - personal, context, fresh... #ecir2013    
    
    
    Karen: more than 50% of mobile Google searches have local intent #ecir2013    
    
    
    Great talk by Bottou: Large Scale Machine Learning in the Real World (Part 2) Causation and Exploration @TechTalksTV http://techtalks.tv/talks/large-scale-machine-learning-in-the-real-world-part-2-causation-and-exploration/58032/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Agreed, very cool! @djoerd: Daan Odijk from @commit_nl gives impressive semantic linking demo for @dwdd at #dir13. @dodijk    
    
    
    My first computer blew up because I forgot to unplug the power before taking it apart
#KieraWilmot    
    
    
        
    
    
    @edgarmeij @dvdgrs @dodijk @TomKenter congrats! :-)    
    
    
    @dvdgrs  it was a great day indeed!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Interesting keynote by Dan Roth at #benelearn2013 - "CCMs can combine  declarative knowledge with data driven statistical models"    
    
    
    CCM overview paper: "Structured Learning with Constrained Conditional Models" by Chang, Ratinov, and Roth http://cogcomp.cs.illinois.edu/page/publication_view/698 …    
    
    
    Great initiative: share your machine learning experiments on openML http://openml.org/  #benelearn2013    
    
    
    #benelearn2013 Laurens van der Maaten: why corruption is good (in machine learning) http://homepage.tudelft.nl/19j49/Publications_files/mcf.pdf …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Julio Gonzalo: temperature = what's measured with a thermometer. What's the thermometer for retrieval?    
    
    
        
    
    
    #sigir2013 follow-up - these were the hot topics this year: http://www.wordle.net/show/wrdl/6916796/SigIR_2013 … (word cloud of the full paper titles) @SIGIR2013    
    
    
    @n0mad_0 Thanks for pointing this out! I corrected the link, enjoy the slides :)    
    
    
    Very much enjoyed reading David Bodoff's reaction to "the Fuhr Challenge": http://dl.acm.org/citation.cfm?doid=2492189.2492191 … - now, how do we conceptualize IR?    
    
    
    @arjenpdevries one inappropriately short summary could be: don't stop at *what* works, focus on *why* it works and *when*.    
    
    
    ECIR 2014 Demos can now be submitted through
http://www.conftool.pro/ecir2014/ . Looking forward to your cool demo!    
    
    
    10 days left to submit your #ECIR2014 demo! http://ecir2014.org/for-authors/     
    
    
    #ECIR2014 demo submission is now closed. We received 25 submissions. Thank you to all demo authors / coders!    
    
    
    Watching Marc Bron defend his PhD thesis. #congrats pic.twitter.com/KbC7xOSaTA    
    
    
    Just sent out the #ECIR2014 demo notifications. Congratulations to accepted authors!    
    
    
    Announcing the @ECIR2014 Best Demo Audience Award. For the first time, ECIR attendees will get to vote for their favourite demo. #ECIR2014    
    
    
        
    
    
    @iFromm @ECIR2014 :-) I'm sure we'll have a great audience! The prize, however, will be for the best demo.    
    
    
    @anneschuth congrats! I'd like a camera ready copy as well.    
    
    
    @anneschuth goed dat jullie dit onder de aandacht brengen!    
    
    
    The paper I'll be presenting at #ecir2011 is now online: http://bit.ly/fHqCxT. Presentation in session 7 on Wed. April 20, 10:30.    
    
    
    It's official: I'm one of the 2011 #google anita borg memorial scholars http://bit.ly/mS6ONj    
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy that our paper "A Probabilistic Method for Inferring Preferences from Clicks" was accepted at #cikm2011 http://ilps.science.uva.nl/biblio/probabilistic-method-inferring-preferences-clicks …    
    
    
        
    
    
    