Mini Sal-Tun Burgers! http://fb.me/Al2DZjZF    
    
    
    Sexy Chef Diet: Week 1
Day 1: 
Breakfast: Wheat Toast with your choice of the following: spray butter, margarine,... http://fb.me/13HxrRfJs    
    
    
    Hey guys, I'm getting ready to travel to Bulgaria... so I will have TONS of great dishes to share... I'll be... http://fb.me/1cGsMAfZ6    
    
    
    Hungry yet? Try this awesome sweet and savory Pistachio Encrusted Honey-Mustard Salmon! http://fb.me/12JayM5aX    
    
    
    Thinking about lunch already? Then try my Sesame & Sprouts Lunch Bagel! http://fb.me/1dQEd6mAB    
    
    
    It's almost dinner... what are you going to make? Try this Hearty Fish Stew! http://fb.me/xE7RX4F9     
    
    
    The countdown for Bulgaria begins... for those of you who don't know, Bulgarian cuisine is similar to Greek... very delicious.    
    
    
    Check out the mundo latino August issue, featuring Mexican Chicken! http://fb.me/17c2Ogu3q     
    
    
    Sometimes, Pizza is the answer.    
    
    
    Headed to Bulgaria... YAH... I'll post when I get there. :-)    
    
    
    YUM... we just had some of our FAMOUS Manicotti's.... THEY WERE SOOOOOOOO GOOD! http://fb.me/BPCLGjVa    
    
    
    Thinking about making pumpkin bread...    
    
    
    LOL... even thought it's 12am, I GOT INSPIRED TO MAKE THE PUMPKIN BREAD! It smells DELISH!    
    
    
    WOW... so much to share already.... I just have to get the camera set up and you will have a a feast for the eyes :-)    
    
    
    I made everyone a delicious vegetable stew with fresh vegetables from the garden, eggplant, potatoes, tomatoes,... http://fb.me/K7dtOCGA     
    
    
    This was at the countryside house... http://fb.me/16GYUgAkz     
    
    
    SEXY PUMPKIN BREAD RECIPE , see it HERE http://fb.me/MVIioeRA    
    
    
    A Bulgarian staple... french fries with Feta Cheese and Lutenitza... (Lutenitza is a combination of tomatoes and... http://fb.me/x2Sin6ua     
    
    
    www.sexychef.net    
    
    
    Yum, that pumpkin bread was DELISH!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/An--Xb0lsIk?a  Rustic Bulgarian Lutenitza - The Sexy Chef Liz    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/TBXZW     
    
    
    As promised, my favorite Bulgarian food, LUTENITZA! Watch as I make it all homemade from the garden! http://fb.me/128zVgh3q     
    
    
    http://fb.me/wSk5lErL    
    
    
    The Bulgarian version of "Fiji" http://fb.me/1hTuFlTa9     
    
    
    Bulgarian Style Stuffed peppers, filled with rice, carrots, onions, garlic and LOVE! Really delish... this also... http://fb.me/1dJ6pwuUw     
    
    
    Welcome to Bulgaria, where grilled meats are EVERYTHING... this is my inlaws specialty! http://fb.me/QhMbx4P7     
    
    
    Getting ready for a great weekend of travel... gonna be making some delicious dishes!    
    
    
    Pizza for breakfast? Oh yes. There is a little shop down the street that makes the best breads, pizzas and... http://fb.me/U1b9l9f0     
    
    
    My favorite Bulgarian Beer... very refreshing !!! http://fb.me/VK6nqEkY     
    
    
    Delishious... baked eggplant, topped with feta cheese and some parsley...however you could use fresh basil as well http://fb.me/16cXh18Ho     
    
    
    My favorite salad, cabbage salad with oil, vinegar and salt. Simply delishious. http://fb.me/YRdUoKzN     
    
    
    Fish soup... totally delish, goes great with cabbage salad... dip in some bread, an amazing lunch! http://fb.me/1dBhLfWJJ     
    
    
    Beautiful and tasty.... makes great wine. Fresh grapes from the vine! http://fb.me/YMwIZ59z     
    
    
    anyone seen this fruit before? http://fb.me/Z1BwhRyt     
    
    
    Chocolate Mousse anyone? Delish! http://fb.me/UiTK4kwN     
    
    
    back in the USA and back to my sexy chef meals... any requests?    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/J54Ft7p-emc?a  Sak Noel - Loca People (Official Video) Clean Version    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/SSlCQ     
    
    
    Went to the cheesecake factory last night, they now have a great "skinnylicious" menu with TONS of choices,... http://fb.me/10FoZ3CPE     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/PtwFpJDWkvo?a  Lady Gaga- You and I Lyrics on Screen HD [HQ Audio]    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/Tvmr1     
    
    
    you guys will LOVE what I'm making tonight... stay tuned    
    
    
    Hungry for lunch... or preparing for dinner, check out this delish Thai-Peanut Noodle Saute! http://fb.me/SHlnrPGi     
    
    
    Weekend cooking plans? Anything exciting?    
    
    
    Need a mid-day pick-me-up? So did I... I just made this AWESOME strawberry-blackberry smoothie... just blend 1/2... http://fb.me/T3NZ60rO     
    
    
    Check it out, me, The Sexy Chef  and Becky Rodriguez got into Baltimore Magazine! http://fb.me/14Y72ouYz     
    
    
    If you LOVE eating... share this on your page! http://fb.me/LxD1lsYh     
    
    
    Gotta love Sun Chips, great for a quick healthy snack.... they serve for a neat pick me up!    
    
    
    Stay tuned, recipes will be posted... great weekend back from Cinncinatti. FUN!    
    
    
    Yummy Potato Croquettes! http://fb.me/Le8F8D7Y    
    
    
    Delicious Mango Grapefruit cocktails! http://fb.me/AG7Gj7yK    
    
    
    Hey Guys! Sorry for being MIA the past week... I was busy planning a SURPRISE party for the hubby. I'M BACK NOW...... http://fb.me/tfHlAq3n     
    
    
    Check it out, Nick being surprised. hehe. http://fb.me/MbCo7km1     
    
    
    Wow, this appetizer was the best ever! Try this Jalapeno Shrimp & Tomato dish, it will blow your mind! http://fb.me/IRW1Oied     
    
    
    Another week, back in the grind... however I just made some DELICIOUS and hearty sandwiches...    
    
    
    Rainbow Trout! Broiled to perfection! http://fb.me/MSnAR8g6    
    
    
    Garden Fresh - Black Bean Tacos... you MUST try these, totally fresh and delicious! http://fb.me/1bHHLRRHe     
    
    
    There is nothing more relaxing than a glass of wine and a fabulous dinner!    
    
    
    Most likely going to make homemade gnocchi's today. :-)    
    
    
    Just applied. Can't wait to meet up at the casting in Nov! @MasterChefUSA    
    
    
    Hot Dog and Egg Breakfast Sandwich! DELISH! http://fb.me/znMKUPId    
    
    
    Great morning, coffee and pumpkin bread!    
    
    
    I am always STARVING at 3pm.... I know i'm not the only one.. coffee usually does the trick haha    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/Z5frmQrR     
    
    
    What can I help you make tonight? http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    Just made mac n cheese while decorating the house! How fun!    
    
    
    Did you have lunch yet? If not... stop and drop everything... you've GOT to make this. Today is the PERFECT day... http://fb.me/KpSx29gA     
    
    
    Headin to Florida in the am. Hope to be inspired to share some ideas while I'm there!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/UdC_8IF5zmw?a  Simply Red - Stars lyrics    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/RYf5P     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/UdC_8IF5zmw?a  Simply Red - Stars lyrics    
    
    
    I favorited a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/RYf5P     
    
    
    Pork Chops with White Beans, Tomato and Rice http://fb.me/KBpxOIHZ    
    
    
    Well, everyone loved the mac n cheese. It was gourmet... ish hehe    
    
    
    Check out this delicious double decker burger we had in Miami! Totally delish! http://fb.me/1eBp040Rv     
    
    
    Amazing post workout lunch. Whole Wheat Linguine with Fresh Spinach and Sausage. WOW!!! http://fb.me/sVPMAZWh     
    
    
    The perfect dessert to serve dinner guests or your family! You can even make them just for yourself... who cares.... http://fb.me/KfzTKkBc     
    
    
    Want an arm workout? Then make my mac & cheese... the grating will kick your ass!... http://fb.me/GTcMBLrv    
    
    
    Baltimore Fans... come to Powerplant THIS FRIDAY to watch me in a fashion show! 10pm    
    
    
    Cooking, as we speak, a vegetable lasagna that I'm presenting tomorrow for the judges of master chef!    
    
    
    Here it is... my Sexy & Spicy Mac & Cheese http://fb.me/LzKEAzsl    
    
    
    Do you like the sexy chef apron? http://fb.me/AqJHuE7F     
    
    
    What are you Thanksgiving plans?    
    
    
    Que Dramatico! http://fb.me/Ebv6toqH     
    
    
    Excited to soon be sharing some holiday recipes, pics and videos!    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving Everyone! Love you all!    
    
    
    What interesting creations do you make with your leftovers (if anything)?    
    
    
    @howie_d miss you!    
    
    
    We made roasted vegetables, carrots, onions, squash, brussel sprouts drizzles with olive oil and balsamic. It was... http://fb.me/yhLQJml9     
    
    
    Have you ever made Shepherd's Pie? I just did... two different versions... You've GOT to check it out. Totally... http://fb.me/Fu0HJz2u     
    
    
    United Flavors Salad... unlike ANY salad you've ever had before... http://fb.me/PhfdBBAq    
    
    
    THE BOOK IS COMPLETE!!! Coming soon... "SEXY CHEF - COOKING WITH CONFIDENCE"    
    
    
    working with Articokes tonight!    
    
    
    Have you made artichokes lately? They are not as difficult as you may have heard and they are quite delishious.... http://fb.me/XZwfMBqA     
    
    
    Do you love Panko? Me too... Try my Panko Encrusted Salmon :-) Less than 10 minutes to make! http://fb.me/1kbkQr226     
    
    
    Happy Saturday! Taste my Ham, Green Pepper and Tomato Omelet! http://fb.me/1iWjgEYM2     
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/o0n8lmfj     
    
    
    Sometimes, there is nothing better than take-out Chinese    
    
    
    http://fb.me/NTCFMzl1    
    
    
    I'm going to be making an indian dish today, Butter Chicken. Will post after :-)    
    
    
    Wow, check out this awesome Butter Chicken Dish... I also through in there a Shrimp dish that is only slightly... http://fb.me/1u41KVyjr     
    
    
    Wow, check out this awesome Butter Chicken Dish. If you've never made Indian food before, this is a great dish to... http://fb.me/IYxT9WW0     
    
    
    I think I've created the most awesome crab cake. Will post soon!    
    
    
    For those of you gnocchi lovers out there, this one is a new creation and a new favorite. Gnocchi with Fresh... http://fb.me/Pkz2MlBY     
    
    
    making fish tacos tonight!    
    
    
    @ThatGuyHugs Thanks Jason! Can't wait to see the photos!    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! I love you all! http://fb.me/1wXlVAhBr     
    
    
    THE BEST CATFISH TACOS EVER! http://fb.me/vy37cyyu    
    
    
    Just made the BEST fish tacos EVER    
    
    
    Yum, pizza! http://yfrog.com/nzjenovoj     
    
    
    YUM! I love this Pizza... it's called Marachiatto - it's feta, tomato, basil and red onion. Try it wish a side of... http://fb.me/ELFgaLbk     
    
    
    Making Homemade pasta and ravioli tonight. :-D    
    
    
    Love this pic, funny right? http://fb.me/HXIso5a8     
    
    
    Our pasta turned out FANTASTIC. Better than EVER. We made spaghetti, ravioli and fettucini. :-D http://fb.me/1j8L2OsW8     
    
    
    I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "" http://fb.me/1hStnhToZ     
    
    
    Stay tuned, SHOOTING ANOTHER VIDEO AS WE SPEAK!    
    
    
    How was everyone's holiday? :-D    
    
    
    Watch my newest video, where my mom and I make homemade pasta! http://fb.me/11Ra6kEMN     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/RF86rQKFaK4?a  The Sexy Chef Liz makes Homemade Pasta for Christmas    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/RF86rQKFaK4?a  The Sexy Chef Liz makes Homemade Pasta for Christmas    
    
    
    AVAILABLE NOW!!!  FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER! GET MY COOK BOOK NOW!!! http://fb.me/N8l7SbE7    
    
    
    AVAILABLE FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER! YOU CAN NOW PURCHASE A COPY OF MY COOK BOOK!... http://fb.me/NI2sHOtI    
    
    
    FINALLY, YOU CAN PURCHASE A COPY OF MY COOKBOOK!!!! Just in time for XMAS! Ships in 3-5 days!    
    
    
    JUST RELEASED MY NEW COOKBOOK "Sexy Chef - Cooking with Confidence" GET YOUR COPY NOW !  http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    GET FREE 2 DAY SHIPPING, JUST ENTER COUPON CODE - DEC15    
    
    
    http://fb.me/Bb5d4ZNu    
    
    
    What is everyone doing for New Years Eve?    
    
    
    Last Nights Taco Feast! http://fb.me/1pE5cKhIL     
    
    
    Happy New Year Everyone! I'm making ravioli again today :-) http://fb.me/1toCPqKo5     
    
    
    I posted 2 photos on Facebook in the album "Sexy Chef Makes Ravioli" http://fb.me/1fBH3Lmxc     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/cDUxke75LPI?a  Sexy Chef Tip - What to do with extra dough    
    
    
    Watch what I use the extra dough for when making pasta. :-D http://fb.me/EVdAEDam     
    
    
    Get "SEXY CHEF -Cooking with Confidence" today!    
    
    
    Paperback - 26.44 http://fb.me/Q0BVEAN5    
    
    
    Download immediatly for only 12.99 http://fb.me/CQZ6SwG5    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/cDUxke75LPI?a  Sexy Chef Tip - What to do with extra dough    
    
    
    I made eggrolls last night with phyllo dough... has anyone else tried this? It worked but I will just use regular wrappers next time.    
    
    
    The best lunch EVER! http://fb.me/QFdsn0Ry    
    
    
    Feeling cold or under the weather? Then this soup is FOR YOU! http://fb.me/LKj6gXYm    
    
    
    4 things you LOVE about Cooking! http://fb.me/Hzscbhv9    
    
    
    Happy Weekend!!!!!    
    
    
    My favorite way to eat a sandwhich, is on an "everything" bagel. :-D http://fb.me/1DPgHUiff     
    
    
    Christmas party... so much great food to make... cant wait.... check out the recipes here:... http://fb.me/NFSFsEtm    
    
    
    I'm ready for lunch... now what to eat??    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow! @ABC11_WTVD    
    
    
    Had Lebanese food last night... loved the Spicy Hummus!    
    
    
    It's Official, Brooklyn NY has the best pizza!    
    
    
    Do you love eggplant? Well these eggplant roll ups are just what you need for a delishious and luxurious meal. http://fb.me/1s0hx81aH     
    
    
    I'm thinking shrimp spring rolls tonight!    
    
    
    Ken Morrill is the BEST photographer ever! http://fb.me/1k1J7211l     
    
    
    Leftovers can always be turned into a meal of greatness :-D    
    
    
    About to enjoy a cerveza... then cook something FABULOUS!    
    
    
    http://yfrog.com/es6hrxrj     
    
    
    Check out this Fried Eggplant....I dipped them in seasoned panko and then pan fried. SO good and crispy! http://fb.me/1IY7yjpPo     
    
    
    Grilled steak with butter! http://yfrog.com/odq66mmj     
    
    
    I made grilled steak with butter last night... medium... nice and juicy. http://fb.me/FeFEXU9E     
    
    
    I'm obsessed with Black Beans... I make them so good!    
    
    
    The wine is screaming my name!    
    
    
    @ManhattanPT Thanks for the follow :-D    
    
    
    Anyone else enjoy homemade waffles this morning?    
    
    
    Where is your favorite New York restaurant?    
    
    
    @DavidTutera David, great meeting you... when will the professional photos be posted?    
    
    
    About to tackle some homemade linguini!    
    
    
    How delicious does this look? I made this homemade Linguini with vegetables, salmon and my cream sauce. It was... http://fb.me/1tDKssVTv     
    
    
    As requested, here is the recipe for this tasty Dish from yesterday! Fettuccine, Salmon and Vegetable Alfredo! http://fb.me/1mx0J2L4O     
    
    
    Scoping out my next creation... http://fb.me/1G1fDosGl     
    
    
    @BravoAndy omg, poor michael and poor rug!!! Literally lmfao though, just sayin...    
    
    
    @mshowalter obsessed. You really made that F-ing cheese super sexy... I was hoping she'd feed you a mustard and pencil sandwich though...    
    
    
    So tomorrow is Valentine's Day... what are your plans? Cooking anything special or headed out to dinner?    
    
    
    ha, this is hilarious. This is from the Crab Bash, this was also in the newspaper. FUN STUFF and funny apparently. http://fb.me/1GoQ5aaEa     
    
    
    we made the BEST reindeer cupcakes this weekend!!!! http://fb.me/Kx76a6Oz    
    
    
    check out the FINISHED product! http://fb.me/GAoxyQdQ    
    
    
    Happy Valentine's Day guys and dolls! Enjoy and have fun! Couples, you know what to do... singles, spend it with... http://fb.me/1A1EypPQS     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Cbwy-kbb0eg?a  Sexy Chef Liz Valentine's Day    
    
    
    Watch what I'm doing tonight for Valentine's Day. Hope you're going to have as much fun as me! http://fb.me/1oEe7jGQv     
    
    
    Watch what I'm doing for Valentine's Day. Hope you're going to have as much fun as me! http://fb.me/1GXS9p0aR     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Cbwy-kbb0eg?a  Sexy Chef Liz Valentine's Day    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/_ovdm2yX4MA?a  Avicii - Levels    
    
    
    I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "Sexy Chef Valentine's Day" http://fb.me/193x8U9ih     
    
    
    How about my Linguini Carbonara for an easy Friday Night dinner! Easy, authentic and delicious! http://fb.me/MZakgfqC     
    
    
    Tonight I'm working on some Beef Wellington as well as a variety of other goodies. :-D    
    
    
    Your Top 3 Favorite Holiday Dishes http://fb.me/LZ5PZC3X    
    
    
    Try this easy Tofu Terriaki today! http://fb.me/1jdl9eMDI     
    
    
    Yah! http://fb.me/1gsZbTABy     
    
    
    I made the BEST eggplant lasagna and creamy risotto tonight... will post later :-D    
    
    
    Here is the recipe for my AMAZING Eggplant Lasagna! It's SOOOO TASTY and really fun to make! Try it tonight! http://fb.me/16LMQP2os     
    
    
    Ha, this was me over the weekend... cooking up a storm! http://fb.me/1oldRnUI9     
    
    
    I made Yuca for the first time EVER last night, it was AWESOME... I love Yuca    
    
    
    Doing a lot of cooking with my mom this weekend... :-) We made Pasta Balls last night... will post later. They were amazing.    
    
    
    Check out my LATEST video... for Bravo! Check it out! http://fb.me/Eiiutumm    
    
    
    CHECK OUT MY BRAVO VIDEO    
    
    
    Don't these look great!? I'll post the recipe later, but just had to share this pic of my delicious Pasta Balls!... http://fb.me/1y2QlidaA     
    
    
    Care for a grape? http://fb.me/1PPeGvZyJ     
    
    
    In the process of baking the MOST DELICIOUS carrot cake... my house smells SO GOOD!    
    
    
    Craving brunch? This is delicious - Fried egg with succulent veggies. This brunch won't let you down. http://fb.me/10WYlfGU1     
    
    
    ha, you can almost make up your own caption for this photo :-D http://fb.me/1ctfaqShf     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/2v8YragSIuI?a  Exposé - Point Of No Return    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/COiIC3A0ROM?a  Al Green-Lets Stay Together    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/hq2KgzKETBw?a  Bryan Adams - Have You Ever Really Loved A Woman?    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/hq2KgzKETBw?a  Bryan Adams - Have You Ever Really Loved A Woman?    
    
    
    As promised, the recipe for the delicious Pasta Balls! They'll make any rainy day FUN!... http://fb.me/1ESWZhvus     
    
    
    Uhh... not sure now sexy this is, but I just cooked duck and now EVERYTHING smells like it... haha    
    
    
    Who loves Whole Foods?    
    
    
    MMM, just made the BEST dinner ever....    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Px2L-obBveo?a  Wild Boar - Gordon Ramsay - F-Word    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/mcdrWXgqGOE?a  Beyonce - Single Ladies (Put A Ring On It) (Official Music    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video from @YouTubeFood http://youtu.be/lmd3KZ4subg?a  Ramsay Rips Apart Chef's Signature Dish - Ra    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/skfx5RKz0oQ?a  Gordon Ramsey - f word - Caviar    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/CBwpTHBaGoU?a  The Sexy Chef Liz explains how to succeed in the culinary wo    
    
    
    Watch my latest video, How To Succeed in the Culinary World

http://www.youtube.com/user/SexyChefLiz?feature=mhee …    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/CBwpTHBaGoU?a  The Sexy Chef Liz explains how to succeed in the culinary world    
    
    
    Fennel keeps showing up in my life so I'm doing a delicious fennel salad tonight, I'll post later :-D    
    
    
    YUM... try my Grilled Tuna with Sweet Potato Mash & Tangy Fennel Salad. It's the perfect start to warm nights!... http://fb.me/1okiFQRlS     
    
    
    @GordonRamsay01 at least I got a smile ;-D    
    
    
    I'm ROOTING FOR YOU! @kaimanachee    
    
    
    Now when you Google "Sexy Chef" I'm FINALLY the first page to come up!!! YES!    
    
    
    Delicious Crab Stir-Fry http://fb.me/JP06CX8l    
    
    
    What's the Sexiest Dish you've ever made?    
    
    
    Check out my Lemon Shrimp with Yucca Mash! It's been a "mash" kind of week so far!... http://fb.me/1TLx9TjA9     
    
    
    Try my Lemon Shrimp! Great for Spring! 

http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2012/03/lemon-shrimp-with-yucca-mash.html … http://fb.me/1HQB2Vw8y     
    
    
    Did you know that TODAY is National Ravioli Day??? Now you do. EAT UP!! http://fb.me/1AtsoX9Nb     
    
    
    Bok Choy and Scallops tonight. I can't wait :-D    
    
    
    Scallop & Bok Choy Noodle Bowl - Delicious and fun to make!... http://fb.me/wZ2plhou     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/CynBSkluTHA?a  The Sexy Chef explains the perfect Fajitas    
    
    
    Okay, who loves Fajitas? Watch my latest Video Clip, Sexy Chef - The PERFECT Fajitas!!!... http://fb.me/1vk6p5a47     
    
    
    So, I'll be making the entire xmas dinner tonight. Exciting. 7 Fishes... whoo hoo... posting to follow :-)    
    
    
    @cocosworld  Coco! I want to help you cook delicious meals that even ICE will love! He'll never know you're eating healthy!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to ME! http://fb.me/1ShJGvpLM     
    
    
    Chocolate martini! http://yfrog.com/h3rblbrhj     
    
    
    Delicious Chocolate Martini last night. :-D http://fb.me/1mHu5mlKx     
    
    
    In the mood to make a delicious sauce:-)
In the m    
    
    
    I don't think I shared this yet... Homemade baked Manicotti. YUM! So much better than boxed manicotti. I will... http://fb.me/1u1TlbiYJ     
    
    
    Someone told me yesterday that I looked "too skinny" to be a chef. They said, "what's the secret?" My reply... "I WORK OUT!"    
    
    
    As promised, here is the recipe for my homemade baked manicotti!... http://fb.me/yKKVbxfn     
    
    
    If you mix Peppermint Schnaps and (fat free) French Vanilla creamer into a shot, it tastes EXACTLY like Wrigley's Gum!    
    
    
    @PanettaSexyTime I expect a follow back ;-)    
    
    
    @mshowalter wow. I really like your profile pic    
    
    
    @PanettaSexyTime Mya :-D    
    
    
    @PanettaSexyTime ha, I can only imagine    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz what's on the menu tonight? :)    
    
    
    Try this fresh side-dish salad, Garbanzo Bean, Tomato and Feta salad with a hint of Lemon!... http://fb.me/1Mr5l1T0P     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/L4C3MYSSBlg?a  Sexy Chef Liz Reports Breaking News, Gordon Ramsay Secret Tw    
    
    
    THIS JUST IN! Breaking News! Must watch NOW! 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=L4C3MYSSBlg … http://fb.me/1EAHff0nH     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/L4C3MYSSBlg?a  Sexy Chef Liz Reports Breaking News, Gordon Ramsay Secret Twin    
    
    
    Beefeater Gin - from London! I LOVE it!    
    
    
    Good Friday! http://fb.me/1XSYvw5Mi     
    
    
    Tuna rolls are the best! :-)    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/183169909814583812/ … Tuna, Sweet Potato Mash-Tangy Fennel Salad. The fennel salad creates a great texture that is a great contrast.    
    
    
    Grilled & Marinated T-BONE STEAK! 
http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/07/marinated-grilled-t-bone-steak.html http://fb.me/wm89uRXv    
    
    
    Marinated & Grilled SALMON!  http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/07/marinated-grilled-salmon.html http://fb.me/F09yakp1    
    
    
    NEW "baked beans" http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/07/new-baked-beans-kidney-beans-green.html http://fb.me/FdbeaRag    
    
    
    Check out these great new Grilling ideas! http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/ http://fb.me/BUs4Bnhh    
    
    
    another sunday funday    
    
    
    Happy Easter! Happy Cooking! http://fb.me/UAhJZ7rf     
    
    
    Happy Easter, Happy Cooking! http://fb.me/1KLylKhUP     
    
    
    Another week started....    
    
    
    I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "Liz's Delicious Dishes" http://fb.me/DxUHTnG8    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/NWZUuomV_Xg?a  The Sexy Chef Liz makes SPICY mango, radish salsa    
    
    
    Watch as I make a delicious Mango, Radish and Spicy Pepper Salsa, goes great with Fish!... http://fb.me/1NVYHQzo1     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/lCc8IEvh70w?a  Gordon Ramsay gets angry over a steak    
    
    
    CHECK IT OUT http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/07/summer-spinach-pepper-pasta.html http://fb.me/F9OIYtt1    
    
    
    Read about this Spicy Mango, Radish and Pepper salsa!... http://fb.me/x4RNr5EC     
    
    
    My fingers are still burning from those damn peppers! haha    
    
    
    Start your HUMP DAY off RIGHT! http://fb.me/1T30Agl72     
    
    
    Ready to make another delicious and SEXY meal tonight :)    
    
    
    hmmm... about to get a snowstorm... oh what fun! I love making yummy things to eat when it snows    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GF5jGn__K58?a  ramsay twins create wine    
    
    
    For those of you who love BBC, check out my latest interview with the Ramsay Twins!... http://fb.me/WrbqKibH     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GF5jGn__K58?a  Ramsay Twins Create Wine - Exclusive BBC Interview    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/oI_vYvHTzyA?a  BBC News intro compil.    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/LXrlDgVplIA?a  Gordon Ramsay Live on BBC News with Sexy Chef Liz    
    
    
    The Much Anticipated Part II of the Exclusive INTERVIEW. Watch now! 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LXrlDgVplIA … http://fb.me/1a0NxMNaP     
    
    
    Just got home fromthe most amazing photoshoot with the very talented Ken Morrill. Now, poppin open some wine and... http://fb.me/1U76FWz9t     
    
    
    Grilling again, we'll see what comes out of that    
    
    
    lol, YES. I'm in! GET ON IT!!!
 (@YouTube http://youtu.be/GF5jGn__K58?a )    
    
    
    Eat your VEGGIES!!! :-D http://fb.me/xXHArJjQ     
    
    
    After a long day (not over yet) I'm enjoying a delicous cocktail:  Kaluha, Coffee, Creamer and Whiskey. Delish!    
    
    
    Has anyone else tried Mano wine? This is a Cab blend which is smooth to the palate yet quite full-bodied. http://fb.me/1Z2EDLQDj     
    
    
    GREAT NEW PASTA DISH! http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/07/jumbo-macaroni-w-green-peppers-peas.html http://fb.me/F5KZ8zbP    
    
    
    Great dinner... intended to hit the gym... but it's late now... maybe early in the AM?    
    
    
    Totally amazing, if you love seafood but are alergic to shell-fish, these "Spicy Krab Kakes" are going to be your... http://fb.me/1tnMIOMJM     
    
    
    Saturday's like this deserve a fresh, tangy cocktail!    
    
    
    Happy Sunday. This the perfect soup for ANY day... Italian Bean Soup- Pasta Fagioli!... http://fb.me/AFiM8Ht3     
    
    
    How many devices does it take to blow up a baby pool? Oh wait, nothing is better than a good ole' mouth!    
    
    
    Check this out: Mini Scallops with Spinach Spaghetti & Spicy Pepper Sauce. :-D... http://fb.me/1NJTyQ5zx     
    
    
    I found the coolest "sweet potatoes" ever... they are purple inside. I'll post them later :-D    
    
    
    Awww, aww  philly philly, aww awww phily where I am from!    
    
    
    I had the MOST AMAZING gnocchi last night at The Brewer's Art from Chef David. Literally outstanding!    
    
    
    @Becky_Wine I love you! I'm so excited that you are NOW on Twitter! Peeps, FOLLOW THIS GIRL!!!    
    
    
    @Becky_Wine bienvenido    
    
    
    Headed to NYC in 30 minutes. Where is your favorite NYC eatery?    
    
    
    NYC was great. Had a chance to try out Iron Chef Morimotos restaurant - Morimoto. The sushi was to die for :-D http://fb.me/zb0Ec6kn     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/t1cX6ru3lKI?a  Summer of Gordon Promo    
    
    
    Check out this fabulous calamari from Del Friscos NYC! http://yfrog.com/oecunaqdj     
    
    
    YUM... If you haven't been to Del Friscos in NYC, you should try it. The calamari was to die for! http://fb.me/1u5UmhtPq     
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz will you be in NY on Monday?! Come where I work! I blow your mind away!    
    
    
    @kaimanachee  welcome to Twitter! :-D    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz I almost thought you were too cool to talk with your Italian friend!! Next time!!!!    
    
    
    FIRST LOOK: @sexychefliz new beta website, in testing phase- hope to launch at the end of the month
http://bit.ly/IvsJ8e   | #web #branding    
    
    
    Pan Fried Cod, Orange Flavored Asparagus and Red Potatoes. Easy fun meal. :-D... http://fb.me/1oa2GN8mQ     
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/183169909814732138/ … Delicious pan-fried Cod with Red Potatoes and Asparagus with Orange    
    
    
    Check out my salad garden... in the city! This is how you make the most of having no yard. :-D http://fb.me/1znCEDBrs     
    
    
    @chipotleeffect Thanks for the follow... :-D    
    
    
    Are you getting ready for CINCO DE MAYO?    
    
    
    @elnino1217 now I need a follow back. :-D    
    
    
    This will be me later... Happy Cinco De Mayo! http://fb.me/24lKUuRKr     
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz , here we go :) .... Where my shot of patron , I see how u r !!!!    
    
    
    I told you there would be a FIESTA! :-D http://fb.me/1mnubkiGL     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/iwV8LXdLbSQ?a  Sexy Chef - Rockette Alumnae Performance NYC The Out Hotel    
    
    
    Enjoying some wine, working on recipies!    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz cooking is great. I love it!!! X    
    
    
    Check it out, Sexy Chef dances in NYC and watch the live performace of Under The Sea!... http://fb.me/Cf7Z1XjB     
    
    
    THE BOOK IS BACK! Get your copy TODAY! http://fb.me/C1utnlLG    
    
    
    For those of you who tried to buy the book without success, HERE YOU GO, THE BOOK IS BACK AND EASY TO BUY!!!! check it out below    
    
    
    http://fb.me/EwYyf4AV    
    
    
    Red Rocket is the BEST!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Happy Mothers Day! I'm making a Mothers Day FEAST for my mom today :-D    
    
    
    Wouldn't you love to wear these cute and super sexy aprons while you cook? Stay tuned, posting some new and... http://fb.me/122XH7huv     
    
    
    BREAKING NEWS!!! The announcement I've been dying to share with everyone!

You can watch me COMPETE on... http://fb.me/1kWo1JEjW     
    
    
    Also, Check out my NEW SEXY CHEF WEBSITE http://www.sexychef.net/  created by Jeffrey Powers .

ALSO, For your... http://fb.me/yqQcnZHW     
    
    
    @BravoAndy Andy, I'm going to be on MasterChef with Gordon Ramsay on Fox June4-5. Would love to chat about it. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GF5jGn__K58&list=UUZG9Uej-Mm6GPdTMaOH0Pdw&index=3&feature=plcp …    
    
    
    @BullfrogAndBaum:  @grahamelliot: #MasterChef season 3 pics! @GordonRamsay01 @Jbastianich @MASTERCHEFonFOX #MC3 pic.twitter.com/98lwuWqL ~nice!    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/7i_m9bVju9A?a  sexy chef Liz on Masterchef with Gordon Ramsay Preview    
    
    
    Watch it here first! The Sexy Chef Liz get's on MASTERCHEF 3 PREVIEW! Check it out...... http://fb.me/OWNTkZqD     
    
    
    Don't forget to get your copy of SEXY CHEF - COOKING WITH CONFIDENCE TODAY! it makes a great new years gift!... http://fb.me/yXAmLL21    
    
    
    I decided to make a delicious sauce. Beer, bathing suit and sauce. Lol, enjoy your weekend!    
    
    
    Happy memorial day! Grill it up baby! :-)
Memo    
    
    
    Looking for a light and delicious summer dessert? Then check out my fresh fruit and angel food cake summer... http://fb.me/Uv5WIxB6     
    
    
    Delicious Summer Dessert. Get it here first. http://pinterest.com/pin/183169909814845829/ … The Sexy-Chef Liz: Fresh Fruit & Angel Food Cake Dessert    
    
    
    This photo just makes my mouth water. http://fb.me/1M28Ad6vT     
    
    
    http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/08/tri-colored-spaghetti-w-spicy-shrimp.html    
    
    
    http://fb.me/BHAySFnq    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/EfpeZ3Lo    
    
    
    Getting ready to grill some of my fav.. TUNA! Yum... I'm making Nick some grilled Pork Chops... I'm sure they will also be FAB!    
    
    
    Hey guys! Do NOT forget to watch me monday on FOX 9pm, with Gordon Ramsay on Masterchef!    
    
    
    Yah, I finally got the full clip! Check it out... Sexy Chef on MASTERCHEF!... http://fb.me/1LLWWP2i4     
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/akwEY4j5CqM?a  The Sexy Chef Liz MASTERCHEF CLIP on FOX with Gordon Ramsay    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/akwEY4j5CqM?a  The Sexy Chef Liz MASTERCHEF CLIP on FOX with Gordon Ramsay    
    
    
    Almost at the beach!    
    
    
    HAPPY NEW YEARS EVERYONE! Remember, it's not too early to open some wine :-)    
    
    
    This will be the BEST meal for NEW YEARS ever! http://fb.me/BgnvtaNA    
    
    
    Check out some of the finalists for master chef on Fox @SexyChefLiz  is on left. Winner gets 250k. Good Luck! pic.twitter.com/v9TPDX7W    
    
    
    @becky_wine heck yes, a napa trip would be amazing right now!    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz hey liz! i've been watching masterchef, i saw you on the first episode- did you make it through the first round!?    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who tuned in!!!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/zUDSaI1p    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FuBs96A6    
    
    
    http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/08/fresh-oregano_12.html http://fb.me/zYh3eqAa    
    
    
    http://fb.me/DAq6dplt    
    
    
    I love Fridays... and I love weekends http://fb.me/FlIog9L0    
    
    
    I love Fridays and I LOVE weekends!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/xrGbr5cV    
    
    
    Looking forward to some YUMMY leftovers that I will be posting about soon!    
    
    
    Tune in again tomorrow for MasterChef on FOX at 9pm. Rooting for my peeps and maybe I'll get another clip :-D    
    
    
    @NewCookingShow Can't wait for this...Nigella you are my IDOL    
    
    
    http://fb.me/H0yotj9Y    
    
    
    CHECK OUT MY VIDEO.... see below    
    
    
    So I made my signature dish last night and the votes were unanimous... APRON APPROVED! LOL. But seriously, this dish is AMAZING.    
    
    
    Just had the best Tortilla de Pappas. MMMM. Will post a photo later    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz Love the new site!!!    
    
    
    Check it out, delicious tortilla de pappas. pic.twitter.com/aCgf79zQ    
    
    
    @ThatGuyHugs thanks Jason! Its by Jeff Powers :-D hope all is well, we'll do some pics soon!    
    
    
    Hope everyone had an AMAZING new years... I sure did. Amazing FOOD, hot music, drinks galore and DANCING. perfect. :-)    
    
    
    tuning into the build a better burger contest to see who won!    
    
    
    Stay tuned for some NEW and HILARIOUS spoof videos. I'm SO excited. :-D    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FIkaPRxC    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Liz's Delicious Dishes" http://fb.me/HulbyygY    
    
    
    Just grilled these delicious salmon burgers!!! pic.twitter.com/20G54fXr    
    
    
    I have some GREAT and FABULOUS recipies to share... You guys will love them. Promise. Hang in there.    
    
    
    Making the food for my girls 30th bday. http://fb.me/1jIAxDElW     
    
    
    cheeses from a great client :-)    
    
    
    If your new years resolution was to start eating healthier... this dish will be your new FAVORITE! http://fb.me/Lka1RrsI    
    
    
    Was one of your resolutions to start eating healthier? PERFECT. Because everything I make is HEALTHY AND SOO... http://fb.me/NjwgFcvi    
    
    
    My new favorite dish... Vegetable Neopolitan. Sooo deliciously amazing. I knocked it out of the ball park... http://fb.me/1w53mD3Ii     
    
    
    The Sexy-Chef Liz: Vegetable Neopolitan... Creamy, Crispy, Tangy, Delectable. http://pinterest.com/pin/183169909814972362/ …    
    
    
    Get 25% off NOW when you buy the Book... just enter the code WINTER at checkout! http://fb.me/RNIOUdCD    
    
    
    CHECK OUT MY NEW MEDIEVAL VIDEOS    
    
    
    http://fb.me/GBNtg25L    
    
    
    One Cornish Hen, coming up! http://fb.me/CrsdjqBS    
    
    
    Making Pasta Salad and then floating around in the pool!    
    
    
    Love this pic. http://fb.me/1ZDQ8V6Nd     
    
    
    What do you need help making tonight? let me know at www.sexychef.net    
    
    
    Mimosas, wheat toast and coffee... breakfast of champions!    
    
    
    My fingers are still burning from chopping those Habaneros!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/FTFYmN2o    
    
    
    just ate a small wheat roll. Yum... hopefully that will hold me over till my day is done!    
    
    
    Thinking of something great to make!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/M60p4Upj    
    
    
    Happy 4TH of july everyone! I was in the pool all day, or else i would have posted. Hope everyones day was great!    
    
    
    Just wishing you a Happy New Year.. completely candid http://fb.me/HLYgYAjC    
    
    
    In order to stay sexy, you need to work out. Getting ready for a run!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/I7307nrv    
    
    
    Check out this great creation!    
    
    
    http://www.facebook.com/pages/The-Sexy-Chef-Liz/137973369563409?v=app_2373072738#!/topic.php?uid=137973369563409&topic=210    
    
    
    Drinking Wine while creating your masterpiece! http://fb.me/Ezqcrdjl    
    
    
    WE MADE IT TO THE NEXT ROUND OF THE PYREX COMPETITION SO YOU WILL ALL HAVE TO VOTE FOR US, I WILL GIVE INFO WHEN I GET IT    
    
    
    Breakfast of champions... Cinnamon/sugar toast! 

It's Simple, toast your favorite bread, spread with butter,... http://fb.me/OC4tTw9P    
    
    
    Check it out... THE BOOK IS REAL! http://fb.me/Ln6fEBnv    
    
    
    Delicious and Light pasta Dish! http://fb.me/G2jeL6I5    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/JfYVuctcasQ?a  MASTERCHEF - Preview #3 from "Auditions #1" airing MON 6/4    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/cdQJqXSbBoA?a  MASTERCHEF - Preview #1 from "Auditions #1" airing MON 6/4    
    
    
    Delicious. Lobster Ravioli with light cream sauce. What do you think? http://fb.me/1szpXH5pq     
    
    
    @Jbastianich Hey Joe, you should follow my BFF, @Becky_Wine she loves wine and thinks you're pretty cool.    
    
    
    I ate these potatoes the other night with grilled tuna. It was heaven.... http://fb.me/1JPp0IfHu     
    
    
    HURRY! It's the LAST DAY to get 25% OFF Sexy Chef-Cooking with Confidence! USE CODE: WINTER http://fb.me/Hw45IV2f    
    
    
    HURRY Last day to get 25% OFF Sexy Chef- Cooking with Confidence!    
    
    
    STARTING TOMORROW... I WILL BE BLOWING UP ALL OF YOUR EMAILS AND PAGES BECAUSE WE WILL NEED YOUR VOTES IN ORDER TO... http://fb.me/Fwf7t3lC    
    
    
    START VOTING FOR AMERICAS HOTTEST CULINARY COUPLE!! http://www.americashottestculinarycouple.com/index.asp?pageId=14&vId=4    
    
    
    START VOTING NOW!!!! WE NEED YOUR HELP IN ORDER TO WIN!! USE AS MANY EMAIL ADDRESSES YOU HAVE!!!... http://fb.me/GqKV4Mgo    
    
    
    @MC3David once a dick, always a dick.    
    
    
    @GordonRamsay01 funny episode. Love Paula... I was hoping she would literally put some south in your mouth. Oh well.    
    
    
    @MC3David thanks for the " heads up". I''ll be sure to be extra " cautious"    
    
    
    DAY 2 OF VOTING STARTS NOW!!!! Please cast ALL of your votes again today and help us win America's Hottest... http://fb.me/EM1MxNHf    
    
    
    PLEASE VOTE FOR LIZ AND NICK AMERICAS HOTTEST CULINARY COUPLE
http://www.americashottestculinarycouple.com/index.asp?pageId=14&vId=4    
    
    
    The Ultimate Breakfast sandwich... http://fb.me/QUNMnmGo    
    
    
    Lunch anyone? http://fb.me/R8OxwjUL    
    
    
    Is anyone else completely OBSESSED with spinach pie? http://fb.me/27U0wJfN0     
    
    
    Now I just need an awards show to go to. http://fb.me/1QWfZvg3F     
    
    
    @GordonRamsay01 funny episode. Love Paula... I was hoping she would literally put some south in your mouth. Oh well.    
    
    
    @MC3Frank you rock frank    
    
    
    @MASTERCHEFonFOX finally a blind tasting. Should have been that way from day 1    
    
    
    LOL. MasterChef is cracking me up... but not really in a great way.    
    
    
    @MC3Stacey I thought you got it...    
    
    
    Check out some of the finalists for master chef on Fox @SexyChefLiz  is on left. Winner gets 250k. Good Luck! pic.twitter.com/v9TPDX7W    
    
    
    Sexy chef just got a new phone!    
    
    
    VOTE FOR LIZ AND NICK, AMERICAS HOTTEST CULINARY COUPLE!! 
http://www.americashottestculinarycouple.com/index.asp?pageId=14&vId=4    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/F_Tcps_Qu-A?a  Fox 45 News Baltimore MasterChef Segment with The Sexy Chef    
    
    
    Check it out! The Sexy Chef Liz on FOX 45 NEWS!!! Don't miss it!!! http://youtu.be/F_Tcps_Qu-A  http://fb.me/PrA43zgt     
    
    
    Check it out! The Sexy Chef Liz on FOX 45 NEWS!!! Don't miss it!!! http://youtu.be/F_Tcps_Qu-A  http://fb.me/PrA43zgt     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/F_Tcps_Qu-A?a  Fox 45 News Baltimore MasterChef Segment with The Sexy Chef Liz    
    
    
    LAST DAY TO VOTE FOR LIZ AND NICK, DO IT HERE NOW
http://www.americashottestculinarycouple.com/index.asp?pageId=14&vId=4    
    
    
    Thansk for the follow. I've always been a huge fan. @BackstreetBoysw    
    
    
    Delicious Veggie Combo http://fb.me/vFLpmW6r    
    
    
    Thank you so much everyone for all of your support and VOTES!    
    
    
    Delicious 5-min. Veggie Burger and Hot Dogs... gourmet of course http://fb.me/IWy6IMUS    
    
    
    Kicked up Pasta Salad... YUM!! http://fb.me/vRVpZ9vR    
    
    
    @michaelianblack when are you coming back to DC? The synagogue misses you.    
    
    
    mmmm, this TOTALLY hits the spot! http://fb.me/Sdz8ciSI    
    
    
    SAVE 10 percent NOW when you purchase Sexy Chef - Cooking with Confidence use code: READ2011    
    
    
    Music, Wine, Spanish Smooth-Jazz... and ofcourse making a cool meal. It's a creation thus far... will post later... :-D    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/MO6xhLtfwW0?a  Taylor Dayne - Love Will Lead You Back    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/xEmdW3_bi4c?a  Heartbreak Hotel    
    
    
    Sup @joshwolfcomedy. Is it true that you really do tweet back? I sure hope so :-D    
    
    
    @ChrisFranjola What up?? You guys should have me on the show to do a cooking segment... it would be REALLY fun ;-)    
    
    
    @KelliBingman nice profile pic Biotch.    
    
    
    @joshwolfcomedy you're so sexy    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @stecalderaro http://youtu.be/wekqaxSxzBU?a  Gordon Ramsay   How To Prepare Scallops    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video from @stecalderaro http://youtu.be/wekqaxSxzBU?a  Gordon Ramsay   How To Prepare Scallops    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GF5jGn__K58?a  Ramsay Twins Create Wine - Exclusive BBC Interview    
    
    
    Sup @joshwolfcomedy. Is it true that you really do tweet back? I sure hope so :-D    
    
    
    good luck tonight. @Charlie4Change sorry I cant make it!    
    
    
    One of the best things about making a delicious meal for dinner is having a variation of it again for lunch!    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/IMcHrbpjtAs?a  nyc real estate    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/IMcHrbpjtAs?a  Real Estate 101 with Bernadette DiFonzo    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/IMcHrbpjtAs?a  Real Estate 101 with Bernadette DiFonzo -- Sexy Chef (@SexyChefLiz) @Becky_Wine    
    
    
    love Julia Child! Happy Birthday! http://fb.me/1QeAIg0ow     
    
    
    @chefartsmith Thanks for following me Art! I think you are amazing... you're my favorite on Top Chef.    
    
    
    What a great day. Chef Art Smith from TOP CHEF is now following me on Twitter. :-D    
    
    
    I had a great Niciose salad today! Great Sunday Lunch! http://fb.me/1kDDqh6q3     
    
    
    @Chef_Aaron <3 you! My favorite!    
    
    
    I'm working on my online newsletter. For those of you who are interested in being on my monthly distribution... http://fb.me/281ky0Yx9     
    
    
    OMG... so delish... perfect for a snowy day! http://fb.me/BTaFbVtO    
    
    
    Making homeade gnocchis!!!!    
    
    
    OMG the gnocchis were FABULOUS... I'll be posting pics and the secrets.... :-)    
    
    
    DELICIOUSNESS!!! http://fb.me/ups4iG6z    
    
    
    just made fantastic swordfish, tuna and rice.... yum.    
    
    
    Beck, this is for YOU http://fb.me/I8k1QpRU    
    
    
    Happy Sept 1st! Enjoy it!    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/RBKvsJJRbQk?a  Sexy Chef Liz Makes Risotto ( and gives tips for going out o    
    
    
    Check out my latest video.... :-D

http://youtu.be/RBKvsJJRbQk  http://fb.me/1i7RGDxLS     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/RBKvsJJRbQk?a  Sexy Chef Liz Makes Risotto ( Surprise Musical Guest Announces    
    
    
    Yum, the best Fall dish! My version of "red beans and rice" http://fb.me/FPud76CR    
    
    
    Fantastic dinner and even better lunch... see below! Fall is arriving... it's getting chilly out!    
    
    
    @HeidnSeek hey lady!    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz can we ask how you found us?    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz we need you on our podcast as a guest!    
    
    
    The EASIEST corn on the cob you will EVER make! http://fb.me/E0CipfmT    
    
    
    Working out and eating right.... the best thing you can do! Don't forget the wine!    
    
    
    Whole Grilled Salmon! http://fb.me/HF9AT120    
    
    
    @BravoAndy cant wait to finally be a guest on your show!    
    
    
    Easy, fun and delishious... don't miss this CHOCOLATE PEANUT BUTTER CAKE! http://fb.me/QpuQVSB0    
    
    
    WE OFFICIALLY WON, WE ARE GOING TO NYC TO COMPETE FOR THE JUDGES!!!! YAHHH THANK YOU ALL SO MUCH FOR YOUR SUPPORT AND VOTES!!!!!!    
    
    
    MY FIRST SHIPMENT OF PYREX PRODUCTS CAME IN... omg... I basically can throw EVERYTHING else away because I have SO MUCH STUFF hahaha    
    
    
    Hey Hey Hey!!! Was at a beautiful wedding the past few days... will be posting great things this week :-D    
    
    
    can officially tell you all.... I'm going to be on the NEW GAME SHOW, "Let's Ask America!" My air date is 9/28...... http://fb.me/1FuTU2PTt     
    
    
    @FriendsEAT @SexyChefLiz I think you both might appreciate a buff shirtless baker. Check out Mancandy and cupcakes http://kck.st/TIFsKS     
    
    
    congrats... I was wondering! “@SexyChefLiz: .. I'm on the NEW GAME SHOW, "Let's Ask America!" My air date is 9/28... http://fb.me/1FuTU2PTt ”    
    
    
    congrats... I was wondering! “@SexyChefLiz: .. I'm on the NEW GAME SHOW, "Let's Ask America!" My air date is 9/28... http://fb.me/1FuTU2PTt ”    
    
    
    @FriendsEAT @SexyChefLiz I think you both might appreciate a buff shirtless baker. Check out Mancandy and cupcakes http://kck.st/TIFsKS     
    
    
    Awesomeness... for breakfast or lunch! http://fb.me/SthRwYvD    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @murdermark http://youtu.be/I4guXPIbIog?a  Murder Mark - "My Garage" (Official Music Video)    
    
    
    What's Your Favorite Crock Pot Meal? http://fb.me/JtiWQsUm    
    
    
    So I have not been home the past SEVERAL nights to actually MAKE something, but TRUST ME... I'll have TONS of... http://fb.me/JJRLFfp8    
    
    
    So I was told that I am now IN THE PREVIEW for the show - "Let's Ask America" which will air on FRIDAY 9/28. MAKE... http://fb.me/v8zFWStS     
    
    
    I'm excited to share the Murder Mark - My Garage Music Video produced by TT The Artist. You can't miss me... I'm... http://fb.me/PrhMgjgW     
    
    
    Nick and I want to thank you ALL for being SO supportive and helpful during the competition! WE ARE GEARING UP FOR... http://fb.me/tnwj1ClL    
    
    
    Sexy-Salmon with Onion, Garlic and Pepper relish! http://fb.me/xuUE5Ka1    
    
    
    I posted 32 photos on Facebook in the album "November 10, 2010" http://fb.me/KI5FMgWk    
    
    
    GEARING UP FOR THE FINAL COMPETITION ON NYC!!!
www.americashottestculinarycouple.com    
    
    
    Hey Guys! Don't forget to watch me tonight on "Let's Ask America" at 7:30pm! Click the link to find your channel!... http://fb.me/1W6QLsQrc     
    
    
    @ABC2NEWS Thanks for interviewing me today about Let's Ask America! Can't wait to see it tonight!    
    
    
    @MikeQReports Hey Mike, are you the one who called me yesterday to set up the interview?    
    
    
    @MikeQReports Hey Mike, are you the one who called me yesterday to set up the interview?    
    
    
    @MikeQReports Hey Mike, are you the one who called me yesterday to set up the interview?    
    
    
    Chicken Cacciatore, made EASY in the crock pot! http://fb.me/PGlVp3eX    
    
    
    @GordonRamsay01 I hope Gordon Ramsay Pub and Grill Vegas is open!    
    
    
    Thanks Ashley and Gran for sharing this dish with me and letting me create my own deliciousness. MYA! http://fb.me/BTX2O5TQ    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @tttheartist http://youtu.be/Ni_-eDFaHeA?a  TT The Artist - Making Of Closer (Episode 1)    
    
    
    ROTINI WITH RED PEPPERS AND PARMESAN http://fb.me/HsJgY8sm    
    
    
    HOTTEST CULINARY COUPLE IN AMERICA - Pyrex Manicotti Surprise! http://fb.me/IUvmdb42    
    
    
    Re-cooping from it all    
    
    
    Bacon, Egg and Cheese... only Healthy! http://fb.me/xHDCOzTA    
    
    
    Now get 20 PERCENT OFF the book! Own it NOW for ONLY $22 !!!!!!! http://fb.me/FJRMMElO    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hungry, planning what to make for DINNER    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/8esNAY4DF0s?a  How To Lift Your Buttocks - Fastest Way To Get A Firm Butt    
    
    
    My Lizabetta!!! @SexyChefLiz they might be doing a veggie episode of #Chopped How awesome??!!!    
    
    
    My Lizabetta!!! @SexyChefLiz they might be doing a veggie episode of #Chopped How awesome??!!!    
    
    
    I LOVE this recipe!    
    
    
    YUM, you have to try this.... http://fb.me/I8IiJdr9    
    
    
    If you're getting hit by this storm, stay safe everyone... this is the perfect time to make soup, sauce, chili...... http://fb.me/1Px99HcL5     
    
    
    Wanna be the HIT of a party? BRING THIS DISH!!!! Creamy Pasta Rosa & Chicken http://fb.me/FVi7CwpY    
    
    
    Happy Halloween! I want to make a pumpkin pie!    
    
    
    I'm excited to make Niki a delicious Filled Cabbage dinner tonight.... I'll be sure to post about it ASAP :-)    
    
    
    Check out these fabulous B-day cupcakes that are not only DELICIOUS but low-fat too http://fb.me/HgksdzUr    
    
    
    Exciting to share some great things with everyone :-)    
    
    
    Excited to share some awesome dishes for everyone :-)    
    
    
    Anyone have any yummy recipes that want to share with the SEXY CHEF?    
    
    
    http://fb.me/y4JlvHGy    
    
    
    Plotting my next creation    
    
    
    Hungarian Style ! http://fb.me/HzGnJVpn    
    
    
    Great Dinner, as usual. :-)    
    
    
    Potatoes anyone?    
    
    
    Vote for Liz ...because she throws it the fuck down!!!    
    
    
    Hey Guys, Please vote for YOUR Sexy Chef Liz HERE!!!  http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54203065 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Please, CAST YOUR VOTE NOW for SEXY CHEF in the PAM Commercial Contest! http://fb.me/JUC7156v    
    
    
    Hey Guys, please check out my latest VIDEO and PLEASE vote for me! Thanks so much! Please vote DAILY! http://lnk.ms/JfqGY    
    
    
    Hey guys! Please vote for your SEXY CHEF in the Pam Video Contest!    
    
    
    YUM!!! http://fb.me/DSXR8kIq    
    
    
    Who likes Spinach??? If you don't I bet I can make you like it... :-)    
    
    
    SUBSCRIBE TO MY BLOG!!! http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    Don't forget to vote today! Click the link and if you like this video,  VOTE AND SHARE! http://fb.me/Mj522pLS    
    
    
    Cake! Cake! Cake! Thanks to Aimee for another excuse to quote Rihanna.    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving Everyone! I wish you all the best today :-D http://fb.me/DZjG6Fh4     
    
    
    Peas and Carrots - they're no longer just "theater chatter" http://fb.me/wUwzKFq5    
    
    
    Are you sick of leftovers yet or just getting started??    
    
    
    Salmon with Chunky Garlic Tomato Sauce and Peas :-) http://fb.me/BYdQWOIZ    
    
    
    The Sexy-Chef Liz    -       http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    We couldn't agree more. #LimeLove “@iiAmDiva: @limefreshmex Fish tacos >>>>>>>”    
    
    
    Cake! Cake! Cake! Thanks to Aimee for another excuse to quote Rihanna.    
    
    
    @bridgedubbya sounds great girl. Keep me posted and count me in!    
    
    
    Check out my GREAT new video! http://fb.me/tnc5FAX2    
    
    
    CHECK OUT MY VIDEO!!! It's also a competition, so you just have to watch it, no voting this time haha    
    
    
    HEY guys, follow my SEXY CHEF page on Facebook! THE SEXY CHEF LIZ    
    
    
    Twitter chat tomorrow! Tune in at 12 pm EST: One lucky tweets will win a pink pony tee! http://ow.ly/2TFKL #PINKPONY10    
    
    
    SUBSCRIBE TO MY BLOG! http://fb.me/yAt6clk7    
    
    
    DELICIOUS!!!! http://fb.me/EqGGgr0c    
    
    
    Check out these delish carrot, potato pancakes.... THEN VOTE FOR ME IN THE PAM COMMERCIAL! http://fb.me/AibSNFQO    
    
    
    need some SWEET recipe ideas? Check this out TODAY: http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    Check out the recipe for Annie's Naturals... http://fb.me/yyALjzmO    
    
    
    Enjoying a Gin Gimlet :-)    
    
    
    amazing dinner... posting later... FYI the voting is going GREAT... we need to be in the top 10, we are currently... http://fb.me/MFw5AqUc    
    
    
    The BEST new recipe that I created... look out tastebuds... http://fb.me/CvKkFiZS    
    
    
    How early can you start drinking wine? 

Answer: It's 5 o'clock somewhere :-)    
    
    
    I'll be posting some fab. stuff with my darling cousin who is also a chef. stay tuned. :-)    
    
    
    Wed. night cocktail anyone? yes PLEASE! http://fb.me/IV9nESHA    
    
    
    Hey guys, help us get into the TOP 10 today... I know you can do this... please vote... THANKS! http://fb.me/NvGAUf5V    
    
    
    Making my famous blueberry muffins... YUM... posting after!    
    
    
    http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54352986 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods  VOTE FOR MY COMMERCIAL here!    
    
    
    enjoy! http://fb.me/DAiW2qdp    
    
    
    happy holidays to everyone. Love you all :-)    
    
    
    I think you will enoy my latest video. It's quite unique... http://youtu.be/jw5cRrkk3MA?a     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @SexyChefLiz http://youtu.be/jw5cRrkk3MA?a  The Sexy Chef Liz makes Holiday Mac' n' Cheese (and more fun stuff)    
    
    
    Watch my holiday video!!! 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jw5cRrkk3MA … http://fb.me/taMaNBgu     
    
    
    Watch my holiday video!!! 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jw5cRrkk3MA … http://fb.me/taMaNBgu     
    
    
    Watch my holiday video!!! 

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jw5cRrkk3MA … http://fb.me/taMaNBgu     
    
    
    @bridgedubbya @BDAloha @mckchico love you Bridge    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz after 20 years you still crack me the eff up. "Mmmmmboo"    
    
    
    DID YOU VOTE TODAY? ONE CLICK VOTE BELOW! 
http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54387681 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Hey guys, here is your DAILY VOTE! Thanks! http://fb.me/SgPoicj3    
    
    
    @KelliBingman in love with you    
    
    
    Hey guys, Please take a moment and VOTE today!
 http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54387681 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    last night's dinner... fabulous to say the least. Tangy Salmon with Garbanzo Bean Hash http://fb.me/Rb8E4KfI    
    
    
    Now see this... garbanzo bean and ham omelet? Oh yes I did... http://fb.me/FycXTebu    
    
    
    Strapped for cash? Now, get the INSTANT FILE DOWNLOAD for ONLY $5.20 !!!!! http://fb.me/FMAQpij6    
    
    
    What's the easiest way to make lasagna you ask? SOLVED. Thanks Kelli    
    
    
    Time Warner Cable is about to drop the only network dedicated to the arts. Send a message to keep Ovation. http://www.bringbackovation.com     
    
    
    #Ravemusic is getting me through the rest of the day! COME ON freakin weekend! #pandora @SexyChefLiz 1 more week    
    
    
    You'll always be a first round pick in my weekend drinking draft. http://some.ly/JfAz1n  @AIMEEALEXANDER2 @porsha @SexyChefLiz    
    
    
    Who climbed all the way to the top on St. Pat's day after 3 car bombs? ME! I <3 Italy @SexyChefLiz pic.twitter.com/yyaHkVKh    
    
    
    #Ravemusic is getting me through the rest of the day! COME ON freakin weekend! #pandora @SexyChefLiz 1 more week    
    
    
    #Ravemusic is getting me through the rest of the day! COME ON freakin weekend! #pandora @SexyChefLiz 1 more week    
    
    
    #Ravemusic is getting me through the rest of the day! COME ON freakin weekend! #pandora @SexyChefLiz 1 more week    
    
    
    We are backn4th between 16-17. PLEASE VOTE!!!!  http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54469674 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Heading over to Taste Mediterranean Grill in Towson to check it out and TASTE their food! :-)    
    
    
    Oh, and PLEASE don't forget to vote! http://fb.me/yZzpDkAe    
    
    
    @ErnieLynnR nyc http://instagr.am/p/Urku06DCiM/     
    
    
    I'm at The Irish Pub (New York, NY) http://4sq.com/W7lxFv     
    
    
    Went hard this weekend. All to do it again next weekend. OCMD @sexychefliz ashjball http://instagr.am/p/Utx2pLkGUL/     
    
    
    Went hard this weekend. All to do it again next weekend. OCMD @sexychefliz ashjball http://instagr.am/p/Utx2pLkGUL/     
    
    
    Went hard this weekend. All to do it again next weekend. OCMD @sexychefliz ashjball http://instagr.am/p/Utx2pLkGUL/     
    
    
    Went hard this weekend. All to do it again next weekend. OCMD @sexychefliz ashjball http://instagr.am/p/Utx2pLkGUL/     
    
    
    Went hard this weekend. All to do it again next weekend. OCMD @sexychefliz ashjball http://instagr.am/p/Utx2pLkGUL/     
    
    
    If you guys want a quick laugh... this video has gotten RAVE reviews thus far. http://youtu.be/adjEzmGh3aE?a     
    
    
    Hey guys, I didn't get a chance to post this yet but enjoy... this is the LET'S ASK AMERICA segment I did... http://youtu.be/wnwEb_FlaD0?a     
    
    
    ABC News interviews the Sexy Chef Liz about her appearance on LET'S ASK AMERICA: http://youtu.be/cs20BP5_Ylw?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hey guys, check out this ABC news interview for my appearance on LET'S ASK AMERICA!... http://fb.me/17Uzdwwhg     
    
    
    Hey guys, check out this ABC news interview for my appearance on LET'S ASK AMERICA!... http://fb.me/2beqB4GVa     
    
    
    DON'T FORGET TO WATCH MY VIDEO FOR ANNIES AND MAKE SURE YOU COMMENT!!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AOsadJpH4UM    
    
    
    The easiest garlic bread ever! http://fb.me/A0ocHzts    
    
    
    The Easiest Lasagna EVER!!! Thanks Kelli http://fb.me/AIZ3QrKx    
    
    
    Delicious Fall Stew: Made in the Crock Pot! http://fb.me/Jfrj1cGf    
    
    
    The Sexy Chef poses with Owner of Taste- Mediterranean Grille! http://fb.me/OjlrT1ER    
    
    
    Making my FAVORITE thing tonight............ SAUCE!!!!!!!!!! more later :-p    
    
    
    Multiple Browsers = MULTIPLE VOTING OPPORTUNITES! Please copy and paste this link into ALL of your different... http://fb.me/Pijzoie9    
    
    
    Check out the BEST SAUCE EVER! http://fb.me/KXPWj8pQ    
    
    
    Check out this DELICIOUS sauce recipe: http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/2010/11/lizs-ultimate-sauce.html http://fb.me/JV1zdnL2    
    
    
    See the AMAZING sauce recipe below...    
    
    
    @iamtravisdavon THAT #BMORE video is TIGHT!!! GET UM!!!!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @iamtravisdavon http://youtu.be/P0qpz1ep0-0?a  Travis Davon (Bossman) Land Of The O Pt II Video (Official    
    
    
    Hey guys! Show some love and check out my boyz video... if you watched #Superbowl, then you'll LOVE this #Bmore... http://fb.me/y2zDUI2D     
    
    
    The Life Changers: http://youtu.be/442JQwdAgcU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    Hey all, please VOTE today... we are ALMOST THERE!  http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54557521 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    while your waiting for your food to cook, chair aerobics are always a good idea :-) http://fb.me/OEqUneXz    
    
    
    The perfect hearty soup for cold weather! http://fb.me/QOnzlW3u    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz WE NEED TO GO TO THIS!!! "@BoyzIIMen: 98 degress/new kids and us....fun summer #thepackagetour”    
    
    
    I want to be Beyonce when I grow up #destinyschildreunion @BDAloha @AIMEEALEXANDER2 @mckchico    
    
    
    Grilled Tofu & Peas... check it out... the best dinner ever! http://fb.me/OkJvrCsK    
    
    
    Good Morning. Please vote, in all your browsers and on your phone. Thanks, we are spot 14... getting  CLOSER! http://fb.me/QVdpR0Ar    
    
    
    Spot 14, getting CLOSER. Please VOTE! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54387681 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Hey guys, want a FREE COPY of my book? CLICK THE FREE GIVEAWAY TAB to find out HOW!    
    
    
    HEY EVERYONE! Thank you for watching my Annies Video... I WON !!!!! Thanks guys!    
    
    
    You knowit girl!!! @bridgedubbya @bridgedubbya @AIMEEALEXANDER2 @mckchico    
    
    
    Hey guys, please VOTE and keep us strong! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54622297 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
        
    
    
    .@VictoriasSecret is adding $25 + $75 to Secret Rewards. Tweet #SecretRewardCard to unlock + spread the word: http://i.victoria.com/WsS     
    
    
    Time for your DAILY VOTE! THANKS! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54659474 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Just made a fantastic sauce... as usual. Posting to follow...    
    
    
    http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54557521 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods One more Vort6y  One More vote    
    
    
    Please VOTE today! Thanks! We are so close! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54770102 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Please take one second and VOTE today! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54387681 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Pierogies and Fries... what a combo! http://fb.me/T5H1vXyk    
    
    
    Don't forget to VOTE, and share this around! http://fb.me/SjlpDPzO    
    
    
    Don't forget to check out my FREE GIVEAWAY... next to the WALL! pass it along!    
    
    
    Last week to VOTE. Please vote SexyCHEF NOW! http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54798933 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/QWl4HcpD    
    
    
    Check out the latest product I found! Stick it Back! Watch and learn! http://fb.me/OyN5DYab    
    
    
    VOTE today! Sexy Chef/PAM PRINCESS!4 days to VOTE http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54888683 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    only 4 days left to VOTE! Please vote NOW, share it around and get us in the TOP 10! We are at number 11! http://fb.me/PeCXBsBi    
    
    
    Check out the FREE GIVEAWAY! http://fb.me/NPCqvEbm    
    
    
    Just finished making a fantasticly light pasta salad!!!    
    
    
    2 days left to VOTE, VOTE FOR US NOW!  http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54203065 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    Hey guys, only 2 days left.... PLEASE keep voting... we love you all! Thanks! http://fb.me/RgmLIzgu    
    
    
    Please vote! Almost over!!!http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=54622074 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
        
    
    
    LAST DAY TO VOTE, PLEASE VOTE NOW AND SHARE AROUND!!! http://fb.me/Ln7iCG0u    
    
    
    What an amazingly delicious and super quick dinner, Gnocchi with Spicy red peppers and peas! http://fb.me/DNwqYxoC    
    
    
    Please VOTE, we were num 5. now we are 6.. VOTE!http://www.brickfish.com/GoToPage.aspx?qsi=55068153 #PAMPullItOff @ConAgraFoods    
    
    
    The Pefect Green Beans! http://fb.me/F6QF2pYa    
    
    
    New favorite dish... Lemon, basil and feta pasta! http://fb.me/KNyhfHTW    
    
    
    Shrimp with Tomato, Basil and Feta... sooo delicious. Mmmmm http://fb.me/DSghibGi    
    
    
    I think I am going to make stuffed peppers tonight.... :-)    
    
    
    Watch my latest product launch!!! It's hot! http://fb.me/CkC2JG38    
    
    
    Happy Valentines Day everyone! What is everyone making for dinner tonight?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sexy Chef Liz and Phillip, owner at Fins Restaurant Bar and Grill (Canton square, B-more MD) http://fb.me/AWlULrZB    
    
    
    Getting PUMPED for the Maryland Public Television Taping tomorrow! :-)    
    
    
    like the hair? http://fb.me/CdQ5nZFp    
    
    
    @bridgedubbya @mckchico love this    
    
    
    Check out my Interview with the executive Chef from Brewer's Art! http://fb.me/Qa6btS06    
    
    
    Stuffed Peppers, get the recipe HERE: http://fb.me/vtNC2Rcf    
    
    
    Watch as the Sexy Chef Liz interviews the owner of Fins Bar & Grille on Canton Square! http://fb.me/RSqve4Sj    
    
    
    This is what I made on MPT the other day, Salmon with Campanelli & Vegetables :-) I'll let you know when to watch. http://fb.me/SyisTG39    
    
    
    Check out this easy Honey Mustard & Sesame Tuna ! Have it for lunch today or dinner tonight! http://fb.me/vV6qMODA    
    
    
    Check it out, it's me on the set of MPT (Maryland Public Television!) http://fb.me/S9cm60Rf    
    
    
    Exclusive Photos and Information regarding Sexy Chef Liz appearing on Maryland Public Television!  http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    SAVE 25% OFF Sexy Chef - Cooking with Confidence TODAY ONLY!!! Just enter the code: HAPPY305 at checkout! http://fb.me/TKHBCcje    
    
    
        
    
    
    Try my Shrimp, tomato and basil pasta today! http://fb.me/BumJRTTc    
    
    
    want an easy dinner tonight? Try my Flounder with Festive Green Beans! Ready in 10 minutes! http://fb.me/VN3qEump    
    
    
    MARK YOU CALENDARS! MPT cooks will first air on March 5th at 2:30pm, March 13th at 1:30pm and March 19th at NOON.... http://fb.me/vZCBzQlE    
    
    
    anyone else make an AMAZING breakfast... and then realize that it's ALMOST time for LUNCH??? :-)    
    
    
    I just transformed boring soup into an awesome rice stew!    
    
    
    Check out this sneak peak of what I was cooking for Maryland Public TV! http://fb.me/ST5lLHfa    
    
    
    Who wants TUNA?    
    
    
    PAN SEARED TUNA- check it out HERE http://fb.me/E6B1lZol    
    
    
    What's up with everyone calling Vegetables, "Veg?" I kind-of, REALLY don't like it... any thoughts?    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef Liz Practices for her Maryland Public Televisi... http://youtu.be/YDGZ678eRsc?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/KMYXr    
    
    
    OMG THIS IS FREAKING HILAROUS! (YouTube http://youtu.be/k3ZMmUyvuog?a)    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LGZK7    
    
    
    What are you making tonight? Try my Spicy Pene and Vegetables... you won't be dissapointed :-) http://fb.me/AS5AoSv7    
    
    
    We're connected on facebook... let's connect on YOU TUBE also! Click the link and let's share videos! http://fb.me/TLBV0yEA    
    
    
    Enjoying a nice cerveza... anyone else?    
    
    
    Mark your calendars Marylanders! TOMORROW is the first premier of MPT COOKS (Maryland Public Television) I will be... http://fb.me/uIhU9HuM    
    
    
    Sexy Chef Liz makes an appearance on MPT COOKS! (Maryland Public Television) http://fb.me/VNqnScfB    
    
    
    Nothing beats fish sticks and a freshing Stella on an early Friday in March!    
    
    
    Don't forget... if you live in Maryland, you can TUNE into Maryland Public Television TODAY... the show is called... http://fb.me/XtFA1IMz    
    
    
    I subscribed to AETZEL1's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/AETZEL1?feature=autoshare    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out the latest Sexy Chef website... lots of great information RIGHT HERE!  http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    I just updated my site... check it out! http://fb.me/MQBNNP48    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/UFqLzLOs    
    
    
    Ok so my camera sucks I will post better photos tomorrow    
    
    
    RT @kerrycooks: Enjoying polenta with tomato braised beans for @MeatlessMonday dinner, thanks @Cooking_Light! http://bit.ly/eQMnsd    
    
    
    Confidence is sexy!!! RT @larsapippen: I love being around my confident friends. Confidence is power!!    
    
    
    Going out for Fajitas & Margaritas tonight... it's International Women's Day so we are going to celebrate!    
    
    
    Any day that starts out like this is guaranteed to be a red banner winner. #PoP! http://awe.sm/5H1ki    
    
    
    I posted 5 photos on Facebook in the album "Sexy Chef on Maryland Public Television!" http://fb.me/TzUDQmkh    
    
    
    I subscribed to FoodNetworkTV's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/FoodNetworkTV?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to FoodNetworkTV http://www.youtube.com/user/FoodNetworkTV    
    
    
    For those of you who could not watch, now you can! Watch Sexy Chef on MPT COOKS! http://fb.me/xfzatHP9    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef Liz - on MPT Cooks for Maryland Public Tele... http://youtu.be/c5xKC4xd7DA?a    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/KhfT0    
    
    
    Sexy Stuffed Mushrooms... http://fb.me/AN6GPJy2    
    
    
    Delicious for lunch or dinner... my fabulous Chicken and Broccoli! http://fb.me/SP9zhXSQ    
    
    
    Don't forget, TUNE IN TOMORROW, 3/13 to MPT (Maryland Public TV) to watch MPT Cooks, I'll be on again, starting at 1:30pm!    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef Liz - on MPT Cooks for Maryland Public Televis... http://youtu.be/c5xKC4xd7DA?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/KhfT0    
    
    
    Are we friends on YOUTUBE? Click now and let's connect! http://fb.me/WyietcOl    
    
    
    This "feel-good Gnocchi" is the perfect meal for any day of your life! Try it tonight! http://fb.me/xqSpcgRT    
    
    
    I subscribed to EasyRecipesHQ's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/EasyRecipesHQ?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to EasyRecipesHQ http://lnk.ms/LfCRH    
    
    
    wow, check out where this video ended up... on some random Salmon website... haha... I love it! http://fb.me/IzSaYRjn    
    
    
    Happy and excited that sexy chef is appearing organically on google :-) sexychef.net    
    
    
    Check out this awesome idea for LUNCH! Spring - Pene with Red Peppers and Carrots! http://fb.me/XMitVhec    
    
    
    I posted 14 photos on Facebook in the album "Mr. Darcy watches Sexy Chef" http://fb.me/FQvVNJbu    
    
    
        
    
    
    Subscribed to kimkardashiandotcom http://lnk.ms/CPpYh    
    
    
    East coast how are u liking Kourtney & Kim Take New York???    
    
    
    Subscribed to SunshineMonk http://lnk.ms/Kx8RJ    
    
    
    I subscribed to SunshineMonk's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/SunshineMonk?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Thoughts on my new business card? http://fb.me/TAHDAgLK    
    
    
    check out this delightful creation, fresh spinach, orzo and boca http://fb.me/HtgKAqE9    
    
    
    Happy St. Pattie's Day everyone! Can I get a LIKE for the Green beer? http://fb.me/WkXMrflZ    
    
    
    Working on bottling my Sexy Sauce...    
    
    
    Your Favorite Slice of Pizza http://fb.me/ViXP3Y9l    
    
    
    Do You Wear An Apron to Cook? http://fb.me/TThtxiGX    
    
    
    I endorse @KimKardashian in the Shorty category #fashion because...she is an icon, always daring- always classy and full of curves.LuvUKim    
    
    
    What's Your GO-TO Monday Meal? http://fb.me/MUuBYNRG    
    
    
    Try my Mahi Mahi with Fresh Tomatoes, Asparagus and white beans tonight! http://fb.me/YjVinY5L    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/L7TMV    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Sexy Chef PILOT - What is sexy? http://youtu.be/YbiFtpAIt5c?a    
    
    
    Check out the test-label for my Sexy Chef Sauce! http://fb.me/y3JUuFOb    
    
    
    FREE SHIPPING! Enter: GROUND in the code section http://fb.me/vPZPcII2    
    
    
    Check out my updated BLOG and let me know your thought, you can easily FOLLOW, delicious dishes: http://sexychefliz.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    Fins Bar & Grill on Canton Square has been my favorite go-to place for over 7 years. Phil will be deeply missed.... http://fb.me/SCKKxnG8    
    
    
    Making some delicious SAUCE tonight... 2 different kinds of my "famous" sauce... getting ready to meet with some manufactures! :-)    
    
    
    Cooking with Confidence    
    
    
    We will always remember Phil for the great person he was. His love for life a... (YouTube http://youtu.be/jFXMYPR4sOs?a)    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M2rPl    
    
    
    check this out... i'm directly in the process of creating the Sexy Chef apron line! What a fun night! http://fb.me/RYPAjKE9    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef Liz interviews owner, Phillip Rizas, at Fins B... http://youtu.be/jFXMYPR4sOs?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M2rPl    
    
    
    I LOVE Berger Cookies! If you live in Baltimore, you KNOW what I mean... if your planning a visit... YOU MUST plan... http://fb.me/JsZL6D2E    
    
    
    Rest in Peace Phil... Watch this video as a tribute to a wonderful man. Interview with Phi,... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jFXMYPR4sOs … via @youtube    
    
    
    Yahhh!!! Today we hit 300 Fans!!! Thank you all, let's keep up this SEXY MOMENTUM! http://fb.me/XERDrjom    
    
    
    Pam Contest http://fb.me/ElNAJBBS    
    
    
    I subscribed to yiannokoul's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/yiannokoul?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to yiannokoul http://lnk.ms/M5ZR1    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M2rPl    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef Liz interviews owner, Phillip Rizas, at Fins B... http://youtu.be/jFXMYPR4sOs?a    
    
    
    CITY'S BEST APPETIZER http://fb.me/UzTcoXXz    
    
    
    The viewing today was amazing. Everyone was there to show their love and supp... (YouTube http://youtu.be/jFXMYPR4sOs?a)    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M2rPl    
    
    
        
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M2rPl    
    
    
    Are you subscribed on YOUTUBE? Now you can be http://www.youtube.com/user/SexyChefLiz?feature=mhum#p/a/u/2/jFXMYPR4sOs http://fb.me/y8gafoXk    
    
    
    Happy Birthday to ME!!! http://fb.me/IoNS4cjs    
    
    
    Check out this quick Mexican Lunch! http://fb.me/F99gEuuD    
    
    
    What's Your Favorite Mexican Dish? http://fb.me/DqqzfUf8    
    
    
    Nothing like lunch with your mom :-)    
    
    
    Check out this amazing way to make Tofu! It's my Spicy Tofu Creole and it's DELICOUS! http://fb.me/GZnvjsv5    
    
    
    I updated the book cover! What do you think? http://fb.me/tkkslgWH    
    
    
    TAKE 20 PERCENT OFF TODAY, enter the code: SPLISH at checkout http://fb.me/CDRgveEA    
    
    
    We made Pizza last night... it was AWESOME :-)    
    
    
    You MUST try my sweet potato fries, they are AMAZING and bursting with FLAVOR! http://fb.me/RJfgLsNH    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/OJtxCaTe    
    
    
    Mexican BEAN SOUP... yum! http://fb.me/P0DGgQg9    
    
    
    Drivin to ocean city!    
    
    
    Best Italian in Ocean City MD - FRESCO'S http://fb.me/ZfHo9sGV    
    
    
    Delicious... best Italian food I've had in a LONG time... Grazie Pino! http://fb.me/IY6ijtYe    
    
    
    Developing a delicious recipe for my first video!    
    
    
    I just found out about another awesome VIDEO contest! Stay tuned, I'll be cooking up some GREAT things this week and posting videos!    
    
    
    Stay tuned, new videos coming out TONIGHT!    
    
    
    Uploading my FIRST video!    
    
    
    Making the video! http://fb.me/VdQx4rrI    
    
    
    :-) http://fb.me/yQkQLcUh    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/gAAWnb    
    
    
    Philadelphia Cream Cheese Mini Stuffed Peppers! http://fb.me/VqLtiirL    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/yzLyHVNtmjo?a The Real Women of Philadelphia, Sexy Chef Liz makes Philly Crea    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LcMNh    
    
    
    Here it is, The Sexy Chef Liz FIRST VIDEO for The Real Women of Philadelphia! Check it out!!! http://fb.me/RI4H0ed7    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- The Real Women of Philadelphia, Sexy Chef Liz makes Phill... http://youtu.be/yzLyHVNtmjo?a    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LcMNh    
    
    
    WATCH MY VIDEO, right on the sight for the real women of philadelphia! http://fb.me/vR6Ea4N2    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Real Women of Philadelphia, Sexy Chef Liz makes Philly C... http://youtu.be/yzLyHVNtmjo?a    
    
    
    watching everyone's videos :-)    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/sETI5MK2C1E?a The Sexy Chef - UNCUT UNEDITIED VERSION... a typical night in t    
    
    
    HAHA.. .check out how my REAL LIFE goes... UN CUT UNEDITED VERSION! http://fb.me/UudVFd5l    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LdXnX    
    
    
    Delicious Tofu Cacciatore! http://fb.me/yE7no0Gp    
    
    
    just did some updating on my blog    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef - UNCUT UNEDITED VERSION... a typical night in... http://youtu.be/sETI5MK2C1E?a    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef - UNCUT UNEDITED VERSION... a typical night... http://youtu.be/sETI5MK2C1E?a    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LdXnX    
    
    
    PAULA DEEN HERSELF just spotlighted me in the REAL WOMEN OF PHILADELPHIA .... click the link and see what she had... http://fb.me/Svs6YywT    
    
    
    Try my fabuloso Sun Dried Tomato and Pesto Stuffed Mushrooms! http://fb.me/HICuFwg5    
    
    
    Check out my SPOTLIGHT from Miss Paula Deen herself... she LOVED my video! http://fb.me/FNR17x6Y    
    
    
    Check out my updated website! http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    Favorite Type of PASTA??? http://fb.me/EdG9ZFeJ    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/LcMNh    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/yzLyHVNtmjo?a The Real Women of Philadelphia, Sexy Chef Liz makes Philly Crea    
    
    
    So, you've heard of P-ditty's "makin' the video" YEAH... it's all that AND MORE... stay tuned...    
    
    
    I'm working on creating a FABULOUS mac'n'cheese for the Real Women of Philadelphai contest!    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JrsW04i-l_0    
    
    
    Sexy Chef - Pumpkin Cheesecake... this never tasted so good! http://fb.me/B8ypUfY0    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/Lnwxp    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- The Sexy Chef makes mac & Cheese for Real Women of Philad... http://youtu.be/UOqEZYNyW2k?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/Lnwxp    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/UOqEZYNyW2k?a The Sexy Chef makes mac & Cheese for Real Women of Philadelphia    
    
    
    Watch my latest video... I'm making Sun-Dried Tomato Philly Cream Cheese Mac'n'Cheese! http://fb.me/IeW8ji0g    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/heFlx2    
    
    
    Just submitted my side dish :-)    
    
    
    Get the recipe HERE for my Philly  Cream Cheese Sun-Dried tomato mac & CHEESE! http://fb.me/HGMcN3bU    
    
    
    Check out my VIDEO in the Philly Cream Cheese Gallery! http://fb.me/LNdds7Vn    
    
    
    We busted out the grill last night!!! It's offically been 1 year since I started my sexy chef blog and YOUTUBE!!!! Love it!    
    
    
    Funny how after a night of hardcore wine drinking... your FAMISHED the next morning...    
    
    
    Wow. I literally had a PLATE full of scallops tonight... it was delish. However, I think what is more delish is... http://fb.me/LRR9RXbE    
    
    
    CHECK OUT OUR LATEST PYREX VIDEO! http://fb.me/NyajssFH    
    
    
    Check out my easy, delicious Lemon-Baked Tilapia! http://fb.me/XGeVCLK0    
    
    
    Check out my LATEST videos!    
    
    
    Working on uploading my delicious ENTREE!    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/flpvJA    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/WkZK3ITGATM?a The Sexy Chef makes Salmon with Pasta, Veggies and Philadelp    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WkZK3ITGATM&feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Don't miss my LATEST video, featuring Philadelphia Cooking Creme!!!  I've taken my salmon with campanelle and... http://fb.me/t9ys7PIS    
    
    
    Check out the recipe here... Philly Cooking Creme, Salmon, Pasta, Veggies... http://fb.me/F7s8NBzY    
    
    
    CHECK IT OUT... http://fb.me/ZR6aGOTs    
    
    
    watching all the great spotlights    
    
    
    What are you doing now?    
    
    
    @sexychefliz That salmon looks delish!    
    
    
    Subscribed to cyankw http://lnk.ms/NFRPP    
    
    
    I subscribed to cyankw's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/cyankw?feature=autoshare    
    
    
        
    
    
    I subscribed to fancy134's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/fancy134?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to fancy134 http://lnk.ms/M7xHL    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/WkZK3ITGATM?a The Sexy Chef makes Salmon with Pasta, Veggies and Philadelphia    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/M8K6G    
    
    
    Updated the Website... check it out!!  http://www.sexychef.net/  via @weebly    
    
    
    So, this is what my prize from  PAM was.... http://fb.me/J2YrRUOi    
    
    
    Like breakfast for dinner? Then you'll LOVE these scrambled eggs with tomatoes and red peppers... for those of you... http://fb.me/GIgXLhSh    
    
    
    Making dinner for a friend tonight... I'm thinking homemade sauce with shells and peas! :-)    
    
    
    I made these BREAKFAST POTATOES today... they were DELISH! http://fb.me/OkT1lK9x    
    
    
    Subscribed to barrybelcher2002 http://lnk.ms/GJP0s    
    
    
    I subscribed to barrybelcher2002's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/barrybelcher2002?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Best Cheesecake Flavor. EVER. http://fb.me/Yf6VdotQ    
    
    
    Just finished making
a Peanut Butter & Chocolate Hazelnut Cheese cake!    
    
    
    crazy busy week... but thankfully I was able to shoot my dessert before the deadline! Uploading NOW    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/MKv6N    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/ZCUjj-CZLfM?a chocolate peanut butter hazelnut cheesecake.wmv    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/lVVIsO    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/ZCUjj-CZLfM?a chocolate peanut butter hazelnut cheesecake.wmv    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/MKv6N    
    
    
    Don't miss my Peanut Butter & Chocolate Hazelnut cheesecake! http://fb.me/xjgcqYot    
    
    
    watching some other great videos and planning my next ones :-)    
    
    
    WHAT IS SEXY CHEF? check out this hilarious and explanitory video... http://fb.me/M0Rm7XaA    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/ZCUjj-CZLfM?a Sexy Chef Liz Makes a Peanut Butter & Chocolate hazelnut cheese    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/MKv6N    
    
    
    @SexyChefLiz That cheesecake looks great!    
    
    
    HAPPY CINCO DE MAYO EVERYONE!!!!!!! http://fb.me/XsoHMbsX    
    
    
    YAH, I LOVE the appetizer I just came up with... it's the best thing I've done yet!    
    
    
    HAPPY CINCO DE MAYo!    
    
    
    I subscribed to ChuckwagonCowboy's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/ChuckwagonCowboy?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to ChuckwagonCowboy http://lnk.ms/NPvcT    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/xc6Rucvb3Rw?a The Sexy Chef Liz Makes Cindo De Mayo Spicy Salmon Sliders    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/NfW1b    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/k30JPN    
    
    
    Cinco De Mayo Salmon Sliders with PICO DE GALLO! See the video NOW. http://fb.me/Au2zkyCi    
    
    
    I'm am forever uploading in the wee hours... it's all good    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/mHHuDZ    
    
    
    Check out my Philly Cream Cheese Bulgarian Banitza! http://fb.me/UcpNOPUy    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/WrO9aqOgIPk?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Bulgarian Three Cheese Banitza    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WrO9aqOgIPk&feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Thanks everyone for the support on my latest video, much appreciated. I'm working on another great side dish for... http://fb.me/LdXskQ6q    
    
    
    I subscribed to newsblastsocialmedia's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/newsblastsocialmedia?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to newsblastsocialmedia http://lnk.ms/Md0YQ    
    
    
    I subscribed to LoveMyPhilly's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/LoveMyPhilly?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    haah, I've been up making videos and drinking margaritas ... not done yet. Just had a 5 hour energy............. VIDEOS!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    Check out my FABULOUS side dish... Creamy Italian Red Potatoes & Green Beans! http://fb.me/10XePnmLF    
    
    
    Just made two GREAT sides... uploading now. You ladies are inspiring!    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/iNxjrG    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/ixCP9M    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/NrXpq    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/wVAcFKa5EVQ?a The Sexy Chef's Creamy Italian Red Potatoes and Green Beans    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Vx7MKRGJzuQ?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Creamy Summer Cabbage Slaw    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/Mh1wV    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Vx7MKRGJzuQ?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Creamy Summer Cabbage Slaw    
    
    
    Watch my Creamy Summer Cabbage Slaw... yummy... works well with grilled meats! http://fb.me/VcqtTr77    
    
    
    Check out how to make my Creamy Italian Red Pototoes & Green Beans! http://fb.me/YQZXJ04Z    
    
    
    Going to be making some shrimp & Linguine with a spicy pink cream sauce tonight... video to follow. Stay tuned!    
    
    
    Yum, try this Creamy Summer Cabbage Slaw! http://fb.me/XZxfOCqT    
    
    
        
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/0QVJoihir9c?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Creamy Shrimp & Linguini with Rosa S    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/P59pg    
    
    
        
    
    
    And watch the video... creamy shrimp and Linguini with Rosa Sauce for the Real Women of Philadelphia! http://fb.me/V0QhIEnc    
    
    
    re-watching my video and making myself hungry!    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/0QVJoihir9c?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Creamy Shrimp & Linguini with Rosa Sauc    
    
    
    @ConstantineRobbins Yes, you can leave the shrimp out, or use chicken. (@YouTube http://youtu.be/0QVJoihir9c?a)    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/P59pg    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/P59pg    
    
    
    If you've been to Italy, Florence in particular... then you KNOW this soup... Ribolita, check it out here! http://fb.me/vZyr3sMP    
    
    
    @ConstantineRobbins Yes, most of my videos DO have music, but for this particul (@YouTube http://youtu.be/0QVJoihir9c?a)    
    
    
    editing and uploading yet another!    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/GdTx-d86ou4?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Vegetable & Cream Cheese Stuffed Man    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/N1F5p    
    
    
    Remember my famous stuffed manicotti dish? I'm bringing it back.... Now watch the video! http://fb.me/W3ywVtUe    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/liKrHo    
    
    
    racing to get my last video uploaded!    
    
    
    finally uploading!! YAH... so excited that my hubby could participate this time! :-)    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/HerXGkCsJwQ?a Sexy Chef and hubby make Asaragus, Bacon and Philly Cream Ch    
    
    
    I submitted my recipe on #RealWomenOfPhiladelphia. Check it out here: http://bit.ly/lCjgVB    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/HerXGkCsJwQ?a Sexy Chef and hubby make Asparagus, Bacon and Philly Cream Chee    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/N46Hh    
    
    
    Watch me and Nick make this DELICIOUS stuffed chicken with asparagus, bacon and cream cheese! http://fb.me/xf1WSANF    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/PL4Jx    
    
    
    Love it, great work guys! (@YouTube http://youtu.be/BOwW4Hxi4qw?a)    
    
    
    I subscribed to mirodancetheatre's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/mirodancetheatre?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to mirodancetheatre http://lnk.ms/N9rsG    
    
    
    I subscribed to rashaanp's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/rashaanp?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Subscribed to rashaanp http://lnk.ms/PL62l    
    
    
    Funny thing just happened... I was shopping in Safeway, as I always do picking up some last minute items for a... http://fb.me/13fgm3KWz    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/SYA5FVyD3Xc?a Pineapple Cherry Cheesecake 0001    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/PNHLn    
    
    
    Check it out, perfect dessert for this HOT DAY... Pineapple cherry cheesecake! http://fb.me/BxfomvuU    
    
    
    Pineapple-Cherry Cheesecake http://bit.ly/jK24Dk    
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/SYA5FVyD3Xc?a The Sexy Chef Liz makes Pineapple Cherry Cheesecake    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/PNHLn    
    
    
    watching the videos!    
    
    
        
    
    
    uploading the last video and hoping for total sucess, also visiting with family for the holiday :-)    
    
    
    Neopolitan Puff Pastries http://bit.ly/isBZhz    
    
    
    Check it out, the final video for the Real Women of Philadelphia Competition... we made Neopolitan Style Puff... http://fb.me/R5s9jBWo    
    
    
    Delicious and refreshing summer cheesecake! Pineapple cherry cheesecake! http://fb.me/RVlSevrB    
    
    
    excited for everyone!    
    
    
    Getting ready to hang by the pool and grill some tuna steaks and veggies for lunch :-)    
    
    
    What a nice 

video 
 (@YouTube http://youtu.be/IzyWv3uwF-Q?a)    
    
    
    I commented on a YouTube video http://lnk.ms/Pdj3d    
    
    
        
    
    
    HAPPY THANKSGIVING everyone! Whose cooking today?? Anything delish?    
    
    
    Take a look at this sexy southwestern mac n cheese. :-) http://fb.me/ZUf3YoGa    
    
    
    Good Morning, wouldn't you like to wake up to this Tomato Basil Omelette?? http://fb.me/tZpEuf4Y    
    
    
    Wow... how good do these grilled Pork Chops look? Just sayin... http://fb.me/10GbxWYyS    
    
    
        
    
    
    Look for the Sexy Chef Liz in Mundo Latino! http://fb.me/BEcxC8fO    
    
    
    OMG... the best Shrimp Ever... Spicy Shriacha Shrimp... check it out! http://fb.me/w9tTmvwU    
    
    
    Here is the pic... that Shriacha Shrimp looks, tastes and IS amazing! http://fb.me/103RZn1dA    
    
    
        
    
    
    I love ordering a "Pesto" meal out because I can usually have enough left over pesto to make another 3 meals!    
    
    
    marinara sauce cooking on the stove... can't beat that...    
    
    
    Hope everyone had an amazing 4th... I'll be sharing some of my delishious 4th party dishes in the am.    
    
    
    Check out these amazing side dishes that I made to go along with our crab feast for the 4th of july! http://fb.me/ACv09CSq    
    
    
    Gearing up for an awesome Cooking Demonstration!    
    
    
    Cocktails http://fb.me/AHvZqQdo    
    
    
    OMG LET'S GET TO 400 PEOPLE!!!!!!!    
    
    
    I think the edition of Mundo Latino is out today... and I am in it. YAH. I gotta get my copy... then I'll post the pics!    
    
    
    DELICIOUS. Try this awesome summer side dish of chickpeas, red peppers and peas. It's my new favorite summer side! http://fb.me/18kTOAjcF    
    
    
    getting ready to publish some delish dishes :-)    
    
    
    Check out this DELCIOUS "Leftover" Sauce by the SEXY CHEF Liz http://fb.me/N1pYH15B    
    
    
    "FOLLOW" MY BLOG http://fb.me/Nk4V8VlY    
    
    
    Full Flavor Sandwich Special, try it! http://fb.me/Br585blp    
    
    
    CHECK IT OUT... my recipe is in the magazine MUNDO LATINO!!!!! ChickPea, Peppers & Peas! http://fb.me/FjYWuczd    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sweet Potato Hash Brown?? Oh YES I did! http://fb.me/18AU25dhg    
    
    
    In the mood for some pasta? yeah, me too... you will LOVE this Sun-Dried Tomato & Basil Pesto Pasta with Shrimp! http://fb.me/yHgVX6Me    
    
    
    Need A Recipe or Idea? http://fb.me/WeCnbWVF    
    
    
    Do You Like Peppers? http://fb.me/yMMKQrBl    
    
    
    Super excited that starting NOW, Sexy Chef will appear in every issue of Mundo Latino! Muchos Gracias!... http://fb.me/P4pNnblz    
    
    
    Starving, but gotta hit up the gym to stay lookin' good, then I'm making something delish tonight :-)    
    
    
    PEROGIES. always a go-to meal :-)    
    
    
    Perogies... a little bite of heaven! http://fb.me/GoRhT3VD    
    
    
    Have you Grilled Egglplant? http://fb.me/BfI1lchu    
    
    
        
    
    
    Sexy Chef, taking over the world. http://fb.me/z1iJw5nY    
    
    
    I'm creating a 4 week sexy chef Diet... EXCITED!    
    
    
    Congradulations Chef David, on that delishious crab dish you created... I knew you would win! :-) http://fb.me/SDSXTASM    
    
    
    Sexy Chef... live. http://fb.me/Hye8jgEe    
    
    
    The delicious dish for the day is my one-pot wonder- MEXICAN CHICKEN... try it out and let me know... I think you... http://fb.me/wSOkE77y    
    
    
    week 1 of the 4 week Sexy Chef Diet Plan is almost complete!    
    
    
    I am almost done my SEXY CHEF COOKBOOK!    
    
    
    "Crab" with Seasonal Veggies and Angel Hair http://fb.me/MUVW808C    
    
    
    Mini Sal-Tun Burgers! http://fb.me/Al2DZjZF    
    
    
    Sexy Chef Diet: Week 1
Day 1: 
Breakfast: Wheat Toast with your choice of the following: spray butter, margarine,... http://fb.me/13HxrRfJs    
    
    
    Hey guys, I'm getting ready to travel to Bulgaria... so I will have TONS of great dishes to share... I'll be... http://fb.me/1cGsMAfZ6    
    
    
    Hungry yet? Try this awesome sweet and savory Pistachio Encrusted Honey-Mustard Salmon! http://fb.me/12JayM5aX    
    
    
    Thinking about lunch already? Then try my Sesame & Sprouts Lunch Bagel! http://fb.me/1dQEd6mAB    
    
    
    It's almost dinner... what are you going to make? Try this Hearty Fish Stew! http://fb.me/xE7RX4F9     
    
    
    The countdown for Bulgaria begins... for those of you who don't know, Bulgarian cuisine is similar to Greek... very delicious.    
    
    
    