Check out my tumblr ---> http://thedecorwriter.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Not a fashion blogger, but this was incredibly insightful ---> HOW-TO: Fix The Broken Relationships Between B.. http://bit.ly/p6XWcb    
    
    
    Saw some chairs by the dumpster this afternoon and thought, "those have potential."  I should've grabbed them :-/    
    
    
    @RL_Stine Wow... wonder what %age of those bats are sparkly vampires named Edward?    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo Idris Elba...NO CONTEST!    
    
    
    I've been writing all day.  Have writing cramps.  Need a beer.  S.O.S!    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo What'd I say...it's no contest.  Perry is an okay actor, and Charlie Sheen hasn't acted well since Wall St.    
    
    
    There's a job that I want to apply to, but I need 200+ followers to qualify.  Twitter powers activate! #help    
    
    
    @designsponge BWAHAHAHA!  I don't mean to laugh, but wow.  #notwinning    
    
    
    I love riding on trains.... RT @susanorlean I am never unhappy when I'm on a train.    
    
    
    Hmmm....well now I'm intrigued...@designcrush @heidimjenkins trust me, people would be offended.    
    
    
    I've been feeling inexplicably lazy these past few days....gah :-(    
    
    
    Just found out, via @HuffingtonPost that there'll be #SATC no.3. Why do they keep taking such a ginormous dump on such an awesome t.v. show?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl These little rugrats are too fresh.    
    
    
    This is just pathetic.  That ONE tweet is nearly 2 years old...WTF RT @AJCBuzz BTW has anyone else noticed @AirTran's moribund Twittah?    
    
    
    CHURCH RT@TreatWomenRight #DearEX - Thank you for being the greatest example of what I don't want, helping me realize that I deserve better!    
    
    
    @TreatWomenRight Reading through these tweets while I'm going through a breakup (for the 2nd go-round) and it's a breath of fresh air.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Haven't been yet,don't plan on going.Looked pretty slow on my way to Piedmont Park yesterday.I'm over the bougie burger trend.    
    
    
    HOToberfest Launch Party Elite Event at Ormsby's on #Yelp: Yes.  This event was so awesome.  Not only did I get two ... http://bit.ly/r4qwDv     
    
    
    I feel left out... #whatearthquake    
    
    
    Is there anything the Gosling can't do?? #swoon @Jezebel @JessicaSuarez    
    
    
    Im so there!  RT@AtlanticStation Join us in the park this Thurs for #TheHangover and remember what happens in Vegas...stays in Vegas!!    
    
    
    Good morning, people!    
    
    
    @GiltGroupe I'm very boring...it's black.    
    
    
    Seriously pondering a move to Los Angeles...    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Hey...were you at Burkhart's last night?  I think I recognized you from Yelp.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Me and my friends bought a few.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta I was the one with the afro...lol    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Yep!    
    
    
    Figures...NIN made the list!  RT @pastemagazine The 25 Creepiest Songs About Love :: Blogs :: List of the Day :: Paste http://bit.ly/rhh9tl     
    
    
    Tornado warnings on teevee going off every 15 minutes is starting to irritate me.  Heard there were spottings in Marietta, though.  #ATL    
    
    
    @susanorlean Nothing much to do with all this rain (in GA).    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta And now warnings have been issued for Fulton and Gwinett counties.  Yikes    
    
    
    Apparently, you can say "bullshit" on cable teevee #rizzoliandisles.  I'm not mad, just...surprised.    
    
    
    Good morning, people.  Glad Atlanta wasn't hit too hard by them thar tornadoes...    
    
    
    Sooooo thankful for a break from this blistering heart #atlanta    
    
    
    Pardon my French, but who the FUCK spams on Twitter???? It can't possibly be effective? Yuck...    
    
    
    Just saw an ad for Shellac in this month's @allure_magazine...glad to know that polish actually works :-)@About_Atlanta @sugarcoatbeauty    
    
    
    Page not found... RT@HuffingtonPost Relatives left 70-year-old woman to die after a fall, went out for pizza    
    
    
    @JenRamos I use a shampoo bar from a D.C. company called Pure, and I love Tresemme Moisturizing conditioner.  I mix it with a bit of EEVO.    
    
    
    @AJCBuzz Wow, really?  Dudes are #specialsauce    
    
    
    My goodness those are gorgeous. I should've requested a @LauraMerkin for my bday last week!  Blargh!!! http://gi.lt/pdYDws  via @GiltGroupe    
    
    
    I'm very excited to get back into the blogging game with my blog, Lindsey Lou! Blogs ---> http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    Super duper...let's make it 7 pts/week...My @Klout score is 20. I improved it by 7 points over the past  30 days! http://klout.com/user/LindseyLou84/score-analysis?n=tw&v=daily_welcome …    
    
    
    @CRAVEla Hi! I'm moving here from Atlanta this month and I'd hoped you'd suggest job hunting tips/websites for writers/communications people    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl YUSS....I might actually have to buy that sh*t now #idrinktapwater    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LMAO....slurp.  Boy I'm thirsty all of a sudden pic.twitter.com/SDtNpSv    
    
    
    LMAO at #RonaldRegan trending.  Lawd...    
    
    
    @1q1b Is this big enough fer ya?It's wallpaper that's also a calendar.  found via @designboom ---> http://www.christiaanpostma.nl/index.htm?calendar_wallpaper.htm … pic.twitter.com/ih0wOTo    
    
    
    @GQMagazine Does @idriselba come with that gym membership...seeing as how he's the new face of Smartwater, I think it's only fair.    
    
    
    I must admit, I'm kind of excited for Lion King 3D...    
    
    
    tgif    
    
    
    LOL. I highly doubt they will...@derekblasberg @NYFW    
    
    
    Jonathan Taylor Thomas is now 30 years old.   I'm 27.  I had a crush on him when I was 10.  Geez...    
    
    
    LMAO...#socialmediafail RT@TravelMagazine Why would we follow back...only tweets are "follow back"?!? RT @CharliesFarm  follow back?    
    
    
    Don't Call It a Comeback...: http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/09/dont-call-it-comeback.html#.TmqA-GWEEkE.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    RyanGosling arrives in Toronto to show off #Drive, Ides, and his hotness! http://www.popsugar.com/Ryan-Gosling-Pictures-Arriving-Toronto-Film-Festival-19016928 … via @popsugar He's lookin' fresher than a muh!    
    
    
    I nominate @tessa, RT@chrisguillebeau I'm looking for good role models / examples of women who travel to faraway places    
    
    
    ...watch with glittering eyes the world around you    
    
    
    I was just called "Ma'am" by a young person.... #imgettingold    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta What on Earth is #TheChew?    
    
    
    I feel the same way about @gilt RT@designcrush I think I can now say, with absolute certainty, that I have an addiction to @Fab    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta That sounds like a show I'd watch, so long as there's less chatter and no Hasselbecks.    
    
    
    I've reserved a spot in Oprah's Lifeclass.  Here's a special invite for my friends to come to class too! http://bit.ly/oprahclass     
    
    
    Trying to find a job across the country is a job in and of itself.  #imtired    
    
    
    Thank goodness!!! @allisonkilkenny @Slate    
    
    
    That sounds so nasty...RT @bastylefilegirl "I'm on my way to an asshole festival, and I hear your the headliner"    
    
    
    Hemingway's Letters | Culture | Vanity Fair http://www.vanityfair.com/culture/features/2011/10/hemingway-slideshow-201110?slide=1&mbid=social_retweet … via @VanityFair    
    
    
    Front Page News on #Yelp: I spent practically the whole day walking around our lovely city, visiting the Midtown pop... http://bit.ly/fyQR2d    
    
    
    @TheLoveList I love chest hair.  It's hawt...    
    
    
    Chris Evans (aka Captain America) has THE PERFECT hairy chest.  OMG... @sarahehoward @TheLoveList pic.twitter.com/0zpBYaoU    
    
    
    Could be be much better...According to @Klout, @LindseyLou84's Klout score is 23.  How influential are you? http://klout.com/user/LindseyLou84/score-analysis?n=tw&v=klout_score …    
    
    
    Black women 'should' date/marry, can ya'll leave us be for 10 damn minutes and let us do w/e we want? Thanks/Bye @WSJ http://on.wsj.com/pksh5d     
    
    
    @TheLoveList Niiiiice!    
    
    
    @allisonkilkenny Nope...otherwise he wouldn't be the token.  Duh!    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta LOL...I'm watching it too.    
    
    
    Check out my Tumblr for makeup and beauty enthusiasts!  http://ow.ly/6C5UX    
    
    
    I hope these showers bring cooler temps.  I was getting used to 60' and sunny...    
    
    
    If you're on tumblr, follow me www.beautystoned.tumblr.com where I tumblr makeup and stuff    
    
    
    Super...a "to-do" list for marketers on #facebook http://ow.ly/6DcaC Greeeat! -_-    
    
    
    My favorite pieces from @dolcegabbana Spring 2012 beauty stoned http://ow.ly/6Ei3L    
    
    
    Love @jetsetter and they're #PanAm inspired campaign.  So cute...would love to go back in time to the swingin' 60s! Welcome to the Jet...    
    
    
    Shopping Snapshots: Sept. 22 - Slide Show - NYTimes.com http://ow.ly/6GBMD    
    
    
    Well, now I feel bad for skipping yoga this morning ---> 6 Tips From a 75-Year-Old Inspiration (Can You Do 200 Push Ups?): via...    
    
    
    Ladies listen up ---> 17 Bad Skin Habits to Kick Now http://ow.ly/6MhhJ (I'm guilty of more than a few of these) via @allure_magazine    
    
    
    "3 Mood Mugs" at Twist Design...Hilarious coffee mugs with Happy, Sleepy and Grouchy emoticon faces.  Guess which one I am?  (It's grumpy)    
    
    
    In Less than a Minute Alan Grayson Explains Occupy Wall Street to the 1% http://ow.ly/6SXwF     
    
    
    @gfreelancing As a freelance writer, I'd LOVE to make around $60K or more.   I'm young and single, so that's enough $ for me...for now.    
    
    
    @gfreelancing You'd think that'd be obvious, but unfortunately it is not.  SMDH    
    
    
    @AlecBaldwin Awesome!  Savannah is so gorgeous this time of year.  Might still be hotter than schweddy balls, though...    
    
    
    #FF to some very knowledgeable B2B marketers and magazines @marketingmag @marketingb2b @b2bonlinemktg @b2bmagazine    
    
    
    @mediajobsdaily Right Click, Copy Img URL.  Best job ever...I'd never get work there ---> http://ow.ly/7lPy9     
    
    
    @mediajobsdaily Without the slide's caption? Yeah.  Hmm...    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta lol.  Maybe, just maybe, someone got locked out of their car?  #pipedreams    
    
    
    I am pretty sure we're all being punked by #HermanCain    
    
    
    @celebitchy http://aplusk.posterous.com/twitter-management …    
    
    
    I have a problem spending all my money on @ebay It's a happy problem, though.    
    
    
    I connected Twitter to my http://flavors.me  page - http://flavors.me/lindseylou84     
    
    
    @AJCBuzz It's in the air, drifting off the Savannah river.    
    
    
    FINALLY I'm getting a new phone:  Samsung Conquer from @sprint.  It'll be my first Android, 4G.  It's an early Christmas Gift to myself!    
    
    
    @thebookmaven Just finished Shopgirl last night/this morning (so it still counts for #fridayreads). Felt similar to Mirabelle in a few ways.    
    
    
    I sobbed too... RT @stephenfry: *sob* http://youtube.com/watch?v=_TBd-U …    
    
    
    @1q1b You're in town?!  For how long?    
    
    
    @1q1b What time do you leave on Monday?  I can hang out Sunday night or Monday morning/afternoon!    
    
    
    @GiltGroupe I love dark nail colors: inky blue, gray, deep purple and vampy red <3    
    
    
    W00T!  I'm going to the Downtown Atlanta Scavenger Hunt!  So excited!!!    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Chile please....I won a registration pass.  Felisha's coming, but if you think you know atlanta better, I can switch you two.    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Yeah I know....I might have to consider changing you two. I want to win that $$$!    
    
    
    This weekend, starting Thursday, is going to be #epic.Yelp's Gilded Age, then the ATL Scavenger Hunt and then ATL Streets Alive.  YAY!!!!    
    
    
    Thrive on #Yelp: The decor is nice...but the lighting is a little too ambient (as in...it's hella dark in there).  T... http://bit.ly/fZrPOw    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl I would say Judge got some Juvederm and Botox and maybe a lift. He looks awful though :-(    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl He appears to have shown more restraint than Sylvester Stallone and Mickey Rourke though    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl I don't know why either.  He looks like a dang football and he USED to be such a hottie. SMH.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Nine 1/2 Weeks http://picnica.ciao.com/uk/28607842.jpg    
    
    
    Good morning!    
    
    
    Fantastic giveaway for a Golden Bamboo Tray Table from @RightBankGirl!   I really, really want it, though!  Enter now!    
    
    
    @rightbankgirl LOL...I forgot I'd already won something from you.  Hmmm...a girl can still hope, though.    
    
    
    I received a FREE Spicy Chicken Sandwich from Chick-fil-A. Go to www.getspicychicken.com to get yours!    
    
    
    I'm attending SVEDKA "Sex & The City 2" Premiere Party -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/11p4.  WOOT! WOOT!    
    
    
    @atl365 I went on a scavenger hunt!  We lost but had sooooo much fun!  Thanks again!    
    
    
    Giveaway sponsored by @aptdweller for $25 gift cert to flying biscuit cafe.  I've never been before, so I should win!!!    
    
    
    Too early in the AM for me to try to explain the naming of slaves (during American slavery period) to someone who admits total ignorance.    
    
    
    @atl365 Yes, some of those clues were really difficult.  Don't know where we were placed.  Got 26/46 points.  I would def. do again next yr!    
    
    
    Oh....I have 100 followers.  I need more, though.  How can I do that???    
    
    
    Ok, so this SATC2 "premiere" movie event @Divanatlanta today was #weaksauce.    
    
    
    @TheWhoopiG The real whoopi goldberg @theviewtv just said you're a big, fat phony!    
    
    
    Wondering if and where @therealbigboi is going to perform this evening.  Hmmmm...inquiring minds NEED to know!    
    
    
    @atl365 Murphy's Law???    
    
    
    %m headed to see @therealbigboi at this free concert!  I hope the crowd isn't ridiculous!  Which it will be I'm sure.    
    
    
    @LindseyLou84    
    
    
    Kitschy Kitchenwares http://bit.ly/cGrnZD    
    
    
    The Signal - BMI-based discount is unfair http://bit.ly/d4dXxV    
    
    
    @aplusk It's not really a Hitler mustache.It's a toothbrush mustache and unfortunately,the style was hijacked and is still asso.w/ Hitler.    
    
    
    Yes!  Going to a cookout!    
    
    
    "Everything is everything, after winter must come spring..."    
    
    
    Cami Cakes on #Yelp: Three Words:  Red Velvet Cupcakes

Five Words:  Get thee to Cami's Cakes

Ok, so as I typical S... http://bit.ly/gZWxpP    
    
    
    VICE on #Yelp: Music wasn't bad and I only drank Corona's so I don't know how good the drink's are.  Oh, and a frien... http://bit.ly/hVaKCl    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder Not too shabby.  About to start another query letter.  Completed two proposals today + a blog post. Need some lunch though.    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder I know.  I'm starving.  I'm roasting a chicken so it might be a late lunch :-(    
    
    
    I JUST HAVE FREE 100 TWITTER FANS! http://tinyurl.com/2alu9d3 .    
    
    
    @celebitchy http://www.tmz.com/2011/12/30/katy-perry-divorce-russell-brand/?adid=hero1 …    
    
    
    I don't know about you, but I love the sound of rain just as I'm about to go to bed.  Play this! RainyMood.com http://bit.ly/1pEoI    
    
    
    @scoutmob Scoutmob Miami perhaps???    
    
    
    You should ignore the email I just sent you! lol RT @ajcbuzz:I'm NOT a casting director so don't email me their booty shots.My poor retinas.    
    
    
    Le Petit Marché on #Yelp: Sunday afternoon (around 3 pm) I had a late, and slightly hungover, breakfast with a coup... http://bit.ly/xJyLXO     
    
    
    Sometimes I wish I were Oscar Wilde clever...but was Oscar Wilde ever that clever?Not even he knew what he was talking about 1/2 the time...    
    
    
    Reading: The No. 1 Habit of Highly Creative People http://bit.ly/c5xMut via @zen_habits    
    
    
    @debng Do you want me to leave nasty comment?    
    
    
    @CRAVEatlanta "Pussy Control" by Prince    
    
    
    @mindykaling No one had ever spit on your bald head and wished for luck???  You are talking about Lakers/Celtics game, right?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Or else it gets the hose again??    
    
    
    @chrisguillebeau Do you have any tips/recommendations/issues with flying on standby?Thinking about Brazil in couple months.    
    
    
    If you're down in the game, don't be makin them faces #Celtics.  You heard the man!!!    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Wild Bill was in Shutter Island????  Who'd he play?    
    
    
    91-84....bam!  #DerekFisher is a fine azz mama jama!!!!    
    
    
    Blogging about: Wednesday Giveaway.http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/06/wednesday-giveaway.html. Pls retweet!    
    
    
    WHITE SUPREMACISTS BOYCOTT NEW IDRIS ELBA MOVIE http://bit.ly/hrMhLc    
    
    
    Twitter #failwhale FTL!    
    
    
    SingleBubblePop http://bit.ly/5FzYHb    
    
    
    @Bethenny I'm totally gonna watch it Bethenny.  I can't wait to see it!!!    
    
    
    Just found out I got ROTD on @yelpatlanta for my review of @burkhartspub http://www.yelp.com/biz/burkharts-pub-atlanta#hrid:OkUZBIKfz4y5GueAm4ENUYAAAAAAA … :-)    
    
    
    Twitter looks...different.    
    
    
    Ingmar Swalue: Dutch Photographer http://bit.ly/ddMuUT    
    
    
    Loft Living http://networkedblogs.com/4L7kl    
    
    
    Styled my profile with a sweet theme using Themeleon by @COLOURlovers http://clrlv.rs/newthemeleon Love it?    
    
    
    Taco Mac on #Yelp: On beer selection alone, this place deserves 5 stars.  The only other places where you'll find t... http://bit.ly/wWgCvT     
    
    
    WATCH: Chuck Todd Tears Into Stephen Colbert http://huff.to/yUhxBL  via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
    Shit Social Media Experts #SSMES Say Starring @MyMelodie http://youtu.be/hCqmIRThlxk  #HASHTAG    
    
    
    No to whale burgers.  YES! to Iceland.  Great post>>> http://www.nicoleisthenewblack.com/2012/01/reykjavik-iceland-perfect-escape.html … @nicolenewblack @visitreykjavik @gAdventures    
    
    
    @designcrush Sometimes bad coffee is better than no coffee at all.    
    
    
    Oh... I didn't know I could do Boba Tea at home.  I might have to give this a try! ohjoystudio's photo http://instagr.am/p/jtg_J/  via @instagram    
    
    
    I'm going to have to agree 100% with you on that one.  I loves my gummies  :-) RT@yelpatlanta gummy vitamins for adults: best idea EVER.    
    
    
    Working on query letters on a rainy Monday morning.  I hate rain.  I hate Mondays.  Rainy Mondays = boo!!!    
    
    
    Watching #snl now and shopping on ebay for vintage leather wares: clutches, gloves, shoes, bags.    
    
    
    @aswinn Your paypal email address is all you need to receive payment through Paypal.  You can also invoice a client, etc. through Paypal.    
    
    
    Cafe Intermezzo on #Yelp: I love Cafe Intermezzo.  I've been to this location, and the one on Peachtree in Midtown/... http://bit.ly/ypVKcR     
    
    
    Jammin' at Sweet Georgia's Juke Joint Elite Event on #Yelp: Another GREAT Yelp Event.  I love the idea of pairing u... http://bit.ly/xNMKVo     
    
    
    What in the samhell is #spoonswaggin?    
    
    
    I want to publish a book about booze...they go hand in hand I think.    
    
    
    Twitterers (or is it Tweeters??): #youmusthave slipped because none of you has explained to me the meaning of #spoonswaggin or #forkswaggin!    
    
    
    @Scholarshipscom My 2012 resolution is to graduate from GSU by May 2013 w/ BA in Journo.  Need scholarships, though.  Ran out of fin. aid.    
    
    
    @ATLINtownPaper @time @TIMENewsFeed Where is a good place to view the #lunareclipse in Atlanta tonight?  Any rcommendations...    
    
    
    @susanorlean Happy Birthday to your little one!    
    
    
    @ATLINtownPaper thanks!    
    
    
    a $5,500 bose giveaway: videowave entertainment system | Design For Mankind http://ow.ly/92mnF     
    
    
    @nikimcneill Me too!  I'm heading out for a beer or something.  I keep forgetting to give myself breaks now that i work for myself :-/    
    
    
    @Bethenny It's true Bethenny.  You're totally hilarious.  You're the funniest housewife of them ALL.    
    
    
    #Ihavenorespect for the Congressmen who voted against DADT or the Dream Act.You all are yellow-bellied, insensitive jerks...suck it.    
    
    
    The Moon's Holiday Gift http://www.nasa.gov/connect/chat/moon_gift.html … via @NASA    
    
    
    Good night #Lunar moon.  My lids are getting very heavy...    
    
    
    #DearEx, #ihavenorespect for you.    
    
    
    Beautiful Time Lapse Video of Last Night's Winter Solstice Lunar Eclipse http://tv.gawker.com/5715592/  via @gawkertv    
    
    
    Just got an email with the headline,"You're hired!"Unfortunately,it was from a resume service. Why would they play w/ my emotions like that?    
    
    
    @pattistanger If the hair that grows out of my head is nappy, am I doomed to be single for life?    
    
    
    @AdrianneCurry Ma'am.  You're totally right.  Breastfeeding your baby in public is shit.  GROSS.  What are you 12?    
    
    
    Colbert Reveals Tragedy, Scoffs at D.C. Audience - FishbowlDC http://www.mediabistro.com/fishbowldc/colbert-reveals-tragedy-scoffs-at-d-c-audience_b27500 … via @fishbowldc    
    
    
    @nikimcneill Your home looks nice and roomy.  Have fun making it lovely!    
    
    
    @veganlady7: Sometimes I wonder if @pattistanger, is a curly-haired girl who just doesn't like her own hair...    
    
    
    @MidtownMile @12thandMidtown That light wall is byootiful!!!    
    
    
    Thinking of changing my twitter handle to @lindseylouATL.  Hmmmm    
    
    
    This woman on #whatnottowear NEEDS a haircut....and chill out with that high yellow weave, girl.    
    
    
    Centennial Olympic Park on #Yelp: Centennial Park is my second favorite park (first is Piedmont, naturally) and I lo... http://bit.ly/egnhP3    
    
    
    @tyrabanks I've always been an innie and I do believe I've only cleaned my bellybutton out once.  Sounds gross saying it out loud :-(    
    
    
    @tyrabanks When does the next cycle of #ANTM start, if you don't mind me asking?    
    
    
    Join me in my http://Freelancer.com  Scavenger Hunt team (HoneyBadger)! $50k in prizes! http://scavenger.freelancer.com/  #scavhunt2012    
    
    
    Designer- Konstantin Grcic http://blog.2modern.com/2010/07/designer-konstantin-grcic.html    
    
    
    Unit 2 Fitness on #Yelp: I'm unofficially a part of Yelp's In It to Thin It competition (me against myself?), so I ... http://bit.ly/x9jzym     
    
    
    The government's new #taskforce moniker for #WikiLeaks, #WTF, needs to be a trending topic!  #ASAP!!!!    
    
    
    @officestylist Love those new designer Iphone cases in your office gifts round-up!  I'm way past due for a new one.  #AsksSanta...    
    
    
    Good lawd.... Trey from #TopChefAllStars is fwoine as hell.  There, I said it.    
    
    
    ❒Taken ❒Single ✔ I'm single and ready to mingle: nothing serious, though.    
    
    
    @ConanOBrien Just dropped the #bullshit bomb on live television.  My ears!  My virginal ears!!!!    
    
    
    @About_Atlanta Tito?  Could they not get Germaine or Latoya??    
    
    
    The problem with drinking a pot of coffee at 5 pm is that not only are you wide awake at midnight, you're also seeing a #doublerainbow! J/K    
    
    
    #secretturnon, @ConanOBrien's beard.    
    
    
    @tyrabanks I love the red lips.  Keep them!  (What shade is that called, btw?)    
    
    
    @365Atlanta LOL!  #seriously...I guess Latoya was busy?    
    
    
    Treehouses...for grown-ups http://blog.2modern.com/2010/07/treehousesfor-grownups.html    
    
    
    Opera Nightclub on #Yelp: This was my first time at Opera and I'm writing this while my irritation is fresh in mind.... http://bit.ly/gyBuWS    
    
    
    Idiots at some fake rodeo-clown "news" site called @TheBlaze insinuates that Trayvon Martin was a trouble-maker b/c he was suspended.    
    
    
    @GeraldoRivera is RIDICULOUS.Saying that as minorities we should avoid wearing hoodies, but white kids get to wear hoodies #separatebutequal    
    
    
    @NoReservations No Reservations is unguent.    
    
    
    @Bethenny I've cut the end of the toothpaste tube to get that last little bit out.  It' not a proud moment for me, needless to say...    
    
    
    It's so late that #Cheers is on. Good night everyone!    
    
    
    Lindsey Lu! Blogs Blogging About: Stylish on a Bike http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/stylish-on-bike.html    
    
    
    5 Ways to Market Yourself During a Recession http://bit.ly/IJXFC (via @the99percent) Great advice!    
    
    
    @TXWriter Great...writing a proposal.  How are you?    
    
    
    @OldSpice Will u give the "lesbian shittasses" @Jezebel a shout out please?We're huge fans...especially me.Pretty please with sugar on it?    
    
    
    ...just went on a twitter-following frenzy.  follow. follow.  follow.  #thatsaproblem    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is blogging about Etsy/Bicyles: http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/etsy-roundup-bicycles.html    
    
    
    @OldSpice voicemail is so manly, that it's awesome:http://oldspicevoicemail.com/female.html  LOLZ    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs: The Little White Dress http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/little-white-dress.html    
    
    
    If you don't make out with your S.O. after they've eaten massive amounts of garlic or onions, #thatsaproblem.  I know from experience :-/    
    
    
    #AGoodRelationship is "like friendship on fire" ~Bruce Lee~    
    
    
    @Foodista #foodquestion How do we get #cookies as trending topic? I'm  eating some fresh cornmeal-lemon sugar cookies and they're heaven!    
    
    
    #thistweetisdedicated2 #cookies.    
    
    
    The Universe House http://bit.ly/9OOCci    
    
    
    @Scholarshipscom The most important thing I learned this year is that patience pays off, and that you're never too old to return to school.    
    
    
    Yelp's Hall of Fame on #Yelp: As per usual, Kathleen M. put together a fabulous event.  I met some old friends, mad... http://bit.ly/HiFFQ8     
    
    
    @NoReservations Hmmm...Akara (which is bean fritters with hot sauce) and then my friend makes ginger beer and peanut chicken.    
    
    
    @KaiseratCB Don't know if you watched Dancing w/ Stars, but JLove was there, cheering for Maksim, said he was "Hot."  Trolling for dates?    
    
    
    I just LOVE it when a client does not pay me in a timely, efficient manner.  Hurrah for freelancing?    
    
    
    Congrats to #Hefner:  Older than my grandma (75) and marrying a chick who's younger than me (26).    
    
    
    #melgibsonruinseverything It's true!    
    
    
    Drinking subpar red wine just so that I can get a little drunkyity drunk drunk drunk?  #betterthanbeingmelgibson.    
    
    
    #melgibsonruinseverything    
    
    
    R.I.P. #TeenaMarie    
    
    
    Stuffing my mouth with delicious, buttery shortbreads because it's still the holidays.    
    
    
    #2010memories When my boyfriend emailed me to tell me he'd moved to Minneapolis a week after he'd moved there.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Carrot cake goes bad if you don't eat it right away,  #logicwin    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Yes...probably.  You could wait and find out...and then be disappointed with crusty, dry cake.    
    
    
    @Hokuboku I just saw Nude Nuns w/ Big Guns yesterday.  Not bad...reminded me of Machete a little bit.    
    
    
    I've a portfolio website, you know!  www.lindsey-gregory.com...
#thingsyoudidntknowaboutme    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Now trying to "Find a Way" to #employment.  Still #betterthanbeingmelgibson though    
    
    
    @EverythingATL OMG!  I'm glad that woman on Marta is okay.  That sounds horrifying.    
    
    
    @yelpatlanta take me with you on vacation please!?  I will bring chocolate cookies.    
    
    
    I don't appreciate it when people ask for your help at a certain time and then are late.  Perpetually late.    
    
    
    Decorating the Sky - http://bit.ly/e4lAfG (via @NASA) Absolutely Gorgeous!!    
    
    
    Why do #writers have such crappy websites?Not that mine is any better (it's not), but I've seen some oogly ones tonight.#workingonit though.    
    
    
    I completed C25K Week 3 Day 1 (--- miles), in 00:15:00, pace 12:55 min/mile, with @RunDouble http://bit.ly/nkhPg3     
    
    
    Watching Family Guy, drinking #coffee and getting some proposals done...then some ashtanga at noon!    
    
    
    Surin of Thailand on #Yelp: I love the food here.  I first came here years ago for a friend's surprise birthday and ... http://bit.ly/aEdZqm    
    
    
    Blossom Tree on #Yelp: I had been feeling adventurous last week and while downtown last week, rather than heading t... http://bit.ly/K59iQs     
    
    
    I feel like such a lame for not really caring about #teamfalcons v. #Aints.  However, as an Atlantan, I'm always default #teamfalcons.    
    
    
    Good morning, good morning, thank you, good morning!    
    
    
    @designcrush Funny Face was much better....there I said it!    
    
    
    it's difficult to assure clients of my freelance fees when they are unfamiliar with the freelance/writing process...haven't figured that out    
    
    
    Birth control!Birth control!Birth control! Until you can control your fertility,you will not be able to control your life~Judge Lynn Tohler~    
    
    
    When will @NoReservations be in Atlanta???  Should I start a petition or something? U watch the show @AJCBuzz?  What do you think?    
    
    
    "I write when I'm inspired, and I see to it that I'm inspired at nine o'clock every morning” ~ Peter De Vries~ (if only)    
    
    
    @TXWriter I've been calling myself a 'copywriter & content strategist' who freelances...hopefully that sounds more professional.    
    
    
    What is #hentai ?    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon #ifihadasuperpower,I'd be able to break into the disposal area in the nice neighborhoods,get the good furniture,no cops called.    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon, I'd fly Sarah Palin to the moon...and leave her there.  #ifihadasuperpower.    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon #ifihadasuperpower, it'd be the ability to get as many followers as @ladygaga...a girl can dream.    
    
    
    Someone please tell my firefox to behave!!!    
    
    
    hello: http://wp.me/pJpwc-ch    
    
    
    hello...again: http://wp.me/pJpwc-cs    
    
    
    @downandoutchic Have you checked out ebay or amazon for the film, yet?    
    
    
    "The path to success is to take massive, determined action."
~Anthony Robbins    
    
    
    "There's nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and open a vein." 
~Walter Wellesley Smith    
    
    
    Quotes About Writing: http://wp.me/pJpwc-cV    
    
    
    Free Personal signatures - cool!: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d1    
    
    
    Anatolia Cafe on #Yelp: I have the dangerous (not really) habit of walking by a restaurant 100 times before I final... http://bit.ly/IMaQk8     
    
    
    I use baby oil gel to moisturize my skin at night and I'm still ashy in the morning.  #blackgirlproblems    
    
    
    Freelance (Writer) Panic: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d4    
    
    
    @officestylist Can I drink this mask too??  That would awesome!    
    
    
    #whitechicks the movie? or #whitechicks that terrible song by trina???  neither    
    
    
    Reading:  "It's Not How Good You Are, It's How Good You Want To Bo."  by Paul Arden...good stuff.    
    
    
    House Tour: Villa Dali http://bit.ly/a9G5mN    
    
    
    Quote of the Day & Weekend Links: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d7    
    
    
      http://bit.ly/9PKZuz    
    
    
    Heard some INTERESTING news about #Inception.If only the audience I saw it with hadn't let out "WTF" I'd have heard the totem fall too!    
    
    
    #CelebPerfumes usually suck...who wants to smell like Halle Berry or Jennifer Anniston?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LOL!  Esp. Janniston.  I heard it smells like cats and tears of sadness.    
    
    
    @veganlady7 Beyonce Heat is ok.  The only #CelebPerfume I truly like is SJP's Lovely and Covet and JLos Glow.  Other ones usually suck.    
    
    
    #TuckerCarlson hypocrite:Mark11:25 if you hold anything against anyone,forgive him, so that your Father in heaven may forgive you your sins.    
    
    
    USHER’S O.M.G SONG RIPPED FROM “HOMER SIMPSON”? http://ow.ly/1rYVg8 LOL...wasn't Will.i.Am sued by Daft Punk for ripping one of their songs?    
    
    
    I was at @TheFoxTheatre to see Massive Attack and thievery Corporation!  Would love to see Lady Antebellum this week.  Hint!    
    
    
    La Fonda Latina on #Yelp: I live down the street and today was only my second time dining here.  I'd gone here befor... http://bit.ly/frVkt0    
    
    
    @ChrisBrown has a major case of 'foot-in-mouth disease' #homophobe, #growup    
    
    
    @themoment Gianni Versace (I think) never made a guest appearance.  AbFab is one of my favorite shows, btw.    
    
    
    @scoutmob I love the fish stew at Six Feet Under    
    
    
    @BFGCom Communications is like prostitution.  First you do it for love...then you do for it money.  #contentmanagerapplication    
    
    
    @piersmorgan You've got some big suspenders to fill.  (Bet you haven't heard that one before...kidding.)  Best of luck to you!    
    
    
    @jenramos I'm seriously envying your walk-in closet and shoe collection.  Very impressive...    
    
    
    LOL @#TitoJackson trending... oh lawd.    
    
    
    I really hate MARTA.  Wish we had the MTA!  Actually I wish I was in NYC.  Three buses to get to midtown is just retarded! #wishuponastar    
    
    
    Apres Diem on #Yelp: Ok...this isn't French food at all.  

Now that that's out the way...I do like the atmosphere. ... http://bit.ly/ikkqrO    
    
    
    Trader Joe's on #Yelp: Um...hello: new favorite wine shop.  Very affordably priced and a decent selection to boot. http://bit.ly/g6alCW    
    
    
    Landmark Midtown Art Cinema on #Yelp: Independent films + Booze = Win!

Also...I really like that they offer those p... http://bit.ly/hX0gAy    
    
    
    I just might win $3000 to explore with @scoutmob, @jetsetterdotcom & @joyus. Join me: http://scoutmob.com/scoutjetshop/scoutmobangel …    
    
    
    Listening to this Lay it Down w/ Lloyd and Labelle.  What is this #hotmess ?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Agreed...why is gramma singing about layin it down???    
    
    
    I have that 2:30 feeling.   I need a nap and some coffee.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl What the heck is formspring?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Yeah...never heard of it.    
    
    
    why is it so dang hot???    
    
    
    #ScottPilgrim is out today???  Might have to see that one tonight, then.    
    
    
    Modern Pool Party http://bit.ly/a80gnQ    
    
    
    Happy New Year!!!!    
    
    
    via http://huff.to/dUlgrz via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
    Buffy the Vampire Slayer marathon!  YAY!!!    
    
    
    Zucca on #Yelp: 1/365

After walking around downtown Decatur for like 1/2 hour to find something to eat, we finally ... http://bit.ly/eJhJl9    
    
    
    Good morning everyone and hello Sunday!    
    
    
    @365Atlanta Hey, do you know anything about the Ferris Wheel that was downtown last night?  Did I miss something???    
    
    
    @365Atlanta But they are sooo much fun!    
    
    
    @downandoutchic Love your Holga Photos...they came out great!    
    
    
    “I just entered to win a Damn You Alexis Piece on #TheCurvyFashionista and YOU should too!  http://tinyurl.com/2fgbt59 Enter then RT!“    
    
    
    Meet the Browns is not funny... #stoppretending and #changethechannel !    
    
    
    Probably still in the middle of re-designing my blog, but, so far so good.  What do you all think?  http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/blog-post.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Strange Man: You cute, you Jamaican? From the islands?
Me: No.
#blackgirlproblems    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon Will there be a Late-Night App for those of us who aren't fancy enough to have iPhones sometime soon??    
    
    
    Slice on #Yelp: I like this place.  It's a great location in downtown Atlanta, on a quiet street and, as a sat at the… http://bit.ly/Mispsi     
    
    
    @garyvee Rose de Rioja (I think I spelled that right)    
    
    
    I like Jennifer Hudson, but why is she oversinging "Feelin Good" in that Weight Watchers commercial???    
    
    
    I really don't feel like working on a Sunday.  Time to open up a bottle of red, watch some SATC DVDs and parse through some mags.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl #EpicSunday?  I knew it...screw work.  #getswinedrunk    
    
    
    Sings, "I want to get away, I want to fly away...yeah yeah yeah!"    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl In GA, we call them shrimps.  #blackgirlproblems    
    
    
    Just wanted to come out on Twitter and let ya'll know I got my 1st pair of skinny jeans and I've worn them out 3 days in a row now :-(    
    
    
    @Lara_Christina LOL...my butt looks so good in them as do my thighs for some reason.  So...enjoy the view?    
    
    
    In Toni Morrison's Sula, birds falling out the sky was an omen.For some it was bad.For others,might have been seen as good/necessary change.    
    
    
    The Shelter on #Yelp: You know those really seedy bars in movies or teevee that look like kind of skanky, but also k... http://bit.ly/eExozR    
    
    
    @AJCBuzz @ajc  The protest against the renaming of Cone and Harris Sts. is at 1 pm tomorrow, but where?    
    
    
    Wait...was that a stupid question?  Probably...    
    
    
    @jenramos Hey Jen, OWN is on 131 if you've got DirecTV.    
    
    
    #2011rules:  Stick to my writing goals!    
    
    
    FROM THE RIGHT BANK in the Independent http://shar.es/XIFvS     
    
    
    Stone Mountain Park on #Yelp: I can't believe I've lived in Atlanta all of 23 years, and I had never so much as hiked… http://bit.ly/MCTTvV     
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! is Blogging About eBay Finds: Vintage "Hollywood Regency" Pieces http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/ebay-finds-vintage-hollywood-regency.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @MargaretAtwood There should be a bar at the top of your page with a search box next to where it says home, profile, etc.    
    
    
    Bored with your closet? Make like ze French http://huff.to/dHybVF via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
    Congrats @AphroChic on being featured in @ElleDecor.  Love the pillows! http://www.elledecor.com/home-shopping/articles/playful-patterns    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Are you referring to JHud's turble rendition of "Feelin Good"? I can't stand that #hotmess!    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogging About:  Wishlist:  Driving Gloves http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/wishlist-driving-gloves.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Looking for new clients...need marketing collateral?  Blog posts?  Website content?  DM me!    
    
    
    I think I've finally figured it out...the only way to get a job these days is to work as an 'intern'...for free...  #nojoke    
    
    
    I checked in at Roll Me (67 Park Place NE) on #Yelp http://bit.ly/IEvDaA     
    
    
    You pray for rain, you gotta deal with the mud too. That's a part of it.
Denzel Washington    
    
    
    Color Trends- 2011 Color Trends for Spring 2011 at Refinery29.com http://www.refinery29.com/2011-color-trends-for-spring-2011.php … via @refinery29    
    
    
    OhEmGee, my pretend husband, @idriselba, is on Twitter!!!!!
#faintsfromexcitement    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LOL....I know I know.  I'm totally off my stalker game :-(    
    
    
    Where'd the day go?  I still have work to do and already after 7!!!!  Maybe I need to lay off Twitter and facebook...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    #JenniferHudson ruined "Feelin Good" in that new commercial.  Took a beautiful, subdued, melancholic song and butchered it.    
    
    
    Has anyone used Google phone service yet?  I might try it out today    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AphroChic Moleskin 12 mth Daily Planner    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging About: Designer Spotlight:  2Michaels http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/designer-spotlight-2michaels.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Watching the new Bachelor on Hulu... why does the intro feel like a "Body by Gilead" video??? #hotmess    
    
    
    Piedmont Park on #Yelp: #Yelp365
4/365

This park, designed by the fellow in NYC who designed Central Park, is my fa... http://bit.ly/geyseH    
    
    
    Happy Birthday!!!: http://bit.ly/cJiuOv via @addthis    
    
    
    Fixin to write a query letter...wish me luck!    
    
    
    SOOOOO thankful for a cool morning today.    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging About Her Wednesday Giveaway!!! http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/wednesday-giveaway.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Wednesday Giveaway!!! http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/wednesday-giveaway.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Chic, Small Spaces http://networkedblogs.com/7s2Fl    
    
    
    Red Shoe Diaries http://networkedblogs.com/7spLh    
    
    
    @simonpegg I just watched Hot Fuzz a couple of days ago.  CC tends to butcher everything...not even South Park is safe.  >:(    
    
    
    Kroger on #Yelp: #Yelp365
5/365

So...I just loaded up on a cart full of groceries at this location and I'm sure I s... http://bit.ly/ge21pM    
    
    
    I'm going to brew some much needed coffee #andthenihitmydougie    
    
    
    "Ah, but a man's reach should exceed his grasp,
or what's a heaven for?" ~Robert Browning~    
    
    
    New Jersey...Dresses! http://networkedblogs.com/7usNi    
    
    
    Modern Book Cases http://blog.2modern.com/2010/09/modern-book-cases.html    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging About:  Dream House Tour: L\ http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/dream-house-tour-lappartement-de-pierre.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Oh....Matt Damon, one of my #Pretendhusbands is in town shooting a movie.  SQUEE!!!!    
    
    
    I love everything about this girl's outfit!  EVERYTHING: http://glo.msn.com/style/sidewalk-style-16-6332.gallery?photoId=26346    
    
    
    Highland Inn Ballroom Lounge on #Yelp: #Yelp365
6/365

Not a bad spot.  Came here for the 2011 Creative Loafing Fict... http://bit.ly/e6cwE7    
    
    
    Sigh....failing at my New Year's Resolution to get more sleep.    
    
    
    #fridayreads I'm going to start Consider the Lobster later today    
    
    
    Parker's on Ponce on #Yelp: If I had more money, I would make it a habit to have a couple of glasses of red wine and … http://bit.ly/PQZlrU     
    
    
    I checked in at Noodle on #Yelp http://www.yelp.com/biz/8PodPpkZPqud0_uQJPfYuA?pt=check_in&ref=twitter&v=4b …    
    
    
    @michaelianblack Chad Kroeger...that name sounds familiar.  Did his family create a line of grocery stores by any chance?    
    
    
    I would love to travel all around the world someday.  How do I make this haapen even though I am #finaciallychallenged?  Stowaway???    
    
    
    Just heard  about #repgabriellegiffords, what a tragedy.  Praying for her and all others who were harmed to pull through.    
    
    
    @MarkToro @MidtownATL I miss Midtown :-(    
    
    
    Copywriting: B2B Print Ad for Maryln Nutraceuticals, Inc. http://wp.me/pJpwc-g7     
    
    
    Editorial: Architecture of the Mind http://wp.me/pJpwc-gq     
    
    
    Editorial: Ghost of a Chair http://wp.me/pJpwc-gH     
    
    
    Editorial: Tree Bookshelf http://wp.me/pJpwc-gL     
    
    
    Editorial: Origami-Inspired Decor http://wp.me/pJpwc-gO     
    
    
    Contributing Blogger: Design Shuffle, Inc. http://wp.me/pJpwc-gS     
    
    
    Website Content: Brand New Black http://wp.me/pJpwc-gY     
    
    
    @TheWoodruff My favorite artist is Kara Walker!    
    
    
    Social Media: Sam's Beauty Blog http://wp.me/pJpwc-h6     
    
    
    I completed C25K Week 1 Day 1 (--- miles), in 00:16:36, pace 12:55 min/mile, with @RunDouble http://bit.ly/nkhPg3     
    
    
    I'm getting a pack of #MOO cards because I've got Klout - thanks to @overheardatmoo! You can too, just click here: http://klout.com/perk/Moo/MooCards?passalong=Mzc0LzEwNjA0NzcvMg&passalongSig=60dd0e918cb5adec511083245e69dc3d7ac62be72c611dfcdb505350a9bc56ac&n=tw&v=perks_completed_passalong&i=1060477 …    
    
    
    "Whip My Hair" is about to become my new ringtone. I said GOTTDAMN...Willow!!!! Ma'am! #groupthink http://bit.ly/ag2eHM    
    
    
    The Sound Table on #Yelp: The food and cocktails more than made up for the spotty service last night.  Came here on a… http://www.yelp.com/biz/w02cwFS07Iq_XVyip5_yyw?hrid=zSeR5uIZmSZDFvC8M9s7mg&pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3 …    
    
    
    The Corner Pub on #Yelp: Meh.

Their collards are whack. Not spicy.  Not meaty or smoky.  Not even seasoned.  Come on… http://www.yelp.com/biz/DMh7G_c0BA0ZF20m5G2eMg?hrid=rVN4xzCfko6YwRRthP_PhA&pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3 …    
    
    
    #SNOWBALLFIGHT in the AM!!!    
    
    
    Good morning!!  and Happy Monday!    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN that's because trey songz is wack as hell.  Yah!    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging About:  Wishlist:  Wool Capes http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/wishlist-wool-capes.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Your husband is hilarious...lol.    
    
    
    And the winner is.... http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/and-winner-is.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    I entered @artblt’s giveaway for 2 tix to #ATL’s @tasteofatlanta. UR a #Foodie if you do!    
    
    
    @TheFoxTheatre Holy shizz....Ms.Jackson (cuz I'm nasty) at the Fox??? #SQUEE    
    
    
    All American Package Store on #Yelp: #Yelp365
#6/365

I'm writing this store's first and only review specifically to... http://bit.ly/hjtxPE    
    
    
    Romney's face looks so ... weird when he's listening to POTUS speak.  Is he mesmerized? Is he confused? I don't know.  #debates    
    
    
    Thank goodness for that..."@ABFalecbaldwin: Mitt likes Big Bird"    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon Can the roots make this happen?"@Bonkano: Romney autotuned remix: I like coal. I love Big Bird. I like coal. I love Big Bird.    
    
    
    "@JensenClan88: A "teacher" in Vegas? SURE. #debates" everyone knows there are no teachers in Vegas...    
    
    
    "@Lara_Christina:Romney looks like he has damp fear sweat in his silk boxers." Sweat doesn't come off silk easily either. PO thang. #debates    
    
    
    "@VanityFair: Romney is BETTER @ making complex points into coherent sound bites!" Add to that, 'I like Big Bird. I like you too.' #debates    
    
    
    "@refinery29: I'm 54!" You had better listen up, then!    
    
    
    "@designcrush: Smirkapalooza."    
    
    
    "@refinery29: What's that on #Romney's flag pin? A bullet hole? A tiny camera? #debates" His master switch???    
    
    
    Why is Romney's flag pin so damn big?  What's he trying to compensate for? #debates    
    
    
    And go to ER with a tummyache. "@Nardster: Romney's health care plan: Give everyone a bottle of Flintstones Vitamins. #debate"    
    
    
    Wait Romney doesn't like Obamacare simply because no Republicans voted for it? #debate    
    
    
    I heard the number 47... y'all.  POTUS time to pull that trump card. #debate    
    
    
    "@oliviawilde: Mitt is smirky, sweaty, indignant and smug with an unsettling hint of hysteria. And he wants to kill BIG BIRD. #debate2012"    
    
    
    These #debates need at least one intermission and two bathroom breaks    
    
    
    @jenramos YAYAYAYAYAYAAYAYAYAYAY!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Thank you!    
    
    
    I completed C25K Week 1 Day 1 (--- miles), in 00:18:30, pace 12:55 min/mile, with @RunDouble http://bit.ly/nkhPg     
    
    
    I feel like this moderator is NOT moderate #VPdebtate    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Watch it anyway...    
    
    
    Leading questions...who is this lady??? #VPdebate    
    
    
    I appreciate that she moves right on to the next subject though...not gonna let these ppl talk and talk and talk #VPdebate    
    
    
    How do you change the Taliban's mind so that they no longer want to blow us up, PAUL RYAN??? #VPdebate    
    
    
    "If I'm not mistaken....Gov. Romney said the same thing.  Changes mind so often, I could be wrong."  #dead #VPdebate    
    
    
    "I've had it up to here..."  Git em Joe!! #VPdebate    
    
    
    I love it that Biden is laffing his ass off at this fool ass Lyin Ryan.    
    
    
    "Show me a policy," #VPdebate    
    
    
    "Can you send me some stimulus money?" Paul Ryan groveled for moolah from Biden/Obama for WI???  #VPdebate    
    
    
    Joe Biden is showing up in a way that POTUS should have showed up last week and how he should show up for the next two debates.    
    
    
    @TeaKuma Maybe he needs to be the angry black man who is tired of the malarkey and has had it up to here with their old ideas/lies.    
    
    
    @HuffingtonPost Biden is whooping Ryan's tail with facts, numbers and those letters about stimulus $ for WI.    
    
    
    "Try to scare ppl into voting for you." Isn't that what the Romney/Ryan campaign is doing?    
    
    
    "I gave you a simple answer: he's raising the cost of Medicare."  #wompwomp #VPdebates    
    
    
    "Just let the taxes expire!" HELLO?!??!!?  Duh!  #VPdebates    
    
    
    @SamuelLJackson Is that Native American an employee?    
    
    
    "I just fundamentally disagree with my friend."  #abortion #vpdebate #biden    
    
    
    @Refinery29 You're kidding right?  Paul Ryan is choking on his own lies.    
    
    
    Nobody is perfect? @LeahMOB  My parents are so smart. Extremely middle class. And are republican... :(    
    
    
    Paul Ryan if you say "Uniquely Qualified," one more goddamn time, I will lay you on my knee and tan that hide.    
    
    
    Check out the ShoeMoney Training System for alot of great free information: http://shmny.me/T6zzXU     
    
    
    Reading: "Half Off Depot! Deal of the Day!"( http://twitthis.com/ix73zj  )    
    
    
    I'm soooo unbelievably excited about the give-away that I won yesterday.  I'm still screaming, scaring the dog!!! Blogging about it Friday!    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs: Tuesday Giveaway: http://bit.ly/bcnGJK via @addthis    
    
    
    Please take a look: http://www.lindseyhgregory.com  RT @tkhonji Looking for freelance copywriter to work w/ us on brochures,website copy annual report.    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs: Where the Wild Things Are: http://bit.ly/a6ZqIn via @addthis    
    
    
    My goal is to finish this by the end of the year !! Wish me luck #C25K http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407486971319/ …    
    
    
    Look what I found on @eBay! http://r.ebay.com/XW7jbE  ASUSTeK COMPUTER Maximus V Extreme, LGA 1155 Motherboard #forsale    
    
    
    TechCrunch Giveaway: A New Samsung Chromebook #TechCrunch http://techcrunch.com/2012/10/19/techcrunch-giveaway-a-new-samsung-chromebook-techcrunch/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Noodle on #Yelp: What can I say?  This place hits the spot. A few pumpkin ciders (don't knock it til you've tried it) … http://www.yelp.com/biz/-NKkPTYeDYqV6cdWskHpNQ?hrid=KE-6cR4abIgDRMholsYARA&pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3 …    
    
    
    If I don't leave the house today, I'm going to go "The Shining" ala Jack Nicholson...All snow and no play makes Lindsey Lou! go crazy!    
    
    
    Cypress Street Pint & Plate on #Yelp: I've walked by this place about 101 times on my semi-daily walks in Midtown an... http://bit.ly/bCoWdK    
    
    
    @tyrabanks Idris Elba SHOULD HAVE WON for Luther!  Duh...    
    
    
    Sweetwater Creek State Park on #Yelp: I've been going on outdoor adventures with le boyfriend and my besties for the p… http://www.yelp.com/biz/IXmKPmG-aBd2YEyQKODabQ?hrid=iQZMgVgdvs7B6O24z3xLjw&pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3 …    
    
    
    Taki Japanese Steak House on #Yelp: Came here this past weekend for a birthday party for a friend and  I'm pretty su... http://bit.ly/cOOatY    
    
    
    Compound on #Yelp: Here's what annoys me about the compound:  1)  Before midnight, it appears to be a chick fest, bu... http://bit.ly/9Ny9jr    
    
    
    Amicalola Falls State Park and Lodge on #Yelp: Another GORGEOUS GA park. 

Located in Dawsonville, the Amicalola State… http://www.yelp.com/biz/yMYs_RywdgDdFZp1ceGHEg?hrid=FmuZnwsuN_DDJUSM_0iLkg&pt=review&ref=twitter&v=3 …    
    
    
    I'm thinking my friends and me (I?) are in desperate need of Luther marathon...or maybe a Stringer marathon?  An Idris Elba Marathon?  All??    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging about:  Hmmmm:  Angled Nesting Shelves http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/hmmmm-angled-nesting-shelves.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo I wouldn't say I'm vindictive.  I do tend to hold grudges and maybe that affects my behaviour towards the begrudged.    
    
    
    @unguides Dude....I would love some free United miles and I am in desperate need of a long vacation.    
    
    
    Green Hornet was a terrible movie.  #hotmess   Seriously, Seth Rogen hasn't been funny since 40 Year Old Virgin...    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! is Blogging About ... Home/Studio Tour:  Lazaro Rosa-Violan http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/homestudio-tour-lazaro-rosa-violan.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @1q1b QUESHIA!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!  Hey!!!    
    
    
    Atlanta Book Exchange on #Yelp: I remember my first foray into ABE; it was 2000 and I had to buy some books for my h... http://bit.ly/cDsBYx    
    
    
    Joe Cariati Petite Decanters.  Gorgeous..Colorful....Fun....Want:  I\ http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/im-loving_19.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    WATCH: Comedian To Receive $1 Million Just For Asking http://huff.to/gQpNt1 via @huffingtonpost-->I can do one better.Can I have $3 million?    
    
    
    Old men are ridiculous:  no gramps, you can't have my phone number!  Gross...    
    
    
    Just caught adv. screening of No Strings Attached, @aplusk and @mindykaling were hilariously hilarious + charmingly charming...as usual :-)    
    
    
    AMC Parkway Pointe 15 on #Yelp: #Yelp365
8/365

Great theater.  Caught the adv. screening of No Strings Attached (go... http://bit.ly/hXyaO5    
    
    
    Amplifyd Platform Pump by Steven by Steve Madden on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376132/ …    
    
    
    Madee Loafer by Steven by Steve Madden on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376140/ …    
    
    
    Brown Tortoiseshell Oversized Frame by Matthew Williamson by Linda Farrow on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376146/ …    
    
    
    Cashmere Jersey Perfect V-Neck by Firth on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376186/ …    
    
    
    Cashmere Ribbed Jersey Short Sleeve Tee by Firth on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376192/ …    
    
    
    Parissa Ballet Flat by Vince Camuto Shoes on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376199/ …    
    
    
    Rose Gold & Diamond Wrap Ring by Vendoro on http://Gilt.com  #giftme http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376230/ …    
    
    
    Dogs by Abrams on Gilt Home #giftme (Cause I love #doggies!) http://pinterest.com/pin/211317407487376361/ …    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl What's wrong with Jackie Chan?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Yeah...I really hate those last-minute bidders too.  Missed out on a $20-something vintage DVF because of onadem >:(    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LOL...awww.  Bless her heart.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LOL She said look ma no hands... way too early for that!    
    
    
    Lookbook: Vintage Trench http://www.polyvore.com/cgi/set?id=27319264    
    
    
    @1q1b Are you sure you're not actually dialling a sex hotline???    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is Blogging About: Lookbook: The Vintage Trench http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/lookbook-vintage-trench.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    "Besides Ye, they can't stand besides me.  Just killed another career, it's a mild day..."    
    
    
    @MrsLimestone I'm home alone...well, my dog is here.  But I'm not any conferences or networking events :-/    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder I used my smartphone once when my Internet went out.  Desperate times call for desperate measures.    
    
    
    @allisonkilkenny not at all.  That kid is a kind of a sweltering douchebag.    
    
    
    #FF My favorite magazines---> @bust_magazine @NylonMag @bostonmagazine @bonappetitmag @ELLEDECOR @FlauntMagazine @GQMagazine @voguemagazine    
    
    
    #FF My favorite bloggers ----> @AllyFTRB @downandoutchic @designcrush @habituallychic @jenramos @nikimcneill @MrsLimestone @Style369    
    
    
    @blogfest2011 Just added my name to waitlist for BlogFest 2011.  I really hope I can get squeezed in :-/    
    
    
    Thanks for all the #FF.  Time to sign off and get dinner and a bottle of Two Buck Chuck from trader joe's.    
    
    
    I'm wearing a trench coat that's older than me!  #IHeartVintage and @eBay_Fashion    
    
    
    @1q1b Make it yourself...    
    
    
    I need a vacation.    
    
    
    via @TheOnion...White Girl...Tried As Black Adult http://onion.com/fh4ZNK  "This is america, nobody deserves to be treated as a black man." LOL    
    
    
    @FashionOffice @KimKardashian HAHAHAAHA....some folks are very self-serving Ruth :-(    
    
    
    Oh...these allergies are redonk!    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl @BreakingNews Oh No!!!  :-(    
    
    
    Womp,Womp,Womp...Steve Harvey's Ex-Wife Of 16 Years BLASTS Steve On Cheating on Her With Other Women...Including Ma.. http://bit.ly/eREVV2    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs ---> An Eclectic, Artistic Home Office http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/eclectic-artistic-home-office.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    @thedecorista Love that room!  it's gorgeous!    
    
    
    @susanorlean That sounds very high.  Think they might lose $ by charging for online access?    
    
    
    @365Atlanta @advtastes Even worse that it's yet another gourmet burger joint.  I thought ATL was at capacity for gourmet burgers...    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder So far so good.  Will need more coffee though...    
    
    
    @eBay Just discovered this "eBay To Go" tool and I love it sooo hard.    
    
    
    eBay Wishlist:  Vintage Wool Coats http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/01/ebay-wishlist-vintage-wool-coats.html … via @AddThis    
    
    
    Just scored a $25 gift certificate from @Restaurant_com for $3...I'm going to buy a few more of these.    
    
    
    @headshell Thanks for that list.I was wondering what to add for me and my BFF's @idriselba movie night.Hard part's choosing what to watch    
    
    
    @MrsHopple I'm gonna have my friend take pics of me in it tomorrow, but here's the coat via poshvintage:  http://bit.ly/gJepG2    
    
    
    Google says it "can't find the Server" at World Star Hip Hop.  Guess it's true that 50 kilt that ish... Po thangs    
    
    
    OMG...this barking dog needs to shut up NOW.    
    
    
    @aswinn I would not be surprised if she did that herself.  Who the eff *wakes up* with a black eye.  Was she sleep-fighting and lost??    
    
    
    @simonpegg Why bother trying come up something new AND funny when you grift all your ideas from someone else and make a quick $?    
    
    
    Shouldn't #askagent be #askanagent?    
    
    
    Jessica Alba nominated for FOUR Razzies for FOUR different movies --> http://huff.to/dTZ5XT via @huffingtonpost(she was terrible in Machete)    
    
    
    @habituallychic Oh...what 'unchic' item?  I'm morbidly curious...    
    
    
    @designcrush Is it like a kiddie version of undressed?  Lots of secks + bad acting?  Am I missing anything?    
    
    
    @habituallychic Ewwww.  Those are so...tacky.    
    
    
    Why does the Fox News Network rail against the "mainstream media" when it IS the mainstream media???  I'm confuzzled by this hypocrisy.    
    
    
    So friggin excited: RT @carenwestpr: This Sunday, @WalkingDead_AMC returns!Catch all the undead action @DieselAtlanta: http://ow.ly/i/1ue5U     
    
    
    @carenwestpr @DieselAtlanta I'll be in there like swimwear. Will @DieselAtlanta be doing weekly viewings for each new epi?    
    
    
    Guest Blog Post: Creative Overflow http://wp.me/pJpwc-hK     
    
    
    I think I'm just going to have chai teas for dinner.    
    
    
    They open their mouth.  #mistakesmenmake    
    
    
    Newly published press release http://lnkd.in/Fzm9nQ    
    
    
    #fakejournalist @AndreaTantaros Vile woman questioning whether POTUS' daughter would take BC. Tacky and tasteless, she fits in at #fauxnews.    
    
    
    All these #laurynhill jokes. Lord I feel so bad for laughing. Everything is not everything :-(    
    
    
    Social Media: Healthline Networks, Inc. http://wp.me/pJpwc-d5G     
    
    
    Service is quicker at bar. (@ Ru San's) on #Yelp http://www.yelp.com/biz/ru-sans-atlanta-3?pt=quick_tip&ref=twitter&v=5a …    
    
    
    No coffee for bfast, makes Lindsey a dull girl....    
    
    
    @designsponge I use clear and I LOVE IT.  I have recommended it to parents and friends.    
    
    
    Design Notebook:Bertoia Diamond Chair: http://wp.me/p1gFQ9-6o     
    
    
    Long time, no see  :-(    
    
    
    What a twat! ---> http://www.guardian.co.uk/politics/2011/apr/01/david-willetts-feminism-lack-of-jobs    
    
    
    Charlie Sheen gets booed in #detroit,responds "I've already got your money, dude." Jokes' on those who spent $ to see that mess.April Fools!    
    
    
    <---- Definitely not an #uglyassvirgo. @TheDailyVirgo    
    
    
    scoutmob.com/revel/scoutmobangel    
    
    
    Seriously thinking about shutting down the blog, re-branding myself and starting allll over again.  Hmmmm...Yes, I'm tweeting on a Saturday.    
    
    
    @habituallychic Oh...I hate when that happens :-(    
    
    
    #propagrindin# ?  @idriselba ...love that twitter is the source of all my favorite new neologisms...    
    
    
    Oh em gee .... these allergies are.  I'm so allergied-up that I can't finish my sentence.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Someone tell JHud to get her man.  That's tacky, with a T.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl That's what I want to know.  I do not want to mess up my fro with no durn bike helmet.    
    
    
    Dogwood Festival, SweetWater 420 Festival, Yelp Culture Week...so excited for the weekend.    
    
    
    @ATLINtownPaper OMG!  I would LOVE a pair of tickets to Midtown Tour of Homes.    
    
    
    Awesome.  Thanks again :-)    
    
    
    My Twitter BFFs: @freelancefolder @elledecor @kellyoxford @chrisbrown @advtastes @nylonmag @mindykaling. Find yours @ http://twitbffs.com    
    
    
    WTF?  Who picked these twitter BFFs?    
    
    
    My Twitter BFFs: @bastylefilegirl @addthis @jenramos @huffingtonpost @habituallychic @designcrush. Find yours @ http://twitbffs.com    
    
    
    I just spent a lot of $$$ on some goodies from @eBay.    
    
    
    @MidtownMile I hope it's free Coca-Cola for life...    
    
    
    @womenonwriting Nope...I enjoy spending 12 minutes to decide on a cereal.  Plus...I'm sure she wants to maintain SOME normalcy in her life.    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo Me and my Momma and my Gramma ---> http://bit.ly/kcP49k    
    
    
    @popafricana CONGRATS on that gorgeous spread!!!!  Wow...    
    
    
    @1q1b Erm....I do that all de time.    
    
    
    @1q1b Does it still I count if I sometimes laugh at my own jokes?  Cause I'm sorta kinda funny on my better days.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl @tomandlorenzo I guess J.Simps just came back from the no-pants dance with the fiancee?    
    
    
    Twist Restaurant & Tapas Bar on #Yelp: It's alright.  This area (Phipps, Lenox and the space in between) has become ... http://bit.ly/mwuGJM    
    
    
    @ActuallyNPH What about Spirit Fingers?    
    
    
    @aswinn Next time just feed a bowl of dirt with a glass of gray water...then he'll care #lol    
    
    
    I've been #twitterstalking ---> time for bed.  See ya'll in the morning!    
    
    
    Going on a Ghost Tour tonight...on Friday the 13th...when it's supposed to storm.  Hmmm....    
    
    
    CNN's Don Lemon is 45?!?!?  Also, he's coming out..but, he's also 45 years old???    
    
    
    @exhaleAtlanta OMFG!!!! Really??!?!!?  Yay!  Thanks so much.  I've been waiting to go to your spa and now I get to!    
    
    
    Deadwood Saloon on #Yelp: I came here with my BFF to commiserate and complain about dumb-ass idiot loser ex boyfrien... http://bit.ly/kTlmPT    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack WTF are you talking about?    
    
    
    @thebookmaven I'm reading Paul Theroux's "Ghost Train to the Eastern Star"    
    
    
    @thebookmaven I believe it begins at 8 am UTC near Christmas island...    
    
    
    Holy Fuck!! RT@allisonkilkenny *Whistle* Spain's unemployment rate for those under 25 is 43.5% as of Feb...    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack ...I hate it when that happens!    
    
    
    @chrisguillebeau Hi Chris, I had a question about http://travelhacking.org/ Can I DM you?    
    
    
    @chrisguillebeau Just emailed you.  Thanks!    
    
    
    Just discovered @airbnb.  OMG....can't wait to start knocking cities around the off my bucket list.    
    
    
    Front Page News on #Yelp: I came here for brunch, sat alone on the patio (it was crowded) had a peroni and the andou... http://bit.ly/imuZy1    
    
    
    @mrjoezee @cmbenz Blargh!  You just missed her; she was there last weekend :-(    
    
    
    Ah...memories.  Watching the very first episode of #sexandthecity    
    
    
    @susanorlean Funny? No.  Convenient?  Yes.    
    
    
    I want to blog for @vogue_italia (specifically Vogue Curvy or Black) How can I make that happen?    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo @KarrineSteffans    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo Beyonce? #namethatvirgo    
    
    
    Come say hello on my (professional) Facebook Fan Page ---> http://www.facebook.com/pages/Decorative-Communications/187386987980709    
    
    
    Finally getting around to scheduling my Week of Transformation @exhaleAtlanta I really need it.  Yoga everyday and some massages...Yay!    
    
    
    @ATL_Events @thekingofpops Yay...I'm in the area and I finally will get around to trying one of your pops.    
    
    
    @scoutmob Sitting on patios while drinking mojitoes and reading.    
    
    
    King of Pops on #Yelp: Finally, I get what all the damn fuss is about.  I hadn't tried a King of Pops popsiscle most... http://bit.ly/lEsr1D    
    
    
    @LeahMOB Clutches pearls.  "My word!"    
    
    
    @aswinn I don't know...but she must Pissed OFF.    
    
    
    Wondering if anyone can recommend an 'affordable' website designer.  I've got a new website and I really want it to look pretty.  DM Please!    
    
    
    @aswinn @GalleyCat LOL...I agree 100%.  What kind of writer doesn't ENJOY reading in the first place???    
    
    
    @downtownatlanta Sweet, with extra lemon.  Duh!    
    
    
    Did not have coffee at all today.  Felt lumpy and poo-ey all day :-(    
    
    
    @FashionOffice Nothing beats a fabulous, minty mojito.    
    
    
    @FashionOffice Make that a blackberry mojito.  Man, those are good.    
    
    
    Planning a EuroTrip next Spring using @dopplr.  Need to get my side-hustle on (all 10 of them!)    
    
    
    @FashionOffice Mint Juleps are delish too!  (basically replace rum w/ whiskey in the recipe, sans lime) #cocktailchat    
    
    
    @simonpegg Looks like something out of Jurassic Park    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Hopefully soon.  Way too hippy-dippy and goofy.    
    
    
    Samuel L. Jackson Narrates Go the F*** to Sleep - GalleyCat http://www.mediabistro.com/galleycat/samuel-l-jackson-narrates-go-the-f-to-sleep_b32306 … via @galleycat  LOLZ...should be awesome!    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Hey!  What's up!    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN I'm not much for blogging these days.  I've moved on to @tumblr ---> http://thedecorwriter.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Thanks :-)    
    
    
    @TXWriter @copyblogger Great article about social media 'experts'  Bookmarked!    
    
    
    @MidtownMile SNAP...I love Piola.  Thanks for heads-up.    
    
    
    100% true...RT @ZodiacFacts #ZodiacFacts As a #Virgo,You love to treat your friends and family, but in times of need, your pride kicks in.    
    
    
    “I want to win free #wine from @herlittledogtoo and @EversavePHL! – http://bit.ly/kk2Wr8 ”    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Mais nous changons tout le temp.  C'est normal, mon cherie.    
    
    
    Getting the hang of my kinda, sorta aggressive query schedule.  Polishing one up for @bust_magazine a fave.    
    
    
    @GrammarGirl Congratulations!    
    
    
    Dying of laughter OMFG --->RT@jimmyfallon Watch Cameron Diaz channel her inner voice on "Other Voices" http://bit.ly/ldMprq  #latenight    
    
    
    @GiltGroupe Love my $29 Gunmetal Slip-On Oxfords...can't wait to snatch up some outfits to match!    
    
    
    @susanorlean I know I'm really late...but what does the #ff mean?    
    
    
    Black Friday Sale at Wine Library http://winelibrary.com/show_special.asp?section=blackfriday … via @winelibrary    
    
    
    @HammocksHighTea K.I.S.S.- two to three grafs Talk about what inspired you to open ur biz, what inspires you, your biz mission, etc.    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack Perms aren't a deterrent from letting my hair down.  They WERE a deterrent from letting it grow, though.    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack When I relaxed it, it did inhibit all of that.  Especially anything to do with water...it had to be braided if at beach/pool    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack Is it b/c there's no place to get relaxers or maybe the natural look is more accepted/acceptable.    
    
    
    @CRAVEatlanta @SpicesofLife Ginger is one of my favorite spices.  Relieves cold symptoms and tastes delicious as a candy.  Nom!    
    
    
    I am now following @winscholarships on Twitter and I earned 25 scholarship points to use towards scholarship drawings! http://bit.ly/cLYhL    
    
    
    Tap on #Yelp: When I lived and worked on Peachtree St.  (not like a streetwalker, my former employer' and my old apa... http://bit.ly/mlyLiG    
    
    
    It's about damn time! RT @ATLINtownPaper MARTA is now selling Breeze cards & allowing customers load fares online at http://www.breezecard.com     
    
    
    @MarieDenee Atlanta    
    
    
    Color Chameleon #polyvore http://www.polyvore.com/cgi/set?id=33372912    
    
    
    Bright! Bold! Huetiful! #polyvore http://www.polyvore.com/cgi/set?id=33373578    
    
    
    @allisonkilkenny If we buy all the gold, can we like...send #glennbeck to a cave in Tehran...forever?    
    
    
    @TheLoveList How did you that?  I need to turn my stupid Palm Pixi into an iPhone...please advise    
    
    
    @jenramos Great post today. Totally agree about needing social interaction...it's very lonely and quiet sometimes.  Even w/ my pooch, Titus.    
    
    
    Sorry to missing #SMDayATL. But I've got a buttload of work to do and I want to have time to enjoy my long, boozy weekend. LOL    
    
    
    @susanorlean I heard on the Twitter can no longer read your DM's when you use your Twitter name to sign in.  Meaning DMs don't work for any1    
    
    
    @MarieDenee What scares me?  "Do I have enough $"  What gives me pause? "Can I find it on @eBay_Fashion?"    
    
    
    @ColleenLindsay I think you need to make an emergency call to the Orkin man or something.    
    
    
    The Pup Truck on #Yelp: Nothing like biting into a bag, fat, juicy....hotdog.  I came here for last month's Castlebe... http://bit.ly/lYpSMb    
    
    
    Ray's Pizza on #Yelp: I've only ever had the pizza here, so I'm not sure what the rest of the food is like.  9/10 I ... http://bit.ly/mOkALl    
    
    
    The Daiquiri Factory on #Yelp: There are some places where you to go for the dranks and to get effed up, not to drin... http://bit.ly/mU5C6x    
    
    
    @ZodiacFacts #Virgo here!    
    
    
    Can't tell is the light outside is coming from the lightening or the various fireworks.... #ATL #Happy4th    
    
    
    Need some pepto bismol and a diet after my weekend food bender. #Happy4th    
    
    
    @ColleenLindsay I LOVE #Luther, via @idriselba.  Can't wait to see tomorrow's episode.    
    
    
    @ZodiacFacts I've felt true passion before...I didn't want to though.  Believe me.    
    
    
    Mac's Beer & Wine Midtown Liquor on #Yelp: Crickey!

I can't believe I haven't written a review on this place yet.  ... http://bit.ly/ijHAGF    
    
    
    @SLPetCareInc @susanorlean The man has repaid his debt to society, both financially and by serving time.  What more would you want from him?    
    
    
    @MargaretAtwood That is my life's dream.  I'm 2/3 there, already got the laughing and the beer-drinking down...now how to become a Walrus.    
    
    
    @ATL_Events @richsullivan @MaraDavis @RFLatl @929davefm #MUSICMIDTOWN OMFG.  It's about time.  #YAY    
    
    
    Barnes and Noble @ Georgia Tech Bookstore on #Yelp: If you're coming here looking for non-textbooks, you'd be better... http://bit.ly/ocw2Re    
    
    
    Dekalb Farmers Market on #Yelp: Yes, it's usually crowded, but that's because the food is cheap AND fresh at the sam... http://bit.ly/qRnsDf    
    
    
    Rooftop 866 on #Yelp: As I was telling my friend, Rooftop 866 is the place you bring a hot date when you plan to put... http://bit.ly/psw2QZ    
    
    
    @nicolenewblack Those people get auto-blocked.  God, I hate #twitterspam with a fury >:(    
    
    
    The Earl on #Yelp: Dear *The* Earl,

Thank you for being one of a handful of places open AND serving food at 10:30 a... http://bit.ly/qpSnjw    
    
    
    Lefont Theatre Sandy Springs on #Yelp: First things first...if you're driving N on Roswell Rd, turn left at the Sunt... http://bit.ly/rn51n3    
    
    
    @susanorlean Tweet away...you should be proud (proud enough to share!)    
    
    
    @susanorlean "circle them"?  Is there a social media thingamabob that I've missed???    
    
    
    The Real Chow Baby on #Yelp: I came here over the weekend, planning to peruse the Westside Shopping District after l... http://bit.ly/nvRFE5    
    
    
    Twisted Taco Tucker on #Yelp: One of the reasons I love Yelp is that, as a person who enjoys planning things, I enjo... http://bit.ly/nDi3wm    
    
    
    @ladygaga is on #soyouthinkyoucandance tonight. Friggin awesome!    
    
    
    @AllyFTRB I would kill for a little sunshine right about now.  :-(    
    
    
    Did you catch @erinloechner and @loving_eco ‘s mega summer giveaway? I just entered!: http://ow.ly/5NaAA     
    
    
        
    
    
    LOL...ridiculous...@AJCBuzz @ajcsundayeditor    
    
    
    OMG....it is still raining.    
    
    
    Joe's On Juniper on #Yelp: Actually, my rating for this place is more like 3.5 stars, but whatevs.  

First things, ... http://bit.ly/qIhDKX    
    
    
    Check out my tumblr ---> http://thedecorwriter.tumblr.com/     
    
    
    Not a fashion blogger, but this was incredibly insightful ---> HOW-TO: Fix The Broken Relationships Between B.. http://bit.ly/p6XWcb    
    
    
    Saw some chairs by the dumpster this afternoon and thought, "those have potential."  I should've grabbed them :-/    
    
    
    @RL_Stine Wow... wonder what %age of those bats are sparkly vampires named Edward?    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo Idris Elba...NO CONTEST!    
    
    
    I've been writing all day.  Have writing cramps.  Need a beer.  S.O.S!    
    
    
    @TheDailyVirgo What'd I say...it's no contest.  Perry is an okay actor, and Charlie Sheen hasn't acted well since Wall St.    
    
    
    There's a job that I want to apply to, but I need 200+ followers to qualify.  Twitter powers activate! #help    
    
    
    @designsponge BWAHAHAHA!  I don't mean to laugh, but wow.  #notwinning    
    
    
    I love riding on trains.... RT @susanorlean I am never unhappy when I'm on a train.    
    
    
    Hmmm....well now I'm intrigued...@designcrush @heidimjenkins trust me, people would be offended.    
    
    
    I've been feeling inexplicably lazy these past few days....gah :-(    
    
    
    Just found out, via @HuffingtonPost that there'll be #SATC no.3. Why do they keep taking such a ginormous dump on such an awesome t.v. show?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl These little rugrats are too fresh.    
    
    
    This is just pathetic.  That ONE tweet is nearly 2 years old...WTF RT @AJCBuzz BTW has anyone else noticed @AirTran's moribund Twittah?    
    
    
    CHURCH RT@TreatWomenRight #DearEX - Thank you for being the greatest example of what I don't want, helping me realize that I deserve better!    
    
    
    @TreatWomenRight Reading through these tweets while I'm going through a breakup (for the 2nd go-round) and it's a breath of fresh air.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Haven't been yet,don't plan on going.Looked pretty slow on my way to Piedmont Park yesterday.I'm over the bougie burger trend.    
    
    
    HOToberfest Launch Party Elite Event at Ormsby's on #Yelp: Yes.  This event was so awesome.  Not only did I get two ... http://bit.ly/r4qwDv     
    
    
    I feel left out... #whatearthquake    
    
    
    Is there anything the Gosling can't do?? #swoon @Jezebel @JessicaSuarez    
    
    
    Im so there!  RT@AtlanticStation Join us in the park this Thurs for #TheHangover and remember what happens in Vegas...stays in Vegas!!    
    
    
    Good morning, people!    
    
    
    @GiltGroupe I'm very boring...it's black.    
    
    
    Seriously pondering a move to Los Angeles...    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Hey...were you at Burkhart's last night?  I think I recognized you from Yelp.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Me and my friends bought a few.    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta I was the one with the afro...lol    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta Yep!    
    
    
    Figures...NIN made the list!  RT @pastemagazine The 25 Creepiest Songs About Love :: Blogs :: List of the Day :: Paste http://bit.ly/rhh9tl     
    
    
    Tornado warnings on teevee going off every 15 minutes is starting to irritate me.  Heard there were spottings in Marietta, though.  #ATL    
    
    
    @susanorlean Nothing much to do with all this rain (in GA).    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta And now warnings have been issued for Fulton and Gwinett counties.  Yikes    
    
    
    Apparently, you can say "bullshit" on cable teevee #rizzoliandisles.  I'm not mad, just...surprised.    
    
    
    Good morning, people.  Glad Atlanta wasn't hit too hard by them thar tornadoes...    
    
    
    Sooooo thankful for a break from this blistering heart #atlanta    
    
    
    Pardon my French, but who the FUCK spams on Twitter???? It can't possibly be effective? Yuck...    
    
    
    Just saw an ad for Shellac in this month's @allure_magazine...glad to know that polish actually works :-)@About_Atlanta @sugarcoatbeauty    
    
    
    Page not found... RT@HuffingtonPost Relatives left 70-year-old woman to die after a fall, went out for pizza    
    
    
    @JenRamos I use a shampoo bar from a D.C. company called Pure, and I love Tresemme Moisturizing conditioner.  I mix it with a bit of EEVO.    
    
    
    @AJCBuzz Wow, really?  Dudes are #specialsauce    
    
    
    My goodness those are gorgeous. I should've requested a @LauraMerkin for my bday last week!  Blargh!!! http://gi.lt/pdYDws  via @GiltGroupe    
    
    
    I'm very excited to get back into the blogging game with my blog, Lindsey Lou! Blogs ---> http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    Super duper...let's make it 7 pts/week...My @Klout score is 20. I improved it by 7 points over the past  30 days! http://klout.com/user/LindseyLou84/score-analysis?n=tw&v=daily_welcome …    
    
    
    @CRAVEla Hi! I'm moving here from Atlanta this month and I'd hoped you'd suggest job hunting tips/websites for writers/communications people    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl YUSS....I might actually have to buy that sh*t now #idrinktapwater    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LMAO....slurp.  Boy I'm thirsty all of a sudden pic.twitter.com/SDtNpSv    
    
    
    LMAO at #RonaldRegan trending.  Lawd...    
    
    
    @1q1b Is this big enough fer ya?It's wallpaper that's also a calendar.  found via @designboom ---> http://www.christiaanpostma.nl/index.htm?calendar_wallpaper.htm … pic.twitter.com/ih0wOTo    
    
    
    @GQMagazine Does @idriselba come with that gym membership...seeing as how he's the new face of Smartwater, I think it's only fair.    
    
    
    I must admit, I'm kind of excited for Lion King 3D...    
    
    
    tgif    
    
    
    LOL. I highly doubt they will...@derekblasberg @NYFW    
    
    
    Jonathan Taylor Thomas is now 30 years old.   I'm 27.  I had a crush on him when I was 10.  Geez...    
    
    
    LMAO...#socialmediafail RT@TravelMagazine Why would we follow back...only tweets are "follow back"?!? RT @CharliesFarm  follow back?    
    
    
    Don't Call It a Comeback...: http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2011/09/dont-call-it-comeback.html#.TmqA-GWEEkE.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    RyanGosling arrives in Toronto to show off #Drive, Ides, and his hotness! http://www.popsugar.com/Ryan-Gosling-Pictures-Arriving-Toronto-Film-Festival-19016928 … via @popsugar He's lookin' fresher than a muh!    
    
    
    I nominate @tessa, RT@chrisguillebeau I'm looking for good role models / examples of women who travel to faraway places    
    
    
    ...watch with glittering eyes the world around you    
    
    
    I was just called "Ma'am" by a young person.... #imgettingold    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta What on Earth is #TheChew?    
    
    
    I feel the same way about @gilt RT@designcrush I think I can now say, with absolute certainty, that I have an addiction to @Fab    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta That sounds like a show I'd watch, so long as there's less chatter and no Hasselbecks.    
    
    
    I've reserved a spot in Oprah's Lifeclass.  Here's a special invite for my friends to come to class too! http://bit.ly/oprahclass     
    
    
    Trying to find a job across the country is a job in and of itself.  #imtired    
    
    
    Thank goodness!!! @allisonkilkenny @Slate    
    
    
    That sounds so nasty...RT @bastylefilegirl "I'm on my way to an asshole festival, and I hear your the headliner"    
    
    
    Hemingway's Letters | Culture | Vanity Fair http://www.vanityfair.com/culture/features/2011/10/hemingway-slideshow-201110?slide=1&mbid=social_retweet … via @VanityFair    
    
    
    Front Page News on #Yelp: I spent practically the whole day walking around our lovely city, visiting the Midtown pop... http://bit.ly/fyQR2d    
    
    
    @TheLoveList I love chest hair.  It's hawt...    
    
    
    Chris Evans (aka Captain America) has THE PERFECT hairy chest.  OMG... @sarahehoward @TheLoveList pic.twitter.com/0zpBYaoU    
    
    
    Could be be much better...According to @Klout, @LindseyLou84's Klout score is 23.  How influential are you? http://klout.com/user/LindseyLou84/score-analysis?n=tw&v=klout_score …    
    
    
    Black women 'should' date/marry, can ya'll leave us be for 10 damn minutes and let us do w/e we want? Thanks/Bye @WSJ http://on.wsj.com/pksh5d     
    
    
    @TheLoveList Niiiiice!    
    
    
    @allisonkilkenny Nope...otherwise he wouldn't be the token.  Duh!    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta LOL...I'm watching it too.    
    
    
    Check out my Tumblr for makeup and beauty enthusiasts!  http://ow.ly/6C5UX    
    
    
    I hope these showers bring cooler temps.  I was getting used to 60' and sunny...    
    
    
    If you're on tumblr, follow me www.beautystoned.tumblr.com where I tumblr makeup and stuff    
    
    
    Super...a "to-do" list for marketers on #facebook http://ow.ly/6DcaC Greeeat! -_-    
    
    
    My favorite pieces from @dolcegabbana Spring 2012 beauty stoned http://ow.ly/6Ei3L    
    
    
    Love @jetsetter and they're #PanAm inspired campaign.  So cute...would love to go back in time to the swingin' 60s! Welcome to the Jet...    
    
    
    Shopping Snapshots: Sept. 22 - Slide Show - NYTimes.com http://ow.ly/6GBMD    
    
    
    Well, now I feel bad for skipping yoga this morning ---> 6 Tips From a 75-Year-Old Inspiration (Can You Do 200 Push Ups?): via...    
    
    
    Ladies listen up ---> 17 Bad Skin Habits to Kick Now http://ow.ly/6MhhJ (I'm guilty of more than a few of these) via @allure_magazine    
    
    
    "3 Mood Mugs" at Twist Design...Hilarious coffee mugs with Happy, Sleepy and Grouchy emoticon faces.  Guess which one I am?  (It's grumpy)    
    
    
    In Less than a Minute Alan Grayson Explains Occupy Wall Street to the 1% http://ow.ly/6SXwF     
    
    
    @gfreelancing As a freelance writer, I'd LOVE to make around $60K or more.   I'm young and single, so that's enough $ for me...for now.    
    
    
    @gfreelancing You'd think that'd be obvious, but unfortunately it is not.  SMDH    
    
    
    @AlecBaldwin Awesome!  Savannah is so gorgeous this time of year.  Might still be hotter than schweddy balls, though...    
    
    
    #FF to some very knowledgeable B2B marketers and magazines @marketingmag @marketingb2b @b2bonlinemktg @b2bmagazine    
    
    
    @mediajobsdaily Right Click, Copy Img URL.  Best job ever...I'd never get work there ---> http://ow.ly/7lPy9     
    
    
    @mediajobsdaily Without the slide's caption? Yeah.  Hmm...    
    
    
    @DavidAtlanta lol.  Maybe, just maybe, someone got locked out of their car?  #pipedreams    
    
    
    I am pretty sure we're all being punked by #HermanCain    
    
    
    @celebitchy http://aplusk.posterous.com/twitter-management …    
    
    
    I have a problem spending all my money on @ebay It's a happy problem, though.    
    
    
    I connected Twitter to my http://flavors.me  page - http://flavors.me/lindseylou84     
    
    
    @AJCBuzz It's in the air, drifting off the Savannah river.    
    
    
    FINALLY I'm getting a new phone:  Samsung Conquer from @sprint.  It'll be my first Android, 4G.  It's an early Christmas Gift to myself!    
    
    
    @thebookmaven Just finished Shopgirl last night/this morning (so it still counts for #fridayreads). Felt similar to Mirabelle in a few ways.    
    
    
    I sobbed too... RT @stephenfry: *sob* http://youtube.com/watch?v=_TBd-U …    
    
    
    @1q1b You're in town?!  For how long?    
    
    
    @1q1b What time do you leave on Monday?  I can hang out Sunday night or Monday morning/afternoon!    
    
    
    @GiltGroupe I love dark nail colors: inky blue, gray, deep purple and vampy red <3    
    
    
    W00T!  I'm going to the Downtown Atlanta Scavenger Hunt!  So excited!!!    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Chile please....I won a registration pass.  Felisha's coming, but if you think you know atlanta better, I can switch you two.    
    
    
    @TAUR3AN Yeah I know....I might have to consider changing you two. I want to win that $$$!    
    
    
    This weekend, starting Thursday, is going to be #epic.Yelp's Gilded Age, then the ATL Scavenger Hunt and then ATL Streets Alive.  YAY!!!!    
    
    
    Thrive on #Yelp: The decor is nice...but the lighting is a little too ambient (as in...it's hella dark in there).  T... http://bit.ly/fZrPOw    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl I would say Judge got some Juvederm and Botox and maybe a lift. He looks awful though :-(    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl He appears to have shown more restraint than Sylvester Stallone and Mickey Rourke though    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl I don't know why either.  He looks like a dang football and he USED to be such a hottie. SMH.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Nine 1/2 Weeks http://picnica.ciao.com/uk/28607842.jpg    
    
    
    Good morning!    
    
    
    Fantastic giveaway for a Golden Bamboo Tray Table from @RightBankGirl!   I really, really want it, though!  Enter now!    
    
    
    @rightbankgirl LOL...I forgot I'd already won something from you.  Hmmm...a girl can still hope, though.    
    
    
    I received a FREE Spicy Chicken Sandwich from Chick-fil-A. Go to www.getspicychicken.com to get yours!    
    
    
    I'm attending SVEDKA "Sex & The City 2" Premiere Party -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/11p4.  WOOT! WOOT!    
    
    
    @atl365 I went on a scavenger hunt!  We lost but had sooooo much fun!  Thanks again!    
    
    
    Giveaway sponsored by @aptdweller for $25 gift cert to flying biscuit cafe.  I've never been before, so I should win!!!    
    
    
    Too early in the AM for me to try to explain the naming of slaves (during American slavery period) to someone who admits total ignorance.    
    
    
    @atl365 Yes, some of those clues were really difficult.  Don't know where we were placed.  Got 26/46 points.  I would def. do again next yr!    
    
    
    Oh....I have 100 followers.  I need more, though.  How can I do that???    
    
    
    Ok, so this SATC2 "premiere" movie event @Divanatlanta today was #weaksauce.    
    
    
    @TheWhoopiG The real whoopi goldberg @theviewtv just said you're a big, fat phony!    
    
    
    Wondering if and where @therealbigboi is going to perform this evening.  Hmmmm...inquiring minds NEED to know!    
    
    
    @atl365 Murphy's Law???    
    
    
    %m headed to see @therealbigboi at this free concert!  I hope the crowd isn't ridiculous!  Which it will be I'm sure.    
    
    
    @LindseyLou84    
    
    
    Kitschy Kitchenwares http://bit.ly/cGrnZD    
    
    
    The Signal - BMI-based discount is unfair http://bit.ly/d4dXxV    
    
    
    @aplusk It's not really a Hitler mustache.It's a toothbrush mustache and unfortunately,the style was hijacked and is still asso.w/ Hitler.    
    
    
    Yes!  Going to a cookout!    
    
    
    "Everything is everything, after winter must come spring..."    
    
    
    Cami Cakes on #Yelp: Three Words:  Red Velvet Cupcakes

Five Words:  Get thee to Cami's Cakes

Ok, so as I typical S... http://bit.ly/gZWxpP    
    
    
    VICE on #Yelp: Music wasn't bad and I only drank Corona's so I don't know how good the drink's are.  Oh, and a frien... http://bit.ly/hVaKCl    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder Not too shabby.  About to start another query letter.  Completed two proposals today + a blog post. Need some lunch though.    
    
    
    @FreelanceFolder I know.  I'm starving.  I'm roasting a chicken so it might be a late lunch :-(    
    
    
    I JUST HAVE FREE 100 TWITTER FANS! http://tinyurl.com/2alu9d3 .    
    
    
    @celebitchy http://www.tmz.com/2011/12/30/katy-perry-divorce-russell-brand/?adid=hero1 …    
    
    
    I don't know about you, but I love the sound of rain just as I'm about to go to bed.  Play this! RainyMood.com http://bit.ly/1pEoI    
    
    
    @scoutmob Scoutmob Miami perhaps???    
    
    
    You should ignore the email I just sent you! lol RT @ajcbuzz:I'm NOT a casting director so don't email me their booty shots.My poor retinas.    
    
    
    Le Petit Marché on #Yelp: Sunday afternoon (around 3 pm) I had a late, and slightly hungover, breakfast with a coup... http://bit.ly/xJyLXO     
    
    
    Sometimes I wish I were Oscar Wilde clever...but was Oscar Wilde ever that clever?Not even he knew what he was talking about 1/2 the time...    
    
    
    Reading: The No. 1 Habit of Highly Creative People http://bit.ly/c5xMut via @zen_habits    
    
    
    @debng Do you want me to leave nasty comment?    
    
    
    @CRAVEatlanta "Pussy Control" by Prince    
    
    
    @mindykaling No one had ever spit on your bald head and wished for luck???  You are talking about Lakers/Celtics game, right?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Or else it gets the hose again??    
    
    
    @chrisguillebeau Do you have any tips/recommendations/issues with flying on standby?Thinking about Brazil in couple months.    
    
    
    If you're down in the game, don't be makin them faces #Celtics.  You heard the man!!!    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Wild Bill was in Shutter Island????  Who'd he play?    
    
    
    91-84....bam!  #DerekFisher is a fine azz mama jama!!!!    
    
    
    Blogging about: Wednesday Giveaway.http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/06/wednesday-giveaway.html. Pls retweet!    
    
    
    WHITE SUPREMACISTS BOYCOTT NEW IDRIS ELBA MOVIE http://bit.ly/hrMhLc    
    
    
    Twitter #failwhale FTL!    
    
    
    SingleBubblePop http://bit.ly/5FzYHb    
    
    
    @Bethenny I'm totally gonna watch it Bethenny.  I can't wait to see it!!!    
    
    
    Just found out I got ROTD on @yelpatlanta for my review of @burkhartspub http://www.yelp.com/biz/burkharts-pub-atlanta#hrid:OkUZBIKfz4y5GueAm4ENUYAAAAAAA … :-)    
    
    
    Twitter looks...different.    
    
    
    Ingmar Swalue: Dutch Photographer http://bit.ly/ddMuUT    
    
    
    Loft Living http://networkedblogs.com/4L7kl    
    
    
    Styled my profile with a sweet theme using Themeleon by @COLOURlovers http://clrlv.rs/newthemeleon Love it?    
    
    
    Taco Mac on #Yelp: On beer selection alone, this place deserves 5 stars.  The only other places where you'll find t... http://bit.ly/wWgCvT     
    
    
    WATCH: Chuck Todd Tears Into Stephen Colbert http://huff.to/yUhxBL  via @huffingtonpost    
    
    
    Shit Social Media Experts #SSMES Say Starring @MyMelodie http://youtu.be/hCqmIRThlxk  #HASHTAG    
    
    
    No to whale burgers.  YES! to Iceland.  Great post>>> http://www.nicoleisthenewblack.com/2012/01/reykjavik-iceland-perfect-escape.html … @nicolenewblack @visitreykjavik @gAdventures    
    
    
    @designcrush Sometimes bad coffee is better than no coffee at all.    
    
    
    Oh... I didn't know I could do Boba Tea at home.  I might have to give this a try! ohjoystudio's photo http://instagr.am/p/jtg_J/  via @instagram    
    
    
    I'm going to have to agree 100% with you on that one.  I loves my gummies  :-) RT@yelpatlanta gummy vitamins for adults: best idea EVER.    
    
    
    Working on query letters on a rainy Monday morning.  I hate rain.  I hate Mondays.  Rainy Mondays = boo!!!    
    
    
    Watching #snl now and shopping on ebay for vintage leather wares: clutches, gloves, shoes, bags.    
    
    
    @aswinn Your paypal email address is all you need to receive payment through Paypal.  You can also invoice a client, etc. through Paypal.    
    
    
    Cafe Intermezzo on #Yelp: I love Cafe Intermezzo.  I've been to this location, and the one on Peachtree in Midtown/... http://bit.ly/ypVKcR     
    
    
    Jammin' at Sweet Georgia's Juke Joint Elite Event on #Yelp: Another GREAT Yelp Event.  I love the idea of pairing u... http://bit.ly/xNMKVo     
    
    
    What in the samhell is #spoonswaggin?    
    
    
    I want to publish a book about booze...they go hand in hand I think.    
    
    
    Twitterers (or is it Tweeters??): #youmusthave slipped because none of you has explained to me the meaning of #spoonswaggin or #forkswaggin!    
    
    
    @Scholarshipscom My 2012 resolution is to graduate from GSU by May 2013 w/ BA in Journo.  Need scholarships, though.  Ran out of fin. aid.    
    
    
    @ATLINtownPaper @time @TIMENewsFeed Where is a good place to view the #lunareclipse in Atlanta tonight?  Any rcommendations...    
    
    
    @susanorlean Happy Birthday to your little one!    
    
    
    @ATLINtownPaper thanks!    
    
    
    a $5,500 bose giveaway: videowave entertainment system | Design For Mankind http://ow.ly/92mnF     
    
    
    @nikimcneill Me too!  I'm heading out for a beer or something.  I keep forgetting to give myself breaks now that i work for myself :-/    
    
    
    @Bethenny It's true Bethenny.  You're totally hilarious.  You're the funniest housewife of them ALL.    
    
    
    #Ihavenorespect for the Congressmen who voted against DADT or the Dream Act.You all are yellow-bellied, insensitive jerks...suck it.    
    
    
    The Moon's Holiday Gift http://www.nasa.gov/connect/chat/moon_gift.html … via @NASA    
    
    
    Good night #Lunar moon.  My lids are getting very heavy...    
    
    
    #DearEx, #ihavenorespect for you.    
    
    
    Beautiful Time Lapse Video of Last Night's Winter Solstice Lunar Eclipse http://tv.gawker.com/5715592/  via @gawkertv    
    
    
    Just got an email with the headline,"You're hired!"Unfortunately,it was from a resume service. Why would they play w/ my emotions like that?    
    
    
    @pattistanger If the hair that grows out of my head is nappy, am I doomed to be single for life?    
    
    
    @AdrianneCurry Ma'am.  You're totally right.  Breastfeeding your baby in public is shit.  GROSS.  What are you 12?    
    
    
    Colbert Reveals Tragedy, Scoffs at D.C. Audience - FishbowlDC http://www.mediabistro.com/fishbowldc/colbert-reveals-tragedy-scoffs-at-d-c-audience_b27500 … via @fishbowldc    
    
    
    @nikimcneill Your home looks nice and roomy.  Have fun making it lovely!    
    
    
    @veganlady7: Sometimes I wonder if @pattistanger, is a curly-haired girl who just doesn't like her own hair...    
    
    
    @MidtownMile @12thandMidtown That light wall is byootiful!!!    
    
    
    Thinking of changing my twitter handle to @lindseylouATL.  Hmmmm    
    
    
    This woman on #whatnottowear NEEDS a haircut....and chill out with that high yellow weave, girl.    
    
    
    Centennial Olympic Park on #Yelp: Centennial Park is my second favorite park (first is Piedmont, naturally) and I lo... http://bit.ly/egnhP3    
    
    
    @tyrabanks I've always been an innie and I do believe I've only cleaned my bellybutton out once.  Sounds gross saying it out loud :-(    
    
    
    @tyrabanks When does the next cycle of #ANTM start, if you don't mind me asking?    
    
    
    Join me in my http://Freelancer.com  Scavenger Hunt team (HoneyBadger)! $50k in prizes! http://scavenger.freelancer.com/  #scavhunt2012    
    
    
    Designer- Konstantin Grcic http://blog.2modern.com/2010/07/designer-konstantin-grcic.html    
    
    
    Unit 2 Fitness on #Yelp: I'm unofficially a part of Yelp's In It to Thin It competition (me against myself?), so I ... http://bit.ly/x9jzym     
    
    
    The government's new #taskforce moniker for #WikiLeaks, #WTF, needs to be a trending topic!  #ASAP!!!!    
    
    
    @officestylist Love those new designer Iphone cases in your office gifts round-up!  I'm way past due for a new one.  #AsksSanta...    
    
    
    Good lawd.... Trey from #TopChefAllStars is fwoine as hell.  There, I said it.    
    
    
    ❒Taken ❒Single ✔ I'm single and ready to mingle: nothing serious, though.    
    
    
    @ConanOBrien Just dropped the #bullshit bomb on live television.  My ears!  My virginal ears!!!!    
    
    
    @About_Atlanta Tito?  Could they not get Germaine or Latoya??    
    
    
    The problem with drinking a pot of coffee at 5 pm is that not only are you wide awake at midnight, you're also seeing a #doublerainbow! J/K    
    
    
    #secretturnon, @ConanOBrien's beard.    
    
    
    @tyrabanks I love the red lips.  Keep them!  (What shade is that called, btw?)    
    
    
    @365Atlanta LOL!  #seriously...I guess Latoya was busy?    
    
    
    Treehouses...for grown-ups http://blog.2modern.com/2010/07/treehousesfor-grownups.html    
    
    
    Opera Nightclub on #Yelp: This was my first time at Opera and I'm writing this while my irritation is fresh in mind.... http://bit.ly/gyBuWS    
    
    
    Idiots at some fake rodeo-clown "news" site called @TheBlaze insinuates that Trayvon Martin was a trouble-maker b/c he was suspended.    
    
    
    @GeraldoRivera is RIDICULOUS.Saying that as minorities we should avoid wearing hoodies, but white kids get to wear hoodies #separatebutequal    
    
    
    @NoReservations No Reservations is unguent.    
    
    
    @Bethenny I've cut the end of the toothpaste tube to get that last little bit out.  It' not a proud moment for me, needless to say...    
    
    
    It's so late that #Cheers is on. Good night everyone!    
    
    
    Lindsey Lu! Blogs Blogging About: Stylish on a Bike http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/stylish-on-bike.html    
    
    
    5 Ways to Market Yourself During a Recession http://bit.ly/IJXFC (via @the99percent) Great advice!    
    
    
    @TXWriter Great...writing a proposal.  How are you?    
    
    
    @OldSpice Will u give the "lesbian shittasses" @Jezebel a shout out please?We're huge fans...especially me.Pretty please with sugar on it?    
    
    
    ...just went on a twitter-following frenzy.  follow. follow.  follow.  #thatsaproblem    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs is blogging about Etsy/Bicyles: http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/etsy-roundup-bicycles.html    
    
    
    @OldSpice voicemail is so manly, that it's awesome:http://oldspicevoicemail.com/female.html  LOLZ    
    
    
    Lindsey Lou! Blogs: The Little White Dress http://lindseyloublogs.blogspot.com/2010/07/little-white-dress.html    
    
    
    If you don't make out with your S.O. after they've eaten massive amounts of garlic or onions, #thatsaproblem.  I know from experience :-/    
    
    
    #AGoodRelationship is "like friendship on fire" ~Bruce Lee~    
    
    
    @Foodista #foodquestion How do we get #cookies as trending topic? I'm  eating some fresh cornmeal-lemon sugar cookies and they're heaven!    
    
    
    #thistweetisdedicated2 #cookies.    
    
    
    The Universe House http://bit.ly/9OOCci    
    
    
    @Scholarshipscom The most important thing I learned this year is that patience pays off, and that you're never too old to return to school.    
    
    
    Yelp's Hall of Fame on #Yelp: As per usual, Kathleen M. put together a fabulous event.  I met some old friends, mad... http://bit.ly/HiFFQ8     
    
    
    @NoReservations Hmmm...Akara (which is bean fritters with hot sauce) and then my friend makes ginger beer and peanut chicken.    
    
    
    @KaiseratCB Don't know if you watched Dancing w/ Stars, but JLove was there, cheering for Maksim, said he was "Hot."  Trolling for dates?    
    
    
    I just LOVE it when a client does not pay me in a timely, efficient manner.  Hurrah for freelancing?    
    
    
    Congrats to #Hefner:  Older than my grandma (75) and marrying a chick who's younger than me (26).    
    
    
    #melgibsonruinseverything It's true!    
    
    
    Drinking subpar red wine just so that I can get a little drunkyity drunk drunk drunk?  #betterthanbeingmelgibson.    
    
    
    #melgibsonruinseverything    
    
    
    R.I.P. #TeenaMarie    
    
    
    Stuffing my mouth with delicious, buttery shortbreads because it's still the holidays.    
    
    
    #2010memories When my boyfriend emailed me to tell me he'd moved to Minneapolis a week after he'd moved there.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Carrot cake goes bad if you don't eat it right away,  #logicwin    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Yes...probably.  You could wait and find out...and then be disappointed with crusty, dry cake.    
    
    
    @Hokuboku I just saw Nude Nuns w/ Big Guns yesterday.  Not bad...reminded me of Machete a little bit.    
    
    
    I've a portfolio website, you know!  www.lindsey-gregory.com...
#thingsyoudidntknowaboutme    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Now trying to "Find a Way" to #employment.  Still #betterthanbeingmelgibson though    
    
    
    @EverythingATL OMG!  I'm glad that woman on Marta is okay.  That sounds horrifying.    
    
    
    @yelpatlanta take me with you on vacation please!?  I will bring chocolate cookies.    
    
    
    I don't appreciate it when people ask for your help at a certain time and then are late.  Perpetually late.    
    
    
    Decorating the Sky - http://bit.ly/e4lAfG (via @NASA) Absolutely Gorgeous!!    
    
    
    Why do #writers have such crappy websites?Not that mine is any better (it's not), but I've seen some oogly ones tonight.#workingonit though.    
    
    
    I completed C25K Week 3 Day 1 (--- miles), in 00:15:00, pace 12:55 min/mile, with @RunDouble http://bit.ly/nkhPg3     
    
    
    Watching Family Guy, drinking #coffee and getting some proposals done...then some ashtanga at noon!    
    
    
    Surin of Thailand on #Yelp: I love the food here.  I first came here years ago for a friend's surprise birthday and ... http://bit.ly/aEdZqm    
    
    
    Blossom Tree on #Yelp: I had been feeling adventurous last week and while downtown last week, rather than heading t... http://bit.ly/K59iQs     
    
    
    I feel like such a lame for not really caring about #teamfalcons v. #Aints.  However, as an Atlantan, I'm always default #teamfalcons.    
    
    
    Good morning, good morning, thank you, good morning!    
    
    
    @designcrush Funny Face was much better....there I said it!    
    
    
    it's difficult to assure clients of my freelance fees when they are unfamiliar with the freelance/writing process...haven't figured that out    
    
    
    Birth control!Birth control!Birth control! Until you can control your fertility,you will not be able to control your life~Judge Lynn Tohler~    
    
    
    When will @NoReservations be in Atlanta???  Should I start a petition or something? U watch the show @AJCBuzz?  What do you think?    
    
    
    "I write when I'm inspired, and I see to it that I'm inspired at nine o'clock every morning” ~ Peter De Vries~ (if only)    
    
    
    @TXWriter I've been calling myself a 'copywriter & content strategist' who freelances...hopefully that sounds more professional.    
    
    
    What is #hentai ?    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon #ifihadasuperpower,I'd be able to break into the disposal area in the nice neighborhoods,get the good furniture,no cops called.    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon, I'd fly Sarah Palin to the moon...and leave her there.  #ifihadasuperpower.    
    
    
    @jimmyfallon #ifihadasuperpower, it'd be the ability to get as many followers as @ladygaga...a girl can dream.    
    
    
    Someone please tell my firefox to behave!!!    
    
    
    hello: http://wp.me/pJpwc-ch    
    
    
    hello...again: http://wp.me/pJpwc-cs    
    
    
    @downandoutchic Have you checked out ebay or amazon for the film, yet?    
    
    
    "The path to success is to take massive, determined action."
~Anthony Robbins    
    
    
    "There's nothing to writing. All you do is sit down at a typewriter and open a vein." 
~Walter Wellesley Smith    
    
    
    Quotes About Writing: http://wp.me/pJpwc-cV    
    
    
    Free Personal signatures - cool!: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d1    
    
    
    Anatolia Cafe on #Yelp: I have the dangerous (not really) habit of walking by a restaurant 100 times before I final... http://bit.ly/IMaQk8     
    
    
    I use baby oil gel to moisturize my skin at night and I'm still ashy in the morning.  #blackgirlproblems    
    
    
    Freelance (Writer) Panic: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d4    
    
    
    @officestylist Can I drink this mask too??  That would awesome!    
    
    
    #whitechicks the movie? or #whitechicks that terrible song by trina???  neither    
    
    
    Reading:  "It's Not How Good You Are, It's How Good You Want To Bo."  by Paul Arden...good stuff.    
    
    
    House Tour: Villa Dali http://bit.ly/a9G5mN    
    
    
    Quote of the Day & Weekend Links: http://wp.me/pJpwc-d7    
    
    
      http://bit.ly/9PKZuz    
    
    
    Heard some INTERESTING news about #Inception.If only the audience I saw it with hadn't let out "WTF" I'd have heard the totem fall too!    
    
    
    #CelebPerfumes usually suck...who wants to smell like Halle Berry or Jennifer Anniston?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl LOL!  Esp. Janniston.  I heard it smells like cats and tears of sadness.    
    
    
    @veganlady7 Beyonce Heat is ok.  The only #CelebPerfume I truly like is SJP's Lovely and Covet and JLos Glow.  Other ones usually suck.    
    
    
    #TuckerCarlson hypocrite:Mark11:25 if you hold anything against anyone,forgive him, so that your Father in heaven may forgive you your sins.    
    
    
    USHER’S O.M.G SONG RIPPED FROM “HOMER SIMPSON”? http://ow.ly/1rYVg8 LOL...wasn't Will.i.Am sued by Daft Punk for ripping one of their songs?    
    
    
    I was at @TheFoxTheatre to see Massive Attack and thievery Corporation!  Would love to see Lady Antebellum this week.  Hint!    
    
    
    La Fonda Latina on #Yelp: I live down the street and today was only my second time dining here.  I'd gone here befor... http://bit.ly/frVkt0    
    
    
    @ChrisBrown has a major case of 'foot-in-mouth disease' #homophobe, #growup    
    
    
    @themoment Gianni Versace (I think) never made a guest appearance.  AbFab is one of my favorite shows, btw.    
    
    
    @scoutmob I love the fish stew at Six Feet Under    
    
    
    @BFGCom Communications is like prostitution.  First you do it for love...then you do for it money.  #contentmanagerapplication    
    
    
    @piersmorgan You've got some big suspenders to fill.  (Bet you haven't heard that one before...kidding.)  Best of luck to you!    
    
    
    @jenramos I'm seriously envying your walk-in closet and shoe collection.  Very impressive...    
    
    
    LOL @#TitoJackson trending... oh lawd.    
    
    
    I really hate MARTA.  Wish we had the MTA!  Actually I wish I was in NYC.  Three buses to get to midtown is just retarded! #wishuponastar    
    
    
    Apres Diem on #Yelp: Ok...this isn't French food at all.  

Now that that's out the way...I do like the atmosphere. ... http://bit.ly/ikkqrO    
    
    
    Trader Joe's on #Yelp: Um...hello: new favorite wine shop.  Very affordably priced and a decent selection to boot. http://bit.ly/g6alCW    
    
    
    Landmark Midtown Art Cinema on #Yelp: Independent films + Booze = Win!

Also...I really like that they offer those p... http://bit.ly/hX0gAy    
    
    
    I just might win $3000 to explore with @scoutmob, @jetsetterdotcom & @joyus. Join me: http://scoutmob.com/scoutjetshop/scoutmobangel …    
    
    
    Listening to this Lay it Down w/ Lloyd and Labelle.  What is this #hotmess ?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Agreed...why is gramma singing about layin it down???    
    
    
    I have that 2:30 feeling.   I need a nap and some coffee.    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl What the heck is formspring?    
    
    
    @bastylefilegirl Yeah...never heard of it.    
    
    
    why is it so dang hot???    
    
    
    #ScottPilgrim is out today???  Might have to see that one tonight, then.    
    
    
    