@Illustruction oooh like the driving game where you make up words for the last three letters of the license plate of the car in front?    
    
    
    @Illustruction oh maaan : ( that just made all my insides feel heavy    
    
    
    INSTAGRAM, WHY YOU DO THIS?    
    
    
    Glittery nuts! It's good to be home for Xmas : ) http://instagr.am/p/TlZ-PVHI45/     
    
    
    My last two posts do not go together AT ALL.    
    
    
    How was your Christmas?    
    
    
    @MarkBugby pretty good, thank you. Spent it with the family : ) Looking forward to my birthday on the 1st! :-0    
    
    
    @JohnCthulhu @Illustruction THIS IS A PROBLEM TO WHICH I CAN RELATE    
    
    
    @Artist_HB Ahh, thanks for listing me : )    
    
    
    So I went back to work today.. ONLY TO REALISE I STILL HAD TWO DAYS OF HOLIDAY LEFT -_-    
    
    
    Whoa    
    
    
    I am carless while my cars are in hospital. Most people would love to be able to work from home but I AM SO LONELY    
    
    
    Here is an early stage of a drawing from photo ref. Just practicing hands, necks, pose, lighting.. pic.twitter.com/kpdkthAu    
    
    
    MOODSWINGS. INDUCED BY EATING ENTIRE CAN OF BAKED BEANS. Is this normal?    
    
    
    Hoo boy did those baked beans have side effects. Who's doing the February Daily Draw on Satellite Soda?    
    
    
    @kukas81 aww thanks! Happy wknd @korrax @edmundsumner @elixat @guillaumefavre @freak_3d @georgenijland @mattguetta @paguthrie @superpeo    
    
    
    On the lookout and free to take on work, you guys! So if you have a project that needs an artist, giz a shout    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/egNM4X  #in    
    
    
    @colinwren Hey Colin, are you looking to have this professionally designed? It really depends what exactly you're after, drop me a msg!    
    
    
    Scribbly bits of a warmup sketch http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpbmQ0     
    
    
    Finished portrait with no ref. In hindsight should have maybe used ref hmm. ONTO THE NEXT.. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpc6YY     
    
    
    Nude alien lady sorta, may work on this more one day. Maybe. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpcb_A     
    
    
    Progress of woman with big boots. For the purpose of anatomy, form, pose and perspective practice. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpctB7     
    
    
    @mayaemilie I like big butts, and I cannot lie    
    
    
    @mayaemilie Thanks dude! I got bored when moving to the detail phase. But I think I'd like to work on it more.    
    
    
    @_XaKu AAAGH *dies* such a nice car :-0 How was it to drive?    
    
    
    @_XaKu How come it was your car for the day? Was it a track day?    
    
    
    @_XaKu whoooa. Have you seen the Audi R8 GT Spyder? http://bit.ly/Z386dj  Oh. My. God. That gear stick with the production number :-0    
    
    
    @_XaKu I KNOW, RIGHT! Phoooar. Carbon fibre everything, oooh yes please    
    
    
    Really want to get back on a motorbike, you guys    
    
    
    @samjermy87 NO. NO SIDE CARS. WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.    
    
    
    @samjermy87 NO. NO, SAM.    
    
    
    @samjermy87 pfff well MAYBE I don't want to go to your sidecar party ANYWAY. Do you ride?    
    
    
    @samjermy87 Ah just do the CBT, I paid £49 for mine and can ride up to 125cc for 2 years. I want to go for the full licence as soon as I can    
    
    
    @CaptainChants Dude I'm thinking of taking mine down, I haven't updated it in years! With my portfolio being everywhere but on my website..    
    
    
    @CaptainChants But then I don't want to lose the domain name GAAAH    
    
    
    When I was stuck in traffic this morning, I grumbled so loudly I startled myself    
    
    
    What's all this beef over horse meat?    
    
    
    Bet no one's said that before    
    
    
    Man, that was dry. SO DRY.    
    
    
    @BelgianBoolean whatcha doooin'?    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata daaang you're EVERYWHERE    
    
    
    Want to draw, but there are so many tasty jobs to apply for :-0    
    
    
    On the lookout to hold an exhibition, you guys. Have YOU done one before?    
    
    
    @Polygoblin hey thanks for the RT, Ben    
    
    
    @kukas81 ah thanks! Hello @vmdolphin @ugyjijes @elixat @guillaumefavre @futuregeist @paguthrie @mattguetta @georgenijland @superpeo    
    
    
    You guys that wanted to model my artwork in 3D, I will be more available to work with you very soon.    
    
    
    @Amelia_Hirst There's a limit? Is it a forever limit, or a limit per day or something? Maybe it's to stop the pornbots    
    
    
    @Amelia_Hirst oh riiight. I have a clean out every now and then, make sure I only follow people that I interact with : )    
    
    
    @ErinHunting will you please upload a half done pic on fb? Then I'll climb all over that like hot toffee. Let's get this collab rolling    
    
    
    @ErinHunting oh man I'M SO CONFUSED. Hey let's do a superhero woman? I've not done that before. I think you should go first :-0    
    
    
    @ErinHunting ah this just gets more and more exciting    
    
    
    New sketchbook performance anxiety    
    
    
    Agencies that send emails requesting me to call back regarding a job offer WHY YOU NO JUST CALL ME?    
    
    
    Still looking for a new career challenge, the next step. A lot of these JDs are way too serious. Design is all about the fun!    
    
    
    Did you ever do an internship? Although I've worked with interns, I am firmly against the idea. Hard work should be PAID with MONEY.    
    
    
    @MoonApe What do you think about internships?    
    
    
    @mayaemilie ooh. Did you enjoy it? How long we're you doing it for before landing the job?    
    
    
    @mayaemilie what's happening? It's the same story over here in Design. It's a battlefield! Artists cannibalising each other's work and stuff    
    
    
    @demafleez Yes that's what I mean. There are some schemes that are free menial labour, and others that are just ripping off good people    
    
    
    @mayaemilie Has your company experienced any of this?    
    
    
    @Darkengrim Hey, where is my sculpture? Do you have the mesh? I could take over if you have the obj for zBrush. Let's finish it!    
    
    
    Parents are coming over for Mother's Day SO EXCITED : ) !!! Mum hugs are the best    
    
    
    Having to tidy away / hide / relocate so many things    
    
    
    @Paul_V3Design Whoa. That is hot.    
    
    
    @toddmotto that's really nice, Todd    
    
    
    @LuminaUSA hey, nice Splat!    
    
    
    You guys, I am now freelance! Gigs are coming in thick and fast so if you need artwork, graphics or branding work done SNAP ME UP    
    
    
    One gorgeous image, hundreds of digital artists' take on it http://bit.ly/X3Yo4J  very inspiring    
    
    
    Looking forward to hopefully working with a rather cool company. The more I think about it the funner it sounds. EVERYBODY CROSS EVERYTHING    
    
    
    Ooh. Cookies.    
    
    
    Amazing what you can accomplish, when you have something else you should be doing http://on.fb.me/YbAnZF  A scribble I'm now neatening up    
    
    
    @theAngieTaylor oh, you're green!    
    
    
    Cookie overdose    
    
    
    What would you do if you were a cookie for a day?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants when does your tablet arrive?    
    
    
    @Polygoblin why? Oh I guess because everybody will want to eat you, right? NOT IF YOU GET THERE FIRST mmm    
    
    
    @odd_enough that's if you're a small man-size cookie. I'm talking big cookie. GIANT COOKIE WITH SOFT CHOCOLATE BITS oh god sugar craving    
    
    
    @odd_enough yeah I'd for sure eat myself. You are what you eat. So you'd be a cookie forever. Like some kind of human centipede cookie man    
    
    
    @CaptainChants AAAH it's going to smell like 'new' I love 'new' smell    
    
    
    @CaptainChants ah yes! New Mac smell is the best.    
    
    
    @CaptainChants they should bottle that. Then we can all smell like new Macs all the time.    
    
    
    @odd_enough @machine906 we can lay cookie eggs and sell them. Like the goose that lay golden eggs, but the cookie version    
    
    
    @CaptainChants man why are we discussing such an awesome idea in such a public place    
    
    
    Aaah familiar freelance. No more free evenings or weekends forever. Still, can't complain when it's doing awesome projects : )    
    
    
    @odd_enough @machine906 cookie worms    
    
    
    @CaptainChants yes    
    
    
    @CaptainChants maaan the role looks ideal. They aren't getting back to me though : ( tried calling and just emailed to find out the deal    
    
    
    @CaptainChants the company and ethos looks good though and I could do so much for them hooo just hope it's still open    
    
    
    @CaptainChants if its gone though I need to keep looking, so I just asked them to let me know either way *hopes*    
    
    
    @odd_enough @marmalade_tim @machine906 cookie worms that turn into cookie butterflies    
    
    
    I want to get back into sculpting. Real sculpting not just 3D. Just got inspired by @garyscottartist    
    
    
    @marmalade_tim @odd_enough @machine906 no, those would be soggy    
    
    
    @garyscottartist will do, thanks Gary. If it's ok with you, I'll be asking your advice on materials! We have very different styles ooh    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I still got my fingers crossed AAAH let's see    
    
    
    @CaptainChants thanks! I'm withholding my stalkerisms and not hounding them. Got lots going on in the meantime anyhoo yay : )    
    
    
    Collaboration happened over on fb between 3 of us artists with very different styles. @CaptainChants can we share it on here?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants hmm I sent another email last night. That's 3 emails and 2 voicemails hmmm    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I have another agency in Reading that looks good that I'll chase up today and see what's goin' down    
    
    
    @CaptainChants YESSS is Rachel on Twitter too?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I do :-0 and this time, not just for the money    
    
    
    @CaptainChants ok, I shared it and made it public but it still links back to the original which is friends only. Will it work still?    
    
    
    Saw one of @CaptainChants' heads, HAD to add a body. Rachel Pierce then rendered it - Stunning! http://on.fb.me/Ws0IVP     
    
    
    @CaptainChants Yeah I saw that. Ha! Awesome. Let's SPREAD THE ARTS    
    
    
    @CaptainChants @canoftoast I love your tumblr by the way    
    
    
    Mmm sour http://instagr.am/p/W4Lv7XnI9g/     
    
    
    Photo: cryptfever: Original Sketch by Chants, modified by Shaz and rendered by moi for teh lulz! :3 YESSS so... http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwgKNZDN     
    
    
    @captainchants @CanOfToast ah, thanks! : )    
    
    
    I've just added the skills drawing, animation and photography to my freelance profile on http://3desk.com     
    
    
    "Shaz, you're always a good human food bin. Here, have this giant plate of obesity. I'll just leave it here" http://on.fb.me/ZQ8SVR     
    
    
    Getting back into compositing YUSSS and also, modelled cloth for the first time : ) pic.twitter.com/1tFVGHAYzT    
    
    
    @Doctoe oh, is that what happened?    
    
    
    One of my favourite things to do is pick the remaining meat off the bones of a whole roast chicken carcass, alone in my room, while sobbing    
    
    
    Ah so now I remember why people with tongue piercings SHOULD NEVER CHEWING GUM    
    
    
    Need to make my main email address something less lame, but EVERYTHING is linked to that address. How does one do this?    
    
    
    Just found a hair that started growing white but then went black again. DOES THIS MEAN I HAVE SUCCESSFULLY REVERSED TIME?    
    
    
    Oh no. It is white at the root and at the tip, just black in the middle. I have not successfully reversed time. THE SAGA CONTINUES.    
    
    
    @giffgaff Hello team giffgaff, is your position for an in-house designer still open? I'm due a call back but am GIDDY WITH EXCITEMENT    
    
    
    @TheFixCreative Karin? IS THAT YOU?    
    
    
    @Donavonyoung3D Oh man I love your cover image :-0    
    
    
    Suddenly over 10,000 visits to my blogger yay! But I need to delete the associated email address meaning the content will be lost huuuff    
    
    
    Rebranding eggabo and creating some custom CVs. Creative 1am inspiration overload is happening NEED MORE DAYS IN THE WEEKEND    
    
    
    Branding is fun, you guys. Wish I could rebrand eggabo every day.    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata actually you could do with a brand image, Picar    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata I uhh.. Yes. Like a piggy. 

..Wut?    
    
    
    Just washed my 20" rims to sell, now reconsidering whether I want to let them go. They look so good now hmm    
    
    
    Should be designing but instead I did a doodle pic.twitter.com/jGFztRzQ7z    
    
    
    @Superfried Your blob round font is BEAUTIFUL. Would I be able to use it as a basis for my logo? Also your portfolio is gorgeous :-0    
    
    
    FONT FETISH    
    
    
    @Orangemoonwerks aww thanks! Hello @lorimcneeartist @jm_desantis @jankovitch @creaturedesigns @stephen_burger @mickaelsmusic @vongormanart    
    
    
    Everybody is telling me off for slouching today    
    
    
    Slouching is good for the soul    
    
    
    Slouch    
    
    
    @machine906 consider me slouched    
    
    
    Working on the much-neglected Twitter follower count for my client. Hoo boy that stuff takes time. But hey I don't want to use a robot.    
    
    
    @A_Will30 @bro_itslalizzle @ospinolicioso NO THANKS, SPAMBOT    
    
    
    @LAS13uk hey smily noseface. You're doing a smashing job on the social media. Just saying hi!    
    
    
    @CaptainChants dude! giffgaff responded! The position was on hold as they were interviewing an internal, who was then offered the job    
    
    
    @CaptainChants but they have other roles so will see..    
    
    
    @CaptainChants also, BlueSkies got back to me with another role yay! Something good is coming I CAN FEEL IT    
    
    
    Wacom wielding giant orange tshirt for my redesigned CV pic.twitter.com/HBxG8pxbvZ    
    
    
    @CaptainChants why must you songbomb me with such an awful tune, this early in the day : (    
    
    
    @LAS13uk aww that smiling noseface makes me happy. Have a smashing day.    
    
    
    @CaptainChants oooh you are ballin' guuurl. What are the upgrades?    
    
    
    I hate your font. And your choice of colours.    
    
    
    @CaptainChants can I also be part of this club? Somebody buy me a burger.    
    
    
    Great little something from the lovely people at @BlueSkiesCareer to help with your creative portfolio http://bit.ly/14sk6XN     
    
    
    This might just be the best thing I've ever seen http://moebio.com/newk/twitter/  ok so it's just an infographic thing BUT SO COOL    
    
    
    @Superfried I like the idea of this boot filling you speak of. Thank you! It's just perfect for the name. Yes of course I'll show you : )    
    
    
    1am inspiration overload AGAIN. Why at this hour? WHYYY. Producing some awesome things though, you guys    
    
    
    ..is anybody there?    
    
    
    I'm so lonely and cold    
    
    
    @brandonjcarr Some of my best drawings are on the backs of envelopes D-: New sketchbooks and clean paper make me nervous    
    
    
    @brandonjcarr OH MY GOD YOU DO THAT TOO? We must be twins <3    
    
    
    5am bedtime. Work in 3 hours. But the redesigned CV is almost ready to be unleashed :-0    
    
    
    @BlueSkiesCareer Thank YOU for creating it! It's nice and simple. Super helpful.    
    
    
    WHEN WILL THE SNEEZES END    
    
    
    @AndyM84 what are you looking for? What car is it for?    
    
    
    @AndyM84 no I was just curious, not offering you any parts or anything :-0 cuz I've got to find loads of parts for my Audi still. Oh god.    
    
    
    @DanMichaelAsh mmm Hugh Jackman *faints*    
    
    
    @AndyM84 I need pedal covers, wing mirror pods, door handles, some more bits of missing interior. This car really wasn't looked after before    
    
    
    @Superfried I used your blob font for the cover of my CV. I could redesign it forever but had to get it out. Thanks! pic.twitter.com/XnRgmz2Isk    
    
    
    @AndyM84 oh my god. Is that gasket damage? What car is that?    
    
    
    @AndyM84 aww I love that car! Yeah I totally get you. I'd love to see the before and after    
    
    
    @AndyM84 that sounds wicked! I look forward to it : ) What needs doing?    
    
    
    @AndyM84 wow :-0 ok.. well I wish you all the best. You'll be so happy when you get back in that driver's seat    
    
    
    @ThisCreative ooh your portfolio is gorgeous! Nice work, you guys : )    
    
    
    @MykeHamilton just creeped your profile and I must say I was drawn in by curiosity. Nice idea. Are you sticking these postcards to windows?    
    
    
    @MykeHamilton Cool, and how are they going down?    
    
    
    @kukas81 YAY thanks! happy wknd @vmdolphin @ugyjijes @elixat @GuillaumeFavre @futuregeist @paguthrie @mattguetta @GeorgeNijland @superpeo    
    
    
    @MykeHamilton Ah yes they sure are. Keep going at it, Myke. All the best for the role at @ThisCreative. Go for it! MAKE IT SO!    
    
    
    Whenever I read 'happy WE' in an #ff I shout WEE with my mindvoice. Obviously, this is not what WE means.    
    
    
    People I'd love to work with are looking at my LinkedIn profile YAY *dances*    
    
    
    Who wants a free thing? I'm collecting LinkedIn references. If you'd like to write me one, I may send you a FREE DIGITAL DOODLE*    
    
    
    *Only if you know/love me or have worked/collaborated with me. No lies please.    
    
    
    Why is there always white catfluff on my roof, BUT NO WHITE CAT #SoftTopWoes #AlmostRoofDownTime    
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/egNM4X  #in    
    
    
    @ronviers Aww Ron that means a lot to me. I've not yet gotten solid commercial experience in it. How would you suggest I phrase it?    
    
    
    @ronviers At the moment I'm looking for a Design/Artwork role, my resumé is tailored for that industry. Though I'd love somebody to notice!    
    
    
    @ooomf hello : ) How did you find me? Your feed is fun to read    
    
    
    Determined to get this project done so I can have a weekend. I feel another all-nighter coming on..    
    
    
    @Darrenzwhlbkl go away, spambot. NO TIME FOR YOUS.    
    
    
    @ooomf d'awww you GUUUYS <3    
    
    
    Just read a job description that requires "feminine highstreet handwriting" what the    
    
    
    2B Pencil brush in PS CS6 with tilt sensitivity. It gets blunt and everything. YES. SO MUCH YES. pic.twitter.com/d830y7ES4T    
    
    
    Photo: Doodle number 194 http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwha-x6d     
    
    
    @MarkBugby Ah yeah. Was going to put a mohican on her but glad I didn't now. Thanks Mark!    
    
    
    YAY! First recommendation on LinkedIn! Thanks @GavinPresman and @INSPIRErational : )    
    
    
    The results of my PS CS6 2B Pencil brushgasm yesterday. Nudity and NSFW as always pic.twitter.com/OvbzXzZW6a    
    
    
    More 2B Pencilgasm is happening today pic.twitter.com/GK2yqGvs4I    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan Hey how are you, Amin?!    
    
    
    Art so good it makes me feel a little bit sick    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt How do you choose what to price your prints?    
    
    
    Huge big thank you to @MarkBugby for recommending my artwork on LinkedIn! : )    
    
    
    PS CS6 2B Pencil may require sharpening soon methinks pic.twitter.com/2mbYxLMpgi    
    
    
    @MarkBugby You get more than me!    
    
    
    Graphic Designer jobs, WHY YOU ARE REQUIRE "SOUND KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERTISE OF MS WORD AND POWERPOINT"?    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt how do you print? I was asking because your prints look cheap :-0 for the amount of awesome that they are    
    
    
    @mayaemilie yeah I'm clean avoiding those jobs. They're clearly not creative, will probably involve admin. Until I get desperate ahaha    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt oh so you do your own shipping? People are asking for prints of my stuff but hoo boy I don't know where to start :-0    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt what's that portal you use for your shop? Your work is presented so nicely on there    
    
    
    @DigitalGuru Thanks for your email and for putting me forward. YAY I hope they call me in :-0 CROSS YOUR FINGERS FOR ME JAMES : )    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt Oh man, I am ALL OVER THAT ..as soon as I get this project done for work. Thanks, Ben!    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I chopped me one of those yesterday! I went for a real short and heavy fringe : ) CHUNKY    
    
    
    OH MY GOD. It is DEFINITELY time for a RAM upgrade #DeathByProgressBars    
    
    
    Beachballin' like a boss pic.twitter.com/wmiFffZv8E    
    
    
    @Jauxiles haha thanks! I was drawn to your style and AAAW NOFACE <3    
    
    
    @paperbanana_com wooo! Hello @bohemiangypsyja @peterpachoumis @patternific @marchetourism @techecon @stefanoepifani @toridraws    
    
    
    Dear artist friends, when your head is bursting with concepts, how do you go about getting it all down AND finishing up pieces?    
    
    
    @BarryTheArtGuy thumbnails YES! I've yet to work on that technique. I tend to get really involved and then it becomes 5am and oops work soon    
    
    
    @odd_enough Yeah actually I tend to sketch it on the backs of envelopes and then take pics of those, import and render later    
    
    
    Whoa. Woke up to the knocking of the HOTTEST DELIVERY GUY I'VE EVER SEEN. I am now set for the day.    
    
    
    @dejanight cool! I like the way you do skin tone. Do you do the eyes last? I do, they're the best bit!    
    
    
    Good to speak to a few good studios and lovely agents today. Job search is going well. Hopefully I'll land something awesome soon : )    
    
    
    In the meantime, freelance and artwork is keeping me sweating. No rest for the relentless.    
    
    
    Thanks @CaptainChants for sharing this http://bit.ly/Tvb2uG  inking brush set for PS. Worth it? Or do you stick to the default?    
    
    
    Skintone is my latest 'thing to conquer' pic.twitter.com/LtYbIr5l0F    
    
    
    Just found a vacancy that requires application by post. POST?    
    
    
    @GameTxtures why did you stop eating bread?    
    
    
    @GameTxtures gluten is the worst! Makes me instantly look pregnant. The worst kind of food baby. Glad you're feeling better though.    
    
    
    Also checking out another company that looks and sounds pretty cool.. WISH ME LUCK, YOU GUYS    
    
    
    @GameTxtures yeah same, I think it's pretty normal. Just that some of us are more sensitive to it..    
    
    
    @GameTxtures me too. Lets do this!    
    
    
    @dejanight they are pretty adamant that ALL APPLICATIONS MUST BE SENT BY POST TO THIS ADDRESS. What the    
    
    
    @GameTxtures @odd_enough or should it be, "Bun of the year" #glutenfree #humourfree    
    
    
    @JamesBlakstarJ I know, right! Though for the attractive salary that's on offer, I'd comfortably be able to afford a stamp : )    
    
    
    @dejanight I'm going for Design and Artworker roles, Branding too. I just love making stuff I can be proud to show off..    
    
    
    @dejanight yeah haha I'm wise to the pornbots, don't you worry    
    
    
    @dejanight thank you, I will definitely get there. No doubt. Just need to focus and knock down some more doors of opportunity.    
    
    
    @TheGlutenBaby @gametxtures is that a food baby made of gluten? Awesome. Actually that blog sounds cool..    
    
    
    Artworking all weekend BUT IT'S OK because it's sunny    
    
    
    Also, I can wear my fringe as a giant oversized quiff. THIS DAY JUST GETS AWESOMMER AND AWESOMMER    
    
    
    Automating localisable text along a curved path with even spacing and collision detection to make translated graphics. There must be a way?    
    
    
    @YemaYema @tonyjohnson C4D IS THE BEST!    
    
    
    @YemaYema @tonyjohnson ah he looks cute. Will you be boning him too?    
    
    
    @YemaYema @tonyjohnson Cool! I look forward to seeing the results : )    
    
    
    @odd_enough I had a microwaved 3 day old chicken carcass. THE BEST KIND OF CARCASS.    
    
    
    @Illustruction BRING TOP HATS BACK    
    
    
    @Mospheric @arronwalker and what's wrong with Intuos3? I am also dreaming of a Cintiq *floats away into space*    
    
    
    @Mospheric @odd_enough @arronwalker yeah, @CaptainChants has one of those and it looks pretty hot    
    
    
    The Yiynova website is awful. THEY EVEN USE COMIC SANS IN A HORRENDOUS BANNER. I don't even.. omg this is so bad http://www.yiynova.com/en/     
    
    
    @CaptainChants the rotating image thing is glitchy. It's completely unnavigable and they use default PS effect brushes and the colours AAARG    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I'm taken aback at how terrible it is. Did that not put you off?    
    
    
    @Superfried ooh I like the first one :-0 yum    
    
    
    @CaptainChants it's definitely a concept I will get in the future. Not at the moment though I'm quite happy with my Intuos3    
    
    
    Surely it's always good to keep inspired by the awesome that is out there, to better yourself    
    
    
    I don't understand why so many artists are put off by other artists that they consider to be "better" than them    
    
    
    Learn from the countless ways to skin cats, and find your own style    
    
    
    @_XaKu @BelgianBoolean AWWW so much love <3 : )    
    
    
    @Superfried Keep it up, you guys. I look forward to more. Say "Hi" to Mark for me *waves frantically* *screams* *runs away*    
    
    
    @BelgianBoolean @_XaKu I'm no longer confortable in this conversation oh god what have I started    
    
    
    Interviews don't scare me. I LOVE interviews. It's the endless, helpless waiting afterwards to hear back that makes me poop a little    
    
    
    @marmalade_tim @BelgianBoolean @_XaKu Ah yeah good plan. WHERE IS IT?    
    
    
    @_XaKu @marmalade_tim @belgianboolean wait what is it that you made? I'm seeing a bunch of HDRs, is that right?    
    
    
    @marmalade_tim @_xaku @belgianboolean ah that is cool!    
    
    
    @_XaKu is this it? Daaang! <3    
    
    
    @_XaKu ahaha yesss. SUCCESS! Curiosity got the better of me but I'm glad I found it : ) That fan letter was nice. Went through your pics too    
    
    
    @CaptainChants @alyssaltallent mmm squelchy    
    
    
    Dad's getting a new car DAD'S GETTING A NEW CAR! Another reason to go visit the ol' parents : )    
    
    
    Dad only wants me to visit because he wants to have my car parked on the drive for all the neighbours to see    
    
    
    Also, Mum's got new chickens and really wants me to meet them oh man I miss my family    
    
    
    In other news, I've finally been forced to create a Word version of my CV    
    
    
    76KB of sheer awesome    
    
    
    @nlr8 I have so many versions now. So tired of hearing that I'm 'overqualified' UUUGH    
    
    
    @Gemini_official your artwork looks like dreams <3    
    
    
    @BethBH oh my god what do you use to dye your hair? It's the colours I so desperately want!    
    
    
    @Polygoblin screenshots please    
    
    
    Reeeally want to draw, but if I start now I won't sleep till at least 5am. INSPIRATION, WHY YOU DO THIS?    
    
    
    “@tonykarpinski: Oil painting , nude pic.twitter.com/25DseHtW1G” I love this    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Love the movement and energy throughout your brand. The showreel is inspiring!    
    
    
    Just watched a Motion Graphics showreel that has inspired me to make some 3D and vector-based illos BUT I HAVE DEADLINES hnnng    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd I certainly am! I was called by Claire (who sounds lovely!) this morning and have been checking you guys out since    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd I must say I am thoroughly impressed so far. I'd LOVE to be involved! You guys look fun and focussed. Gives out a great vibe : )    
    
    
    @ArtsyPabster I'm going to do it. Right after I whoop this deliverable. Are you going to do it too? I can't hold it in! I'M SO INSPIRED.    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Claire is from an agency. For sure, thanks! Let me know what happens. I'm sure Claire has passed on my CV already but I'll check    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Awesome, thank you Rachel. Have a smashing evening and hopefully see you soon : )    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Rachel! Gemma has indeed received my CV YAY! : ) Ok I better get on top of my work this end so yes speak soon : )    
    
    
    @ArtsyPabster Really? After I beat a deadline I just want to do more stuff, MAKE NEW DEADLINES. They drive portfolio and skill set    
    
    
    Making translated graphics for the Japanese Partners. I am a whole new level of confused.    
    
    
    I urgently need a good handwritten Japanese font that retains legibility down to possibly 8pt. WHO KNOWS ONE? Preferably free please thanks.    
    
    
    Got this 20" beauty floating around my room. Can't bring myself to let it go <3 @Audi http://instagram.com/p/X79d3zHI4U/     
    
    
    Have you seen the Google Street View Hyperlapse yet? http://vimeo.com/63653873#  Just incredible    
    
    
    @CaptainChants @ihearthorchata Everybody loves me today. I think my heart is going to explode.    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata @CaptainChants Hey look I'm in your favourites! I just wiped my pear on my jeans to clean it but it's now got jeanfuzz on it    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata @captainchants all is good here, Picar. Getting better by the day in fact! How are you?    
    
    
    @ricardopresto wait WHAT? I thought this was Photoshop trickery but this is a real thing?

THIS

is

too

cool.    
    
    
    @cikes hello Chris, are you guys at Volume expanding into London? That sounds exciting    
    
    
    @ricardopresto ah nooo THE MAGIC IS GONE    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Good morning, how are you? Hey it turns out that your HQ is 3mins from where my company's HQ was! WEIRD huh :-0    
    
    
    @tonykarpinski ah this is so beautiful. I want to be a cheetah when I grow up.    
    
    
    @Superfried @siscott77 oh god that's amazing    
    
    
    BACK TO THE DRAWING BOARD. To get these Japanese graphics out of the way before working on my portfolio : )    
    
    
    DESIGNERS: If you work or have worked at an agency, how did you get in there in the first place without agency experience?    
    
    
    I've had feedback on several occasions that, because I'm a Head of Design, I cannot do an Artworker role    
    
    
    All I want to do is make cool stuff for people to enjoy and LEARN ALL THE THINGS    
    
    
    @nlr8 Yup I went from showing off the big titles, to diluting them, to putting them at the end of the list. Now I may have to lose them.    
    
    
    @Gafyn Thanks Gafyn. Where was your in-house work?    
    
    
    @Gafyn wow, and what are you doing now?    
    
    
    @Gafyn Groovy. Oh boy, wish me luck, Gafyn. I hope to hear good news form another agency tomorrow. I will keep an eye on the way you roll    
    
    
    @fartpalace Are you sure it wasn't pus?    
    
    
    @fartpalace oh god now I feel bad    
    
    
    The floppy disk means save, and 14 other icons that don't make sense anymore: http://ow.ly/jH8o6  thanks @3seven9    
    
    
    @shad_0 @3seven9 I quite like the history behind them to be honest : ) adds an extra dimension    
    
    
    @3seven9 @shad_0 changing them would be like changing a language. Do you think they will ever change? Language is dynamic after all    
    
    
    3 more translated Japanese graphics to go LET'S DO THIS *screams internally* cheer me on, you guys. I need you.    
    
    
    @talkthomas YESSS thanks Thomas! I'M ON IT. Also, thank you for your kind comment. What did you find interesting about my blog?    
    
    
    From the commissioned 3D animation for IBIS Capital. See the finished bird in flight http://www.ibiscapital.co.uk/  pic.twitter.com/nQAdKz27Bo    
    
    
    @talkthomas wow thank you so much :-0 that's so kind aaah I'm going to melt. Yes, when it's something you love doing, it's just playtime : )    
    
    
    @talkthomas thanks, Thomas. You too, enjoy your evening. It's nice to meet you.    
    
    
    “@fightpunch: Obsessed with designing guns lately, playing too much FPS. pic.twitter.com/VaaW1pRDMi” wow! I love this    
    
    
    Think the time is approaching to finally change my Twitter egg    
    
    
    @nlr8 @captainchants @pgcreatives I'M IN A MEETING BUT AAAH THIS LOOKS INTERESTING THANKS NICOLE    
    
    
    @nlr8 @CaptainChants @pgcreatives ah guys, 'lose' is spelt 'loose'. PLEASE CORRECT THAT. Spelling errors are not the lick. I'll look today.    
    
    
    @lolwarlol dungarees aren't fashionable?    
    
    
    @lolwarlol pff. Never been one to follow fashion. Let's all wear dungarees forever!    
    
    
    Virgin Media. Why must you suck like so?    
    
    
    The Japanese graphics are sent! Yesss now I can focus in fun things tomorrow. Namely a cool piece of artwork for a record label. Stay tuned.    
    
    
    @Superfried did you also avoid joining Facebook when it came out?    
    
    
    @Superfried same here. Some sort of complex to do with fear of addiction to either. Use fb for art stuff but glad I joined Twitter now.    
    
    
    @Superfried so many great contacts on Twitter. Fb is full of people I went to school with that post pictures of babies and food YAWN    
    
    
    Going to make a 3D illo today. Once I've spoken to the record label people about their artwork yesss.    
    
    
    I know they say "pencil before pixel" but hot dang all I want to do is go straight to 3D    
    
    
    Would probably save a bunch of time if I have a clear concept sketched out first though, right? 3D gurus, help me out here    
    
    
    Kinda just have it in my head and freestyle    
    
    
    @Superfried that's what it's all about. Conversations with real people. It really helps your brand, too. But you know that already : )    
    
    
    @Superfried fb does have its plus points. You can make stuff spread quite easily on there, get your name out with offers and cool stuff    
    
    
    @Superfried to get people liking and sharing, as a business tool. Depends how you want to use it really. I'm glad you don't post food/babies    
    
    
    @fartpalace I love your constant anger    
    
    
    My mum has named one of our chickens "Daffy"    
    
    
    Photo: Skintone. Needs work. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwiht6OK     
    
    
    Cycling weather YAY!!! : )    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick you want to be my cycling buddy? We can ride into the sunset together JUST LIKE WE ALWAYS PLANNED    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick why won't you be my cycling buddy : (    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick cycling, on a bike? God you are SO not the outdoorsy type are you haha. May go for the first ride of the year today iunno    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick not cycling as in cycling the server    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick because my car is AT THE GARAGE as you know full well. Hey I get it back today with a whole new clutch pedal *grinnn*    
    
    
    Just rediscovered @FengZhuDesign and he's on Instagram! Such incredible, fast artwork with an immense level of detail    
    
    
    I still really want a Nokia 3310    
    
    
    @maxwelloginni Hey Max, what happened with your harddrive disaster in the end?    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick I know, right. I used to stare at that phone in catalogues and drool    
    
    
    I want to draw a squid. A big, wet squid.    
    
    
    With SLIME. Yes.    
    
    
    Excited about a new opportunity that's come up involving Motion Graphics. YAY! Fingers crossed.    
    
    
    Also waiting to hear back from another studio that looks exciting oh man so many waits aaa    
    
    
    @snarkies aww well done! That's great news! : ) best of luck in your new workplace    
    
    
    Yay App screen design! This is fun, you guys. Just remembered how much I know about UX. FEELS GOOD.    
    
    
    @jakobgilmore who have you got? I've got Sandra Bollock    
    
    
    Chicken. Roast chicken. All I want is chicken. Why is there no chicken?    
    
    
    @Gemini_official ah dang! When was this? Yeah I start showing my brake lights miles before I stop now, and make sure they are backing off    
    
    
    Looking forward to getting my car back. Tons of problems and seems the only thing I can do is throw money at it.    
    
    
    Oh, no no. Those aren't just normal spark plugs, those are PLATINUM ... :-|    
    
    
    Oh, no no. You don't have clutch cables, you have a HYDRAULIC SYSTEM and because it's Quattro, that'll be 5 hours labour please ... :-0    
    
    
    Oh, no no. You need new front brake disks. But yours are made of RARE AFRICAN BEETLE WINGS ... D-:    
    
    
    Oh, no no. All the parts I got for you are genuine and have a year's warranty on them. Oh yeah, you paid extra for that ... :-c    
    
    
    Oh, no no. Don't worry about that intoxicating fuel smell in the cabin, THAT'S THE LEAST OF YOUR WORRIES AHAHA ... O.o    
    
    
    I love my mechanic    
    
    
    @Rachela8 I know, right. That would crush my childhood : (    
    
    
    @Rachela8 @simonapps Let's not forget that the media love to crawl all over stuff like this and hype it up. It could just all be dirty lies    
    
    
    @moodstrike My bill is now almost at the price I paid for the car! But hey I don't want to give it up, it's my dream car : )    
    
    
    @jakobgilmore Well oh my. He's got a cute smile. You should take it as a compliment :-0    
    
    
    @moodstrike Yeah exactly, it got so bad that I was faced with the horrible decision of whether I should consider selling it. Aaagh.    
    
    
    I wish cars were bionic and healed themselves omg how cool would that be    
    
    
    @talkthomas Yeah dude. I went from manual, to auto, back to manual. Didn't like cruise control either nooo. GIVE ME ALL THE CONTROLS.    
    
    
    @talkthomas Paddleshift was cool though. Steering wheel controls for the radio too, I miss that.    
    
    
    @moodstrike Exactly. I couldn't take that risk. Also I'm totally in love with my car. Shame it's been so horribly neglected before me    
    
    
    @talkthomas You see those cars that park themselves? Nooo thank you    
    
    
    @moodstrike aww thanks! : ) I hope yours is smooth sailing from here, too.    
    
    
    Ok so, I just got the bill from my mechanic. LOOKS LIKE I WON'T BE EATING FOR THE REST OF THE MONTH.    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Would you like to buy my 20"s? PLEASE BUY MY 20"s    
    
    
    @MarkBugby you never know unless you try. Also your wheels have 4 holes, these rims have 5. I HAVE A SPARE WHEEL KIT THAT WOULD FIT THOUGH?    
    
    
    Been in Illustrator all day. Still on Illustrator. Hopefully get this done before it suddenly becomes 2am :-0    
    
    
    YAY I GOT MY CAR BACK!!! Good day to get it back, too. Been driving about all day with the hood back : ) ..Think I'm burnt    
    
    
    @jasonbroberts COOL! You attract flies like when one wears a yellow t-shirt? I LOVE red hair omg so striking    
    
    
    @JamesBlakstarJ Pff I just had to fight for the last, tightest parking spot on my road. I parallel parked like a GENIUS.    
    
    
    @MarkBugby a little purple Audi TT : )    
    
    
    @MarkBugby ooh I like Focuses. Turbodiesel, nice. Yup just got a flywheel in mine, too. Oh, no no. Not just any flywheel, mine's DUAL MASS    
    
    
    @PTMuffins ahaha.. I.. I dunno either. It just happened I couldn't stop myself    
    
    
    I just high-fived a mosquito    
    
    
    NO MORE OPEN WINDOWS EVER    
    
    
    @Polygoblin what's your strategy now? Also, how did you choose who to unfollow?    
    
    
    @scribblepuff AWWW SO KIND. Thank you so much : ) I look forward to seeing more comics from you.    
    
    
    @odd_enough @Polygoblin Ah, sweet. I try to keep mine around the 200 mark but lately it's gone a bit over. So many good artists out there!    
    
    
    @AllyAlbon Aww I love that! Very nice. Like a flowery giraffe pony <3    
    
    
    @MichelleGArt RED: heat, passion, love, appetite, lust, warmth, danger, blood, beauty, happiness, courage, force, anger, fire, seduction..    
    
    
    @Mat_Stomp Yay. I FOUND A HEALTH FREAK! Hi : )    
    
    
    Going cycling, fasted. Going to beat my 7mi on Sunday and not die at the end of it this time. WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT. Time to get on form.    
    
    
    Back from 8mi bike ride in the sun. FEELS GOOD. Soon I'll be back doing 20mi with no sweat. Yesss.    
    
    
    Good to hear from an exciting job opportunity this morning!    
    
    
    @odd_enough Why can't you do it anymore? I'm pushing hard to get my 6pack back. Hip and collar bones are back on show. BEAST MODE.    
    
    
    @mystichobodev @odd_enough ahaha yup. Almost got squished by at least 2 buses and 4 cars and a motorbike today. Ugh.    
    
    
    @odd_enough @AndyM84 Pff. I don't want to hear your excuses. Just do it.    
    
    
    @odd_enough @AndyM84 Do, or do not. It's no good to "try" http://www.redlemonclub.com/brand-you/on-why-its-no-good-to-try-you-must-do …    
    
    
    @Illustruction ooh I LOVE IT! Are you happy with how they came out in the end? Good choice on colour    
    
    
    @asterixinspace HOW DARE YOU    
    
    
    @lolwarlol @asterixinspace ahaha! Hey look we're famous    
    
    
    @AllyAlbon and what is "Ally-fied"?    
    
    
    Might be getting a bodybuilder housemate! Yesss    
    
    
    Stuck on the shoulders.. thinking to cover it with hair. YES! HAIR! pic.twitter.com/Y8h7rryxMY    
    
    
    If only it was socially acceptable to store pie in one's hair, for easy-access instant sustenance any time of day or night. If only.    
    
    
    If only hair was actually strawberry laces. If only.    
    
    
    I wish I was a jelly bean    
    
    
    Just realised I'm working tomorrow, so should probably NOT stay up all night on the Wacom pic.twitter.com/5zaWjP449Q    
    
    
    @colinwren Makes sense. My best concepts happen at 1am. Must be when I'm half-asleep therefore closer to my subconscious?    
    
    
    @jayp2468 Yes. But it would be sweet. GET IT? SWEET? *self highfive* .. *slowclap* .. *I'll see myself out*    
    
    
    Determined to draw machine things and get awesome at it pic.twitter.com/uM4D1g9Jj6    
    
    
    Music so good it makes you close your eyes and tilt your head back mmm    
    
    
    Working on silhouettes to start with, then will work on some ref studies for good ol' fashioned hardcore practice pic.twitter.com/CGns7EHrp9    
    
    
    Want to see what my professional graphics and design is like? Bit different to my personal stuff ha pic.twitter.com/9XndNDQtGW    
    
    
    @ronviers there's a lot of back and forth with this client. I've been there for a while so have most of the say now, but still collaborative    
    
    
    @sav_1987 yeah! Thanks Sav. How's your job front?    
    
    
    @sav_1987 get a job in that 5 months? How's the project going? What is it this time, anything interesting?    
    
    
    @sav_1987 you want to be my intern again? AAAW sweet!    
    
    
    @sav_1987 could definitely do with an extra pair of hands especially with layout work in AI. There's always plenty to do.    
    
    
    Need a decent font substitute for Helvetica    
    
    
    Working on a new product for a client. Making new stuff is the funnest.    
    
    
    Don't know what I just ate, but pretty sure it wasn't food anymore    
    
    
    Just noticed that the home icon on the twitter app is a little birdhouse aww cool    
    
    
    Shoes. SHOES.    
    
    
    @MarkBugby as was abundantly clear this morning. Too much info? Too much info.    
    
    
    Isn't it cool that bees puke honey    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan bees don't poop    
    
    
    Those that use autounfollow tracker bots, you realise you lose more followers every time it spams your account or DMs people? STOP IT    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan I know right. You ever heard the term "bee anus"? Me neither.    
    
    
    Oh. I love when I open a template file in AI all hyped about creating a thing, and it tells me all the linked files have moved. I LOVE THAT.    
    
    
    TextWrangler is pretty sweet    
    
    
    @Gafyn Hey, I hope you're well. I applied to an awesome sounding place, they said I sound like I'm more suited to an agency environment..    
    
    
    @Gafyn They said something along the lines of I'm too much of a passionate designer for the role I don't even    
    
    
    @Gafyn ..but the agencies still want the agency experience. Whaaat. I'm beginning to really LOVE freelancing though.    
    
    
    @Gafyn There is another place I've got my fingers crossed for. So let's see. Ohh it's all so exciting.    
    
    
    @Luminersss ah dude keep strong and DO WHAT YOU LOVE, always. You cannot go wrong if you follow your passion.    
    
    
    @Luminersss s'cool, yo. Just remember that you're doing this for you. Surround yourself with people that support your dreams and aspirations    
    
    
    @nlr8 Dude, would you be interested in taking part at the Croydon Bakeoff? http://christopm.com/index.php/the-great-croydon-bake-off/ … Take a look and let me know @ChristoPM    
    
    
    @ChristoPM You may want to fix your banner image on Twitter. Half of it is cropped off. Thanks.    
    
    
    @odd_enough You are just so NICE. Hi @Dralex789 @Mospheric @Polygoblin @TheonlyAlexW @ruthmadeline @mystichobodev @axl99 @_XaKu @Saferdan    
    
    
    @sav_1987 Depends what sort of project I'm working on. Usually ComputerArts Mag, Smashing Mag, WebDesignerDepot never fail to inspire    
    
    
    @sav_1987 I'm a busy lady. I like it that way.    
    
    
    @ronviers Hey Ron. I really appreciate your support and kind words of encouragement. It means a lot. Have a great day : )    
    
    
    @DI_KittyPants nice to meet you, Sarah. OH LOOK I'm your 200th follower : ) *dances*    
    
    
    @ChristoPM it's uhh.. It's still not fixed there umm. Oh, same goes for your official bakeoff twitter there. Please fix it. Thanks.    
    
    
    @fightpunch I just LOVE that tooth head. Also love your style of drawing, it looks so effortless hnnng    
    
    
    @Jauxiles what happens? NO DON'T TELL ME    
    
    
    @GraceSandford ahaha thanks! Nice to meet you. Yes it's umm.. iunno I just.. I felt inspired and it kinda just happened hmm    
    
    
    My hands were full so I licked the iPhone to answer it OH GOD THE SALTY GREASY HORROR THAT ENSUED    
    
    
    @drumstudiosltd hello! Your work looks great, though have you got plans to optimise your site for mobile devices?    
    
    
    @ChristoPM What, after you cheated on me by going to another Designer? I don't think so, chum.    
    
    
    @ChristoPM Just because that Designer was CHEAP, might I add. Seriously though, fix it. Thanks, chum.    
    
    
    @drumstudiosltd Yay! I look forward to it. Nice to meet you.    
    
    
    You can see more of my exhibition graphics work, print and web stuff for one client here: https://www.facebook.com/LuminaLearning/photos_stream …    
    
    
    @VolumeLtd Yaaay!    
    
    
    @Gafyn I know, right? Thanks Gafyn. I'll keep pushing forward.    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Wow. Thank you very much! I'm slightly overwhelmed with all kinds of feels    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad this may be a big fat question but, how did you become a Creative Director?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad ohhh I see. Cool! So what do you do day to day? Have you always had an interest in games?    
    
    
    Designing infographics for automisation yaaay. Good to work with devs that are up to date with current trends and love to be challenged    
    
    
    Also, how do people eat green bananas I AM COVERED IN STICKY    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad omg how did you get into Blizzard?! What were you doing?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad ahaha cool! I LOVE the character concepts in WoW. Are you happy with what you do now?    
    
    
    oh no oh NO OH NO I feel an inspiration wave coming on NOOO IT'S BEDTIME WHY DOES THIS ALWAYS HAPPEN annng    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad ohh I bet. AH I WISH omg would be SWEET if I could draw sexy freaks all day and get paid for it! I'm a designer by profession    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad well, digital artist really. Multi disciplined and always keen to grow my skill set. I LOVE concept drawing, always have.    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad that is my dream, omg don't say such things you'll get me excited!!! What kind of artwork are you looking for?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad That's my forte! If you have some concepts in your head now, I'd be keen to explore them cuz WHY NOT    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Money is important but not the driving force. Within reason, that is.    
    
    
    Ok going to finally clear out my room tomorrow, so that I can clear desk clear mind something something    
    
    
    Also, work is suddenly really full on with this new project. AWESOME!    
    
    
    Uh I got so into this work that I forgot to send the invoice oops    
    
    
    Recruitment people, a "great place to work" is NOT a 'benefit' or an excuse for a woeful salary omg    
    
    
    @toddmotto filenames with spaces in WHY    
    
    
    Beautiful cycling weather! Going to go for a quick 8 miles brb    
    
    
    Much harder ride than anticipated :-0 caused by doing an hour of resistance before going. Swallowed some meaty flies, too. BACK TO WORK : )    
    
    
    @Daniel_Guru hello, I invited you to connect on LinkedIn because the invite email I got looked dodgy :-0 Hope you're well    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad I like where this is going. I like it a LOT. Watch this space. What's the timescale on this?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad hoo boy YES PLEASE! Thank you, Tom!    
    
    
    @sarahljay I really like your website : )    
    
    
    @RyanThinker Why? I'm torn between Freelancing and Employment I JUST DUNNO. Also, hi! Nice to meet you.    
    
    
    @estrildid ohhh nooo : ( I shrunk out of my expensive jeans, thinking of boiling them in the washing machine to shrink them hmm    
    
    
    @estrildid yeah, usually stretching whilst wet does the trick    
    
    
    @RyanThinker Oh, so companies are actively headhunting you? That's awesome. Recently, I made a pros and cons list between the two..    
    
    
    @RyanThinker What are the things you feel you are missing out on?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad I see. Cool! Well of course I'd love to be involved, if you'll have me. It sounds exciting! Do keep me posted    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad In the meantime, I've always looked for a useful reason to draw weapons : )    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad oh wow! Thank you so much, Tom! AAA!    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Drop top? Why 1996? It's nice. Is it within reach? Just get something that isn't going to cause months of heartache like mine!    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Though, ultimately, mine is beginning to prove its worth. I reckon go for it, if it's something you really want. Why not.    
    
    
    May the fourth something something    
    
    
    Saturday is so not good to go cycling on. Almost ran over so many people #PedestrianOverload    
    
    
    I HAVEN'T SEEN STARWARS there I said it am I the only one?    
    
    
    @ColtonGeil None of them :-0    
    
    
    @ColtonGeil Yup they go way over my head. I did try to watch them once but snoozed all the way through    
    
    
    @RyanThinker It was fascinating, actually. Employment ended in a giant list of blockers / cons. Freelance had so many opportunities / pros!    
    
    
    @RyanThinker Do you not get that through your clients or out of work activities?    
    
    
    @RyanThinker Oh I see. I've had at least 2 agents calling me every day! Nothing landed. Thinking now whether it's something I really want    
    
    
    @estrildid I DID IT! Put the giant jeans in the wash. Let's see if they shrink to fit, fingers crossed    
    
    
    Yay I'm going to get to draw a MOTORBIKE LOGO! Sweet : )    
    
    
    Just watched the webinar for #AdobeMAX and aaa! So many exciting movements. This is going to be really great!    
    
    
    @jakobgilmore aaa! What for?    
    
    
    Why are there still May the 4th jokes happening I don't even    
    
    
    @glitchritual ahaha excellent ...*cries*    
    
    
    @CaptainChants dude, check out @yoillo ..what you reckon? Worth a mosey?    
    
    
    I'm taking on commissions once again! I'll draw you anything. ANYTHING.    
    
    
    @christian_fei I LOVE DRAWING OCTOPUSESESS!    
    
    
    YAY! Got a gig! Now to get down to business : )    
    
    
    @Francext @christian_fei Two.. Octopi? Octopusses? Octopi.    
    
    
    @Francext @christian_fei Octuplets    
    
    
    @Francext @christian_fei Wait, do you really want octopusessesssssees drawn?    
    
    
    Confused by octopi    
    
    
    Every time I draw I see myself get better and faster and that just makes me feel warm and gooey inside    
    
    
    @Jauxiles omg @CaptainChants check this out. How much do you want to collab over this right now?    
    
    
    Oh golly I just LOVE UV GLOSS pic.twitter.com/6tMv03kLPV    
    
    
    Surprising myself at how good this commission is turning out, considering I've not really explored mech this thoroughly before. YESSS : )    
    
    
    @twisted_k hey, when you work out does your sweat sometimes smell like popcorn?    
    
    
    @twisted_k eeew! Yeah I get real salty sometimes. About to go for a quick 8 miles after an hour of resistance. I'll update you on the smells    
    
    
    @twisted_k cycling, just hit 4mi    
    
    
    @twisted_k ok, 8.57mi done. Sweat has no smell. Normal saltiness level. I'm apparently well hydrated. Hot dang it was WINDY.    
    
    
    Happy to see that more video games and concept artist recruitment people are looking at my LinkedIn : )    
    
    
    Will be riding a 600cc motorbike for the first time on Sunday. Have to do the theory test and omg when did those get so hard :-0    
    
    
    Totally awesome when a client is happy : )    
    
    
    @christian_fei I have plenty of squidlike things in my portfolio, check it out here: http://eggabo.tumblr.com/post/12848463644 … there's more in my archive    
    
    
    @christian_fei Let me know if you would like a commissioned piece, and we can sort something out for you : )    
    
    
    @Jauxiles I just had a vision from the Matrix    
    
    
    @talkthomas It's just so feely. Wasn't expecting it hidden in this booklet but ah, just adds a touch of glamour doesn't it    
    
    
    "That'll do" is the worst thing you can say as a creative. Take pride in what you do.    
    
    
    @talkthomas Yes, time and budget do have to be taken into account.    
    
    
    @talkthomas  It can be easy to get carried away, but we must learn ways to get faster and better without compromising quality    
    
    
    @talkthomas I get you http://cdn.chud.com/7/7b/7b7f0125_triangle.jpg …    
    
    
    @talkthomas Ha. Yup. Just been chasing one invoice for over a week now. That's the not-so-awesome part of freelancing.    
    
    
    Wow. Motorbikes are really sexy :-0    
    
    
    After this commission is done I'll definitely be exploring more mech and drawing bikes    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt Ben, how do you handle NSFW warnings? Do you think they are necessary? I've just plastered them all over my LinkedIn    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt Ah yeah, that's true. I love that about your work. Such a tease.    
    
    
    That feel when a project is so fun that you forget to shower for a week <3    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Well oh my. How does she run? Are you pleased?    
    
    
    Ok so, after two days of staring at and drawing motorbikes, this literally exploded out of me pic.twitter.com/nVnmfn14OQ    
    
    
    @odd_enough I actually couldn't help it wtf. It's the fastest skin tone I've ever done as well! May as well finish it now hey    
    
    
    @CaptainChants ooh.. Was it Shaz_2?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants so, you're totally not into them in that way? It could be worth a shot..    
    
    
    Ok so this week I have proved that I have no self control when it comes to double cream and I can't help but drink it like juice    
    
    
    Can't wait to get out on the bike tomorrow. I'm going to sweat out all the cream. ALL OF IT.    
    
    
    Mmm cream    
    
    
    @LauraHohman oh my god your hair is such a beautiful colour :-0    
    
    
    @talkthomas my invoice didn't get paid in time : ( another weekend with no money. Tom why do people think this is ok?    
    
    
    So far I've had an average of over 20 recruitment agents call me a week, all loving my CV and proposing jobs    
    
    
    I get about 6 potential positions emailed through to me every day    
    
    
    But I dunno, you guys. Nothing screams "awesome". Nothing looks like it would be worth the move back into employment.    
    
    
    Freelancing has been great so far. Tough, but great. Really enjoying helping a variety of clients and growing my skills in the right places    
    
    
    It's hit me hard this time round when a big client hasn't paid an invoice I was heavily relying on. That part of freelancing is crappy    
    
    
    I gotta tighten up my contracts and get serious. Got to remember that this is my life and my business now, not just a hobby anymore.    
    
    
    That's what makes it exciting. The thrill! I GET TO DRAW FOR A LIVING, YOU GUYS!!!    
    
    
    @moodstrike well it was kind of a forced choice for me as my job wasn't paying enough. It was also no longer challenging or growing me.    
    
    
    @moodstrike so I cut loose and started accepting clients and jobs that were knocking on my door anyway. I've always had people want stuff.    
    
    
    @moodstrike the only thing is that now I have to set out terms and contracts at the start, so that both parties are clear from the outset    
    
    
    @moodstrike are you following @MoonApe? He's really great at tips and motivation in short, easily digestible snippets.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Green pants pic.twitter.com/50mIZL6jUj    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt I just love the word boobs. BOOBS.    
    
    
    @demafleez It's tough financially, with clients wanting everything for nothing. Also, I'm not a natural business person, so that's new.    
    
    
    There really is no way of falling off a 600cc motorbike without injuring yourself. Let's hope I can walk again by Thursday!    
    
    
    I have a fat bruise that, if you squint really hard and use a lot of imagination, looks a bit like a face    
    
    
    @talkthomas Aww I'm fine, thanks Tom. I need to be 100% by Thursday as I'll be back on it :-0 The bike is fine - it was cushioned by my leg    
    
    
    @JoshCallowayArt really nice stuff on your blog, Josh. Nice to meet you    
    
    
    Today I learned that as good as the engine sounds, throttling one's vehicle does in fact, have a considerable effect on fuel consumption    
    
    
    Passed my motorbike theory test! : )    
    
    
    @lolwarlol Thanks, Bozwonk!    
    
    
    @talkthomas Dude. Throttling one's vehicle, with some control, is the way to live life. That's what fuel is for!    
    
    
    @MarkBugby YAY! Also got back my ability to walk. MOTORBIKE DAY TOMORROW!    
    
    
    Contracts contracts contracts    
    
    
    @Luminersss meet people that share the same interests. As much as you should keep pushing for what you love, friends can bring you down.    
    
    
    @Luminersss yup it's important to also keep up your morale, too    
    
    
    Fell off the bike AGAIN and obtained some fresh bruises. But you guys! Leaning into bends is the funnest!    
    
    
    My brand new Doc Martens are pretty much covered in oil and gear change scars. Yesss! pic.twitter.com/3qZ5Ol7ML6    
    
    
    @talkthomas there was blood this time. I fell within a minute of getting on it this morning! Up the road and BOOM    
    
    
    @talkthomas but Tom! The rest of the day my progress and confidence was exponential! Apparently it looks like I'm experienced :-0    
    
    
    @talkthomas I'm pretty determined. When I'm determined, nothing gets in my way : )    
    
    
    @samgrinsell ah yeah, brakes are pretty important ahaha. I'm talking about the motorbike here though : )    
    
    
    @talkthomas I will be careful. I have no intention of riding like a dick. Though my legs are a bit black and blue atm, I value my bones.    
    
    
    @talkthomas Yeah exactly, drivers have no idea about what is involved in riding. So much info to constantly process :-0 I'll be safe    
    
    
    @samgrinsell and blood! Battle wounds, these are.    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata @Luminersss actually today that's true. I'm sweaty and covered in bike grease. I also have wet hair that stinks like helmets    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata @Luminersss NOT THOSE KINDS OF HELMETS ugh fffffs    
    
    
    When it rains it pours. Got so many freelance gigs rolling in that I've got to schedule time to eat! Good times : )    
    
    
        
    
    
    So I ran over my motorbike instructor today    
    
    
    @odd_enough not quite. 50 points is a proper rundown. Mine was just over the toes ahaha oops. I reckon 30.    
    
    
    @ronviers that's nice! It's a 600cc..    
    
    
    @MarkBugby I just want to get the license : ) then I can think about getting a bike at a later date    
    
    
    @ronviers they sure do! But the tests have to be done on a 600    
    
    
    @ronviers Honda Hornet. Makes a good sound, it does.    
    
    
    @ronviers I like dirt bikes but the saddles tend to be a bit high for me. Perhaps I can get one with some foam shaved off the seat to lower    
    
    
    NACHO, NACHO MAAAN    
    
    
    Wow, so many coding jobs coming through every day. WELL, at least I'm clearer than ever that I don't want to go back to back end    
    
    
    It's good to be clear on your goals, and the direction you want to be headed : )    
    
    
    @rycz hey, thanks for adding me to your list! Have a great day : )    
    
    
    @jessejayjones lovely to meet you. Thank you for your kind words : )    
    
    
    Woken up by a tiny fly crawling into my left nostril. WHAT A MORNING <3    
    
    
    Drawing far too many women recently, and not enough creatures / mechs    
    
    
    @MIKA_GMR Oh, I thought I did? The answer is YES, OF COURSE! Which one would you like to model? I'm already excited about seeing the result!    
    
    
    @odd_enough ahaha yeah, I thought I'd use the 'favourite' function finally    
    
    
    Look who's standing triumphantly next to an excellently parked Honda Hornet after the Module 1 motorbike test! pic.twitter.com/XNUT5zCem8    
    
    
    I'm so happy I can't sleep    
    
    
    @DanielDimmick your spelling makes no sense    
    
    
    Writing contracts is so not my favourite    
    
    
    @Luminersss ah yay! Go you!    
    
    
    I want to be a jingle singer for a living    
    
    
    Hoo boy, INFOGRAPHICS    
    
    
    That is what I'm designing today. What are YOU designing?    
    
    
    Hoo boy, onto a logo design now    
    
    
    I had a floppy broccoli for dinner    
    
    
    Wow those two words are just made for each other

Floppy

Broccoli    
    
    
    Floppy broccoli and logo design. This is my evening.    
    
    
    @MarkBugby it was floppy before I overcooked it, I'll have you know    
    
    
    So the car's back at the garage for the 1,985,974th time    
    
    
    Oh god. Trending topics are always so cringe-worthy.    
    
    
    Dusting off the DSLR skills from my Photography days for this new contract yaaay    
    
    
    @MarkBugby just got it back, new window reg and door handles. Cosmetic stuff really : )    
    
    
    Had a pair of jeans since I was 16, a few days on the motorbike and the crotch is ripped to shreds!    
    
    
    The urge to draw is overwhelming. Might give into this desire before cracking on with contracts tonight.. STAY TUNED    
    
    
    Just got back from a car show and it was pretty awesome, you guys. It's nice to be in a venue full of people that share a passion    
    
    
    You might say, that I was 'fuelling a passion'

..ahaha.

HAHAHA

HAHAHAHAHA FOLLOW ME ON TWITTER    
    
    
    I want an ice cream and a cry    
    
    
    Back in Reading now after a fabulous few days of weddings and family time : )    
    
    
    Oh boy. A day of accounts! ...oh boy    
    
    
    My epilator is broken. I SHALL BE HAIRY FOR ANOTHER WEEK, but I found this hilarious review when buying a new one http://amzn.to/16JnwY4     
    
    
    On the lookout for a good illustration agency..    
    
    
    Great to go to a Digital Arts exhibition last night at my old uni and connect with some familiar faces    
    
    
    The quality of C4D work is so good! Gets better every year.    
    
    
    Inspired by a conversation I just had. I love inspiration. pic.twitter.com/cpUqwknvmj    
    
    
    @kennybadex oh, you're familiar with C4D too?    
    
    
    @kennybadex ah totally agree. Not a fan of Maya but that's because I've found C4D to be so easy to use..    
    
    
    LinkedIn emails are so close to being marked as spam. The unsubscribe thing is not working, neither are the email settings. HELP D-:    
    
    
    This happened after looking at some uhhh, inspiration. Which one would you like to see painted? pic.twitter.com/xpnqWLOhEB    
    
    
    THERE'S A NEW MAC PRO?    
    
    
    OH BOY. SPREADSHEETS. *wilts*    
    
    
    @ToadsCaravan hello. You sound interesting. Hope you're having a smashing day so far.    
    
    
    iOS 7 looks kind of hot hmm    
    
    
    I want to paint like Dmitriy Samohin because omg wow    
    
    
    Something smells like burning angels    
    
    
    OMG THE SMOKE ALARM RUN    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan Check this guy's artwork out https://www.facebook.com/DmitriySamohin  amazing, right? He's a tattoo artist    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan Yeah, he's got the skintone and the lighting so right ahhh I love it!    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata hi : )    
    
    
    @GraphicBurger is your site down? That branding mock-up looks great BUT I CAN'T HAVE IT aaa    
    
    
    @GraphicBurger ohhh. I'm in Reading.. I noticed a few other people on your fb page with a similar problem    
    
    
    @GraphicBurger yay! I hope you guys get it up and running soon : ) thanks!    
    
    
    If only I could shed skin like a reptile OH THE FUN I WOULD HAVE    
    
    
    That thought was brought to you by a floating aphid skin, landing on my keyboard. Gross.    
    
    
    YAY I have a tricycle license!    
    
    
    @markscottwood Free CV Writer can help. Free CV Writer, the free CV Writing service that's free. Sign up with Free CV Writer today. Free.    
    
    
    No floating dead aphid skins today    
    
    
    @markscottwood I'm not really a spambot, honest. I'm just lonely.    
    
    
    @GraphicBurger YEAH! It's working today. Thanks guys! You're awesome.    
    
    
    @GraphicBurger As in, a hack?    
    
    
    @canvasmag hey, how've you been? You look busy! That's good..    
    
    
    @momarkmagic those look great!    
    
    
    Who knows of someplace I can get giant posters of bugs? I mean HUGE. Maybe a huge poster with lots of thumbnails hmm. HELP. Thanks <3    
    
    
        
    
    
    10 benefits of good Design http://www.orphicpixel.com/10-benefits-of-good-graphic-design/ …    
    
    
    @JelisaUK hey Jelisa! How are you? Yeah for sure, I want to go to a museum or zoo soon so will have a look see. Thanks!    
    
    
    @MoonApe hey Alex. I just wanted to tell you that your stuff is really motivating. It's inspiring the way you share your experience.    
    
    
    @zombryn hello! Are you going to Animgather?    
    
    
    @zombryn ohh this is what I've been looking for! Yes, I'll be there : )    
    
    
    @zombryn who else from twitterland is going?    
    
    
    @twisted_k hey, there's a big animation meet-up in London on the 20th July, will you be going?    
    
    
    Who's going to Animgather 2013?    
    
    
    @zombryn yeah, you liked my post and that's how I found you on here. I'll check it out! Thanks Bryn    
    
    
    So many recruiters phoning me today. What's going on?!    
    
    
    Photo: The first in a series of teeth and gums studies. Got gum disease? I want to see! http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwnovXTe     
    
    
    Photo: I’ll probably paint this guy with a gums and teeth based colour palette for training http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwnp4vKa     
    
    
    @BambiSlammer Mark did you change your twitter handle? How are you doing these days? How's the car?    
    
    
    @twisted_k yeah! Check it out here https://www.facebook.com/events/514534241934722/ … Things are good thanks, I've decided to follow my passion : ) where've you been?    
    
    
    @arteechoke oooh I love that chain and the simplicity and the mmm    
    
    
    @FreakyZoid ahaha stupid Microsoft    
    
    
    @AndyAkers21 @irondavy great read : ) if it looks right, it is right. I've had this debate with devs that insist on making things "correct"    
    
    
    Bleached my hair yesterday. In the process I also managed to bleach 2 tshirts, 2 towels, a pair of trousers and a pillow.    
    
    
    Got the Sesame Street theme tune in my head AND NOW SO HAVE YOU AHAHA    
    
    
    Realised that I have over 900 connections on LinkedIn, all professionals in the concept art, film and games industry as well as illustration    
    
    
    Today I'm focusing on a concept that will enable me to practice painting teeth and gum style textures mmm moist    
    
    
    omg recruitment people I am NOT INTERESTED in your amazing UI opportunities leave me be ffs    
    
    
    I drew an inside-out dude. Painting him now. Dunno what to do for arms hmm pic.twitter.com/OjCLg31jkt    
    
    
    Photo: Meet Mr Gummy. Working on getting that subsurface scattering look that gums have, like on the ribs... http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwnwpl8t     
    
    
    @glitchritual Hey Ty. You have skulls, don't you? Where do you get them?    
    
    
    Rather enjoying drawing meat creatures with foetus eyes pic.twitter.com/4D5FrNqiP5    
    
    
    @glitchritual @lessashamed ah cool. Then you boil them, right? Hmm I might go and ask some local butchers see if they have some sheep heads    
    
    
    @glitchritual oh god that sounds SO DELICIOUS. Do you then eat the face meat? I don't want to look at the brain ewww EWWW    
    
    
    @lessashamed @glitchritual every kind of head definitely sounds fun. But maaan where am I going to get a pot big enough to boil them hmm    
    
    
    @matthewfaulder have you done one of those before? I'm super curious..    
    
    
    Really into drawing well-built men recently hmm. This defo needs painting : ) http://instagram.com/p/a67DOQHIwP/     
    
    
    @Dralex789 oooh reminds me of Limbo    
    
    
    @yollia hello! I procrastibaked yesterday! WE MUST BE TWINS    
    
    
    @Dann_Sw woooooah thank you so much omg I'm overwhelmed omg so kind woah    
    
    
    @Dann_Sw Your work is pretty sweet, Danny :-0 loving the weapons especially and the DETAIL I'm just blown away wow    
    
    
    This pic.twitter.com/aiVvOKb0R2    
    
    
    @Rowan_the_boat it's cool, right? Face tentacles    
    
    
    Don't you just want to lick this guy? pic.twitter.com/tvf1As6gX9    
    
    
    Have a thing for drawing well built man monsters recently oooh yum pic.twitter.com/xBYAHEzjrR    
    
    
    @odd_enough I like this    
    
    
    4am bedtime how did this happen    
    
    
    Can't wait to finish my man monster when I wake up yay    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt hey Ben, do you use Etsy? How come you chose BigCartel for your prints?    
    
    
    Tempted by a job offer aaagh    
    
    
    You guys, what is this new trend of bots favouriting tweets? It's sucking the life out of the room, maaan    
    
    
    @FreakyZoid oh DUDE I meant to ask you, are you coming to this? https://www.facebook.com/events/514534241934722/?fref=ts … be cool to see you    
    
    
    @Luminersss your art is getting better and better, yo    
    
    
    @odd_enough are you a bot?    
    
    
    Oesophagus    
    
    
    I stepped on glass earlier, now it's really hurty : ( somebody make me a sympathy art please kthanks    
    
    
    Nothing can stop me from sending my art to cool magazines in the hope of getting featured. NOT EVEN THIS BLEEDING FOOT.    
    
    
    I hope the bleeding foot is still there when I wake up. I also hope it stops being bleedy.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo: Skin, gums and teeth are rather improving even if I do say so myself : ) http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwoTtWBQ     
    
    
    Yay games recruitment people are connecting with me on LinkedIn. It's all going to plan : )    
    
    
    Really keen to discover concept artists whether it's creatures, vehicles or weapons.. If you know a wicked artist, link me!    
    
    
    @ronviers He's one of my favourite artists. He has an attitude and a philosophy that a lot of artists could learn from.    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Thanks, Tom! *fist in the air followed by celebratory jiggle* ..How are you doing?    
    
    
    @ronviers Yeah man, totally awesome. I've been following his tutorials for years now. It's incredible of him to do such valuable videos.    
    
    
    @ronviers I especially like his videos about what it takes to be serious about your passion. The investment of time, work, practice ..self.    
    
    
    @ronviers For sure. I like what you say about bringing someone's idea to life. Even when they may not always know what they want.    
    
    
    @_1000portraits cool, what a wicked idea! What is your aim from this 1,000 portrait project?    
    
    
    @jmgallo @wwwbigbaldhead omg I love this :-0 has inspired me to do another bw piece wow    
    
    
        
    
    
    I finished Foetusface. Hmm need to work on that stretchy translucent wet skin look. pic.twitter.com/Tn084NrPrc    
    
    
    Added more stuff to my Creature Ref album on fb if you want to see https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10152961187045007.1073741826.535695006&type=1&l=14e8158a7a …    
    
    
    @ronviers well if ever you'd like me to help out, I'm here for you : )    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad omg I'd love to see that! I'm good thanks, busy : ) YES we must make that more public and get more peoples down. You coming?    
    
    
    @_1000portraits An exhibition sounds wicked! You've a great attitude; it's really positive and that's infectious. Keep going : )    
    
    
    @WeeMadAggie ahaha thanks, Kristen!    
    
    
    Oh boy I just love @Spotify's branding. It's the little touches such as the "Fictitious" section on their app updates    
    
    
    I shall name him Trapezius Clawface pic.twitter.com/Cr0rfIZu27    
    
    
    Photo: This is Trapezius Clawface http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwoklZit     
    
    
    Whoa I'm connected to Masa Narita, the Lead Modeller for Iron Man 3! Connect with me here http://lnkd.in/egNM4X  #in    
    
    
    Trapezius Clawface is complete. Onto the next! I have a feeling it's going to be female :-0 pic.twitter.com/hJQGAs1Jes    
    
    
    Photo: Peek-a-boo. Need to perfect that crinkled skin look mmm love it. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwonH1mx     
    
    
    Because YES parasites. Very early WIP pic.twitter.com/oM3NfBACp1    
    
    
    @ped_o thank you : ) it was super quick so I'm pleased with how it came out    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt Ben. BEN! I set up BigCartel so that we can be twins. Also, are you on a paid subscription with them? I just got the free one    
    
    
    The shop is set up now, so you can get prints! Ooo to decide what to put up first..    
    
    
    I'd like some peacocks    
    
    
    Whoa. ALBINO peacocks. They are so beautiful I want to cry    
    
    
    @MarkBugby They are just so breathtakingly pretty.    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Yes MAKE time and come down! I'm more into bikes than F1 but I just love speed. I'd rather be doing it than watching it though    
    
    
    Experienced sexism to a hilarious new level yesterday. Being into technology and cars, I got used to it but that doesn't make it ok    
    
    
    It doesn't help that a lot of female drivers, generally speaking, do suck at driving. Come on girls, FIX UP. You're letting the side down.    
    
    
    Also, that many females don't take an interest in the mechanics of the vehicles they're pushing. Therefore know very little.    
    
    
    This means that a lot of garages find it easy to rip off female drivers. It's up to YOU to learn about your car so you can diagnose stuff.    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad omg the new one? M3s are beautiful cars    
    
    
    Anyway, it's how you deal with it. Sexism is rife and even more so when interacting with male-dominated industries. Bring it on!    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Whoa, nice! That car is so gorgeous I'd love to take one for a spin. Have you sat in it?    
    
    
    @MarkBugby Oooh lovely! Looks good in the sun, hey? My next car will be a Mercedes    
    
    
    @scribblepuff I agree. What I'm saying is that a lot of females do not make the effort to learn, and that doesn't help the situation    
    
    
    @scribblepuff Makes sense. I see what you're saying. From my perspective as a female petrol head, I guess it does get to me at times    
    
    
    @scribblepuff My motorbike instructor was having none of it when we went to look at bikes. One of the sales guys was being SO sexist!    
    
    
    A lot of people are endorsing me for skills on LinkedIn. Awesome! But I'm going to reach my skill limit uh oh. Also, how is this happening?    
    
    
    Good to see that a bunch of you guys are coming along to Animgather 2013 https://www.facebook.com/events/514534241934722/ … Be sure to spread the word    
    
    
    The Pixar Theory: Do all of the Pixar movies exist within the same universe?http://jonnegroni.com/2013/07/11/the-pixar-theory/ … thanks @JonNegroni    
    
    
    Just read the brief for an illo for a magazine and HOOO BOY I am bursting with concepts and giddy and mmm    
    
    
    If you know of any magazines looking for illos, hit me up! Specifically mags specialising in film and games    
    
    
    @jonnysun I love you    
    
    
    @glitchritual my sketches are on my tumblr. I'm going to focus it on completed pieces from now though, keep the rest behind the scenes    
    
    
    @glitchritual I'd love to paint one of your pieces :-0    
    
    
    @n8Bliss what is all this about Pacific Rim I hear? How are you N8?    
    
    
    omgomgOMG SOMEBODY WANTS ME TO DESIGN THEIR CHARACTER CONEPTS OMG    
    
    
    Also working on lots of additional illo gigs I am so happy right now    
    
    
    *strolls off into the sunset, holding hands with her Wacom*    
    
    
    Watching animated videos all day and getting paid for it. Put your mind to it, and dreams can come true.    
    
    
    Progress shot of parasite boy. Compound eyes aplenty. pic.twitter.com/CfrrooEwF2    
    
    
    Huge animation gathering happening at Hyde Park tomorrow! Come along and bring your picnics #Animgather    
    
    
        
    
    
    #Animgather TODAY at Hyde Park! Animators and artists gather to feast upon each other's knowledge and picnics. See you there.    
    
    
    We are at #Animgather 2013    
    
    
    @sketchseven hey Chris, when did we lose each other on Twitter! It was awesome to meet you in real life :-0    
    
    
    @Indi_pops hey! Thank you for arranging such a wonderful day. I look forward to the next #Animgather : )    
    
    
    @maxwelloginni @CaptainChants yeeeah! Do we have a group photo?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants @maxwelloginni here is a pic of my chickens that almost count as doves pic.twitter.com/IrZzLuiRSe    
    
    
        
    
    
    Being back home in London is great but, I really miss my Wacom, you guys.    
    
    
    Particularly since I've got an illo to be working on :-0    
    
    
    Pen and paper it is, storyboarding for an animation project in between small feasts. It's good to be home : )    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad it was pretty awesome I must say. It's a shame we didn't see your face but we will make plenty more opportunities!    
    
    
    Tattoo design is under way! Using this gig to work on my presentation of ideas for concept artwork going forward    
    
    
    Woke up next to a giant grasshopper. AT LEAST I WASN'T ALONE <3    
    
    
    Illustration for @NewEmpress magazine is almost done! Can't wait to see it printed so that millions can enjoy : )    
    
    
    Here's a sneaky peek at my illustration for @NewEmpress magazine. Coming out at the end of the month :-0 pic.twitter.com/dztvejXNJK    
    
    
    Hoo boy. A morning of calls with some exciting people for some exciting projects coming up : )    
    
    
    Really enjoying life. Now that my passion and my career has merged into one, beautiful beast.    
    
    
    @NewEmpress hey thanks for the RT : )    
    
    
    "Improve your broadband performance, don't use your Internet" - silly Virgin Media    
    
    
    @virginmedia I know, right! Crickey indeed. Our Internet has been slowed down because of high usage during peak times. We work from home :-0    
    
    
    @virginmedia wireless, we've had problems from day 1 with it. Help!    
    
    
    @virginmedia thanks! Will give it a go and pass it into my tech-savvy housemate. Hope we get back online soon..    
    
    
    AAAGH SPASMING EYELID    
    
    
    Totally love meeting clients that you just click with. This is how magic happens.    
    
    
    Oh, HTML. My old friend.    
    
    
    Beautiful. Think they're nickel coated or something that I'm allergic to. So long as I don't lick them I'll be ok. pic.twitter.com/uYYJSOPOeQ    
    
    
    @MarkBugby yup I got gloves. Staying callous-free. I upped the weight today. Feeling it now : )    
    
    
    @MarkBugby sure. I get used to them so easy though, needing to up the load every 2 weeks.. I'll be doing deadlifts soon :-0    
    
    
    Check it out, you guys. I've rediscovered C4D and omg how it's come along since R11.5 :-0 https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10153119755265007&set=a.10151374700785007.809507.535695006&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    @odd_enough I'm eating meatballs right now    
    
    
    Flickery GI aaargh D-: gonna work on some email templates to ease these animation woes    
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson @MIKA_GMR thank you! rendering 100F now to see what this does...    
    
    
    No more flickery GI! https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10153127999095007&set=a.10151374700785007.809507.535695006&type=1&theater … rendered with Sky Sampler in the end    
    
    
    @ronviers this is for a client. I like 3D : ) it's awesome that I'm getting to do more of it at the moment.    
    
    
    Big thanks for all the endorsements in Creative Direction, you guys : ) http://uk.linkedin.com/in/eggabo/  connect with me here if you like    
    
    
    @ronviers thank you so much, Ron. That's really kind of you.    
    
    
    Yay passed my motorbike test! : ) pic.twitter.com/Xgo6i4hl7l    
    
    
    @RubberPenguin wooo thanks Dan! : )    
    
    
    @jetwashpilot I am official now. Category A business : )    
    
    
    WASP    
    
    
    Just got to show my parents my Motorbike certificate in the flesh. They were so proud :' )    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ArtsyPabster Yaaay! Are you excited?    
    
    
    Just noticed that the signature on my paintings is different every time http://eggabo.tumblr.com/  WHO AM I?    
    
    
    @Inkybat omg what a beautiful picture <3    
    
    
    WHERE IS MY DRIVING LICENSE? Come on @DSAgovuk I want to see the neeew motorbike icon with no restriction code *wooo*    
    
    
    My new driving licence! IT IS HERE! I am officially a Motorcyclist. My photo looks a bit like a bearded inmate hmm    
    
    
    Putting AE back in the dock feels like putting on a fresh pair of socks that are still warm from the iron    
    
    
    I don't iron my socks    
    
    
    @sketchseven You want to see my crinkly sock collection?    
    
    
    @sketchseven I just don't know anymore    
    
    
    @Liz_DSA @DSAgovuk @DVLAgovuk hello Liz! Thanks for your reply. My licence came y/day YAY! I just want to wave it around and show everybody    
    
    
    @CaptainChants WHAT? No more bleach?    
    
    
    @CaptainChants where are the pics dude? I'm going to bleach my ends till they go CRISPY like fried chicken    
    
    
    @CaptainChants I saw a 12 year old with my hairstyle yesterday. The bleached front bit on the same side and everything. I puked/cried inside    
    
    
    @CaptainChants ARE WE MUTTONS NOW? It's way past my bedtime.    
    
    
    @Liz_DSA hey Liz check this out! : ) pic.twitter.com/LehXA14Tld    
    
    
    @CaptainChants lulz was that Picar?    
    
    
    Rendering with depth of field wooo lookin' FUZZY : )    
    
    
    Animation's looking pretty sweet and YAY I've found a Sound Engineer that is weaving musical magic as we speak!    
    
    
    Also, making logos omg so exciting    
    
    
    WHAT AN EVENTFUL WEEK. Just seeing opportunities everywhere this is just amazing    
    
    
    Client is happy = I am happy yaaay    
    
    
    OMG CELEBRATIONS STOPPED DOING GALAXY TRUFFLES WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN AND FOR WHAT REASON NOOO    
    
    
    @Liz_DSA Liz are you getting MARRIED?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sketchseven that's what I'm used to. Hence the extra accentuated weakness tasteness. I'm happy and busy and omg so many projects.    
    
    
    @sketchseven THERE WAS CRISPY LIMESCALE AT THE BOTTOM OF THE MUG, CHRIS    
    
    
    Wooo! Animation is complete! Check out "Box" on Vimeo http://vimeo.com/74043865     
    
    
    Car hair everywhere. AND IT'S NOT EVEN MY CAT. Aww look how cuuute he/she is pic.twitter.com/4Rqt6vwS8P    
    
    
    @sketchseven CAN WE KEEP HIM/HER CAN WE CAN WE?    
    
    
    omg you can sculpt in C4D now? OOOH    
    
    
    Already missing being on a motorbike D-:    
    
    
    Designing tattoos today. Sweet : )    
    
    
    Just designed a motorbike-based piece. Now onto some more logo concepts hoo boy busy busy    
    
    
    Feng Zhu is such great ear candy while on the Wacom    
    
    
    @Liz_DSA oooh congratulations!!! Awww <3    
    
    
    @Liz_DSA when's the big day? Do you have your dress?    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza hello!    
    
    
    Onto the next piece of motion graphics for this client! Think I'll stick to AE given the tiny timescale on this one :-0    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza Smashing, thank you : ) Would be good to meet the man behind the legend. Do you visit Lumina these days?    
    
    
    Logo designing and cooking slow cooker yums on the menu today wooo    
    
    
    By the way I HAVE A SLOW COOKER NOW, guys. I'm going to slow cook all the things.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson Whoa. I've not been out on the pedals in months! Have fun Dave; work those quads and glutes. Enjoy it!    
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson About to go and get ingredients now I CAN'T WAIT. Going to make a lamb thing with veg, using this *handy recipe booklet*    
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson I'm hitting the weights today. YAY FOR GROWTH. Have a great day : )    
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson That's the plan! Oh yeah I forgot about butchers hmm I live in an area saturated with them..    
    
    
    @dave_A_davidson Ooh! Doing HIIT and resistance. Got my housemate's dumbbells and squat them. Tried to do a pull-up yesterday. Tried.    
    
    
    @Paul_V3Design definitely pedals before but now I've discovered the motorbike omg.. They are 2 very different experiences    
    
    
    @jordanaltria You what?    
    
    
    @Paul_V3Design I just love the thrill    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza I may be in the West End on Sunday actually.. Kingston area.    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza oh, definitely legend! Those guys sing your praises : )    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza oooh that's exciting! Enjoy it    
    
    
    @CaptainChants dude I'm totally loving my slow cooker *grinnns* BRING ON WINTER    
    
    
    @CaptainChants yeah. Made a lamb thing that was ok - bit overcooked. Today I made a chicken thing with veg and MMM! Felt like eating hugs    
    
    
    @CaptainChants oh nooo it washed out? Was it not permanent? I'm in need of a trim and a re-bleach. Yo you coming out tomorrow in KTown?    
    
    
    @zombryn @CaptainChants OOOH we can all share recipes and hugs    
    
    
    @CaptainChants oh bruv lame. Feel better soon <3 preferably by tomorrow evening : ) we're going for food probabobs. That washed out quick    
    
    
    @CaptainChants @zombryn HAHAHA starting a slow cooker movement. @dave_A_davidson has one too    
    
    
    I'm preparing for an animation all-nighter. ARE YOU?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Hooo weee! I want screenshots and a full review of your experience plzkthanks    
    
    
    I want to be on the front cover of a magazine. A cool magazine.    
    
    
    Wait not me as in my face. Me as in my artwork which, is me I guess.    
    
    
    I also want to go and frolic in the rain, naked. But I got a logo to finalise. Clients first, frolicking later. I guess.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad Cool! I ended up talking logos with a client until the early hours. A revised version is now sent. Onto the animation now..    
    
    
    @nottheothermark @JuttaWiemann WHAT'S GOING ON HERE THEN?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Want to continue animating all night but I'm so sleepy and got a NEW MATTRESS! It feels like a thousand back massages.    
    
    
    Wooo my artwork is in THIS magazine : ) http://newempressmagazine.com/2013/09/our-issue-11-cover-unveiled/ …    
    
    
    @BrandInfluenza Hello! How was your trip? What were you doing in NY? Yes, it would be good to chat this week : )    
    
    
    Spending my Friday night in with the Mac, moving keyframes. This is indeed the life.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad how is it going over there?    
    
    
    @WhyAlwaysMad That sounds like a conversation 'to be continued dot dot dot'    
    
    
    Concept arting today! Creature designs all over my screens right now. So awesome.    
    
    
    One more tattoo design.. Then I'll be FREE this weekend! ..to work on my portfolio    
    
    
    Logo sent! Character design feedback received. Now onto a brochure design.    
    
    
    Bought more bleach for my ombre hair. THE URGE TO GO BLONDE AGAIN. IT IS OVERWHELMING.    
    
    
    @glitchritual haha DANG IT YOU NOTICE EVERYTHING    
    
    
    Mum calls, "what are you up to?"
Me, "drawing a naked woman."
Mum, "oh ok. Have you had dinner?"

I have the coolest family    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photo: Been doing a lot of animations and design work recently. You know what that means; sooner or later, a... http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwxaJ5mo     
    
    
    Photo: Quick colour and highlight pass http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwxaSD8O     
    
    
    @odd_enough Hello Jordan Cain. I am happy that you are happy.    
    
    
    @a_rehmankhan HIGH FIVE    
    
    
    @sketchseven thanks, dude : )    
    
    
    @odd_enough @mystichobodev what just happened? You guys, I'm animating again today. My eyes are TURNING INTO RECTANGLES AND KEYFRAMES    
    
    
    Falling asleep to the sound of rendering <3    
    
    
    @alex_picar hello Picar! I was thinking of you today. How are you?    
    
    
    @alex_picar I am also fine. Why are you not drawing anymore? Has something happened to your drawing hand?    
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt Hello Ben Newman. Are you familliar with Glenn Arthur's artwork? https://www.facebook.com/glennarthurart     
    
    
    @BenNewmanArt hello Ben Newman, where do you get your certificates of authenticity printed? Would you recommend doing them with prints?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Photoset: Yay I’m in New Empress Magazine! Had fun doing this Hitchcock-themed sketch http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwyQT8y6     
    
    
    This will be on his skin FOR THE REST OF HIS LIFE. I'm so honoured I think I might cry :' ) pic.twitter.com/0tupjoneQV    
    
    
    @sketchseven I actually sobbed with joy twice    
    
    
    @sketchseven DON'T MAKE ME CRY AGAIN    
    
    
    As much as I want to focus on things other than coding, floating misaligned menus force me to go into the back end. Oh well LET'S DO THIS.    
    
    
    Recently my site was hacked by some viagra salesmen. Thus new website soon : )    
    
    
    Evil viagra salesmen hackers = 0, eggabo = 1    
    
    
    Website is taking shape :-0 NO TIME FOR SLEEP http://bit.ly/HsC4QF     
    
    
    Wordpress is great UNTIL IT MAKES YOU TEAR YOUR HAIR OUT, SCREAM AND SOB while drinking a nice cold glass of cloudy apple juice oooh yum    
    
    
    @TheDotFoundry Hello, guys is your website working? I keep getting the Forbidden screen : (    
    
    
    @TheDotFoundry thanks for your reply. I just wanted to look over your price list again but it can wait. Loving the print samples!    
    
    
    Going to put naked ladies on my business cards. Because that's how we do.    
    
    
    @tonyjohnson me too WE MUST BE TWINS    
    
    
    Opening support tickets all over the internet. FEELS GOOD. Have that, 'incorrect MX records'.    
    
    
    Wow Google's customer service is really spot on. No wonder they are where they are.    
    
    
    Inspiring philosophies & big ideas from people that are passionate & focused http://www.focusforwardfilms.com/  well shot videos, too    
    
    
    Upgraded to Mavericks and OH NO lost loads of work due to incompatible software AAAH oh well here we go again, Adobe..    
    
    
    Oooh. Multiple display optimisation FINALLY.    
    
    
    This new animation's lookin' pretty slick EVEN IF I DID HAVE TO EDIT IT FROM SCRATCH my eyes they are so sleepy g'night you guys    
    
    
    Going to be in New Empress Magazine again yaaay : )    
    
    
    Nsync is the perfect boy band for website designing DIRTY POP POP P-P-P-POP    
    
    
    Doing a portrait of my favourite vampire crush from the 90's can you guess who?    
    
    
    This is for a magazine. The deadline is tomorrow. I only started today hooo weee.    
    
    
    @odd_enough guess again. YOU HAVE 2 MORE GUESSES    
    
    
    @odd_enough HINT: he's not from a movie    
    
    
    @ronviers @odd_enough David Bowie was a vampire?    
    
    
    @mayaemilie YOU WIN ONE HUG! Yeah I was torn between Spike and Dru. Went for Spike in the end.    
    
    
    @alex_picar hello Picar    
    
    
        
    
    
    @alex_picar oh. I've been away from twitter for a while.. Hey Picar I'm drawing Spike! What are you drawing?    
    
    
    Limited edition prints coming soon pic.twitter.com/gbm9kjM3tI    
    
    
    Deadline in a few hours aaah pic.twitter.com/5cbiyGOV07    
    
    
    @mayaemilie Are we the same person?    
    
    
    Photo: This is a quick portrait of my favourite vampire crush from the 90’s. I totally had the hots for... http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYw10BxnrK     
    
    
    @alex_picar weather is good, bit cold. Chickens are good. No chickens eaten. No motorbike yet. Not part of a MC yet.    
    
    
    @alex_picar Make me a sandwich, Picar.    
    
    
    @mayaemilie I was a regular. Fancied Angel too. Remember when he got his own show? I was not a fan of that at all.    
    
    
    @mayaemilie wooo! Thanks dude : )    
    
    
    In case you missed it yesterday. I drew Spike from Buffy! To appear in @NewEmpress mmm pic.twitter.com/A9onX4kr8p    
    
    
    @mayaemilie LOOK AT US, going around, fancying all the vampires    
    
    
    @alex_picar mmm cheesy    
    
    
    @alex_picar NO. But I will google this main dude right now.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @alex_picar maaan. That main dude is not hot. You lied to me on Christmas month, Picar.    
    
    
    Cleaned out my MacPro for the week. Who wants a dustball fight? pic.twitter.com/EuMWM4QD8x    
    
    
    @alex_picar at least he's on a motorcycle    
    
    
    @alex_picar IF ONLY. Haha riding motorcycle jokes uh oh    
    
    
        
    
    
    Someone just told me I look under 18. I don't even know, you guys.    
    
    
    Hard drive officially dead. WESTERN DIGITAL HOW COULD YOU    
    
    
        
    
    
    Audi Sport Quattro concept artwork mmm http://www.netcarshow.com/audi/2013-sport_quattro_concept/1600x1200/wallpaper_2d.htm …    
    
    
    @Illustruction oooh like the driving game where you make up words for the last three letters of the license plate of the car in front?    
    
    
    @Illustruction oh maaan : ( that just made all my insides feel heavy    
    
    
    INSTAGRAM, WHY YOU DO THIS?    
    
    
    Glittery nuts! It's good to be home for Xmas : ) http://instagr.am/p/TlZ-PVHI45/     
    
    
    My last two posts do not go together AT ALL.    
    
    
    How was your Christmas?    
    
    
    @MarkBugby pretty good, thank you. Spent it with the family : ) Looking forward to my birthday on the 1st! :-0    
    
    
    @JohnCthulhu @Illustruction THIS IS A PROBLEM TO WHICH I CAN RELATE    
    
    
    @Artist_HB Ahh, thanks for listing me : )    
    
    
    So I went back to work today.. ONLY TO REALISE I STILL HAD TWO DAYS OF HOLIDAY LEFT -_-    
    
    
    Whoa    
    
    
    I am carless while my cars are in hospital. Most people would love to be able to work from home but I AM SO LONELY    
    
    
    Here is an early stage of a drawing from photo ref. Just practicing hands, necks, pose, lighting.. pic.twitter.com/kpdkthAu    
    
    
    MOODSWINGS. INDUCED BY EATING ENTIRE CAN OF BAKED BEANS. Is this normal?    
    
    
    Hoo boy did those baked beans have side effects. Who's doing the February Daily Draw on Satellite Soda?    
    
    
    @kukas81 aww thanks! Happy wknd @korrax @edmundsumner @elixat @guillaumefavre @freak_3d @georgenijland @mattguetta @paguthrie @superpeo    
    
    
    On the lookout and free to take on work, you guys! So if you have a project that needs an artist, giz a shout    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/egNM4X  #in    
    
    
    @colinwren Hey Colin, are you looking to have this professionally designed? It really depends what exactly you're after, drop me a msg!    
    
    
    Scribbly bits of a warmup sketch http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpbmQ0     
    
    
    Finished portrait with no ref. In hindsight should have maybe used ref hmm. ONTO THE NEXT.. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpc6YY     
    
    
    Nude alien lady sorta, may work on this more one day. Maybe. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpcb_A     
    
    
    Progress of woman with big boots. For the purpose of anatomy, form, pose and perspective practice. http://tmblr.co/Z3QGYwdpctB7     
    
    
    @mayaemilie I like big butts, and I cannot lie    
    
    
    @mayaemilie Thanks dude! I got bored when moving to the detail phase. But I think I'd like to work on it more.    
    
    
    @_XaKu AAAGH *dies* such a nice car :-0 How was it to drive?    
    
    
    @_XaKu How come it was your car for the day? Was it a track day?    
    
    
    @_XaKu whoooa. Have you seen the Audi R8 GT Spyder? http://bit.ly/Z386dj  Oh. My. God. That gear stick with the production number :-0    
    
    
    @_XaKu I KNOW, RIGHT! Phoooar. Carbon fibre everything, oooh yes please    
    
    
    Really want to get back on a motorbike, you guys    
    
    
    @samjermy87 NO. NO SIDE CARS. WE TALKED ABOUT THIS.    
    
    
    @samjermy87 NO. NO, SAM.    
    
    
    @samjermy87 pfff well MAYBE I don't want to go to your sidecar party ANYWAY. Do you ride?    
    
    
    @samjermy87 Ah just do the CBT, I paid £49 for mine and can ride up to 125cc for 2 years. I want to go for the full licence as soon as I can    
    
    
    @CaptainChants Dude I'm thinking of taking mine down, I haven't updated it in years! With my portfolio being everywhere but on my website..    
    
    
    @CaptainChants But then I don't want to lose the domain name GAAAH    
    
    
    When I was stuck in traffic this morning, I grumbled so loudly I startled myself    
    
    
    What's all this beef over horse meat?    
    
    
    Bet no one's said that before    
    
    
    Man, that was dry. SO DRY.    
    
    
    @BelgianBoolean whatcha doooin'?    
    
    
    @ihearthorchata daaang you're EVERYWHERE    
    
    
    Want to draw, but there are so many tasty jobs to apply for :-0    
    
    
    On the lookout to hold an exhibition, you guys. Have YOU done one before?    
    
    
    @Polygoblin hey thanks for the RT, Ben    
    
    
    @kukas81 ah thanks! Hello @vmdolphin @ugyjijes @elixat @guillaumefavre @futuregeist @paguthrie @mattguetta @georgenijland @superpeo    
    
    
    