Ow RT @PaulCarsten: @SCMP_News say Wahaha chairman Zong Qinghou was injured in attack last Friday. Tendons in arm cut apparently.    
    
    
    Tendons in hand of China’s former richest man severed in attack. But he's said to be back in office today http://www.scmp.com/news/china-insider/article/1312187/chinas-former-richest-man-zong-qinghou-injured-knife-attack …    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle @digitalhen Very true. The air is better here! Wish I had a desk tho    
    
    
    @digitalhen Yup. It's weird.    
    
    
    Does being happy help you earn more? Yes, says economist http://gu.com/p/3tp8d/tw  Not the other way around?    
    
    
    Why Reuters Ditched Its Big Web Push. One word: money http://www.buzzfeed.com/matthewzeitlin/why-reuters-ditched-its-big-web-push …    
    
    
    Bo Xilai jail letter to family: my name will be cleared one day https://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1312577/bo-xilai-jail-letter-my-name-will-be-cleared-one-day …    
    
    
    The Hoi Tin Tong tiff: How much turtle goes in turtle jelly? https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1312232/power-turtle-jelly-lies-its-recipe-hoi-tin-tong-founder …    
    
    
    +1 Good resource RT @raykwong: Neato. Interactive guide to China's maritime disputes. http://on.cfr.org/18buEJm  HT @CFR_Comm    
    
    
    @hofrench @raykwong delete the extra l at the end of URL. That worked for me    
    
    
    @MeOldChina64 You make Hong Kong proud    
    
    
    Damn RT @yurikageyama: In case you didn't know it, we missed Cheeseburger Day yesterday Sept. 18.    
    
    
    Hong Kong couple get 3+ yrs of jail for torturing maid who was 'forced to wear diaper' http://reut.rs/187Uako  via @GraceL129    
    
    
    Under NYT Sports: Former Women’s Chess Champion, a Chinese Grandmaster, Close to Regaining Title http://nyti.ms/15E1jc7     
    
    
    Batten down the hatches RT @pstebbings: Severe Typhoon #Usagi on course to make a direct hit on #HongKong on Sunday http://bit.ly/17LbcnA     
    
    
    My heart is breaking RT @WantChinaTimes: Faye Wong divorce post used as poetic rejoinder to Bo Xilai http://bit.ly/18cTkRC     
    
    
    Hong Kong-Listed Company Wison Shares Details of China Corruption Investigation http://nyti.ms/15EDQY8     
    
    
    Hong Kong Riddled With British Spies, Reports Say (Riddled!) http://on.wsj.com/1693uXB     
    
    
    Instagram seems to think I have an iPhone 5. I don't. #ios7glitch pic.twitter.com/o2G0obk0NT    
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne I knew it. That explains everything.    
    
    
    Sammy's Kitchen legacy burns as bright as its neon cow http://bit.ly/1aN6C9O  How's the actual food @DougMeigs?    
    
    
    @DougMeigs Thanks! Have yet to walk in despite passing it many times    
    
    
    In Khartoum, worry that collapse of book culture is a direct mirror of country’s decline http://nyti.ms/15BaF8p     
    
    
    Bizarre threesome. Donald Tsang wanted to meet pope but was asked to help Berlusconi on fraud case, says ex-senator http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1313365/donald-tsang-pope-and-berlusconi-aide …    
    
    
    @ongreno Unagi! http://bit.ly/2B4LJN     
    
    
    How much it costs to make a hoodie: $31.40 in Asia versus $38.10 in the US http://nyti.ms/1duLF4k     
    
    
    @ongreno @bencsin It's all about Ranch 99    
    
    
    Brad Pitt, Angelina Jolie and 'super typhoon' Usagi are all set to converge on Hong Kong at once http://ti.me/1eu8IiO     
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Brad Pitt must be so jealous    
    
    
    Yao Ming - the face of FT Magazine's China edition http://on.ft.com/hPWiSS     
    
    
    Hacking U.S. Secrets, China Pushes for Drones http://nyti.ms/15JiOYt     
    
    
    Hundreds stranded at Hong Kong airport by Typhoon #Usagi http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1315258/hundreds-stranded-hong-kong-international-airport-typhoon-usagi …    
    
    
    #Usagi RT @ObservatoryHK: Signal No. 8 is expected to be issued at or before 7:00 p.m. today (22 Sep 2013).
http://bit.ly/1f6lPbc     
    
    
    Unbelievable MT @typhoonfury: These domestic helpers said not allowed home until 9pm, 2hrs after T8 issued #Usagi pic.twitter.com/6SU4Hw2A6w    
    
    
    @henrykhh Where is this photo?    
    
    
    @henrykhh Thanks! That does look crazy @roygrubb    
    
    
    @TylerRidings @typhoonfury Or it's not as simple as that.    
    
    
    Kale - or 'curly headless cabbage' - mystifies France http://nyti.ms/18iFQ72     
    
    
    Hong Kong Airlines sorry but offers no compensation after Rene Izquierdo's rare guitar damaged http://bit.ly/18PWPeY     
    
    
    MT @Badcanto: Chinese media: #HK is going to cancel the export restriction of infant formula on Oct 1st http://bit.ly/18PXI77     
    
    
    @digitalhen @Badcanto I see another protest coming...    
    
    
    The villagers don't sound so humble RT @jonah_kessel: Humble Chinese Village Basks in Legacy of Three Kingdoms Era http://bit.ly/16TkLl0     
    
    
    Open internet in Shanghai free-trade zone includes access to Facebook, Twitter, NYT site http://www.scmp.com/news/china-insider/article/1316598/exclusive-china-lift-ban-facebook-only-within-shanghai-free-trade …    
    
    
    Robots may revolutionize China's electronics manufacturing as more youth unwilling to do manual labor http://on.wsj.com/1fdLr5Z     
    
    
    "Egypt in some ways is a more civil society than China": Peter Hessler http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/09/23/in-china-its-never-like-this-an-interview-with-peter-hessler/ …    
    
    
    Twitter posts job for head of media partnerships for Greater China MT @NiuB: Twitter sets sights on HK and Taiwan http://bit.ly/18mQcTf     
    
    
    The Most Controversial Dictionary Ever Published: Webster's Third http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/09/23/the_story_of_ain_t_david_skinner_s_book_about_america_its_language_and_the.html …    
    
    
    Satisfry. Nice. RT @GuardianUS: Burger King aims to satisfry with new low-calorie french fries http://bit.ly/14De59Q     
    
    
    US consul will continue to speak out on universal suffrage for Hong Kong http://blogs.wsj.com/chinarealtime/2013/09/24/consul-u-s-will-continue-to-speak-out-for-democracy-in-hong-kong/ …    
    
    
    Ashley Madison, the Website for Cheaters, Lands in Hong Kong http://zite.to/18n45CV  HK 'extremely popular hub'    
    
    
    This map shows where you are most likely to die from air pollution  http://www.businessinsider.com/world-map-of-air-pollution-2013-9 …    
    
    
    "If you build it, they will come" - Hollywood stars at Wanda's Qingdao film complex kickoff http://www.jingdaily.com/dalian-wanda-ceo-china-to-be-center-of-the-global-film-industry/36445/ …    
    
    
    David Webb: What Alibaba Wants From Its IPO And What It Will Likely Get  http://onforb.es/1gWB16e     
    
    
    Fonterra's plan for China-only Anmum brand moves 'full steam ahead' http://reut.rs/19CLXCh     
    
    
    @StarrWulfe oh, Hong Kong    
    
    
    Beautiful, but so much criticism of Calatrava projects http://nyti.ms/1fjPWvV     
    
    
    @Rydaine Beyond me why fake Versailles didn't succeed. Fake Hollywood will buck the trend!    
    
    
    Why We Hate Infographics (And Why You Should) http://insights.qunb.com/why-we-hate-infographics-and-why-you-should …    
    
    
    Anthony Lawrence, legendary BBC journalist, dies aged 101 in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1317747/anthony-lawrence-legendary-bbc-journalist-dies-aged-101-hong-kong …    
    
    
    40 percent of Hongkongers suffer from some degree of insomnia  http://www.timeout.com.hk/big-smog/features/61204/the-city-that-cant-sleep.html#.UkQK5cK5QJk.twitter … via @timeouthk    
    
    
    @joannachiu I bet @ErnestKao knows    
    
    
    Seymour Hersh on 'pathetic' US media. 'Get rid of 90% of editors and start promoting editors you can't control' http://gu.com/p/3j5vd/tw     
    
    
    A Cubicle to Call Home http://nyti.ms/18vrhNx  Photos: “Anywhere with air-conditioners will do" for Mr. Cheng who roams Mong Kok to pass time    
    
    
    Hong Kong sets an official poverty line today http://bit.ly/15AAd7l     
    
    
    Billshut jobs: No doubt we have all wondered what HR managers contribute to the world http://www.scmp.com/business/article/1311095/ask-yourself-morning-my-job-load-billshut … Another good one by Tom Holland    
    
    
    LOL RT @caligarn: These fucking idiots, @PhoRestaurant , are trying to trademark the word "Phở".    
    
    
    103-yr-old dines out every night, always orders fish. Spends US$100 on average (I guess I would too at 103) http://nyti.ms/1fvzNDR     
    
    
    Who Made Speed Dating? http://nyti.ms/16FDH2A  Answer: An Orthodox rabbi in Beverly Hills    
    
    
    For Chinese, Murakami is a window on the world http://ajw.asahi.com/article/behind_news/people/AJ201309290013 …    
    
    
    At the State Department, diversity can count against you. 'It's un-American' http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2013/09/24/at-the-state-department-diversity-can-count-against-you/ …    
    
    
    19.6% of Hongkongers under new poverty line  http://bit.ly/1651xsR  | That puts HK above US, Japan http://bit.ly/WzWWFS     
    
    
    Mainland Chinese woman sues Hong Kong middlemen over forged Guinea-Bissau passport http://bit.ly/16520v7     
    
    
    Lunch with the FT: Daniel Ek. Spotify founder holds meetings on High Line http://www.ft.com/cms/s/2/ca45f6b8-25bd-11e3-aee8-00144feab7de.html …    
    
    
    "Western publishers are the gatekeepers of what we read from China" - as it is for other "world literature" http://bit.ly/162Kub1     
    
    
    Run-ins with China's "feisty females" http://reut.rs/jd2Kpt     
    
    
    Reading: We Like You So Much and Want to Know You Better by Dave Eggers http://nyti.ms/1fzAtbc  via NYT Mag    
    
    
    Apple Passes Coca-Cola as Most Valuable Brand http://nyti.ms/16N0Wru     
    
    
    The Lost Slumgullions of English http://nyti.ms/15KT65O     
    
    
    Owner of Happy Printing Co in Tai Kok Tsui still prints with movable type. It's how he learned Chinese and Eng http://bit.ly/1fCDF5Z  #HK    
    
    
    How Dave Eggers gets Silicon Valley wrong http://reut.rs/19OB3KT     
    
    
    Multitasker! MTR probe over driver filmed clipping toenails on moving train http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1321208/mtr-probe-over-driver-filmed-clipping-toenails-moving-train …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Good point!    
    
    
    I.M. Pei's first project in Hong Kong faces wrecking ball http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1321585/causeway-bay-lose-urban-oasis-im-peis-sunning-plaza-faces-wrecking …    
    
    
    MT @_sofiamt: Employee at @NMAtv resigns with KAnye West interpretative dance http://bit.ly/14ZYjpM     
    
    
    Good lineup! MT @yurikageyama: Sign up for @AAJAAsia conference Oct. 18-20 in Tokyo and learn journalistic tricks 
http://bit.ly/19SlnF9     
    
    
    New tourist rules MT @stanyee Do not: "Eat a whole piece of bread in one mouthful" Do: "Use shower curtains in hotel" http://bit.ly/1eYNxFG     
    
    
    There's, like, dirt on the ground MT @MabelSieh There's Prob a Good Reason Why Bieber was Carried on the Great Wall 
http://bit.ly/17rlgDg     
    
    
    He saved the government $1 billion. And then he was furloughed. http://wapo.st/16iOzId     
    
    
    LA's Grand Central Market going upscale hipster? Hope not  http://touch.latimes.com/#section/-1/article/p2p-77629441/ … HT @kenbensinger    
    
    
    A woman?! #sexistovertones RT @noruweijin: China’s Poisoned Air Prompts Woman to Devise Green Tax http://j.mp/GA0Aiz     
    
    
    Can't decide if Ross Ulbricht, of the ‘http://Amazon.com  of drugs,’ is a super genius or not http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2013/10/ross-ulbricht-charged-with-running-silk-road.html …    
    
    
    Did Google doodle for National Day carry a hidden message? http://shanghaiist.com/2013/10/03/netizens_grasp_at_straws_with_google_national_day_tiananmen_doodle.php …    
    
    
    U.S. shutdown has already produced at least one winner: China http://nyti.ms/18Qi4Bk     
    
    
    McDonald's treated like sex offenders: Australian town protests branch cuz too close to nursery and school http://bbc.in/1fKg03u     
    
    
    @ulysseas That is probably true. So much for the "Asia pivot"    
    
    
    An addendum to HK ivory seige MT @BBCWorld: Poisoning of 80 elephants in Zimbabwe "affects whole world" http://bit.ly/16I11Ue     
    
    
    More Chow Tai Fook stores than KFCs in Hong Kong  http://on.wsj.com/16JeTh1  #interactive via @digitalhen    
    
    
    JMSC director @yingworld concerned potential HKU pick  has little knowledge of HK or China http://bit.ly/16JfBdY     
    
    
    Link to professor's views on HKU vice-chancellor pick (in Chinese) http://bit.ly/16JfQ8Q     
    
    
    I Know How You're Feeling, I Read Chekhov: Reading literary fiction improves empathy, EQ http://nyti.ms/18TqyYw     
    
    
    Downtown L.A. to hold first Sriracha festival http://www.latimes.com/food/dailydish/la-dd-first-sriracha-festival-20131002,0,6822764.story …    
    
    
    Adobe announces security breach. Hackers had access to credit card info of 2.9m customers http://nyti.ms/174IURI     
    
    
    Hongkongers can travel to 152 countries visa free, Chinese only 44 http://shanghaiist.com/2013/10/04/hong_kong_passport_allows_holders_to_travel_to_152_countries_visa_free.php … via @inbeijingse    
    
    
    North Point tour walking goes back to 1967 Hong Kong riots http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325476/north-point-tour-takes-participants-back-1967-hong-kong-riots …    
    
    
    Silk industry's demise in 1920s marked start of domestic helpers' rise in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325419/silk-industrys-demise-marked-start-domestic-helpers-rise-hong-kong …    
    
    
    Germany's Sochi Olympics uniform "a cross between a pot-bellied pig and a parrot" http://spon.de/ad2ZI     
    
    
    The humble brag & more RT @nytimes: Cultural Studies: Twitter Bios and What They Really Say http://bit.ly/1f9QoMm     
    
    
    Henry M. Paulson believes major fiscal reform imminent in China http://nyti.ms/18ZrOcw     
    
    
    HKJA condemns barring of HK reporters at APEC http://bit.ly/1bBveWN     
    
    
    Slow news day eh? MT @Badcanto: Apple Daily headline: White Woman Works as Dishwasher in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/1bBvKEl     
    
    
    New HKU head Peter Matheison has his work cut out for him http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325905/new-hku-head-ready-move-forward …    
    
    
    Now in color: Federal Reserve to Unveil a Redesigned US$100 Bill http://nyti.ms/17ayiSe     
    
    
    Great photo of Victoria Harbour race (via SCMP) pic.twitter.com/Y3YwrCUEP0    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle Yeah must've been early. There was definitely a lot less hype about the event this year    
    
    
    @JRush_Asia Asian Gandalf    
    
    
    Obama’s Absence Leaves China as Dominant Force at #APEC http://nyti.ms/17bieQ7     
    
    
    Those giant monitors are comical MT @Helene_FR: Fox News and its weird new newsroom http://bit.ly/17Q3olx     
    
    
    Why not "muffnut"? Who names these things? RT @bibekbhandari: After "cronut," now there's this thing called "duffin" http://bit.ly/GEwwSy     
    
    
    Iron Man ride in HK to be Disney's first based on Marvel since it bought the comic book company in 2009 http://nyti.ms/15SwLFs     
    
    
    “A Short History of the Highrise” Very neat project using NYT archives and photos from readers worldwide http://nyti.ms/19bbOnR     
    
    
    HK journo group protests eviction over Aquino heckling http://bit.ly/1hyKL71  http://bit.ly/1hyKMb4  Pic at consulate via @STForeignDesk    
    
    
    The existential angst of Hong Kong's 'monster parents' - they're not all at fault http://huff.to/1bQUqVX     
    
    
    MT @wikileaks: WIKILEAKS RELEASE #HongKong: 21,166 emails from US intelligence contractor #Stratfor http://bit.ly/15XZCmz  #gifiles    
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Yeah, the next few links WikiLeaks tweeted looked more like emails    
    
    
    A treatise on role of culture and creativity in a city. Writer also points out Hong Kong devoid of both http://creativetimereports.org/2013/10/07/david-byrne-will-work-for-inspiration/ …    
    
    
    Plan to build Angkor Wat-like temple unhinged by scandal and monk's sex tape http://flip.it/KaTyC  via @bostonmagazine    
    
    
    Coastal Syria sounds beautiful - this funeral scene there is also poignant http://nyti.ms/17kCaiw     
    
    
    Hitler's guide to dating: First question girls should ask "What is your racial background?" http://nyti.ms/19fTl9L     
    
    
    WSJ wrote about urban biking trend in Bangkok not too long ago. Now it's Hanoi http://on.wsj.com/GKAU2L  Tour de SE Asia?    
    
    
    A trial more important than Bo Xilai's http://nyti.ms/17kv1yX     
    
    
    To apologize or not? Aquino suggests it's a cultural issue http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1327109/hong-kong-manila-hold-talks-bus-hostage-crisis … #manilahostagedrama #hk    
    
    
    Cliff hanger! encourage them to do what? MT @W7VOA: I kid you not, @ASEAN has just issued this news release http://bit.ly/15UFTcE     
    
    
    @ongreno My biggest takeaway: Malcolm Gladwell was on the cover of Costco Connection?    
    
    
    Thom Yorke calls Spotify 'the last desperate fart of a dying corpse' http://gu.com/p/3jb7t/tw     
    
    
    Pokfulam village is first HK site on world 'risk list'
http://bit.ly/18Oy6Ll   via @rthk_enews    
    
    
    Is it up, up and away for ‘Superman’ Li Ka-shing? http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1328061/it-and-away-superman-li-ka-shing …    
    
    
    In China, Nothing Says 'I Love You' Like Matching Shirts http://on.wsj.com/16Ss13r  "We want everyone to envy us." I don't know, man    
    
    
    How a sausage giveaway started a war between instant-noodle kings in China http://reut.rs/1fjUvFz     
    
    
    Blame the decline of campy Hong Kong horror films on mainland censors http://bit.ly/16Tz1gr     
    
    
    Robert Kuok is "twin-rooted" in Malaysia and China. Fate of his empire unknown http://bit.ly/16TAIub     
    
    
    Assembling PS4s was a graduation requirement for Foxconn "interns": FT http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/88524304-319f-11e3-817c-00144feab7de.html …    
    
    
    NYT just launched its T Magazine in Chinese http://bit.ly/1ecpRuJ     
    
    
    Japan’s ‘Kill Bill’ Restaurant Opens in Hong Kong http://on.wsj.com/GHIVW2     
    
    
    Photo wins Urban Photo of the Year award  http://bit.ly/19EUwlf  via SCMP #HK pic.twitter.com/OWIwGliTwR    
    
    
    Spinning tragedy: The true cost of a T-shirt http://fw.to/KDp5UiJ  #china #hk #cambodia #canada    
    
    
    Those Laptops That Snowden Took To Hong Kong And Russia Actually Have Nothing On Them http://zite.to/16DFhqb     
    
    
    Oops. Haruki Murakami Wins The Nobel Prize For Literature!….in Japan. For a few minutes. http://zite.to/17wY0Q6     
    
    
    Who Made That Android Logo? http://nyti.ms/15YYDrA     
    
    
    A nice little interactive of Herald Tribune front pages in this retrospective http://nyti.ms/1cMiqN5  pic.twitter.com/8ZgFHaGpyq    
    
    
    Old IHT gem: Dying reporter's message "Please ring up my paper and tell them there is a big story here" http://nyti.ms/1cMjwIx     
    
    
    Extra corpses needed for University of Hong Kong's medical school http://bit.ly/1eksV88  Anyone? Anyone?    
    
    
    @alicemuwu Trendy cafes are not worth the rent increases. We got out just in time    
    
    
    BuzzFeed will use crowd-sourced translation for its French, Spanish and Portuguese sites http://on.wsj.com/16YIPpt     
    
    
    No cauliflower for the world's oldest runner, Fauja Singh, now retired http://gu.com/p/3jfav/tw     
    
    
    The science, and superstition, behind BuzzFeed listicle lengths http://nie.mn/16Bky6l     
    
    
    Um. Hong Kong TV Reporter Claims He Witnessed UFO http://zite.to/16ZMaVi     
    
    
    Could high-rise fish farms revive Hong Kong's fishing industry? http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/14/world/asia/hong-kong-fishing-trawler-ban/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Iceland: Where one in 10 people will publish a book http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24399599 …    
    
    
    Why the 'Sit-able City' is the Next Big Idea http://fw.to/ESIX9hC     
    
    
    Beautifully written. The Russia Left Behind http://www.nytimes.com/newsgraphics/2013/10/13/russia/ …    
    
    
    INYT is not the newest Apple product http://bit.ly/1hSmuJk     
    
    
    The paywall for NYT site and apps is also down for a week. Hurrah! http://bit.ly/1hSnop6     
    
    
    Chocolate newspapers! Why didn't we think of this earlier? pic.twitter.com/IBPzrtZ5dH    
    
    
    Day One of Sinosphere: People's Daily's phallic building, and other interesting posts http://bit.ly/17EZZlq     
    
    
    Modern Subways Zip Below, but a City’s Trams, Slow and Sweaty, Plod On http://nyti.ms/166dYGO  #HK    
    
    
    Boris Johnson trumps George Osborne in China charm game http://on.ft.com/191xfqN     
    
    
    .@andrewjacobsNYT visits Beijing's first RV park. It's luxurious! (video) http://nyti.ms/1enotFM     
    
    
    Donated. Good luck! MT @baoyuan: Want to help survivors of human trafficking, women? Give to  http://bit.ly/19OzYa6  #NYCMarathon    
    
    
    Vietnamese American from OC's Little Saigon suspected of aiding Al Qaeda http://www.latimes.com/local/la-me-1012-terrorism-arrest-20131012,0,4995659.story … ht @comradewong    
    
    
    TTTT is just as bad RT @scottkmurphy: Hilarious...Tang Tang Tang Tang: Sir David Tang’s new boutique - http://bit.ly/1amCRK3     
    
    
    It takes IKEA half a decade to design a kitchen http://qz.com/135040  You fooled me into reading an earnings story @qz! Touché.    
    
    
    At 28, New Zealander Is Youngest To Receive Man Booker Prize http://nyti.ms/168viei     
    
    
    Aw. Originally called dancing bears RT @klustout: Germany's Haribo 'Gummy Bear King' dies age 90 http://bit.ly/1690B8D  #RIP    
    
    
    "Vague: The Power of Generalizations to Impress the Bored" via The Malcolm Gladwell Book Generator http://bit.ly/1aLeeZ3  ht @tinssoldier    
    
    
    Death in Hong Kong Fuels Feelings of Discrimination. "It's getting worse and worse" http://nyti.ms/1bwGjo6     
    
    
    Cha chaan tengs offer more coffee per cup than Starbucks http://bit.ly/1aLfpYs     
    
    
    @bibekbhandari yup    
    
    
    The Man Who Forgot Everything ie. the 'Memento' guy http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/books/2013/10/henry-gustav-molaison-the-man-who-forgot-everything.html?utm_source=www&utm_medium=tw&utm_campaign=20131015 …    
    
    
    African restaurants under the radar in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/16hbfoK     
    
    
    Classy rodents RT @zhongnanhai: 11 rats found in business class on a Hong Kong —> Xiamen flight http://bit.ly/1hY7nhq     
    
    
    Could it be? McDonald's appears to be losing customers http://on.wsj.com/1eoIw6M     
    
    
    This looks interesting. HK Literary Festival has 3 Indonesian migrant writers on panel discussion http://www.festival.org.hk/program/the-help-their-stories-panel-discussion/ …    
    
    
    Call for 'de-Americanized World' Provokes Alarm in U.S., Fart Jokes in China http://blog.foreignpolicy.com/posts/2013/10/16/chinese_reaction_editorial_xinhua_de_americanized_world#.Ul_-iSds0Cw.twitter …    
    
    
    On same day, NYT and Foreign Policy publish posts on China's tuhao nouveau riche http://bit.ly/GRFhZC  http://atfp.co/1cYRRnH     
    
    
    Lots of photos of Boris Johnson in a  helicopter over Hong Kong http://zite.to/1gncAnC  via Daily Mail    
    
    
    3 million living in modern slavery in China, No. 2 in world: Global Slavery Index (India is No. 1) http://www.globalslaveryindex.org/country/china/     
    
    
    What Happens When a Language Has No Numbers? http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/10/16/piraha_cognitive_anumeracy_in_a_language_without_numbers.html …    
    
    
    Snowden gave all his classified documents to journalists he met in Hong Kong, before flying to Moscow http://nyti.ms/1bDeqL6     
    
    
    Western Market is an example of mismanaged redevelopment http://www.scmp.com/property/hong-kong-china/article/1333306/hong-kongs-historical-districts-buildings-risk-profit …    
    
    
    Heels on a slippery boat deck is a great idea! Xinhua gallery of Chinese female navy soldiers http://bit.ly/16SG07c  via Sinocism    
    
    
    Michael Bay: Yes, the story being passed around is not all true! (But the A/C and metal carts were real) http://bit.ly/16SGOJ8     
    
    
    What a daredevil on horse and buggy on PCH MT @NathanUnbound: When L.A.'s most famous streets were dirt roads: http://bit.ly/1i0J9Dt     
    
    
    Former US ambassador to ADB thinks studying abroad can be a waste. Calls it "fancy" education http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2013/10/17/should-more-americans-study-abroad/studying-abroad-can-be-an-expensive-waste-of-time …    
    
    
    @StarrWulfe @AAJAAsia @AAJA @yurinagano @aekubo Y'all have fun!    
    
    
    India digs for treasure after Hindu holy man said a former king appeared to him in a dream http://bigstory.ap.org/article/india-digs-treasure-tip-hindu-holy-man …    
    
    
    Businessman with ties to HK and LA accused of being mob boss in China http://bigstory.ap.org/article/us-businessman-accused-being-mob-boss-china …    
    
    
    A Sri Lankan Journalist Eagerly Toes the Line http://nyti.ms/16hvqbw     
    
    
    Know your kale http://nyti.ms/19Yd1PT     
    
    
    @pcheung630 @AP_Interactive @njgriffiths Congrats!    
    
    
    Must see TV in China: "Chinese Characters Dictation Competition" http://on.wsj.com/H6CvQV  ht @clemtan    
    
    
    HK plans to ban adverts for baby sex-selection trips http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1335572/health-chiefs-plan-ban-adverts-overseas-baby-sex-selection-trips …    
    
    
    Hong Kong woman at centre of sex scandal involving Auckland mayor http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1335579/hong-kong-woman-centre-sex-scandal-involving-auckland-mayor … Something doesn't add up here    
    
    
    #HKTV rally schedule today, via http://on.fb.me/1gugT0B  pic.twitter.com/0dThDaAGOj    
    
    
    Colorful #infographic of international movies with Hong Kong sets http://bit.ly/15TXsHB     
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Your secret is safe. Absolutely no one saw your tweet.    
    
    
    Nothing says freedom like Tony Stark RT @jasonli: Iron Man stopped by the #wewantfreetv protest in Hong Kong. http://bit.ly/18yHFPi     
    
    
    Hong Kong cemeteries rejected a man's application based on race/religion http://bit.ly/1eD2ZEM  Good story @jj_ngo    
    
    
    NYT is working to make numbers-based stories clearer for readers http://nyti.ms/1bFZVpJ     
    
    
    Great photo series on @hongwrongblog following  maids in-training in Indonesia to HK homes. Didn't know they went thru that much    
    
    
    In South Korea, "it still shocks to see the leaders of huge public companies relying on fortune-tellers" http://nyti.ms/16lfAfS     
    
    
    "Dishonesty of headlining may seem a minor issue. It isn’t" says Tim Parks http://www.nybooks.com/blogs/nyrblog/2013/oct/17/headline-headaches/ …    
    
    
    Letter: Sun Yat-sen welcomes to Henry Ford to South China "where much of the intelligence, energy and wealth is" http://nyti.ms/17ZlJso     
    
    
    Ford tried to play catch up in Asia with taxi bid in Hong Kong http://nyti.ms/1a52RwY     
    
    
    Some things @LAScanner has learned about LA: Nothing good ever happens at a pay phone http://bit.ly/16rO630     
    
    
    Sinosphere: Is 'Superman' Li Ka-shing taking off from China and headed for – Europe? http://nyti.ms/1ab1L2K     
    
    
    Why Can Neil Patrick Harris Say That’s ‘Too Gay’ and Straights Can’t? On 'lavender linguistics' and hurtful slurs http://nyti.ms/16pPd8s     
    
    
    Outrage over 'white-skinned girl' college scholarship in Thailand http://t.bangkok.coconuts.co/2013/10/22/whites-only-european-owned-thai-co-offers-money-whitest-students …    
    
    
    Instagram Selfies and Hong Kong's Free TV Movement http://zite.to/1bb5lYX     
    
    
    Ack RT @stanyee: *cough* HK air pollution 'very high' at all 3 roadside stations, 157 in Central    
    
    
    Xi Jinping, watch out RT @ericfish85: Nanjing mayor was sacked for plagiarism: http://bit.ly/1cVtViH     
    
    
    A clamassacre?.. nice MT @C_Murderous: I survived! But barely. This vid is bananas.  #Halloween http://bit.ly/1cVDduX     
    
    
    @blummer102 He kind of asks for it    
    
    
    Who says The Times isn't with it? NYT stylebook moves into 21st century with "email" "website" "to tweet" http://www.theatlanticwire.com/national/2013/10/tweet-and-email-are-now-fit-print/70864/ …    
    
    
    @ChinaFile Link goes to "access denied" page for me    
    
    
    How to Say “Truthiness” in Chinese http://j.mp/1a1CmV4     
    
    
    "If you needed a new first name, what would it be?" Security question on health care website http://on.wsj.com/HgEvFv     
    
    
    @MabelSieh Didn't he also not know who Donald Tsang was? Maybe he is just bad with names    
    
    
    @MabelSieh Just don't bring up the touchy subject!    
    
    
    Answer depends on who you are RT @george_chen: Bloomberg Chinese cover story: Welcome to Hong Kong? I don't care! http://bit.ly/1fWO5MY     
    
    
    SCMP is hiring subs/copy editors/miracle workers http://bit.ly/17gD6eN     
    
    
    She may not know where North Korea is, but this old lady wants to know why China is giving it money http://nyti.ms/1eMvRdP     
    
    
    Btw @NYTSinosphere is not officially NYT or Sinosphere    
    
    
    Wear yellow and carry jade when you visit these haunted places in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/HgzYni     
    
    
    How to eat a cockroach. First, deep fry it twice http://fw.to/U22FQfT  via @MalcomMoore    
    
    
    The art of the corporate apology, Chinese edition http://qz.com/139029  via @qz    
    
    
    Google's autocomplete spells out our darkest thoughts http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2013/oct/22/google-autocomplete-un-women-ad-discrimination-algorithms …    
    
    
    @ChinaFile Thanks!    
    
    
    8 Filipino troops keep China in check in the South China Sea  http://nyti.ms/H5osKV  #snowfallonsteroids    
    
    
    China downsizes English-language section in its national college exam http://on.ft.com/18igLHj     
    
    
    Choosing an English name is liberating for Chinese - names like Scort, Police Car and Inside It's Raining http://nyti.ms/1hdT8aY     
    
    
    What's this Tai Po minibus doing in ...  Zanzibar?? via @petespurrier pic.twitter.com/vlBn2CmVlc    
    
    
    @jgriffiths Funny they left the signs and ads on    
    
    
    How convenient. Now New Express and reporter confess and apologize for "false stories" http://bit.ly/1dyfHHs     
    
    
    North Korea has a crystal meth problem http://bit.ly/1dyi78R     
    
    
    Ousted professor Xia Yeliang: U.S. universities turn blind eye as they enter China http://on.wsj.com/1c5hKih     
    
    
    AP photographer's tour of Peru is beautiful and varied http://bo.st/17l7XXD     
    
    
    "Hong Kong is... dying" is the top result on Google auto-complete. Some results are very telling http://bit.ly/17nVkce     
    
    
    Browsing NYT's style changes: it's now lychee, not litchi; and sweatpants is one word. You're welcome.    
    
    
    @olivesophierose ... around the time when Radio and Film became passé    
    
    
    “No Woman, No Drive” Stuns Saudi Arabia, inspired by some Jamaican guy http://globalvoicesonline.org/2013/10/26/video-no-woman-no-drive-stuns-saudi-arabia/ … via @globalvoices    
    
    
    Fitting headline: One day in the life of Mikhail Khodorkovsky http://on.ft.com/H4Kopq     
    
    
    Cannibals are the new zombies in movie trends http://nyti.ms/1dx77II     
    
    
    Write for no payment? Don't do it. An essay on professional worth http://nyti.ms/H9hPau     
    
    
    Indonesia to ban masked monkey shows in capital http://bigstory.ap.org/article/indonesia-boots-masked-monkey-shows-capital …    
    
    
    Chinese Wikipedia Becomes Front Line for Views on Language and Culture http://nyti.ms/16FaDcI     
    
    
    Finally RT @zhongnanhai: Glasses that could translate a Chinese menu into English http://bit.ly/1dBzjdy     
    
    
    Pretty good. This Hong Konger's Kim Jong-un costume just won Halloween http://online.thatsmags.com/post/this-hong-kongers-kim-jong-un-costume-just-won-halloween#.Um34rh2vjQ0.twitter …    
    
    
    Butcher goes on envy-fueled massacre in Brooklyn. At least NYPost didn't call him a Chinese alien again http://bit.ly/1hml2l4     
    
    
    MT @william_fitz: Google now has an Asia Pacific blog covering Google and the Internet from .au to .in! http://bit.ly/1ajCPbj     
    
    
    Must read RT @nytopinion: A (mostly) civil argument between @nytkeller and @ggreenwald about the future of news: http://bit.ly/16DLdBD     
    
    
    After Crash In Beijing, Moves to Halt Flow of News  http://nyti.ms/17oDTdK     
    
    
    Love is a conveyor belt of warmth RT @DougMeigs: 44 Hong Kong Movie Subtitles Gone Wrong - via Buzzfeed: http://bit.ly/19OLtfg     
    
    
    California city sues hot sauce maker for fouling air with "spicy odor" http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-irwindale-sues-sriracha-20131028,0,2608897.story …    
    
    
    Always learning. Will have to brace myself for the first tip, but thanks @SubvCopyEd for the idea  http://bit.ly/HdrDAj     
    
    
    What are the hardest languages to learn #graphic http://voxy.com/blog/index.php/wide-infographics/what-are-the-hardest-languages-to-learn-infographic/ …    
    
    
    Britney Spears' music used by British navy to scare off Somali pirates http://gu.com/p/3kvc8/tw     
    
    
    Scientist Links Asia’s Yeti to Ancient Bear http://thediplomat.com/asia-life/2013/10/scientist-links-asias-abominable-snowman-to-ancient-bear/ …    
    
    
    Absurd article.  In essence: Chinese mistress culture runs deep so live with it http://www.atimes.com/atimes/China/CHIN-01-291013.html …    
    
    
    From China to Los Angeles, Taking the Electric Bus http://nyti.ms/HtIJJU     
    
    
    That guy is obviously an apparition MT @SCMP_News China's worst photoshopped propaganda photo? http://bit.ly/1gb1lxz  http://bit.ly/1gb1iSr     
    
    
    @jgriffiths Or she is just really really far away    
    
    
    No need to panic. Women just "can't decide which way to go when they drive." Thanks, Beijing police! http://nyti.ms/1gZ3nlV     
    
    
    Ultimate origami MT @newsmary: Fold-your-own paper torso with removable organs. http://bit.ly/16J30r0     
    
    
    @feng37 That would've been fun!    
    
    
    Merkel Balks at EU Privacy Push http://spon.de/ad4d2  #cognitivedissonance    
    
    
    Indian Communist politician ousted for sleeping in bed of cash http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-india-cash-bed-20131030,0,5066773.story …    
    
    
    This is getting ridiculous RT @beijingcream: NO. http://bit.ly/19d8nxt  HT @joshchin http://bit.ly/19d8qJs     
    
    
    Student calls an editor a "paper-work expert." I guess he's not entirely wrong.    
    
    
    'Tis the season (already) pic.twitter.com/1UDlDcmw5w    
    
    
    @_jlam no!    
    
    
    ! RT @zhongnanhai: You can now use electronic devices during takeoff and landing in the United States. #finally http://bit.ly/HxCAN0     
    
    
    Snowden starts new job at Russian Internet company on Friday http://nyti.ms/17Zicv7     
    
    
    Australian embassies are being secretly used to intercept phone calls and data across Asia for #NSA http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/exposed-australias-asia-spy-network-20131030-2whia.html …    
    
    
    Former Philippine president to apologize in person in Hong Kong http://nyti.ms/16OGSWY     
    
    
    Organizer hoping for ultramarathons in 4 "Da" cities  — Dalian, Dali, Datong and Daqing http://bit.ly/HxXDPn     
    
    
    Turkey Legalizes the Letters Q, W, and X http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/10/24/turkey_prime_minister_erdogan_s_democratizaton_package_legalizes_letters.html …    
    
    
    Good story. Can rebranding help fish sauce be Vietnam's Champagne? http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/11/can-fish-sauce-be-vietnams-champagne/281071/ …    
    
    
    In Praise of Art Forgeries http://nyti.ms/1hD0yod  "Forgers also remind us that great art depends on the ideas of artists"    
    
    
    Godard/Woody is my favorite RT @brainpicker: Paris vs. New York, in minimalist infographic parallels and contrasts http://bit.ly/17A5j08     
    
    
    Declining Asian populations in Chinatowns won't be good for new immigrants http://on.ft.com/1iB3tve     
    
    
    For all the changes in Hong Kong, this 1988 NYT profile of Mong Kok holds up well http://nyti.ms/1bOXmRI     
    
    
    China to end use of prisoners' organs for transplants in 2014 http://reut.rs/19lMr3h  Only country that allows it    
    
    
    Ha. New York Times corrects: Writer’s name is not ‘Chillian J. Yikes’ http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/mediawire/228215/new-york-times-corrects-reporters-name-is-not-chillian-j-yikes/#.UnYiZdC1tiU.twitter …    
    
    
    Villager fined for running hikers' hostel at his house in New Territories http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1346912/hong-kong-government-urged-allow-flexible-operation-hostels-hikers …    
    
    
    Good one, Google! http://on.mash.to/171n4zP  pic.twitter.com/n6kbtk5KYR    
    
    
    @blersing @george_chen And probably more respect too!    
    
    
    How China Profits From Our Junk - by the son and grandson of scrap metalists http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/11/how-china-profits-from-our-junk/281044/ …    
    
    
    Snacks and sweets face price sting from humble bee http://on.ft.com/184TWYv     
    
    
    Catchy way to remember the order of China's dynasties http://nyti.ms/1hJgvJv     
    
    
    Secrets of a Game Show Writer http://nyti.ms/1hJ56cL  What did they do before Google, though?    
    
    
    Chinese water bottler Nongfu Springs accuses Beijing newspaper of defamation http://reut.rs/HxtP66     
    
    
    #INYT MT @AAJAAsia: What it's like to work in HK as a US journalist via @mcknightkristin and @andybechtel http://bit.ly/1a4OtnR     
    
    
    Insane photos of a pirate execution in Kowloon City, 1891 http://disq.us/8fzspf  #HK    
    
    
    'Kafka' case: LA couple accused of starving adopted daughter to death in Qatar to give their side of story http://nyti.ms/1hIYJX0     
    
    
    Hong Kong's English-language skills slip in Asia ranking http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1348626/hong-kongs-english-language-skills-slip-says-ef-education-first …    
    
    
    Bloomberg News Is Said to Curb Articles That Might Anger China http://nyti.ms/1dTugTD     
    
    
    Finally, what we've all been thinking: Hong Kong's little bubble of self-importance http://bit.ly/18hXJli     
    
    
    16 Differences Between Living In Hong Kong And Taiwan - in comic form http://www.buzzfeed.com/kevintang/16-differences-between-living-in-hong-kong-and-taiwan …    
    
    
    Acquiesce. Acquiesce. Aquiesce. NMATV on Bloomberg News and China http://bit.ly/19aGQbW     
    
    
    Salt tip is a good one! RT @_jlam: Hong Kong Life Hacks by @hk_magazine http://bit.ly/19aHqGu     
    
    
    Fallows: the best possible PR campaign Chinese officials could undertake would be to let reporters roam freely http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/11/this-latest-chinese-censorship-news-is-important-and-bad/281319/ …    
    
    
    "In fiction, as in life, characters don’t have to be likable to be lovable." Mohsin Hamid http://nyti.ms/19aJZs9     
    
    
    Scale of typhoon destruction in Philippines compared to 2004 Indian Ocean tsunami http://on.wsj.com/16Q0gWz     
    
    
    Alibaba's 11.11 shopping day in China is bigger than 'Black Friday' http://on.wsj.com/17Juaih     
    
    
    The Craigslist killers http://gu.com/p/3k6d9/tw  #longread    
    
    
    Here, For Some Reason, Is A Chinese Rap Video About Cleveland http://beijingcream.com/2013/11/here-for-some-reason-is-a-chinese-rap-video-about-cleveland/ …    
    
    
    Nice! MT @JeromeTaylor: My photos of Hong Kong's gay #pride march have been picked up by @hongwrongblog: http://bit.ly/18kGb85     
    
    
    Huffington Post to launch in Korean in early 2014 http://www.hani.co.kr/arti/english_edition/e_international/610659.html …    
    
    
    @clemtan Even cooler name: Batman bin Suparman    
    
    
    @clemtan Weird Singapore    
    
    
    More Hotels Are Saying Welcome in Mandarin http://nyti.ms/17jVJsA     
    
    
    Mapping the destruction in Tacloban http://nyti.ms/HQP4Au  pic.twitter.com/AMukgAEDT9    
    
    
    Be Terrified: Hong Kong's Banker Babies Are Learning Finance in Pre-K http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2013/11/be-terrified-hong-kongs-banker-babies-are-learning-finance-in-pre-k/281354/ …    
    
    
    Former Gov Chris Patten's regrets on Hong Kong http://on.wsj.com/1bsAM1x     
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Baby banker rejected my loan application! Noo....    
    
    
    Primer on the Third Plenum via Caixin http://bit.ly/HQWIe1     
    
    
    Freee could use a few more Es MT @1rick: My piece on strange Japanese startup names (http://bit.ly/1cPPu7N )    
    
    
    Amphitheater of the Dead: Hong Kong Hillside Cemeteries (photos) http://weburbanist.com/2013/11/08/amphitheater-of-the-dead-hong-kong-hillside-cemeteries/ …    
    
    
    Newsroom cuts have hit visual journalists harder than copy/layout editors since 2000 http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/mediawire/229302/visual-jobs-in-newsrooms-have-fallen-by-nearly-half-since-2000/#.UoG96Jd_CKc.twitter …    
    
    
    This changes everything RT @adamnajberg: We've been eating our apple a day all wrong http://bit.ly/19Zv48z     
    
    
    @tinssoldier The answer is, of course. From the bottom.    
    
    
    "Maybe Godot never appears because everyone is mispronouncing his name." http://nyti.ms/17jU06z     
    
    
    Awful. Bloody End for Iranian Rockers Seeking Musical Freedom in U.S. http://nyti.ms/19dnxP3     
    
    
    @lalarimando @MeOldChina64 I found the pronunciation key helpful.. for that inner broadcaster in me    
    
    
    Ariel Levy's “Thanksgiving in Mongolia” took me by surprise http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2013/11/18/131118fa_fact_levy?mbid=social_retweet …    
    
    
    3 journalists departing NYT for digital http://nyti.ms/1dmjVPb     
    
    
    Descendants of Confucius used to get special honors and titles http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/technology/article/1354787/study-finds-single-bloodline-among-self-claimed-confucius …    
    
    
    Philippine domestic helpers in Hong Kong battle to contact loved ones. Collection boxes at Worldwide Plaza http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1354759/philippine-domestic-helpers-hong-kong-battle-contact-loved-ones …    
    
    
    Even Native Chinese Speakers Aren't Sure What The Government Said About Market Reform http://www.businessinsider.com/3rd-plenums-communique-on-the-market-2013-11 … #cpcdoublespeak    
    
    
    'I don't work for Bloomberg': Bloomberg on Bloomberg News allegations http://politicker.com/?p=72764  via @mattschiavenza    
    
    
    Wife of Calif governor puts up with his "tendency to muse philosophically on every bit of policy minutia" http://nyti.ms/1btpA6x     
    
    
    Super Small Gun Enthusiast, a Chinese picture book for kids http://bit.ly/1btnaES     
    
    
    Slate's econ correspondent loves Hong Kong's MTR. Who doesn't? http://www.slate.com/blogs/moneybox/2013/11/12/hong_kong_mtr_costs_great_transit_at_low_cost.html …    
    
    
    Double room at Beijing's storied hotel goes for $600. Not that you can book one, of course http://nyti.ms/1gIy1ih     
    
    
    @sarahefung @bencsin I wish I could unsee that conversation! Gravity ruined for me too now    
    
    
    Especially haunting via Tyler Hicks/NYT http://nyti.ms/HY4W3f  pic.twitter.com/32vQdgGmsB    
    
    
    George Clooney's Rules for Living: Don't talk smack unless you can play the game http://www.esquire.com/features/george-clooney-interview-1213 …    
    
    
    An exclusive interview with the Dalai Lama - FT http://www.ft.com/cms/s/2/d49d13aa-4749-11e3-b4d3-00144feabdc0.html …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 it's Clooney! Who wouldn't?    
    
    
    Exclusive: Sriracha founder reveals the 'secret' wholesale price of his sauce http://www.marketplace.org/topics/business/numbers/exclusive-sriracha-founder-reveals-secret-wholesale-price-his-sauce#.UoOsK2wyDpc.twitter …    
    
    
    Should one pose questions on Twitter? RT @Garvey_B: Learned how to tweet today pic.twitter.com/GSGsHv1rs5    
    
    
    At Bloomberg, Special Code Keeps Some Articles Out of China http://nyti.ms/19kHq75     
    
    
    He's got a point MT @WSJ: "OK. You're a runner. Get over it." Chad Stafko writes about the problem with some runners http://bit.ly/1fCNpcY     
    
    
    Is it even fair to compare China to Nazi Germany? (in terms of reporting for foreign journalists) http://nyti.ms/18tv8tB  via Sinosphere    
    
    
    Abe commends Chinese student for saving Japanese boy http://nyti.ms/HZPP9h     
    
    
    Bizarre twist. British spy found dead in sports bag may have locked himself inside by accident http://nyti.ms/1gKwRmt     
    
    
    Did the New York Times Just Get Blocked in China -- Again? | FP Passport http://blog.foreignpolicy.com/posts/2013/11/13/did_the_new_york_times_just_get_blocked_in_china_again?wp_login_redirect=0#.UoVp0QH6ddM.twitter …    
    
    
    HK's Kim Jong-un impersonator was asked to shoot commercial with Dennis Rodman http://hongwrong.com/kim-jong-un-impersonator/ …    
    
    
    Was it principle or money? RT @NewYorker: Why Did Snapchat Turn Down Three Billion Dollars? http://bit.ly/1e6JDYI     
    
    
    Social media marketing done right MT @tinssoldier What started as a sassy tweet to a telecoms firm... http://www.buzzfeed.com/scottybryan/this-is-the-best-twitter-conversation-you-will … via @jenn1marsh    
    
    
    NYT's homepage featuring Wes Anderson's nice little short/ad pic.twitter.com/CxPuYmLVII    
    
    
    @tinssoldier You just took away a journalist's income    
    
    
    Amid New York Times departures, Jack Shafer says no journalist is irreplaceable http://reut.rs/1bAVNJh     
    
    
    Stop with the millennial trend stories (a rant in comics form) https://medium.com/the-nib/875d45297612 …    
    
    
    For Chess, a Would-Be White Knight: Bringing chess to the masses, with play-by-play commentary http://nyti.ms/1epHQOL     
    
    
    Identity checks by Hong Kong police beat NY and London. Claim no racial profiling http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1364087/police-tactics-queried-after-16m-spot-checks-last-year …    
    
    
    "Boxing’s not so well kept dirty secret is that, financially, most fighters can never stop" http://www.sbnation.com/longform/2013/11/20/5119180/manny-pacquiao-vs-brandon-rios-fight-2013-profile … #pacquiao    
    
    
    Why Lego thrives in China http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/currency/2013/11/lego-company-asian-toy-industry-sales-in-china.html …    
    
    
    How books about sport got serious http://on.ft.com/1bYoaBk  High vs low culture    
    
    
    OED's word of the year: selfie. Just glad it wasn't sharknado http://blog.oxforddictionaries.com/2013/11/an-infographic-of-selfie/ … #infographic    
    
    
    The evolution of "because" as preposition. Awful usage, because.. just because http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/11/english-has-a-new-preposition-because-internet/281601/ …    
    
    
    For Chinese political cartoonists, a picture can say a thousand words - and lead to jail  http://www.scmp.com/magazines/post-magazine/article/1355746/drawing-ire …    
    
    
    Haitian photographer wins major U.S. copyright victory years after posting photos on TwitPic http://nyti.ms/1drAjC7     
    
    
    Foreign trainees from China, Vietnam falling prey to Japanese employers http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2013/11/24/national/foreign-trainees-still-falling-prey-to-japanese-employers/ …    
    
    
    So many things wrong with this article. An expat career woman on Beijing flings.  http://www.dailymail.co.uk/home/you/article-2511313/My-sweet-sour-dating-experience-An-expat-career-woman-Beijing-flings.html …    
    
    
    Only 10% of MOOC students finish classes. Why godfather of free online education is changing course http://flip.it/a5AvC     
    
    
    Rich brats? No way MT @Garvey_B: Children of rich Chinese families home alone in Canada turn into brats http://m.scmp.com/news/china/article/1364563/children-rich-chinese-home-alone-canada-face-challenges …    
    
    
    I admit I have been ignoring bitcoin articles, but it's no longer possible. Catching up with this http://vimeo.com/63502573     
    
    
    Beautiful and strange photos of Hong Kong 150 years ago http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702303531204579206764210666466#3 …    
    
    
    @jamesplloyd Oh right. But the general idea is there    
    
    
    Biz journalists, take note MT @petesweeneypro @apgalbraith  "Stupid Things Finance People Say" http://www.fool.com/investing/general/2013/11/14/stupid-things-finance-people-say.aspx …    
    
    
    Not just for military purposes. Drones offer journalists a wider view http://nyti.ms/1duzFUe     
    
    
    Signs of change in news mission at Bloomberg http://nyti.ms/1duBOiF     
    
    
    Alas, @ChuBailiang is not a seller of air purifiers in Beijing http://sinosphere.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/11/25/u-s-embassy-stocks-up-on-air-purifiers/?smid=tw-share …    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @adolfux: Asian Digital Media Awards 2013. Best online infographic #scmp #wan-ifra http://instagram.com/p/hILl6ED3M7/     
    
    
    @_sofiamt May the force be with you, @tinssoldier    
    
    
    What's Chinese for Dowager Countess? @DowntonAbbey goes to China http://www.marketplace.org/topics/world/whats-chinese-dowager-countess-downton-abbey-goes-china …    
    
    
    On newspapers in Myanmar: “You have to be ready to fight. And ready to lose” http://nyti.ms/18jQaka     
    
    
    CSI in the art world: Pollock's lover insists painting is real http://www.nytimes.com/2013/11/25/arts/design/a-real-pollock-on-this-art-and-science-collide.html/?ref=international-home …    
    
    
    Seriously? Mother 'may have invented girl's abduction' in Kowloon City http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1365704/mother-may-have-invented-girls-abduction-kowloon-city …    
    
    
    It's just good grammar. MT @jakeadelstein: Adding a period in text messages=anger? Really. The Period Is Pissed http://www.newrepublic.com/article/115726/period-our-simplest-punctuation-mark-has-become-sign-anger …    
    
    
    Jhumpa Lahiri on her struggle to achieve simplicity. She also has a nice writing desk http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/books/2013/09/video-jhumpa-lahiri-at-work.html?mbid=social_retweet …    
    
    
    Vietnamese ice coffee "is to Starbucks what pho is to chicken soup" http://roadsandkingdoms.com/2012/bevporn-vietnamese-ice-coffee/ …    
    
    
    Let's Kill All the Hawks and Doves! As Lazy Metaphors, That Is. via @tnr http://www.newrepublic.com/article/115734/hawks-doves-origins-metaphors-war-peace-supporters …    
    
    
    New Clues May Change Buddha’s Date of Birth http://nyti.ms/1evwE37     
    
    
    Don't cross the old people. Elderly mahjong players slam 'needless' crackdown on parlours http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1366494/elderly-mahjong-players-slam-needless-crackdown-games …    
    
    
    A thorough round-up on the Bloomberg-China story  http://chinadigitaltimes.net/2013/11/bloomberg-continued-fire-self-censorship/#.UpVIJLIzPuI.twitter … ht @sophie_beach    
    
    
    Stock up NOW RT @LANow: Sriracha plant must cease operations that cause odors, judge rules http://lat.ms/InanK8     
    
    
    And so it begins... "Asia is on the cusp of a full-blown arms race."  http://fw.to/aVMnL8B     
    
    
    Euphemism gymnastics in this one. With Glut of Lonely Men, China Has an Approved Outlet for Unrequited Lust http://nyti.ms/1ez0t2Q     
    
    
    In China, Loss of a Child Means Orphan Parents http://nyti.ms/18oSYwf  with a Downton reference    
    
    
    Photographer has wonderful sense of humor in his series of train passengers in China http://shanghaiist.com/2013/11/26/check_out_these_vivid_and_amazing_p.php …    
    
    
    Chinese state workers get toothpaste as freebies this year. Last year, they were iPads http://nyti.ms/18pUU7N     
    
    
    @PRforplants It doesn't. We seem to move from summer straight to winter.    
    
    
    Hong Kong private investigator caught up in Irish ‘Wobbly Boots’ case http://on.ft.com/1ikSZ8K     
    
    
    Op-ed: Good on Buzzfeed for banning the negative book review http://nyti.ms/1gqvpCV     
    
    
    “No Animals Were Harmed” Don't always believe the label on films and TV  http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/feature/animals-were-harmed-659270 …    
    
    
    Britain has a curry crisis http://nyti.ms/1exodnd     
    
    
    Naked resignation: quitting without another job lined up  http://www.foreignpolicy.com/articles/2013/11/25/chinas_jack_kerouac … #china    
    
    
    Flawed system for judging research is leading to academic fraud in China http://econ.st/18ZfACA     
    
    
    Random: Here's a photo of Kanye West as a 10 year old in Nanjing in 1987 http://online.thatsmags.com/post/heres-a-photo-of-kanye-west-as-a-schoolchild-in-nanjing-in-1987#.UpryvYLtK-Q.twitter …    
    
    
    Maoism in Europe: At its peak, there were 10,000 members in Germany http://gu.com/p/3kyez/tw     
    
    
    Forget about being Hong Kong's would-be first lady, Lisa Kuo is a saint http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1369902/lisa-kuo-family-comes-first … #standingbehindhenrytang    
    
    
    Zhang Yimou apologises for breaching China's one-child policy http://gu.com/p/3kp5d/tw     
    
    
    Taiwan has one of the highest recycling rates in the world http://nyti.ms/1dGSa83     
    
    
    Incredibly touching. Mother and son agree that she is a good doctor, but “maybe not the best mother.” http://www.buzzfeed.com/kathleenmclaughlin/the-aids-granny-in-exile …    
    
    
    Shrunken yellow jumpsuit worn by Bruce Lee on auction  http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1371154/bruce-lee-game-death-jumpsuit-auction …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 If you can fit it!    
    
    
    Please hold the handrail; don't keep your eyes on your mobile phone. #MTR    
    
    
    @Film_Monitor Might be for some? I just found it funny the MTR felt the need to make the announcement    
    
    
    Saving journalism jobs one list at a time RT @BuzzFeed: BuzzFeed is hiring! http://www.jobscore.com/jobs/buzzfeed     
    
    
        
    
    
    The fascinating marine archaeology side of the South China Sea dispute http://on.wsj.com/1b0ibM3     
    
    
    Matte. Clearly an owner with restraint RT @JoshTANoble: Spotted in Sheung Wan: neon pink matte-finish Bentley. pic.twitter.com/x703YZ9qz9    
    
    
    Linguist explains the rules of summoning Benedict Cumberbatch http://the-toast.net/2013/12/02/a-linguist-explains-the-rules-of-summoning-benedict-cumberbatch/ …    
    
    
    Quite the discussion under comments for Hong Kong's Troubling Shortage of Men http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/12/hong-kongs-troubling-shortage-of-men/281942/ …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Yawn    
    
    
    "Shamate" phenomenon is like a KISS revival with a social message http://www.foreignpolicy.com/articles/2013/12/02/meet_chinas_shamate_un_hip#.Up2WJ3M2dKc.twitter …    
    
    
    Understanding why North Korea arrested Merill Newman http://www.nknews.org/2013/12/understanding-why-north-korea-arrested-merill-newman/ …    
    
    
    Kumbaya MT @W7VOA: #Thailand’s PM in brief remarks makes no dramatic announcement, asks all to join hand for a peaceful solution.    
    
    
    It's spreading. The California Vowel Shift. Are you a victim? http://www.portlandmonthlymag.com/news-and-profiles/culture/articles/dude-wheres-my-accent-december-2013 … ht @StanCarey    
    
    
    +1 MT @rob_schmitz: Excellent essay by Pete Hessler on Photographer Shen Wei's work: http://www.chinafile.com/shen-wei-s-chinese-sentiment …    
    
    
    Miniature pig roams Tiananmen, confounding police and Beijing http://nyti.ms/1dOTKER     
    
    
    Food carts in Los Angeles come out of the shadows http://nyti.ms/1dR5F5b  #dangerdogs    
    
    
    Very cool: Inside the Faber-Castell pencil factory in Stein, Germany (video) http://nyti.ms/1gD9SHg     
    
    
    @Rydaine I see mostly teen lit    
    
    
    Funny tale of a weird encounter in which Biden winks at pool reporter during handshake of the VPs http://nyti.ms/1eRsgec  #china    
    
    
    Young Indian women learn how to tie saris in classes costing up to $500 http://on.wsj.com/1eY6fv7     
    
    
    Amsterdam Has a Deal for Alcoholics: Work Paid in Beer http://nyti.ms/1dR7Vtb  No surprise program has long waiting list    
    
    
    China’s ban on bitcoin doesn’t make a difference—it was banned already http://qz.com/154420     
    
    
    Amazon reviews for Samsung's $45,000 TV. Comes with free batteries! http://www.slate.com/blogs/future_tense/2013/12/04/samsung_40_000_tv_funny_amazon_reviews_for_un85s9_85_inch_smart_tv.html …    
    
    
    Why it's dangerous to hero-worship tech entrepreneurs http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/11/silicon-valley-isnt-a-meritocracy-and-the-cult-of-the-entrepreneur-holds-people-back/ …    
    
    
    The pursuit of happiness has not stopped Bhutan from frantic urbanization http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/2/83ba0adc-5b86-11e3-a2ba-00144feabdc0.html# …    
    
    
    Who needs knitting needles when you have your arms? Yep, WSJ looks at arm knitting http://on.wsj.com/1eRg5yd     
    
    
    McMaster University sounds like a fake school.    
    
    
    We should all adjourn for the dayRT @nitabhalla: Indian parliament adjourned until Monday as a mark of respect for #Madiba #RIPNelsonMandela    
    
    
    #FF @UpWorthIt because genius    
    
    
    I thought it was a British accent MT @raykwong :-) Paper says strangers in China think you're smart if you smile http://jcc.sagepub.com/content/early/2013/11/28/0022022113513922.abstract …    
    
    
    China's new favorite reality show spark a parenting revolution? #Unlikely http://nyti.ms/1khTL1I     
    
    
    Ali moved to tears when he found out Mandela listened to his fights in prison. Lovely tribute from Nov http://huff.to/1jFPaGs     
    
    
    Skirmish breaks out between U.S. reporters and Japanese press at Biden press conference http://on.wsj.com/1cVALnw     
    
    
        
    
    
    China's anti-graft tsar reportedly a fan of House of Cards http://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1374922/anti-graft-tsar-wang-qishan-fan-tv-series-house-cards-report-says …    
    
    
    Retracing the footsteps of DH Lawrence in the Alps http://on.ft.com/IxdDCm     
    
    
    Man Asks Internet to Hunt Down His Lost Crush ... and it all started in Hong Kong http://www.slate.com/blogs/xx_factor/2013/12/06/reese_mckee_creepy_new_zealand_man_launches_international_hunt_for_lost.html …    
    
    
    New documents shed light on JPMorgan's 'Sons and Daughters' China hiring program http://nyti.ms/1eXT6Sc     
    
    
    Chinese parents hire investigators to spy on children studying in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1375605/parents-hire-private-investigators-keep-eye-their-student-children …    
    
    
    Stalking is legal in Hong Kong, says Michael Jackson, HKU law professor http://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1375605/parents-hire-private-investigators-keep-eye-their-student-children … #waitwhat    
    
    
    “More than the Japanese and Chinese, Koreans are very expressive about their feelings.." On musical boom in Seoul http://nyti.ms/1gOiFGz     
    
    
    Asked what he planned to do once he got home, Merrill Newman quipped: "Probably take my shoes off" http://www.latimes.com/local/la-me-merrill-newman-20131208,0,3251403.story …    
    
    
    Kimchi listed as a UNESCO intangible cultural heritage  http://j.mp/IK8KoU  via @noruweijin    
    
    
    @bibekbhandari @akannampilly I had to look that one up. Sounds yummy!    
    
    
    Yet another wistful look at "journalism's golden age" RT @george_chen: Among the ghosts of Fleet Street: http://on.ft.com/1d1eHHC     
    
    
    This ode to the durian almost makes me want to give it another try. Almost. http://nyti.ms/1gC8nJs     
    
    
    Now even Youku isn't a haven for pirated content http://reut.rs/1aDXNMw     
    
    
    Down with smarm. Spot-on rant, er, essay, on anti-snark #hatersgonnahate http://gawker.com/on-smarm-1476594977 …    
    
    
    Uncle Jang was “ideologically sick and extremely idle and easy-going" http://gu.com/p/3y3at/tw     
    
    
    In TVB production, a drama about bitcoin. They call it C-Coin #點金聖手 h/t @gracel129    
    
    
    It's not easy to paint diorama backdrops at the American Museum of Natural History http://nyti.ms/1f0zNaL     
    
    
    Wall Street mothers: "As husbands do domestic duty, these women are free to achieve" Gee, thanks. http://nyti.ms/1bPUnMQ     
    
    
    That story you were presumably guessing about http://nyti.ms/1gLHQJJ     
    
    
    The Manhunt for Christopher Dorner http://fw.to/kIDBw3Q  Wish I could binge-read it. But interesting rollout, @latimes    
    
    
    The fascinating history behind Ukraine's toppled Lenin statue http://zite.to/ILqW1D     
    
    
    Google hands: the permanence of digital errors in Google Books' scanning process http://flip.it/Ldftt     
    
    
    Spies’ dragnet reaches a playing field of elves and trolls http://flip.it/uS6H3  #NSA    
    
    
    No Contest: Edward Snowden is Person of the Year http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/johncassidy/2013/12/no-contest-edward-snowden-is-person-of-the-year.html?utm_source=www&utm_medium=tw&utm_campaign=20131209 …    
    
    
    IKEA wolf toy flies off the shelves as the latest symbol of protest in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1377007/toy-wolf-rude-name-becomes-must-have-hong-kong-protesters … pic.twitter.com/kITwknS0J6    
    
    
    Muggles are slow MT @AlexHoegberg: My ex-colleagues at Zhejiang Uni have developed an #InvisibilityCloak http://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1376652/chinese-scientists-upbeat-development-invisibility-cloak …    
    
    
    Oh those fleshy lips. The male koala’s hefty come-hither call http://nyti.ms/1gUlmX9     
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Not so cute are they?    
    
    
    Staff at IKEA stores had already resorted to referring to Lufsig as "that stuffed toy" to avoid accidentally swearing http://huff.to/1feEfUb     
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle Want to test it out on the streets?    
    
    
    Why Canada and the U.S. should merge, eh? Hear her out http://on.wsj.com/1gLalaq     
    
    
    Justin Bieber arrives in Manila, to visit typhoon-hit areas http://www.rappler.com/entertainment/45626-justin-bieber-visit-yolanda-areas …    
    
    
    Chinese hackers attacked European ministries via email with "naked photos" of Carla Bruni-Sarkozy: report http://nyti.ms/1hJzCoD     
    
    
    Thanks to smog, Chinese people are funnier! http://shanghaiist.com/2013/12/10/the_5_surprising_benefits_of_smog_a.php …    
    
    
    What you've been waiting for @feng37 http://hk-magazine.com/events/article/balls-mall … via @adamawhite    
    
    
    In HK sign language, "American" is just the "crazy" gesture http://www.scmp.com/magazines/post-magazine/article/1344336/then-now-sign-language-hong-kong … (This story needs to be a video @SCMPVideoMojo)    
    
    
    IKEA's Lufsig has its own Facebook page https://www.facebook.com/Lufsig?ref=nf  #HKprotests    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle I believe it's the Cantonese pronunciation of its Chinese name sounding obscene    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle Ha! Can I watch?    
    
    
    Hey, I can read full articles on @ForeignPolicy. No paywall with the redesign? For a limited time only?    
    
    
    @stegersaurus @yennikwok I think I have one in my closet somewhere...    
    
    
    Headlines you wish you had thought of: The Desolation of Smog http://www.foreignpolicy.com/articles/2013/12/03/desolation_of_smog_china_london_pollution …    
    
    
    NYU retracts spyware claim on Chen Guangcheng's iPad and iPhone. Calls it "misunderstanding" http://nyti.ms/1gVgJvV     
    
    
    Nice night outdoors for a cheesy old Hong Kong movie @ The New Central Harbourfront http://instagram.com/p/hva1TIiTb8/     
    
    
    Google abandons Hong Kong data centre because of plot ratio rules http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1377908/google-abandons-its-hong-kong-data-centre-project …    
    
    
    Favorite time of the year: NPR Music's 50 Favorite Albums Of 2013 http://n.pr/IHDQ0G     
    
    
    After typhoon, effort to protect Filipino women from rape falters, UN says http://nyti.ms/1gYeHLm     
    
    
    I can't imagine working anywhere for 33 years http://nyti.ms/1f5lgdZ     
    
    
    CY Leung says on his blog he bought a Lufsig for daughter. Way to take the air out http://www.ceo.gov.hk/chi/blog/blog20131211.html … pic.twitter.com/h694PGlaQK    
    
    
    @wingp Hehe    
    
    
    Yes! RT @ww_tsuuhan_ww: ラーメン食べるときにどうぞ pic.twitter.com/e9WN6chiSA    
    
    
    "Shitstorm" and "flashmob" make it into the most respected German-language dictionary http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/11/13/denglisch_a_shitschturm_erupts_as_english_words_make_their_way_into_the.html …    
    
    
    @lienh I was thinking to keep your hair from getting in the way    
    
    
    No one is immune from Beijing’s ‘gravity machine’. @davidpilling sums it up http://www.ft.com/intl/cms/s/0/32470bd8-619d-11e3-b7f1-00144feabdc0.html?siteedition=intl# …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 ...in which the moon comes to Beijing. Not the other way around.    
    
    
    This video out of China with dancing "African" kids made my day http://nyti.ms/1h24OMQ     
    
    
    Bizarre. Sign language interpreter at Mandela memorial says he saw ‘angels’ http://nyti.ms/1f9smhI     
    
    
    This is huge. Guangzhou beats Hong Kong at lawn bowling http://zite.to/1bA3wXm     
    
    
    Hobbit physics: The problem with dwarves standing up in floating barrels http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2013/12/should-dwarves-stand-up-in-floating-barrels/ …    
    
    
    The Wizard of Macau: As Citibank intern in the 80s, he drove a Rolls-Royce to work http://on.wsj.com/1h39fXR     
    
    
    Fulbright scholar in Beijing, known for Laowai Style video, studied crosstalk comedy for months http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/arts-culture/article/1379333/laowai-style-one-americans-mission-share-power-comedy-china …    
    
    
    Smog in Beijing like LA in the 60s: US EPA head  http://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1379327/smog-beijing-la-60s-us-epa-chief-gina-mccarthy-says …    
    
    
    Wow. A new newspaper to be launched in LA http://www.laobserved.com/archive/2013/12/kushner_unveils_plans_for.php#.UqrXlBw8cK8.twitter …    
    
    
    Hawker, 71, in coma after tire falls from sky and hits him in Tai Kok Tsui http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1379750/seven-hurt-one-critically-after-truck-wheel-breaks-free-and-flies-tai …    
    
    
    Police arrest elderly pimps in Hong Kong hotel sex syndicate http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1379697/police-arrest-elderly-pimps-hong-kong-hotel-sex-syndicate … 50s is considered elderly?    
    
    
    Tulou art for sale: landscapes and Xi Jinping http://instagram.com/p/iB02o1CTSo/     
    
    
    Fortune cookies! RT @hermanywong: An American Chinese takeout joint in China http://m.theglobeandmail.com/news/world/egg-rolls-fried-rice-chinese-food-returns-spiritual-home-much-changed/article15993490/?service=mobile …    
    
    
    Huge court win for new immigrants to HK. No more 7-yr requirement for social assistance http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1384616/i-won-welfare-stigma-puts-me …    
    
    
    Unless you're Paulo Coelho, "writing is seen as about as useful and profitable as whale-snot collecting" http://nyti.ms/1cKTHXT  #brazil    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 I knew we were in the wrong industry    
    
    
    Got herbal tea? @ Mong Kok Market 旺角街市 http://instagram.com/p/iDuJNwCTVn/     
    
    
    China reports first human case of #H10N8 avian flu. But H10 is not new http://www.cidrap.umn.edu/news-perspective/2013/12/china-reports-first-human-case-h10n8-avian-flu …    
    
    
    North Korea's Dennis Rodman problem: Hermit Kingdom has become a punch line http://on.wsj.com/JCfWEk     
    
    
    Obama's half brother launches book in Guangzhou. It alleges factual errors in 'Dreams From My Father' http://bigstory.ap.org/article/ap-interview-obamas-brother-writes-about-abuse …    
    
    
    China about to overtake Dominican Republic as source for immigrants in New York http://nyti.ms/1jiO34u     
    
    
    Why Max Baucus is a strange choice for U.S. ambassador to China http://wapo.st/J6oinb     
    
    
    Odd Christmas tradition in Japan: KFC http://thediplomat.com/2013/12/a-kentucky-fried-christmas-in-japan/ …    
    
    
    Chinese forger surprised to find himself in middle of $80 million art fraud case in New York http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2013-12-19/the-other-side-of-an-80-million-art-fraud-a-master-forger-speaks …    
    
    
    Why you see Upworthy-style headlines everywhere. Blame Facebook http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2013/12/why-are-upworthy-headlines-suddenly-everywhere/282048/ …    
    
    
    #Indonesia RT @dailydot: Copywriter tweets about working 30 straight hours, dies shortly after: http://bit.ly/1jfSrkS     
    
    
    Rodman's basketball diplomacy traces back to an Irish betting company and the pope http://nyti.ms/1jmOOJZ     
    
    
    @kellyfincham It's got many disparate angles!    
    
    
    Carp released in religious act, then caught by fishermen downstream in China http://nyti.ms/1jnS1Jf     
    
    
    How to say: Please reboot the server MT @shanghaiist: Chinese web jargon explained http://fb.me/1KBVDdmG4     
    
    
    So sorry.. Average British person says “sorry” eight times a day http://nyti.ms/1cFKXC5     
    
    
    But what happened to person under the train? RT @mtrupdate: 1403 Person under the train at East Rail Line has just resolved. Major delay    
    
    
    Japanese dumpling king shot dead in front of company this week http://nyti.ms/1fr3diC     
    
    
    Mozart effect still not true, say Harvard researchers http://news.harvard.edu/gazette/story/2013/12/muting-the-mozart-effect/ …    
    
    
    China still won't see salmon for a while. China vents anger over Dalai Lama's planned Norway visit http://reut.rs/1cVR4m1     
    
    
    Takes at least 4 men, naturally RT @mpspavor: Mounting a horse. #Rodman #paddypower #dprk pic.twitter.com/FO1hQa1C1n    
    
    
    With neat slideshow of a long career MT @jflorcruzCNN: Western journalists' China visa dramas http://www.cnn.com/2013/12/21/world/asia/china-journalists-jaime-florcruz/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Why your name matters and debunking the implicit-egotism theory http://flip.it/yXQJE     
    
    
    Guy traded 10,000 Bitcoins for two pizzas - in 2010, when worth 0.003 cents http://nyti.ms/1coEGfP  #noregrets    
    
    
    Where the U.S. government gets its clothes: not always conflict-free http://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2013/12/23/world/where-the-government-gets-its-clothes.html …    
    
    
    @blummer102 Netizens think Alhambra is in L.A.? Not true!    
    
    
    Pays to live on top floors. Most of Kowloon will be gone MT @SCMP_News: How melting ice will change HK's shores http://www.scmp.com/infographics/article/1388959/under-sea-how-shrinking-ice-will-change-hong-kongs-shorelines?fb_action_ids=10201746772404109 …    
    
    
    @KristieHang Um, I'm from Jackson, Mississippi?    
    
    
    @trey_menefee @leoaw I wouldn't mind seeing Wan Chai underwater    
    
    
    @LeoAW @trey_menefee #Atlantis    
    
    
    @blummer102 Yeah, LA County, but they aren't LA police    
    
    
    Are you qualified to be a journalist in China? Take the test http://nyti.ms/JUfRw3     
    
    
    The FBI considered “It’s a Wonderful Life” to be Communist propaganda http://qz.com/160999     
    
    
    Down the Instagram rabbit hole http://nyti.ms/1dyI2y1  Around the world ... and back to, surprise, Brooklyn    
    
    
    Canadian teachers' group calls on colleges to sever ties with Chinese Confucius Institutes http://www.caut.ca/news/2013/12/17/universities-and-colleges-urged-to-end-ties-with-confucius-institutes …    
    
    
    Myanmar maids prepare for work in Hong Kong, learning English and Chinese http://www.irrawaddy.org/burma/burmese-maids-prepare-work-hong-kong.html#.UrqL1tf1fWw.twitter …    
    
    
    Five Filipino siblings orphaned by typhoon refused to be separated  http://nyti.ms/K2cG5B  A glimpse at post-trauma adoption policies    
    
    
    I'm enjoying bothering WeChat friends with Christmas greetings just to see it snow trees! pic.twitter.com/PphqzrLBEr    
    
    
    Smugglers' tunnel led from Shenzhen garage, outfitted with rail track and wagon -AFP http://www.news.net/article/745048/?sid=3640oscfv4b33nt90dvgf02ah4 …    
    
    
    E-books tracking reader habits: People read only a chapter in yoga books http://nyti.ms/K1FjQo     
    
    
    The Disneyfication of Tibet http://www.washingtonmonthly.com/magazine/january_february_2014/ten_miles_square/the_disneyfication_of_tibet048349.php …    
    
    
    In downtown L.A., where cars rule the roads, growing number of pedestrians are kept in line http://nyti.ms/K4Hbb9     
    
    
    @_sofiamt Touché    
    
    
    Hong Kong reports first H7N9 death, 80-yr-old man from Shenzhen http://bit.ly/1brBUk7  #birdflu    
    
    
    'Fewer kids, more pigs' should be everyone's mantra MT @JournoDannyAsia: BBC News - 11 slogans that changed China http://bit.ly/1brCsX3     
    
    
    What I want to do when I grow up: Carve and sell tiny table sets in Beijing http://bit.ly/1brDuCh     
    
    
    Badass HK govt during Snowden saga is one of Time Out's top heroes in 2013 http://www.timeout.com.hk/big-smog/features/62694/hks-top-10-heroes-and-villains-2013.html#.Urwa39s0Mq8.twitter …    
    
    
    Put your burnt-out Christmas lights in the recycling bin. They're headed to China http://ti.me/1c7VGB5     
    
    
    How to spot a fake HK$1,000 banknote http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1390530/alert-after-more-fake-hk1000-notes-seized …    
    
    
    Windfall of Chinese investments - in Toledo, Ohio http://nyti.ms/1hHd2KN  Govt pitched city's feng shui    
    
    
    Li Ka-shing's investment in BitPay a smooth move, according to economist http://bit.ly/19OOLAw     
    
    
    The year we broke the Internet: "Readers are gullible, the media is feckless, garbage is circulated around" http://www.esquire.com/blogs/news/we-broke-the-internet?src=soc_twtr …    
    
    
    Living longer than your only child. That's tough and means growing old with little financial support in China http://reut.rs/1dcmGE3     
    
    
    For FT, @mohsin_hamid goes sci-fi  http://on.ft.com/1ad6bDx     
    
    
    James Franco in column defends selfies as the new way "to look someone right in the eye"  http://nyti.ms/1jMuody     
    
    
    Sherlock Holmes is in the public domain, American judge rules http://nyti.ms/1jPz1nh     
    
    
    @VPearson_TMT @kerryamonaghan @MindBodyGreen Wonder if that huge pic of Dalai Lama might be misleading. He is not a vegetarian    
    
    
    OMG .@AP: In unexpected move, Chinese President Xi drops in at a traditional Beijing bun shop for lunch: http://apne.ws/1cwk1Fp     
    
    
    Tycoon gives away his entire $800 million fortune before jumping to death http://www.independent.co.uk/news/people/news/tycoon-robert-wilson-gives-away-800million-fortune-before-plunging-to-death-in-suicide-9027278.html …    
    
    
    China corruption crackdown expands with vote-buying scandal. The real news: there are elections? http://on.ft.com/Kd7pc1     
    
    
    Secret slums: Ramshackle rooftop villages of Hong Kong | Urbanist http://weburbanist.com/2013/12/28/secret-slums-ramshackle-rooftop-villages-of-hong-kong/ …    
    
    
    Protesters carrying colonial flag trespass onto PLA's #HK headquarters http://bit.ly/JBghXR     
    
    
    Questlove goes to Japan... and brings tired-ass Asian jokes. But also posts contrite apology http://blog.angryasianman.com/2013/12/questlove-goes-to-japan-and-brings.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    When a web server has an existential crisis MT @nxthompson  the best "404 File Not Found" page ever. http://bit.ly/1ejbSCF     
    
    
    The American who gave his life to Chairman Mao  http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/12/an-interview-with-chairman-maos-american-translator/282647/ …    
    
    
    How JPMorgan's Sons and Daughters hiring program took form http://nyti.ms/1kUinRv     
    
    
    "terrorists" RT @XHNews: Eight terrorists were killed, and one was captured by police in a terrorist attack in Xinjiang    
    
    
    Left without family after Brooklyn stabbings, father returns to Fuzhou. After all that hard work http://nyti.ms/1cgtJHb     
    
    
    Usually a city pays its mayor; Michael Bloomberg paid to be the mayor. At least $650 million http://nyti.ms/1jYqE8Y     
    
    
    Ultimate junket MT @mgerrydoyle: are you a journo? want a free trip to a place everyone wants but no one wants to be http://bit.ly/1dOjFYG     
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Like buying your own island? http://bzfd.it/1eJOly5     
    
    
    Murky indeed. Japan's homeless recruited for murky Fukushima clean-up http://reut.rs/1hOGRZN     
    
    
    Every terrorist attack in Russia since 1991 mapped http://gu.com/p/3yfn5/tw     
    
    
    The decline of Wikipedia: it's failing to replenish supply of editors http://techre.vu/1badpJw     
    
    
    Jackie Chan drew more page views on http://SCMP.com  than Edward Snowden. Well. http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1393138/scmpcoms-top-10-most-popular-hong-kong-stories-2013 …    
    
    
    @bencsin #hkproblems    
    
    
    Divining China's direction by what Xi ate: translucent filling of fatty pork signifies transparency http://nyti.ms/1ciCPDm     
    
    
    Concert held in HK on Monday to commemorate the 10th death anniversary of Canto–pop diva Anita Mui. pic.twitter.com/DCeiKAgmvt via @cctvnews    
    
    
    What's in a name of a Chinese restaurant in the US? #GoldenDragonKing #datagraphic http://www.chinatownies.com/?p=11     
    
    
    Loan sharks smell blood in China waters http://on.wsj.com/1eky6Eo     
    
    
    Hot Chicks coming soon in North Point pic.twitter.com/enm5ye0ZeH    
    
    
    In Bangladesh, water is everywhere. So why can't children learn to swim? http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/12/where-swimming-is-a-vaccine/282726/ …    
    
    
    Meatball the Californian garbage-eating black bear has his own hedcut http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304753504579282532175239014 … pic.twitter.com/g60QU5prth    
    
    
    Looks comfy MT @ProfChrisTurney: A day in life of AAE on the Shokalskiy http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4RSKyGPZFXA&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    "TED actually stands for: middlebrow megachurch infotainment" http://gu.com/p/3yfvc/tw     
    
    
    If we are what we eat, then a final meal would seem to be the ultimate self-expression http://www.laphamsquarterly.org/essays/last-meals.php?page=all …    
    
    
    American Apparel ads seem so at home yet discordant to its LA surroundings. Thoughtful photo series: http://nyti.ms/1l9kfmG     
    
    
    On her left-behind child: “I want so much to teach her the real meaning of a mother." http://wapo.st/1eRi0qE     
    
    
    IKEA Heights: soap opera filmed entirely in an IKEA without its permission http://www.youtube.com/user/IKEAHeights … ht @digitalhen @ianpatterson99    
    
    
    Does a fiction writer need to visit China to write about it? http://nyti.ms/1jYlWYK     
    
    
    “If I can get this deal with The New York Times, I will be able to ... make the world a better place” http://nyti.ms/Kj3VnQ     
    
    
    Someone should bring laptops MT @larryau 1000+ elders in line to vote for @hkupop poll, over an hour wait #Jan1March http://bit.ly/1anu0sj     
    
    
    @larryau Oh good.. would be unfortunate if time ran out    
    
    
    Hong Kong #Jan1march peaks at 11,000. Last year it was 26,000 (police peak figures) http://bit.ly/1lzG3b6     
    
    
    Who says there's no art in HK MT @ErnestKao: Street banner showing all your favourite politicians in hell #Jan1March pic.twitter.com/TQ7HkoLMbU    
    
    
    Journalism's Surrender: Time Inc tears down separation btwn editorial and business http://wp.me/p33JF9-Tc1     
    
    
    U.S. to China: We hacked your Internet gear we told you not to hack http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/12/nsa-cisco-huawei-china/ … #ohtheirony    
    
    
        
    
    
    "If we remain silent, we will have no way to go but to let Beijing have full control of our fate" #HKUPOP http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1395349/voters-queue-hour-take-part-civil-referendum …    
    
    
    Song dynasty relics dug up in Kowloon City http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1395272/ancient-relics-dug-kowloon …    
    
    
    @MabelSieh Alas it's always been about money    
    
    
    Yau Leung called the Chinese Cartier-Bresson. His best known work:  http://blogs.telegraph.co.uk/culture/timwong/100072543/yau-leung-was-the-chinese-cartier-bresson-why-isnt-he-better-known/ … #HK pic.twitter.com/o4MIdLotdZ    
    
    
    And had to write about it MT @gerrymullany: @NickKristof changes byline; calls middle initial 'a bit ostentatious'   http://nyti.ms/1dqfpAA     
    
    
    My New Year's resolution: "Fly to the Diaoyu islands and be a Chinese with an attitude" http://www.scmp.com/news/asia/article/1395717/chinese-balloonist-rescued-japan-after-failed-flight-disputed-islands … via @tinssoldier    
    
    
    I wonder what the fox would say MT @JulieMakLAT: Walmart recalls donkey meat in #china b/c it was really fox meat http://lati.ms/scuBF     
    
    
    "[SNL] is not going to be controversial here - unless... they make a joke about China" Sohu CEO http://j.mp/19CqZtE     
    
    
    Attacker sets fire to Chinese Consulate in San Francisco http://nyti.ms/1dqG7ZQ     
    
    
    No one will shake President Hollande's hand http://bit.ly/19MXUcH  pic.twitter.com/vCQQQ1IHSn    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Awkward.    
    
    
    Ow RT @PaulCarsten: @SCMP_News say Wahaha chairman Zong Qinghou was injured in attack last Friday. Tendons in arm cut apparently.    
    
    
    Tendons in hand of China’s former richest man severed in attack. But he's said to be back in office today http://www.scmp.com/news/china-insider/article/1312187/chinas-former-richest-man-zong-qinghou-injured-knife-attack …    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle @digitalhen Very true. The air is better here! Wish I had a desk tho    
    
    
    @digitalhen Yup. It's weird.    
    
    
    Does being happy help you earn more? Yes, says economist http://gu.com/p/3tp8d/tw  Not the other way around?    
    
    
    Why Reuters Ditched Its Big Web Push. One word: money http://www.buzzfeed.com/matthewzeitlin/why-reuters-ditched-its-big-web-push …    
    
    
    Bo Xilai jail letter to family: my name will be cleared one day https://www.scmp.com/news/china/article/1312577/bo-xilai-jail-letter-my-name-will-be-cleared-one-day …    
    
    
    The Hoi Tin Tong tiff: How much turtle goes in turtle jelly? https://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1312232/power-turtle-jelly-lies-its-recipe-hoi-tin-tong-founder …    
    
    
    +1 Good resource RT @raykwong: Neato. Interactive guide to China's maritime disputes. http://on.cfr.org/18buEJm  HT @CFR_Comm    
    
    
    @hofrench @raykwong delete the extra l at the end of URL. That worked for me    
    
    
    @MeOldChina64 You make Hong Kong proud    
    
    
    Damn RT @yurikageyama: In case you didn't know it, we missed Cheeseburger Day yesterday Sept. 18.    
    
    
    Hong Kong couple get 3+ yrs of jail for torturing maid who was 'forced to wear diaper' http://reut.rs/187Uako  via @GraceL129    
    
    
    Under NYT Sports: Former Women’s Chess Champion, a Chinese Grandmaster, Close to Regaining Title http://nyti.ms/15E1jc7     
    
    
    Batten down the hatches RT @pstebbings: Severe Typhoon #Usagi on course to make a direct hit on #HongKong on Sunday http://bit.ly/17LbcnA     
    
    
    My heart is breaking RT @WantChinaTimes: Faye Wong divorce post used as poetic rejoinder to Bo Xilai http://bit.ly/18cTkRC     
    
    
    Hong Kong-Listed Company Wison Shares Details of China Corruption Investigation http://nyti.ms/15EDQY8     
    
    
    Hong Kong Riddled With British Spies, Reports Say (Riddled!) http://on.wsj.com/1693uXB     
    
    
    Instagram seems to think I have an iPhone 5. I don't. #ios7glitch pic.twitter.com/o2G0obk0NT    
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne I knew it. That explains everything.    
    
    
    Sammy's Kitchen legacy burns as bright as its neon cow http://bit.ly/1aN6C9O  How's the actual food @DougMeigs?    
    
    
    @DougMeigs Thanks! Have yet to walk in despite passing it many times    
    
    
    In Khartoum, worry that collapse of book culture is a direct mirror of country’s decline http://nyti.ms/15BaF8p     
    
    
    Bizarre threesome. Donald Tsang wanted to meet pope but was asked to help Berlusconi on fraud case, says ex-senator http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1313365/donald-tsang-pope-and-berlusconi-aide …    
    
    
    @ongreno Unagi! http://bit.ly/2B4LJN     
    
    
    How much it costs to make a hoodie: $31.40 in Asia versus $38.10 in the US http://nyti.ms/1duLF4k     
    
    
    @ongreno @bencsin It's all about Ranch 99    
    
    
    Brad Pitt, Angelina Jolie and 'super typhoon' Usagi are all set to converge on Hong Kong at once http://ti.me/1eu8IiO     
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Brad Pitt must be so jealous    
    
    
    Yao Ming - the face of FT Magazine's China edition http://on.ft.com/hPWiSS     
    
    
    Hacking U.S. Secrets, China Pushes for Drones http://nyti.ms/15JiOYt     
    
    
    Hundreds stranded at Hong Kong airport by Typhoon #Usagi http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1315258/hundreds-stranded-hong-kong-international-airport-typhoon-usagi …    
    
    
    #Usagi RT @ObservatoryHK: Signal No. 8 is expected to be issued at or before 7:00 p.m. today (22 Sep 2013).
http://bit.ly/1f6lPbc     
    
    
    Unbelievable MT @typhoonfury: These domestic helpers said not allowed home until 9pm, 2hrs after T8 issued #Usagi pic.twitter.com/6SU4Hw2A6w    
    
    
    @henrykhh Where is this photo?    
    
    
    @henrykhh Thanks! That does look crazy @roygrubb    
    
    
    @TylerRidings @typhoonfury Or it's not as simple as that.    
    
    
    Kale - or 'curly headless cabbage' - mystifies France http://nyti.ms/18iFQ72     
    
    
    Hong Kong Airlines sorry but offers no compensation after Rene Izquierdo's rare guitar damaged http://bit.ly/18PWPeY     
    
    
    MT @Badcanto: Chinese media: #HK is going to cancel the export restriction of infant formula on Oct 1st http://bit.ly/18PXI77     
    
    
    @digitalhen @Badcanto I see another protest coming...    
    
    
    The villagers don't sound so humble RT @jonah_kessel: Humble Chinese Village Basks in Legacy of Three Kingdoms Era http://bit.ly/16TkLl0     
    
    
    Open internet in Shanghai free-trade zone includes access to Facebook, Twitter, NYT site http://www.scmp.com/news/china-insider/article/1316598/exclusive-china-lift-ban-facebook-only-within-shanghai-free-trade …    
    
    
    Robots may revolutionize China's electronics manufacturing as more youth unwilling to do manual labor http://on.wsj.com/1fdLr5Z     
    
    
    "Egypt in some ways is a more civil society than China": Peter Hessler http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/worldviews/wp/2013/09/23/in-china-its-never-like-this-an-interview-with-peter-hessler/ …    
    
    
    Twitter posts job for head of media partnerships for Greater China MT @NiuB: Twitter sets sights on HK and Taiwan http://bit.ly/18mQcTf     
    
    
    The Most Controversial Dictionary Ever Published: Webster's Third http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/09/23/the_story_of_ain_t_david_skinner_s_book_about_america_its_language_and_the.html …    
    
    
    Satisfry. Nice. RT @GuardianUS: Burger King aims to satisfry with new low-calorie french fries http://bit.ly/14De59Q     
    
    
    US consul will continue to speak out on universal suffrage for Hong Kong http://blogs.wsj.com/chinarealtime/2013/09/24/consul-u-s-will-continue-to-speak-out-for-democracy-in-hong-kong/ …    
    
    
    Ashley Madison, the Website for Cheaters, Lands in Hong Kong http://zite.to/18n45CV  HK 'extremely popular hub'    
    
    
    This map shows where you are most likely to die from air pollution  http://www.businessinsider.com/world-map-of-air-pollution-2013-9 …    
    
    
    "If you build it, they will come" - Hollywood stars at Wanda's Qingdao film complex kickoff http://www.jingdaily.com/dalian-wanda-ceo-china-to-be-center-of-the-global-film-industry/36445/ …    
    
    
    David Webb: What Alibaba Wants From Its IPO And What It Will Likely Get  http://onforb.es/1gWB16e     
    
    
    Fonterra's plan for China-only Anmum brand moves 'full steam ahead' http://reut.rs/19CLXCh     
    
    
    @StarrWulfe oh, Hong Kong    
    
    
    Beautiful, but so much criticism of Calatrava projects http://nyti.ms/1fjPWvV     
    
    
    @Rydaine Beyond me why fake Versailles didn't succeed. Fake Hollywood will buck the trend!    
    
    
    Why We Hate Infographics (And Why You Should) http://insights.qunb.com/why-we-hate-infographics-and-why-you-should …    
    
    
    Anthony Lawrence, legendary BBC journalist, dies aged 101 in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1317747/anthony-lawrence-legendary-bbc-journalist-dies-aged-101-hong-kong …    
    
    
    40 percent of Hongkongers suffer from some degree of insomnia  http://www.timeout.com.hk/big-smog/features/61204/the-city-that-cant-sleep.html#.UkQK5cK5QJk.twitter … via @timeouthk    
    
    
    @joannachiu I bet @ErnestKao knows    
    
    
    Seymour Hersh on 'pathetic' US media. 'Get rid of 90% of editors and start promoting editors you can't control' http://gu.com/p/3j5vd/tw     
    
    
    A Cubicle to Call Home http://nyti.ms/18vrhNx  Photos: “Anywhere with air-conditioners will do" for Mr. Cheng who roams Mong Kok to pass time    
    
    
    Hong Kong sets an official poverty line today http://bit.ly/15AAd7l     
    
    
    Billshut jobs: No doubt we have all wondered what HR managers contribute to the world http://www.scmp.com/business/article/1311095/ask-yourself-morning-my-job-load-billshut … Another good one by Tom Holland    
    
    
    LOL RT @caligarn: These fucking idiots, @PhoRestaurant , are trying to trademark the word "Phở".    
    
    
    103-yr-old dines out every night, always orders fish. Spends US$100 on average (I guess I would too at 103) http://nyti.ms/1fvzNDR     
    
    
    Who Made Speed Dating? http://nyti.ms/16FDH2A  Answer: An Orthodox rabbi in Beverly Hills    
    
    
    For Chinese, Murakami is a window on the world http://ajw.asahi.com/article/behind_news/people/AJ201309290013 …    
    
    
    At the State Department, diversity can count against you. 'It's un-American' http://www.washingtonpost.com/blogs/wonkblog/wp/2013/09/24/at-the-state-department-diversity-can-count-against-you/ …    
    
    
    19.6% of Hongkongers under new poverty line  http://bit.ly/1651xsR  | That puts HK above US, Japan http://bit.ly/WzWWFS     
    
    
    Mainland Chinese woman sues Hong Kong middlemen over forged Guinea-Bissau passport http://bit.ly/16520v7     
    
    
    Lunch with the FT: Daniel Ek. Spotify founder holds meetings on High Line http://www.ft.com/cms/s/2/ca45f6b8-25bd-11e3-aee8-00144feab7de.html …    
    
    
    "Western publishers are the gatekeepers of what we read from China" - as it is for other "world literature" http://bit.ly/162Kub1     
    
    
    Run-ins with China's "feisty females" http://reut.rs/jd2Kpt     
    
    
    Reading: We Like You So Much and Want to Know You Better by Dave Eggers http://nyti.ms/1fzAtbc  via NYT Mag    
    
    
    Apple Passes Coca-Cola as Most Valuable Brand http://nyti.ms/16N0Wru     
    
    
    The Lost Slumgullions of English http://nyti.ms/15KT65O     
    
    
    Owner of Happy Printing Co in Tai Kok Tsui still prints with movable type. It's how he learned Chinese and Eng http://bit.ly/1fCDF5Z  #HK    
    
    
    How Dave Eggers gets Silicon Valley wrong http://reut.rs/19OB3KT     
    
    
    Multitasker! MTR probe over driver filmed clipping toenails on moving train http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1321208/mtr-probe-over-driver-filmed-clipping-toenails-moving-train …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Good point!    
    
    
    I.M. Pei's first project in Hong Kong faces wrecking ball http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1321585/causeway-bay-lose-urban-oasis-im-peis-sunning-plaza-faces-wrecking …    
    
    
    MT @_sofiamt: Employee at @NMAtv resigns with KAnye West interpretative dance http://bit.ly/14ZYjpM     
    
    
    Good lineup! MT @yurikageyama: Sign up for @AAJAAsia conference Oct. 18-20 in Tokyo and learn journalistic tricks 
http://bit.ly/19SlnF9     
    
    
    New tourist rules MT @stanyee Do not: "Eat a whole piece of bread in one mouthful" Do: "Use shower curtains in hotel" http://bit.ly/1eYNxFG     
    
    
    There's, like, dirt on the ground MT @MabelSieh There's Prob a Good Reason Why Bieber was Carried on the Great Wall 
http://bit.ly/17rlgDg     
    
    
    He saved the government $1 billion. And then he was furloughed. http://wapo.st/16iOzId     
    
    
    LA's Grand Central Market going upscale hipster? Hope not  http://touch.latimes.com/#section/-1/article/p2p-77629441/ … HT @kenbensinger    
    
    
    A woman?! #sexistovertones RT @noruweijin: China’s Poisoned Air Prompts Woman to Devise Green Tax http://j.mp/GA0Aiz     
    
    
    Can't decide if Ross Ulbricht, of the ‘http://Amazon.com  of drugs,’ is a super genius or not http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2013/10/ross-ulbricht-charged-with-running-silk-road.html …    
    
    
    Did Google doodle for National Day carry a hidden message? http://shanghaiist.com/2013/10/03/netizens_grasp_at_straws_with_google_national_day_tiananmen_doodle.php …    
    
    
    U.S. shutdown has already produced at least one winner: China http://nyti.ms/18Qi4Bk     
    
    
    McDonald's treated like sex offenders: Australian town protests branch cuz too close to nursery and school http://bbc.in/1fKg03u     
    
    
    @ulysseas That is probably true. So much for the "Asia pivot"    
    
    
    An addendum to HK ivory seige MT @BBCWorld: Poisoning of 80 elephants in Zimbabwe "affects whole world" http://bit.ly/16I11Ue     
    
    
    More Chow Tai Fook stores than KFCs in Hong Kong  http://on.wsj.com/16JeTh1  #interactive via @digitalhen    
    
    
    JMSC director @yingworld concerned potential HKU pick  has little knowledge of HK or China http://bit.ly/16JfBdY     
    
    
    Link to professor's views on HKU vice-chancellor pick (in Chinese) http://bit.ly/16JfQ8Q     
    
    
    I Know How You're Feeling, I Read Chekhov: Reading literary fiction improves empathy, EQ http://nyti.ms/18TqyYw     
    
    
    Downtown L.A. to hold first Sriracha festival http://www.latimes.com/food/dailydish/la-dd-first-sriracha-festival-20131002,0,6822764.story …    
    
    
    Adobe announces security breach. Hackers had access to credit card info of 2.9m customers http://nyti.ms/174IURI     
    
    
    Hongkongers can travel to 152 countries visa free, Chinese only 44 http://shanghaiist.com/2013/10/04/hong_kong_passport_allows_holders_to_travel_to_152_countries_visa_free.php … via @inbeijingse    
    
    
    North Point tour walking goes back to 1967 Hong Kong riots http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325476/north-point-tour-takes-participants-back-1967-hong-kong-riots …    
    
    
    Silk industry's demise in 1920s marked start of domestic helpers' rise in Hong Kong http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325419/silk-industrys-demise-marked-start-domestic-helpers-rise-hong-kong …    
    
    
    Germany's Sochi Olympics uniform "a cross between a pot-bellied pig and a parrot" http://spon.de/ad2ZI     
    
    
    The humble brag & more RT @nytimes: Cultural Studies: Twitter Bios and What They Really Say http://bit.ly/1f9QoMm     
    
    
    Henry M. Paulson believes major fiscal reform imminent in China http://nyti.ms/18ZrOcw     
    
    
    HKJA condemns barring of HK reporters at APEC http://bit.ly/1bBveWN     
    
    
    Slow news day eh? MT @Badcanto: Apple Daily headline: White Woman Works as Dishwasher in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/1bBvKEl     
    
    
    New HKU head Peter Matheison has his work cut out for him http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1325905/new-hku-head-ready-move-forward …    
    
    
    Now in color: Federal Reserve to Unveil a Redesigned US$100 Bill http://nyti.ms/17ayiSe     
    
    
    Great photo of Victoria Harbour race (via SCMP) pic.twitter.com/Y3YwrCUEP0    
    
    
    @mgerrydoyle Yeah must've been early. There was definitely a lot less hype about the event this year    
    
    
    @JRush_Asia Asian Gandalf    
    
    
    Obama’s Absence Leaves China as Dominant Force at #APEC http://nyti.ms/17bieQ7     
    
    
    Those giant monitors are comical MT @Helene_FR: Fox News and its weird new newsroom http://bit.ly/17Q3olx     
    
    
    Why not "muffnut"? Who names these things? RT @bibekbhandari: After "cronut," now there's this thing called "duffin" http://bit.ly/GEwwSy     
    
    
    Iron Man ride in HK to be Disney's first based on Marvel since it bought the comic book company in 2009 http://nyti.ms/15SwLFs     
    
    
    “A Short History of the Highrise” Very neat project using NYT archives and photos from readers worldwide http://nyti.ms/19bbOnR     
    
    
    HK journo group protests eviction over Aquino heckling http://bit.ly/1hyKL71  http://bit.ly/1hyKMb4  Pic at consulate via @STForeignDesk    
    
    
    The existential angst of Hong Kong's 'monster parents' - they're not all at fault http://huff.to/1bQUqVX     
    
    
    MT @wikileaks: WIKILEAKS RELEASE #HongKong: 21,166 emails from US intelligence contractor #Stratfor http://bit.ly/15XZCmz  #gifiles    
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Yeah, the next few links WikiLeaks tweeted looked more like emails    
    
    
    A treatise on role of culture and creativity in a city. Writer also points out Hong Kong devoid of both http://creativetimereports.org/2013/10/07/david-byrne-will-work-for-inspiration/ …    
    
    
    Plan to build Angkor Wat-like temple unhinged by scandal and monk's sex tape http://flip.it/KaTyC  via @bostonmagazine    
    
    
    Coastal Syria sounds beautiful - this funeral scene there is also poignant http://nyti.ms/17kCaiw     
    
    
    Hitler's guide to dating: First question girls should ask "What is your racial background?" http://nyti.ms/19fTl9L     
    
    
    WSJ wrote about urban biking trend in Bangkok not too long ago. Now it's Hanoi http://on.wsj.com/GKAU2L  Tour de SE Asia?    
    
    
    A trial more important than Bo Xilai's http://nyti.ms/17kv1yX     
    
    
    To apologize or not? Aquino suggests it's a cultural issue http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1327109/hong-kong-manila-hold-talks-bus-hostage-crisis … #manilahostagedrama #hk    
    
    
    Cliff hanger! encourage them to do what? MT @W7VOA: I kid you not, @ASEAN has just issued this news release http://bit.ly/15UFTcE     
    
    
    @ongreno My biggest takeaway: Malcolm Gladwell was on the cover of Costco Connection?    
    
    
    Thom Yorke calls Spotify 'the last desperate fart of a dying corpse' http://gu.com/p/3jb7t/tw     
    
    
    Pokfulam village is first HK site on world 'risk list'
http://bit.ly/18Oy6Ll   via @rthk_enews    
    
    
    Is it up, up and away for ‘Superman’ Li Ka-shing? http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1328061/it-and-away-superman-li-ka-shing …    
    
    
    In China, Nothing Says 'I Love You' Like Matching Shirts http://on.wsj.com/16Ss13r  "We want everyone to envy us." I don't know, man    
    
    
    How a sausage giveaway started a war between instant-noodle kings in China http://reut.rs/1fjUvFz     
    
    
    Blame the decline of campy Hong Kong horror films on mainland censors http://bit.ly/16Tz1gr     
    
    
    Robert Kuok is "twin-rooted" in Malaysia and China. Fate of his empire unknown http://bit.ly/16TAIub     
    
    
    Assembling PS4s was a graduation requirement for Foxconn "interns": FT http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/88524304-319f-11e3-817c-00144feab7de.html …    
    
    
    NYT just launched its T Magazine in Chinese http://bit.ly/1ecpRuJ     
    
    
    Japan’s ‘Kill Bill’ Restaurant Opens in Hong Kong http://on.wsj.com/GHIVW2     
    
    
    Photo wins Urban Photo of the Year award  http://bit.ly/19EUwlf  via SCMP #HK pic.twitter.com/OWIwGliTwR    
    
    
    Spinning tragedy: The true cost of a T-shirt http://fw.to/KDp5UiJ  #china #hk #cambodia #canada    
    
    
    Those Laptops That Snowden Took To Hong Kong And Russia Actually Have Nothing On Them http://zite.to/16DFhqb     
    
    
    Oops. Haruki Murakami Wins The Nobel Prize For Literature!….in Japan. For a few minutes. http://zite.to/17wY0Q6     
    
    
    Who Made That Android Logo? http://nyti.ms/15YYDrA     
    
    
    A nice little interactive of Herald Tribune front pages in this retrospective http://nyti.ms/1cMiqN5  pic.twitter.com/8ZgFHaGpyq    
    
    
    Old IHT gem: Dying reporter's message "Please ring up my paper and tell them there is a big story here" http://nyti.ms/1cMjwIx     
    
    
    Extra corpses needed for University of Hong Kong's medical school http://bit.ly/1eksV88  Anyone? Anyone?    
    
    
    @alicemuwu Trendy cafes are not worth the rent increases. We got out just in time    
    
    
    BuzzFeed will use crowd-sourced translation for its French, Spanish and Portuguese sites http://on.wsj.com/16YIPpt     
    
    
    No cauliflower for the world's oldest runner, Fauja Singh, now retired http://gu.com/p/3jfav/tw     
    
    
    The science, and superstition, behind BuzzFeed listicle lengths http://nie.mn/16Bky6l     
    
    
    Um. Hong Kong TV Reporter Claims He Witnessed UFO http://zite.to/16ZMaVi     
    
    
    Could high-rise fish farms revive Hong Kong's fishing industry? http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/14/world/asia/hong-kong-fishing-trawler-ban/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Iceland: Where one in 10 people will publish a book http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-24399599 …    
    
    
    Why the 'Sit-able City' is the Next Big Idea http://fw.to/ESIX9hC     
    
    
    Beautifully written. The Russia Left Behind http://www.nytimes.com/newsgraphics/2013/10/13/russia/ …    
    
    
    INYT is not the newest Apple product http://bit.ly/1hSmuJk     
    
    
    The paywall for NYT site and apps is also down for a week. Hurrah! http://bit.ly/1hSnop6     
    
    
    Chocolate newspapers! Why didn't we think of this earlier? pic.twitter.com/IBPzrtZ5dH    
    
    
    Day One of Sinosphere: People's Daily's phallic building, and other interesting posts http://bit.ly/17EZZlq     
    
    
    Modern Subways Zip Below, but a City’s Trams, Slow and Sweaty, Plod On http://nyti.ms/166dYGO  #HK    
    
    
    Boris Johnson trumps George Osborne in China charm game http://on.ft.com/191xfqN     
    
    
    .@andrewjacobsNYT visits Beijing's first RV park. It's luxurious! (video) http://nyti.ms/1enotFM     
    
    
    Donated. Good luck! MT @baoyuan: Want to help survivors of human trafficking, women? Give to  http://bit.ly/19OzYa6  #NYCMarathon    
    
    
    Vietnamese American from OC's Little Saigon suspected of aiding Al Qaeda http://www.latimes.com/local/la-me-1012-terrorism-arrest-20131012,0,4995659.story … ht @comradewong    
    
    
    TTTT is just as bad RT @scottkmurphy: Hilarious...Tang Tang Tang Tang: Sir David Tang’s new boutique - http://bit.ly/1amCRK3     
    
    
    It takes IKEA half a decade to design a kitchen http://qz.com/135040  You fooled me into reading an earnings story @qz! Touché.    
    
    
    At 28, New Zealander Is Youngest To Receive Man Booker Prize http://nyti.ms/168viei     
    
    
    Aw. Originally called dancing bears RT @klustout: Germany's Haribo 'Gummy Bear King' dies age 90 http://bit.ly/1690B8D  #RIP    
    
    
    "Vague: The Power of Generalizations to Impress the Bored" via The Malcolm Gladwell Book Generator http://bit.ly/1aLeeZ3  ht @tinssoldier    
    
    
    Death in Hong Kong Fuels Feelings of Discrimination. "It's getting worse and worse" http://nyti.ms/1bwGjo6     
    
    
    Cha chaan tengs offer more coffee per cup than Starbucks http://bit.ly/1aLfpYs     
    
    
    @bibekbhandari yup    
    
    
    The Man Who Forgot Everything ie. the 'Memento' guy http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/books/2013/10/henry-gustav-molaison-the-man-who-forgot-everything.html?utm_source=www&utm_medium=tw&utm_campaign=20131015 …    
    
    
    African restaurants under the radar in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/16hbfoK     
    
    
    Classy rodents RT @zhongnanhai: 11 rats found in business class on a Hong Kong —> Xiamen flight http://bit.ly/1hY7nhq     
    
    
    Could it be? McDonald's appears to be losing customers http://on.wsj.com/1eoIw6M     
    
    
    This looks interesting. HK Literary Festival has 3 Indonesian migrant writers on panel discussion http://www.festival.org.hk/program/the-help-their-stories-panel-discussion/ …    
    
    
    Call for 'de-Americanized World' Provokes Alarm in U.S., Fart Jokes in China http://blog.foreignpolicy.com/posts/2013/10/16/chinese_reaction_editorial_xinhua_de_americanized_world#.Ul_-iSds0Cw.twitter …    
    
    
    On same day, NYT and Foreign Policy publish posts on China's tuhao nouveau riche http://bit.ly/GRFhZC  http://atfp.co/1cYRRnH     
    
    
    Lots of photos of Boris Johnson in a  helicopter over Hong Kong http://zite.to/1gncAnC  via Daily Mail    
    
    
    3 million living in modern slavery in China, No. 2 in world: Global Slavery Index (India is No. 1) http://www.globalslaveryindex.org/country/china/     
    
    
    What Happens When a Language Has No Numbers? http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/10/16/piraha_cognitive_anumeracy_in_a_language_without_numbers.html …    
    
    
    Snowden gave all his classified documents to journalists he met in Hong Kong, before flying to Moscow http://nyti.ms/1bDeqL6     
    
    
    Western Market is an example of mismanaged redevelopment http://www.scmp.com/property/hong-kong-china/article/1333306/hong-kongs-historical-districts-buildings-risk-profit …    
    
    
    Heels on a slippery boat deck is a great idea! Xinhua gallery of Chinese female navy soldiers http://bit.ly/16SG07c  via Sinocism    
    
    
    Michael Bay: Yes, the story being passed around is not all true! (But the A/C and metal carts were real) http://bit.ly/16SGOJ8     
    
    
    What a daredevil on horse and buggy on PCH MT @NathanUnbound: When L.A.'s most famous streets were dirt roads: http://bit.ly/1i0J9Dt     
    
    
    Former US ambassador to ADB thinks studying abroad can be a waste. Calls it "fancy" education http://www.nytimes.com/roomfordebate/2013/10/17/should-more-americans-study-abroad/studying-abroad-can-be-an-expensive-waste-of-time …    
    
    
    @StarrWulfe @AAJAAsia @AAJA @yurinagano @aekubo Y'all have fun!    
    
    
    India digs for treasure after Hindu holy man said a former king appeared to him in a dream http://bigstory.ap.org/article/india-digs-treasure-tip-hindu-holy-man …    
    
    
    Businessman with ties to HK and LA accused of being mob boss in China http://bigstory.ap.org/article/us-businessman-accused-being-mob-boss-china …    
    
    
    A Sri Lankan Journalist Eagerly Toes the Line http://nyti.ms/16hvqbw     
    
    
    Know your kale http://nyti.ms/19Yd1PT     
    
    
    @pcheung630 @AP_Interactive @njgriffiths Congrats!    
    
    
    Must see TV in China: "Chinese Characters Dictation Competition" http://on.wsj.com/H6CvQV  ht @clemtan    
    
    
    HK plans to ban adverts for baby sex-selection trips http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1335572/health-chiefs-plan-ban-adverts-overseas-baby-sex-selection-trips …    
    
    
    Hong Kong woman at centre of sex scandal involving Auckland mayor http://m.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1335579/hong-kong-woman-centre-sex-scandal-involving-auckland-mayor … Something doesn't add up here    
    
    
    #HKTV rally schedule today, via http://on.fb.me/1gugT0B  pic.twitter.com/0dThDaAGOj    
    
    
    Colorful #infographic of international movies with Hong Kong sets http://bit.ly/15TXsHB     
    
    
    @Steve_Dunthorne Your secret is safe. Absolutely no one saw your tweet.    
    
    
    Nothing says freedom like Tony Stark RT @jasonli: Iron Man stopped by the #wewantfreetv protest in Hong Kong. http://bit.ly/18yHFPi     
    
    
    Hong Kong cemeteries rejected a man's application based on race/religion http://bit.ly/1eD2ZEM  Good story @jj_ngo    
    
    
    NYT is working to make numbers-based stories clearer for readers http://nyti.ms/1bFZVpJ     
    
    
    Great photo series on @hongwrongblog following  maids in-training in Indonesia to HK homes. Didn't know they went thru that much    
    
    
    In South Korea, "it still shocks to see the leaders of huge public companies relying on fortune-tellers" http://nyti.ms/16lfAfS     
    
    
    "Dishonesty of headlining may seem a minor issue. It isn’t" says Tim Parks http://www.nybooks.com/blogs/nyrblog/2013/oct/17/headline-headaches/ …    
    
    
    Letter: Sun Yat-sen welcomes to Henry Ford to South China "where much of the intelligence, energy and wealth is" http://nyti.ms/17ZlJso     
    
    
    Ford tried to play catch up in Asia with taxi bid in Hong Kong http://nyti.ms/1a52RwY     
    
    
    Some things @LAScanner has learned about LA: Nothing good ever happens at a pay phone http://bit.ly/16rO630     
    
    
    Sinosphere: Is 'Superman' Li Ka-shing taking off from China and headed for – Europe? http://nyti.ms/1ab1L2K     
    
    
    Why Can Neil Patrick Harris Say That’s ‘Too Gay’ and Straights Can’t? On 'lavender linguistics' and hurtful slurs http://nyti.ms/16pPd8s     
    
    
    Outrage over 'white-skinned girl' college scholarship in Thailand http://t.bangkok.coconuts.co/2013/10/22/whites-only-european-owned-thai-co-offers-money-whitest-students …    
    
    
    Instagram Selfies and Hong Kong's Free TV Movement http://zite.to/1bb5lYX     
    
    
    Ack RT @stanyee: *cough* HK air pollution 'very high' at all 3 roadside stations, 157 in Central    
    
    
    Xi Jinping, watch out RT @ericfish85: Nanjing mayor was sacked for plagiarism: http://bit.ly/1cVtViH     
    
    
    A clamassacre?.. nice MT @C_Murderous: I survived! But barely. This vid is bananas.  #Halloween http://bit.ly/1cVDduX     
    
    
    @blummer102 He kind of asks for it    
    
    
    Who says The Times isn't with it? NYT stylebook moves into 21st century with "email" "website" "to tweet" http://www.theatlanticwire.com/national/2013/10/tweet-and-email-are-now-fit-print/70864/ …    
    
    
    @ChinaFile Link goes to "access denied" page for me    
    
    
    How to Say “Truthiness” in Chinese http://j.mp/1a1CmV4     
    
    
    "If you needed a new first name, what would it be?" Security question on health care website http://on.wsj.com/HgEvFv     
    
    
    @MabelSieh Didn't he also not know who Donald Tsang was? Maybe he is just bad with names    
    
    
    @MabelSieh Just don't bring up the touchy subject!    
    
    
    Answer depends on who you are RT @george_chen: Bloomberg Chinese cover story: Welcome to Hong Kong? I don't care! http://bit.ly/1fWO5MY     
    
    
    SCMP is hiring subs/copy editors/miracle workers http://bit.ly/17gD6eN     
    
    
    She may not know where North Korea is, but this old lady wants to know why China is giving it money http://nyti.ms/1eMvRdP     
    
    
    Btw @NYTSinosphere is not officially NYT or Sinosphere    
    
    
    Wear yellow and carry jade when you visit these haunted places in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/HgzYni     
    
    
    How to eat a cockroach. First, deep fry it twice http://fw.to/U22FQfT  via @MalcomMoore    
    
    
    The art of the corporate apology, Chinese edition http://qz.com/139029  via @qz    
    
    
    Google's autocomplete spells out our darkest thoughts http://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2013/oct/22/google-autocomplete-un-women-ad-discrimination-algorithms …    
    
    
    @ChinaFile Thanks!    
    
    
    8 Filipino troops keep China in check in the South China Sea  http://nyti.ms/H5osKV  #snowfallonsteroids    
    
    
    China downsizes English-language section in its national college exam http://on.ft.com/18igLHj     
    
    
    Choosing an English name is liberating for Chinese - names like Scort, Police Car and Inside It's Raining http://nyti.ms/1hdT8aY     
    
    
    What's this Tai Po minibus doing in ...  Zanzibar?? via @petespurrier pic.twitter.com/vlBn2CmVlc    
    
    
    @jgriffiths Funny they left the signs and ads on    
    
    
    How convenient. Now New Express and reporter confess and apologize for "false stories" http://bit.ly/1dyfHHs     
    
    
    North Korea has a crystal meth problem http://bit.ly/1dyi78R     
    
    
    Ousted professor Xia Yeliang: U.S. universities turn blind eye as they enter China http://on.wsj.com/1c5hKih     
    
    
    AP photographer's tour of Peru is beautiful and varied http://bo.st/17l7XXD     
    
    
    "Hong Kong is... dying" is the top result on Google auto-complete. Some results are very telling http://bit.ly/17nVkce     
    
    
    Browsing NYT's style changes: it's now lychee, not litchi; and sweatpants is one word. You're welcome.    
    
    
    @olivesophierose ... around the time when Radio and Film became passé    
    
    
    “No Woman, No Drive” Stuns Saudi Arabia, inspired by some Jamaican guy http://globalvoicesonline.org/2013/10/26/video-no-woman-no-drive-stuns-saudi-arabia/ … via @globalvoices    
    
    
    Fitting headline: One day in the life of Mikhail Khodorkovsky http://on.ft.com/H4Kopq     
    
    
    Cannibals are the new zombies in movie trends http://nyti.ms/1dx77II     
    
    
    Write for no payment? Don't do it. An essay on professional worth http://nyti.ms/H9hPau     
    
    
    Indonesia to ban masked monkey shows in capital http://bigstory.ap.org/article/indonesia-boots-masked-monkey-shows-capital …    
    
    
    Chinese Wikipedia Becomes Front Line for Views on Language and Culture http://nyti.ms/16FaDcI     
    
    
    Finally RT @zhongnanhai: Glasses that could translate a Chinese menu into English http://bit.ly/1dBzjdy     
    
    
    Pretty good. This Hong Konger's Kim Jong-un costume just won Halloween http://online.thatsmags.com/post/this-hong-kongers-kim-jong-un-costume-just-won-halloween#.Um34rh2vjQ0.twitter …    
    
    
    Butcher goes on envy-fueled massacre in Brooklyn. At least NYPost didn't call him a Chinese alien again http://bit.ly/1hml2l4     
    
    
    MT @william_fitz: Google now has an Asia Pacific blog covering Google and the Internet from .au to .in! http://bit.ly/1ajCPbj     
    
    
    Must read RT @nytopinion: A (mostly) civil argument between @nytkeller and @ggreenwald about the future of news: http://bit.ly/16DLdBD     
    
    
    After Crash In Beijing, Moves to Halt Flow of News  http://nyti.ms/17oDTdK     
    
    
    Love is a conveyor belt of warmth RT @DougMeigs: 44 Hong Kong Movie Subtitles Gone Wrong - via Buzzfeed: http://bit.ly/19OLtfg     
    
    
    California city sues hot sauce maker for fouling air with "spicy odor" http://www.latimes.com/local/lanow/la-me-ln-irwindale-sues-sriracha-20131028,0,2608897.story …    
    
    
    Always learning. Will have to brace myself for the first tip, but thanks @SubvCopyEd for the idea  http://bit.ly/HdrDAj     
    
    
    What are the hardest languages to learn #graphic http://voxy.com/blog/index.php/wide-infographics/what-are-the-hardest-languages-to-learn-infographic/ …    
    
    
    Britney Spears' music used by British navy to scare off Somali pirates http://gu.com/p/3kvc8/tw     
    
    
    Scientist Links Asia’s Yeti to Ancient Bear http://thediplomat.com/asia-life/2013/10/scientist-links-asias-abominable-snowman-to-ancient-bear/ …    
    
    
    Absurd article.  In essence: Chinese mistress culture runs deep so live with it http://www.atimes.com/atimes/China/CHIN-01-291013.html …    
    
    
    From China to Los Angeles, Taking the Electric Bus http://nyti.ms/HtIJJU     
    
    
    That guy is obviously an apparition MT @SCMP_News China's worst photoshopped propaganda photo? http://bit.ly/1gb1lxz  http://bit.ly/1gb1iSr     
    
    
    @jgriffiths Or she is just really really far away    
    
    
    No need to panic. Women just "can't decide which way to go when they drive." Thanks, Beijing police! http://nyti.ms/1gZ3nlV     
    
    
    Ultimate origami MT @newsmary: Fold-your-own paper torso with removable organs. http://bit.ly/16J30r0     
    
    
    @feng37 That would've been fun!    
    
    
    Merkel Balks at EU Privacy Push http://spon.de/ad4d2  #cognitivedissonance    
    
    
    Indian Communist politician ousted for sleeping in bed of cash http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-india-cash-bed-20131030,0,5066773.story …    
    
    
    This is getting ridiculous RT @beijingcream: NO. http://bit.ly/19d8nxt  HT @joshchin http://bit.ly/19d8qJs     
    
    
    Student calls an editor a "paper-work expert." I guess he's not entirely wrong.    
    
    
    'Tis the season (already) pic.twitter.com/1UDlDcmw5w    
    
    
    @_jlam no!    
    
    
    ! RT @zhongnanhai: You can now use electronic devices during takeoff and landing in the United States. #finally http://bit.ly/HxCAN0     
    
    
    Snowden starts new job at Russian Internet company on Friday http://nyti.ms/17Zicv7     
    
    
    Australian embassies are being secretly used to intercept phone calls and data across Asia for #NSA http://www.smh.com.au/federal-politics/political-news/exposed-australias-asia-spy-network-20131030-2whia.html …    
    
    
    Former Philippine president to apologize in person in Hong Kong http://nyti.ms/16OGSWY     
    
    
    Organizer hoping for ultramarathons in 4 "Da" cities  — Dalian, Dali, Datong and Daqing http://bit.ly/HxXDPn     
    
    
    Turkey Legalizes the Letters Q, W, and X http://www.slate.com/blogs/lexicon_valley/2013/10/24/turkey_prime_minister_erdogan_s_democratizaton_package_legalizes_letters.html …    
    
    
    Good story. Can rebranding help fish sauce be Vietnam's Champagne? http://www.theatlantic.com/international/archive/2013/11/can-fish-sauce-be-vietnams-champagne/281071/ …    
    
    
    In Praise of Art Forgeries http://nyti.ms/1hD0yod  "Forgers also remind us that great art depends on the ideas of artists"    
    
    
    Godard/Woody is my favorite RT @brainpicker: Paris vs. New York, in minimalist infographic parallels and contrasts http://bit.ly/17A5j08     
    
    
    Declining Asian populations in Chinatowns won't be good for new immigrants http://on.ft.com/1iB3tve     
    
    
    For all the changes in Hong Kong, this 1988 NYT profile of Mong Kok holds up well http://nyti.ms/1bOXmRI     
    
    
    China to end use of prisoners' organs for transplants in 2014 http://reut.rs/19lMr3h  Only country that allows it    
    
    
    Ha. New York Times corrects: Writer’s name is not ‘Chillian J. Yikes’ http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/mediawire/228215/new-york-times-corrects-reporters-name-is-not-chillian-j-yikes/#.UnYiZdC1tiU.twitter …    
    
    
    Villager fined for running hikers' hostel at his house in New Territories http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1346912/hong-kong-government-urged-allow-flexible-operation-hostels-hikers …    
    
    
    Good one, Google! http://on.mash.to/171n4zP  pic.twitter.com/n6kbtk5KYR    
    
    
    @blersing @george_chen And probably more respect too!    
    
    
    How China Profits From Our Junk - by the son and grandson of scrap metalists http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/11/how-china-profits-from-our-junk/281044/ …    
    
    
    Snacks and sweets face price sting from humble bee http://on.ft.com/184TWYv     
    
    
    Catchy way to remember the order of China's dynasties http://nyti.ms/1hJgvJv     
    
    
    Secrets of a Game Show Writer http://nyti.ms/1hJ56cL  What did they do before Google, though?    
    
    
    Chinese water bottler Nongfu Springs accuses Beijing newspaper of defamation http://reut.rs/HxtP66     
    
    
    #INYT MT @AAJAAsia: What it's like to work in HK as a US journalist via @mcknightkristin and @andybechtel http://bit.ly/1a4OtnR     
    
    
    Insane photos of a pirate execution in Kowloon City, 1891 http://disq.us/8fzspf  #HK    
    
    
    'Kafka' case: LA couple accused of starving adopted daughter to death in Qatar to give their side of story http://nyti.ms/1hIYJX0     
    
    
    Hong Kong's English-language skills slip in Asia ranking http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1348626/hong-kongs-english-language-skills-slip-says-ef-education-first …    
    
    
    Bloomberg News Is Said to Curb Articles That Might Anger China http://nyti.ms/1dTugTD     
    
    
    Finally, what we've all been thinking: Hong Kong's little bubble of self-importance http://bit.ly/18hXJli     
    
    
    16 Differences Between Living In Hong Kong And Taiwan - in comic form http://www.buzzfeed.com/kevintang/16-differences-between-living-in-hong-kong-and-taiwan …    
    
    
    Acquiesce. Acquiesce. Aquiesce. NMATV on Bloomberg News and China http://bit.ly/19aGQbW     
    
    
    Salt tip is a good one! RT @_jlam: Hong Kong Life Hacks by @hk_magazine http://bit.ly/19aHqGu     
    
    
    Fallows: the best possible PR campaign Chinese officials could undertake would be to let reporters roam freely http://www.theatlantic.com/china/archive/2013/11/this-latest-chinese-censorship-news-is-important-and-bad/281319/ …    
    
    
    "In fiction, as in life, characters don’t have to be likable to be lovable." Mohsin Hamid http://nyti.ms/19aJZs9     
    
    
    Scale of typhoon destruction in Philippines compared to 2004 Indian Ocean tsunami http://on.wsj.com/16Q0gWz     
    
    
    Alibaba's 11.11 shopping day in China is bigger than 'Black Friday' http://on.wsj.com/17Juaih     
    
    
    The Craigslist killers http://gu.com/p/3k6d9/tw  #longread    
    
    
    Here, For Some Reason, Is A Chinese Rap Video About Cleveland http://beijingcream.com/2013/11/here-for-some-reason-is-a-chinese-rap-video-about-cleveland/ …    
    
    
    Nice! MT @JeromeTaylor: My photos of Hong Kong's gay #pride march have been picked up by @hongwrongblog: http://bit.ly/18kGb85     
    
    
    Huffington Post to launch in Korean in early 2014 http://www.hani.co.kr/arti/english_edition/e_international/610659.html …    
    
    
    @clemtan Even cooler name: Batman bin Suparman    
    
    
    @clemtan Weird Singapore    
    
    
    More Hotels Are Saying Welcome in Mandarin http://nyti.ms/17jVJsA     
    
    
    Mapping the destruction in Tacloban http://nyti.ms/HQP4Au  pic.twitter.com/AMukgAEDT9    
    
    
    Be Terrified: Hong Kong's Banker Babies Are Learning Finance in Pre-K http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2013/11/be-terrified-hong-kongs-banker-babies-are-learning-finance-in-pre-k/281354/ …    
    
    
    Former Gov Chris Patten's regrets on Hong Kong http://on.wsj.com/1bsAM1x     
    
    
    @cjgraham82 Baby banker rejected my loan application! Noo....    
    
    
    Primer on the Third Plenum via Caixin http://bit.ly/HQWIe1     
    
    
    Freee could use a few more Es MT @1rick: My piece on strange Japanese startup names (http://bit.ly/1cPPu7N )    
    
    
    Amphitheater of the Dead: Hong Kong Hillside Cemeteries (photos) http://weburbanist.com/2013/11/08/amphitheater-of-the-dead-hong-kong-hillside-cemeteries/ …    
    
    
    Newsroom cuts have hit visual journalists harder than copy/layout editors since 2000 http://www.poynter.org/latest-news/mediawire/229302/visual-jobs-in-newsrooms-have-fallen-by-nearly-half-since-2000/#.UoG96Jd_CKc.twitter …    
    
    
    This changes everything RT @adamnajberg: We've been eating our apple a day all wrong http://bit.ly/19Zv48z     
    
    
    @tinssoldier The answer is, of course. From the bottom.    
    
    
    "Maybe Godot never appears because everyone is mispronouncing his name." http://nyti.ms/17jU06z     
    
    
    Awful. Bloody End for Iranian Rockers Seeking Musical Freedom in U.S. http://nyti.ms/19dnxP3     
    
    
    @lalarimando @MeOldChina64 I found the pronunciation key helpful.. for that inner broadcaster in me    
    
    
    Ariel Levy's “Thanksgiving in Mongolia” took me by surprise http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2013/11/18/131118fa_fact_levy?mbid=social_retweet …    
    
    
    3 journalists departing NYT for digital http://nyti.ms/1dmjVPb     
    
    
    Descendants of Confucius used to get special honors and titles http://www.scmp.com/lifestyle/technology/article/1354787/study-finds-single-bloodline-among-self-claimed-confucius …    
    
    
    Philippine domestic helpers in Hong Kong battle to contact loved ones. Collection boxes at Worldwide Plaza http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1354759/philippine-domestic-helpers-hong-kong-battle-contact-loved-ones …    
    
    
    Even Native Chinese Speakers Aren't Sure What The Government Said About Market Reform http://www.businessinsider.com/3rd-plenums-communique-on-the-market-2013-11 … #cpcdoublespeak    
    
    
    'I don't work for Bloomberg': Bloomberg on Bloomberg News allegations http://politicker.com/?p=72764  via @mattschiavenza    
    
    
    Wife of Calif governor puts up with his "tendency to muse philosophically on every bit of policy minutia" http://nyti.ms/1btpA6x     
    
    
    Super Small Gun Enthusiast, a Chinese picture book for kids http://bit.ly/1btnaES     
    
    
    Slate's econ correspondent loves Hong Kong's MTR. Who doesn't? http://www.slate.com/blogs/moneybox/2013/11/12/hong_kong_mtr_costs_great_transit_at_low_cost.html …    
    
    
    Double room at Beijing's storied hotel goes for $600. Not that you can book one, of course http://nyti.ms/1gIy1ih     
    
    
    @sarahefung @bencsin I wish I could unsee that conversation! Gravity ruined for me too now    
    
    
    Especially haunting via Tyler Hicks/NYT http://nyti.ms/HY4W3f  pic.twitter.com/32vQdgGmsB    
    
    
    George Clooney's Rules for Living: Don't talk smack unless you can play the game http://www.esquire.com/features/george-clooney-interview-1213 …    
    
    
    An exclusive interview with the Dalai Lama - FT http://www.ft.com/cms/s/2/d49d13aa-4749-11e3-b4d3-00144feabdc0.html …    
    
    
    @cjgraham82 it's Clooney! Who wouldn't?    
    
    
    Exclusive: Sriracha founder reveals the 'secret' wholesale price of his sauce http://www.marketplace.org/topics/business/numbers/exclusive-sriracha-founder-reveals-secret-wholesale-price-his-sauce#.UoOsK2wyDpc.twitter …    
    
    
    Should one pose questions on Twitter? RT @Garvey_B: Learned how to tweet today pic.twitter.com/GSGsHv1rs5    
    
    
    At Bloomberg, Special Code Keeps Some Articles Out of China http://nyti.ms/19kHq75     
    
    
    He's got a point MT @WSJ: "OK. You're a runner. Get over it." Chad Stafko writes about the problem with some runners http://bit.ly/1fCNpcY     
    
    
    Is it even fair to compare China to Nazi Germany? (in terms of reporting for foreign journalists) http://nyti.ms/18tv8tB  via Sinosphere    
    
    
    Abe commends Chinese student for saving Japanese boy http://nyti.ms/HZPP9h     
    
    
    Bizarre twist. British spy found dead in sports bag may have locked himself inside by accident http://nyti.ms/1gKwRmt     
    
    
    Did the New York Times Just Get Blocked in China -- Again? | FP Passport http://blog.foreignpolicy.com/posts/2013/11/13/did_the_new_york_times_just_get_blocked_in_china_again?wp_login_redirect=0#.UoVp0QH6ddM.twitter …    
    
    
    HK's Kim Jong-un impersonator was asked to shoot commercial with Dennis Rodman http://hongwrong.com/kim-jong-un-impersonator/ …    
    
    
    Was it principle or money? RT @NewYorker: Why Did Snapchat Turn Down Three Billion Dollars? http://bit.ly/1e6JDYI     
    
    
    Social media marketing done right MT @tinssoldier What started as a sassy tweet to a telecoms firm... http://www.buzzfeed.com/scottybryan/this-is-the-best-twitter-conversation-you-will … via @jenn1marsh    
    
    
    NYT's homepage featuring Wes Anderson's nice little short/ad pic.twitter.com/CxPuYmLVII    
    
    
    @tinssoldier You just took away a journalist's income    
    
    
    Amid New York Times departures, Jack Shafer says no journalist is irreplaceable http://reut.rs/1bAVNJh     
    
    
    Stop with the millennial trend stories (a rant in comics form) https://medium.com/the-nib/875d45297612 …    
    
    
    For Chess, a Would-Be White Knight: Bringing chess to the masses, with play-by-play commentary http://nyti.ms/1epHQOL     
    
    
    Identity checks by Hong Kong police beat NY and London. Claim no racial profiling http://www.scmp.com/news/hong-kong/article/1364087/police-tactics-queried-after-16m-spot-checks-last-year …    
    
    
    "Boxing’s not so well kept dirty secret is that, financially, most fighters can never stop" http://www.sbnation.com/longform/2013/11/20/5119180/manny-pacquiao-vs-brandon-rios-fight-2013-profile … #pacquiao    
    
    
    Why Lego thrives in China http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/currency/2013/11/lego-company-asian-toy-industry-sales-in-china.html …    
    
    
    How books about sport got serious http://on.ft.com/1bYoaBk  High vs low culture    
    
    
    OED's word of the year: selfie. Just glad it wasn't sharknado http://blog.oxforddictionaries.com/2013/11/an-infographic-of-selfie/ … #infographic    
    
    
    