    
    
    
    Scared of sleeping tonite... Scared to end today.... !    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fuck you all Fuck you!!!!    
    
    
    What its love? Its not the beauty of first attraction that have lasted, its not looks that makes look good for days. Then whats love?    
    
    
    100 pages to an artist's model. Celebration treat @Flamin icicle.    
    
    
    Waiting for husband to come home. IT sucking life and my crudling time :-(  Curse you proj manager    
    
    
    100th post on the blog. Hit it.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @NeilNMukesh :David was awesome, u were great undoubtedly. Hope u get the best in your movie carrier. don't wanna loose a good actor like u.    
    
    
    My Blog got a changed address, now find me writing @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.com . Keep Reading :)    
    
    
    Love technology... Power is ON...    
    
    
    I get this question quite often, "Why Cleora!!??"  Lets know why??  With New Profile Photo @ //flamin-icicle.blogspot.in/    
    
    
    Some time in life expression is powerful and impact capable than opportunity of making empty show off... Thanks to hypocrites.    
    
    
    leaving behind the lanes of broken trust, letting go of the darkness that hurt Fly high my soul fly higher, reach to the sun or burn in fire    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Flamin Icicle posted a song 
http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    mind wandering here & there, but had to force it near... end result I SUCK!! God help me here...    
    
    
    Now am Tweeting in blog too... Follow Me!! tweet.. tweet...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    New features @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.com/ ... Now you can share ME on Facebook and follow my tweets..    
    
    
    Join the club @ http://www.facebook.com/groups/103334186412597/ … Flamin' Icicle Facebook group    
    
    
        
    
    
    I added 5 important life event in facebook... connect me on http://facebook.com     
    
    
    Is it a heart beat or a broken heart, to love the one or hate someone li'l  care you share that's not for everyone.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @NeilNMukesh All the best... dear.    
    
    
    Suffocated of Live or Breathe to Die... check it out @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.in/2013/03/breathe-to-die.html …    
    
    
    Sometime expressions are lost beneath suppressed thought, catch a missed post @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.in/2013/03/i-shared-this-over-my-facebook-on-5th.html … in Lost Inspiration.    
    
    
    LCO Sayin' SO.... @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.in/     
    
    
    Argo a well deserving movie, more over an operation which makes you feel worthy of being alive.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Honesty  is a treasure, don't waste it brushing and polishing others shoes.  Character is a virtue, don't juggle it to entertain others ego.    
    
    
    Need to speed up my RC... I suck at this... guessing RC's my Achilles Heal :( Grrr!!    
    
    
    Oh! Mi Cleora.... @ http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.in/     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Vivekviswamg : If you are in, follow me too...    
    
    
    Its doesn't feel good when there is 0 followers... so my friend got to forcefully add me... I hope he can spare his lady Hitler!    
    
    
    Doesn't feel right to be alive.    
    
    
    A post devoted to sadness and motivation to move on, by Cleora.
http://tearsofbrokendreams.blogspot.com/2010/11/its-sad-how-loss-comes.html    
    
    
    Most frquently irritating used work phases I would add "proactive" to the list... Make it 31 http://linkd.in/186ya7i     
    
    
    Why Sequels Will Never Die:Hollywood's Summer of 'Flops' Was Actually Its Best Year Ever-Derek Thompson-The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2013/09/why-sequels-will-never-die-hollywoods-summer-of-flops-was-actually-its-best-year-ever/279352/ …    
    
    
    Your Story is Your Brand | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130905033034-52594-your-story-is-your-brand …    
    
    
    Warning: Your Nice Boss May Be Killing Your Career | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130904141442-8353952-how-your-nice-boss-may-be-killing-your-career …    
    
    
    My tribute to my favorite author Edgar Allan Poe-Grave Hast Thyself  http://flamin-icicle.blogspot.in  LCO latest poem, from the brown classic pages.    
    
    
    49 days Wasted a lot Now time to get up and work But right at this moment am jus MOTIVATIN' myself    
    
    
    but I know will be through coz I believe Have faith in fate    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    