Updated Version Of iOS Shipping Today With New Languages For Siri http://www.businessinsider.com/ios-siri-japanese-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=tools … via @sai_tools    
    
    
    Sign language 'turned into text' http://pulse.me/s/6SxAS  (Braille conversion next?)    
    
    
    AT&T Expands LTE Coverage To New Orleans, Cleveland, More http://pulse.me/s/6VcP1     
    
    
    “@VolokhConspirac: (Sasha Volokh) http://bit.ly/xysHxV ” [An entertaining way to remember Pi]    
    
    
    @AP: UCLA professor wins $250K computing prize for AI. http://apne.ws/FORfer%0A     
    
    
    The Navy Is Getting Its Forces Ready For Iran In The Strait Of Hormuz http://www.businessinsider.com/the-navy-is-getting-its-forces-ready-for-iran-in-the-strait-of-hormuz-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=defense … via @BI_Defense    
    
    
    Military Industrial Complex  http://www.businessinsider.com/top-25-us-defense-companies-2012-2?op=1 …    
    
    
    Here Are The Amazing Kiva Robots That Amazon Just Bought For $775 Million http://www.businessinsider.com/here-are-the-amazing-kiva-robots-that-amazon-just-bought-for-775-million-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Draw Something Is Pummeling Zynga's Top Mobile Game http://www.businessinsider.com/chart-of-the-day-words-with-friends-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    @Tsoukalos So U don't buy the sunken marshes of southern Spain /w grd radar proof as valid?    
    
    
    REPORT: The Next iPhone Will Have A Larger 4.6-Inch Display http://www.businessinsider.com/report-the-next-iphone-will-have-a-larger-46-inch-display-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=tools … via @sai_tools    
    
    
    Asia Is Undergoing One Of The Fastest Military Buildup On The Planet http://www.businessinsider.com/military-spending-in-southeast-asia-is-skyrocketing-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=defense … via @BI_Defense    
    
    
    House Votes Against Facebook Password Amendment http://pulse.me/s/7vb42     
    
    
    11 Disgusting Ingredients You Eat Every Day That Food Companies Don't Talk About http://www.businessinsider.com/11-disgusting-ingredients-that-arent-advertised-in-food-2012-3?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=advertising … via @BI_Advertising    
    
    
    These Are The Best Countries In The World http://www.businessinsider.com/these-are-the-best-countries-in-the-world-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=bi … via @businessinsider    
    
    
    5th Circuit Court Dares Obama's Justice Department To Answer Whether Courts Can Strike Down Laws http://www.businessinsider.com/5th-circuit-court-dares-obamas-justice-department-to-answer-whether-courts-can-strike-down-laws-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=politics … via @bi_politics    
    
    
    IT'S REAL: Check Out What It's Like Using Google's Crazy Computerized Glasses http://www.businessinsider.com/check-out-what-its-like-using-googles-crazy-computerized-glasses-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=tools … via @sai_tools    
    
    
    Apple retains master decryption key for iCloud http://pulse.me/s/7LYyV     
    
    
    Most police track phones' locations without warrants - http://frommobile.cnn.com/3ZfyTK     
    
    
    There's Ammonia In Plenty Of Food, Not Just Pink Slime http://www.businessinsider.com/theres-ammonia-in-plenty-of-food-not-just-pink-slime-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=warroom-contributor … via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    @jennahunger Congrats #jetsetter    
    
    
    @Reuters: Internal NBC News probe determined "seasoned" producer to blame for misleading clip of Sanford 911 call http://reut.rs/IaIAHW     
    
    
    Here's Why Employers Can Get Away With Firing Pregnant Women http://www.businessinsider.com/employers-can-legally-fire-pregnant-women-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=careers … via @BI_Careers    
    
    
    News from @AP: Calif. artist Thomas Kinkade dies at age 54. http://apne.ws/HwOv6J%0A     
    
    
    Facebook And Dropbox Apps Vulnerable To Security Hole http://pulse.me/s/7TjJl     
    
    
    These Pantry Items Are Most Likely To Be Total Frauds  http://www.businessinsider.com/guess-which-item-in-your-pantry-is-most-likely-to-be-fraudulent-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=yourmoney … via @BIYourMoney    
    
    
    Disruptor Technology Alert! Meet Siri's Less Popular Sister: Trap.it http://www.businessinsider.com/trapit-personalized-news-reader-grew-out-of-same-program-that-created-siri-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Checkout AppBundle for iPhone! Get 200+ Apps in 1, Including Games, Utilities, Camera and Entertainment Apps. http://tiny.cc/appbundle     
    
    
    News from @AP: Mike Wallace, '60 Minutes' star interviewer, dies. http://apne.ws/HnyK2w%0A     
    
    
    Facebook and Dropbox iOS Apps to Get Security Fixes http://pulse.me/s/7Vre7     
    
    
    Hotel Caught Injecting Banner Ads on “Complimentary” Wi-Fi Network http://pulse.me/s/7X7DJ     
    
    
    Five Best Bluetooth Headsets [Hive Five] http://pulse.me/s/7XkE1     
    
    
    29 Easter eggs in your iPhone.  http://www.businessinsider.com/iphone-tips-and-tricks-2012-4 …    
    
    
    US Navy deploys 2nd aircraft carrier to Gulf amid Iran nuke tensions http://pulse.me/s/7YvnP     
    
    
    Amazon's Security System Is Making It Easy To Use Stolen Credit Cards http://www.businessinsider.com/amazons-security-system-makes-it-easy-to-use-a-stolen-credit-card-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=yourmoney-contributor … via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    USA has highest teen pregnancy.  http://www.businessinsider.com/why-there-are-so-many-teen-moms-in-the-us-2012-4 …    
    
    
    Facebook buys Instagram  http://cnet.co/IaJqao     
    
    
    Why College Isn't for Everyone - Businessweek via @BW http://buswk.co/HuVOSF     
    
    
    “@SAI: The Best Hackers In The World All Come From One Country by @boonspoon http://read.bi/I0Mcsk ”  (yes, top 10 are from China)    
    
    
    "Twisting" Signals Could Mean Nearly Infinite Wireless Spectrum [Wireless] http://pulse.me/s/6y0yF     
    
    
    The United States Army Rolls Out Custom App Marketplace for iPhone!  http://pulse.me/s/7om1s     
    
    
    Breathe Life Into Your Electric Car’s Quiet Motor With XLR8 http://pulse.me/s/840YK     
    
    
    Report: UC Davis Police should not have pepper-sprayed protesters http://usnews.msnbc.msn.com/_news/2012/04/11/11146298-report-uc-davis-police-should-not-have-pepper-sprayed-protesters?lite#.T4YPdgxSyGY.twitter … via @msnbc_us    
    
    
    What You Need to Know About the New Google Plus Design http://pulse.me/s/83tYA     
    
    
    What if the government rejects the Constitution? http://pulse.me/s/861ef     
    
    
    Android gives 'no permissions' apps access to sensitive info http://pulse.me/s/84Jbe     
    
    
    Non-Programmers May Soon Be Able To Create Apps Too http://pulse.me/s/86o4q     
    
    
    Antibiotic Resistant Bacteria Found In A Four Million-Year-Old Cave http://www.businessinsider.com/antibiotic-resistant-bacteria-has-been-found-in-a-four-million-year-old-cave-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=main-contributor … via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    The Secret Service Prostitution Scandal Is The 'Biggest In History' http://www.businessinsider.com/secret-service-prostitution-scandal-is-the-biggest-in-history-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=politics … via @bi_politics    
    
    
    Groupon's App Has Disappeared From Apple's App Store http://www.businessinsider.com/groupons-app-has-disappeared-from-apples-app-store-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    AT&T Wasn't Doing Enough To Stop iPhone Thefts, Alleges Lawsuit http://www.businessinsider.com/att-lawsuit-alleges-company-wasnt-doing-enough-to-stop-phone-thefts-2012-4?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Plasma fusion energy potential is two-thirds of the way there. http://rt.com/usa/news/plasma-fusion-energy-nuclear-080/ …    
    
    
    Apple Asks iPhone Owners for Security Info on Home Screen http://pulse.me/s/8cRA0     
    
    
    @andersoncooper Congrats on being included in The Top 10 Most Influential Political Voices on Twitter! http://issuu.com/bursonmarsteller/docs/united_states_g20influencers …    
    
    
    Huge Spike In Number Of Teens Dying From Prescription Drug Abuse: Study http://pulse.me/s/8fflb     
    
    
    US taxes cost some expatriates their citizenship http://pulse.me/s/8eMuN     
    
    
    Ala. judge orders man to jail for sagging pants http://pulse.me/s/83RXH     
    
    
    Rumor: iPad Mini coming this fall priced at $249-299 http://pulse.me/s/8eL0o  (So will the original be called the MaxiPad?)    
    
    
    @jpbrubaker Make it a McWorkout.    
    
    
    Verizon expands LTE coverage through New York state, Georgia, and elsewhere http://pulse.me/s/8gSbF     
    
    
    Misleading App Tops Charts, Highlights Apple’s Inattention To Details http://pulse.me/s/8loZN     
    
    
    Landmark breast cancer study finds 10 strains, revolutionizes treatment options http://pulse.me/s/8lTgR     
    
    
    Scientists: Fish are sick where BP's oil spill hit http://pulse.me/s/8lzIs     
    
    
    How Mobile Technologies Are Shaping a New Generation http://pulse.me/s/8krQt     
    
    
    Silent Hives http://pulse.me/s/8o6uW  Pesticides are killing bees and the FDA has failed to take action.    
    
    
    Instapaper vs Pocket vs Readability: Read later app for iPhone shootout! http://pulse.me/s/8n68t     
    
    
    Is There Any Hope For Yahoo? http://pulse.me/s/8s564     
    
    
    Things The Facebook Generation Will Not Buy http://pulse.me/s/8qyIx     
    
    
    Brain stem cell discovery could change treatment of brain injury http://pulse.me/s/8rugV     
    
    
    MIT Hagelstein Cold Fusion Demonstration has been producing excess heat for two months straight http://pulse.me/s/8plO7     
    
    
    Apple pushing the iPhone to business with new ‘iPhone at Work’ webpage via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/04/21/apple-pushing-iphone-business-iphone-work-webpage/ … pic.twitter.com/mAPQunna    
    
    
    Next generation iPhone rumored to use new in-cell touch panel displays via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/04/20/generation-iphone-rumored-incell-touch-panel-displays/ … pic.twitter.com/xgqGa952    
    
    
    Today’s Apps Gone Free: Parking Lot, Sketch Maker, Qvoid, And More http://pulse.me/s/8rQDS     
    
    
    Wal-Mart covered up bribe campaign in Mexico, report says http://pulse.me/s/8soA5     
    
    
    Boy's soccer ball lost in tsunami, found in Alaska http://pulse.me/s/8uHSU     
    
    
    Vatican crackdown on U.S. Catholic nuns http://pulse.me/s/8rKTg     
    
    
    The Next iPhone: What In-Cell Touch Panel Technology Means http://pulse.me/s/8vjdC     
    
    
    iPhone & iPad theft in NY up 44% since last YR (via @iMore). IME lockout is long overdue! http://www.imore.com/2012/04/23/iphone-ipad-theft-york-44-year/ … pic.twitter.com/puw4MBZI    
    
    
    1 In 2 New Graduates Are Jobless Or Underemployed http://pulse.me/s/8tp2k     
    
    
    Brain fog: Ways to combat short term memory loss http://pulse.me/s/8v0vR     
    
    
    Romnye's Budget Plan: More For War, Cuts For The Poor http://pulse.me/s/8tqQt     
    
    
    Microsoft sells AOL patents on to Facebook http://pulse.me/s/8vHhb     
    
    
    MT Former BP Engineer Charged in Gulf Spill for deleting text msgs http://on.wsj.com/I7gyQd  via @WSJ    
    
    
    @dawtree Only in your dreams #Herminy    
    
    
    The Most Violent States In America http://pulse.me/s/8xB7p     
    
    
    Napolitano faces questions on Secret Service http://pulse.me/s/8zxck  She has no business running Homeland Security    
    
    
    With A New Educational Platform, TED Gives Teachers The Keys To A Flipped Classroom http://pulse.me/s/8yG9Z  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    What Your Klout Score Really Means http://pulse.me/s/8ynp9     
    
    
    Microsoft Security Essentials Updates with Better Performance, Virus Detection, and Interface Changes [Microsoft ... http://pulse.me/s/8A5q1     
    
    
    Creating Innovators: Why America's Education System Is Obsolete http://pulse.me/s/8A8xR     
    
    
    Klout Goes Mobile With New iPhone App http://pulse.me/s/8Azwi     
    
    
    Today’s Apps Gone Free: Wee Sing And Learn ABC, Dummy Defense, Holidays Plus, And More http://pulse.me/s/8A3LG     
    
    
    Comparing Five Of The Top Web-Based Storage Solutions http://pulse.me/s/8AbWX     
    
    
    Google increases Gmail to 10GB of free storage — double what Google Drive gets via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/04/24/google-increases-gmail-10gb-free-storage-double-google-drive/ … pic.twitter.com/0ULsbjyJ    
    
    
    As House Passes CISPA, The Fight Is Just Beginning - Forbes http://shar.es/21ZPY  via @sharethis    
    
    
    iPhone apps gone free. http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/04/todays-apps-gone-free-smash-cops-icolorama-loom-photomosaic-builder-and-more …    
    
    
    “@VolokhConspirac: Legalizing Spousal Necrophilia in Egypt?: Al Arabiya rpts:
Egypt’s Nat'l Council for Women http://bit.ly/IskHcX ” BIZARRE!    
    
    
    A Story About Just How Bizarre Apple’s App Approval Process Has Become http://pulse.me/s/8ERWW     
    
    
    Today’s Apps Gone Free: Postale, Cycle Tracker Pro, Raccoon Rising, And More http://pulse.me/s/8EmQs     
    
    
    Cringe At the Ugliest Cameras Ever Made [Cameras] http://pulse.me/s/8F0yC     
    
    
    New Skype Version Brings Unique Feature Along With Assorted Minor Fixes http://pulse.me/s/8L37q     
    
    
    @mstrau Are U on FourSquare?    
    
    
    SUPERSIZE PRICE TAG: America's Growing Obesity Sends Costs Soaring http://pulse.me/s/8Ko7D     
    
    
    Number of US newborns with drug withdrawal triples http://pulse.me/s/8KRhq     
    
    
    Itsy-bitsy teeny cell towers are coming http://pulse.me/s/8Kwo6     
    
    
    The $7 trillion fiscal cliff coming in 2013 http://pulse.me/s/8JBwi     
    
    
    Now you can block retweets from individual users with Tweetbot 2.3 for iPhone and iPad via @iMore pic.twitter.com/93j88izG    
    
    
    Chocolate Toothpaste? New Product Rethinks 'Sweet Tooth' http://pulse.me/s/8LojQ     
    
    
    The Thought-Patterns of Success http://pulse.me/s/8JQCf     
    
    
    Lawmakers: Demarco Hid Key Information On Principal Reduction http://pulse.me/s/8Mtvt     
    
    
    @darjbrock Doesn't surprise me. Humans have genes no other animal has. Clear indicator of manipulation.    
    
    
    @andersoncooper Keep up the good work. Surprises ahead!    
    
    
    Today’s Apps Gone Free: Quicky, AdSenseZen, Silly Owls, And More http://pulse.me/s/8PDIu     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Updated: Could The Next iPhone Arrive In June? http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/the-story-behind-the-story-could-the-next-iphone-arrive-in-june/ …    
    
    
    4 DAYS OF HELL: Man Reveals Horrific Details Of Prison Experience http://pulse.me/s/8QWx8     
    
    
    Chen Says U.S. Officials Lied to Speed His Exit http://pulse.me/s/8QnCJ     
    
    
        
    
    
    Fed Up With Sluggish Neutrinos, Scientists Force Light To Move Faster Than Its Own Speed Limit http://pulse.me/s/8S7ci  via @PopSci    
    
    
    New iPhone to feature 4-inch display, metal case, smaller dock connector, fall release http://pulse.me/s/8QPuI     
    
    
    Apple Is Rejecting Apps That Use Dropbox http://www.businessinsider.com/apple-is-rejecting-apps-that-use-dropbox-2012-5?utm_source=twbutton&utm_medium=social&utm_campaign=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    Tablets Quickly Becoming the Portable PC of Choice http://pulse.me/s/8SQ7P     
    
    
    Nine Dangerous Things You Were Taught In School (119 points) http://pulse.me/s/8Q92l     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Smoking iPhone 4S In Australia Reminds Us Of The Importance Of Authorized Repairs http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/smoking-iphone-4s-in-australia-reminds-us-of-the-importance-of-authorized-repairs/ …    
    
    
    Here's Where To Learn About The Future Of Social Commerce http://pulse.me/s/8RL9s     
    
    
    Twitter rumored to have talked about acquiring iOS app Camera+ via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/05/03/twitter-rumored-talk-acquiring-ios-app-camera/ … pic.twitter.com/GRxbJwXz    
    
    
    Email Is Like Stress in a Bottle, Study Shows [Email] http://pulse.me/s/8ZXi8     
    
    
    The 10 Best Digital Cameras http://pulse.me/s/2yB4X     
    
    
    Apple details security updates covered in iOS 5.1.1 update via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/05/08/apple-details-security-updates-covered-ios-511-update/ … pic.twitter.com/ixRd4J7x    
    
    
    From @appadvice: MIT Students Develop Ridiculously Cool Way To Transfer Data With A Finger Swipe http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/mit-students-develop-ridiculously-cool-way-to-transfer-data-with-a-finger-swipe/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Finally A Great Idea From AT&T: Family Data Plans http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/finally-a-great-idea-from-att-family-data-plans/ …    
    
    
    A set of top Computer Science blogs (202 points) http://pulse.me/s/91ECA     
    
    
    10 Incredibly Useful Travel Websites http://pulse.me/s/91ImH     
    
    
    Twitter protects Occupy protester's privacy http://pulse.me/s/91yur     
    
    
    DOJ official: Warrant requirement for location data 'cripples' law enforcement http://www.technolog.msnbc.msn.com/technology/technolog/doj-official-warrant-requirement-location-data-cripples-law-enforcement-758793 … via @msnbc    
    
    
    Obama Loses 40% of West Virginia Vote to an Inmate http://pulse.me/s/94EpT     
    
    
    Coming Soon: A Meaner, Nastier, Even Less Effective Congress http://pulse.me/s/951V1     
    
    
    Fannie Mae Is Off the Dole: Sign of a Housing Bottom? http://pulse.me/s/93PKX     
    
    
    Chevron Brazil Spill Shows Transocean Ltd still can't get it right  http://pulse.me/s/97oo5     
    
    
    U.S. Postal Service Loses $3.2 Billion. Time to scrap this monopoly.  http://pulse.me/s/96lNi     
    
    
    Facebook Co-Founder May Have Sidestepped Taxes By Dropping Citizenship http://pulse.me/s/98Oop     
    
    
    @LewisHowes Nothing's free in LA. Starving actors need to pay for their acting lessons!    
    
    
    If you're not registered for @klout, check it out! Sign up today and let's see how we compare! http://klout.com/?n=tw&v=invite_tw_button …    
    
    
    According to @klout, my Klout score is 52. How influential are you? http://klout.com/#/JDoughtry?n=tw&v=klout_score …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Apple Now Approving Apps Using [revised] Dropbox SDK http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/apple-now-approving-apps-using-dropbox-sdk/ …    
    
    
    17% of cancer cases caused by infections.  http://ohsonline.com/articles/2012/05/12/infections-cause-1-in-6-cancer-cases-worldwide.aspx …    
    
    
    Op-Ed: N. America's radiation threat: another mainstream news blackout http://www.digitaljournal.com/article/324272  via @digitaljournal    
    
    
    @mdealoia I know the feeling. With bifocals I'm forced to look down my nose at anything on a screen. :)    
    
    
    @alwysactv Nice, eh? #ClevelandWeather    
    
    
    Facebook Boosts Mobile App With Bigger Photos in Your News Feed http://pulse.me/s/9fffD     
    
    
    12 year old explains how government and banking system defrauds the citizens. http://www.goldismoney2.com/showthread.php?32594-12-Year-Old-Attacks-Banking-System-in-Econ-Lesson-Video-of-the-Year&s=eb106d4ab0cccd86e7bb9d6a9e67a1e7 …    
    
    
    Jesse Jackson paid to keep quiet? Known voter fraud in OH & PA in '08 election? And more? http://www.westernjournalism.com/wikileaks-obama-team-stole-election-bribed-jesse-jackson-and-took-russian-money-in-2008/ …    
    
    
    RAVN social media for events is shutting down according to their distributed email.    
    
    
    From @appadvice: AppAdvice Daily: Chrome For iOS Coming Soon? http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/appadvice-daily-chrome-for-ios-free-apps-and-a-free-download/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Feed Me Oil, Mountain Bike Pro Cycling Computer, Converter, and More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-feed-me-oil-mountain-bike-pro-cycling-computer-converter-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Facebook Pages Manager Coming Soon to USA.  http://getapp.cc/app/US/514643583 …    
    
    
    Teen Finds Human Finger In Arby's Sandwich http://pulse.me/s/9loZz     
    
    
    Reports: HP poised to eliminate up to 30,000 jobs http://pulse.me/s/9m8jU     
    
    
    Natural gas prices drop on rising supplies http://pulse.me/s/9lXZZ     
    
    
    Commercial rocket will fly to the space station http://pulse.me/s/9loYq     
    
    
    Egypt’s Coptic Christians to shun Islamists in next week’s presidential vote http://pulse.me/s/9kjoR     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: PicShop HD, Blosics, Blast Ball, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-picshop-hd-blosics-blast-ball-and-more/ …    
    
    
    @andersoncooper #Jeopardy glad to see you won! #EliWhitney :)    
    
    
    @martinltpm Glad to see you enjoy Outlook. I have two add ons for LinkedIn and FB to allow me easily to add people who email me.    
    
    
    Blooms! http://instagr.am/p/K0vvZiwyyr/     
    
    
    More evidence for a 7.85-inch "iPad-mini" this fall http://pulse.me/s/9lz2p     
    
    
    Top 10 Pervasive Tech Myths That Are Only Wasting Your Time [Lifehacker Top 10] http://pulse.me/s/9pw4L     
    
    
    Day After IPO, Mark Zuckerberg Marries Longtime Girlfriend Priscilla Chan http://pulse.me/s/9qllY  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Checklist Again, Piatto, Locationizer, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-events-map-piatto-locationizer-and-more/ …    
    
    
    SpaxeX's Historic ISS Cargo Ferry Launch Aborted at the Last Second http://pulse.me/s/9pOJ0  via @PopSci    
    
    
    Italy Earthquake Leaves Six Dead, 50 Hurt http://pulse.me/s/9rlay     
    
    
    The TSA Needs to Adapt http://pulse.me/s/9o1MG     
    
    
    Polymaths are flexible thinkers. http://pulse.me/s/9nGR3     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Bills On Your Table HD, Super Lemonade Factory, My Cashflow, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-bills-on-your-table-hd-super-lemonade-factory-my-cashflow-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Why You Should Read Engagement Marketing http://pulse.me/s/9sF9a     
    
    
    iOS 5.1.1 Untethered Jailbreak ‘Absinthe 2.0′ To Drop This Week [Jailbreak] http://pulse.me/s/9rGzG     
    
    
    Don't Write Windows Phone's Obituary Just Yet, Samsung's New Focus 2 Is A Winner [REVIEW] (T, MSFT) http://pulse.me/s/9rXfa     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Fruit Tumble, Bouncy Seed, Ringtone Maker Plus Silent Sound, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-fruit-tumble-bouncy-seed-ringtone-maker-plus-silent-sound-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Updated: Preparing For The iOS 5.1.1 Jailbreak http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/preparing-for-the-ios-5-1-1-jailbreak/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Ducky's Coffee, 2 Days, GPlayer, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-duckys-coffee-2-days-gplayer-and-more/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    'Frequent and severe' sexual violence alleged at women's prison in Alabama http://pulse.me/s/9ybK3     
    
    
    Birther Theories Debunked Again As Hawaii Verifies Records http://pulse.me/s/9wVi9     
    
    
    California nuke trouble could prompt rule review http://pulse.me/s/9zkzH     
    
    
    Jury deals blow to Oracle in case vs. Google http://pulse.me/s/9yFSI     
    
    
    Facebook, banks sued over pre-IPO analyst calls http://pulse.me/s/9xWBl     
    
    
    Military-grade scopes and apps for iPhone and iPad boast geotagging and nightvision via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/05/23/militarygrade-scopes-apps-iphone-ipad-boast-geotagging-nightvision/ … pic.twitter.com/gkT5rcRc    
    
    
    World News - Pakistan jails doctor who helped CIA find Osama bin Laden http://worldnews.msnbc.msn.com/_news/2012/05/23/11827022-pakistan-jails-doctor-who-helped-cia-find-osama-bin-laden?lite …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Gizmon's Clip-On Camera Accessories For iPhone Stand Out From The Competition http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/gizmons-clip-on-camera-accessories-for-iphone-stand-out-from-the-competition/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Photo Slice, Carmen, Unstoppaball DX, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-photo-slice-carmen-unstoppaball-dx-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Update: Unthethered jailbreak for iOS 5.1.1 available for download http://pulse.me/s/9DmSr     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Easy 5K With Jeff Galloway, Splashtop CamCam, Kitchenator, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-easy-5k-with-jeff-galloway-splashtop-camcam-kitchenator-and-more/ …    
    
    
    How Facebook's Timeline is like genital herpes http://pulse.me/s/9F4eN     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Absinthe "Lockdown" Error Fortunately Has A Quick, Easy Fix http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/absinthe-lockdown-error-fortunately-has-a-quick-easy-fix/ …    
    
    
    SpaceX Capsule Has 'New Car' Smell : Discovery News http://news.discovery.com/space/astronauts-spacex-120526.html …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Compulse, Go There Square: A Stella And Sam Adventure, Superimpose, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-compulse-go-there-square-a-stella-and-sam-adventure-superimpose-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Vatican faces widening of leaks scandal http://pulse.me/s/9G6vy     
    
    
    Why America Is Slouching Towards Third World Status http://pulse.me/s/9H3lZ     
    
    
    Postal Service offers $15,000 buyouts to 45,000 mail handlers http://pulse.me/s/9DwoE     
    
    
    Everything You Need to Know About Sunscreen http://pulse.me/s/9Gw3W     
    
    
    Facebook once again rumored to be making a phone, this time with iPhone talent via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/05/27/facebook-rumored-making-phone-time-iphone-talent/ … pic.twitter.com/qwgsfu6U    
    
    
    Adonit Jot Pro stylus for iPad review via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/05/09/adonit-jot-pro-stylus-review/ … pic.twitter.com/Kv3L8W6h    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Report: Apple Integrated TV Begins Trial Production http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/report-apple-integrated-tv-begins-trial-production/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: #Todo, Bead It, Gears, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-todo-bead-it-gears-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: The Chronic Dev Team Updates Absinthe Jailbreak Tool http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/chronic-dev-team-updates-absinthe-adds-support-for-iphone-4s-new-build-of-ios-5-1-1/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Facebook Tapping Apple Engineers For Its Upcoming Smartphone http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/facebook-tapping-apple-engineers-for-its-upcoming-smartphone/ …    
    
    
    Cool and useful gadgets for the savvy iPhone road warrior http://pulse.me/s/9KHIS     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Leaked Images Suggest A Completely Redone iPhone http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/the-next-iphone/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Screenshot Journal, Fotor, MovBeats, And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-screenshot-journal-fotor-movbeats-and-more/ …    
    
    
    World's most sophisticated cyber weapon burns computers in Middle East http://pulse.me/s/9JApR     
    
    
    Radioactive traces found in fish off Calif. http://pulse.me/s/9JMDR     
    
    
    1,600-year-old mosaic at Israeli synagogue damaged http://pulse.me/s/9KRPT     
    
    
    10 Undeniable Reasons Why You Should Exercise Your Self-Awareness (And How to Start) http://pulse.me/s/9Jqyd     
    
    
    INFOGRAPHIC: A Crystal Clear Breakdown Of How The US Economy Uses 5 Major Forms Of Energy http://pulse.me/s/9LbdF     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Jailbreak Only: MyWi Updated - Adds Support For iOS 5.1.1 http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/jailbreak-only-mywi-updated-adds-support-for-ios-5-1-1/ …    
    
    
    Mining Legacy: Tale of a Toxic Town http://pulse.me/s/9KWm0     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Movie360, Charadium II, ColorManager And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-movie360-charadium-ii-colormanager-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Loopseque Kids, Snapseed, Light The Night And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/05/todays-apps-gone-free-loopseque-kids-snapseed-light-the-night-and-more/ …    
    
    
    JUDGE: Dear Oracle, You're Not Getting A Dime From Google Over Android (ORCL, GOOG) http://pulse.me/s/9PbCo     
    
    
    2 New Elements Named on Periodic Table http://pulse.me/s/9PqRX     
    
    
    Is there no limit to gov’t power? Apparently not. http://m.wired.com/threatlevel/2012/05/warrantless-spying-challenge/ …    
    
    
    Obama Ordered Wave of Cyberattacks Against Iran http://pulse.me/s/9PGqo     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Dream:scape, Hotel Dash: Suite Success, ReconBot And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-dreamscape-hotel-dash-suite-success-reconbot-and-more/ …    
    
    
    AT&T announces new data roaming packages via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/06/01/att-announces-data-roaming-packages/ … pic.twitter.com/onLA9dur    
    
    
    The Data's In: Honesty Really Does Start at the Top http://pulse.me/s/9R2Ld     
    
    
    Scientific American Reader: 'Old Person Smell' Is Real, but Not Necessarily Offensive http://goo.gl/mag/JRv6M     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Hector: Badge Of Carnage, Eye Illusions, Scramblies And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-hector-badge-of-carnage-eye-illusions-scramblies-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Tea, AirMusic, Sky Gnomes And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-tea-airmusic-sky-gnomes-and-more/ …    
    
    
    iPhone 5 rumored to be getting low power, Wi-Fi Direct enabled chipset... and AirDrop? via @iMore pic.twitter.com/F3cq4CNI    
    
    
    Apple may announce iOS 6 June 11, including new maps, camera, and photo apps http://pulse.me/s/9SovV     
    
    
    MRT @RawStory: Bolivia's Pres. Morales talks of nationalizing natural resources. http://goo.gl/B7q0D  Watch LiIon battery $ climb.    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Prioritask, iMoodJournal, Little Things And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-prioritask-imoodjournal-little-things-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Facebook comments, ads don't sway most users: poll http://pulse.me/s/9Y44V     
    
    
    Bad News Piles Up for China's Economy http://pulse.me/s/9ThoD     
    
    
    Wal-Mart's proxy vote shows dissent against execs http://pulse.me/s/9XlPM     
    
    
    The Xbox 360, Now A True Cable Box Killer http://pulse.me/s/9XCtD  via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Microsoft's SmartGlass to turn your iPhone and iPad into secondary Xbox screens via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/06/04/microsofts-smartglass-turn-iphone-ipad-secondary-xbox-screens/ … pic.twitter.com/ZHmSqUCk    
    
    
    Budget airline using iPads to reduce aircraft's weight, fuel consumption and running costs via @iMore pic.twitter.com/SkJ2WAW6    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Sonic & SEGA All-Stars Racing, Starry Sky, UniqBoard And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-sonic-sega-all-stars-racing-starry-sky-uniqboard-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Apple bringing the Google battle to Maps in iOS 6 via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/06/05/apple-bringing-google-battle-maps-ios-6/ … pic.twitter.com/0mZ3T3nW    
    
    
    The Internet Changes Wednesday, But Most People Won’t Notice http://pulse.me/s/a0eFO     
    
    
    Facebook Engagement Dips: 34% Spend Less Time on Site [STUDY] http://pulse.me/s/9ZSMc     
    
    
    Viral ‘Privacy Notice’ On Facebook Is Fake http://pulse.me/s/9ZTDn     
    
    
    New Firefox 13 supports more secure browsing http://pulse.me/s/9ZHDM     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Discover The Even More Efficient iCalendar, Plus A Chance To Win A Copy http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/discover-the-even-more-efficient-icalendar-plus-a-chance-to-win-a-copy/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Bag It, Runner's Log, Turtle Rescue And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-bag-it-runners-log-turtle-rescue-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Camera+ Sells Eight Millionth Copy On Second Anniversary    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today’s Apps Gone Free: Monsters Ate My Condo, Part, Paranormal Agency And More    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Facebook App Center Launches With Over 600 Facebook-Connected Apps http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/facebook-app-center-launches-with-over-600-facebook-connected-apps/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Report: Apple To Unveil New App Called Organize http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/report-apple-to-unveil-new-app-called-organize/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Quotes Folder, Calorie Counter And Diet Tracker, Dollar Origami And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-quotes-folder-calorie-counter-and-diet-tracker-dollar-origami-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Ex-Miss Pennsylvania will 'continue to pursue the truth' about pageant http://pulse.me/s/a4jzu     
    
    
    Secret Ways to Fascinate Anyone http://pulse.me/s/a5tbU     
    
    
    Why 3D Printing is About to Transform Our World http://pulse.me/s/a0llR     
    
    
    San Francisco mounts security cameras that try to predict the future behavior of people http://pulse.me/s/a5Sfm     
    
    
    MAULDIN: A Dysfunctional Nation [Greece] http://pulse.me/s/a7Lc9     
    
    
    Foreclosure Nightmare uncovers fraud http://pulse.me/s/a6TKM     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Dracula: The Official Stoker Family Edition, Learn Spanish, Snabbit And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-dracula-the-official-stoker-family-edition-learn-spanish-snabbit-and-more/ …    
    
    
    @alwysactv I'm soaking up the sun on the beach! :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    10 things that you need to know about sex: http://pulse.me/s/a99Tw     
    
    
    10 things you need to know to be happier: http://pulse.me/s/a8VQP     
    
    
    iOS 6 to be announced Monday at WWDC http://pulse.me/s/a7CGe     
    
    
        
    
    
    iOS 6 to catch up and leap ahead. 
http://www.businessinsider.com/ios-6-key-features-2012-6?op=1 …    
    
    
    iOS 6 GM expected in early September ahead of new iPhone http://lnkd.in/w3kubi     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Cut The Buttons, Real Piano Pro, Spring Cleaning And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-cut-the-buttons-real-piano-pro-spring-cleaning-and-more/ …    
    
    
    ITC rejects Google patents in HTC's legal dispute aganist Apple http://pulse.me/s/aeGCq     
    
    
    The big list of iOS 6 features via @iMore http://www.imore.com/2012/06/13/big-list-ios-6-features/ … pic.twitter.com/zAlXmCHD    
    
    
    Vodafone creates a signal-boosting, solar-charging umbrella to juice your cellphone whatever the weather http://pulse.me/s/afQuH     
    
    
    BRUTAL: Nokia Will Axe 10,000 Jobs (NOK) http://pulse.me/s/agbuY     
    
    
    Nokia Stock Down By More Than 10% On Massive Overhaul: Revised Forecasts, Exec Changes, Vertu Gone, Scalado Acquired http://pulse.me/s/agiyi     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Microsoft Updates My Xbox LIVE App - Control Your Xbox With Your iPhone http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/microsoft-updates-my-xbox-live-app-control-your-xbox-with-your-iphone/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Updated Fuze Join App Brings Video Conferencing To The iPhone 4/4s (free!) http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/updated-fuze-join-app-brings-video-conferencing-to-the-iphone/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Flight Control Rocket, SPY Mouse, Multi Measures And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-flight-control-rocket-spy-mouse-multi-measures-and-more/ …    
    
    
    More Americans Blame Bush, Not Obama, For Economic Woes: Poll http://pulse.me/s/agQYL     
    
    
    China vows to probe 'forced abortion photo' http://pulse.me/s/ag3dx     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Lock 'N' Load, Magic Ink - The Wonderful Wizard Of Oz, Crash And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-lock-n-load-magic-ink-the-wonderful-wizard-of-oz-crash-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Primo Do, Ballistic SE, Tower Of Fortune And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-primo-do-ballistic-se-tower-of-fortune-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Pocket Gets Updated With Improved Reading Options And A Handful Of Fixes http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/pocket-gets-updated-with-improved-reading-options-and-a-handful-of-fixes/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Project 83113, Blobster, Solids Elementary HD And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-project-83113-blobster-solids-elementary-hd-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Time for a typewriter renaissance? http://pulse.me/s/appir     
    
    
    7 Layout Secrets of the Big Retail Chains http://pulse.me/s/aoOMt     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Grim Joggers, Verde, Monster Shooter: The Lost Levels And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-grim-joggers-verde-monster-shooter-the-lost-levels-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Flipboard Becomes 'Trusted' Google+ Partner http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/flipboard-becomes-trusted-google-partner/ …    
    
    
    Stunning Blade Runner Animation Made With 3000 Watercolors http://m.wired.com/underwire/2012/06/blade-runner-animation-watercolor/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Cloth, Smart Notes, PalmPEDi And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-cloth-smart-notes-palmpedi-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Hon Hai Chairman Tells World To Wait For iPhone 5, Fall Of Samsung http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/hon-hai-chairman-tells-world-to-wait-for-iphone-5-fall-of-samsung/ …. Wow! Racism or is it truth?    
    
    
    @andersoncooper Wife said “He seems like a nice guy.” I told her that you were down to earth. Did I make your day? :)    
    
    
    House Panel Votes to Sanction Holder http://pulse.me/s/asQiF  via @WSJ  Take THAT Obama!    
    
    
    Oil prices slide to 8-month low.  So why are pump prices not 25% lower!? http://pulse.me/s/atIXA     
    
    
    Hamas scion turned Christian and Israeli spy making film on Islam http://pulse.me/s/as9yl     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Flipboard Adds Google+ And YouTube Integration http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/flipboard-adds-google-and-youtube-integration/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: League Of Evil, OSnap!, TinyWallet And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-league-of-evil-osnap-tinywallet-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: FUUSIO, iSlash HD, Fast Remote Desktop And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-fuusio-islash-hd-fast-remote-desktop-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Small U.S. Manufacturers Give Up on 'Made in China' http://pulse.me/s/ayi3H     
    
    
    Woman Claims Citi Wrongly Forcibly Evicted Her From Her Home http://pulse.me/s/ayKuw     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Banca, PomodoroPro, Draw Along With Stella And Sam And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-banca-pomodoropro-draw-along-with-stella-and-sam-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Hearts Tournament, Easy Calendar, Toy Defense And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-hearts-tournament-easy-calendar-toy-defense-and-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Tweetbot's Super Secret Settings Are A Secret No More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/tweetbots-super-secret-settings-are-a-secret-no-more/ …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's Apps Gone Free: Marvel KAPOW!, Pocket Check-Up, Band Together And More http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/06/todays-apps-gone-free-marvel-kapow-pocket-check-up-band-together-and-more/ …    
    
    
    Android Getting Crushed By iOS In App Retention http://pulse.me/s/aIxqd     
    
    
    Apparently Chinese culture considers talking about human rights abuse to outsiders is treason.  http://pulse.me/s/aHE0x  via @WSJ    
    
    
    Barclays to pay $400M-plus to settle LIBOR charges http://pulse.me/s/aHGS1  Will we ever see the end of banking corruption?    
    
    
    Facebook Just Fixed One Of The Biggest Complaints Users Have About Its iPhone App (FB) http://pulse.me/s/aJsMt     
    
    
    Apple Planning Major Overhaul of iTunes to Emphasize iCloud and Sharing http://pulse.me/s/aITML     
    
    
    Flash won't be supported in Android 4.1, new installs to be disabled on August 15th http://pulse.me/s/aLrYg     
    
    
    Analyst: RIM's New BlackBerry Operating System 'May Never See The Light Of Day' http://pulse.me/s/aL9Eq     
    
    
    @AppAdvice I’m going through withdrawal. Save me! :)    
    
    
    @Tsoukalos You’re a trip. Enjoy the show AND the tweets blasting the biased and ignorant.    
    
    
    @AppAdvice something in the FB link doesn’t work. :’(    
    
    
    Follow AppAdvice on Twitter and Facebook for your chance to win iOS apps! http://www.facebook.com/appadvice?sk=app_211922635540356 …    
    
    
    PSA: if you sync contacts with Facebook, then you might be sending E-Mails to the @facebook.com address http://pulse.me/s/aPQH1     
    
    
    What Multitasking Does To Our Brains [Productivity] http://pulse.me/s/aRFfX     
    
    
    Bankers constantly lying, defrauding; most still not in jail http://pulse.me/s/aR25y     
    
    
    MRT @AppAdvice: Hello to the iPad "mini" http://apadv.co/OjhwKq  I just hope it’s not named “The MiniPad”.    
    
    
    From @appadvice: AT&T To Activate Database Of Stolen Handsets Tuesday http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/07/att-to-activate-database-of-stolen-handsets-tuesday/ …    
    
    
    Act as if You're a Certain Type of Person to Become that Person [Mind Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/b00mW     
    
    
    We’re destroying the seas http://pulse.me/s/b540g     
    
    
    Adolescent angst: 5 facts about the teen brain http://pulse.me/s/b5w0l     
    
    
    The Public Sector Vs. The Private Sector In One Colossal Chart http://pulse.me/s/b6ykw     
    
    
    Your Cell Phone Is Under More Surveillance Than Ever [Privacy] http://pulse.me/s/b605W     
    
    
    Next Twitter for iPhone Version to Bring Interactive Tweet View http://pulse.me/s/b58pC     
    
    
    When economy gets bad, women dress to impress? http://pulse.me/s/b94c2     
    
    
    @mdealoia Those guys are hilarious #topgear    
    
    
    Clue to why human body can't fight HIV discovered http://pulse.me/s/bebHJ     
    
    
    Extreme Drought Spreads Across More Than Half Of The US http://pulse.me/s/bfWbC     
    
    
    From @appadvice: If The Cops Get Your Smartphone, They're Free To Impersonate You http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/07/if-the-cops-get-your-smartphone-theyre-free-to-impersonate-you/ … http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/07/if-the-cops-get-your-smartphone-theyre-free-to-impersonate-you/ …    
    
    
    @Rock1chef Just heard on WKSU that they'll be airing an interview with you!    
    
    
    Wall Street Professionals Admit: Yes, Lots of Us Are Corrupt http://pulse.me/s/bua1H     
    
    
    The Financial Crisis Was Foreseeable … Thousands of Years Ago http://pulse.me/s/bsACC     
    
    
    Australian Airline Qantas to supply an iPad for every passenger on its 767 flights via @iMore http://www.imore.com/australian-airline-quantas-supply-ipad-every-passenger-its-767-flights … pic.twitter.com/SSnf8nNi    
    
    
    The circle of madness is closing. A blogger's thoughts on the Aurora shootings. http://pulse.me/s/btpCc     
    
    
    Affordable Care Act Reduces Fund for Uninsured, Worrying Hospitals http://pulse.me/s/bDbKw     
    
    
    Blossom Music to hear Beethoven's grand 5th Symphony. http://pnr.ma/azFCjI     
    
    
    Boy or Girl? Does the Mother Control Outcome? http://pulse.me/s/bMEm1     
    
    
    Assault Rifle Made With a 3-D Printer. Where there's a will, there's a way. http://pulse.me/s/bDimG  via @PopSci    
    
    
    The First Shirt That Lowers Your Body Temperature http://pulse.me/s/bP3x1  via @PopSci    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    IRS pays billions in refunds to identity thieves http://pulse.me/s/bR4Mi     
    
    
    September 12 release of iPhone 5. http://m.blogs.computerworld.com/smartphones/20768/iphone-5-release-date-september-12-reports-claim?source=CTWNLE_nlt_wktop10_2012-08-03 …    
    
    
    Congress Shelves Cybersecurity Bill http://pulse.me/s/bY567     
    
    
    Rare New Form of Procrastination Identified http://pulse.me/s/c0hfJ  via @Inc    
    
    
    Surprise! iOS and Android printing gotchas | Mobile technology - InfoWorld http://pulse.me/s/c3Tm5     
    
    
    Review: 6 AirPrint solutions for iPhones and iPads (and Android) - InfoWorld http://pulse.me/s/c3IQi     
    
    
    @martinltpm Sounds like me #WhatIAmReading    
    
    
    Today’s Apps Gone Free: Unstoppable Fist, eSonar Pro, File Manager And More http://pulse.me/s/caH4l     
    
    
    11 More Wonderful Words With No English Equivalent http://zite.to/SeSPgK  via @zite    
    
    
    University of Georgia newspaper staff quits after non-student named editorial director http://zite.to/Ns60hX  via @zite    
    
    
    From @appadvice: SMS Security Hole Uncovered, One Not Fixed In iOS 6 http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/08/sms-security-hole-uncovered-one-not-fixed-in-ios-6/ …    
    
    
    Android malware threats triple to almost 15,000 in Q2 http://zite.to/OthZGf  via @zite    
    
    
    Ten hidden controls of the iPhone headphones http://zite.to/OCr19n  via @zite    
    
    
    A Major Secret Of The Brain Discovered http://zite.to/OCKmHB  via @zite    
    
    
    Cannabis and the Adolescent Brain http://zite.to/MDQf6c  via @zite    
    
    
    Swap Your Soap, Save Your Heart? http://zite.to/Nc7ffl  via @zite    
    
    
    War on Health: The FDA's Cult of Tyranny by Gary Null http://zite.to/NSa6y7  via @zite    
    
    
    10 Detachable iPhone Lenses for Mobile Photographers http://zite.to/PAN28F  via @zite #iPhone    
    
    
    iPhone 5 Specs Outed http://pulse.me/s/colYD  #iPhone    
    
    
    App Store iOS Deals & Free Applications For August 18, 2012 http://zite.to/PnAY9L  via @zite    
    
    
    Study: Less religious states give less to charity http://pulse.me/s/cqIwt  via @AP    
    
    
    Oovoo for Android and iPhone gains simultaneous four-way video chat http://www.theverge.com/2012/8/21/3256958/oovoo-android-iphone-simultaneous-four-way-video-chat-update …    
    
    
    What You Might Not Know About Your iPhone and iPad http://zite.to/OOKmii  via @zite    
    
    
    The Real Reason America's Schools Stink http://pulse.me/s/cq00Q     
    
    
    11worst companies to work for in the USA.  http://jobs.aol.com/articles/2012/08/14/the-11-worst-companies-to-work-for-in-america/?a_dgi=aolshare_linkedin …    
    
    
    60 Years of American Economic History, Told in 1 Graph - Atlantic Mobile http://zite.to/PFuh0d  via @zite    
    
    
    Samsung to owe over $1 Billion to Apple over patent violations. http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/08/jury-reaches-verdict-in-samsung-vs-apple-trial/ …    
    
    
    10 Great Salary Calculators to Save you Time http://lnkd.in/ia-pFW     
    
    
    Is it time for a major industry shift?
http://lnkd.in/ynUFw2     
    
    
    Why Are Trace Chemicals Showing Up in Umbilical Cord Blood? http://zite.to/NDNN1b  via @zite    
    
    
    Apple and Google are in talks to settle patent issues: Reuters http://www.theverge.com/2012/8/30/3280125/apple-google-tim-cook-larry-page-patent-talks …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: Why Did The FBI Have 12 Million Apple UDIDs On One Laptop? http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/09/why-did-the-fbi-have-12-million-apple-udids-on-one-laptop/ …    
    
    
    12 Million Apple User IDs Nabbed http://pulse.me/s/cYVTe  #FBI    
    
    
    Thieves cash in on mobile fraud http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-19519065 … http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-19519065 …    
    
    
    Broken on Purpose: Why Getting It Wrong Pays More Than Getting It Right http://prsm.tc/5qdxtW  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Columbus economy ranked 7th in U.S. http://www.bizjournals.com/columbus/news/2012/09/10/columbus-economy-ranked-7th-in-us.html?ana=twt …    
    
    
    What's Different About Apple's EarPods? http://pulse.me/s/dgHs3     
    
    
    Apple says Lightning to HDMI and Lightning to VGA adapters are on the way | The Verge http://pulse.me/s/dhAZ7     
    
    
    'Innocence of Muslims' producer's identity in question; actors say they were duped, overdubbed http://pulse.me/s/dfRTF     
    
    
    California man confirms role in production of anti-Islam film blamed for protests http://pulse.me/s/dfKRJ     
    
    
    The iPhone 5 Outscores the Galaxy S III [Benchmarks] http://pulse.me/s/dm9TH     
    
    
    And Now Let Us Gasp In Astonishment At What Just Happened To The Newspaper Business http://pulse.me/s/dkz0n  via @businessinsider    
    
    
    BII REPORT: How Our Mobile Behavior Is Evolving http://pulse.me/s/diVIh  via @businessinsider    
    
    
    These PCs [from China] Come Pre-Installed With All Your Favorite Malware [Malware] http://pulse.me/s/dkj77     
    
    
    Europe Gets Lightning to Micro USB Adapter [for iPhone 5] http://pulse.me/s/diMFz     
    
    
    The Warp Drive Could Become Science Fact : Discovery News http://zite.to/Pt5bCH  via @zite    
    
    
    Seattle cancer study: DNA can pass into woman's body from foetus before reaching brain http://bit.ly/QGiiQi  via @MailOnline    
    
    
    Want better results in face-to-face discussions with others? Put your cell phone out of sight. 
http://lnkd.in/gUCuTW     
    
    
    iOS 6 Tracks iPhone Users http://pulse.me/s/eg15G 
Here's how to stop it.    
    
    
    New In iOS 6: Create An Email Signature With Custom Clickable Links

http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/10/new-in-ios-6-create-an-email-signature-with-custom-clickable-links/ … http://appadvice.com/appnn/2012/10/new-in-ios-6-create-an-email-signature-with-custom-clickable-links/ …    
    
    
    FBI issues Android warning http://prsm.tc/Io32CS  via @prismatic    
    
    
    Incredible CSI-Like "Enhance!" App Fixes Your Unfocused Photos http://pulse.me/s/ewi3E     
    
    
        
    
    
    Google’s Chrome Remote Desktop Screen Sharing Service Comes Out Of Beta, Adds Real-Time Audio For Windows http://prsm.tc/3GlhW0     
    
    
    @AndreaVagas congrats! :)    
    
    
    Hey #PhoneReports a cool new name for the app would be Tweeet.    
    
    
    Five MIT Students Have Solved A Universally Annoying Problem http://pulse.me/s/gW825     
    
    
    Confessions of a Hotel Insider http://pulse.me/s/gTDkN     
    
    
    Most parents 'lie to children' http://pulse.me/s/hFO4I 
(And we wonder why kids learn to distrust their parents?)    
    
    
    Hey @PhoneReports a cool new name for the app would be Squeeter. (look up in Urban Dict.) :-)    
    
    
    Strong observations. As the economy improves, I expect to see mass migrations. 
http://lnkd.in/Wsuv3r     
    
    
    I wonder when #mailbox will support IBM AS/400 #Irrelevant #Friday #BeingSilly    
    
    
    Enjoying #mailbox app. If ability for rules based folder destination added, I’d never use Outlook again, @mailbox !    
    
    
    I have nothing to say. #hashtag    
    
    
    Holy Crap, This Insane 300 Foot Rope Swing Looks Like Heart Stopping Fun http://pulse.me/s/j0bNk     
    
    
    Why my shared links are no longer being seen by most of you. http://pulse.me/s/j9kjs     
    
    
    @RCoristin05 Congrats on the flowers!    
    
    
    @SeanMalarkey Lovely! #bootcamp    
    
    
    College is 6X higher today than in 1990. http://read.bi/WuVdYK     
    
    
    Does crime drop when immigrants move in? http://www.npr.org/2013/03/08/173642807/does-crime-drop-when-immigrants-move-in …    
    
    
    Department On Aging = DOA. Other acronyms to avoid. http://theweek.com/article/index/240787/10-acronyms-with-unintended-double-meanings …    
    
    
    LinkedIn to Buy Pulse Newsreader for More Than $50M http://pulse.me/s/jruU4     
    
    
    RT Fascinating story of CEO who dodged 9/11 tragedy and survived 2004 tsunami | http://bloom.bg/ZHTduX     
    
    
        
    
    
    RT FBI can't demand confidential customer records from telecommunication companies: federal judge | http://bloom.bg/YeyyhA  Civil rights!    
    
    
    @sbanwart I recall those days. #Daze #NoSleep #YoungKids    
    
    
    Top 10 Jankiest Life Hacks That Actually Work Wonders http://pulse.me/s/jAZfv     
    
    
        
    
    
    Yet another reminder that privacy is a bygone civil right thanks to the "Patriot" Act. Paranoid Government. http://pulse.me/s/jNThL     
    
    
    The Shocking Revelations About Secret Government TrapWire Spying Are [Apparently] True - http://pulse.me/s/jP5Q8     
    
    
    I love Dropbox because 1. iCloud Sync sux. 2. More iOS apps are integrated with it. 3. Easy to use. 4. Flexible. http://db.tt/HlEAZDVW     
    
    
    How A Tool For Perfect Human Vision Grew From One Of NASA's Greatest Blunders http://pulse.me/s/k10VJ     
    
    
    How to Be a 50-Plus Brain 'SuperAger' http://zite.to/10j7sWz  via @zite    
    
    
        
    
    
    A high efficiency 23-phase motor could revolutionize industry. http://www.drives.co.uk/fullstory.asp?id=3804 …    
    
    
    Obama's neglect of Civil Rights or Gov't accountability continues to haunt him. http://pulse.me/s/kpc5x     
    
    
    Skimming the Surface: The Return of Tesla's Surface Waves http://pulse.me/s/kpLD4     
    
    
    These Are The Last Words Of Another Kid Who Just Killed Himself By Texting While Driving http://pulse.me/s/kCvul     
    
    
    Newly Discovered Android Malware Was Downloaded Millions Of Times http://prsm.tc/8OMfFY  via @prismatic    
    
    
    High levels of lead found in imported rice from China.  http://cir.ca/story/us-rice-imports-contain-lead/all …    
    
    
    Can US Gov't block inventions that can disrupt the economy? Like maybe new energy saving devices? Maybe so.  http://cir.ca/story/us-patents-stalled-by-secrecy-orders/all …    
    
    
    The Most Well-Read Cities In America, According To Amazon (AMZN) http://pulse.me/s/l0nXY  Congrats, Cincinnati, you're #8!    
    
    
    18 Drawings You'll Swear Are Actual Photographs http://pulse.me/s/kZeNa     
    
    
    A 6-inch tall, 6-year-old skeleton confuses Stanford researchers and UFO conspiracists alike http://pulse.me/s/llPlw     
    
    
    Four Cybersecurity Breaches That Could Rattle The World http://pulse.me/s/lk0jb     
    
    
    The lying liars who lie about psychiatry http://zite.to/13gSzWY  via @zite    
    
    
    Another Facebook Trojan. Beware! - Microsoft warns of new Trojan hijacking Facebook accounts http://pulse.me/s/lAl9S     
    
    
    From @appadvice: BlackBerry Messenger Finally Coming To iOS And Android This Summer -- AppAdvice http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/05/blackberry-messenger-finally-coming-to-ios-and-android-this-summer …    
    
    
    Say goodbye to the Home Button on iPhone 6. http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/05/saying-goodbye-to-apples-iconic-home-button …    
    
    
    Nestle recalls DiGiorno, California Pizza Kitchen frozen pizzas http://cir.ca/s/7mV  via @Circa    
    
    
    Lipsticks found with carcinogens http://cir.ca/s/9mV  via @Circa    
    
    
    High Fructose Corn Syrup Addictive Like Cocaine, Says Researcher http://zite.to/10U9sms  via @zite    
    
    
    Scientists discover compound in marijuana that stops cancer. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/mobileweb/2012/09/19/marijuana-and-cancer_n_1898208.html …    
    
    
    From @appadvice: AT&T subtlety increases customer phone charge.  http://appadvice.com/appnn/2013/05/att-wants-customers-to-dig-a-little-deeper-each-month-for-phone-service …    
    
    
    Shortcuts every iPhone user needs to know.  - 13 Secret Features Hidden In Your iPhone (AAPL) http://pulse.me/s/m5q1L     
    
    
    Drug company pleads guilty to giving kickbacks to doctors http://cir.ca/s/uoW  via @Circa    
    
    
    Even roaches avoid corn syrup fructose. ;) http://cir.ca/s/voW  via @Circa    
    
    
    Study Links Exposure To Bug and Weed Killers and Higher Risk For Parkinson’s http://zite.to/13gDoLP  via @zite    
    
    
    Google explains more details than the NSA will admit.  - http://pulse.me/s/mvbnv     
    
    
    Fracking companies block data on health effects by sealing lawsuit settlements http://cir.ca/s/KrX  via @Circa    
    
    
    Reusable colonoscopy tools are unclean 3 out of 20 times http://cir.ca/s/7xX  via @Circa    
    
    
    As hepatitis A outbreak spreads, Costco offers free vaccine http://cir.ca/s/8xX  via @Circa    
    
    
    Give the Feds an inch, and they'll always take a mile. Every time, history has shown this.  http://www.technologyreview.com/news/515861/nsa-surveillance-reflects-a-broader-interpretation-of-the-patriot-act/?ref=rss&utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews …    
    
    
    Once again FDA ignores food safety, allows outrageous amounts of radiation in milk and meats. West Coast in trouble. http://www.forbes.com/sites/jeffmcmahon/2011/04/14/why-does-fda-tolerate-more-radiation-than-epa/ …    
    
    
    @drjekyll17 you’ve been hacked. Your account sent me SMS as well.    
    
    
    Graphs shows when major Online media companies were added to PRISM. http://www.wired.com/threatlevel/2013/06/yahoo-failed-fisa-fight/ …    
    
    
    Yep. pic.twitter.com/NvM2kdN7RT    
    
    
    NSA wire taps anyone they want; even Obama.  - http://pulse.me/s/n0MdG     
    
    
    "Legal" doesn't mean "constitutional". - http://pulse.me/s/n6pB2     
    
    
    Following an estimated 50,000 dead bumblebees, Oregon state officials temporarily restrict pesticide. http://cir.ca/s/pkZ     
    
    
    Germany is furious of US wiretapping of EU offices.  - http://pulse.me/s/nE05R     
    
    
        
    
    
    Facebook for Android sends your cell number to FB without even logging in.  - http://pulse.me/s/nE8sq     
    
    
    Two senators challenge NSA claimed effectiveness. http://www.businessinsider.com/wyden-and-udall-dont-believe-intelligence-officials-2013-7 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    35 Science 'Facts' That Are Totally Wrong http://read.bi/1cRPDSn     
    
    
    The beginning of the fall of ethical capitalism began in 1970. http://www.forbes.com/sites/stevedenning/2013/06/26/the-origin-of-the-worlds-dumbest-idea-milton-friedman/ …    
    
    
    Number of governments supporting domestic spying growing | http://bloom.bg/18y3mjS     
    
    
    Intelligence chief apologizes to Congress for lying. http://cir.ca/s/67Z     
    
    
    Vice President Joe Biden Railed Against NSA Domestic Spying In 2006 http://read.bi/18ASYYO     
    
    
    AT&T will start selling your smartphone browsing history if you don't Opt Out.  http://m.techcrunch.com/2013/07/05/att-considers-selling-your-browsing-history-location-and-more-to-advertisers-heres-how-to-opt-out/ …?    
    
    
    WARNING: Samsung's Spyware App used to deliver JayZ tunes.  http://appleinsider.com/articles/13/07/05/samsungs-free-jay-z-album-delivered-via-android-spyware-app …    
    
    
    Privacy does not need to be sacrificed for protection. Big Brother FAIL. - http://pulse.me/s/nSYw7     
    
    
        
    
    
    Drinking cow milk may do more harm than good to people's health. http://drhyman.com/blog/2013/07/05/got-proof-lack-of-evidence-for-milks-benefits/ …    
    
    
    AT&T will start selling your smartphone browsing information. To opt out, go here: https://cprodx.att.com/cmp/cmpa/manage.jsp …    
    
    
    TV Station Makes Excruciating Error, Reads 4 Wrong Names Of Asiana Crash Pilots Including 'Sum Ting Wong' And 'Ho Lee Fuk'    
    
    
        
    
    
    World's oldest lunar calendar found in Scotland, 10,000 years old. http://cir.ca/s/w2a     
    
    
    Cashiers, NC. http://instagram.com/p/b-IOpQuck_/     
    
    
    750 million cell phones may have outdated SIM card security that could lead to stolen identities and false char... - http://pulse.me/s/omU8K     
    
    
    Google’s $35 Chromecast lets you beam video from ‘any device’ to your TV | VentureBeat http://venturebeat.com/2013/07/24/chromecast-lets-you-beam-video-from-android-and-ios-to-your-tv/#.UfEDxoAcqrM.twitter …    
    
    
    Feds want your passwords? Where's the search warrant? - http://pulse.me/s/ozQbh     
    
    
        
    
    
    Man comes back to life after flatlining for 45 minutes http://cir.ca/s/HQe     
    
    
    Oldest rock art in North America found in Nevada by archaeologists, dating more than 10,000 years. http://cir.ca/s/JQe     
    
    
    Autism risk linked to induced and augmented labor. http://cir.ca/s/KQe     
    
    
    The Link Between Narcissism And Wealth? http://read.bi/12KqGXM     
    
    
    The DEA Pays AT&T For Real-Time Access To 26 Years Of Phone Records http://read.bi/15yp9RG     
    
    
    Almost seems state corruption grade is proportional to closeness to D.C. http://read.bi/19fI9bM     
    
    
    The world's Big Brother has arrived.  - http://pulse.me/s/pQq8H     
    
    
    Give them an inch and they always take a mile.  - PATRIOT Act Author  The NSA Is Actively Violating The Law http://pulse.me/s/q03u2     
    
    
    BlackBerry Messenger for iOS coming soon? A little too late, BlackBerry. - http://pulse.me/s/q1Inf     
    
    
    QuickOffice is FREE! - Google makes QuickOffice free  gives away 10 GB in Drive storage http://pulse.me/s/qsZV7     
    
    
        
    
    
    In 1961  the US almost detonated two nuclear bombs over North Carolina by accident http://pulse.me/s/qxmpt     
    
    
    Haunted House Reactions Are Back   and Funnier Than Ever http://pulse.me/s/qPEeT     
    
    
    This Magic Projection Box Will Melt Your Brain http://pulse.me/s/qR2kl     
    
    
    http://www.imore.com/top-5-secret-ios-7-gestures-how-get-more-done-faster …    
    
    
    Money Saving Phone Calls  How to Negotiate Down Your APR http://pulse.me/s/rIcht     
    
    
    Facebook Removing Option To Be Unsearchable By Name  Highlighting Lack Of Universal Privacy Controls http://pulse.me/s/rQMWM     
    
    
    Moo. pic.twitter.com/jjz6uH9zYI    
    
    
    Excellent trend charts across 7 centuries. http://www.businessinsider.com/700-years-of-data-in-12-must-see-charts-2013-10?utm_content=buffer4c52c&utm_source=buffer&utm_medium=facebook&utm_campaign=Buffer …    
    
    
    http://www.businessinsider.com/easy-ways-to-lose-weight-2013-10?utm_source=buffer&utm_campaign=Buffer&utm_content=bufferd5c3b&utm_medium=facebook …    
    
    
    Who makes your fav beer? - Who Actually Owns Your Favorite Beers http://pulse.me/s/vzmDV     
    
    
    China Is Openly Discussing How To Nuke The US http://www.businessinsider.com/china-wants-to-nuke-the-us-2013-11 … via @bi_contributors    
    
    
    http://www.buzzfeed.com/peggy/mind-blowing-tricks-every-iphone-and-ipad-user-should-kno …    
    
    
    Flashlight app caught collecting and selling user data http://pulse.me/s/IgSqs     
    
    
    http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/12/whos-hiring-and-who-isnt-in-five-charts/ …    
    
    
    China successfully lands spacecraft on Moon http://pulse.me/s/Jqahk     
    
    
        
    
    
    Millions of Plastic Microbeads from Specialty Soap Have Contaminated the Great Lakes and Damaging Health. http://pulse.me/s/Jr5Vv     
    
    
    Accurate comparison of healthcare costs is complex, but the facts indicate Americans are being gouged.  http://www.upworthy.com/his-first-4-sentences-are-interesting-the-5th-blew-my-mind-and-made-me-a-little-sick-2?c=reccon1 …    
    
    
    The NSA Actually Intercepted Packages to Put Backdoors in Electronics http://pulse.me/s/JJQNM     
    
    
    NSA reportedly intercepting laptops purchased online to install spy malware http://pulse.me/s/JIny4     
    
    
    