The culture you join: make sure it's a match. “@beki70: Collegiality in the Workplace http://wp.me/phSsV-Sl ”    
    
    
    Meeting faculty @Penn: Fox, Foster and Ungar. And having lunch w/ WiCS and dinner w/ SWE students. Love being on campus! #yahoolabs    
    
    
    #accessibility “@yahooaccess: Check out updated Voice Search app for iPhone from @YahooSearch, now with awesome...: http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/yahoo!-search/id361071600?mt=8 …”    
    
    
    Treat it like your 'best' paper! “@diazf_y: last few hours before paper submission deadline: read the whole thing...  at least four times.”    
    
    
    Best ad: I'd vote for Clint.    
    
    
    #yahoo a proud sponsor! “@SCSatCMU: What the hack: CMU students seek hackers at this weekend's #TartanHacks, http://bit.ly/yybYDg ”    
    
    
    Scientific leadership: “@YahooJobs: 2 of 5 Best Paper nominations at WSDM2012 go to #yahoolabs http://bit.ly/wRyIT0  #WSDM2012”    
    
    
    Still has great promise: “@MIT_CSAIL: What do you think about the future of AI? http://ow.ly/8UniN ”    
    
    
    #hacku In your spare time... “@egoodman: Berkeley History needs help breaking a code in a Civil War-era diary. Do it. http://bit.ly/wMlxXN ”    
    
    
    Accessibility an issue for Gdocs: Columbia University excludes Google Docs http://www.zdnet.com/blog/igeneration/columbia-university-excludes-google-docs/15155 …    
    
    
    Yahoo!'s Content Optimization and Relevance Engine (C.O.R.E.) creates 13 million story combos a day. http://visualize.yahoo.com/core/  #Yvisualized    
    
    
    "@informor: Nice move, Yahoo!, show some value, communicate huge traction. http://visualize.yahoo.com/core/  (via @ayman, @fkschmidt)";-)    
    
    
    In CA for Science Week - attending workshops and talks by brilliant #yahoolabs scientists.    
    
    
    Hey @Predictalot: When will Elections markets be open?    
    
    
    #hacku “@ydn: RT @bluesmoon: The source for yslow is open on github: http://yhoo.it/zOpKXm  Thanks Marcel and team.  #wpo #performance”    
    
    
    “@ayman: Nice, more neat data fun: http://clues.yahoo.com/ ” #hacku #bigdata #yahoolabs    
    
    
    #accessibility “@gvucenter: BrailleTouch Helps Visually Impaired Users http://fb.me/QzeewznO ”    
    
    
    @eegilbert Let us know the air time and/or link. Look forward to listening!    
    
    
    Looking forward to flying this! “@CBSNews: Boeing's 787 Dreamliner: Flying the friendlier skies (via @CBSSunday) http://bit.ly/Atqphe ”    
    
    
    Sounds like #yahoolabs :-) “@yardi: ... + social scientists... :) RT @fortnow: Why the world needs computer scientists http://bit.ly/Ac1GBl ”    
    
    
    @jakehofman Wishing you so much joy... and a little sleep ;-)    
    
    
    John Nash to NSA: "As ciphers become more sophisticated.. cipher breaking by skilled teams <goes away>" I wish. http://www.nsa.gov/public_info/_files/nash_letters/nash_letters1.pdf …    
    
    
    Read the Wiki article, signed the petition. Bad bill. Oppose HR3699, the Research Works Act http://wh.gov/K25     
    
    
    Made me look ;-) “@pennockd: I have to admit the #BMW takeover ad on http://yahoo.com  right now is pretty awesome”    
    
    
    @eegilbert finds a decoder ring for email rank graph Via @nprnews: Researcher Decodes Workplace Rank From Emails http://n.pr/xnBXzv     
    
    
    TV on the web: Yahoo leading with data-based programming. http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052970204883304577223630028525366.html?mod=WSJ_hp_LEFTTopStories …    
    
    
    Cool. @yahooaccessibility, see: “@asbruckman: Accessibility chair for #cscw2013 will be @derrickcogburn! Send ideas, we'll be accessible!”    
    
    
    #hacku #yahoo “@gtcomputing: Come to the Yahoo! @hacku Kickoff Thurs, 6-8 pm in Klaus 1443  http://ow.ly/9dPdT  via @gtacm” @gtcomputing    
    
    
    Congrats Etsy! “@chaddickerson: huge welcome to @rasmus, who is joining the @etsy engineering team full-time.”    
    
    
    In ATL for visit to  @gtcomputing. Faculty meetings and our great #HackU  event. Bring it!    
    
    
    And we're off! #HackU underway at @gtcomputing with 20+ teams. Go Jackets: Go! Hack! Win!    
    
    
    And, on the other side of the pond: “@ydn: RT @andycobley: Many thanks to @ydn for kicking off #HackU at @DundeeUniv, briliant job !”    
    
    
    Hacking Jackets. Just getting started - great minds at work! #hacku #gtcomputing pic.twitter.com/nCxbnIRD    
    
    
    Hey #hacku hackers: can you fix this? “@TechCrunch:New Android Malware Uses Facebook To Spread http://tcrn.ch/xfTyc2  by @sarahintampa”    
    
    
    You can't hack on an empty stomach - Chik-Fil-A is served in KACB 2443. Come and get it! #hacku @gtcomputing    
    
    
    Twitter is the perfect muse for a hack idea. Spend 20 minutes drinking from the firehose, grab a Red Bull and start coding! #hacku @gtacm    
    
    
    I have a black Nike golf cap w/ Yahoo! logo - will trade for a Google or Facebook cap. @gtacm See me in Klaus 1116 before 11:30am. #hacku    
    
    
    It's #hacku Hadiku time. Best haiku posted by @gtcomputing hacker in Klaus 1116 before noon gets a cool pair of Yahoo! earbuds.    
    
    
    My BurmaShave ode to #hacku. Got a cool idea... That'll change the world... Just one damn bug... Let's give it a whirl. HackU    
    
    
    Hey @gtacm hackers - when you finish your hacks, be sure to check out our internship openings: http://bit.ly/Aq5lmn  #hacku #gtcomputing    
    
    
    We're up to 21 hacks and counting as we count down the final half hour of @gtcomputing #hacku 2012!    
    
    
    @TheMarco Glad you could join us - hope to see you on campus again soon. See if you can bring some hiring reqs next time!    
    
    
    Opportunity for AI, or any intelligence. “@danariely: United States' economy: Over-regulated America http://econ.st/wNWWWQ ”    
    
    
    Key is focus on people. Takes commitment, vision, passion. “@WittedNote:long-horizon research require monopoly? http://nyti.ms/wigq59 ”    
    
    
    Congrats to the #hacku winners from @gtcomputing! Full list: http://developer.yahoo.com/hacku/show/2012/feb/gt … CodeBook by Daniel Hooper took the top prize. More soon!    
    
    
    Yahoo! on Campus - a blog is born. Here's the opening post, with many more since. http://shar.es/gYALp     
    
    
    So true: networking and reputation rule. “@YahooJobs: Your Reputation Is Your Résumé http://bit.ly/A6wSRv  #resume #careers #edu”    
    
    
    At UMass CS talk by @5harad from #yahoolabs on Computational Social Science. A full house! pic.twitter.com/0GT90rcz    
    
    
    As one of the first #ofoto users, this is sad. But here we go, Shutterfly. “@news999: Kodak Sells Online Business... http://yhoo.it/wp0jHG ”    
    
    
    Great talk Monday @UMD: "No Free Lunch in Data Privacy",Ashwin Machanavajjhala - Yahoo! Research, 11am 4172 AVW.    
    
    
    @informor @yardi @eegilbert Looking forward to seeing you all at the talk on Weds!    
    
    
    Attention grad students: Proposals due Friday! Yahoo! Key Scientific Challenges Program 2012 http://shar.es/gEy3w     
    
    
    Congrats to all the hackers.! “@Yahoo_On_Campus: New blog post: Hack U™ 2012 at Georgia Tech http://www.yoncampusblog.com/blog/2012/03/06/hack-u-2012-at-georgia-tech/ …”    
    
    
    Still my fave. “@Yahoo: Happy 100th birthday, Oreo! http://yhoo.it/yvEcGE  ...created March 6, 1912 in a Manhattan bakery.”    
    
    
    Working to connect great scientists with remarkable research. Looking for unique opportunities.    
    
    
    Duke InCube Students Visit Yahoo! http://shar.es/gTFF4  Thanks @jhubert and team!    
    
    
    Data science needs media mgmt “@pennmkse: Why open science failed after the gulf oil spill http://goo.gl/mag/2oxCe  - zives”    
    
    
    The Yahoo! purple truck is going to roll at UCLA Tuesday – Y!STAR donation and reception http://shar.es/p1Iec     
    
    
    Some friends of mine get to play the prisioners delimma. What would Nash do?    
    
    
    Hack was at Yahoo! before FB was. Ref: @chaddickerson Facebook, hackathons for advertisers too http://bit.ly/AF43Ls  via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    Some truck! “@Yahoo_On_Campus: New blog post: Y!STAR donation at UCLA - happening now http://www.yoncampusblog.com/blog/2012/03/13/ystar-donation-at-ucla-happening-now/ …”    
    
    
    #pennapps “@ted_drake: Hack the Change: Solve real problems this weekend in Philadelphia  http://hackthechange.com/  @YDN @RandomHacks #HackU #in”    
    
    
    Big data + Sports: Matheletes rule: In Relentless Jocks-Nerds War, Hope For Peace Through Analytics  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    “@GTRI: Hey...it's Pi day everyone!  3.14” So, go run the Pi Mile at Tech @gtcomputing    
    
    
    To Hack Master @jhubert: Good luck and keep in touch! #hacku    
    
    
    Cool, @jhubert. More great #hacku on campus coming up!    
    
    
    Creative people (that includes coders) have to push through initial ineptness. Thoughtful post: http://www.raptitude.com/2012/03/why-your-work-disappoints-you/ … via @jellyfish    
    
    
    “@duncanjwatts: Social contagion: What do we really know?: http://poptech.org/e1_duncan_watts  via @AddThis” #yahoolabs    
    
    
    You will be missed. Keep the research light aglow. “@WittedNote: Farewell @YahooLabs it was a fantastic ride. Hello @google”    
    
    
    Spreading some purple cheer: Yahoo! Visits With Berkeley Women In Business http://yhoo.it/zRveEL  via @ydn    
    
    
    Congratulations! “@yardi: new GaTech Interactive Computing and CS School Chairs are Annie Antón and @fortnow. http://bit.ly/GBgWo8 ”    
    
    
    “@UTCompSci: UTCS Students- @Yahoo! 24 hour #HackU competition begins tomorrow at 12:30pm. Prizes! Food! Giveaways! http://bit.ly/yah032312 ”    
    
    
    #hacku at @UTCompSci this weekend. Cool ideas will come to life.  https://mobile.twitter.com/Yahoo_On_Campus/status/182916809559785473?photo=1 …    
    
    
    @gtcomputing Hey, what's the good word? “@YahooJobs: Front end Engineer for our #Atlanta Campus http://bit.ly/GIetnk ”    
    
    
    @yahoo is hacking with students @UTCompSci and @HackUindia this weekend. “@saurabhsahni giving a talk on Y! BOSS at #HackU, #IITKGP”    
    
    
    Hack should bridge, not divide. “@catehstn: Fantastic article on the whole squoot thing - women are not perks - http://dld.bz/bfZ4Y ”    
    
    
    Honoring a great mind. “@CSNewsUpdate: David L. Waltz, Computer Science Pioneer, Dies at 68 - New York Times http://bit.ly/GZj9Zs ”    
    
    
    @landay of interest? “@FreeTheFeross: GLIIMPSE, a smooth transition between markup code and rendered documents http://j.mp/GOrFtS ”    
    
    
    Not your grandma's craft: Sewing evolves from home-ec into home engineering. http://boingboing.net/2012/03/22/sewing.html …    
    
    
    Live to code: Hacker Culture: The Key To Future Prosperity? http://techcrunch.com/2012/03/25/hacker-culture-the-key-to-future-prosperity/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    Never give up - inspiring TED talk. Regina Dugan: From mach-20 glider to humming bird drone http://on.ted.com/B9Iq  #TED    
    
    
    Nice video. Impressive. #accessibility “@google: Our friend Steve takes a memorable test ride in a self-driving car http://goo.gl/OuFEM ”    
    
    
    “@Yahoo_On_Campus: Attn Rutgers students: @YahooLabs Research Scientist @ayman Shamma speaks 4/4. pic.twitter.com/ZHFqL1o6 #YRSMS #yahoo #fb ”    
    
    
    Good stuff! @pennapps @gtcomputing “@ydn: Hack Event Survival Guide by @Ted_Drake http://www.tdrake.net/hack-event-survival-guide/ … @RandomHacks”    
    
    
    A little mental exercise before vegging out on the weekend: How to multiply numbers in your head: http://www.decisionsciencenews.com/2012/03/29/how-to-multiply-numbers-in-your-head/ … #funwithmath    
    
    
    An important conference coming up in Beijing. Really. http://nfc03.nokiaresearch.com/CRAP2012/cfp.pdf …    
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs: On Campus, all the time... “@ayman: Heading to @DrewUniversity today to give a talk to the CS Department!”    
    
    
    New fuel for mobile app developers and hackers: “@ydn: Yahoo!’s Mojito is Now Open Source: http://yhoo.it/HDTtA3 ”    
    
    
    Duncan Watts speaking at CMU to a full house. Topic: "Doing Social Science on the Web" #yahoolabs pic.twitter.com/KfXeazld    
    
    
    @ayman speaking at Rutgers #YRSMS seminar to a SRO packed room. Thanks @informor! pic.twitter.com/F9pn5AKh    
    
    
    <rush rush, scramble scramble>    
    
    
    Brilliance Blazing on Campus: Congratulations to the 2012 Yahoo! Labs Key Scientific Challenge Award Recipients http://www.yoncampusblog.com/blog/2012/04/10/yahoo-honors-future-thought-leaders-through-key-scientific-challenges-program/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hackathon @ Tufts. Good to see the hack fun spreading  http://www.tuftsdaily.com/mobile/tufts-computer-science-students-to-host-university-s-first-hackathon-1.2729202 …    
    
    
    @inaudiblewords looks like a hack for LinkedIn. Agree the title is unfortum    
    
    
    Way to go Eric! MT “@gtcomputing: Professor @eegilbert tries to transcend #socialmedia “Slacktivism” http://dthin.gs/J9nPLq  via @GeorgiaTech”    
    
    
    Air Graffiti mentioned here. Invented in late 90s in @ronbrachman lab. "AT&T Aims to Avoid Opening ..."  http://allthingsd.com/20120419/att-aims-to-avoid-opening-can-of-worms-as-it-opens-up-its-network/?mod=atdtweet …    
    
    
    Go @gtcomputing! Hacking for security - cool. Students chow down on cyber security weaknesses http://wp.me/p1zvth-1Ss  #hacku    
    
    
    At Penn for great Machine Learning symposium honoring Vapnik. Talks by Kearns, Scapire, Jordan. Stimulating!    
    
    
    Good stuff. I like #8! 8 Core Beliefs of Extraordinary Bosses http://www.inc.com/geoffrey-james/8-core-beliefs-of-extraordinary-bosses.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    Beam me up Scottie! “@mashabletech: Space Shuttle Enterprise to Fly to NYC Today - http://on.mash.to/ICyelo  via @spacedotcom”    
    
    
    @duncanjwatts Will miss the lunchtime brainstorms. Good luck!    
    
    
    A pretty goid catch, indeed. #goodnews http://espn.go.com/espn/story/_/id/7849214/rockies-pitcher-twitter-friendship …    
    
    
    Pearls from Crockford, including "I think every programmer should work in customer support for [their] product." http://coding.smashingmagazine.com/2012/04/27/yahoos-doug-crockford-on-javascript/ …    
    
    
    Attn @UCIbrenICS Hear @YahooLabs scientist Lihong Li talk Mon 5/7 1pm, Bren 4011. Snacks? Sure. Science? You bet! http://bit.ly/IxbsgP     
    
    
    UMass CS annual outstanding achievement each year build community across generations. This year I am honored by their …http://lnkd.in/bt6vT2     
    
    
    And the original: #hacku http://developer.yahoo.com/hacku  Best Practices for Hackathon Demo Days http://techcrunch.com/2012/05/05/putting-plans-to-work-best-practices-for-hackathon-demo-days/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    #yahoolabs scientist Elad Yom-Tov speaks at Xerox PARC 5/17 on using the internet for medical research. http://www.parc.com/event/1711/why-the-internet-is-sometimes-better-than-the-real-world-for-medical-research.html …    
    
    
    Today @UCIbrenICS hear #YahooLabs scientist Lihong Li speak on Machine Learning, 1pm, Bren 4011    
    
    
    @lreyzin Good luck up North, stay in touch! I'm impressed with the program and people at UIC. As a GA native, I share your views of ATL.    
    
    
    @lreyzin Yahoo! committed to Y! Labs w/ Research. Ron now head of Labs, we're rebuilding/refocusing on biz plus academic outreach.    
    
    
    Attention UW Students: @YahooLabs scientist Ricardo Baeza-Yates speaks Monday 5/14 at 3:30pm, CSE 405 @csenews    
    
    
    Proud of our Emily as she graduates from @DukeMEMPCareer with her MEM degree. Onward!    
    
    
    Awesome tribute to a Mom on this Mother's Day weekend.  http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424052702304070304577398062395398318.html?mod=e2tw …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @fkschmidt: Attention UW Students: @YahooLabs scientist Ricardo Baeza-Yates speaks today at 3:30pm, CSE 405 @csenews    
    
    
    Great opportunities for research scientists to create new science with big data. @YahooLabs is hiring - it's a new world!    
    
    
    Preview: @YahooLabs looking for Research Scientists and Postdoctoral Researchers in new Mobile Innovations Group. Job ad link coming.    
    
    
    @bitly @hmason Congratulations to bit.ly. Lots of new features in this release - much more than 'just a coat of paint'!    
    
    
    “@EPrinceton: FCC names members of its Open Internet Advisory Committee, including Jen Rexford http://www.broadcastingcable.com/article/485192-Comcast_Exec_Among_FCC_s_Open_Internet_Monitors.php …” Congrats Jen!    
    
    
    Talk @Stanford 5/30: Social Computing and User Generated Content: A Game-theoretic Approach, Arpita Ghosh, 4:30PM, Y2E2, room 101    
    
    
    TODAY Talk @Stanford: Social Computing and User Generated Content: A Game-theoretic Approach, Arpita Ghosh, 4:30PM, Y2E2, room 101    
    
    
    Congrats all! “@benbendc: BIG NEWS! Nick @Feamster and Marshini Chetty @ineffablicious are joining #UMD faculty in CS and #i_UMD #HCIL”    
    
    
    The next big thing? Higher Education's Online Revolution http://on.wsj.com/LHzn8l     
    
    
    @Miraglia Congratulations!    
    
    
    It's D Day. Nothing on the news during the day - why? Remember the fallen, thank a Vet.    
    
    
    “@sympapadopoulos: Great talk by @ayman A fresh look into social signals as a means to understand content #ICMR2012 @YahooLabs ”    
    
    
    Cool job! “@YahooJobs: front end Engineer for #flickr http://bit.ly/L7Ja8F  & work with @ysaw @rossharmes & @schill #javascript #html5”    
    
    
    Same here, way to go! “@arnabdotorg: @winteram congrats!”    
    
    
    @dsweld @lazowska Congratulations, great to know Ben Taskar is joining UW CSE ! @YahooLabs looks forward to more collaborations.    
    
    
    Nice, what's next? “@gvucenter: Enron e-mail study by @eegilbert shows how gossip flows in cyberspace. Video: http://ow.ly/buI0P ”    
    
    
    Ah. The 5th screen is a reality. “@TechCrunch: Siri ... Gets 'Eyes Free' Car Integration http://tcrn.ch/LE7Biq  by @chrisvelazco”    
    
    
    This field created by @yahoolabs in '08: “@techreview: The New Science of Computational Advertising http://techre.vu/N9JdqH ”    
    
    
    Webinar - TODAY! “@YahooJobs: MT @yuilibrary: Open Hours Thursday with @caridy and @ekashida talking about Y! Axis, http://bit.ly/M3Zp5D ”    
    
    
    My college notes, books and Algol numerical methods printouts head to the recycle bin. #fb #in pic.twitter.com/2eqIhCaP    
    
    
    Clever little machine. MT @UTCompSci: Google will release a new Doodle for Alan Turing's 100th birthday on Saturday. http://www.google.com.au/ .”    
    
    
    Great jobs, fun culture still @yahoo “@YahooJobs: Summer 2012 Intern Welcome Event!    http://bit.ly/LoB7rD  it was a great event”    
    
    
    Listening to Sir Roger Penrose's invited talk at the Alan Turing Centenary Conference in Manchester, UK http://www.turing100.manchester.ac.uk/index.php/conference/conference/livestream … #turing100    
    
    
    @YahooLabs is looking for big thinkers: Machine Learning Applied Scientist https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/yahoo_global_cs/jobdetail.ftl … @YahooJobs    
    
    
    @YahooLabs job: Applied Scientist, Pricing/Marketplaces. Come create new internet marketplaces https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/yahoo_global_cs/jobdetail.ftl … @YahooJobs    
    
    
    From the career services office to social media: 35% students use LinkedIn for job search.  http://blog.linkedin.com/2012/06/27/top-companies-students/ …    
    
    
    Great advice for great leaders.  http://m.inc.com/?incid=42834     
    
    
    Pentagon Digs In on Cyberwar Front http://on.wsj.com/M7Z1ob     
    
    
    @pennmkse details here: http://cbsn.ws/NtqNyN     
    
    
    Wow - our daughter just completed the Seattle-to-Portland event... On a mountain bike.  Way to go, Carlee!    
    
    
    “@arnabdotorg: Signing off from Twitter for the next day while my entire stream talks about nothing but Marissa Mayer.”    
    
    
    Mike Krzyzewski for his country: 'The ultimate honor' http://usat.ly/OKKuib  via USA TODAY "There are times when you have to feel."    
    
    
    About time some truth came out on this. Vint Cerf tells Internet history revisionists to shove it http://news.yahoo.com/vint-cerf-tells-internet-history-revisionists-shove-210542455.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    Explanation of the great recession of 2018: Jeb Hensarling: Dodd-Frank's Unhappy Anniversary http://on.wsj.com/OjNSEk     
    
    
    Might be a good time to sign up for Yahoo! Instant Messenger “@mashabletech: Google Talk Is Down For Most Users - http://on.mash.to/MIj42c ”    
    
    
    Well said: "It's the students and the cards": @beki70: On Not Leaving Academia http://wp.me/phSsV-VR ”    
    
    
    @mashabletech    
    
    
    Smooth-Talking Hacker Remote-Wipes Reporter's iPad, MacBook http://lnkd.in/bQwecz     
    
    
    Add this to #intonow. End of Channel Surfing? http://on.wsj.com/OI29J2     
    
    
    Achint Thomas gives a talk to Yahoo! Interns http://shar.es/vFfTP  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @yahoolabs is hiring! Applied Scientist, Pricing & Marketplaces https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/jobdetail.ftl?job=34781&lang=en&sns_id=twitter#.UC2OASTHFFR.twitter …    
    
    
    @hmason Why doesn't your aunt like Yahoo!? How can I help? We do care about our customers.    
    
    
    @yahoolabs is hiring: Research Scientist, HCI Research group https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/jobdetail.ftl?job=32101&lang=en&sns_id=twitter#.UC5ASEVusjU.twitter … #li    
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs: actively hiring research scientists. Here's one of many openings in NL, NLP, Statistics, Mobile, Systems …http://lnkd.in/4gsBDW     
    
    
    Also @yahoolabs, with scientist openings around the world. Exciting future! “@ydn: .@Yahoo is hiring!  http://bit.ly/RklhTD  via @YUILibrary”    
    
    
    Great article. Congrats colleagues! “@MSFTResearch: The Big Apple's Big Data advantage... http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2012/08/20/the-big-apples-big-data-advantage/ … via @FortuneMagazine”    
    
    
    Come join the quest @yahoolabs: Research Scientist, Machine Learning https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/jobdetail.ftl?job=36579&lang=en&sns_id=more …    
    
    
    Come grow with us! @YahooLabs: Research Scientist, Machine Learning https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/yahoo_global_cs/jobdetail.ftl?job=1247352 …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has openings for Research Engineers in the US: http://bit.ly/PAYHRi  and in Haifa: http://bit.ly/O1pl4r  . Check it out!    
    
    
    Moving into our new home. “@YahooLabs: Mimosa Monday in Yahoo! Labs Sunnyvale! pic.twitter.com/pBuWapZ1”    
    
    
    Gotta be BigDog #ipto RT @DARPA: #DARPA Big Dog nominated for @RobotHallofFame. Which robot will you vote for? http://ow.ly/d7xzW     
    
    
    Sleep? RT @mheadd: Eat. Sleep. Code. @PennApps is back. http://2012f.pennapps.com/  #Philly #Hacking #OpenData #hacku    
    
    
    Hack @PennApps today, build @Yahoo tomorrow! MT This Fall's PennApps is Sept 14-16. Make sure to sign up! http://fb.me/C7FwQ4Ze  #ydn #hacku    
    
    
    @YahooLabs is hiring scientists around the world. Researching, creating and building cool products! http://bitly.com/bundles/o_3oarn3v6oh/1 …    
    
    
    @Yahoo will be there! RT @GTRI: Join us for the Hungry, Hungry Hackers cyber security competition Aug. 25 http://www.hungryhungryhackers.org     
    
    
    @informor Check out the *several* openings in @yahoolabs worldwide! http://bitly.com/bundles/o_3oarn3v6oh/1 … More coming soon, NYC Lab has room to grow ;-)    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has the science, solutions and insights to create new products. And we are hiring: http://bit.ly/SIAImm     
    
    
    @asbruckman Sounds like an email diode to me.    
    
    
    CRA's Grad Cohort: great event for female PhD students who are just starting. https://www.facebook.com/groups/58020017457/ … @YahooLabs proud to sponsor!    
    
    
    More great news... RT @allthingsd: Yahoo Hires Former Amazon Exec Kathy Savitt as Marketing Head -by @triciad http://dthin.gs/SKiHnQ     
    
    
    So true! MT @benbendc Kleinberg: "I realized computer science is not just about technology, it is also a human topic" http://www.nature.com/news/computational-social-science-making-the-links-1.11243 …    
    
    
    MT @gtcomputing: Photo: ...student creation in the student org's room http://on.fb.me/PQoxRo  Another creative use for @Yahoo faceplant balls    
    
    
    Great advice. RT @FastCoDesign: Finally: A superclean bike light that attaches with magnets http://bit.ly/SRZO3S     
    
    
    Great Labor Day Manifesto. "We strive to: http://edgeperspectives.typepad.com/edge_perspectives/2012/09/the-labor-day-manifesto-of-the-passionate-creative-worker.html …"    
    
    
    Research Scientist openings at Yahoo! Labs - come invent the future in ML, NLP, MM, Mobile, Systems and more! http://bitly.com/bundles/o_3oarn3v6oh/2 …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs is hiring: Applied Scientist, Pricing & Marketplaces https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/jobdetail.ftl?job=34781&lang=en&sns_id=twitter#.UEd1pmP0Mwk.twitter …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has the science, solutions and insights to create new products. And we are hiring: http://bit.ly/SIAImm     
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs: Seeking Great Scientists http://lnkd.in/SNY-Jh  http://lnkd.in/bGiNXJ     
    
    
    OK, props to the creators of today's Google doodle. Beam me up, Scottie!    
    
    
    In memory of the fallen on 9/11. Never forget: Twin Towers: Their legacy in New York City signs http://flic.kr/s/aHsjw8yEy1     
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs: We're hiring! These are for Content and Personalization. http://bit.ly/S4TcJS , http://bit.ly/Rz0ZF4     
    
    
    A cool, clear, calm morning in NJ. Exactly as it was 11 years ago. Remember the fallen, comfort the survivors. Never forget    
    
    
    Hey @PennApps - @Yahoo is stoked to see so many coming to Philly this weekend. What will you build using YUI, YDN?  http://yhoo.it/SFIWP0     
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs: Seeking Great Scientists http://shar.es/u78dH  via @sharethis    
    
    
    When you're done with @PennApps, head over to #HackRU at Rutgers on October 13th. It's going to be awesome! http://hackru.org/  @ru_usacs    
    
    
    How to run the  best hackathon. By @PennApps. Most awesome! Final Day Logistics http://tmblr.co/ZPVkJuTMS4JV     
    
    
    Nothing new to #cameroncrazies @dukeblueplanet MT @WSJ: Ever heard of 'tifo'? Well, it's spreading in America. http://on.wsj.com/PyJumz     
    
    
    Hearing demos from 15+ API providers @PennApps Over 12 universities from VA to MI to MA plus local. 300+ hackers. #hacku    
    
    
    Full house @PennApps for API demos. pic.twitter.com/x1LHfo72    
    
    
    Let the hack demos begin. Over 90 of them. Awesome! @PennApps #hacku @ydn    
    
    
    MT@PennApps: For those not in Hall of Flags - #PennApps livestream is up at http://www.ustream.tv/channel/pennapps-demos … - check it out! #hacku @ydn    
    
    
    @yahoo award for best mobile hack @PennApps goes to Perimeter. I want that! #hacku    
    
    
    @PennApps winners of "Best Mobile Hack" - Perimeter from @umich Congrats! pic.twitter.com/0XHUqr2S    
    
    
    This Electioneering hack is well done and timely - and gets  the @yahoo runner up prize: cool swag. #PennApps #hacku http://www.electioneering.us/     
    
    
    @MaxScheiber @TeddyGuenin @jeffgrimes9 @asgoel Hi Max and team - OK if I ship everything to Jeff? He gave me his address.    
    
    
    MT @PennApps: PennApps Winners - The list of all winners is below (you can see the list of proj… http://tmblr.co/ZPVkJuTdH-qg  #hacku #pennapps    
    
    
    @hmason Hey thanks Hilary - we agree with your comment and are working on it.    
    
    
    Happy Belated Birthday, Smiley! 9/19, the Emoticon Turns 30 :-) - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2012/09/today-the-emoticon-turns-30/262571/#.UFsFuyc3Hdg.twitter …    
    
    
    @paytango @pennapps mention: “@mashabletech: Swipe no more? @Venmo's Andrew @Kortina talks mobile payments - http://on.mash.to/S7U6cV ”    
    
    
    From India: "Yahoo! Internship program – what makes it so popular?" http://blog.internshala.com/2012/08/internship-yahoo-tip/ …    
    
    
    The new @Yahoo weather app? I want that! Only in Android now? Rats - get the iOS app out!    
    
    
    @JJTopsparks Hi - congrats to team Perimeter @PennApps! Are you interested in @YahooJobs this summer? We'd like to know!    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist @mounialalmas keynote talk @TPDL2012: "User Engagement in the Digital World" It's much more than page views!    
    
    
    “@YahooLabs: Recruiting at the MobileHCI conference in beautiful San Francisco! pic.twitter.com/jGUvLNxo” We're hiring: http://bit.ly/ToSlbc     
    
    
    @pennapps prep for next hackathon MT @ydn: Check out bottle, an HTML5 framework for mobile UI components. http://bit.ly/PgNENl  #YUI    
    
    
    And congrats on the @Yahoo Mobile Mention Award! MT @MaxScheiber: http://www.thedp.com/article/2012/09/max-scheiber-missing-sleep-in-mcclelland … - what I learned from two @PennApps all-nighters.”    
    
    
    @eegilbert Hey, congrats. Now your productivity will soar! Sic 'em on @ayman ...    
    
    
    @Yahoo is hiring, seen here @gtcomputing: GATechCareerFair081 http://flic.kr/p/de8Kwt  Check out the openings: http://bit.ly/PLcCpm     
    
    
    Can U.S. Universities Stay on Top? http://on.wsj.com/Uz7sN0     
    
    
    Interesting comparison of global supply, demand, and government/industry investment. http://lnkd.in/aEjJPk     
    
    
    A great week @YahooLabs - Beverly Harrison accepted our offer to join the Mobile Experiences team led by Lars Erik Holmquist. Watch us grow!    
    
    
    A great week @YahooLabs - Beverly Harrison accepted our offer to join the Mobile Experiences team led by Lars Erik Holmquist.    
    
    
    Speed Mentoring with @Yahoo Women in Tech http://yhoo.it/VdBxSv  via @ydn How to support and encourage leadership development.    
    
    
    @marissamayer: "Companies are all about people, and the companies with the best talent win." Come win with us. @YahooJobs @YahooLabs    
    
    
    @landay New @YahooLabs scientists Jofish Kaye and Beverly Harrison are eager to visit  DUB Center for talks and collaboration. When?    
    
    
    Check with @isbellHFh for info on cobot#1 MT “@SCSatCMU: RT @heatherknight: Cobot is reverse trick-o-treating...: http://bit.ly/YodS5n ”    
    
    
    Calling all hackers! MT @ydn: RT @esuhonen: Join @ydn: Community Moderator, Evangelist & Architect, Outreach Mgr, more http://bit.ly/SwzMCE     
    
    
    Back from 2 weeks of no power thanks to Hurricane Sandy - and catching up on things. DM me anything I missed.    
    
    
    Yahoo! Labs announces 2012 Faculty Research and Engagement Recipients. Congratulations! http://www.yoncampusblog.com/     
    
    
    Announcing Yahoo! Labs ACE Awards: http://www.yoncampusblog.com/blog/2012/11/14/yahoo-announces-the-2012-ace-award-recipients/ …    
    
    
    And @yahoo intern! MT @georgiatech: Congrats to alumnus Joy Buolamwini (CS '12) - 2013 #Rhodes Scholar! http://www.gatech.edu/newsroom/release.html?nid=171801 … @GTComputing    
    
    
    Great perspective on why internal VC operations are sub-optimal at best: http://wp.me/p1NyQx-GU  via @richde    
    
    
    For the sports nut on your shopping list: greatest gift is letting them in on how great @yahoo #sportstacular app is. Fast, focused and fun!    
    
    
    @yahoolabs on campus: MT@FrancescoBonchi: Yesterday a busy day at CMU. Today University of Maryland, then heading to California    
    
    
    Francesco Bonchi, @YahooLabs scientist, spoke today @UMD on "Mining Propagation Data (in Social Networks)" https://talks.cs.umd.edu/talks/232     
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist @jofish talk at Stanford CS547 Friday 12/7: "Comfortable, Communal and Creative Computing" http://hci.stanford.edu/courses/cs547/speaker.php?date=2012-12-07 …    
    
    
    Talk @UCIBrenICS 12/3 Francesco Bonchi, Sr Research Scientist, @YahooLabs: Mining Progagation Data (in Social Networks) http://cml.ics.uci.edu/?page=events&subPage=aiml …    
    
    
    MT “@reid: My CEO at the White House with the President. Purple folder? Check. (via @ysaw) http://flic.kr/p/dx2FLr ”    
    
    
    University R&D Is Threatened by the #FiscalCliff http://techre.vu/V85T8C  (via @TechReview). This is more important than #My2K. Fix it now.    
    
    
    Today! @UCIBrenICS Francesco Bonchi, Sr Research Scientist, @YahooLabs Mining Progagation Data (in Social Networks) http://cml.ics.uci.edu/?page=events&subPage=aiml …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs proud to help sponsor CRA-W's Grad Cohort in Boston 4/5/13. Application form: https://computingresearch.wufoo.com/forms/k7w0p5/     
    
    
    Hal, I'm feeling sick...Technology will replace 80% of what doctors do http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2012/12/04/technology-doctors-khosla/ … via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    @YahooLabs paper MT @mounialalmas: #wsdm2013 Absence time and user engagement: Evaluating Ranking Functions http://www.dcs.gla.ac.uk/~mounia/Papers/wsdm2013.pdf … w/ @gdupret    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has 2013 summer internship openings for strong PhD students in CS, Stats, Design. http://labs.yahoo.com . Come grow with us!    
    
    
    @YahooLabs job opening: Research Scientist, Systems https://tas-yahoo.taleo.net/careersection/jobdetail.ftl?job=39503&lang=en&sns_id=twitter#.UMCUe6Pdz14.twitter …    
    
    
    A tune to memorialize December 7. http://www.youtube.com/watch_popup?feature=player_embedded&v=x2ml2wWBCm8 …    
    
    
    Great talk by @ericries on making innovation real. Appropriate as @Yahoo innovates for growth. Love "innovation accounting".    
    
    
    It's not quite a digital day, but #121212 has a nice ring to it.    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has intern openings for PhD students: real-world problems, tons of data and opportunities to publish http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    Great talk @hmason - thanks for visiting @yahoo today.    
    
    
    @YahooLabs has intern openings for PhD students: real-world problems, tons of data and opportunities to publish http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    @arnabdotorg @nicholasgorski @yahoolabs Thanks Arnab! We are growing and having fun, new energy from @marissamayer    
    
    
    #demandaplan “@YahooTicket: House to observe a moment of silence to honor #Newtown victims: http://yhoo.it/12kDNOj ”    
    
    
    @YahooLabs #internship eg: Ph.D student, qualitative/ethnographic research from iSchool, informatics, HCI, STS http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    More @YahooLabs intern openings: User study/prototype on perceptions of local recs & environment, potential paper. http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    @YahooLabs Haifa Intern openings: Content quality insight and experiments; NLP aspects in Answers; User engagement. http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    Intern jobs @YahooLabs Haifa: Content quality insight and experiments; NLP aspects in Answers; User engagement. http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    Intern jobs @YahooLabs Haifa in: Exotic recomend settings, Algo advancements, Innovative features, Platform/System design, Web experiences    
    
    
    Awesome idea. Tiny Bluetooth Stickers Ensure You'll Never Lose Anything Ever Again http://www.businessinsider.com/snapnfind-indiegogo-project-2012-12?0=tools … http://www.indiegogo.com/sticknfind     
    
    
    More! Intern jobs @YahooLabs Silicon Valley: Content/sentiment understanding in UGC; User behavioral understanding http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    Intern jobs @YahooLabs Silicon Valley: Search Vertical Ranking; Email anti spam; Search Assist and Query Suggestion http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    Congrats Magda! “@csenews: New post from UW CSE News: Magda Balazinska:  As American as apple pie http://is.gd/d2w0i9 ”    
    
    
    @YahooLabs among organizers of "Workshop on Web Search Click Data" @wsdm2013 http://www.wsdm2013.org/     
    
    
    Noonan: Hats off to Obama's Internet savvy campaign. About Those 2012 Political Predictions http://on.wsj.com/U4hfwC     
    
    
    Wanted: Big Data Intern @YahooLabs NYC to script/code/model new algorithms. PhD CS/Stats,strong coding+stat-ML skills http://y.ahoo.it/uhMpv     
    
    
    From @YahooLabs Webscope: MT @sinanaral: Get Our Data!  http://bit.ly/4qbync  G7 Yahoo Property & IM Data... http://bit.ly/bKM5p7     
    
    
    @YahooLabs Congratulations @hsmcramer - Mattias Rost, Louise Barkhuus, Henriette Cramer, Barry Brown got a CSCW Best Paper Nomination    
    
    
    Just in time for @PennApps MT @caridy: mojito 0.5.2 is now in npm: 2x fast, 1/2 memory footprint and 1/2 startup: https://github.com/yahoo/mojito/wiki/ReleaseNotes0_5_2 …    
    
    
    Get Your Hack On – Yahoo! Is Back @PennApps http://shar.es/4UD0J  Come have a Cocktail with us!    
    
    
    POP for @PennApps - Design Your App on Paper, Animate It With Your iPhone Camera http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1671490  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    @YahooJobs Bad bit.ly URL, please resend.    
    
    
    Hey @PennApps hackers - tutorial on @Yahoo Mojito: http://y.ahoo.it/KnjkD  And more: http://y.ahoo.it/7v1OQ . See you at Friday's API talk!    
    
    
    Oh, Snap! Flickr Takes on Instagram. http://dthin.gs/13G3xnV  You've gotta get this Flickr app!    
    
    
    Get Your Hack On – Yahoo! proud to sponsor Best Mobile Hack @PennApps http://shar.es/4UD0J  Come have a Cocktail with us!    
    
    
    Catch @YahooMobile Cocktails API talk by @diervo at #PennApps tonite! Here's a preview: http://y.ahoo.it/iQ21q     
    
    
    At #pennapps with the awesome @Yahoo team. 500 hackers from 40 schools. Let the fun begin! pic.twitter.com/ia1kZ7S9    
    
    
    @diervo presenting @yahoo Mojitos demo at #pennapps - $500 prize for best mobile hack! pic.twitter.com/2NdHuuOr    
    
    
    #pennapps @temiri Yahoo! Best Mobile Hack winners get a paid trip to NYC to interview for this job!  Mobile  Engineer, http://bit.ly/11zZACJ     
    
    
    Awesome posts from @temiri, bringing the hacks to life “@PennApps: Who's Hacking What: Merge http://tmblr.co/ZPVkJuc7fnRm ”    
    
    
    If it feels like Friday but tomorrow is Monday, then I must have been @PennApps - and can't wait till the next hackathon. Nice job, all!    
    
    
    Congratulations to @zan2434 & Mosaic team from MIT/Pitt, winners of the @Yahoo sponsored Best Mobile Hack #PenApps http://y.ahoo.it/YtBVb     
    
    
    The stars aligned today as all three of my daughters' teams won! Go #villanova #duke #gatech    
    
    
    What does it mean to be a good Campus Relationship Manager? Trust, technical depth and attention to detail at a minimum. Is that you?    
    
    
    Great meeting @mtdukes here: // Discussing journalism’s computational future http://www.reporterslab.org/computation-journalism-symposium/ … via @ReportersLab    
    
    
    The Sports Graph mentioned at Comp+Journalism panel. Something to add to the @yahoo #Sportstacular app. #CompJ    
    
    
    Nicolas Lemann, Columbia: Journalism is like big data: acquire, analyze and display the essence of a story. #CompJ    
    
    
    @eegilbert from @gtcomputing mentions @yahoolabs' @ayman work in second order effects in #twitter analysis at #CompJ Symposium    
    
    
    Coders create tools, writers use to tell stories MT @DioniLWise: @albertocairo Do all journalists need to learn code? #CompJ”    
    
    
    @eegilbert that was quite a game last night. Way to go Illini!    
    
    
    “@YahooJobs: Yahoo ranks number 8 as best place to work http://read.bi/WMFWNx  #yahoo #bestplace” And we're hiring!    
    
    
    Eric Bax, Research Scientist @YahooLabs, speaking at UC Irvine's AI/ML seminar Mon, Feb 11 in Bren Hall 4011 at 1pm. Food too! @UCIbrenICS    
    
    
    Run Your Family Like a Business http://on.wsj.com/Z0PpqE  - Use agile techniques to ease household stress? Or common sense?    
    
    
    TODAY! Eric Bax, Research Scientist @YahooLabs, speaking at UC Irvine's AI/ML seminar Feb 11 in Bren Hall 4011 at 1pm. Food too! @UCIbrenICS    
    
    
    Internship opportunities @yahoojobs - a chance to grow and have fun! http://m.facebook.com/story.php?story_fbid=273424632789034&id=833404&_rdr …    
    
    
    @PennApps runner up for @Yahoo Best Mobile Hack are visiting our NYC mobile engender team today!    
    
    
    Great reflection piece to start the weekend: "9 Unconventional Habits of Extraordinary Success" http://www.marcandangel.com/2013/02/08/9-unconventional-habits-of-extraordinary-success/ … via @marcandangel    
    
    
    @YahooLabs congratulates NYU on new Center for Data Science initiative #bigdata http://datascience.nyu.edu/about/     
    
    
    @YahooLabs Tarun Bhatia on panel at #RPSummit13 - what's your favorite ad tech algo? pic.twitter.com/ndVAL7Ru    
    
    
    Key techie take-away from Tarun: we need to make algorithms exciting, effective and expressive. #RPSummit13 @YahooLabs    
    
    
    @YahooJobs Rocking the Penn Career Fair! pic.twitter.com/VsNLeuMMVf    
    
    
    @Thejakeyboy Racking up the miles, I see. Safe trip, keep in touch!    
    
    
    Artful post, great comments. "Why you should always ask a question at an academic talk": http://blogs.cornell.edu/danco/2013/02/18/on-asking-questions-and-academic-love/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Is this snappy enough? MT @gtcomputing: @eegilbert & @cjhutto find that happy, snappy tweets gain most followers http://bit.ly/13QZFig     
    
    
    @cmunell True!    
    
    
    Congress Should Listen To @MarissaMayer (stay in DC and collaborate!) http://techcrunch.com/2013/02/26/congress-should-listen-to-marissa-mayer/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @YahooLabs Sponsors NYU Center for Data Science w/ servers, seminar: http://cds.nyu.edu/yahoo-labs-a-founding-sponsor-of-nyu-initiative-data-science-and-statistics-and-center-for-data-science/ … #datascience    
    
    
    Imagining how I’d like my devices to communicate with me during my daily habits… http://www.fastcompany.com/node/3005262  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Brilliant. Users build knowledge graph MT @techreview: FB wants a database describing things http://techre.vu/XDuuHo     
    
    
    Congratulations! MT @YahooLabs  Research Scientist Henriette Cramer's paper nominated for Best Paper at #cscw2013 http://www.yoncampusblog.com/ ”    
    
    
    @YahooLabs Sponsors NYU Center for Data Science w/ servers, seminar: http://cds.nyu.edu/yahoo-labs-a-founding-sponsor-of-nyu-initiative-data-science-and-statistics-and-center-for-data-science/ … #datascience    
    
    
    “@munmun10: Nice, useful resource! MT @yahoolabs @danielequercia some of the talks i attended at #cscw2013 http://bit.ly/13tTCo3 ”    
    
    
    Recognizing patent awards @yahoolabs Science Week. Congratulations inventors! pic.twitter.com/zbFOJ9DOdW    
    
    
    Happy Pi Day! Is our love of Pi irrational? (Ouch!)    
    
    
    @BillGates posts @jakehofman talk about how things go viral. Nice!  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wSwOszoHuoI&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    It's all about personalization. MT @hmason: Sometimes I want to follow people. Or topics. Or content sources. Why not all in one place?    
    
    
    Jason Gay scores a 10 with this amazing story.
http://lnkd.in/yq4mtr     
    
    
    Congrats Munmun! MT @MSFTResearch: Profiles of women in computing. Meet Munmun De Choudhury, researcher @MSFTResearch http://twitpic.com/cblcce     
    
    
    Do you love connecting brilliant people at top universities, helping grad students and spinning up new research collaborations? We need you!    
    
    
    Congratulations to Bob Kahn! Respect for the silent genius behind TCP/IP MT ... Share UK Engineering Prize http://dthin.gs/XUhP5Y     
    
    
    Master Inventors honored @YahooLabs http://us.careers.yahoo.com/lifeatyahoo/content/1331/lang/en …    
    
    
    Onward! RT @FastCompany: As Google Reader dies, Marissa Mayer makes a move: Yahoo! is buying Summly http://trib.al/qKl0ZrE     
    
    
    @mounialalmas presenting "Measuring Web User Engagement" at Women in Science and Engineering Workshop (WISE) on 3/28 http://events.inf.ed.ac.uk/wise2013/     
    
    
    @nickdaloisio: “Definitely with the approach they are taking at the moment — they’re moving at light speed, ..." http://gigaom.com/2013/03/25/summlys-teenaged-founder-says-he-wants-to-help-make-yahoo-great-again/ …    
    
    
    4/3 talk @Stanford: Anirban Dasgupta, @YahooLabs, "Mechanism For Crowdsourced Judgement Elicitation", noon, Y2E2 101 http://rain.stanford.edu/     
    
    
    @nickdaloisio Great segment! Stop by and meet head of @yahoolabs when you're in NYC. We're at 6th & 40th St.    
    
    
    Please! I need this! MT @WSJCorpIntel: Ford: $50K prize for better mobile app to go with its hybrid cars: http://on.wsj.com/Yfjzoh  #hacku    
    
    
        
    
    
    Talk 3/28 by @YahooLabs @mounialalmas: "Measuring Web User Engagement" http://events.inf.ed.ac.uk/wise2013/  #wise2013    
    
    
    @adelebeid @mheadd Didn't HP Labs measure it by % sales from products launched with Labs technology over last xx months?    
    
    
    @YahooLabs proud to sponsor UMass CS Graduate and Undergraduate Awards, our future scientific leaders https://www.cs.umass.edu/news/latest-news/2013-outstanding-achievement-and-advocacy-awards-recipients-announced … @umasscs    
    
    
    @YahooLabs'Suju Rajan will speak @umasscs Machine Learning and Friends Lunch"The Internet Ordered For You" 4/4/13 https://people.cs.umass.edu/~mlfriend/pmwiki/pmwiki.php …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs' Anirban Dasgupta's talk @Stanford RAIN Seminar noon TODAY, Y2E2 101: "Eliciting and aggregating information from the crowd"    
    
    
        
    
    
    Suju Rajan, Research Manager @YahooLabs presenting @umasscs on Machine Learning applied to Personalization pic.twitter.com/LISJATzFff    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@jasonWSJ: Still think Michigan in seven.” Yeah, I wore my UM shirt yesterday.    
    
    
    @yahoolabs We live in a data sandbox - and we are hiring. "Data Science: The Numbers of Our Lives" http://nyti.ms/16UkquO  #datascience    
    
    
    Here's a great NLP problem: create a rules interpreter for the @USGA    
    
    
    Poetry from Jason Gay: "The gracious duel that will be the brilliant memory." Thumbs Up to a Great Masters Duel http://on.wsj.com/138GmlB     
    
    
    OK, where do I sign up? RT @mounialalmas: For my @YahooLabs colleagues :-) RT @nicholasritchey Human Foosball! pic.twitter.com/ag29qqrUrS    
    
    
    A Sunday reflection on steering the moral ship: The Meaning of the Gosnell Trial http://on.wsj.com/10okZQC     
    
    
    In case you missed it: @YahooLabs Eric Bax presented "Pricing Information and Validating Network Classifiers" today @UCSDJacobs    
    
    
    Come to @yahoolabs for both. RT @HarvardBiz: To Work with Data, You Need a Lab and a Factory http://s.hbr.org/10cZBXb     
    
    
    @YahooLabs Sponsors the AMPLab, and Donates Servers to Help University Research http://shar.es/JR2Uu     
    
    
    @inaudiblewords see this? MT A cheap way to alter ammonium nitrate fertilizer renders it unusable in IEDs http://techre.vu/11CYGnc     
    
    
    A great event - will you be there? RT @nickdaloisio: Excited for Yahoo! Hack Day Europe which starts tomorrow!!!!    
    
    
    So true! MT @mheadd: "The Most Important Part of Your Hackathon? Your Sponsors." by @temiri - hackathon champ. http://tessrinearson.com/blog/?p=661     
    
    
        
    
    
    You meet some impressive people on this job. #usa pic.twitter.com/5k6drRCMg5    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Eric Bax talk "Validating Network Classifiers and Pricing Information" 5/7, UW CSE http://www.cs.washington.edu/research/ml/seminars/ … @csenews    
    
    
    Nice pic! MT It’s been one year since the opening of @MSFTResearch #NYC. Happy first birthday! http://bit.ly/132YLRy  pic.twitter.com/07EUFJ1eIh    
    
    
    @vera_newhouse @nycmedialab See @YahooLabs's Webscope program w/ over 40 datasets ready for academic research! http://y.ahoo.it/Xr+hW     
    
    
    MT @Limosineproject: Keynote by Dr. Gianmarco De Francisci @YahooLabs A Platform for Mining Big Data Streams http://ow.ly/kM9x7  #www2013    
    
    
    Nice! @syardi, @cjhutto and @eegilbert paper at #chi2013 "A Longitudinal Study of Follow Predictors on Twitter" http://bit.ly/17JA5Q4     
    
    
    TODAY at noon! @YahooLabs Eric Bax talk: "Validating Network Classifiers and Pricing Information", UW CSE http://www.cs.washington.edu/research/ml/seminars/ …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Ron Lavi talk 5/21, UW Theory Seminar: " Conditional Equilibrium Outcomes via Ascending Price Processes..." @csenews    
    
    
    Welcome to 40th St.! RT @YahooInc: The talented @Milewise team joined our NY mobile hub today. Welcome to Yahoo! http://bit.ly/ZRKeZ3     
    
    
    @CBSNews Thank you. This was a very moving ceremony.    
    
    
    Class act. MT @CBSNews Moving photos of Prince Harry's visit to @ArlingtonNatl including hand-written note to fallen pic.twitter.com/kL9jwoBI53    
    
    
    @yahoolabs MT @danielequercia: In rio for #www2013 workshop keynote tomorrow afternoon. Presentation on Friday.    
    
    
    We're growing - come join us! RT @YahooLabs Sunnyvale welcomes Yandong Liu to the team! http://www.linkedin.com/pub/yandong-liu/7/8a2/a87 …    
    
    
    MT @YahooLabs: Frank Bentley @bentley79 joins our Sunnyvale Lab! Excited to have the MIT/Moto guru aboard! http://linkd.in/10IrRHm     
    
    
    @cu_wics Enjoyed lunch with Columbia's WiCS leaders. Great ideas for next academic year: speakers, sponsorships, more pic.twitter.com/e9pT2Vmhwq    
    
    
    Congrats! MT @danielequercia: proud to be in @YahooLabs: 5 #kdd2013 papers accepted! ;) RT @FrancescoBonchi: results:  4 papers accepted    
    
    
    Today at #www2013: Keynote by @YahooLabs' Gianmarco Morales: "SAMOA: A Platform for Mining Big Data Streams" http://www.ramss.ws/2013/program/     
    
    
    @YahooLabs presents TODAY at #www2013: (Big) Usage Data in Web Search, by Ricardo Baeza-Yates and Yoelle Maarek http://www2013.org/program/big-usage-data-in-web-search/ …    
    
    
    “@xamat: "Measuring User Engagement" - Excellent #www2013 tutorial http://www.slideshare.net/mounialalmas/measuring-userengagement … via @denisparra” @YahooLabs    
    
    
    MT @SarahFKessler: Google+ recognizes that diluting quality hurts future use, something @Flickr already does well: http://www.fastcompany.com/3006481/flickrs-secret-weapon-photo-sharing-wars-future …    
    
    
    Tweet that News! RT @YahooInc: .@yahoo delivers #bestoftheweb http://bit.ly/12xX2DJ  by @marissamayer    
    
    
    MT @ronbrachman: @YahooLabs continues its tradition of excellence - 8 accepted papers @ #kdd2013 Congrats to @FrancescoBonchi co-author on 4    
    
    
    MT@nicolastorzec: More data to play with: Yahoo partners w/ Twitter to bring tweets directly into the @Yahoo newsfeed http://bit.ly/12xX2DJ     
    
    
    Headed to Pittsburgh tomorrow to celebrate our Bill Wysocki's MS degree from CMU's INI. Great things await Bill and Libby!    
    
    
    At CMU commencement, congratulations to Bill Wysocki and other graduates! pic.twitter.com/eleiOeN9Em    
    
    
    Thoughtful reflection - nicely done! “@asbruckman: On Google Glass and Gargoyles: a Call to Action http://wp.me/pMtBi-iN ”    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Ron Lavi talk TODAY at UW Theory Seminar: " Conditional Equilibrium Outcomes via Ascending Price Processes..." @csenews    
    
    
    @jasonWSJ just saw your Monday column. Beautiful. Congrats, Dad!    
    
    
    Christos Faloutsos talk @YahooLabs 6/6 11am. "Large Graph Mining – Patterns, Tools and Cascade Analysis" http://labs.yahoo.com/event/big-thinker-christos-faloutsos-at-yahoo/ …    
    
    
    CMU's Jason Hong giving a Tea Talk for @YahooLabs scientists "HCI and Smartphone Data at Scale" @SCSatCMU pic.twitter.com/oXYNy6PMmL    
    
    
    Blog post on measuring how users engage with the web: http://wp.me/p3teg2-3C  via @mounialalmas @yahoolabs #science    
    
    
    Tomorrow @yahoolabs Christos Faloutsos' Big Thinker talk: Large Graph Mining – Patterns, Tools and Cascade Analysis pic.twitter.com/aGQY8G69j3    
    
    
    Today @yahoolabs Big Thinker Christos Faloutsos talk on Large Graph Mining pic.twitter.com/vEBJTM9pYa    
    
    
    @cmunell Hi NELL. I think *you* are a creative work.    
    
    
    Know anyone who loves building relationships between academia and industrial labs, connecting brilliant people and enabling new research?  …    
    
    
    Headed to #ICML2013 in Hotlanta next week w/ @YahooLabs scientists. Stop by our table!    
    
    
    Check this out! RT @IntoNow: Twitter sharing is now working!   Thanks everybody! http://into.tv/i/cvMN     
    
    
    @ydn launches Pure - A set of small, responsive CSS modules that you can use in every web project.http://purcss.io  #hacku @PennApps    
    
    
    Headed to @ICML2013, found Emily Fox and David Mimno in the waiting lounge at EWR.    
    
    
    #ICML2013 here we come... Eventually. EWR departure now delayed 2 hrs.    
    
    
    We're at #ICML2013 - ya'll stop by and visit! @YahooLabs pic.twitter.com/dmN0pir9o5    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check this out: RT @IntoNow: Twitter sharing is now working!   Thanks everybody! http://into.tv/i/cvMN     
    
    
    @YahooLabs is delighted to sponsor the innovative "Inferning" workshop at #icml2013 this year. Check it out! http://inferning.cs.umass.edu/     
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientists @pchalasani, Na Dai and Zohar Karnin at #ICML2013. Great talks, brilliant people. pic.twitter.com/rPflV7dHVO    
    
    
    Booth tables at #icml2013. The crowd just left for dinner.  @yahoolabs looking forward to Weds talks. pic.twitter.com/w0ycUxrr1w    
    
    
    @YahooLabs Zohar Karnin presented his poster at #ICML2013 last night. Last day of talks today - workshops start tomorrow.    
    
    
    Spark: Open Source Superstar Rewrites Future of Big Data #yahoo http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/06/yahoo-amazon-amplab-spark/all/ …    
    
    
    @cmunell Dear Nell, Marissa Mayer is a CEO: @marissamayer    
    
    
    @syardi Thanks for the tweet about clunky processes on Yahoo!. I've alerted our special division set up by Marissa to handle such issues.    
    
    
    @cmunell Hi Nell, Marietta is a city.    
    
    
    Photo gallery from University of Illinois Chancellor visit to @Yahoo! on 6/18: http://shar.es/xYQG4  @IllinoisCS    
    
    
    I'd like to hook up this latte foam printer to @Flickr! MT Coffee Shop Prints Your Face With Its Foam http://www.fastcocreate.com/node/1683254     
    
    
    @dggoldst just saw your #BrainGames #1 bit. Cool! Will you be on any future shows?    
    
    
    @informor Stop by our table if you are at #sigmod13    
    
    
    Clarity. “@ThisWeekABC: VIDEO WEB EXCLUSIVE: @Peggynoonannyc talks about President Ronald Reagan and the #IRS. http://abcn.ws/13g0K9o ”    
    
    
    Encore careers: the hits keep on coming! http://www.washington.edu/alumni/columns-magazine/june-2013/essayist/ …    
    
    
    Full house to hear Rob Schapire's talk, "Explaining AdaBoost" @YahooLabs #BigThinker pic.twitter.com/3cPxP6KZeF    
    
    
    @SCSatCMU's William Cohen presenting @YahooLabs on "Learning to Construct and Reason With NELL" pic.twitter.com/Cr22fiQBfh    
    
    
    @elad1 I asked him this. He didn't use it directly in this talk but it can be used for temporal reasoning research.    
    
    
    “@WSJLive: With One Microsoft, can Ballmer turn the software giant around? http://on.wsj.com/10OZkyH ” #OxyMoron    
    
    
    MT @YahooLabs: Met our new scientists? Check out our Facebook page.Come grow with us! https://www.facebook.com/YahooLabs     
    
    
    Thinking about youngest daughter Carlee as she and her #Boealps team summit Mt. Rainier today. #SoProud    
    
    
    MT @mounialalmas: Full paper "Online Multitasking: What Web Analytics think we do..."accepted at #cikm2013 w/  @gdupre et.al. @YahooLabs    
    
    
    We’re really at the beginning of search: @YahooLabs @pmika Peter Mika - Livemint http://www.livemint.com/Companies/PSCSptBu8CZEXtUUI5d8fN/Were-really-at-the-beginning-of-search.html … "It's about understanding..."    
    
    
    Yahoo! Yodel is back in the #AllStarGame  ad.    
    
    
    @JCP_L so disappointed to have lost power just 2 hours before a dinner party. I phoned it in and see the no-info status on the web. Help!    
    
    
    David Karp: http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324507404578593602476366638.html …    
    
    
    David Karp: "I don't know how you could live in Palo Alto," he says. "It's just boring." Yep. #madeinnyc    
    
    
    Getting ready for #SIGIR2013 with Dublin's liquid sunshine, tenacious spirit and a pint or two. Great program ahead! pic.twitter.com/2bceYLhDXD    
    
    
    Ricardo Baeza-Yates and Estefania Ricart at #SIGIR2013 Dublin. Our booth is ready, come see us! @YahooLabs pic.twitter.com/hUfpKDYzBL    
    
    
    Meeting and making good friends at #sigir2013 - come see us at the @YahooLabs booth! pic.twitter.com/BQIokhMm5a    
    
    
    @YahooLabs short paper authors Cigdem Aslay and Neil O'Hare answering questions at their busy poster. #sigir2013 pic.twitter.com/1WC28g1xI0    
    
    
    @edgarmeij @fabreetseo Enjoy Ricardo's talk - tweet us a photo of his Keynote talk if you can!    
    
    
    Ricardo Baeza-Yates keynote, "An Engaging Click" presented to a packed room at #sigir2013. @YahooLabs https://mobile.twitter.com/edgarmeij/status/362604562110095360/photo/1 …    
    
    
    @JimiShan thanks for the photo of Ricardo at #sigir2013it    
    
    
    Growing @YahooLabs:Yahoo’s Mayer to Rebuild Research Lab With 50 PhD Hires in 2013 - Bloomberg http://bloom.bg/15yxNTq     
    
    
    Can Hiring Scientists Help Save Yahoo? By @addythebaddy http://www.fastcompany.com/3015196/where-are-they-now/can-hiring-scientists-help-save-yahoo … via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Come grow with us: @YahooLabs Puts on 50 New Thinking Caps http://shar.es/yfmJJ  "Building new directions is what it's all about."    
    
    
        
    
    
    @UTCompSci hosts Shivaram Kalyanakrishnan @YahooLabs 8/12: "PAC Subset Selection in Stochastic Multi-armed Bandits". http://www.cs.utexas.edu/~ai-lab/fai/#upcoming …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Today 11am: @YahooLabs talk by Shivaram Kalyanakrishnan. POB 2.402 http://www.cs.utexas.edu/~ai-lab/fai/#Shivaram%20Kalyanakrishnan …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @landay Good luck @CornellNYCTech. @YahooLabs has great relationships there, look forward to further collaborations. Come visit us in NY!    
    
    
    Tom Mitchell recognizes @YahooLabs among others for supporting NELL research. We are proud to support this important work. #ACMWebinarNELL    
    
    
    Significant indeed! @yahoolabs proud to sponsor OAA Awards p8 and Marlin FREP plus seminars p6. @umasscs https://www.cs.umass.edu/sites/default/files/uploads/sigbits_summer2013.pdf …    
    
    
    Lunch @yahoolabs NYC w/ scientists and collaborators. We're hiring! pic.twitter.com/mtNxRgGcdB    
    
    
    @seinecle @yahoolabs Indeed yes! Na Dai and Meizhu Liu couldn't join us today. And <amazing female scientist TBA> joins in 3 weeks!    
    
    
    This help? "breaking exhausting sleep cycles" http://f-st.co/11PZ7ac  MT @nickdaloisio: I am least tired when I go to sleep and most tired...    
    
    
    Congrats Oren @etzioni! RT @tommmitchell: Oren Etzioni to head major new AI research effort at Allen Institute http://news.cs.washington.edu/2013/09/04/uw-cses-oren-etzioni-to-lead-new-allen-institute-for-artificial-intelligence/ …    
    
    
    Next time: @yahoolabs will hold a prediction market MT @gabestein: @lukew says @Yahoo logo redesign has ~3 contenders http://bit.ly/17uhAMG     
    
    
        
    
    
    Hey @PennApps! @Yahoo_On_Campus is baaaack as a sponsor. @pmaloka, @pulahshah, and @nickmeyer will show our APIs. Show us your stuff!    
    
    
    @PennApps Hey, how about some love for the sponsors at the other end of the alphabet?    
    
    
    Full house (balcony too) @PennApps for API demos. pic.twitter.com/XF5FPU51Ch    
    
    
    Winning the Yahoo prize for Best Mobile Hack @PennApps is SuperDuper Mario - they also took 2nd place overall. Congratulations!    
    
    
    Robin Murphy presenting the @yahoolabs Big Thinker Series talk today! http://labs.yahoo.com  pic.twitter.com/RiuI700rXj    
    
    
    On this 9/11, remembering the fallen and the heros.  #neverforget    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Chris Wilkens speaking at Duke's CS/Econ seminar on Friday, 9/13: "Utility-Target Auctions". http://econ.cs.duke.edu/seminar.php     
    
    
    @YahooLabs and Summly scientist Inderjeet Mani speaking @Columbia 9/16 on "Automatic Summarization: Old Problems and New Challenges"    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Chris Wilkens speaking TODAY at Duke's CS/Econ seminar: "Utility-Target Auctions". http://econ.cs.duke.edu/seminar.php     
    
    
    Chris Wilkens presenting at Duke's CS/Econ Seminar sponsored by @yahoolabs pic.twitter.com/t7PogjHm32    
    
    
    Inderjeet Mani speaking @CUSEAS today at 2:30pm, 750 Shapiro: "Automatic Summarization, Old Problems and New Solutions"    
    
    
    @CUSEAS bulletin board pic.twitter.com/HqEyrGkR96    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Inderjeet Mani @CUSEAS  describing text summarization, fm Summly to Yahoo and beyond. pic.twitter.com/l2ex3vVGXd    
    
    
    Look who's leading off the "40 under 40".  http://money.cnn.com/gallery/magazines/fortune/2013/09/19/40-under-40.fortune/ … via @FortuneMagazine    
    
    
    @hmason Hey - me too! Happened last night, had to change my password. Bother.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @yahoolabs Our NY Lab is growing! We welcome new hires Amanda Stent and Huan Wang. pic.twitter.com/BKLhP1Da81    
    
    
    Full table at lunch! @YahooLabs #NYC Come grow with us. pic.twitter.com/u80SqjBQwF    
    
    
    A wonderful opportunity for @YahooLabs to help. RT @antonioregalado: Octogenarians: Fastest growing demographic group in the U.S.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fall comes to Ken Lockwood Gorge. Walking in crunchy leaves makes me smile. pic.twitter.com/HF7JIl8DFZ    
    
    
    Shameless plug: $25 Stream Ads campaign credit to the first 1,000 advertisers who sign up with Yahoo http://marketinginfo.yahoo.net     
    
    
    Talk Thurs @11:40 @YahooLabs Scientist Edo Liberty: Simple and Deterministic Matrix Sketches  @RU_USACS http://www.stat.rutgers.edu/home/pingli/Bigdata.html …    
    
    
    Today! @ 11:40 @YahooLabs Scientist Edo Liberty: Simple and Deterministic Matrix Sketches  @RU_USACS http://www.stat.rutgers.edu/home/pingli/Bigdata.html …    
    
    
    @YahooLabs scientist Edo Liberty presenting to @RU_USACS #BigData seminar series. Full house! pic.twitter.com/GIakMbqKFp    
    
    
    First CS career fair at @umasscs - great event, wonderful talent. Thanks! @YahooUniversity @yahoojobs pic.twitter.com/OjG3SXMcCX    
    
    
    @eegilbert Stop by our Lab in Barcelona when you're in town.    
    
    
    Hoping to meet @ABrightMonster after @BigFishBroadway today. Great show! Thx @abrightman for the tip.    
    
    
    Where am I?: "Rental car center. Please exit" (No fair looking at location data.)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Pogue  Hi, I work w/ @YahooLabs in NYC and have an event to discuss. Please DM best way to discuss w/ you?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @YahooLabs Lianjie Hong leads the Online User Engagement workshop at #cikm2013 tomorrow! http://www.ueo-workshop.com/     
    
    
    That's 3 for 2013! MT @YahooLabs: Congratulations! RT @ibordino: "Penguins in Sweaters" Best Paper at CIKM 2013 @mounialalmas @yelenamm    
    
    
    Today: @YahooLabs proud to co-organize User Engagement Workshop at #cikm2013. http://www.ueo-workshop.com/     
    
    
    Looking forward to this talk! RT @ayman: Welcome Fei-Fei! http://flic.kr/p/hxu6Bs     
    
    
    Welcome @cu_wics to @YahooInc in #NYC - loved showing you our awesome mobile dev team and @YahooLabs scientists! pic.twitter.com/vZb0RboyxW    
    
    
    Hey @HackDuke hackers - we want to hear about your cool mobile hacks. I want to see a Cameron Camera that gfives me the full experience!    
    
    
    MT @ESchmidtDesigns: Only 1 in 10 engineers are women. We should probably fix that. @GoldieBlox http://www.upworthy.com/if-3-little-girls-did-this-to-my-house-id-do-everything-i-could-to-get-them-full-rides-to-stanford?g=2&c=fea …    
    
    
    @mounialalmas speaking @CityUniLondon on Friday at 1:00pm on User Engagement http://www.city.ac.uk/informatics/school-organisation/centre-for-human-computer-interaction-design …    
    
    
    Visiting @Princeton today for "Celebrate Princeton Invention". @YahooLabs is proud to sponsor!    
    
    
    @mounialalmas from @YahooLabs  speaking on User Engagement @CityUniLondon today at 1:00pm in A109, College Building    
    
    
        
    
    
    This Friday, @mounialalmas from @YahooLabs speaks at UCL on User Engagement http://www.cs.ucl.ac.uk/event_details/?eventnum=944 …    
    
    
    @MLrecruiting4MS @YahooLabs will be there! I have a conflict that week - please look for @MikeSefanov at out booth.    
    
    
    “@kdd_news: Following #KDD2013, GigaOm's @derrickharris writes about Yahoo's past and future. http://lnkd.in/bQxHVpj ” Well, kinda...    
    
    
    Today! @mounialalmas speaks at UCL on User Engagement. Room 6.12, Malet Place Eng, 1:00pm. http://www.cs.ucl.ac.uk/event_details/?eventnum=944 …    
    
    
    @munmun10 Have enjoyed following you from internship to industry to academia - congratulation on the @gtcomputing position!    
    
    
    Donating to the @VFoundation on #GivingTuesday in gratitude for good health.    
    
    
    Welcome to the NY Lab! RT @JR_Scally: Great first day at @YahooLabs - ready to build some awesome things!    
    
    
    #PearlHarbor - the #NeverForget that I grew up with. Sad to see it fading.    
    
    
    @Pogue where is all they long tail content? I'm still looking for the movie 'Zotz'.    
    
    
    @arnabdotorg Thanks Arnab - I didn't know this trick!    
    
    
    @qhardy It's Christmas - give @Pogue a break!    
    
    
    Tess would know! MT @mheadd: "Running an Inclusive Hackathon" by @_tessr. Great read for those organizing an event. https://medium.com/hackers-and-hacking/630f3f2e5e71 …    
    
    
    