I'm in, long as they're veggie! RT @pekingspring: just hit upon the idea of making candy hearts, but with "fuck off" and "cunt" on them.    
    
    
    Someone did it to me yesterday. RT @YourFilm_MN: why do people think that safe in-car phone use means SCREECH TO A HALT WHEREVER THEY ARE?    
    
    
    Off to Steel Wheels to rummage for some rock memorabilia for a mate's 40th    
    
    
    Neil Young's Like a Hurricane on the radio - awesome    
    
    
    This should have a sign on it reading "the sixties were shit". http://tweetphoto.com/14002410    
    
    
    11 already!!! Still loads to do before beer o'clock.    
    
    
    Windows XP this morning. I'd forgotten how much it makes me want to take a sledgehammer to a computer.    
    
    
    HP Photo & Imaging Director, like digital Hotel California - you can de-install any time you like, but it just won't leave.    
    
    
    OK. Simple Monday task: 1) Scan expenses receipts, 2) invoice customer. Now turning into an epic. I'm going to explode soon.    
    
    
    Finally, we have scanning capability again!  HP + Windows XP, productivity gains up there with the quill pen.    
    
    
    OK, I give up. It's costing more to claim than the actual worth. Time to negotiate a per diem.    
    
    
    BTW. Up yours, Microsoft. And up yours, HP.    
    
    
    Early lunch. Watching This Morning on ITV. Phil Schofield  & Holly Wotsit have just done a piece on how to improve your sex life.    
    
    
    With live actors demonstrating positions. Although they're not allowed to do 'the movements' according to daytime TV rules. Hilarious.    
    
    
    Now we've got a bloke dressed as Elvis cooking via webcam from Spain. Seriously, the things we miss when we go to the office.    
    
    
    Or perhaps I took the wrong cold remedy pill this morning?    
    
    
    Elvis is about to do duck in orange sauce instructed by Phil Vickery    
    
    
    Why don't they put this stuff on at night??? It's brilliant.    
    
    
    Elvis isn't wearing an apron. The rhinestone outfit is bound to show up the suace splashes. Uh-huh-huh.    
    
    
    Sadly I have to leave This Morning's Cook In with Elvis to go to the office and relative normality. My eyes have been opened.    
    
    
    @stuarthoward That looks fantastic    
    
    
    Trying out we7. Lots more interruptions than Spotify, although the premium subscription is cheaper at the minute (same price inc mobile).    
    
    
    Feel poorly. Heavy cold. Might even be man flu.    
    
    
    Is it just me, or is Lord Adonis a dead ringer for Mr Burns?    
    
    
    @justingsouter  Lord Adonis is here: http://bit.ly/lKEhA, Mr Burns is here: http://bit.ly/bc4B9Q. Or is that the other way around?    
    
    
    How would he know? He hasn't kicked a ball in donkeys...RT @TheJournalNews: NUFC: Joey Barton: I'm now a better player: http://bit.ly/aDuC9J    
    
    
    @jerri_murtagh Naked Twister - always  a good ice-breaker back in the day...  or maybe not.    
    
    
    I'm going to get weird followings cause I said 'Naked Twister' aren't I? Still learning.    
    
    
    Clearly, playing on Social Media instead of getting out 2 proposals that must be delivered today is more important.  I'm off to re-focus.    
    
    
    @subtitling I'm at that event. Suffering major man flu, I struggled to remember the name of my business on the phone this am. Should be fun.    
    
    
    Arsenal vs. Barcelona. Saw Barca the other night, they were like the Harlem Globe Trotters - without a bucket of water chucked over the ref.    
    
    
    'Cortez The Killer' - Neil Young    
    
    
    @hannahbryan Like the website!    
    
    
    Quality tax disc holder: http://bit.ly/dtOqFj    
    
    
    'Stairway' comes number 1 in Planet Rock best ever rock song poll.  Sometimes its nice to have a constant. Damned good track too!    
    
    
    Songs you (probably) shouldn't play at a vicar's tea party - #1 Closer, by NIN    
    
    
    @Dushyantor Not sure Tiger's wife would be happy with him sliding back into anything at the moment. Oo-er.    
    
    
    @YourFilm_KO Perhaps not, but worth hanging onto a copy.    
    
    
    Is against ageism in job advertisements. Particularly from public funded organisations.    
    
    
    One small change makes the point: "Looking for people to front a PR campaign:white's only, tyne&wear/northumberland". Pretty bad now, huh?    
    
    
    It was originally "aged 20-35". Don't be ageist (or racist)! You know who you are!!!    
    
    
    I'm waiting to be PAT tested    
    
    
    Very, very clever. But I'm holding out for a "handsome" button. RT @paul_vaclik: Coming soon to Photoshop: http://bit.ly/cFZpcj    
    
    
    @woodss Assuming your arm remains attached, of course.    
    
    
    PAT time!    
    
    
    2 hours later - our computers talk to each other again, to the printer, and to the internet. PAT testing? I'd rather the office burned down.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Ouch, scary. Running washing machines, tumble dryers, and dish washers while you go to work is the biggest risk apparently.    
    
    
    Playing with my new toy, a Bose docking station for my iPhone.    
    
    
    Richie Blackmore's Rainbow - tremendously self-indulgent.    
    
    
    Waiting for my wife to come home from her sister's and fix the various clocks/timers in the house. Why can't they all just run off a Mac?    
    
    
    www.smartworks-it.com    
    
    
    New company branding and website is live today: http://bit.ly/ccy7cU    
    
    
    @julianleighton Interested in the concept of a "spare" creme egg...    
    
    
    Proof that politicians are stupid & vengeful. RT @TheJournalNews: MP Kevan Jones stirs up Joanne Lumley over campaign: http://bit.ly/c21Wq3    
    
    
    Fed up being internal IT manager. I'm outsourcing the lot. Never mind paperless, I'm going for the computerless office (servers at least).    
    
    
    London Calling    
    
    
    Ruud Gullit on next table during meeting. Resisted odd compulsion to shout across "Aalreet, Ruud. Toon supporter" by way of introduction.    
    
    
    @subtitling the fairness space is a bit crowded at the moment - how about a party based on truth? #ge2010    
    
    
    Pistols on today. Seems only right.    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Kick Out The Jams by MC5    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Both, but the single is outstanding on its own.    
    
    
    @stuarthoward not forgetting Dusty Carpet (takes some beating) and Chewing Gum (sticks to the rails) at 20s.    
    
    
    If there's a volcanic ash cloud above us, does it mean that when it starts to rain it'll be raining Volvic?    
    
    
    Why does the cat only eat the front ends of mice?    
    
    
    Just in case you think that Nick Clegg is a fresh, dynamic, and decisive alternative: http://bit.ly/dji7p2 #canwehavesomebetterpoliticians    
    
    
    Mind I'll give Clegg his due - he did do that Derren Brown memory trick thing at the end where he remembered every questioner's name.    
    
    
    Mrs Clegg can send him shopping knowing she's never going to run out of toilet rolls, or moist wipes, or any of that stuff I always forget.    
    
    
    @davidcoxon That's pretty much how Derren Brown does t as well ;)    
    
    
    Orange Bus are nominated for a Dadi award! Vote now http://vote.dadiawards.com/     
    
    
    @leeanne_b The old Salvation Army temple on Westgate Road, Newcastle?    
    
    
    Customer tells me there's a 3 week delay in payments due to a change in their IT system. Has the computer confiscated your cheque book???    
    
    
    Which is a mite different from what the Mail reports! RT @mikebutcher: What Nick Clegg actually said. And he's right http://bit.ly/aR25Ek    
    
    
    Walking like Frankenstein's monster this morning. Overtraining has taken it's toll and now my hamstrings are exacting revenge.    
    
    
    I have a ticket going spare for #DIBI if anyone would like it. Regrettably I'm unable to attend.    
    
    
    Venting my frustration with the bast... people that came up with IE8.  No xhtml support? Shrink to fit broken? My plea? Use another browser.    
    
    
    @jerri_murtagh Bio Gel Nails? Possibly B&Q?    
    
    
    Dear MS, have spent 1+1/2 days refactoring an app cause IE won't print/download like all other browsers. To whom should I send my bill?    
    
    
    TFI Friday    
    
    
    This made me chuckle: http://bit.ly/dwoFH0    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Definitely not supporting IE6    
    
    
    Good song for an election week: http://bit.ly/cLVtPe    
    
    
    Paperwork and admin this morning. Love it.    
    
    
    @justingsouter You could still wear it, but with trainers...    
    
    
    @libwella The BBC has 'Find your constituency' at http://bit.ly/cb8mid, as does the Guardian at http://bit.ly/aKSlS3 (and its better)    
    
    
    Regardless of who you choose, I urge everyone to vote tomorrow (unless you're a Nazi). People died so that we could.    
    
    
    @libwella There's also 'They work for you' http://bit.ly/dufANB which has questionnaire responses from candidates. Pretty cool.    
    
    
    @woodss Valid points, I would have loved to have voted on #debill for example. But someone has to run the show, there's tricky times ahead.    
    
    
    Sounds like geek civil unrest! RT @AlexJReid: They are throwing BlackBerry handsets at people, although why someone would choose a curve...    
    
    
    Neil Kinnock on radio 4 saying he's always been a supporter of PR... yeah, right, and was in love with Margaret Thatcher.    
    
    
    Mandelson was gushing about PR as soon as he saw the exit polls last night. Exactly how dishonest do you have to be to become a politician?    
    
    
    And Gordon Brown, resign for the sake of your own dignity, man.    
    
    
    Nick Clegg, it's time to get a backbone, son.    
    
    
    So Nick Clegg has spoken. Now we should get to see what David Cameron is really like.    
    
    
    Give the Tories enough rope. And a plastic bag. And a satsuma… (via @pekingspring)    
    
    
    The Stone Roses. Splendid.    
    
    
    Major de-clutter going on the office. Hope I don't chuck out any important stuff.    
    
    
    Just watched Cameron's speech, inviting a collaborative government with the Lib Dems. I must say I'm quite proud of him.    
    
    
    Dear Politicians, I don't want PR, I want my say on the issues I care about. The technology is here in front of me! PR is last year's model.    
    
    
    VAT return. Urrgghhh!    
    
    
    Here we go again... (via @TheJournalNews): NUFC: Chris Hughton won't be given any money for new players: http://bit.ly/cj0hyw    
    
    
    For a couple of days I thought politicians might be concerned with the voters, but now it seems they've reverted to narrow self interest.    
    
    
    Didn't have enough characters to write "Bastards" after that last post. More characters please, Twitter.    
    
    
    How can you sack the Fonz??? You can't sack the Fonz!!! RT @channel4news: West Ham sack Gianfranco Zola.    
    
    
    @chrisbarber86 SOAP's very bloaty, designed by enterprise bods, but it does have  advantages over REST (like security and authentication)    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays - SEO -- http://supermondays.eventbrite.com    
    
    
    I was horrified to learn that I'm 83% David Milliband. Shoot me now.    
    
    
    Although it's a bit like a choice between being shot or stabbed, quite frankly.    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe A man of taste indeed. Hopefully my STB will have recorded it for me to watch at my leisure.    
    
    
    @DifferenceEngin Or no streaming. Looks like the free, invite only access might be getting ditched.    
    
    
    There's always we7. Seems Spotify is reacting to the competition by copying their pricing model.    
    
    
    But who has the fullest catalogue? I can say we7 is great for any prog rock dinosaurs out there, but then Spotify ain't bad there either.    
    
    
    @jd I can recommend Planet Rock. And Classic FM. Both have great iPhone apps.    
    
    
    Not before Supermonday, we hope!! RT @LanceUlanoff: Is SEO Dying? http://bit.ly/bsSPuM via: @HotInTechnology    
    
    
    Is 'God 2.0' not the bloke who tried to patent the human genome a few years back?    
    
    
    For atheists, strictly speaking, I suppose he would be 'God 1.0'.    
    
    
    Been building up to it, it's now or never for the ultimate prog rock album... Tales from Topographic Oceans by Yes. I may be some time...    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Back from the journey, almost swept away by the dreamy lyrics and soundscapes. I have learned that I am not that prog!    
    
    
    Head's spinning with Topographic  Oceans. The cure for over-prog? Slash and Ian Astbury...    
    
    
    The EU has allowed genetically engineered crops into Europe. You can read more and sign a petition here http://www.greenpeace.org/GEpetition    
    
    
    Bullfighter comes second! http://bit.ly/aVvArC    
    
    
    Tweet number 666, a devil of a tweet    
    
    
    Strange buzzing in the office. Like a hyperactive wasp.    
    
    
    !!! RT @channel4news @frasereC4: Bradford: Stephen Griffiths accused of 3 murders calls himself "The Crossbow Cannibal" http://ht.ly/1R2VJ    
    
    
    @fixmyalloys no, and no, I understand    
    
    
    @fixmyalloys though you should be able to access your windows pc using a service like GoToMyPC    
    
    
    I'm attending The SMACS and SuperChristmas -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/25Zv    
    
    
    Dammit, I'm going for a run.    
    
    
    Sandwiches and iced knee for lunch    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Every little helps, I suppose.    
    
    
    Why am I ready to sleep now when I was wide a-bloody-wake at 4am this morning? No time for sleep, I've things to do!!!    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh 38974 is a lot of followers. But perhaps not enough to affirm deity. Are you saying the prayer came from 'down below'?    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh With a bit of social media coaching, he could make 50000 double quick... "I've just worked in a mysterious way , please RT" .    
    
    
    @justingsouter Of course, you could get @god up to 50000 followers no problem.    
    
    
    This is bound to end in tears: RT @LanceUlanoff: Mars Trip Simulation To Lock Up 6 Men In Mock Spaceship For 18 Months http://bit.ly/9nyX4A    
    
    
    Cooking risotto. And drinking beer. Who says men can't multi-task?    
    
    
    iPhone has just suggested 'Subaru' whilst I was trying to type 'signature'. I've never used the word 'Subaru' in my life (up to this point).    
    
    
    Know what I miss about this time on a Friday? CRACKERJACK!!!    
    
    
    Has just launched iComptroller - a new, super-simple, finance application for small businesses. www.icomptroller.com    
    
    
    @EmmyPips I always like it when people cut one leg shorter than the other - though I'm sure that won't happen to you.    
    
    
    It's clearly bed time. Confused between #NEFOLLOWERS and NEE FOLLOWERS!    
    
    
    @AlexJReid I was pleased to learn that, with iPhone 4, Apple had invented digital zoom.    
    
    
    @leeanne_b Really? Punch Ed Balls. Guess he's like Marmite. Diane Abbot - made a great speech on civil liberties during the 42 days thing.    
    
    
    @LeeABaker Happy Birthday, Matey. Forty again? I had a decent meal in the Silkroom the other week.    
    
    
    After 2000 years of stony silence will @HadriansWall reveal its secrets? Well no, but the lady takes a really nice photograph. #nefollowers    
    
    
    Just noticed John Prescott on here, spewing out his odd brand of class hate . Surely you'll be struggling with 140 caracters Mr P?    
    
    
    @docuguy Yeah, but do you really want to end up eating mutant produce from Monsanto et al? #organic    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB I predict drunkenness    
    
    
    Cat came in this morning COVERED in poo. Birds dive bombed him to protect a nest - top defensive move. I'm working on a way to adapt it.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh It was pretty funny actually, especially as the wife got to clean him up. And he's quite the patient patient, which helps.    
    
    
    Off to Lui's in Tynemouth for gargantuan veggie breakfast.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Avoidance involved 'bootcamp' on the beach, which nearly killed me. Need to find better avoidance strategies.    
    
    
    Top breakfast btw    
    
    
    @AllotmentAli I use F-Prot from Frisk. Fast, cheap, unobtrusive, and works really well.    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB Well, ultimately the football will disappoint, the lasting memory will be of an arm round a stranger  - your new best mate.    
    
    
    Fabulous. RT @woodss: RT @ryandownie: Pizza Hut Ireland are giving out a free Pizza every time a goal is scored against France.    
    
    
    Grumpy this morning. Late night last night. And required to wear tie today.    
    
    
    Parked in town, paid by phone, returned to a ticket. #newcastlecitycouncil #fail    
    
    
    So far I'm watching most of the world cup via terrestrial channels, on a retro Sony TV set, and really enjoying it. 100% reliable too.    
    
    
    Interesting. DabbleDB has been bought by Twitter: http://dabbledb.com/    
    
    
    As I can't be arsed to blow a vuvuzela for 90 minutes, wondering whether I'll be allowed into St. James' with a hoover for next season.    
    
    
    @subtitling I was just disappointed that Lord Saville didn't say "UhUhUhUhUhUhUh.... 'ows about that then?"    
    
    
    This ambush marketing that Budweiser are getting huffy about looks like fun. Unless you're Robbie Earle .    
    
    
    Using @icomptroller to invoice a client in Finland requiring EU reverse charge mechanism for VAT - easy peasy    
    
    
    I'd completely forgotten!!! RT @MaxMerch: Remember Ladies and Gents, This Sunday Is FATHERS DAY! http://bit.ly/cQuGmc    
    
    
    Java or Python?    
    
    
    Has anyone ever actually shown their arse in Fenwick's window? Could there be an opportunity for some of the empty high street shop fronts?    
    
    
    @subtitling Not really a fan of ONE myself - but there is a job to be done in the region    
    
    
    @LeeABaker Did we get out of bed the wrong side this morning? Mind you, agree about EC trains.    
    
    
    @Markedintime So true. Perhaps a better risk balance, like "I'll show my arse in Fenwick's window if Newcastle finish above fourth bottom"    
    
    
    Cosgrove Hall, the company that made Danger Mouse, has gone out of business http://bit.ly/cZoVwR    
    
    
    @BACKConsulting Marvellous, doesn't that just take you back?    
    
    
    @YourFilm_KO Have a good tirme. I hope your mates are kind to you!    
    
    
    Twitter: "Something is technically wrong". Yes it is.    
    
    
    @LeeABaker So he did more than just bash his bishop then    
    
    
    @souterconsults It's not one of those dinner clubs where they eat rare animals and human flesh, is it?    
    
    
    Who'd have thought it, Germany miss penalty in 1-0 defeat by Serbia.    
    
    
    Mind, this Stella is pretty strong! Will I make the full 90 minutes or will it be an early bath for me?    
    
    
    My team for Slovenia: James,Johnson,Terry,Upson,Cole A,Lennon,Gerard,Barry,Cole J,Crouch,Defoe; playing 4-4-fucking-2.    
    
    
    @tmjackson Dawson or Upson is a difficult call. Both look good but make mistakes. If only Titus Bramble was there... ;)    
    
    
    @YourFilm_KO Glad to see you made it!    
    
    
    Not a great report fot the NE http://bit.ly/9RZBkl  @GIRL_GEEKS_NE: RT @hmtreasury Find out what the economic picture is like in your region    
    
    
    @Financetree It does, but that shouldn't stop us from trying to throw out the bathwater - just that we should be careful when we do it.    
    
    
    David Beckham for England player-manager for the Euros. Think about it, it makes sense! #BeckhamforEnglandmanager    
    
    
    @skipchris Although we shouldn't overlook great English candidates either, David Beckham for example #BeckhamforEnglandmanager    
    
    
    @skipchris BTW since when was Sir Alf Ramsey foreign???    
    
    
    @skipchris Southern, yes, but foreign is stretching it a bit!    
    
    
    @ethicalhack3r  I think most do, in one form or another    
    
    
    Watching the #budget live: http://bit.ly/a50Uil    
    
    
    There's blood all over the floor here #budget    
    
    
    VAT 20% from next January. Unrest in the house!    
    
    
    Reduced rate VAT rises to 6%    
    
    
    Capital gains 28% for higher rate tax payers #budget    
    
    
    Harriet Harman's upset that there's no money for equality focus groups on Gruinard, or a visitor centre at the bottom of Lake Windermere.    
    
    
    @icanzilb Thx for the feedback    
    
    
    iOS 4 upgrade has broken Planet Rock app. NOOOOOOO!!!!!!!!    
    
    
    And Classic FM app. Bastards!!!    
    
    
    Apparently I can now multi-task, I just can't listen to Purple while I do it #fail    
    
    
    Off to watch the match. In a quiet room, on my own, in case it goes badly (I don't like people seeing me cry, or ranting like a lunatic).    
    
    
    @davidcoxon Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    Pepe Le Pew, poss? RT @KateSlaterPR: RT @realradio: A raccoon's been spotted in a Durham back garden - http://bit.ly/bJhCAD #NEFollowers    
    
    
    Dear Fabio, I enjoy being humiliated by Germany as much as the next man, but surely its time for a different trick from the FA bag?    
    
    
    simplecdn has imploded! darn! anyone know any good, inexpensive, CDN providers that will allow me to stream video to our site?    
    
    
    Fox has taken all of our chickens. Again. Thinking of having the fox killed. Anyone got any better ideas?    
    
    
    @LouiseNorthwood That old chestnut? "I was just showing him how to tweet..."    
    
    
    @MyOtherLifeBand Try wordpress.com, can be turned into more than a blog; or blogger.com (Google)    
    
    
    @tmjackson We had a cockerel built like Foghorn Leghorn last time, and even he succumbed.    
    
    
    @coldclimate it seems they're not confident of restoring the service    
    
    
    @spoutingshite RealVNC possibly. I can also recommend LogMeIn.com    
    
    
    Just squished one of those tiny red spiders (accident). Big explosion. There's no way you can fit that much spider into such a small bod.    
    
    
    Heard some outrageous gossip about Steven Gerrard this morning.  I'll check the web - if it's on the web it must be true.    
    
    
    Getting paid can be even more satisfying RT @jnanagarbha: Rediscovering the satisfaction of invoicing. I really should do it more often! #fb    
    
    
    Top tip: if you have a hitman after you,  don't use gowalla/foursquare from your phone.    
    
    
    On the other hand, "I'm marooned on a desert island" would have saved Robinson Crusoe a whole load of grief.    
    
    
    What with all this twittering and blogging, how can we ever find time to do any actual work? Its a government conspiracy, I'm telling you...    
    
    
    I'm hoping that 'What are you doing?' isn't a question to take literally, otherwise this whole exercise could get very boring very quickly    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh i've bitten the bullet and registered for this thing - still convinced its 99.9% dross    
    
    
    @JamieFDHurst There was some Floyd on we7 last time I looked    
    
    
        
    
    
    @richardmlane You could look at Sky over the internet.    
    
    
    @JamieFDHurst It's very good. More ads. Spotify just edges it for me, but we7 has music catalogues that Spotify doesn't.    
    
    
    Wonder if he's got a few "squid" on the result?    
    
    
    back from #TDC practical wisdom lecture, especially enjoyed the guys from ethical superstore    
    
    
    @canny_lass I'm interested in Whitley Bay regeneration, but can't make tonight. I'd be keen to attend next event.    
    
    
    Name badge, check; attractive conference bag, check; business cards, check; clean underpants, check. Right I'm off to Thinking Digital. #TDC    
    
    
    @monitorcreative  Hi Caroline, if you're not using an invoicing tool we'd love feedback on our app icomptroller.com. We're in early beta.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Could just make government data sets free for download - the API, infastructure, etc costs can then be borne by the developer?    
    
    
    @AlexJReid geotag litter eyesores and fly tipping too - but don't get me started on that because I become 'disproportionate' in my responses    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Indeed. That's the gamble. There are ways to start cheap, of course.    
    
    
    @jonoble I hoping it has been - I'm going there tomorrow    
    
    
    1st day back in the office after ThinkingDigital, which I really enjoyed. Lots of work to pick up - I hate Mondays    
    
    
    Interesting. Our office landlord has started offering virtual offices: http://www.fabriam.com/virtual_office/    
    
    
    New blog post on Founder Dating @TechHub http://bit.ly/bvhYQ9    
    
    
    heart pounding, gasping for air... are lunchtime gym sessions really that good for you?    
    
    
    Testing jtwitter on my mobile. Who needs iphone or android?    
    
    
    New blog post: Founder Dating @TechHub http://bit.ly/bvhYQ9    
    
    
    @libwella Keep an eye on the hedgehog. Sometimes when you see them during the day its because they are poorly. And birds/flies attack them.    
    
    
    @rosscooney True, but the days when I'm a statue seem to be the ones when the pigeon has had a particularly bad tummy!    
    
    
    Wonder  if any begin "Thou shalt not..."? RT @channel4news: Vatican sets out new rules to stamp out paedophilia  - http://bit.ly/9Czvq0    
    
    
    @JamieFDHurst @AlexJReid 924s were horrid (not proper Porches some say), but I always loved the 928 - nearly bought one 10-12 years  back    
    
    
    Problems with 3GS and iOS4. Nice to know it isn't just 'a few' people (as O2 claimed to me yesterday): http://bit.ly/9LA0iN    
    
    
    Not that lots of people with a problem is a good thing, but it's good that it's more likely to be fixed soon.    
    
    
    Watching The Open. Can't stand golf, but John Daly is looking like Bing Crosby's version of Psychedelia. Hilarious.    
    
    
    Actually, it's more like Vivienne Westwood and Pringle of Scotland had all out war - and Daly is the peace deal.    
    
    
    After my initial scepticism, I now think this sort of tool could be great; we need to replace email; add encryption to stop H.M. Gov snoops    
    
    
    Statue day!    
    
    
    Statistician on R4 predicted this weekends premier league scores: Newcastle & Boro go down; hoping he's the same bloke Alistair Darling uses    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh and well done you for making it all hang together    
    
    
    Ready for the weekend. In the words of Terry Collier: 'That's what a weekend should be - sport, sleep, slippers and sex'.    
    
    
    @LouiseNorthwood Durham passport office was super quick when I did that.    
    
    
    Interesting opportunity for freelance PHP. DM me if interested.    
    
    
    @LouiseNorthwood @TheStarPA Thanks for the RTs!    
    
    
    @richardmlane I took an upgrade to iOS4 on Friday which has improved my 3GS quite a lot... so far    
    
    
    Speechless, near catatonic due to relegation shock. Wake me up when we're back in the premier league!    
    
    
    Up and at 'em this morning. Inspired by digital jewelry that can be stroked to cause a piece worn by a loved one to vibrate. #supermondays    
    
    
    Playing with Flipboard on my new iPad - awesome!    
    
    
    @libwella Everybody calls their home 'Dunroamin'. My parents have a house that used to be called 'Westoe' - very grand for a 3 bed semi.    
    
    
    @libwella What about going to the front door and naming it the first thing you see as you look out? Unless it's dog poo...    
    
    
    Knocking off for the day to watch Man U get thrashed.    
    
    
    @rosscooney image 9 is the standout for me, image 10 at a push. Please no superman logos!    
    
    
    Almost knocking off time and I'm nowhere near through my todo list for today - although I have debated the finer points of stone masonry    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperSummer Soiree -- http://supersummer.eventbrite.com    
    
    
    Still searching for a PHP dev to work  for 3 months @bdaily_info    
    
    
    Checking my call list for this week. I wrote 'WANKER' next to one name, due to poor response. He's since proved helpful. Feeling guilty now.    
    
    
    Crossing out the word 'WANKER'.    
    
    
    Sitting outside cafe in jesmond. Life's good.    
    
    
    Too knackered to do any more work, bring me beer. Beer I say!    
    
    
    @BACKConsulting Does the Rhubarb challenge involve eating the stuff?    
    
    
    @BACKConsulting There's rules right? Like not being allowed to puke immediately afterwards... that sort of thing?    
    
    
    I've just caught a mouse with my bare hands. Cat  just looked on - be impressed my boy, be impressed.    
    
    
    Eagerly awaiting FA Cup Final kick off. Still a top day, but whatever happened to 'Its a Cup Final Knockout'? And pre-match Scooby-doo?    
    
    
    Not long now, teams are warming up. Abide With Me soon, a lump in the throat, and God Save the Queen. Makes you proud!    
    
    
    @woodss ditto - will be flagging by mid afternoon probably.    
    
    
    ...and this morning I caught a bird with my bare hands - not so difficult this time, I simply took it from the cat's mouth. Bird ok.    
    
    
    @davegardnerisme I have a well thumbed copy of Sams "Pure Java 2" by Kenneth Litwak - great basis. Then Java site for related technologies.    
    
    
    Chelsea. Again. Oh well.    
    
    
    @michaelpeacock They'll become exciting again when you get to 90, I imagine.    
    
    
    What makes an invoice? http://bit.ly/bRpO44 #accounting #invoicing    
    
    
    Hans Rosling on the Today program on Radio 4: http://tinyurl.com/mlq7vy    
    
    
    Thanks @ajkavanagh @SGltd for the excellent @supermondays summer soiree last night    
    
    
    @BACKConsulting Might be on for it if you can eat a finger of raw ginger whilst I trough the rhubarb!    
    
    
    @kristianlunde Using TweetDeck myself    
    
    
    Hear Hear! RT @_StuartLynn: RT @JamieForster iOS4 is pants. For a company that bitches about microsofts unstable platform ...    
    
    
    Dear O2, can I have a crap old phone to enable me to actually make phone calls until Apple get their sh*t together?    
    
    
    Finally at the end of a long day of being bullied by various technologies (Google App Engine, JasperReports, and MS SQL Server)    
    
    
    OK, after about 5 minutes on Bing the phrase springs to mind 'Google clone'. Now I really am going home.    
    
    
    @HadriansWall excellent    
    
    
    Once again, I find myself in awe of Flipboard. It's so impressive.    
    
    
    @alenadundas you can do them with a bloodspot test these days, maybe he meant that.    
    
    
    @daftks Hi, you could try our web app for invoicing, icomptroller.com    
    
    
    @rosscooney Sadly I live in a workplace where video over the web is a far off futuristic concept, so I have to wait for transcripts or demos    
    
    
    You lucky, lucky man! RT @DeclanMetcalfe: I'm at Starbucks At Newport Pagnell Services http://bit.ly/bSkAtW    
    
    
    @BACKConsulting Oh my. Before you know it it'll be PHP this, and Webkit that, and you'll be writing rude things on walls about Bill Gates.    
    
    
    Danny La Rue died the other day! I saw a clip of his act from the 70s, basically a bloke in a frock singing badly. Why did my parents laugh?    
    
    
    Sidetracked by the maths quiz at http://tinyurl.com/olccu9. Prepare to put reputations on the line.    
    
    
    Just registered at http://www.tweetmondo.com to search for Twitter users close to me!    
    
    
    Forgot to bring my morning banana to the office... energy draining away... Its really pecking my head. How set in my ways???    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/6lgg0 - Traffic holdup on the way back from the gym, a family of swans. Wonderful.    
    
    
    I've finally got my banana. Good start to the afternoon.    
    
    
    @KarlFreeman Hi Karl, recently launched an invoicing/book-keeping tool , iComptroller.com; would love your feedback esp as a freshbooks user    
    
    
    @canny_lass Sorry to hear about @Off_Spring. It IS better to try and fail than not to try. To quote Churchill: "KBO".    
    
    
    @easbynow Indeed, steak bakes are out. A cheese pastie or a mini-quiche would have been more appropriate.    
    
    
    Checking out pigeons using Twitter. There's loads, probably some of them aren't the real deal, but @feral_pigeon might be worth a look    
    
    
    #musicmonday The Saturdays. Hopeless - but look fantastic!    
    
    
    Mild threats in letter to the office from TV Licensing. Cheeky tw*ts want me to pay for a stamp to tell them we don't have a TV. FRO I say.    
    
    
    @rosscooney Mind you're cutting it a bit fine with the training, man!    
    
    
    Thinking about chucking out some obsolete computer equipment until someone pointed me to this http://tinyurl.com/nkpt8j    
    
    
    Someone trying to tell me that BNP voters aren't racist. Yeah, right. RT @channel4news Who voted BNP and why? http://bit.ly/188PTj    
    
    
    Outside the Skylight Cafe. Large Americano and 'Stairway' to start a busy day.    
    
    
    Quality... RT @channel4news *Video* BNP's Nick Griffin egg attack outside Houses of Parliament http://bit.ly/17pUrM    
    
    
    Thinks @feral_pigeon talks more sense than Nick Griffin    
    
    
    Interesting to see how many people are hacked off with O2. I have a stylish but near-functionless Nokia 6500c and all this passes my by    
    
    
    Avoiding right hooks thrown by the cat while I'm trying to work. Pound for pound he could be a contender.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Poetry can blow you away, check out Wilfred Owen http://tinyurl.com/klx52z esp. 'Dulce et Decorum Est'    
    
    
    @easbynow Having read this, it strikes me as particularly lazy journalism. Typical crap I've been hearing for years. RT http://is.gd/Xbps    
    
    
    Going to 'Delivering the Future', an exhibition of graduate work by students of Northumbria Uni School of Computing    
    
    
    Banging headache this morning. Have self-prescribed black coffee and Voltarol.    
    
    
    Follow Friday @feral_pigeon. That pigeon's enlarged my mind. He's a poet-warrior in the classic sense.    
    
    
    Just started my new blog: http://davidlavery.blogspot.com/    
    
    
    #beatlesporn 'Something in the way she moos, attracts me like no other lover'    
    
    
    Hello, World http://tinyurl.com/lovlkt    
    
    
    Finally standardised my web identity across google, facebook, linkedin, and twitter - the rest can all go to hell    
    
    
    Just added myself to the http://wefollow.com twitter directory under:  #tech #internet #entrepreneur    
    
    
    This looks cool from Google http://tinyurl.com/kvlm4x    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh I shall blog about it at some point... after the dust has settled    
    
    
    Eye test confirms I need reading glasses for close up. Age related.    
    
    
    Had to finish off a poor mouse this morning. Cat-mangled beyond repair I'm afraid.    
    
    
    I hope there's someone around to do that to me when the time comes    
    
    
    Just not with the wife's stone chicken patio ornament, please    
    
    
    Called Setanta to cancel my package due to recent relegation - the argument to stay was that I could now watch Gateshead in the conference    
    
    
    @channel4news How about the Blairs?    
    
    
    Checking out Seesmic desktop to help me filter my stream and keep tabs on Facebook too    
    
    
    Pissed off with our ISP, who claims to have lost our DD mandate. I have to double check back to February to make sure that's the case. Grrr!    
    
    
    A new one to the repertoire! RT @feral_pigeon poo on a passer-by    
    
    
    What about the hungry? 'Let them eat IE8'  http://bit.ly/eKriB    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays -- 29th June at the Beehive -- http://supermondays.eventbrite.com/?ref=twittershare    
    
    
    Just when the exterminate button on my remote is on the blink ! RT @channel4news: David Miliband on the prog tonight.    
    
    
    @mikeyparker action without measurement is like... being blind in a nudist colony??    
    
    
    @mikeyparker I was having a Carry On/Benny Hill moment...    
    
    
    @mikeyparker How about 'action without measurement will still produce an equal but opposite reaction - so be very careful'    
    
    
    This looks like fun RT @TCEurope: Guardian releases crowd-sourcing app to pick over MPs expenses http://tcrn.ch/4A6 by @mikebutcher    
    
    
    Very droll RT @channel4news: Overheard in the newsroom: "At least he fixed the roof while the sun was shining..." http://bit.ly/CrslI    
    
    
    Trying to hold a telephone meeting. First a fire alarm at their end, then a fire alarm (drill) at our end. F*&&*?!*    
    
    
    As its Friday, a cheery Scarfe cartoon (an oldy but goody) to round off the week http://bit.ly/TaqYD    
    
    
    Just spent a boring half hour going through MPs expenses on-line. Dull. There's a receipt for 'chick boys' in there somewhere, I know it!    
    
    
    @mikeyparker The Stig 'unveiling' was still pretty impressive though    
    
    
    Impressed by the power of Google Apps, particularly for startup or microbusinesses.    
    
    
    Rule 1's pretty much it! RT @saratpediredla: Loving the northern translation for the rules for HackNorth http://www.hacknorth.com/rules/    
    
    
    @mikeyparker can help public transport with quality of service feedback, personal safety and security, reliability data, anti-vandalism...    
    
    
    Kid dressed as Jimmy Connors on 'Murray Mound'. Pass the rifle.    
    
    
    @mikeyparker #WDYTYG As well as UGC for reliability, security, and quality on public transport, what about dating? Couples meet on buses!!!    
    
    
    GO on Murray son!! Break up in the 2nd set... NO! I'm catching it now    
    
    
    Sorry 3rd set. Excitement got to me!    
    
    
    3rd set in the bag! 2-1. Shoot me now    
    
    
    Cat's just eaten a Daddy Long Legs    
    
    
    And left me a drumstick behind I notice. Nice one    
    
    
    I haven't used Outlook (or Outlook Express/Windows Mail) in years.  Outlook 2010 isn't on my shopping list, and I'm feeling pretty relaxed.    
    
    
    I'm attending CloudCamp North-East England July 29th, 2009 -- http://bit.ly/y9496    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh I hope she's ok    
    
    
    1 million people follow Yoko Ono???    
    
    
    @Pete_sherpa I assume that's a rhetorical question. Though pot, kettle, and black also sprang to mind.    
    
    
    @Markedintime I was worried about the Blair resemblance - thought I'd got away with it! Rotten eggs anyone?    
    
    
    @ninacliff It's expensive. Have a look at ZOHO CRM - it's free for up to 3 users.    
    
    
    Branding the Ego http://bit.ly/mxahE    
    
    
    @rosscooney Well spotted! One or two problems with TwitterFeed but should get blog updates posting to Twitter from now on.    
    
    
    Busy day. #WDYTYG, dipping out for a mysterious meeting this pm,  finally Thursday Fizz. Yikes! (Further cartoon expletives to follow)    
    
    
    Running late now. Lummee!    
    
    
    Hello, World http://bit.ly/RgsrA    
    
    
    #wdytyg lots of transport data, some public but not publicised it seems    
    
    
    #wdytyg i see benefit in getting more commercial digital people involved with this group    
    
    
    #wdytyg nexus: 23% of people want real time transport data via mobile    
    
    
    Fun with the Google App Engine http://bit.ly/uEeNz    
    
    
    Excellent Thursday Fizz do last night. Great atmosphere.    
    
    
    Trying to make a gazillion phone calls before the weekend. Why?? They'll all still be there Monday morning.    
    
    
    Had I invented Google, would I have called it 'Gazilliun'?    
    
    
    Wondering why the blasted Facebook Twitter app doesn't feed my updates to fb.    
    
    
    #followfriday @feral_pigeon. He's the boss, he's the VIP, he's a championship. He's the most tip top - Top Pigeon    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Dark humour I know, just couldn't resist it.    
    
    
    Guilty pleasure, watching Countdown via time shift. Make a word out of this: KRAOTYBUO    
    
    
    Watching Glastonbury highlights on red button. Friendly Fires and Fleet Foxes v impressive. Crosby, Stills, and Nash awesome yesterday.    
    
    
    Wife jumping around the lounge to the Specials!    
    
    
    Interesting article on Google and the Mobile and Enterprise markets  http://bit.ly/4EAUyF    
    
    
    Looking forward to #supermondays tonight.    
    
    
    @iambigred There's some good stuff here: http://www.freemaptools.com/    
    
    
    First iPhone app is in the iTunes store now. Medilocate. It helps you to find the available NHS services around you. Woohoo.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid For various reasons I chose Appcelerator, but my next project could suit Phonegap nicely.    
    
    
    There's a kid busking in Central Arcade with a Cello. Wonderful. I love Newcastle.    
    
    
    @ChiOnwurah Labour MPs stop moaning about cuts. Either lead, follow, or get out of the way.    
    
    
    @tmjackson maybe she has 6 boyfriends?    
    
    
    Listening to Happy Mondays on the train. Come on and tell me twice-a.    
    
    
    @mikeyparker you're lucky you're not on this sodding train, then    
    
    
    This train will terminate at Darlington?!? But that's not where I'm going!!! Should have got off this heap and changed at York!!!    
    
    
    @davidcoxon Running for 2 hours? Not more trouble with the police, surely ;-)    
    
    
    New rule: don't ask your wife to order fancy dress for you on-line    
    
    
    Moving email and calendar to Google Apps. Some issues with email redirection caused by DNS host.    
    
    
    Early start, off to Durham for an all-dayer. Looking forward to #TAAD later.    
    
    
    Sitting in a durham car park listening to the true genius of a dear friend. Should be at a conference. Rock n roll.    
    
    
    Is it just me or are Google's driving directions generally about as accurate as sticking a pin in a map blindfolded?    
    
    
    @orangebus Many congratulations!!!    
    
    
    Working form home (or watching tennis if you prefer) this afternoon. Tight game in progress Murray v Roddick.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/9a9c4 - Why you shouldn't let your wife choose a fancy dress costume for you.    
    
    
    Guilty pleasure: Planet Rock. Not 'arf. And doing expenses and various other business paperwork.    
    
    
    Slightly hungover. No meetings today. Excellent opportunity to make progress on my pet projects.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh about NHS records? I like the idea of choosing, not the idea of giving it to giant US companies.    
    
    
    Fail. 46% in the UK citizenship test  http://bit.ly/1irE0Y.    
    
    
    @subtitling The New City Library in Newcastle has free wifi, and it's a pretty cool building too. Well worth a visit.    
    
    
    Hats off to Bytemark Hosting today.    
    
    
    Looking for a chemist, dentist, or optician in your area? The medilocate iphone app is in the iTunes store now!    
    
    
    Top tip for those of us who need a quick workaround for pages that go haywire under the new IE8 'standards' http://bit.ly/naQLr    
    
    
    Cricket on the radio; cup of tea; bit of coding. Top morning.    
    
    
    Blowers on now. Now the ashes  begins.    
    
    
    Cool, Aggers on Twitter for ashes updates @Aggerscricket    
    
    
    RT You might say Windows is just DOS that boots to Explorer! @richrad Chrome OS is just Linux that boots directly into the Chrome browser.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh  I understand you can take paracetamol (safely) in conjunction with ibuprofen    
    
    
    Just finished writing a proposal. Had to be in tonight. Just In Time or what?    
    
    
    TMS day 3 of the 1st test. At stumps yesterday Jason Gillespie (ex Aussie) said Ponting must be 'as happy as a fat spider'. Precious.    
    
    
    @Dushyantor but if you expect things to go wrong and they usually do, then you'll never be disappointed    
    
    
    Hats off to Monkseaton Computers http://bit.ly/a9KTUV - helped me out of a sticky internet connectivity spot yesterday.    
    
    
    EastCoast wifi no longer free? Guessing the only improvement will be to their cashflow. But its a v. poor service, so no cash from me.    
    
    
    @Pete_sherpa Sounds cool - sorry for the late reply    
    
    
    Can't believe Tony Curtis has passed away...http://bit.ly/bIPGjX (via @DeclanMetcalfe)    
    
    
    @fuselagetown Are you turning British?    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays -- 27th July @ the Beehive -- http://bit.ly/16xcbM    
    
    
    @rosscooney Aren't typos all part of the fun though?    
    
    
    Interesting comment on the Google App Engine by  @rosscooney  http://bit.ly/cLjti    
    
    
    What makes a good networking event ? http://bit.ly/pcVBr    
    
    
    What Makes a Good Networking Event? http://bit.ly/Gv99S    
    
    
    Wow! RT @channel4news: A motorcyclist jumped the gap in Tower Bridge last night! We've got the video http://bit.ly/9IuvO    
    
    
    And I'm a teapot. RT @channel4news: Michael Owen gives his first Man U press conference and says he isn't injury prone. http://bit.ly/15ida0    
    
    
    @leeanne_b UX workshop would be very interesting    
    
    
    @leeanne_b how UX design could improve productivity in business apps, optimal design for mobile apps, and consistency across platforms    
    
    
    Trying to download windows 7 release candidate. It's killing our bandwidth, though I suspect that's an ISP issue.    
    
    
    Looking for an experienced PHP dev for bdaily, http://bit.ly/5D5iaA. DM me if interested.    
    
    
    @mynameiscolin the bdaily is still here - it'll be in your inbox tomorrow morning.    
    
    
    @leesimpson Thx    
    
    
    PLEASE NO !!! RT @YourFilm_KO: Kinnear to return as NUFC manager??   http://tinyurl.com/ntvr4n    
    
    
    showing off my new picture, courtesy of my wife and her new LG phone. A good likeness I think!    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Gooseberry & ginger jam? You're picking ingredients at random now!    
    
    
    @davidcoxon MS have been trying to push ie8 for a week or so. I've managed to stop it on my Vista laptop, but one of our XP boxes got caught    
    
    
    Loving my new picture, drawn by my wife on her new phone. Not sure she's got my neck quite right though.    
    
    
    Test match about to start. England won toss and are batting.    
    
    
    @hannahbryan I think the place is fabulous, I'm suffering a little office envy!    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Listening. Test Match Special online, a national institution. Blowers at the mike right now!    
    
    
    @rosstimson have you checked out  the easy_install doc at http://bit.ly/tIePw ?    
    
    
    England middle order batting very poorly here - again    
    
    
    @woodss Agreed    
    
    
    @leeanne_b we got married at Eshott and it was wonderful.    
    
    
    @leeanne_b Twitter site -> Settings -> Design tab -> Change background image -> upload image and save. Should do the trick.    
    
    
    Can't believe I've only one week left before I leave Orange Bus. Really looking forward to the future and many new opportunities.    
    
    
    As a North-East based #PHP'er, would you like to meet on the 3rd Thursday of every month? #phpne http://twtpoll.com/0lbmfp (via @phpne)    
    
    
    Last day today, then out into the big bad world...    
    
    
    @libwella I'm certainly hoping so ;)    
    
    
    @fuselagetown where are you off to?    
    
    
    I'm attending Open Data -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/1TKF    
    
    
    So far some very interesting responses to our job ad: http://bit.ly/aU7gW5    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Any idea whether you can hack a polar heart monitor? Might be interesting to try.    
    
    
    Still recovering my composure after nearly writing myself off cycling this morning (3 times!). It's a dangerous world out there at 5.30am!    
    
    
    Came off (like a human cannonball); narrowly avoided same 5 mins later; then only cat-like reflexes saved me from head-on with car.    
    
    
    Not good conditions for semi-slicks    
    
    
    I blow you a kiss, it should reach you tomorrow, as it flies from the other side of the world. Spotify    
    
    
    Writing a 'responsibility matrix' for our part of a greater whole. My name's mentioned far too many times!    
    
    
    Rimsky-Korsakov on Spotify. Cool.    
    
    
    If I ever get out of here, thought of  givin' it all away, to a registered charity, all I need is a pint a day, if I ever get out of here...    
    
    
    Close to the knuckle. RT @pekingspring: Fake Steve Jobs on Third-World labour: http://bit.ly/jbu9h    
    
    
    If every footballer were to punch someone repeatedly every time his team beat Newcastle, then we should all be afraid  http://bit.ly/10XHRz    
    
    
    Pietersen out for series. Did Vaughan pack in too early? RT @Aggerscricket: Bell 3, Colly 4, Bopara 5? Looks a bit thin, doesn't it    
    
    
    @saratpediredla How does that work? "Sorry, Mr Important Customer, can't shake your  hand in case you've got swine flu"    
    
    
    @saratpediredla That's spooky. I thought you'd read it rather than had personal experience.  Was he/she wearing a mask?    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh was it swine plaster?    
    
    
    One to think about, RT @TechCrunch: On the Apparent Apple Suicide http://tcrn.ch/Dpc by @johnbiggs    
    
    
    Thinking Neil Young is awesome, "Its better to burn out than to fade away. My, my, hey, hey."    
    
    
    @saratpediredla Try not to punch him :)    
    
    
    Also not going to see @yiannopoulos. I've nothing to say to him + I don't want to make him feel important + better things to do.    
    
    
    @CycleRepairShed I did indeed, thanks to your good work. Great day for cycling - bike's dirty again now though :)    
    
    
    Just finished work, off to #TAAD in great haste    
    
    
    iWise "Wisdom on Demand" http://bit.ly/YKFjs. And they have an API! Could make an interesting tweet off between Freud and Jung.    
    
    
    Or an iWise Twitter debate between St. Augustine and Richard Dawkins perhaps?    
    
    
    @rosscooney still 2 working days to go 'til Monday too!    
    
    
    @davidcoxon Works curry? A Baltic Balti perhaps?    
    
    
    Anyone reccomend an iphone app for twitter?    
    
    
    @kristianlunde thx for the twitterific tip, I'll give it a try    
    
    
    Just sooooo impressive. RT @davidcoxon: completely completely awsome RT @HausProjects: Just WOW. http://bit.ly/y2DsW  (RT @Documentally)    
    
    
    Bhjjjjjjj    
    
    
    Trying to tweet with my thumbs on iphone    
    
    
    @Alex_McVey :) I think it's my most coherent tweet so far    
    
    
    Found tweetdeck for iphone! Neither tweetie nor twitterific would work properly.    
    
    
    @easbynow I must have lost some tweets - many (belated) happy returns!    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe new iPhone - setup has taken precedence over all other activities!    
    
    
    Cloudy day today. Off to Cloud Seminar this afternoon, then Cloudcamp tonight.    
    
    
    After yesterday i'm thinking the future is definitely cloudy    
    
    
    Watching Avon from Blake's 7 in Emmerdale. Seems to be getting it on with Madge from Neighbours. Odd.    
    
    
    He's dressed as a biker and seems to have lost his perspex computer he used to carry everywhere, his only friend. Orac was the name, I think    
    
    
    @AlexJReid you feeding sap with idocs?    
    
    
    Amen to that. RT @ThursdayFizz: RIP Sir Bobby Robson you were a True Legend.    
    
    
    How true. RT @Toltecjohn: "Long is the way and hard, that out of hell leads up to light" John Milton -- a new poem - http://bit.ly/gPORe    
    
    
    @ThursdayFizz Are you thinking of doing it in one day, or two?    
    
    
    @ThursdayFizz I've done west2east: 3 days is good, 2 days challenging, 1 day is for extreme types! Those hills are BIG. #east2west    
    
    
    @saratpediredla Congratulations on the new office!    
    
    
    @ThursdayFizz I can get lost going to the corner shop! Spent the c2c following the guy in front (can get his advice though). #east2westcoast    
    
    
    Beginning to wonder what the alcohol hand rub - that's been installed in the offices to combat swine flu - tastes like.    
    
    
    @mikeyparker top tip - dusty carpet in the 2.30, it's never been beaten    
    
    
    Stuck in an eighties time warp and loving it! Pet Shop Boys, what a band.    
    
    
    @YourFilm_KO Very good    
    
    
    Here in my pocket I got the story of the blues. Maggie, Maggie, Maggie! Out, Out, Out!    
    
    
    Bad news, it's my favourite TV news source. RT @channel4news: http://bit.ly/1fZFrN    
    
    
    England's middle order wobbling. Why would you not play a guy averaging nearly 100?    
    
    
    England getting skittled. All out for under 100? #ashes    
    
    
    England all out for 102. Why bring in Harmison for Flintoff and then choose to bat? Bowl first morning at Headingley, surely. #ashes    
    
    
    Excited about going to Headingley tomorrow. Will it be as frantic as today or will we be watching the Aussies bat all day? #ashes    
    
    
    Back  from watching England getting caned at Headingley. Despite that a great time was had by all.    
    
    
    @Aggerscricket HTC magic handset is a google android  phone - great for tweeting    
    
    
    At the vets :(    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh lame cat - she's on metacam for a week    
    
    
    Breaking Into Heaven with The Stone Roses... man    
    
    
    Is there a better band on the planet than the New York Dolls? Actually lots, but I always find their anarchy strangely appealing.    
    
    
    @Alex_McVey Good choice!    
    
    
    I did it... I finally did it http://bit.ly/sb5u2    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays -- Tuesday 1st September -- http://bit.ly/10wWn9    
    
    
    @fuselagetown belated happy birthday!    
    
    
    Great 'graphic RT @paul_vaclik: How much?? This is fascinating and very worrying http://bit.ly/17FBsR    
    
    
    @rosscooney Expecting a big finale on the last day of the Software City blog :)    
    
    
    @Aggerscricket RT @AlexJReid - I've not had any issues since I changed the twidroid to use TwitPic rather than its own photo host.    
    
    
    @Aggerscricket RT @ajkavanagh: twidroid is about the best. I have problems with pics too though.    
    
    
    @Aggerscricket RT @ajkavanagh:  I get problems with twitpic but I think it is actually a vodafone problem.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid First approach for me. Though it could make your workflow less flexible - unless you AJAX or x-site script to load rules from DB.    
    
    
    Foxhunters, GRRRRRRR!!!!! RT @TheJournalNews: Northumberland hunting case a waste of money http://bit.ly/1uNhCP    
    
    
    And ISPs, while I'm on. Ours has kindly reset all domain MX records this morning, so no email. Thanks, guys.    
    
    
    Hanging's too good for 'em    
    
    
    Coding furiously at the Google App Engine wheel - python rather than java    
    
    
    @julianleighton Many congratulations!    
    
    
    @davidcoxon makes you look a bit like lance Armstrong ;-)    
    
    
    No longer working at bdaily    
    
    
    Beer time, after a very eventful day. "May you live in interesting times" as they say.  Newcastle 1-0 tomorrow with Ranger for first goal?    
    
    
    Quite extraordinary, and I'd thought I'd seen everything #nufc    
    
    
    Ditto!RT @willmcgugan: How I use my landline: 50% talking to mum, 25% hanging up on telemarketers, 25% locating my mobile by calling myself.    
    
    
    Never do something today that you can put off until tomorrow. Until tomorrow comes and you've a pile of TODOs the size of Wales!    
    
    
    Great. Opportunity for the cities of our region. RT @TechCrunch: San Francisco Opens The City’s Data http://tcrn.ch/7CnT by Guest Author    
    
    
    Afternoon coffee and cherry/coconut flapjack (vegan of course). Ahhhhh    
    
    
    Old mate training for the Nine Edges Endurance fell run. Respect.  And a top blog too: http://bit.ly/1hLNab    
    
    
    Upgraded broadband + skyplayer subscription = #ashes heaven. It's good to be the boss.    
    
    
    Poor #ashes record, though. I Stayed in England team hotel in Leeds and somehow drained all their cricketing ability - like that X-men girl.    
    
    
    Enjoyed my first day of being my own boss again    
    
    
    Thought provoking; and not, I think, completely black and white. http://bit.ly/tuSSk    
    
    
    Interesting take on a constitutional mess. UK becoming untenable? RT @channel4news: Brown’s silence on Megrahi release http://bit.ly/3ChATG    
    
    
    @PeterBoneMP wants to rename the August Bank Holiday as 'Margaret Thatcher Day'. Pillock.    
    
    
    Puncture this morning. Spent 5 mins with repair kit getting cold & damp, then phoned wife to pick me up. Bear Grylls or what?    
    
    
    Now effecting puncture repair on kitchen table. Pleased wife is out.    
    
    
    @subtitling wondered why I was getting   funny looks riding it up the cycle track...    
    
    
    Question: why do puncture repair kits never have sandpaper?    
    
    
    Puncture repair caused brake issue, now realigned. High winds caused second brake issue, now realigned. Sorted now. And wet.    
    
    
    @Menage_A_Moi Voltarol tablets. Work for me every time. Available without prescription, as they say.    
    
    
    @subtitling google mail - free or pay versions can both host a company domain.    
    
    
    Just watched west ham & millwall fans doing the 2009 version of "The Football Factory". Scary stuff.    
    
    
    No!! I used the words d-o-m-a-I-n and h-o-s-t in a tweet, here comes the flood. Schoolboy error!    
    
    
    Why do @NewcastleCC pay large for quality paving in the city centre, then maintain it with tarmac blobs? It looks third world!    
    
    
    iPhone app review: "Significant shutter delay. Took a pic of our new puppy, but when I checked the camera roll he'd come out fully grown"    
    
    
    While I'm on, you'd think the whoppingly expensive iPhone would have a zoom feature on the camera. Even my old, crap, Nokia had zoom.    
    
    
    Here's an expensive phone, and here's a shop you can go to to buy software to make it work like the cheaper phones... what are they, BMW?    
    
    
    Here's to #grumpythursday    
    
    
    @Menage_A_Moi  Cool. It's well hidden if it has - time to get the iPhone bumf out.    
    
    
    2 things I hate 1) Javascript 2) Internet Explorer. But not necessarily in that order. One of them a necessary evil, the other not necessary    
    
    
    @Dushyantor  Wolfsburg, eh? Beware Obafemi Martins. He's crap, but capable of a wonder strike from nowhere.    
    
    
    @Dushyantor  Not since KK had a perm and did his stuff for Hamburg, I suppose. Mind you, Chamberlain said that and look what happened there.    
    
    
    Waiting for the weekend to arrive, looking forward to a pleasant lunch to usher it in; #followfriday @AlexJReid @Menage_A_Moi    
    
    
    Splendid RT @TCEurope: Spotify has its iPhone app approved by Apple - we told you so http://bit.ly/AXyhA by @mikebutcher    
    
    
    No work today; on extended weekend break. Smart move, looking at the weather.    
    
    
    I wouldn't mess with Joe Jordan - he was a scary man in the 70s and looks like he could still punch out a horse.    
    
    
    About time too! RT @influenceinfo: O2 has applied to the FSA to act as an independent financial services provi… (cont) http://deck.ly/~74St9    
    
    
    Metro inspectors at Central behaving like prison guards herding criminals again. Why don't you treat your customers as customers?    
    
    
    @AlexJReid ... not forgetting Smoke On The Water!!!    
    
    
    NO!  RT @toonnews: Is Martin Healey Good Enough For Newcastle? - Newcastle United Blog http://bit.ly/fkAFG    
    
    
    It's Time for the Nasty Party http://bit.ly/9mhil    
    
    
    My iPhone 4S is constantly crashing since iOS7 upgrade. Apple, you bastards.    
    
    
    New blog post "It's Time for the Nasty Party": http://tinyurl.com/my8scw    
    
    
    Am I the only person unbothered that Wogan's packing in??? I know he has followers but personally I'd rather listen to silence.    
    
    
    Any chance that Chris Moyles could follow Wogan out the door?    
    
    
    Interesting... RT @TechCrunch: Did Yoko Ono And Sky News Just Ruin Apple's Beatles Surprise? http://bit.ly/QAww0 by @jasonkincaid    
    
    
    @AlexJReid  I read McCartney's interview in Sunday's Observer, and he said he wanted the iTunes thing but that there was some block at EMI.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid It'll fix the world economy by itself when it happens!    
    
    
    Who Would Win a Fight Between a Lion and a Tiger? http://bit.ly/hYDlT    
    
    
    @mikeyparker Google changes explained: http://bit.ly/CXqSx    
    
    
    ust took the Twitter IQ Test: http://tinyurl.com/mxeszp     
    
    
    Similar apologies, bl**dy spammers. RT @davidcoxonSORRY if i just sent everyone multiple dm's - foolisly did an IQ test    
    
    
    It's like the last days of Tony Blair. The office next door is moving out and they're shredding everything by the sound of it.    
    
    
    Off to TEDx Leeds. Should be an interesting evening.    
    
    
    Interesting #TEDxLeeds. Clive  Grinyer excellent, really enjoyed Charles Cecil. Norman Lewis has too bleak an outlook! Tx @ntiLeeds @herbkim    
    
    
    Check out Hull Digital Live 2009 - October 14th 2009 at http://www.amiando.com/hdlive    
    
    
    Good idea, v. interesting subject. RT @kristianlunde: @supermondays I would like to suggest  Test Driven Development (TDD) as a topic...    
    
    
    Just bought 'The Death of Bunny Munro' , Nick Cave's new novel. From a bookshop! Retro. Can I get thru this pm's work without starting it?    
    
    
    And there's live 1-day Eng/Aus cricket on Skyplayer. Too many distractions!    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Europe? Definitely Van Halen's uncool younger brother. Go ahead and Jump.    
    
    
    Thx @hannahbryan @Alex_McVey for the Decadent House Party. Really good vibe.    
    
    
    Feeling poorly, can't seem to stop puking. If Derren Brown is about to stick me to my seat, then it could be bad news for the upholstery.    
    
    
    Not stuck  #derrenbrown    
    
    
    Seem to have stopped puking though. Cheers Derren #derrenbrown    
    
    
    Worn out. Long bike ride, then cutting back the ivy from the walls of our house (using the world's heaviest ladder). Work is easier!    
    
    
    Sitting in the vet's. There's a tiny westie  in here with the loudest bark ever, and it WON'T STOP!!    
    
    
    Really enjoying green tea at the moment    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh @AlexJReid Already eaten dinner, so no photo possible. Imagine delicious, and that'll be about right.    
    
    
    'That's the way love goes', Janet Jackson. Clearly in the mood for early 90s RnB today.    
    
    
    Message from Windows 7: "Internet Explorer has stopped working". Amen to that.    
    
    
    ACME stands for A Company that Makes Everything (via @herbkim). Wonder if Wile E. Coyote is still their best customer !?    
    
    
    Up past 10.30 last night fixing mod_rewrite issue with the company website. Now tired and a bit grumpy. Sometimes small is not beautiful.    
    
    
    Late start this morning. Lots to do before a business lunch (with cakes).    
    
    
    @ThePickards I always find cake to be an important part of a business lunch :)    
    
    
    @AlexJReid No coding yet, but I've got some ideas to use SimpleDB in a couple of side projects    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh You must do VAT returns far more energetically than I do. What am I doing wrong?    
    
    
    @woodss It was running locally on Google App Engine SDK - looking to release it to the cloud in the next few weeks.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid That's one of the suggested uses!    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Amazon are keen to promote S3 or their edge service for BLOB data, and SimpleDB for meta data, with EC2 running the application..    
    
    
    Good (long) lunch meeting (with cake). Now, looking out of the window, it seems its the end of the world (or at least the sky is very black)    
    
    
    Looking forward to #TEDxNewcastle tonight. I think the last time I was at the Tyneside Cinema was as a teenager (to see 'Tommy').    
    
    
    Trying to make my broadband provider understand that 200Kbps <> 2Mbps... and that 2Mbps is better.    
    
    
    ...and that I'm paying for 2Mbps    
    
    
    @rosscooney It's currently 200K down and 50K up - should be 2M down and 512K up. At least its in proportion ;)    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Indeed so. I upgraded the connection so I could join the 21st century and actually view Youtube videos.    
    
    
    Broadband issues resolved. Thanks, un-named provider. I can now get down to some work before #TEDxNCL    
    
    
    Am I Being Brainwashed? (#TEDxNCL) http://bit.ly/Q9eOG    
    
    
    Would be happier if  that read 'should' RT @channel4news: Brown tells Snow bankers could be jailed. Video: http://bit.ly/3eW4R8    
    
    
    Good luck to @souterconsults and everyone else sleeping rough for #bytenight tonight. Definitely worth a few quid of anyone's money!!    
    
    
    Just read the full ruling of the Keegan case, and very interesting it is too.    
    
    
    Collected car after service. Saw  shiny new car. Want shiny new car.    
    
    
    Off to do a demo this afternoon. Fingers crossed.    
    
    
    Good demo today, but somehow you always come away with more work to do than when you went in :)    
    
    
    Morning of teleconferences. Photos have suddenly disappeared from TweetDeck.    
    
    
    Actually, Twitter itself is pretty broken at the moment    
    
    
    @stuarthoward Is it Elvis?    
    
    
    I'd forgotten - would have been 69 today I believe. RT @AlexJReid: Happy Birthday to Mr Lennon.    
    
    
    Anyone going to Hull Digital next week? Any tips on accommodation, venues etc.?  #hdlive09    
    
    
    @nickbelluk How about a bit of Prog Rock: http://bit.ly/znHLT ?    
    
    
    Filling out 13 page Vendor Evaluation questionnaire. In black ink.    
    
    
    Am I the only one who thinks IE8's rendering engine is appallingly slow? And poor.    
    
    
    @subtitling A restorer Jarrow way. Forget the name, but F1 cars in Newcastle http://bit.ly/Y3MOw, got them to do up gold wheels for me once    
    
    
    Newcastle Brown no longer to made on Tyneside? Are they serious? Are they stupid?    
    
    
    Save Our Dog!!! #SOD    
    
    
    Chimney sweep has arrived. Not at all like Dick Van Dyke.    
    
    
    Seriously, though, it's a great business opportunity for a micro-brewery to produce 'Real Newcastle Brown' #SaveOurDog    
    
    
    Hopefully the brewery will see sense and keep production, and jobs, here #SaveOurDog    
    
    
    Rose at 4.50, off to Hull Digital #hdlive09, then client meeting in Leeds late afternoon.    
    
    
    I question the value of high speed broadband to someone with no electricity, water, or sanitation. #hdlive    
    
    
    #hdlive Noded working very interesting. How would it work with public sector projects?    
    
    
    #hdlive How to get your company noticed. Networking, Twitter and RSS apparently.    
    
    
    #hdlive How to get your company noticed. Start a fight.    
    
    
    #hdlive Find out what journalists are writing about at journa-list.com    
    
    
    #hdlive @charlesarthur talk on getting your company noticed - excellent    
    
    
    #hdlive ONE and Yorkshire Forward involved in 100Mb b2b network project. News to me.    
    
    
    @robkilby congratulations, what kind of car is the robmobile going to be?    
    
    
    Great #hdlive yesterday, favourite was Mike Butcher's talk on startups. Funny, inspiring, and true. Would be good for #TDC10    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays -- Monday 26th October -- http://bit.ly/10wWn9    
    
    
    Contact me offline and I'll give you details RT @GIRL_GEEKS_NE: RT @BeckieD  Anyone in north east who offers 1 on 1 German tutoring?    
    
    
    @chrisbarber86 Mind you, orgasma ribbon would probably sell far better than organza    
    
    
    @lauramaddison I really like f-prot antivirus    
    
    
    Social Networking Etiquette http://bit.ly/xhtRh    
    
    
    Looking around for new office space - not much fun (although good meeting this morning)    
    
    
    Getting all corporate with MS. Have created Windows7 guest on Mac host using Sun VirtualBox. Loving the VirtualBox seemless mode.    
    
    
    I'm attending BACKFlip Networking - Gateshead -- http://backflip.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw    
    
    
    @stuarthoward Stuart, keep tweeting that link. I'm finding the JustGiving site is often down - I'm sure people will understand    
    
    
    Will the police step in with 'threat to public safety' concerns? RT @channel4news: latest report on the BNP protest http://bit.ly/1yIcYZ    
    
    
    Hoorah, have finally got my java app to talk to sql server database    
    
    
    Thinking that Windows 7 might just be Vista in disguise...    
    
    
    @saratpediredla Did you get his business card ;) ?    
    
    
    @saratpediredla Nice    
    
    
    Teleconference discussing arcane SQL Server licensing - it's like open source never happened. Did I dream the GPL?    
    
    
    Online http://bit.ly/2HdfM6. RT @julianleighton: Excellent article by A A Gill in the Sunday Times today about the whole BNP/ BBC carry on.    
    
    
    Getting to quite like SQL Server. Acid test when I put it under load!    
    
    
    @rosscooney I  liked #supermondays format last night. Perhaps we could vote online for the groups prior to the event to free up time?    
    
    
    @rosscooney And the grub was spot on #supermondays    
    
    
    Go Arnie! RT @TechCrunch: Schwarzenegger Gives California Legislature A Hidden Finger  http://bit.ly/fD7cA by @arrington    
    
    
    @JTatCarrot sorry I haven't got back - liked the office, taking a couple of days prevarication time.    
    
    
    Late night metro - interesting experience.    
    
    
    Off to town for #TAAD... and fossils    
    
    
    Excellent event at #TAAD last night. And the old Hancock Museum is looking good these days.    
    
    
    Check out Thinking Digital 2010 at http://www.amiando.com/thinkingdigital2010    
    
    
    Makes sense. After all, why would they stop with me? RT @TechCrunch: Microsoft Tortures Little Kids    
    
    
    This is just a class, class tune - and unashamedly old fart http://bit.ly/Wxhjn    
    
    
    Thinking of two historical figures who tried to become president of Europe without an election:  Napoleon Bonaparte and Adolf Hitler.    
    
    
    In the gym changing rooms, the pub singer is in the building. In the shower to be precise. Ah once more from the top-ah...    
    
    
    Not loving the difference in date handling between Oracle and SQL Server, and IMHO SQL Server wins. Choke!    
    
    
    Rolled  out of bed to do emails - penmanship indicates I might be in a stroppy mood today. Gym, then office, before I do any more damage.    
    
    
    @willemodendaal I've used 7Zip for years and it's very good - it also unpacks Unix tars and other formats    
    
    
    @AidanGarnish I know, those repeating tautologies that say the same thing in different ways...    
    
    
    Or Billy Smart's Big Top, perhaps. RT @pekingspring: Toon fans - welovemikeashley@stjamespark has a certain ring to it, doesn't it?    
    
    
    OK. Oracle distributed transaction errors, javascript prototype framework, then what?    
    
    
    I'm in Liverpool and I'm WET    
    
    
    No spare kex either, laaa!    
    
    
    My fault, had strange urge to walk around city centre instead of just getting into a taxi    
    
    
    Thought I spotted Rafa at the Dole Office    
    
    
    Hungover    
    
    
    Vote David! RT @davidcoxon: has been nominated in computer weekly's blogger of the year awards. http://bit.ly/1HcFcr (CATERGORY 3)    
    
    
    50s football  on TV - Lofhouse challenges keeper to head home in Cup Final, wheels away celebrating, keeper unconscious in the net. Class.    
    
    
    Am I the only one thinking JEdward winning Xfactor would be the funniest thing ever? Think about it for a minute, it really is hilarious.    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperStartup, 20th November 2009 -- http://bit.ly/7TS9L    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperTelly, Monday 30th November 2009 @ Northumbria -- http://bit.ly/Pyr4g    
    
    
    Early finish tonight. Instructed to leave early to buy envelopes and dishwasher tabs by my iphone. Now if I can only get it to innovate...    
    
    
    @manojranaweera Interesting. I'll check my dairy for 9/10th.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid I agree about OXO greens. We use Kallo veggie stock cubes - they're really nice    
    
    
        
    
    
    @stuarthoward "Passionate about sending our work down to Yorkshire"    
    
    
    lol RT @AlexJReid: "...but it's built on that very stable core Vista technology, which is far more stable than the current Mac platform."    
    
    
    Enjoyed BACKFlip last night. Cheers, guys, very good event.    
    
    
    I'm attending IT in the Community 2009 -- http://bit.ly/2iIxvX    
    
    
    1980s throwback with Whitesnake via my new Spotify premium    
    
    
    struggling to get a bet on #paddypower #fail    
    
    
    Pleased it's the weekend. Only 2 more working days 'til Monday.    
    
    
    @rosscooney Eh?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Remember tomorrow night that a vote for JEdward is a vote against tyranny #xfactor    
    
    
    Mmmmm... RT @mikebutcher: Badda Bing! Microsoft woos newspapers by funding their stick to beat Google http://bit.ly/tBb4D    
    
    
    @infomixer Devo possibly?    
    
    
    Good day in Leeds yesterday, but must catch up on work today.  I'll hide in the office - no-one will think of looking for me here.    
    
    
    Commuting into Newcastle on Metro. Had short trousers the last time I did this.    
    
    
    @davidcoxon Still couldn't imagine my old English teacher using the word 'grok' - unless he was choking to death.    
    
    
    IE9 already? It's getting like buses - you wait years for one, then 3 turn up in quick succession.    
    
    
    Never Go Back http://bit.ly/2UZFtW    
    
    
    Marvelling at the genius of Marmite flavoured cashew nuts!    
    
    
    Interesting indeed RT @YourFilm_KO: Interesting...RT @TelegraphTech: Twitter launching paid business accounts http://tinyurl.com/yf5yrut    
    
    
    2nd prize 2 copies of Win7 (Sorry!!) RT @davidcoxon: RT @jonoble: One lucky soul at VBUG Wednesday will win Win7 Ult - http://bit.ly/4vbJME    
    
    
    I think it's good Twitter makes money from services. It's important that applications we come to rely on are stable in the long term.    
    
    
    Playing Atari Battlezone online - surely the 1st ever 3d game (thx @Fionathegeek)    
    
    
    Now totally hooked on Battlezone http://bit.ly/8VxnxJ    
    
    
    Watch out for those missiles! #Atari #Battlezone - exactly like driving a real tank (in a monochromatic world of polyhedra)    
    
    
    Is it just me, or is #TweetDeck missing loads of Tweets from the timeline at the moment?    
    
    
    This is the 3rd time in 3 days we've had fire alarm testing at the office - my patience is wearing thin.    
    
    
    90 minutes later my printer is ready to use... no, can't find the drivers #Win7    
    
    
    A test page has been sent to your printer... it hasn't arrived. Now it talks to me?! #Win7    
    
    
    Please note the message on your screen #Win7    
    
    
    I give up - quicker to transcribe the document from screen to paper using a quill pen and my wrong hand.    
    
    
    @Infosanity It's a Lexmark 1400 series wireless - works fine from every other machine in the office, just not the one I need to use    
    
    
    Having lunch in the Quadrata in Newcastle. Think I've found new office space in the old part of town.    
    
    
    Feeling the Schadenfreude: http://bit.ly/6P5iIs - so much for the stitch up between Magna, Merkel, and the German unions!    
    
    
    Feeling rough, heavy cold coming on. But I'm off out to get hugely drunk later so that should fix it...    
    
    
    Planet Rock! #guiltypleasure    
    
    
    Spin class nearly killed me this morning. Correlation between weekend beer consumption and Monday morning fitness? Never occurred to me.    
    
    
    Python, Java, and Ruby all in one day. Head spinning, but #SuperTelly at #Supermondays should be just what the doctor ordered.    
    
    
    Great #supermondays #tellynet last night. All 3 presentations technically fascinating but Hemlock talk by @utku sticks in the mind.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Does Santa have AIDS??? Don't tell me that, I'm only just getting over being told that he doesn't exist!!!    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Makes sense, though, that the government try to break the internet. They have their legacy to think of.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Someone needs to have a word with my bedroom about global warming! #polarbearsrefuge    
    
    
    Nightly ritual of cat crawling under blanket and covering herself, except today our cleaner has double folded her blanket. Hilarious.    
    
    
    Congratulations! RT @YourFilm_KO: Chuffed to say YourFilm has just become a member of the Entrepreneurs Forum.    
    
    
    Early start.    
    
    
    10 Internet predictions for 2010... http://bit.ly/56kN2T    
    
    
    Mixed feelings about this... RT @ne_business: City leaders reveal economic masterplan for Newcastle and Gateshead: http://bit.ly/5LDk5J    
    
    
    @AnthonySterling If you paid by credit card there's maybe a chance you can get your cash back    
    
    
    @AnthonySterling Ah yes, the blessed form    
    
    
    Roger's Profanisaurus - easily the best iPhone app to date. Random profanity? There's an app for that. (Tx @Fionathegeek)    
    
    
    Pizza Hut, what would I do without you at the end of the working week?    
    
    
    Probably Dominoes.    
    
    
    @fuselagetown mine's a thimbleful!    
    
    
    Alistair Darling, Are You Serious? http://bit.ly/5xFsuS    
    
    
    @lee_mcintosh There's a mod_dav plugin for Apache that supports WebDAV, and Apache Tomcat supports WebDAV out of the box.    
    
    
    Furious Java coding, like my life depends on it - 'cause it probably does.    
    
    
    Amen to that!RT @saratpediredla: Ok. If I get one more PDF that I need to print, write and scan back in, I will scream. 2 words : WEB FORMS!    
    
    
    Any Joomla freelancers out there looking for work?    
    
    
    Worked out why my sleepless night. I took the 'day' pill instead of the 'night' pill from my day/night cold remedy pack!    
    
    
    I just donated to @WikimediaUK. Help them make Wikipedia as great as it can be - donate now: http://donate.wikimedia.org.uk    
    
    
        
    
    
    Definitely quicker than O2. RT @mikebutcher, @xdamman: Sperm has 37.5MB of DNA info. Ejaculation represents a data transfer of 1,587.5TB    
    
    
    Although there's a longer preamble before the eventual transfer I suppose.    
    
    
    'Hi, Darlin'. Fancy coming back to my place for a spot of high speed data transfer?"    
    
    
    Not sure that would work    
    
    
    One for the caption competition. 20 quid to their nominated charity for the best effort. RT @OneNorthEastrda: http://twitpic.com/u04db    
    
    
    Please tag entries #onexmascaption    
    
    
    For those of you finishing early today, remember that its Black Eye Friday. Be careful out there.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Mobile's all about data to me. Not really bothered about the layout; or surfing.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Wandered Edinburgh with the wife last week with iphone maps held aloft. Looked like a weird Star Trek away team, but top app use    
    
    
    OK, 25 quid to charity for your best caption.  http://twitpic.com/u04db    
    
    
    OK, 25 quid to charity for the best caption: http://twitpic.com/u04db. #onexmascaption. Otherwise its going to the donkey sanctuary.    
    
    
    Them Crooked Vultures on Channel 4 News    
    
    
    Check out Dan Pink and Drink at http://www.amiando.com/danpink    
    
    
    Entries close at 5pm GMT. 25 quid to your charity for the best caption: http://twitpic.com/u04db. #onexmascaption.    
    
    
    Great cars. The recent 9-3 Aero was an awesome turbo RT @paulsthinking: @chashallett: GM closes Saab. http://bit.ly/4snsQh    
    
    
    1 hr left. Can you beat the wit of @richardcarter? 25 quid to your charity for the best caption: http://twitpic.com/u04db. #onexmascaption.    
    
    
    And the winner is... @richardcarter: "what's that smell? I thought we said zero emissions!" http://twitpic.com/u04db #onexmascaption    
    
    
    Sage advice. RT @mattcutts: Do just a tiny bit of work, protect your Google/Gmail account: http://bit.ly/7wg9zz .    
    
    
    New post: Cyberbullying In The Name Of... http://bit.ly/8oaUj7    
    
    
    The donkeys did get a small consolation prize. I just couldn't resist those sad eyes... #onexmascaption    
    
    
    Should give them time to write it! RT @stuarthoward, @millsustwo: We won't release PositionApp™ until > 5000 iPhone devs follow @positionapp    
    
    
    I've just got a score of 14 weeks, 4 days, 6 hours on the @differenceengin game. http://bit.ly/5Xrib7    
    
    
    Wound down for the holidays. Happy Christmas one and all...    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays: Flash Talk Monday (29th November 2010) -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/2ivj    
    
    
    What is TEDxGateshead Women?? I mean unless they're talking about... you know... er... womany stuff... then surely we men can join in too?    
    
    
    @woodss I went down to have a look at Newcastle Business Village and was quite impressed.    
    
    
    I'm going to the CloudSeminar at MFC (http://www.amiando.com/cloud_seminar) - will it be a bigger crowd than Boro's last home game?    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays, 25th January 2010 -- http://supermondays.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw    
    
    
    @justingsouter I was home in time for the darts! Speed shopping is the way forward.    
    
    
    First morning of my new job has come and gone in a flash    
    
    
    Apparently, in my temporary absence from Twitter, Vince Cable has become very popular... surely there are worse bogeymen about?    
    
    
    @Pete_sherpa I have a perm position with Orange Bus, starting this morning.    
    
    
    Checking out the Planet Rock iPhone app. Cool. "She makes you burn with a wave of her hand, yeah". It doesn't get better than that.    
    
    
    It must be Purple half hour. Fabulous.    
    
    
    listening to Black Sabbath by Black Sabbath on the Planet Rock iPhone app (http://tr.im/planetrock)    
    
    
    And it tweets too!    
    
    
    Ported Java App to SQL Server (2008). Client can't/won't upgrade from 2000. Bless.    
    
    
    I'm going to DIBI (http://www.amiando.com/dibi)    
    
    
    @EmmyNewman I thought it was a teen hair dye experiment of yours!    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB I'm there    
    
    
    Same thing with Basil Brush! RT @leesimpson: I wonder if they thought no one would notice when they recast the voice of Lewis in Family Guy.    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB Sounds good to me    
    
    
    Where was he when I was selling magic beans? RT @AlexJReid: OH: "I used t' buy fake twenty pund notes at school like - aanly fifteen pund."    
    
    
    Can't believe I got a parking ticket last night at #TAAD? At 9.45!! It can't be economically viable to employ traffic wardens at that time.    
    
    
    is heading to that London, having got up half an hour before I went to bed.    
    
    
    Microsoft Dallas - Fish or Fowl? http://bit.ly/b56PL8    
    
    
    Microsoft "Dallas" Project - Fish or Fowl? http://bit.ly/dvrU2W    
    
    
    Waiting in the 1st class lounge at Kings X after a good meeting - nice tea, Tony Blair waving his hands about on telly...    
    
    
    Home at last. Good day. Sleep now...    
    
    
    Hitler and the iPad http://bit.ly/dwqGDQ - interesting use of subtitling    
    
    
    Sorry, but even if the Town are still shambolic, for Victor Moses to choose Wigan shows no ambition. Unless its to play in lge 1 in 2 yrs.    
    
    
    @EmmyNewman Is nude the red colour, or the beige? I must say I've never seen anyone in the buff who is either colour, including myself.    
    
    
    @EmmyNewman Cool. Wonder what the wife'll say when I tell her I want to paint the upstairs landing nude?    
    
    
    I seem to have opened a huge can of worms. Big, fat, wriggly buggers too.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Burst tyre    
    
    
    Pixie Lott on TV, bad coffee, and the smell of rubber. Waiting in line at the tyre place.    
    
    
    Project teleconference at 3. Chances? I'm toast. Again.    
    
    
        
    
    
    There's only so much Pixie a man can take. Are we nearly there yet?    
    
    
    "Wind and Wuthering" - Genesis. How old???    
    
    
    Very tired. Superbowl fever grabbed me in the early hours. I only wanted to watch The Who at half time!    
    
    
    @michaelpeacock I got chased by HMRC once for a debt that I'd paid months before, just 'too early'.    
    
    
    A new version of the iPhone software is available. Various fixes, but not one to stop it confusing Bruce Springsteen with Black Sabbath.    
    
    
    Just misread "necessary evil" as "necessary Elvis" uh-huh-huh    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Real men drink their tea black!    
    
    
    Excellent event at @NEBytes last night, very interesting. Thanks to everyone there, especially @apwestgarth for his excellent presentation.    
    
    
    Top @Supermondays last night with @AlexJReid and @lornajane - two highly enjoyable talks    
    
    
    Very grumpy this morning    
    
    
    This is top class. Grump is lifting. RT @channel4news: computer-simulated angry Gordon Brown on Taiwanese TV: http://bit.ly/aw458 #mustsee    
    
    
        
    
    
    @AlexJReid Great pic though. True art.    
    
    
    @spoutingshite Aren't RBS 'losses' just write downs of bogus assets? So working harder won't count. Do we see their operating profit/loss?    
    
    
    Pretty smart for a cat. He makes most of my business decisions. Perhaps that's why I'm pennyless with a cupboard full of tuna.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Pearl Jam this morning - Backspacer    
    
    
    Nine Inch Nails now - hide the shoelaces, belts, etc. What's the matter with me, it's a Friday??    
    
    
    Would have to be modelled on "Ask the Hoff"! RT @Zenithus: @chrisbarber86 No idea what sort of @LINGsCARS app to bring out! Any suggestions?    
    
    
    I'm in, long as they're veggie! RT @pekingspring: just hit upon the idea of making candy hearts, but with "fuck off" and "cunt" on them.    
    
    
    Someone did it to me yesterday. RT @YourFilm_MN: why do people think that safe in-car phone use means SCREECH TO A HALT WHEREVER THEY ARE?    
    
    
    Off to Steel Wheels to rummage for some rock memorabilia for a mate's 40th    
    
    
    Neil Young's Like a Hurricane on the radio - awesome    
    
    
    This should have a sign on it reading "the sixties were shit". http://tweetphoto.com/14002410    
    
    
    11 already!!! Still loads to do before beer o'clock.    
    
    
    Windows XP this morning. I'd forgotten how much it makes me want to take a sledgehammer to a computer.    
    
    
    HP Photo & Imaging Director, like digital Hotel California - you can de-install any time you like, but it just won't leave.    
    
    
    OK. Simple Monday task: 1) Scan expenses receipts, 2) invoice customer. Now turning into an epic. I'm going to explode soon.    
    
    
    Finally, we have scanning capability again!  HP + Windows XP, productivity gains up there with the quill pen.    
    
    
    OK, I give up. It's costing more to claim than the actual worth. Time to negotiate a per diem.    
    
    
    BTW. Up yours, Microsoft. And up yours, HP.    
    
    
    Early lunch. Watching This Morning on ITV. Phil Schofield  & Holly Wotsit have just done a piece on how to improve your sex life.    
    
    
    With live actors demonstrating positions. Although they're not allowed to do 'the movements' according to daytime TV rules. Hilarious.    
    
    
    Now we've got a bloke dressed as Elvis cooking via webcam from Spain. Seriously, the things we miss when we go to the office.    
    
    
    Or perhaps I took the wrong cold remedy pill this morning?    
    
    
    Elvis is about to do duck in orange sauce instructed by Phil Vickery    
    
    
    Why don't they put this stuff on at night??? It's brilliant.    
    
    
    Elvis isn't wearing an apron. The rhinestone outfit is bound to show up the suace splashes. Uh-huh-huh.    
    
    
    Sadly I have to leave This Morning's Cook In with Elvis to go to the office and relative normality. My eyes have been opened.    
    
    
    @stuarthoward That looks fantastic    
    
    
    Trying out we7. Lots more interruptions than Spotify, although the premium subscription is cheaper at the minute (same price inc mobile).    
    
    
    Feel poorly. Heavy cold. Might even be man flu.    
    
    
    Is it just me, or is Lord Adonis a dead ringer for Mr Burns?    
    
    
    @justingsouter  Lord Adonis is here: http://bit.ly/lKEhA, Mr Burns is here: http://bit.ly/bc4B9Q. Or is that the other way around?    
    
    
    How would he know? He hasn't kicked a ball in donkeys...RT @TheJournalNews: NUFC: Joey Barton: I'm now a better player: http://bit.ly/aDuC9J    
    
    
    @jerri_murtagh Naked Twister - always  a good ice-breaker back in the day...  or maybe not.    
    
    
    I'm going to get weird followings cause I said 'Naked Twister' aren't I? Still learning.    
    
    
    Clearly, playing on Social Media instead of getting out 2 proposals that must be delivered today is more important.  I'm off to re-focus.    
    
    
    @subtitling I'm at that event. Suffering major man flu, I struggled to remember the name of my business on the phone this am. Should be fun.    
    
    
    Arsenal vs. Barcelona. Saw Barca the other night, they were like the Harlem Globe Trotters - without a bucket of water chucked over the ref.    
    
    
    'Cortez The Killer' - Neil Young    
    
    
    @hannahbryan Like the website!    
    
    
    Quality tax disc holder: http://bit.ly/dtOqFj    
    
    
    'Stairway' comes number 1 in Planet Rock best ever rock song poll.  Sometimes its nice to have a constant. Damned good track too!    
    
    
    Songs you (probably) shouldn't play at a vicar's tea party - #1 Closer, by NIN    
    
    
    @Dushyantor Not sure Tiger's wife would be happy with him sliding back into anything at the moment. Oo-er.    
    
    
    @YourFilm_KO Perhaps not, but worth hanging onto a copy.    
    
    
    Is against ageism in job advertisements. Particularly from public funded organisations.    
    
    
    One small change makes the point: "Looking for people to front a PR campaign:white's only, tyne&wear/northumberland". Pretty bad now, huh?    
    
    
    It was originally "aged 20-35". Don't be ageist (or racist)! You know who you are!!!    
    
    
    I'm waiting to be PAT tested    
    
    
    Very, very clever. But I'm holding out for a "handsome" button. RT @paul_vaclik: Coming soon to Photoshop: http://bit.ly/cFZpcj    
    
    
    @woodss Assuming your arm remains attached, of course.    
    
    
    PAT time!    
    
    
    2 hours later - our computers talk to each other again, to the printer, and to the internet. PAT testing? I'd rather the office burned down.    
    
    
    @AlexJReid Ouch, scary. Running washing machines, tumble dryers, and dish washers while you go to work is the biggest risk apparently.    
    
    
    Playing with my new toy, a Bose docking station for my iPhone.    
    
    
    Richie Blackmore's Rainbow - tremendously self-indulgent.    
    
    
    Waiting for my wife to come home from her sister's and fix the various clocks/timers in the house. Why can't they all just run off a Mac?    
    
    
    www.smartworks-it.com    
    
    
    New company branding and website is live today: http://bit.ly/ccy7cU    
    
    
    @julianleighton Interested in the concept of a "spare" creme egg...    
    
    
    Proof that politicians are stupid & vengeful. RT @TheJournalNews: MP Kevan Jones stirs up Joanne Lumley over campaign: http://bit.ly/c21Wq3    
    
    
    Fed up being internal IT manager. I'm outsourcing the lot. Never mind paperless, I'm going for the computerless office (servers at least).    
    
    
    London Calling    
    
    
    Ruud Gullit on next table during meeting. Resisted odd compulsion to shout across "Aalreet, Ruud. Toon supporter" by way of introduction.    
    
    
    @subtitling the fairness space is a bit crowded at the moment - how about a party based on truth? #ge2010    
    
    
    Pistols on today. Seems only right.    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Kick Out The Jams by MC5    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Both, but the single is outstanding on its own.    
    
    
    @stuarthoward not forgetting Dusty Carpet (takes some beating) and Chewing Gum (sticks to the rails) at 20s.    
    
    
    If there's a volcanic ash cloud above us, does it mean that when it starts to rain it'll be raining Volvic?    
    
    
    Why does the cat only eat the front ends of mice?    
    
    
    Just in case you think that Nick Clegg is a fresh, dynamic, and decisive alternative: http://bit.ly/dji7p2 #canwehavesomebetterpoliticians    
    
    
    Mind I'll give Clegg his due - he did do that Derren Brown memory trick thing at the end where he remembered every questioner's name.    
    
    
    Mrs Clegg can send him shopping knowing she's never going to run out of toilet rolls, or moist wipes, or any of that stuff I always forget.    
    
    
    @davidcoxon That's pretty much how Derren Brown does t as well ;)    
    
    
    Orange Bus are nominated for a Dadi award! Vote now http://vote.dadiawards.com/     
    
    
    @leeanne_b The old Salvation Army temple on Westgate Road, Newcastle?    
    
    
    Customer tells me there's a 3 week delay in payments due to a change in their IT system. Has the computer confiscated your cheque book???    
    
    
    Which is a mite different from what the Mail reports! RT @mikebutcher: What Nick Clegg actually said. And he's right http://bit.ly/aR25Ek    
    
    
    Walking like Frankenstein's monster this morning. Overtraining has taken it's toll and now my hamstrings are exacting revenge.    
    
    
    I have a ticket going spare for #DIBI if anyone would like it. Regrettably I'm unable to attend.    
    
    
    Venting my frustration with the bast... people that came up with IE8.  No xhtml support? Shrink to fit broken? My plea? Use another browser.    
    
    
    @jerri_murtagh Bio Gel Nails? Possibly B&Q?    
    
    
    Dear MS, have spent 1+1/2 days refactoring an app cause IE won't print/download like all other browsers. To whom should I send my bill?    
    
    
    TFI Friday    
    
    
    This made me chuckle: http://bit.ly/dwoFH0    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Definitely not supporting IE6    
    
    
    Good song for an election week: http://bit.ly/cLVtPe    
    
    
    Paperwork and admin this morning. Love it.    
    
    
    @justingsouter You could still wear it, but with trainers...    
    
    
    @libwella The BBC has 'Find your constituency' at http://bit.ly/cb8mid, as does the Guardian at http://bit.ly/aKSlS3 (and its better)    
    
    
    Regardless of who you choose, I urge everyone to vote tomorrow (unless you're a Nazi). People died so that we could.    
    
    
    @libwella There's also 'They work for you' http://bit.ly/dufANB which has questionnaire responses from candidates. Pretty cool.    
    
    
    @woodss Valid points, I would have loved to have voted on #debill for example. But someone has to run the show, there's tricky times ahead.    
    
    
    Sounds like geek civil unrest! RT @AlexJReid: They are throwing BlackBerry handsets at people, although why someone would choose a curve...    
    
    
    Neil Kinnock on radio 4 saying he's always been a supporter of PR... yeah, right, and was in love with Margaret Thatcher.    
    
    
    Mandelson was gushing about PR as soon as he saw the exit polls last night. Exactly how dishonest do you have to be to become a politician?    
    
    
    And Gordon Brown, resign for the sake of your own dignity, man.    
    
    
    Nick Clegg, it's time to get a backbone, son.    
    
    
    So Nick Clegg has spoken. Now we should get to see what David Cameron is really like.    
    
    
    Give the Tories enough rope. And a plastic bag. And a satsuma… (via @pekingspring)    
    
    
    The Stone Roses. Splendid.    
    
    
    Major de-clutter going on the office. Hope I don't chuck out any important stuff.    
    
    
    Just watched Cameron's speech, inviting a collaborative government with the Lib Dems. I must say I'm quite proud of him.    
    
    
    Dear Politicians, I don't want PR, I want my say on the issues I care about. The technology is here in front of me! PR is last year's model.    
    
    
    VAT return. Urrgghhh!    
    
    
    Here we go again... (via @TheJournalNews): NUFC: Chris Hughton won't be given any money for new players: http://bit.ly/cj0hyw    
    
    
    For a couple of days I thought politicians might be concerned with the voters, but now it seems they've reverted to narrow self interest.    
    
    
    Didn't have enough characters to write "Bastards" after that last post. More characters please, Twitter.    
    
    
    How can you sack the Fonz??? You can't sack the Fonz!!! RT @channel4news: West Ham sack Gianfranco Zola.    
    
    
    @chrisbarber86 SOAP's very bloaty, designed by enterprise bods, but it does have  advantages over REST (like security and authentication)    
    
    
    I'm attending SuperMondays - SEO -- http://supermondays.eventbrite.com    
    
    
    I was horrified to learn that I'm 83% David Milliband. Shoot me now.    
    
    
    Although it's a bit like a choice between being shot or stabbed, quite frankly.    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe A man of taste indeed. Hopefully my STB will have recorded it for me to watch at my leisure.    
    
    
    @DifferenceEngin Or no streaming. Looks like the free, invite only access might be getting ditched.    
    
    
    There's always we7. Seems Spotify is reacting to the competition by copying their pricing model.    
    
    
    But who has the fullest catalogue? I can say we7 is great for any prog rock dinosaurs out there, but then Spotify ain't bad there either.    
    
    
    @jd I can recommend Planet Rock. And Classic FM. Both have great iPhone apps.    
    
    
    Not before Supermonday, we hope!! RT @LanceUlanoff: Is SEO Dying? http://bit.ly/bsSPuM via: @HotInTechnology    
    
    
    Is 'God 2.0' not the bloke who tried to patent the human genome a few years back?    
    
    
    For atheists, strictly speaking, I suppose he would be 'God 1.0'.    
    
    
    Been building up to it, it's now or never for the ultimate prog rock album... Tales from Topographic Oceans by Yes. I may be some time...    
    
    
    @DeclanMetcalfe Back from the journey, almost swept away by the dreamy lyrics and soundscapes. I have learned that I am not that prog!    
    
    
    Head's spinning with Topographic  Oceans. The cure for over-prog? Slash and Ian Astbury...    
    
    
    The EU has allowed genetically engineered crops into Europe. You can read more and sign a petition here http://www.greenpeace.org/GEpetition    
    
    
    Bullfighter comes second! http://bit.ly/aVvArC    
    
    
    Tweet number 666, a devil of a tweet    
    
    
    Strange buzzing in the office. Like a hyperactive wasp.    
    
    
    !!! RT @channel4news @frasereC4: Bradford: Stephen Griffiths accused of 3 murders calls himself "The Crossbow Cannibal" http://ht.ly/1R2VJ    
    
    
    @fixmyalloys no, and no, I understand    
    
    
    @fixmyalloys though you should be able to access your windows pc using a service like GoToMyPC    
    
    
    I'm attending The SMACS and SuperChristmas -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/25Zv    
    
    
    Dammit, I'm going for a run.    
    
    
    Sandwiches and iced knee for lunch    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Every little helps, I suppose.    
    
    
    Why am I ready to sleep now when I was wide a-bloody-wake at 4am this morning? No time for sleep, I've things to do!!!    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh 38974 is a lot of followers. But perhaps not enough to affirm deity. Are you saying the prayer came from 'down below'?    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh With a bit of social media coaching, he could make 50000 double quick... "I've just worked in a mysterious way , please RT" .    
    
    
    @justingsouter Of course, you could get @god up to 50000 followers no problem.    
    
    
    This is bound to end in tears: RT @LanceUlanoff: Mars Trip Simulation To Lock Up 6 Men In Mock Spaceship For 18 Months http://bit.ly/9nyX4A    
    
    
    Cooking risotto. And drinking beer. Who says men can't multi-task?    
    
    
    iPhone has just suggested 'Subaru' whilst I was trying to type 'signature'. I've never used the word 'Subaru' in my life (up to this point).    
    
    
    Know what I miss about this time on a Friday? CRACKERJACK!!!    
    
    
    Has just launched iComptroller - a new, super-simple, finance application for small businesses. www.icomptroller.com    
    
    
    @EmmyPips I always like it when people cut one leg shorter than the other - though I'm sure that won't happen to you.    
    
    
    It's clearly bed time. Confused between #NEFOLLOWERS and NEE FOLLOWERS!    
    
    
    @AlexJReid I was pleased to learn that, with iPhone 4, Apple had invented digital zoom.    
    
    
    @leeanne_b Really? Punch Ed Balls. Guess he's like Marmite. Diane Abbot - made a great speech on civil liberties during the 42 days thing.    
    
    
    @LeeABaker Happy Birthday, Matey. Forty again? I had a decent meal in the Silkroom the other week.    
    
    
    After 2000 years of stony silence will @HadriansWall reveal its secrets? Well no, but the lady takes a really nice photograph. #nefollowers    
    
    
    Just noticed John Prescott on here, spewing out his odd brand of class hate . Surely you'll be struggling with 140 caracters Mr P?    
    
    
    @docuguy Yeah, but do you really want to end up eating mutant produce from Monsanto et al? #organic    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB I predict drunkenness    
    
    
    Cat came in this morning COVERED in poo. Birds dive bombed him to protect a nest - top defensive move. I'm working on a way to adapt it.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh It was pretty funny actually, especially as the wife got to clean him up. And he's quite the patient patient, which helps.    
    
    
    Off to Lui's in Tynemouth for gargantuan veggie breakfast.    
    
    
    @ajkavanagh Avoidance involved 'bootcamp' on the beach, which nearly killed me. Need to find better avoidance strategies.    
    
    
    Top breakfast btw    
    
    
    @AllotmentAli I use F-Prot from Frisk. Fast, cheap, unobtrusive, and works really well.    
    
    
    @PeteWatson_PB Well, ultimately the football will disappoint, the lasting memory will be of an arm round a stranger  - your new best mate.    
    
    
    Fabulous. RT @woodss: RT @ryandownie: Pizza Hut Ireland are giving out a free Pizza every time a goal is scored against France.    
    
    
    Grumpy this morning. Late night last night. And required to wear tie today.    
    
    
    Parked in town, paid by phone, returned to a ticket. #newcastlecitycouncil #fail    
    
    
    So far I'm watching most of the world cup via terrestrial channels, on a retro Sony TV set, and really enjoying it. 100% reliable too.    
    
    
    Interesting. DabbleDB has been bought by Twitter: http://dabbledb.com/    
    
    
    As I can't be arsed to blow a vuvuzela for 90 minutes, wondering whether I'll be allowed into St. James' with a hoover for next season.    
    
    
    @subtitling I was just disappointed that Lord Saville didn't say "UhUhUhUhUhUhUh.... 'ows about that then?"    
    
    
    This ambush marketing that Budweiser are getting huffy about looks like fun. Unless you're Robbie Earle .    
    
    
    Using @icomptroller to invoice a client in Finland requiring EU reverse charge mechanism for VAT - easy peasy    
    
    
    I'd completely forgotten!!! RT @MaxMerch: Remember Ladies and Gents, This Sunday Is FATHERS DAY! http://bit.ly/cQuGmc    
    
    
    