Tax stuff is to the accountant!!  Makes you stay in check with your business and lifestyle.    
    
    
    The future of communications. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712972874913/ … The future of communications    
    
    
    There's some truth in Warhol.  What have you got away with???http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712972874926/ …    
    
    
    There's some truth in Warhol. What have you got away with??? http://fb.me/1N7APUWSY     
    
    
    Mr. Hucklebuck gives a compaction equipment firm a visual face lift. We need to show you a before photo.  http://twitpic.com/928si8     
    
    
    Thank you #EarlScruggs! The first time I saw him perform with @JeffStahler, we sat so close Earl could spit on us. http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/culture/2012/01/steve-martin-earl-scruggs.html …    
    
    
    The #design thought of the day. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712972900346/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    The secret to success... http://fb.me/1d3qJEXKT     
    
    
    April 2nd is Children's Book Day, thanks to Hans Christian Anderson.    
    
    
    April 4th. Go out and whack someone.  After all, it's World Pillow Fight Day.    
    
    
    One long day celebrating the life of Robert G Donnelly.  A #WWII Vet and a career firefighter, a man's man. What a legacy he leaves...    
    
    
    @customink an interesting t-shirt company with who knows their brand. http://www.customink.com/about/     
    
    
    Thomas Kinkade, 'Painter of Light,' dies at 54. How will this effect the art world?  http://www.news-press.com/article/20120406/LIFESTYLES/120406041/Thomas-Kinkade-Painter-Light-dies-54 …    
    
    
    Great info graphic on "How to Lead a Creative Life". http://ow.ly/i/ysJK     
    
    
    Great info graphic on "How to Lead a Creative Life". http://ow.ly/i/ysJK  http://fb.me/1wkVyW54C     
    
    
    April 10th Golfers' Day. Hey! we get to wear those funny pants and hats!!    
    
    
    April 12th: Look Up In the Sky Day but not straight up at a bird...    
    
    
    @JordanHull will be interviewed tomorrow, Friday at noon on WYSO with Niki Daktoa.  You can stream it from here; http://www.wyso.org/     
    
    
    Go the extra mile quote from my friend @MichaelKalter http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712972988798/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Why go the extra mile? http://fb.me/1NSeuXl2G     
    
    
    Agency said they wouldn't work with an #illustrator because they're too expensive.  They prefer a designer to illustrate the project.  WHAT!    
    
    
    @o_fishel The client said a designer will do the illustration work for hire.  The illustrator will want more because of global usage rights.    
    
    
    This looks like a day in Dayton if caught on film. http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=316AzLYfAzw …    
    
    
    Share the love. @JordanHull wins another fan!! Thanks social media. http://michaelverity.com/video-introducing-jordan-hull/ …    
    
    
    Cool! Found another post about @JordanHull's music. http://boomblam.wordpress.com/2012/04/10/jordan-hull-nashvilles-finest/ …    
    
    
    #sellmore. Good topic today on @gotomeeting. "When prospects go silent". Fact: most clients drop their agencies after 2 years 8 months.    
    
    
    Honored to be part of 
@CedarvilleUniversity's design advisory board.  A staff with passion for their students.    
    
    
    Who's calling you for assignments? AD, CD or AE's? #illustrators #illustration #scotthull    
    
    
    @ICONconference Who's calling you for assignments these days? AD, CD or AE's?  #scotthull    
    
    
    April 20th: Look Alike Day.  Which is everyday in car design...    
    
    
    @ReCourses  A light-hearted but informative view of the history of content marketing: http://brow.se.com/J6yTZG     
    
    
    @AndrewRocco And the City of #Dayton is trying to make Dayton a  technology/creative center????    
    
    
    Fun time with the boy on Record Day! Hit 3 shops.    
    
    
    Thursday noon!! Your last chance to get discount tickets to help out kids in need... http://hannahstreasure.org/events/events.html …    
    
    
    Great article on @JordanHull. His June release, "Who's Gonna Teach You How To Live" with cover design by @MikeyBurton. http://www.knoxville.com/news/2012/apr/27/knoxville-music-jordan-hull/?print=1 …    
    
    
    Can you give me some stats on the power of visual communication?  Why pictures?    
    
    
    Can someone suggest a good #CRM for small business that works with your web site and emails?    
    
    
    Are you on @Pinterest? Follow me: http://pinterest.com/scotthull/     
    
    
    @TimGough adds another American Illustration win!! This on underground music scene in Atlanta. Congratulations Tim!! http://fb.me/1WuhmzrqJ     
    
    
    @DaveReinbold can make a sketch look sooooo cool! http://fb.me/1zDi0QXPH     
    
    
    Updating our mailing list.  Amazing how many people contact us!! Now, which ones will really buy our services?    
    
    
    @ReCourses @scotthull Dave, aways enjoy your insights in bridging business and creativity.    
    
    
    What if clients thought this way? http://twitpic.com/9hkyao     
    
    
    As a creative, do you think you're not living up to your potential? http://lnkd.in/FDx7xp     
    
    
    @ideaguy If they're not hit by a car...    
    
    
    Who's watching @thepitch? #thepitch    
    
    
    #thepitch.  95% of the agencies claim they have the best creative.    
    
    
    #ThePitch Wonder how many agencies will show off their awards to the prospect as part of their pitch?    
    
    
    #ThePitch HELP!!! What song pops in your mind?? @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    @novosedlik #thepitch Should be interesting to see where the client goes: customer or the old fashion brand. @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    @radbcc #ThePitch I find it interesting every firm says they're the best.  The best at what?? @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thePitch Hive... burrrrr. What about the hourly rate or overtime rate?    
    
    
    #ThePitch @ThePitch_AMC  Now they're hitting the customer's emotions.  Very good.  Interesting to see what the client does.    
    
    
    #thePitch @ThePitch_AMC  Hive seemed to pull out the old tried and true where FKM hit on the customer emotions as word of mouth advertising.    
    
    
    #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC  OK, both agencies have over 100 folks.  Wonder what the client paid the 2 firms to make the presentation? ProBono?    
    
    
    @FKMagency @ThePitch_AMC #thepitch.  Found your firm understands the emotional side of the brand.  Congratulations.    
    
    
    How important is it to draw out ideas?  #visualthinking @scotthull http://fb.me/1tMSbeWFi     
    
    
    @beccabernstein @radbcc @ThePitch_AMC What other buzz words would you use for "value"?    
    
    
    Good insight at the #NMDayton event, "Expanding Your Brand & Reach Through Video." Informative info.  #VisualThinking is the future.    
    
    
    @RicMoody53 Ric thanks for sharing your knowledge of equipment today at #NMDayton.  What was the make of light?    
    
    
    @colindul What a great way to enjoy the moment as a writer!    
    
    
    @dan_roam's webinar "The Magic of Visual Thinking" was really insightful!  Can't wait to go over it again even though I remember 65%+ of it.    
    
    
    @ScottHull artist, Larry Moore captured painting the final shuttle launch. What an opportunity!!... http://fb.me/1RMtH6Xy9     
    
    
    My thought on bridging the gap between business and creativity. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973118841/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    This will get your morning going! @HarvardBiz - Outsourcing the Old Folks - Marc Freedman - Harvard Business Review: http://s.hbr.org/J6G09L     
    
    
    366 Days, or How I Tricked Myself into Being Awesome - @Lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5907717/366-days-or-how-i-tricked-myself-into-being-awesome …    
    
    
    @Swalot_of_Hoenn Conversation... You can't create a viral video... Idiots.  good observation. #thepitch    
    
    
    @ThePitch_AMC Give people something they didn't know they were missing. #thepitch    
    
    
    @melissary I think a lot of people caught the "viral video" mistake. #thepitch    
    
    
    @melissary Let's see the viral video presentation... oh wait!  tech problem. #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    What's the start up cost on this "viral" idea??? #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    Definitely rooting for @booneoakley on this one. Love the idea! What did we miss about the winner?#thepitch @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    @booneoakley Glad to hear Greg is doing better.    
    
    
    @ashabean Thank Ash for the kind words.  What point in the interview did you find helpful?    
    
    
    @ScottHull's artist @MarkPernice provides graphics for the @Printmag article on sports uniform advertising.... http://fb.me/1DEsodFTK     
    
    
    @ashabean What added value could I bring to your business as an artist?    
    
    
    it's now 15mb of fame...    
    
    
    @dan_roam @iamcodyjames Sorry I miss it last night.  Looking forward to the  webinar post and comments.  The last one was informative.    
    
    
    @markpernice talking at CSCA in Columbus tonight at Gateway Film Center!!! You can hear this @Scotthull Associate guy tell his story.    
    
    
    @GermanVillage Is this for green dogs only? http://twitpic.com/9nba8u     
    
    
    @ThePitch_AMC I'm finding the client's brief  isn't so brief.  They better know the audience. #thepithch    
    
    
    #thepitch At least she said she use to bar tend. @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    @ThePitch_AMC If you want to know what your customer wants, go ask the customer.
#thepitch    
    
    
    @ThePitch_AMC Maybe the agencies need to talk to a group of nuns and ditch the monks? #thepitch    
    
    
    I'm starting to think #thePitch is choosing has been agencies.  Please prove me wrong... @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch You can do it Mary!!! @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch I have to agree with the clear bottle idea. @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch YES MARY!!!! @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch  Off to the Olive farm...
@ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    Fun time at @CSCA with @MarkPernice. Check out the opening trailer. http://vimeo.com/41497187  http://fb.me/22etHAkn7     
    
    
    Alro enjoying the opening of the pool... http://twitpic.com/9pol67     
    
    
    Alro one big day hanging around the pool today... http://twitpic.com/9pooju     
    
    
    Arlo agrees, nothing like the Indy 500 on Memorial weekend. http://twitpic.com/9q159v     
    
    
    Who told the kids when an ice cream truck plays music, it means they're out of ice cream???    
    
    
    #thepitch Got to love that Mid West warmth.    
    
    
    #thepitch  Hey,Director of Social Influence as a job title???  Who came up with that?  Would it be more of a "Branding Officer"?    
    
    
    #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC  "You can prick your finger but don't finger your prick." George Carlion.    
    
    
    #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC  What a tuff job as Director of Social Influence when you have to PR TOD.    
    
    
    @tim_nolan FYI. Breakthrough work cannot not sourced from Getty Images.  So true Tim....#ThePitch    
    
    
    #thepitch @ThePitch_AMC The graphics from Muse look like they came from a template.    
    
    
    Get Jordan Hull's song In The Summer for free in exchange for one tweet: http://trkurl.com/oRchVY  #TFAT    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone for sending me birthday wishes! If nothing else, life has made me a lot of friends over the years!!!    
    
    
    #AmericanSongwriter magazine did a short interview with @JordanHull and his single release today!! http://www.americansongwriter.com/2012/06/daily-discovery-jordan-hull-in-the-summer/ …    
    
    
    #Dayton !  @JordanHull is playing @BlindBob's tomorrow at 9PM.   http://www.facebook.com/events/301166729973264/ … http://twitpic.com/9tibk6     
    
    
    @JordanHull with that 1967 summer of love Neil Young look. Check his music out!  He has a free download. http://twitpic.com/9tlzos     
    
    
    “Designers can illustrate but illustrators can't design. “ A statement made by a designer this morning.  Someone define design...    
    
    
    #thepitch Got to like Jose's view on business and not just another idea. @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch Here comes the reality....    
    
    
    #thepitch It's all about the story.  It's nice that they let you use your imagination.  @ThePitch_AMC    
    
    
    #thepitch  And @bandujo understands the customer.  Great job!!    
    
    
    #thepitch Interesting how the advertising world has interest.  Time to bring back #ThirtySomething.    
    
    
    @InfusedFrancis Francis, Can wait to see how infusionsoft will work for our business.  I'm still importing contacts.    
    
    
    #sethgodin Seth Godin tells us about today's marketing for success.... http://fb.me/1ICHwODRw     
    
    
    #illustrators #icon7 Illustrators and art buyers, What do you hope to gain at Icon 7?    
    
    
    #icon7 Sounds like a fun event. Can't wait to hear your take aways of inspiration.    
    
    
    Must be what left brainers think? #design, #aiga, #icon7 http://twitpic.com/9x4njy     
    
    
    I love conferences to learn about new trends. Here's how #Twitter can help make a difference. http://huff.to/LylI86  via @HuffPostEdu    
    
    
    @andyperez Great question Andy!  Who would your dream client be?    
    
    
    @andyperez Like your thinking on the perfect client!!! Craft breweries are the the new Starbucks for beverage design!    
    
    
    @InfusedFrancis Thanks for the twit link!  Starting to use infusionsoft and want to learn all I can!!! check out http://www.scotthull.com     
    
    
    #HOWlive How were @mikeyburton and @Vonster's presentations?  Sorry I missed the HOW conference and connecting with good friends.    
    
    
    A Sunday by the pool researching great stories on our artists.  Could be a new reality show!!!    
    
    
    6 tips for keeping a company creative. http://holykaw.alltop.com/6-tips-for-keeping-a-company-creative … via @GuyKawasaki    
    
    
    Found a book on recycled art in a college library. Is this listed on the designers 10 must reads? #howlive, #icon7 http://twitpic.com/a0htfc     
    
    
    @ReCourses Dave, surprised this book wasn't on the top 10bks for graphic design students. pic.twitter.com/ryq2VTRE    
    
    
    @danielgblackman @crankypressman Got to love those folks at Crankypressman.  They do great work!!    
    
    
    Scott Hull Associates' @Vonster (Von Glitschka) gave Adobe, with a little art some class at @HOWconference.... http://fb.me/1KyiX3qG2     
    
    
    @Vonster #HydeParkonHudson. http://bit.ly/LP74eQ  Couldn't agree more! Did you see Bill Murray on Letterman?    
    
    
    @Vonster #BillMurray introduced his hologram that night on #Letterman.  Look into the future. http://popwatch.ew.com/2012/06/08/bill-murray-hologram-david-letterman-video/ …    
    
    
    Trust is the one essential element for healthy critique groups and creative collaborations.  http://bit.ly/crctrst     
    
    
    I so agree with @MikeyBurton idea of "Work For Work".  We like to deliver on the promise of delight.    
    
    
    Honored to set in the live interview with my Filmically Perfect buds!  Checkout Friday @ 12:30PM EST on WYSO: http://www.publicbroadcasting.net/wyso/ppr/index.shtml …    
    
    
    @aigacincinnati @kclasita Show what you love to do and what makes you, you.    
    
    
    @fwmedia In today's communication world, business can be run anywhere as long as you have internet hook up and passion.    
    
    
    Why I'm a Visual Ambassador: "Art Fears Business Fears Art" from Seth Godin's Blog.... http://fb.me/2eWdOFuac     
    
    
    A table with a mind of its own. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973439032/ …    
    
    
    OMG! I broke the ceramic cow... http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973439050/ …    
    
    
    Pre order @JordahHull's new album "Who's Gone to Teach You How to Live?  Releases Tuesday!!! http://store.ropeadope.com/product/jordanhull …    
    
    
    @MikeyBurton tells his "mishap to miracle story to... http://fb.me/1OEgyL0zz     
    
    
    Check out @jordanhull's "tables turn" acoustic filmed in Philly: http://youtu.be/8hzg9J9tYWA  via @youtube    
    
    
    BIG DAY FOR @JordanHull! Album Release in Nashville @12thandPorter! Buy it for your ears. http://store.ropeadope.com/product/jordanhull … via @http://    
    
    
    Of course Mom & Dad sends @JordanHull milk & cookies to celebrate his album release show. http://twitpic.com/a6a7mm     
    
    
    You have to read this review by Knoxville DJ, @WayneBledsoe on @JordanHull's new album.  WOW!!  http://www.knoxville.com/news/2012/jul/14/knoxville-music-jordan-hull-rhett-miller/ …    
    
    
    @MikeyBurton and @ScottHull Associates are so honored to help @OutofPrint donate 6,200 books to Africa!... http://fb.me/zyfTHvJq     
    
    
    @PenelopeDullaghan shares her @Teamotions collaboration with @Motto.  @ScottHull Associates... http://fb.me/2jafOiw0m     
    
    
    It's finally here! @JordanHull's 'Who's Gonna Teach You How To Live?' purchase on iTunes. Buy/LIKE the album right here http://itunes.apple.com/us/album/whos-gonna-teach-you-how-to/id533997751 …    
    
    
    This is the summer to have a pool.  We're living right.    
    
    
    @NewMediaDayton  Anyone outthere have knowledge of CRM??    
    
    
    Illustration Friday is featuring our own Curtis Parker! Curtis & @ScottHull Associates thanks @IF!!... http://fb.me/VuZmwute     
    
    
    PLEASE HELP! @JordanHull's on the charts! The more comments &likes on iTunes the longer the new album is on the charts. http://itunes.apple.com/us/album/whos-gonna-teach-you-how-to/id533997751 …    
    
    
    John Maggard has taken his realistic style to motion.  Check out this crazy mind!... http://fb.me/KJfirtxM     
    
    
    You never know who @MegHunt is helping.  This time @Target House.... http://fb.me/RORuV5ot     
    
    
    Now this is the summer of fun! @JordanHull and the Cobra boys making music http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sMMPe8SqzCI …    
    
    
    Here @JordanHull is busking the streets of #Knoxville, TN while touring. Summer fun building fans! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=z-aq9dsYVVc …    
    
    
    Great story! @ScottHull Associates' Larry Moore paints last shuttle launch.... http://fb.me/1nmy6bP84     
    
    
    What is Art? http://ow.ly/i/O8Bz  #VisualAmbassador http://fb.me/22jvzUe4n     
    
    
    @ScottHull Associates' Larry Moore takes best of show winner, Bucks County Plein Air.  Living his passion! http://fb.me/24fIlyBiw     
    
    
    Where's Bo Jackson? @ScottHull Associates' Mark Riedy tells his story on original type and illustration to... http://fb.me/OTPAXEpS     
    
    
    @ScottHull Associates: ORIGINAL ART WORKS. Now I want to share why.   #VisualAmbassador http://ow.ly/i/O8HP  http://fb.me/1EL4gAt2x     
    
    
    WE WIN GOLD! Way to go Penelope Dullaghan & David Lesh for being noticed for your art in healthcare... http://fb.me/29hEPXAzi     
    
    
    Thanks to @altpick for the shootout on Mark Riedy and @BoJackson!  http://altpick.com/news/6826  @scotthull    
    
    
    Focus... is the key:  http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973614807/ … via @pinterest #visualambassador    
    
    
    Conceptual packaging for summer. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973614832/ … via @pinterest #visualambassador    
    
    
    Lessons I've learned to share. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973623730/ …    
    
    
    ;-) Lessons I've learned http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973623767/ …    
    
    
    Curtis Parker adds so much to a project. It's almost spiritual.... http://fb.me/1O9nina0B     
    
    
    THE HAND http://www.ropeadope.com/archives/article/5689/#.UBxKriA9Fb4.twitter …    
    
    
    As #VisualAmbassador I've learned to build on long-term relationships. It's not easy but the true secret to... http://fb.me/1awQBqXPl     
    
    
    Roll out the red carpet for @MarkPernice and the EBIE awards! http://scotthull.com/artists/blog/mark-pernice/ …... http://fb.me/2eJzMwavT     
    
    
    Thanks @Altpick for reposting the Art Fears Business Fears Art.... http://fb.me/1aAS0FCsx     
    
    
    Thanks once again to @Altpick for posting the article on @Penelope Dullaghan.  http://altpick.com/news/6846 ... http://fb.me/2e1hr9Dbd     
    
    
    How important is design? Without it one tacky mess. Great post by @ThisIsSethsBlog http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2012/08/a-tacky-mess-the-masses-vs-great-design.html?utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+typepad%2Fsethsmainblog+%28Seth%27s+Blog%29 … #visualambassador @Scotthull    
    
    
    So cool to see how @Citgo gets impact milage with Lorraine Tuson's artwork.... http://fb.me/2dJx6OY4q     
    
    
    Thanks Bryan Bowers for the photos & videos from last nights @JordanHull Chapel Hill show. He's liv'n the dream! http://twitpic.com/ahfuy8     
    
    
    Cool video! @JordanHull &Band tour adventure, set to a song on Jordan's new album. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MDHToCuw0vc&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    How important can outsourcing be? Seth Godin Blog: Buying the thing your project truly needs http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2012/08/buying-the-thing-you-truly-need.html … via @ThisIsSethsBlog    
    
    
    What type of artist are you?  Love this chart by @CaldwellTanner. http://twitpic.com/aizxo8     
    
    
    Interesting question by a client today.  "What makes you more creative?"  Answer: "Reputation" #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Found Arlo crashed on the bench while reading his favorite book.  What a life! http://twitpic.com/akmivo     
    
    
    Got my tickets for @FilmDayton Festival 2012!  Who's going? http://tkt.ly/SyrUMS  #ticketleap    
    
    
    Check this out! Artists were a threat even in the 50's. http://twitpic.com/akqedd     
    
    
    Do you rate yourself successful?  Check out this chart. http://fb.me/1llP1oVmw     
    
    
    Thanks for the shout out @altpick on Penelope Dullaghan! http://altpick.com/news/6873  @ScottHull Associates http://fb.me/A4UIVFsL     
    
    
    Hot dogs and Spaghetti.  Got to love it!! http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973752671/ …    
    
    
    dreaming of you, pillows.  BEWARE: She could be pissed for what you did in her dream. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973752677/ …    
    
    
    Turning a Shaker idea into a modern idea.  We call is an electric Amishman concept. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973752698/ …    
    
    
    Yes, indeed. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973761012/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @Vonster for sharing the great freelance video. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-lY9Nl8QrOA&feature=youtube_gdata_player#visualambassador …    
    
    
    As @MikeyBurton says, "Freelance Ain't Free'. Funny video.... http://fb.me/CiJdR38g     
    
    
    Film Buffs, let's face it, why would Dorothy want to go home to Kansas? #oz    
    
    
    Get day @FilmDayton Festival where Brent held court.  Kid knows his movies!! http://twitpic.com/ao22oi     
    
    
    To those of you who know me and have worked with me: What would you say I do? In other words, what is my value proposition?    
    
    
    Now you'll understand why Artists struggle with the business side.... http://fb.me/CXmKDXbD     
    
    
    GREAT interview with @MegHunt and Illustration Fridays! Check it out!!... http://fb.me/2cWnCQi4a     
    
    
    What Successful People Do With The First Hour Of Their Work Day http://www.fastcompany.com/node/3000619  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    The most asked question by clients and creatives, "What about the copyright?" Here's a great article.... http://fb.me/24xmktcGr     
    
    
    WOW! Found out @JordanHull is the featured artist on @WorldCafe this week! http://www.npr.org/2012/09/03/160391520/next-jordan-hull …    
    
    
    He's getting more ink! @JordanHull gets a shout from @WNYC. http://www.wnyc.org/npr_articles/2012/sep/03/next-jordan-hull/ …    
    
    
    Smart Creative Women interviews @PenelopeDullaghan. Check it out!... http://fb.me/1AffpaoQw     
    
    
    @JordanHull is in Columbus tomorrow doing an interview on @WCBE905Columbus around 10:30AM then a late show at Bethel Road Pub. Check it out!    
    
    
    WOW! @JordanHull played a show with John Legend, Train, Guided by Voices, Ohio Players. Plus@WorldCage featured artist. http://www.npr.org/2012/09/03/160391520/next-jordan-hull …    
    
    
    Great music weekend in Dayton!  Got to hang with friends new and old.  Thanks @AndyGrammer for showing up!! http://twitpic.com/atbz2l     
    
    
    WOW @JordanHull! So cool to hear David's introduction.  Click red speaker above the photo. @nprmusic: Next: Jordan Hull http://n.pr/RupOwp     
    
    
    Heard an interesting presentation on in-house design vs. design agency. Question: Who are the gatekeepers where ideas are created?    
    
    
    Looking forward toOctober's @SummitUpCon ference.  CHECK OUT the line up!  http:www/summitup.org. @shelbyq @OhlmannGroup @seancreighton    
    
    
    @aigacincimentor   talk last night on Design Matters?. Yes, that's the back of my head. http://www.lpk.com/2012/09/lpks-nathan-hendricks-explains-why-designers-are-screwed-at-aigas-design-week-event/ … @LPK @nathanhendricks @AIGAcin    
    
    
    Love this info graphic; Inside the Mind of a Freelancer | infographic from Mashable http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712973909372/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    Now I understand why @MikeyBurton is a fan of bears...  #visualambassador http://fb.me/1SKrFBSkq     
    
    
    Check out one of @AndreaEberbach sketches on bread history!  This girl is good!!! http://fb.me/28dyY2CuG     
    
    
    @JordanHull &Band played the ChicagoHardRock then Wilbert's in Cleveland.  One busy boy. (Taken with Instagram at... http://bit.ly/SRVCCr     
    
    
    @JordanHull at @HardRockCafeChicago sharing his art!  Thanks @emily_quirk !  http://flic.kr/p/daPX8w     
    
    
    Thanks @Altpick for the shout out interview with Smart Creative Women & @PenelopeDullaghan. Check it out!... http://fb.me/ymmK6Ng7     
    
    
    @ifri Thanks @AlternativePick for the shout out to our friends at Illustration Fridays!  @alt http://altpick.com/news/6954     
    
    
    Fun find, Signage for Blind Bob's. #Fontly http://font.ly/font/4090  pic.twitter.com/wkaHNDg9    
    
    
    Great interview with Milton Glaser by Saundra Marcel.  Check it out!!!... http://fb.me/2bU8sK8Hk     
    
    
    Talk about turning a simple idea into something to remember. Good job @JWT... http://fb.me/1jb3rNvgY     
    
    
    Talk about turning a simple idea into something to remember. Good job JWT!... http://fb.me/29hajYkiv     
    
    
    Got to get this @iPhone case. It's like a Swiss Army Knife. http://www.fastcodesign.com/1670876/an-iphone-case-thats-as-handy-as-a-swiss-army-knife?utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+fastcompany%2Fheadlines+%28Fast+Company%29#1 …    
    
    
    This week I've talked to a lot of Marketing and Creative Directors, one big problem: Client's Bad Ideas.  This... http://fb.me/1MNLZrvnc     
    
    
    Love the little hidden gems you find when in @YellowSprings. Fall has begun! http://twitpic.com/azy34j     
    
    
    Penelope Dullaghan and @Motto gets a shout out from @altpick. What a great case study!... http://fb.me/25oLsp2eh     
    
    
    Got my framed print of @TimGough's silkscreen from the album "Midweek Mountain Get Away". Cool art and good... http://fb.me/1fs88JZqp     
    
    
    Interview with Patti Gay @theillstratorsmarket.  Thanks Colin for the help!... http://fb.me/2dG48KUbH     
    
    
    Von Glitschka aka @Vonster did some exploring of "The Naked Grape".... http://fb.me/X4yMn6Xk     
    
    
    @JordanHull &band gives a jazzy sound to "Better Judgement". These folks are having fun making their art! http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=-1X72J3307o …    
    
    
    @meghunt Please, let's not wish our life away!    
    
    
    @MarkPernice & Andy Hayes show off their latest creative work.... http://fb.me/1QEXQkMgD     
    
    
    @davegray Dave, just got a copy of The Connected Company.  Looking forward in reading about your findings!    
    
    
    Wine label artwork: A sneak peak of Lorraine Tuson's process.  Love the final!! @scotthull http://fb.me/1lGrCZyze     
    
    
    @PenelopeDullaghan adds one more image toward building Shamabhala’s visual assets.... http://fb.me/1Y0Xkwyao     
    
    
    Oh... Happy Thanksgiving to our Canadian friends !!    
    
    
    @TheOnion gives their Swing State Analysis on Ohio. http://www.theonion.com/video/the-onions-swing-state-analysis-ohio,29840/?utm_source=Facebook&utm_medium=SocialMarketing&utm_campaign=standard-post:section:default …    
    
    
    Mark Riedy's 54ft Relief sculpture design we did for the Great American Ballpark. Now a Rookwood collectable! http://fb.me/JipmJSSw     
    
    
    @JordanHull adds a little harp to @OldManLuedecke. Fun tune!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IFn3sPj0QuU …    
    
    
    "Rollin in my sweet baby's arms" video of @OldManLuedecke with Joel and Jordan.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IFn3sPj0QuU …    
    
    
    @MikeyBurton's first batch of the Golden Axe Cider brand design is now bottled and shipping!! http://fb.me/t6QVfL8Y     
    
    
    Off to expand my knowledge on social marketing at @SummitUpCon.    
    
    
    Nice shout out by Philly's @thewollenfox on @JordanHull new album!  Link to a free listen. http://theswollenfox.com/featured-track-jordan-hull-red-lights/ …    
    
    
    I could use your help. How would you convince someone about "The Value of the Visual Voice"? #visualambassador @scotthull    
    
    
    As a Visual Ambassador, I love Seth Godin's thinking.  Great question: "What is school for?" Listen!... http://fb.me/2ioBRUg5c     
    
    
    @bingkahuna Nick it's good to have you as a fellow tweeter!!    
    
    
    This afternoon, working to focus on the business behind the art.  #visualambassador    
    
    
    OK, we just had call number 7 today from the Obama and Romney people.  These next 2 weeks are going to be a pain in Ohio.    
    
    
    Not a bad day. Only 2 polictical calls so far today.  Where did you guys go???    
    
    
    Lookout @AIGA INDY! @Vonster is coming to town to share his thoughts on "Drawing Conclusions"... http://fb.me/xCQ5x9Bc     
    
    
    Graph explaining what it takes to come up with a really great idea. #Visualambassador http://fb.me/1l6xARBZr     
    
    
    How does the value of a "visual voice" relate in your world?    
    
    
    Early voting has begun in Ohio. Find your voting location to vote for Ohio's President! http://OFA.BO/rv958j     
    
    
    A weekend hearing all about the guys running for President of Ohio.    
    
    
    Doing a little client calling today asking about their problems. Research; safety net or trampoline to propel... http://fb.me/1lLORJa6W     
    
    
    What is "The Key to Memory?" @BenBarry from @Facebook shares his thoughts.... http://fb.me/202HgZgyL     
    
    
    Looking for a way to help the NY and New Jersey folks from #Sandy? Donate to a group I trust right in NYC.... http://fb.me/1oG05cDEl     
    
    
    RETWEET Looking for a way to help the NY and New Jersey folks from #Sandy? Donate to a group I trust right in NYC.... http://fb.me/1oG05cDEl     
    
    
    It's remarkable how blogs can speard the word.Check out @hookandinemag on @JordanHull.  http://www.hookandlinemag.com/2012/10/oh-sandy-jordan-hull.html …    
    
    
    Old ways never fail, Storytelling-part art, part science-100% imagination -  http://www.smartinsights.com/content-management/content-marketing-strategy/storytelling-part-art-part-science-100-imagination/ … via @smartinsights #visualambassador    
    
    
    Political calls started at 9AM today.  We've had 5 so far and it's only 10:15AM. Who will be President of Ohio?    
    
    
    Tweet what illustration majors from @CCADedu want to know about life after school.  May or may not include in my Nov. 14th talk.    
    
    
    Will someone answer the dang phone!!! It's Obama again... no it's Romeny.    
    
    
    Today vote early and often.    
    
    
    @CCADedu Hey Designers & Marketers!  What do you want illustration majors to know about your job?  How can they be of service?    
    
    
    Got three calls from @Obama today reminding me to vote.  Pist me off that he just kept talking when I asked questions then hung up.    
    
    
    Will @HileryClinton run for President in 2016?    
    
    
    WOW! John Maggard puts movement to his art. When asked what fuels his creativity? Answer: Industrial archelology... http://fb.me/12a3meYSC     
    
    
    OK, the election is over.  Everyone back to work.  Wait, you don't have a job?    
    
    
    Folks are praising GoldenAxe Cider and their art by our own @MikeyBurton!!! Sorry it's not in the States yet.... http://fb.me/2zUgM34OV     
    
    
    As an artist you want to create. Checkout Curtis Parker's latest personal exploration painting. http://fb.me/2vry38Pzn     
    
    
    Got to share this! Shout out to GoldenAxe Cider for top cider and credit to our own @MikeyBurton for the art!!!  . http://fb.me/2zUgM34OV     
    
    
    Suddenly nothing happend!!! That's how it feels in Ohio after all the election buzz.    
    
    
    @jpmagg3 Welcome to the world where you feel like your yelling your message to people in an airport.    
    
    
    #GrandmaMoses really opened my mind to never grow old creativity.  @ClorisLeachman was amazing in the play! Check... http://fb.me/27qzwGdwY     
    
    
    @jpmagg3  I've always been your first...    
    
    
    Another Creative Art Project: Thank an artists!! http://www.good.is/posts/urban-air-los-angeles-artist-transforms-billboards-into-floating-gardens# … #Visualambassador    
    
    
    Very educational meeting with @Jessica_A_Barry today regarding young creatives and understanding business.  @saa_edu is on top of the game.    
    
    
    @saa_edu Jessica, your insight supports my passion/vision to bridge the gap between business and creativity.  Yes, a #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Fighting the man, @Moderndogdesign sells studio to fund copyright infringement lawsuit. Want to help?... http://fb.me/17DIXt7fr     
    
    
    WOW! What a story for all artists & creative people.  Copyright or copy right?... http://fb.me/1KRqRaAjE     
    
    
    Updating the @ScottHull Associates' email list because we love our clients. Want to be on the list?    
    
    
    @Scotthull We update the list because spamming is bad...    
    
    
    Where ideas come from?  An inside look at Curtis Parker's process.  #VisualAmbassador http://fb.me/21bDPydiB     
    
    
    What! Found an interesting article on @MikeyBurton's book cover project.... http://fb.me/wE9i2OS9     
    
    
    On my drive home after a meeting the stop signs weren't working.  It was chaos!!    
    
    
    Found the perfect Christmas gift for my social media friends!!! Let me share the love... http://twitpic.com/bdjtj8     
    
    
    @flickster @saa_edu @CSCArts More awards!!! @saa_edu is doing something right!  Will deserved!!!!    
    
    
    @ModernDog's story is in @Adweek about there copyright battle with @Disney & @Target. Video is attached.... http://fb.me/1BtnE0sIq     
    
    
    CHECKOUT the box design for Golden Axe.  Mr. @MikeyBurton, I can't wait to see the apple cider on store shelves. http://fb.me/1JhopP40l     
    
    
    Our client Orchard Group has made a BIG impact in the Sandy hurricane relief!  Let link you to their blog.... http://fb.me/1o1z3wIdi     
    
    
    @Vonster Sports players started making the big bucks when they realized they were entertainor.  Look at WWE...    
    
    
    With Hostess going under, buy stock in Little Debbies    
    
    
    Love talking to my kids about creativity growth.  Three amazing thinkers.    
    
    
    My son caught this listing on the movie marquee.  Had to circle back for a photo!!! 
@frankenweenie #frankenweeni http://twitpic.com/be2hlm     
    
    
    It came from the mountain, There WILL be a second coming of the Twikie. @hostess @twikie http://twitpic.com/be31ho     
    
    
    @noudles04 You and Mike are included.  I didn't say which 3 kids...    
    
    
    I think Abe & Rebecca should have had "The Electric Amishmen" for their reception band.
#BreakingAmish    
    
    
    @colindul Colin, You're a good Dad.  It will come back to reward you.    
    
    
    WOW. @OhioState and @NotreDame are the only undefeated college football teams in the country.    
    
    
    @Dan_Roam If you liked the shuttle stuff, checkout this article and video on @LarryMoore who was at the last launch.  http://scotthull.com/artists/blog/larry-moore-painting-history-the-last-shuttle-launch/ …    
    
    
    Time to adventure on your own? Top 10 Vital Elements of a Successful New Freelancer’s Website. http://freelanceswitch.com/freelance-marketing/vital-website-elements/ … via @freelancesw    
    
    
    Let's face it, #BreakingAmish must have had limited canadenites for the show. After all, Amish don't have TVs.    
    
    
    Just watched #BreakingAmish.  In December they're doing #AmishMafia. Come on... next will be breaking Jewish.    
    
    
    @PenelopeDullaghan has such a fun loving spirit in her art. http://fb.me/1KFrv4lZF     
    
    
    @jpmagg3  You never know where "darker'n the inside of a cow" came from.  My guess Mr. Hartford picked it up from an Amishman.    
    
    
    Look into the future: "This decade is about using the Internet to enable real-world interactions," So ture!!  http://www.fastcodesign.com/1671085/3-big-insights-from-todays-top-design-thinkers#1 …    
    
    
    Curtis Parker impacts another city, Emeryville, CA with this mural for @Panera.  Thanks Jay, Don and team. http://fb.me/xBT9IEz0     
    
    
    Movie lover? Check out this info graphic on the most improtant films. http://www.fastcodesign.com/1671111/infographic-the-2000-most-important-films-of-all-time … #Movie    
    
    
    The house is filled with the smell of turkey.  Should have kept the bird outside.    
    
    
    As God as my witness, I thought turkeys could fly.http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=lf3mgmEdfwg …    
    
    
    My @Klout Score has climbed from 58 to 59! http://klout.com/user/Scotthull/score-analysis?n=tw&v=mobile_change …    
    
    
    Fun newsletter by video! @JordanHull even gets a shout out!!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_O56Gxd1YT0&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    One long day yesterday. My Aunt Nedra's funeral with all my McMillian cousins.  Fond memories with new ones made.    
    
    
    My @Klout Score just reached 60! How influential are you? http://klout.com/user/Scotthull/score-analysis?n=tw&v=mobile_decile …    
    
    
    @Tom4Success Is that a Wheaton Terrier in you profile photo?    
    
    
    It's great to hear about the value art can bring a brand.  @PenelopeDullaghan has worked her magic again.... http://fb.me/1HtMCrBUI     
    
    
    HEY CREATIVES IN INDY, the @Vonster will be speaking this Thursday in your town!! See you there!... http://fb.me/1aPkJTusd     
    
    
    The R&D Lab of Creativity: Inside the Sketchbooks of Beloved Illustrators and Designers http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2012/11/23/laurence-king-sketchbooks …    
    
    
    @DavidLesh, “All it takes is imagination. Yours and mine.” Here's why.... http://fb.me/2aT1ENEBp     
    
    
    Who's going to the AAF Indianapolis and AIGA Indy Present: "Drawing Conclusions" by @Vonster? http://www.eventbrite.com/s/b9Fe     
    
    
    Talk about a “life of their own”. @JohnMaggard's artwork now used as engineering aids in colleges and... http://fb.me/2gGkpVn2N     
    
    
    Thanks @Altpick for the @MegHunt shout out!! http://altpick.com/news/7153  http://fb.me/25ofa6ugY     
    
    
    Thanks @aigaindy for the great lunchen today with @Vonster at the @TheJazzKitchen. What a great turnout!    
    
    
    Great offer for 5 freebies to the first movers for @DanielPink 's new book,"To Sell Is Human" http://bit.ly/119S1Rx   (via the Pink Blog)    
    
    
    @MegHunt gives @ JamieOliver's magazine a little visual spice this year.... http://fb.me/1NO1iPakl     
    
    
    Who doesn't love the @Beatles. David Reinbold pays his tribute in art.... http://fb.me/1K2EH0fvn     
    
    
    Let December begin at the Hull house!!! http://twitpic.com/bilbho     
    
    
    My friends' give holiday decorations a different twist.  Oh the MidWest... http://twitpic.com/bilc5d     
    
    
    @Vonster Those Amish can be sneaky and mean.    
    
    
    Interesting how companies like @Panera Bread are investing in art. Checkout Curtis Parker.... http://fb.me/2jtj9iMub     
    
    
    Love the 70's? Check out last nights interview with #LedZeppelin and #DavidLetterman. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KEdmJRqoMaI …    
    
    
    What's a good mailing list source for #illustration?    
    
    
    @JeffStahler caught a photo of Flippo the Clown's car today. Remember #Flippo WBNS -10 Columbus? http://twitpic.com/bj6fp9     
    
    
    How @LisaBallard adds more than a stocking stuffer for  @Airheads Candy.... http://fb.me/12zXFs2de     
    
    
    Love it when @Altpick posts @MegHunt's stories to their blog!!... http://fb.me/1IctrM5IZ     
    
    
    It great to peak into someone's sketchbook to see what they think about. Check out @TimGough sketchbook.... http://fb.me/1sxfjTbVf     
    
    
    @altpick is sharing Curtis Parker's process to the success of @PaneraBread's Emeryville... http://fb.me/2krUeCBQF     
    
    
    @altpick is sharing Curtis Parker's process to the success of @PaneraBread's Emeryville... http://fb.me/2mP2Cs4PI     
    
    
    Does art heal? @AndreaEberbach gives #healthcare a holistic visual touch. http://fb.me/2kPMGAEaQ     
    
    
    #Marketers and #businessowners, Seth Godin makes a great point about "Beggars can't be choosers".  http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/typepad/sethsmainblog/~3/6UWwuwa7jeg/beggars-cant-be-choosers.html …    
    
    
    Thanks @FoodMentalist for kind words about @MikeyBurton Design and Illustration!... http://fb.me/239JGkFgh     
    
    
    @StudioBowesArt Good question about negotiation resources. Most don't understand #WorkForHireContracts, it the lawyers' covering their butts    
    
    
    One of my favorite Dayton homes; Hawthore Hill, home the #WrightBrothers built. That's @SteveWright for the tour. http://twitpic.com/bl4hub     
    
    
    Nativity the Pop Opera, the brainchild of storyboard artist J. Todd Anderson. Show opens this weekend.
http://www.daytoncitypaper.com/the-angels-and-the-audience-know/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @Altpick for featuring @MegHunt on this weeks newsletter! http://altpick.com/reports/121212/  http://fb.me/2zDJzQ64z     
    
    
    @MikeyBurton shares how a literary classics project reaches underprivileged child.... http://fb.me/1KmfgvALq     
    
    
    Please share about the value of growing equity with visual assets. @HaywardBaker & @JohnMaggard a great case study.  http://fb.me/1bKtdfTae     
    
    
    No dubt, it's safer in the wilderness than it is in a city.    
    
    
    Last show today at 2.  @JToddAnderson's @NativitythePopOpera.   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uDub8N-RecM&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    @BrettHull, our movie journalist son said "the movie #Titanic is the #Applebees of movies."    
    
    
    If the @Amish can have a Mafia, what's wrong with the design community? First action: spec work.
#amishmafia    
    
    
    @LarryMoore is always a winner in our hearts. http://fb.me/2CIkdxON5     
    
    
    @MARTYneumeier As long as business creativity is in the hands of the few, wealth will be distributed unevenly. http://tinyurl.com/97swqm9     
    
    
    @RyanBubnis knows how great eggnog looks in a @MegHunt glass! http://fb.me/2komYADlc     
    
    
    How @MarkPernice's face gets 1.5 million hits. http://scotthull.com/artists/blog/mark-pernice-2/ … http://fb.me/1E9dC3Xcl     
    
    
    Looking over the numbers from our latest CRM campaign. 51% opened the email with 17% downloads so far.  That's a lot of eyes!    
    
    
    Remembering the old days with our kids. http://twitpic.com/bnheo0     
    
    
    #AmishMafia, really? Making @LancasterPA look like the new city of crime???    
    
    
    Von Glitschka, AKA @Vonster gives you a chance to share his Jolly St. Nick.... http://fb.me/2wTdtl1rv     
    
    
    Not just any invitation, a @MegHunt wintery wedding invitation.... http://fb.me/24Oy283e1     
    
    
    As  #VisualAmbassador, let me share the answer to the question: " Why some art has more value?" http://fb.me/CGEj9fOB     
    
    
    My facial tattoo is going to look so cool when I'm working as a janitor for McDonalds. http://shorturl.xaijo.com/luisa     
    
    
    @Barron'sFinacial tagged Curtis Parker for the 12th year to illustrate the close of the year. Last year they were... http://fb.me/2ngbpVEN6     
    
    
    GREAT WISDOM to artists from @sethgodin: "What you waiting for?"  http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2012/12/what-you-waiting-for.html …    
    
    
    40% agree the best thing about holiday parties is spending time with family&friends.
@MikeyBurton graphic #Ziploc http://twitpic.com/bo0uqu     
    
    
    Most popular time to kick off a holiday party: 57% say 7pm, 30% say 8pm, 12% say 4pm. A @MikeyBurton graphic #Ziploc http://fb.me/1F5KcAHFf     
    
    
    Some fun holiday stats from #Ziploc with graphics by @MikeyBurton.    
    
    
    The holiday movie fest begins at the Hull's.  "One Eyed Jack" with #MarlonBrando and now "#TheLastWaltz" with #TheBand & Friends.    
    
    
    56% of people wrap their gifts by hand and get festive with the paper.  A @MikeyBurton graphic for #Ziplock http://fb.me/Q0hcv3mx     
    
    
    How are you using the Moleskine Professional Notebook in your creative business? http://www.moleskineus.com/pmop4626-moleskine-professional-large-notebook.html …    
    
    
    55% keep your guests' kids busy with fun games and yummy food at your party. A @Mikey Burton graphic #Ziploc http://fb.me/1Uh4y2Bky     
    
    
    What movie should we catch tonight?  Lincoln, The Hobbit, This is 40 or Life of Pi?    
    
    
    @timgough Thanks Tim!!! The Hobbit it is!    
    
    
    35 percent of you prefer sugar cookies during the holidays!  A @MikeyBurton graphic #Ziploc http://fb.me/2dBZ5I2B7     
    
    
    80% of you prefer the presence of your cheerful guests over any present at all!  A @MikeyBurton graphic #Ziploc http://fb.me/1W2iKKMwd     
    
    
    DAYTON, OHIO -
Where women make their hair bigger just because they're bored.    
    
    
    Are your kids tracking Santa? http://www.google.com/santatracker/  http://fb.me/1QM91dJgi     
    
    
    Santa tracker from our government: http://www.noradsanta.org/en/track.html     
    
    
    49% of holiday party hosts will surf the web for delicious dishes to serve.  A @MikeyBurton graphic #Ziploc http://fb.me/26UkrVmZY     
    
    
    Another round of gift giving!! The snow makes this one special.    
    
    
    @MegHunt helped make someone's spirits a litter brighter!... http://fb.me/1C9kXJZrD     
    
    
    What's your pick for the worst movies of 2012 supercut [video]? http://holykaw.alltop.com/worst-movies-of-2012-supercut-video … via @GuyKawasaki    
    
    
    Do you have a #To-Do-List for 2013? Check out Thomas Edison's To-Do List, 1888 list from Brain Pickings. http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2012/06/01/thomas-edison-to-do-list-1888/ …    
    
    
    @WayneBledsoe: Top 10 albums of 2012 encompassed heart and soul of Knoxville.  @JordanHull's album makes the list!  http://www.knoxville.com/news/2012/dec/28/wayne-bledsoe-top-10-albums-of-2012-encompassed/ …    
    
    
    Continuing the holiday of movies, #Django was very entertaining.  As the movie jouralist said, "It's one that will hang around."    
    
    
    "Attention is the economy of the internet." Why not grow your creative wealth. #visualambassador    
    
    
    @Infusionsoft Just registered for infusionCon!  See you in March!    
    
    
    Are you living in distractions? I am. Get podcast to start your 2013 from @ToddHenry.... http://fb.me/2FuLb2fws     
    
    
    Just sold all our saving for gold. Not getting close to the cliff...    
    
    
    @DanielPink Hey! Just found my copy of "To Sell is Human" in the mail!! Will look it over to morning, then the webinare.    
    
    
    Well you know the Holidays are over when Arlo comes walking up with decorations.  Nice photo Brett. http://twitpic.com/brlqap     
    
    
    Started my New Year's afternoon with @DanielPink's webinar on ideas, trends and blogs to watch in 2013. I feel so much wiser.    
    
    
    This is such a simple idea but what an impact.  Thanks @DanielPink. http://www.danpink.com/2013/01/the-perfect-4-minute-film-to-start-your-new-year …    
    
    
    Call me "Mr. Lucky".  Had the traditional New Years' pork and sauerkraut.    
    
    
    Creatives, as #VisualAmbassador I want to help you get the word out, "Here, I made this". Check out @SethGodin's post. http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/typepad/sethsmainblog/~3/Pvk3AEZc67o/difficult-and-scary.html …    
    
    
    @Altpick, you're so good to us for sharing Curtis Park and @BarronsWSD cliff cover. http://altpick.com/news/7212  http://fb.me/1VYrRUyE1     
    
    
    Who's going? @Recourses 10th Annual New Business Summit January 23-25 Nashville, TN http://ow.ly/eQ9pF  #nbs2013    
    
    
    So cool to have your logo in a 3D figure. Well deserved @MikeyBurton! @ScottHull #VisualAmbassador http://fb.me/2eGo0lwK5     
    
    
    Look who's #7! @JordanHull makes another top 10 list for 2012. http://www.nodepression.com/profiles/blogs/ten-best-acoustic-songs-of-2012 …    
    
    
    Ran across this video. @JordanHull's first big show at @CanalStreet on Dec 6, 2005. What a great voice even at 16!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=edZ3l6WksiE&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    After a weekend of football, Arlo goes into a coma... http://twitpic.com/bt5u6s     
    
    
    Our man, Andy Hayes@hucklebuck helped out @CSCArts with a cool poster for @eriktjohnsonus. Send your love for a... http://fb.me/2970JIAyt     
    
    
    And the hits keep coming! @JordanHull on @CabinCountryTN. Nice job folks! Like your idea about sharing the music. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GIQOz46hJ10&feature=share …    
    
    
    Nothing like seeing how artists think visually.  Thank @timgough for sharing. http://instagr.am/p/UPyKdJnNM5/     
    
    
    Von Glitschka continues to amaze. Since his design course on @Lynda.com launched it has been the most watched... http://fb.me/1sZdUm6YJ     
    
    
    Talking with a few #illustration students made me think what Kodak must have been saying 10 years ago.    
    
    
    #Illustration is a lot like the record industry.  We'll ALWAYS listen to music but the way it's delievered will... http://fb.me/1QEBQTugw     
    
    
    @DanielPink, what's the headset you use with your computer?  You told us on your New Years day webinar.    
    
    
    Getting help from Mr. @Hucklebuck on branding materials of @ScottHull Associates. Finished our brochure, now #CRM triggers for #NBS2013.    
    
    
    Heading out to meet with the Wright Brothers family regarding the family brand.  How the brothers inpacted the world!    
    
    
    A morning with the bro connections! Meeting with #WrightBros. nephew then #CoenBros. storyboard artist. What bro will be my PM connection?    
    
    
    @MegHunt, you're now illustrating animals for #Smithsonian!
Made me read the article on turtles. http://fb.me/v9J54C5p     
    
    
    Today's a big event for CSCA! How do I know?  Andy Hayes, Mr. @hucklebuck's poster will grab your attention.... http://fb.me/1SfOLUzTN     
    
    
    #Costofliving Sometimes it's good living in #Dayton, Ohio. Last week I paid $3.39... http://twitpic.com/bw3pxp     
    
    
    At times I feel we never get clients only projects.    
    
    
    What is college for? Now you can tell that design student how to pay off their $100K+ investement for just $12.00. http://twitpic.com/bwnxot     
    
    
    Nice story today on @nprnews "All Things Considerd" on Janis Joplin. To think she would have been 70 today. http://www.npr.org/2013/01/19/169799810/janis-joplin-the-queen-of-rock …    
    
    
    Oh, a calm evening listening to a little touch of #HarryNilsson.  So good! http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Little_Touch_of_Schmilsson_in_the_Night …    
    
    
    Business card can be so cool!  Look how 20 famous people used them as mini billboards.... http://fb.me/1GGstWZhG     
    
    
    Thanks @recourses for the opportuntiy to hang with @blairenns and @michaelgass as part of the mix.#nbs2013 #visualambassador    
    
    
    Vice President Joe Biden swearing now. Sounds like the debates. Live Video:http://bit.ly/Wm7GJt     
    
    
    #NBS2013 Business card can be so cool! Look how 20 famous people used them as mini billboards. http://www.flavorwire.com/364847/the-fascinating-business-cards-of-20-famous-people …    
    
    
    @Polaroid moves to retail-service with a chain of (Genius-like) Photobars. New forms of delivery. #visualambassador
http://www.digitaltrends.com/photography/a-trip-to-polaroids-new-fotobar-retailer/ …    
    
    
    @brianmercer great to join your twitter. Now I'll know all the new trends in viedo broadcasting!! #visualambassador    
    
    
    Fun article on The Pencil Factory where @MarkPernice makes great ideas happen. @thepencilfactory  @scotthull... http://fb.me/2bkdPoDw0     
    
    
    Andy Hayes aka, Mr@Hucklebuck's CSCA poster across Columbus is on the @FrenchPaper site!... http://fb.me/271HMWBe4     
    
    
    Heading to the warmth of the south today. It's 5degrees here. Looking forward to taking in #NBS2013 and expanding my business skills.    
    
    
    @MegHunt's Smithsonian magazine story gets a shoutout from @Altpick!  Thanks folks!!!  http://altpick.com/news/7276  http://fb.me/18WfkMozb     
    
    
    What a wealth of information today at #NBS2013.  Thanks Blair and Dave! So many notes @blairenns @blairenns @ReCourses    
    
    
    Thank you for the opportunity New Business Summit!  So much GREAT information. What will tomorrow bring? @recourse... http://fb.me/ADgFMOix     
    
    
    Fun honky tonk, Robert's in #Nashville. A true honky tonk!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DGePLVZQG5I … #nbs2013    
    
    
    Attended #NBS203 this week. I have to say "The Win Without Pitching Manifesto" by @BlairEnns is a must read.http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1605440043/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_alp_5I.arb1Z8D7Z3 … via @amazon    
    
    
    Kick'n Nashville in beautiful weather.    
    
    
    Big surprise while in Nashville's @Grimeys today. @yolatengo did an acoustic set early afternoon. http://twitpic.com/bymk0p     
    
    
    @JordanHull & I pulled up at the stoplight in front of Zanies. Robert Plant was standing talking to folks.  http://twitpic.com/byt82z     
    
    
    Athens, great find in #Nashville. Was on @DinersDriveIns&Dives.  Order what they featured on the show. http://twitpic.com/byt8jh     
    
    
    Love recordshop graphics.  @Grimeys in #Nashville, even #Dayton's @GuidedByVoices did a record release there. http://twitpic.com/byt97s     
    
    
    Ms.@PenelopeDullaghan gives us a peek of her @CommArts Annual Illustration judging hotel room. First class for a... http://fb.me/2mzabfZ8c     
    
    
    @michaelgass shares@DavidCBaker's "My Social Media Presence Strategy" http://www.fuelingnewbusiness.com/2013/01/22/david-baker-my-social-media-presence-strategy/ … @recourse #visualambassador #NBS2013    
    
    
    Traveled with Yo La Tengo, Mark Sandman of Morphine and Jordan Hull on my way home.    
    
    
    Back from @Recourse's New Business Summit focused on positioning. This was my first email this morning.... http://fb.me/ypBXGG14     
    
    
    @ICONconference Your career and life journey is all about positioning. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xaLDRSg6vic … #visualambassador    
    
    
    #Illustrators & #Desginers: I'm making a check list and need your input, "What does a quaified client look like?"    
    
    
    @ICONconference #Illustrators I'm making a check list and need your input, "What does a quaified client look like?" #visualambassador    
    
    
    @ICONconference If the client has power, what is the source of their power? Yours is relationship through positioning. Your expertise.    
    
    
    #SuperBowl, Illustration is a big part of the big game. Super Bowl poster collection. Can you name the artist?... http://fb.me/272QSFmwo     
    
    
    Just thinking, "What makes you more creative?" Could it be Reputation.    
    
    
    @Scotthull  so far we have pain, necessity and deadlines added to the question, "What makes you more creative?"    
    
    
    I keep hearing creative folks frustrated with the process.  @ToddHenry's article may help you understand the... http://fb.me/1T5GoTny3     
    
    
    3 years. 440,000 books. Great job @OutofPrintClothing! Thanks for including @MikeyBurton's bookcovers.... http://fb.me/1wrPkQzOp     
    
    
    @Batterii Enjoyed 
@ChadAReynolds
 presentation today at AAF Dayton today. Now I want to know more about #coolhunting and #cocreation.    
    
    
    @ChadAReynolds Had lunch today with an old friend of yours, John Gleason.  We talked about your great presentation at AAF Dayton.    
    
    
    One of our favorite creatives, @landor_dot_com's Dale Doyle tells his packaging peeves.... http://fb.me/25mQfj8mF     
    
    
    SUPERBOWL Weekend! Something Mark Riedy did for The SuperBowl program several roman numerals ago.... http://fb.me/W4Y3CXXc     
    
    
    What a great tired this morning after 3 great meetings yesterday.    
    
    
    A #GroundhogDay marathon.  Now to watch the movie.    
    
    
    Getting ready with a few #SuperBowl snacks.  This should WOW the folks. http://twitpic.com/c0hjuy     
    
    
    @OurGreatAmerica 11.2 million pounds of chips will be munched down today! That's equal to 4 million pounds of fat, but screw it...    
    
    
    49.2 million cases of beer are estimated to be sold today. #SuperbowlXLVII    
    
    
    Inforgraphic: SuperBowl Ads of 2013 Cheat Sheet. http://www.nerdwallet.com/blog/shopping/2013/super-bowl-infographic/#.UQ7X-2h2nio.twitter … #superbowl    
    
    
    Charge up those creative batteries, #BeautyIsEmbarrassing film about @WayneWhite will do it creative folks!... http://fb.me/2nR9MIps3     
    
    
    @michaelgass shares Top 10 Mistakes in Web Design That Hurt Ad Agency New Business http://dld.bz/Ck24     
    
    
    If you're in the communciation business you must follow @michaelgass.  I meet Mike at #NBS2013.  One smart guy.    
    
    
    What would @design-illustration student's like the hear about, 1.student networking, 2.internships and 3.IsIllustration Dead?    
    
    
    Penelope Dullaghan shares her thoughts on judging @CommArts illustration.... http://fb.me/2w8Dv2QR0     
    
    
    If your school is cutting out art, have the educators read this; "Top 10 skills children learn from the arts"... http://fb.me/26ZY0RE1D     
    
    
    Thanks @michaelgass for sharing 6 Practical Tips for Ad Agency RFP Responses.  What do you feel about RFPs?  http://dld.bz/akTJ     
    
    
    Creatives, your school is cutting out art? RETWEET this! "Top 10 skills children learn from the arts"... http://fb.me/26ZY0RE1D     
    
    
    @FuelLines
Great question: How Well Do You Really Know Your Advertising Agency? http://dld.bz/bgV57     
    
    
    You'll pay a lot... What is your value? Creatives, how are you letting others know their ROI? http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/02/youll-pay-a-lot.html … #visualambassador    
    
    
    Home from a day of judging @ccad's AOI show.  Some pictures need to be posted.    
    
    
    @itsbillmain Good point Bill, it's about positioning your talent so the customer knows your expertise.    
    
    
    Full day judging @CCADedu's illustration show. A few folks that helped out. #visualambassador http://fb.me/2Ke0gWCL2     
    
    
    @CCADedu @GrahamErwin Great judging with you this afternoon.  Funny the students never heard of @CommArts.  Come on instructors!!    
    
    
    @dicemanart great showing today at @CCADedu AOI.  Looking forward to our conversation.    
    
    
    @dicemanart @GrahamErwin  Looking forward to our upcoming conversation. I'll send you a list of questions later this week.    
    
    
    I have to share with the world a video titled, "The Last Advertising Agency on Earth." Thanks @MichaelGass for... http://fb.me/2KkRWsPEl     
    
    
    @michaelgass You have some great information.  Glad to share your findings with the world!    
    
    
    @wilkinsteez Thanks for being part of today fun at @ufindlay.  Love sharing ideas with smart folks!    
    
    
    @jens937 Great spending time with you and your students today @ufindlay!  Lets go and build something interesting!!    
    
    
    @Emily_Barnhart Remember, success and wealth is made in your spare time.  Play with your thoughts.    
    
    
    @www_jam_zbz So good to have you in today class @ufindlay!!! Heard some good things about your web work!    
    
    
    @devon_marti Enjoyed the energy in your class today @uFindlay!! You guys made the afternoon fun!!!    
    
    
    @samanthaholman1 Sam, remember to go the extra mile!  You'll find less competition there. #VisualAmassador    
    
    
    @Adda_boy_jo Well, as you saw at @uFindlay, art has not made me famous but it has made me a lot of friends!  #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    @EAFG_Studios @uFindlay. Don't forget that 90% of information that comes to the brain is visual.  Why not build visual assets for companies?    
    
    
    Did anyone at the @uFindlay talks today take pictures or videos?????    
    
    
    @MirandaLeePanda I'll see what Jens has. Hey, you're the radio lady!!! Like to learn more about your job.    
    
    
    @MirandaLeePanda Bummer!  Sorry I missed you on the radio.  When are you on and what's the station?  Can I pick it up on line?    
    
    
    Talking to students yesterday it hit me, success and wealth is made in your spare time so play with your thoughts.    
    
    
    @LPK So true! Drawing reflexs observation. The @Vonster pointed out a #SaulBass quote, "Design is thinking made visual".    
    
    
    @lindsymairi My son runs into Brittany Howard from time to time at a cool bar that's a double wide called Santa's in Nashville.    
    
    
    Once again @altpick shares the love from the @ScottHull.com blog.  This one titled, "The Last Advertising Agency... http://fb.me/2jZXtoPxY     
    
    
    Jeffrey Gitomer | Challenge for Today http://www.salesblog.com/jeffrey-gitomer/ … via @gitomer #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    @Altpick shares our love on Valentines.  Check out some of the hearts.... http://fb.me/AN6dXYAy     
    
    
    Thanks Katlin for the interview about the AOI show @CCADedu for your March publication.    
    
    
    ‏@FuelLines
Infographic: Social Media Demographics for Ad Agency New Business http://dld.bz/bgV5z     
    
    
    ‏@michaelgass
How many of us deal with this? 20 Tips to Create a Niche Blog for Ad Agency New Business http://ow.ly/hKERT     
    
    
    Off to @WYSO for the "Reinvention Stories" reception.  How many times have you reinvented yourself?    
    
    
    @michaelgass Where do you find this great content for Fuel Lines?  Amazing information for Agencies!  http://www.fuelingnewbusiness.com     
    
    
    While touring @WYSO, there in the main studio was @JordanHull music.  Thanks @NikiDakota for supporting local tale http://twitpic.com/c4pxtm     
    
    
    Got the behind story about @WYSO "ReInvention Stories" on Radio+ShortFilm+InteractiveDocumentary. Launches 2/26! http://twitpic.com/c4q3fa     
    
    
    @michaelgass Like they say, if you want to lead, you got to read.    
    
    
    A must see @FrazePavilion July 28th,  @SteveMartinToGo & his band! Sign me up for the front row!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=jMjfw9rznrs …    
    
    
    Interesting: 5 Ways Brands Are Cutting Out Agencies | http://www.digiday.com/brands/5-ways-brands-are-cutting-out-agencies/ … via @digiday    
    
    
    Do you draw? Von Glitschka aka: @Vonster is speaking at #SXSW on "Drawing Conclusions".  It's a fun talk!!... http://fb.me/1liAWcZjO     
    
    
    Got my tickets for Steve Martin at the @FrazePavilion http://www.fraze.com/steve-martin/  @SteveMartinToGo    
    
    
    Hey Creative Thinkers, what soical media tools do you use for inspiration? #visualambbassador    
    
    
    ‏@michaelgass posts another wise fact.
Consistency is Key To Ad Agency New Business Programhttp://dld.bz/akW8    
    
    
    Haven't watched TV in a while.  Never seen so many ads on builiding your social media and web awarness.  Secret: Be Different    
    
    
    What does this drawing say about the kid at the doctor's office. Eyeing cupcakes... http://twitpic.com/c695gs     
    
    
    #VisualAmbassador: The new consumer dialog in the information age. @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712974996988/ …    
    
    
    #VisualAmbassador: Original Art Works.  @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712974996998/ …    
    
    
    "The commercials this year feel like they're promoting products."  The humor of Steve Martin    
    
    
    Artists, let's start the week out with a simple. Pass this on to other creative folks. #VisualAmbassador http://fb.me/2fJfARffS     
    
    
    Oscars left out Andy Griffith and Larry Hagman in the show's annual tribute 'In Memoriam' tribute!!!
http://www.cnn.com/2013/02/25/showbiz/oscars-in-memoriam-montage/index.html …    
    
    
    @jens937 @DNBwalkup Thanks for the kind post Jens!!!    
    
    
    Are you getting tired of Shepard Ferry's @OBEYGIANT knock offs? #VisualAmbassador http://twitpic.com/c7n6oq     
    
    
    Interesting use of Animals for Infographic – http://www.fubiz.net/2013/03/01/animal-infographic/ … via @Fubiz #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Andrea Eberbach, artist of "Cancer Reconfigured"  #Artofhealing @ScottHull @AndreaEberbach http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975039105/ …    
    
    
    11 Nuggets Of Advice For Design Students, Direct From The Pros http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1671972  via @FastCoDesign #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Once agaign, ‏@michaelgass posts a great read: 25 Tips for Driving Traffic to Your Ad Agency s Blog http://dld.bz/a6DH  #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Lorraine Tuson, artist - amazing info graphic showing DNA. #ArtofHealing #VisualAmbassador http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975039180/ …    
    
    
    Andrea Eberbach, artist for Catholic Healthcare. #ArtofHealing #VisualAmbassador http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975039198/ …    
    
    
    @CBSSunday had an very interesting story on an art forger.  Is it collectable art?... http://fb.me/2ezdvS8yK     
    
    
    More good stuff @michaelgass, 14 Tips for Creating An Agency Blog for New Business http://dld.bz/akXF     
    
    
    The art of asking @TED_TALKS. This brings a tear to the eye and value of the arts.  So cool!!! http://www.ted.com/talks/amanda_palmer_the_art_of_asking.html … #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    @883WLFC Hey, you might like this music  http://www.jordanhull.com .  Why not give him some air time?    
    
    
    @michaelgass your content is so helpful and worthy to share.  New business is always a challenge.    
    
    
    Just did a survey about "What Qualifies a Customer". 90% of the artists said money. I like what @SethGodin has to say http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/03/im-making-money-why-do-more.html …    
    
    
    ‏How bad do you hate Cold Calling? @michaelgass tells more in
"Is Cold Calling an Effective New Business Tactic?" http://dld.bz/akVd     
    
    
    What do you think? Forget Gen Y! Baby Boomers are the real entrepreneurial risk takers: http://ow.ly/i8Pyc   | via @IncMagazine    
    
    
    ‏@LcklndSprngsten writes about Nashville Five /// Jordan Hull : @JordanHull http://wp.me/p220Ee-F9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Marketers and creative thinkers: What's killing you today?... Most are saying, clients only want what they know. #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    The"10 Nuggets of Advice for Illustrative Design Students, Direct From a Pro" for @CCADedu is being reschedule because of snow.    
    
    
    @Scotthull @TED_TALKS  Thanks for sharing the great presentation on "The Art of Asking"!  Every creative could learn for this @Ted_Talks.    
    
    
    What a day with my team developing automation for marketing illustrative design. Doesn't happen overnight... #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    With social media most think it's magic dust but it takes organization, optimizing, finally customizing.  I want to go direct to customizing    
    
    
    I had a dream last night that I saw a PT Cruiser without vanity plates.  Now that's distrubing @ericditmer    
    
    
    Our kids grew up with @peeweeherman. Oh boy, I should have screened this one from our boys. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AFyWQTtIqkk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Wonder if Phil Hartman is regretting not listening to Captain Carl's advise? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AFyWQTtIqkk&feature=youtu.be … @peeweeherman    
    
    
    Good point @Vonster: @Illustrator how do you get a document to stay at the size MY CLIENT INSISTS not what your engineers force feed us?    
    
    
    @wallingphoto great seeing you shooting at #NMDayton @CakeHopeandLove! Where can we see the photos?    
    
    
    Great truth @michaelgass. Content is king. Ad Agencies Need More Content for New Business http://dld.bz/bgV5B  #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Working on business growth today. "Business only has two basic functions; marketing & Innovation." From #PeterDrucker #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    One lesson I'm learning. Crew on an idea and gain weight.    
    
    
    As parents we're as happy as your sadest child. Great words of wisedom.    
    
    
    Where are they now? Why, right here. pic.twitter.com/L5k5z4y7Wh #SNL    
    
    
    Cool write up from an attendee of Von Glitschka aka  @Vonster SXSW talk!... http://fb.me/Kxqgkyjy     
    
    
    The new consumer dialogue. #VisualAmbassador @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975106412/ …    
    
    
    Art is textures & patterns.  #visualambassador http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975106423/ …    
    
    
    Wondering, if entering @printmag is worth the $85 per entry investment?  Seems pricey. http://fb.me/wHBEThPK     
    
    
    Does @PrintMag get infront of the buyers of design or just other designers?    
    
    
    My life is like a flat tire down memory lane.  #VisualAmbassador @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975120335/ …    
    
    
    One of my favoite clients, @DeidreEvans, creative lady for Mentos and Airheads gave a talk. Plus gave out bags of... http://fb.me/2gFoMRYrJ     
    
    
    AAF Dayton thanks @deidreevans, creative lady for @MentosUS & @airheadscandy. Fun hearing the stories behind their product design.    
    
    
    If you are over 12, do you still eat @airheadscandy?  
#Visual Ambassador    
    
    
    Congratulations all Columbus College of Art & Design students on the Art of Illustration exhibition at Rivet... http://fb.me/2SftRRJKe     
    
    
    "30 years ago, nearly half of 16-year-olds had driver's license. By 2010 it dropped to 28%" #SocialMedia impact? http://www.latimes.com/business/autos/la-fi-hy-autos-teen-driver-20130316-1,0,7422833.story …    
    
    
    How can art help #healing? Here's my findings. Thanks @Altpick for the post.  http://altpick.com/news/7453 ... http://fb.me/10fWlEWdJ     
    
    
    Infographics on LinkedIn Facts Figures and statistics 2012   #Infographic @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975150426/ …    
    
    
    #Infographic on how the Top 50 non-profits use #SociInfographic @ScottHull http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975150454/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @CCADedu for the nice write up on judging the student illustration show.  http://www.ccad.edu/blog/2013/03/student-art-of-illustration-show-in-16th-year/?utm_source=Columbus%20College%20of%20Art%20%26%20Design&utm_campaign=8c72ce585e-Alumni_Newsletter_March_2013&utm_medium=email … #visualambassador    
    
    
    @michaelgass askes the hard question,
Is Advertising a Respected Profession? http://dld.bz/asFVG     
    
    
    Glass Falls, Baylor Cancer Center Healing Garden, Dallas, TX by Wayne Design Group, photo via Wayne  http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975155005/ …    
    
    
    The Art of Healing Dolls @art_ofhealing http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975155021/ …    
    
    
    Look at the positioning of 15 Advertising Agencies Featured in AMCs - #ThePitch. Thanks @michaelgass, great post!  http://dld.bz/by9uV     
    
    
    From my journal: We are defined by the experiences and actions of our lifetime.  @scotthull #visuala http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975159539/ …    
    
    
    Film on the #WrightBrothers flying. Talk about the power of visuals. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fBQfXbrHbiw …    
    
    
    Art in APPs. Fun story in @NewYorker explaining "The Story of my App".  http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/culture/2013/03/christoph-niemann-petting-zoo-app.html … #visualambassador    
    
    
    At #comiccon with my son. I'll share pictures later.    
    
    
    The power of info graphics in getting your attention. @art_ofHealing http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975170348/ …    
    
    
    What a smart idea when traveling... @art_ofHealing http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975171909/ …    
    
    
    The Anatomy Of An Agency through an infographic. #VisualAmbassador @Michael Gass http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975172113/ …    
    
    
    Fonts for your résumé. Serif vs Sans: The Final Battle.  #VisualAmbassador http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712975175024/ …    
    
    
    Wondering, if entering @HOWmag is worth the $110 per entry investment? What is the ROI?? Who reads it? http://fb.me/2inoCl9mA     
    
    
    @acomport We had the same trick pulled on us this morning in Ohio.    
    
    
    A day of learning more of the ins and outs of customer relationship marketing at #Infusioncon.    
    
    
    Just re read @BlairEnns book "Win Without Pitching Manifesto" on the plane.  A must read for creatives!    
    
    
    WOW, 2000 marketing driven people handing out business cards and photographing name tages. My people! #icon13    
    
    
    Here we go! #icon13 pic.twitter.com/U4nO44DDWb    
    
    
    Just interviewed by June @BigIdeasBlog.  Love her title, "Brand Journalist". #Icon13 #visualambassador    
    
    
    Really thinking hard where illustrative design is going by 2015. What's your point of view? #VisualAmbassador #icon13    
    
    
    Bridging the gap between strategy and execution.  Do you have this problem as well? #icon13 #visualambassador    
    
    
    My job as Visual Ambassador? Marketing, selling and talking to people. In other words, making friends fast. #VisualAmbassador #icon13    
    
    
    The main plants in the garden. #icon13 pic.twitter.com/EINqo1Zk0t    
    
    
    Creatives remember: The difference between helping and selling is 2 letters. #Visualambassador #icon13    
    
    
    Word of wisedom today: "And, does your Twitter, Tumblr, Facebook etc. represent those 2-5 brand mantra words?" @TheSharkDaymond #ICON13    
    
    
    Listening to @MariSmith on social midia at #Icon13. Sure providing some great reminders for our business of networking.    
    
    
    3 days of heavy study on customer relationship marketing.  Now to apply this new information to our 32 years of... http://fb.me/2077fnIFt     
    
    
    At #Icon13 so much information in 3 days. Good thing we had a session on Getting Things Done with Dave Allen!!!    
    
    
    Once again, all my grand ideas cost me more than a grand!! #Icon13 #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    As #VisualAmbassador, what do you think I do?
#Icon13 @scotthull    
    
    
    @AndreaEberbach's "Reconfigured Goddess" book was just presented to breast cancer patients at the IU Simon Cancer... http://fb.me/KvZ19YmO     
    
    
    #Infographic How Much time should a company invest in Social Media each week?... http://fb.me/P7ymmjc6     
    
    
    @rmcclurkan Thanks for sharing the tweet!    
    
    
    Back from @Infusioncon I found smart people talking to other smart people over and over again.  Glad to be one of... http://fb.me/2sOLoxZUi     
    
    
    @Vonster @CengageLearning What a fee for a book that will be dated in 6 months. Is the author the instructor?   http://amzn.to/14LXQIH     
    
    
    Great idea using social media by @cabincountryTN.  Our own @JordanHull. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmIS6AqePD0 …    
    
    
    @Vonster @CengageLearning OH, royality check.  Does she have a deal with the school?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @creativeamerica: Copyright law exists to promote creation of artistic works, not to stifle free flow of ideas. http://bit.ly/ZBDLMW     
    
    
    RIP ‏@BloombergNews:  Legendary film critic Roger Ebert has passed away: Chicago Sun-Times    
    
    
    @JordanHull gets a feature on Ropeadope : Radio.  Take a listen.  http://shar.es/dIKZZ  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @michaelgass Looks like Tom Sawyer season on the Mississippi.    
    
    
    The act bring humanity and connection to change someone else. That's what artists do. #VisualAmbassador #artist    
    
    
    David Reinbold gives  Mad Men  a little of his style. HEY! Starts April 7th @MadMen_amc #MadMen http://fb.me/2as1h6znm     
    
    
    #Advertising World! Just a reminder wth David Reinbold's illustrations that @MadMen_amc starts TONIGHT!!  #MadMen http://twitpic.com/chqk8v     
    
    
    Tip of the day: Urine conducts electricity...  See the value of of the @Art_ofHealing. Retweet! #VisualAmbassador http://twitpic.com/chs2d1     
    
    
    Got to love healthcare insurance companies. 26% increase last year, now 34% increase this year. It's costing more than a house payment.    
    
    
    @GrahamErwin Great job Graham!!!!    
    
    
    This is great! Thoughts on the Creative Career. Thanks @MikeyBurton for point this out.... http://fb.me/1qEfXHoDk     
    
    
    Check out @USATODAY  'Is Work Killing You?' Downsizing takes toll by upsizing stress. Creativity?  http://usat.ly/Xu64CC  #visualambassador    
    
    
    Those at #NMDayton. Check out David Allen's book "Getting Things Done". 
@gtdguy http://www.davidco.com  #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    What I've leard a #VisualAmbassador: Seth Godin's take, Paying attention (to someone else's agenda) http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/typepad/sethsmainblog/~3/c11bjJf_znE/paying-attention-to-someone-elses-agenda.html …    
    
    
    Love Meg Hunt Illustration. Recent art for Jamie magazine— filled with Japanese dragony goodness.... http://fb.me/2q4LiYxMw     
    
    
    I had the opportunity to meet the final 5 of #DoolittleRaiders 3 years ago at @AFmuseum in Dayton. Amazing story!
 http://www.cnn.com/2013/04/14/opinion/greene-doolittle-raiders/index.html?eref=igoogledmn_topstories …    
    
    
    Visuals telling the story, "Why I Love Cheese".  Are you an addict? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kLsYZIJlR0I …... http://fb.me/2wVeX7pq7     
    
    
    TEACHERS: Heard @SirKenRobinson speak on creativity. Check this interview with @BlueManGroup  founders. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lo4wAW4EiAQ … #BlueSchool    
    
    
    Thursday Von Glitschka aka. @Vonster to speak at ColumbusSocietyofCommunicatingArts @CSCA, Friday... http://fb.me/2s0eiYZSZ     
    
    
    This is why you shouldn't sallow your chewing-gum!  The after effects... http://twitpic.com/cks3ff     
    
    
    This will stop you in your tracks when hiking in Ohio... http://twitpic.com/cl0h60     
    
    
    Our own @timgough featured on @Altpic today! http://altpick.com/timgough  http://fb.me/2Qp0uZCFZ     
    
    
    Connected @Vonster with J Todd Anderson, storyboard artist to the Coen Bros for dinner.  Oakwood Club felt like @MadMen_AMC. #Coenbrothers    
    
    
    Got my @CommArts illustration annual. Great selection of talent with an understanding where illustration is going.
#VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Great chat with Brian Bowes @StudioBowesArt on, How do you consume information?  What's your thought? #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Checkout Micahel Bast & the art of flavor in packaging Snappea Crips.... http://fb.me/1taZSwL7b     
    
    
    Hey Creative Folks: "The real issue is not talent as an independent element, but talent in relationship to will,... http://fb.me/2jsMo7Yom     
    
    
    Once again @michaelgass shares how social media is changing.  A boutique agency moves its website to Pinterest http://dld.bz/b7ycv     
    
    
    Why @facebook is blue. The science of colors in marketing.... http://fb.me/2iZqD98un     
    
    
    Everyone needs to know, @michaelgass  has some of the best post on agency / new business social media.  Someone you must follow.    
    
    
    So much fun to looking into sketchbooks and journals.  This is a page from @MegHunt  Meg Hunt Illustration.  The... http://fb.me/1wUvQ8xhu     
    
    
    Question from David Baker:  How many firms do you know that have failed from lack of talent? That's what I... http://fb.me/Ra8l9q9Y     
    
    
    I've been using social media for years!!! Only my tools have become a little more compact. #VisualAmbassador... http://fb.me/Jd40bmuG     
    
    
    A tribute to Penelope Dullaghan, founder of @IllustrationFriday.... http://fb.me/IboTpJrs     
    
    
    @StudioRia Thanks for the retweet. Penelope has done an amazing job keeping @ifri Illustration Friday going!!    
    
    
    Must hear, @ChrisOatley The Reality Of Being A Professional Artist: LIVE Q&A With Noah Bradley THIS WEDNESDAY! http://otly4.me/1105eQ8     
    
    
    @StarWars Day??? May the 4th be with you. Is this a @Disney marketng idea?
#VisualAmbassador #StarWarsDay    
    
    
    Attendtion Creative Folks: New Guild Website Launches | Graphic Artists Guild.  Will it help your business?  https://www.graphicartistsguild.org/about/new-guild-website-launches#.UYZ-1QSbNds.twitter …    
    
    
    What a find! Rare John Hartford "Aereo Plain" album that brought bluegrass into a new era, newgrass  #JohnHartford http://twitpic.com/coi91e     
    
    
    How many creative peolpe live this way? Avoiding fear by indulging in our fear of fear http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/typepad/sethsmainblog/~3/mg2jmjMuTeM/avoiding-fear.html …
#VisualAmbassador #fear    
    
    
    Back from a day in #Indy. Pictures in a couple weeks.    
    
    
    Read this review, you'll love it! It will give you the reasons why artists are today's business leaders.... http://fb.me/27mSpLrS0     
    
    
    Great chatting about your work Matt! @YeahMattHouston    
    
    
    What is success for you?    
    
    
    Does anyone in Ohio know about #ReserveNationalHealthInsurance? Can't find many complaints. #healthinsurance    
    
    
    @swissmiss Seth Godin is one of my favorite thought leaders.  We need to listen and apply our talents as artists.
#VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    @SirKenRobinson speaking today's truth about education. You have to listen!... http://fb.me/2hzSkQbzO     
    
    
    Our friend ‏@michaelgass56m shares a 7 Step Guide to Successful Infographic Production for Ad Agency New Business http://dld.bz/aymEW     
    
    
    Art and Healing, is there a connection?  Check out @altpick article on @AndreaEberbach... http://fb.me/2mFWhDd73     
    
    
        
    
    
    What a moment!  Went into @Starbucks and heard @HarryNilsson's "A Little Touch of Schmilsson" playing.  What a great singer/songwriter.    
    
    
    WOW share this! AshleyTunney spoke out today on #Bechet's.  One positive young lady despite this journey! http://www.wdtn.com/dpp/news/behcets-disease-advocate?ref=scroller&categoryId=10001&status=true#.UZatXpUrFrg …    
    
    
    @mariarickert it's a pleasure to support someone who's passionate about bettering ourselves.    
    
    
    What's my job? Knowing what to do next.    
    
    
    Buzzed from the gallons of tea during my meeting with John Gleason.  The man has real insight to the business side of creativity.    
    
    
    @Jordanhull My boy has always had great taste in music. I still play the album.    
    
    
    @mikeyburton A must adventure on my next trip to Akron.    
    
    
    @AAFNational  American Advertising Federation conference, #Admerica features the art of Curtis Parker!... http://fb.me/1dMHuECUm     
    
    
    Infusionsoft User Groups are they worth your time? http://www.infusionsoft.com/usergroups#.UaZMx78xDVg.twitter …    
    
    
    @flickster Thanks for the birthday wishes Matt!    
    
    
    Thanks folks for the birhtday wishes.  I'm just one more year wiser.    
    
    
    Penelope Dullaghan latest commission from Save the Children. Malala Yousafzai one amazing girl.... http://fb.me/2n9nPYguX     
    
    
    @MikeyBurton beer label makes it into this month's Esquire... http://fb.me/1VMehjUPo     
    
    
    ‏@michaelgass shares the power of the visual voice. Ad Agencies Need More Content for New Business http://dld.bz/bgV5B     
    
    
    The inspiration behind the artists David Reinbold.... http://fb.me/2LmjbYzD7     
    
    
    A peek at Meg Hunt Illustration for the St. Johns Bizarre.... http://fb.me/2mz55FcRk     
    
    
    I gave @Jordanhull +K about Music on @klout http://klout.com/Jordanhull/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    I gave @ThisIsSethsBlog +K about Marketing on @klout http://klout.com/ThisIsSethsBlog/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    I gave @meghunt +K about Illustration on @klout http://klout.com/meghunt/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    I gave @tedtalks +K about Business on @klout http://klout.com/tedtalks/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    I gave @tedtalks +K about Social Media on @klout http://klout.com/tedtalks/topics?n=tw&v=plusk_gave&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    Creative folks check out this email.  Some interesting articles on branding. http://e2.ma/share/inbound/t/437qe/cyoeu …    
    
    
    You have to check out the video trailer for @jaybaer new book, #Youtility. Very cool! http://convinceandconvert.wistia.com/medias/52lpg5691w?utm_campaign=Argyle+Social-2013-04&utm_medium=Argyle+Social&utm_source=General+Use&utm_term=2013-04-24-13-23-55 …    
    
    
    Thank you @altpick for the shout out on @MegHunt!  http://altpick.com/news/7678  #visualambassador http://fb.me/6kQz0R97N     
    
    
    Love @bjnovak post: "The government has been watching us online?!?" cried the generation that posted absolutely everything online.    
    
    
    My Klout Score is 61. Not bad for a boomer. Join me on Klout to discover yours today. http://klout.com/user/Scotthull?n=tw&v=daily_welcome&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    Check out my response to this question about Creativity on @klout. http://www.klout.com/user/Scotthull/answer/what-is-a-good-book-to-read-on-creativity-and-why-do-you-like-it?n=tw&v=first-person-experts-response-share&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    Check out my response to this question about Design on @klout. http://www.klout.com/user/Scotthull/answer/what-are-some-good-ways-to-stay-inspired?n=tw&v=first-person-experts-response-share&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    You should check out "@JordanHull - "So Sweet, So Subtle"" on @NoDepression: http://ning.it/16dPE1Z     
    
    
    @markpernice @Jordanhull @nodepression Thanks Mark for the shout out!!!    
    
    
    Nice chat with @toddhenry on his upcoming book #DieEmpty. Then saw Retirement Will Kill You @BloombergView
http://www.bloomberg.com/news/2013-06-11/retirement-will-kill-you.html …    
    
    
    @michaelgass So true, you got to read if you want to lead.    
    
    
    http://twitpic.com/cx2age  - Will the dog make Sainthood?    
    
    
    God works in strange and mysterious ways... Dog Butt Looks Like Jesus Christ In A Robe http://twitpic.com/cx2age  via @TwitPic #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Learning how hard a #CRM campaign can be to produce. Thank goodness for JensHatch@jens937&CoreThomas @alohacorey. Wait to you see our ROI.    
    
    
    @dan_roam to put superman in today setting, did the have Clark Kent changing clothes in #Starbucks?    
    
    
    Is #ManOfSteal worth spending money to see?    
    
    
    Sometimes you have to look reality in the eye, and deny it. @GarrisonKeillor.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Gamers, my boy Brett Hull did this video on the top characters for #SuperSmashBrothers 4. Please retweet!! https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=qRCf-VNuZe8 …    
    
    
    Nothing like #surfing the summer away in #Ohio.    http://www.twitpic.com/cxsvpp  via #visualambassador    
    
    
    Welcome to the first day of summer with a song by @JordanHull.  Be sure to retweet and share the summer of love!!! http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sMMPe8SqzCI …    
    
    
    @Jordanhull Back at you my son!    
    
    
    ‏@michaelgass is a great resource. The Top List of Advertising Agency Networks for New Business http://dld.bz/Ck28     
    
    
    On billboard: "Ponderosa: Grilled in America" but it doesn't tell you what they're grilling came from America. @AndrewRocco    
    
    
    @michaelgass Alway enjoy your words of wisdom to the agency world.  So much so, find myself retweeting from time to time!!!!    
    
    
    @JordanHull’s “In the Summer” is jangly folk pop, with just enough sauciness to make it a must on any summerplaylist. http://todaysretro.wordpress.com/tag/jordan-hull/ …    
    
    
    What'd you think of #MadMen's season finale? Here's a story on the new #SterlingCooper&Partners logo, including... http://fb.me/Wfy3pB3h     
    
    
    It greaves me to share the news of David Lesh's passing from cancer on Friday. An amazing artist, thinker and friend. http://www.petoskeynews.com/news/obituaries/pnr-david-early-lesh-sr-20130624,0,1786820.story …    
    
    
    @hearsparkbox  You guys know how to party on a Friday.  Can't wait to see your new digges!!    
    
    
    #customerservice?; #AT&T, our phone and internet service is out Thursday.  We'll be there between today and July 1st by 8PM. COME ON AT&T!!    
    
    
    For those interested, a funeral Mass for #DavidLesh on Monday, July 8, @ 11:00 AM at IHM. Immediately following... http://fb.me/1jakrYLVn     
    
    
    Who's seen this label by @MikeyBurton in Smith Journal?  Sorry, Golden Axe can't be found in the USA yet. http://fb.me/21ixbijWs     
    
    
    #Art, what a crime by today's youth. At least that's what most schools and corporations think. #VisualAmbassador... http://fb.me/DJU4GkQm     
    
    
    What are some of the best mobile apps for graphic design? Answer on @klout #GraphicDesign http://www.klout.com/user/Scotthull/answer/what-are-some-of-the-best-mobile-apps-for-graphic-design?n=tw&v=first-person-experts-response-share&i=1128015 …    
    
    
    Our amazing fireworks thanks to @JordanHull. http://twitpic.com/d0v2im     
    
    
    You're doing a great job @BruceTurkel!  Enjoying your thoughts on branding with @FoxNews.    
    
    
    Shepard Fairey proves, is it copyright or copy right? OUCH! Your thoughts?... http://fb.me/2yHuaYPOZ     
    
    
    31 years ago today I took Ms. Kathy Jean as my bride. She's one amazing woman and my best friend. Thanks @jpmagg3 for introducing us.    
    
    
    Who watched the new @NBCCamp last night?  Your thoughts? Heard they're using some great music in one scene July 24th.  More later...    
    
    
    Our very own Von Glitschka @Vonster was taged to provide graphic exporation with Landor's client Gevalia. Thanks... http://fb.me/PBjPMCeE     
    
    
    Detoxing from a wedding weekend.  This is going to take a few days...    
    
    
    Can you find the hidden message in the new @Wendy's logo?  Let me give you a little help.... http://fb.me/2w7epSfeN     
    
    
    Once again @FuelLines gives us a little more insight.  This time 12 Ways to Get Personal Using Twitter http://ow.ly/n1K4h     
    
    
    And who says there's no value in art? @nytimes: Detroit’s Creditors Eye Its Art Collection http://nyti.ms/17rmkVQ     
    
    
    An interesting find at the record store today.  Anyone seen this ablum, #Dayton? http://twitpic.com/d3r85s     
    
    
    My buddy Lee found some information on album I found by the band #Dayton. Thanks Lee!!! http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dayton_(band) … #music #discofunk    
    
    
    This was one exciting day 25+ years ago.  @lindseydhull came into this world and has made it special for all.  Happy Birthday Princess!    
    
    
    On today is the day @lindseydhull was born into this world.  What a differance she is making!! Love you Princess!! #BirthdayGirl    
    
    
    Some happy brothers on @LindseydHull's wedding day!! http://twitpic.com/d3zxmh     
    
    
    A shout out about @JordanHull's song "In the Summer" @NBCcamp http://lockelandspringsteen.com/2013/07/23/features-jordan-hull-in-the-summer/ …    
    
    
    SLIP OFF YOUR SLACKS and slap on the sleaze, @JordanHull's lines from the track "In The Summer'. @NBCCamp will end with this song tonight!    
    
    
    If you like the music on @NBCCamp check out the closing song by @JordanHull, "In the Summer".    
    
    
    An evening with @SteveMartinToGo  and friends. It will be fun!!    
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo, why dont you come over for tea with the misses and me in #Dayton, #Ohio?    
    
    
    #Movie and #Video #Geeks; you must checkout this top 10 list movies that should be video games.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmTUyMX9Sdk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Heard this guy, @NickyFiddle play one mean fiddle at tonight's show with @SteveMartinToGo, @SteepCanyon & @ediebrickell .    
    
    
    Got to love the merch at concerts. SteveMartin knows how to turn it up a knoch. @Stevemartintogo #VisualAmbassador http://twitpic.com/d59zve     
    
    
    @Vonster it was a beautiful night for an outdoor show.  Steve Martin knows how to do a bluegrass show.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Our kids look at the world a little different which we love.  @JordanHull's concept, this is how we got pigs...  http://twitpic.com/d5k0t2     
    
    
    If you're into VIDEO GAMES and MOVIES, retweet this! Funny stuff!!  #geeks #videogames #movies http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmTUyMX9Sdk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Scott Hull Associates' just added Matt Houston to the group! Matt helps out on "Adventure Time" with charactors... http://fb.me/1FaSXgShD     
    
    
    As a creative, don't you love working with clock watching cube dewellers? #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Some days you can go crazy working with clock wathcing cube dewellers. #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Matt Houston captured one of my favorite quotes, "Always forward never straight". Thanks for sharing Pops quote... http://fb.me/FTdb5LAL     
    
    
    All businesses want is to improve Productivity, Profitablitiy and Peace of Mind. How does #IllustrativeDesign help?    
    
    
    Let's take artists out of the relm of technician and into the world of idea generator. #illustrativeDesign #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Todd Henry asked the question, "Where Do Great Ideas Come From?" (Hint: Not Where You Think)... http://fb.me/1AJ2EU6fY     
    
    
    @erinmharris thanks for sharing the tweet!    
    
    
        
    
    
    PLEASE SHARE Marketing driven or Market driven? The real question.... http://fb.me/2ipGuabX7     
    
    
    Share this #VideoGames #geeks ! you have to check out this  youtube on movies that should be Video Games. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmTUyMX9Sdk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Got to get me this #JohnHartford t-shirts. The cover of one of the best #bluegrass albums ever.  http://twitpic.com/d863i1     
    
    
    Think about it creatives. No one will every have your resume or ever will. You create your own life.  #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Creative people. One of the big lessons of staying young, KEEP CURIOUS!  #VisualAmbassador #creative #artist    
    
    
    HIistory made? @justinahrens shares the First TV Commercial Shown After JFK Assassination http://zite.to/1adjfNo  #JFK    
    
    
    One of those great evenings where your backyard feels like a resort.  Only thing missing is someone serving beaverages.    
    
    
    I'm finding being "busy" has taken on new meaning. It's the conservation of mental bandwidth http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/08/conservation-of-mental-bandwidth.html … #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Arlo our family Wookee. #starwars http://twitpic.com/d9a80h     
    
    
    Fun moment today having lunch and digital marketing converstation with @TheC3Group.    
    
    
    Such wisedom from #JohnHartford on the #banjo. http://twitpic.com/da2y7j     
    
    
    Retweet!! A review on #EarthwormJim. Good observation.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=KKzs45bF_v4 … #video #videogreek    
    
    
    @CameronWeim great to meet you Friday. You're with a very energetic team out to change the world @TheC3Group.    
    
    
    Would you agree; Great design = getting people to do what you want?... http://fb.me/KwjqVp11     
    
    
    I like what @toddhenry shares, like this one - 12 things we know about how the brain works - http://buff.ly/17grJP6     
    
    
    RETWEET! #VideoGames lovers, check out this review on Starfox 64. Like this guys take on video games. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VLaB6fAHXu8 … #Starfox64    
    
    
    Von Glitschka aka.@vonster is a man of many talents. Check out his fabric design. So glad I work with such great... http://fb.me/3j7sPdwjY     
    
    
    HEY, @altpick selected Andrea Eberbach as today's featured artist!!! Go check out the beautiful work.... http://fb.me/EEkWaEwY     
    
    
    #Beatle fans, Hear the Isolated Vocal Tracks for The Beatles’ Climactic 16-Minute Medley on Abbey Road.  Amazing http://www.openculture.com/2013/09/hear-the-lush-isolated-vocal-tracks-for-the-beatles-climactic-side-two-medley-on-abbey-road.html …    
    
    
    RETWEET Alternative Pick has us zeroed in! We just update Lorraine Tuson samples a few minutes ago and here you... http://fb.me/2zPlkzeej     
    
    
    All this talk about #Syria! Mr. Horse comments on the current world situation. https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=dQ3acvz5LfI …    
    
    
    So nice to have @AltPick close the week out with a focus on Andrea Eberbach!!  http://altpick.com/news/7941 ... http://fb.me/1RBdUHLwZ     
    
    
    MUST READ! Steve Jobs's 10 Best Quotes for Advertising Agencies. Thanks @michaelgass for sharing  http://dld.bz/aneE7     
    
    
    Oberservation to success. The secret for today's promotion&marketing.... http://fb.me/1F2DYFiel     
    
    
    Branding is like puberty, your voice might change.  #VisualAmbassador #Branding    
    
    
    Our buddies at Golden Axe Cider tapped @MikeyBurton to give their first beer a look. Monster Mash double IPA! http://fb.me/6uoZkMnOL     
    
    
    Making a differance. Touching tribute to DavidLesh from Brad Holland and the Illustrators' Partnership.... http://fb.me/6ifafdu34     
    
    
    WHAT?? The @ClevelandBrowns win!!! There is a god...    
    
    
    8 calls hearing,"We want the hightest customer service as possible" & going to 3 locations. @PenskeCares, Your service bar must be low.    
    
    
    @PenskeCares REALLY?!! Finest Serice Possible. With a reservation, 31/2 hrs of calls plus 3 NashvilleHomeDepots. Is that be best you can do?    
    
    
    Anyone ever lease a @Penske truck in Nashville? Poor HomeDepot rental people. Confirmed rental, On arrival sent to 3 stores. @PenskeCares??    
    
    
    Greetings @PenskeCares is there a place  where I can forward my info so you can look into my Penkse experience on Saturday?    
    
    
    @PenskeCares as you requested, I sent you my contact information and confer number through http://pensketruckrental.com .    
    
    
    Gee, I was put on hold 5 times for 25 minutes+ & disconnected twice on Saturday. Now @PenskeCares responses once I tweet.  Tweet sucess.    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/181cEyi4Z     
    
    
    In my years as pursuer of all things creative, one big leason "Money Flows to Vision."   #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Check out what people are saying about #MonsterMashBeer.  The label was designed by @MikeyBurton... http://fb.me/KTWnrM3o     
    
    
    My art teacher daughter explained a line to me, "It's a dot that went on a walk." Now we know where lines come from. #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    @marmaladebleue @mikeyburton Good thing for you, #monstermashbeer is only sold in Australia.  Cheers!!!    
    
    
    Great post by Landor Associates,Dale Doyle on brand&packaging.  Heck, art for Sour Patch Kids by Michael Bast... http://fb.me/1voNwFpIO     
    
    
    Got a call from a gov client saying "they can't pay the bill until they have the funds" OK, I'm not paying taxes while the gov is shutdown    
    
    
        
    
    
    Which Halloween costume will you see the most of this year? Zombies- Princesses-Superheroes-Duck Dynasty-Vampires-  write in your vote.    
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo Hey Steve, enjoyed your show at the Fraze this summer!! Which guy was you?    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm not saying I'm Batman. I'm just saying no one has ever seen me and Batman in a room together. http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234351/ …    
    
    
    start with a magazine or newspaper clipping and let the child expand the picture http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234359/ …    
    
    
    this would be killer coming out of a veggie dip bowl (this is ridiculous! lol) http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234364/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    How art can make thing look appealing Illustrator: Ryo Takemasa http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234427/ …    
    
    
    ManyThanks http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234463/ …    
    
    
    Out of print clothing with Mikey Burton http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976234469/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PatriceHall Thanks for the retweet!  What do you want from a fortune cookie???    
    
    
    What are the best web sites to reach creative art directors and buyers of illustration?  #illustration #promotion #PR    
    
    
    Why use photography for a food project? Lorraine Tuson's art can give food flavor. #Foodart #packaging http://twitpic.com/dgpnc0     
    
    
        
    
    
    @SethGodin really hits it about pricing creative services. As @MikeyBurton says, "Freelance Ain't Free".... http://fb.me/37rUb2lRZ     
    
    
    Picked up a power cord for my #iPhone.  Getting in the car my son sees the package and says, "Oh, Apple Juice".    
    
    
    Art by John Maggard: Who could forget the @Jane Smith logo for the King Cobra http:http://www.scotthull.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976255657/ …    
    
    
    #OhioState College Mascots; @BrutusBuckeye through the years. Someone wasn't thinking branding. http://shar.es/E79c3  via @sharethis    
    
    
    What a day for the Sauerkraut Festival!! Can't wait for the sauerkraut ice cream! http://www.sauerkrautfestival.com  @SauerkrautFest    
    
    
    Follow me on @twitter or do something with your life...    
    
    
    Ran across a talk I did, "Discussing the "F" word". This is one point I tend to forget: "FEAR IS A LIAR." http://twitpic.com/dh7hng     
    
    
    Off to get my head filled with social goodness. http://www.summitup.org  #SummitUp #VisualAmbassador @davidebowman    
    
    
    Time doesn't exist until we invent it. Now there's a thought. Read on http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/10/time-doesnt-exist.html …    
    
    
    Session one #SummitUp complete.  @ToddHenry supported the fact illustrative design folks must first know their productive passion.    
    
    
    Interesting to hear human behavior relating to product developement from @eadaul. "The Why" #SummitUp    
    
    
    Original Art Works!!! Great Session #SummitUp: A Picture is Worth 1000 Words http://bootcampdigital.com/live-blog-from-summitup-a-picture-is-worth-1000-words/#sthash.y7y1rbne.uxfs … via #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
        
    
    
    I have to say, @KristaNeher's #SummitUp presentation had a LOT of good material when it comes to the value of visuals in your social media.    
    
    
    Has it come down to copyright or copy right? Read on.... http://fb.me/2sKquCGFS     
    
    
    It's always good to see your smiling face @KendraRamirez.  You add so much to #SummitUP!!    
    
    
    @wallingphoto @toddhenry @susanpkm317 Well there I am!  Julie is everywhere with her camera.  An event isn't an event without Julie!    
    
    
    The future is leaving. No time for mediocrity. #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    the truth about life.  #VisualAmbassador http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976288561/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    It feels good when you walk into a Panera Bread and see art from Scott Hull Associates' Lorraine Tuson!!! http://fb.me/36rrsB6H6     
    
    
    Folks, there ain't no left-side/right-side thinking... just one, beautifully creative brain.... http://fb.me/3wOpMKBn0     
    
    
    What I try to live by. "Be so good they can’t ignore you" – Steve Martin   @SteveMartinToGo #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Tick or Treat, Lisa Ballard gave @AirheadsCandy a little Halloween treat in packaging. #packaging #Halloween... http://fb.me/2V2k1LzdK     
    
    
    Which costumes top the list this #Halloween?  Mark Riedy  helps you with the break down. Do you agree??? @riedym... http://fb.me/2sydN4Bwp     
    
    
    Who's going as Miley Cyrus on "Twerk or Treater"?  RETWEET THIS!! #VisualAmbassador @MileyCyrus #Halloween @AIGA http://fb.me/2PiovpvZA     
    
    
    About every morning I find Arlo doing his yoga. He's so dedicated. #yoga #pets http://twitpic.com/djqu4j     
    
    
    NO,NO,NO!!!! What does "no" mean.  http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/11/what-no-means.html …    
    
    
    The worst client comments turned into posters.... http://fb.me/6tfIypr9B     
    
    
    Is illustration dead? Well, if the horse is dead, dismount.  #VisualAmbassador @ICONconference #illustration #illustrator    
    
    
    Retweet! Brett Hull's latest short, #HoleInMe #Isolation.  https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4JhhWJTras … @FilmDayton #depression #filmmaking #screenwriting #film    
    
    
    Hey @ChicagoBears Fans!!! "I love Brian Piccolo" What a find today. @DaBears #brianpiccolo #brian'sstory  http://twitpic.com/dkobk2     
    
    
    Thinking of a number between 1 and 10.  Just FYI… #FYI #visualthinking    
    
    
    Have you seen this mural in Panera Bread by Lorraine Tuson? If so, Retween or Comment.  @PaneraBread... http://fb.me/16Fw2WyCO     
    
    
    #Snowwhite is tweaking?  Really #Disney???  #VisualAmbassador http://twitpic.com/dl1x7m     
    
    
    Record $142.4M For Francis Bacon Art; Warhol Fetches $57.3M. Today's Illustrator $3K. http://n.pr/1bD9VQg     
    
    
    Has technology cheapened good creative?  #AIGA @aigacincinnati @ICONconference @Behance    
    
    
    Have you seen this mural in Panera Breads by Curtis Parker? If so, Retween or Comment. @PaneraBread #visualambassador http://fb.me/12pp8O6tl     
    
    
    Can someone suggest a good wireless or plug-in headset for #iphone4s ?  It would be great if I could use it for Skype calls as well.    
    
    
    Please RETWEET! Film kid, @BrettHull101's latest short, https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4JhhWJTras … #artnoir #eddiemuller #GuyMaddin    
    
    
        
    
    
    If this isn't a #BrainSnack. Minimalist lines posters by Michal Krasnopolski.... http://fb.me/28eTbPYIN     
    
    
        
    
    
    This is to all my creative left handed friends.  Your life must be hell!... http://fb.me/2vwNEBnzk     
    
    
    Got to get one. @FastCoDesign shares the ultimate calendar for running a business. http://f-st.co/yg4BwLJ  pic.twitter.com/gvNbWXNwaL    
    
    
    #Starwars, now @WillFerrell’s #Anchorman2 Is Changing the Way Movies Are Marketed. http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/will-ferrell-s-anchorman-2-changing-way-movies-are-marketed-154076Will … #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lisa Ballard can make circles and logs look so cool.  #VisualAmbassador http://fb.me/2WFbCAOm1     
    
    
    @marmaladebleue @mikeyburton @AllanPeters  Touched by Danielle's post!  I was put on this earth to help people make their dreams come true.    
    
    
    While at the grocery today, check for the secret message hidden in the bananas.    
    
    
        
    
    
    #Thanksgiving Day: Preparing for the big dinner.  Did the 7 hour sleep diet and worked great.  Will power held beautifully.    
    
    
    #Thanksgiving Day: Before big dinner, next 5 minute shower diet, followed by 30 second tooth brushing diet.  Book says these really work.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanksgiving Day: Almost time for dinner.  Going on twenty minute starvation diet before dinner.    
    
    
    Thanksgiving Day: Satisfied with today's dieting.  Going to dinner now.    
    
    
    Why go out #BlackFriday? When you can ship your pants. Even @Kmart will ship your pants. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I03UmJbK0lA …    
    
    
    Weight fluctuating wildly because of all those photos of Thanksgiving dinner you're posting. Back to twice a day 20 minute starvation diet.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanksgiving done, let the decorating of #Christmas begin. Do you agree with these "Festive Finds"? http://twitpic.com/dn76hn     
    
    
    @Midas said I needed a new altenator. $400+ & 4days later I find myself stuck on the highway with a dead battery & bad alternator. Not Happy    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great presentation today! @blairenns with guest @michaelgass 30 Posts in 30 Days. Learned so much! Well worth it. http://bit.ly/15DmWZV     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Trying to get my new title to catch on: Visual Ambassador. Art Pimp was taken. #VisualThinking #VisualAmbassador... http://fb.me/15mcfX3Q9     
    
    
    Twitter sing along!! I’ll sing the first line, and you’ll sing the last few words. DECK THE HALLS WITH …?   #CHRISTMASSONGS #Deckthehalls    
    
    
    Keith Richards' 70th birthday today, so @Tremendo_us made him a song! Presenting "The 12 days of Keefmas!"... http://fb.me/3y6HQ9Gbs     
    
    
    That’s right, you sing the last few words.
“Deck the halls with Salvador Dali!”   
Fa la la la la la, la la la la
‘Tis the season to be…?    
    
    
    Now this is real estate Christmas marketing. Got to love the creativity. #marketing #realtor #realestate http://twitpic.com/dphwnc     
    
    
    SHARE THIS! Ran across this informative radio show about "Its A Wonderful Life" (1946) - https://itun.es/i6FN5WG  #iTunes #itsawonderfullice    
    
    
    ITS A WONDERFULLIFE,George&Mary dancing the Charleston when the gym floor parts. Who played dirty pool? LittleRascals Carl "Alfalfa" Switzer    
    
    
    Interesting comments by @BruceTurkel, brand guy on #DuckDynasty with @JudgeJeanine @FoxBusiness http://youtu.be/VWyywDlR3F4  #branding    
    
    
    So fun to see how others use there "#visualvoice" for the Christmas. Thanks for sharing Curtis Parker.... http://fb.me/2JaBnE9YV     
    
    
    Creating the Beautiful Star poster, for Curtis Parker all starts with a pencil&paper.... http://fb.me/2KZuzjkzX     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Christmas isn't Christmas without @PeeweeHerman's Christmas Special. http://www.happyholidayspeewee.com     
    
    
    The 10 Worst Corporate Logo Changes Of 2013. Do you agree? http://www.businessinsider.com/10-worst-corporate-logo-changes-2013-2013-12 … via @BI_Advertising #graphicdesign #logos    
    
    
    The perfect stocking stuffer… http://twitpic.com/dpzqat     
    
    
        
    
    
    My goal for 2014, Don't work hard, work intelligent.  Problem is, more ideas keep coming to me. #Vis http://pinterest.com/pin/220535712976610603/ …    
    
    
    Thinking about getting a computer.  I’ll need to get electricity in the house first. @applenws @APPLEOFFIClAL    
    
    
    I wonder, if a turtle loses its shell is it naked or homeless?  #Creativity #VisualAmbassador    
    
    
    Interview with #BillyCorgan. "The future of rock is God. #Christians need to make better music & stop copying #U2.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ybOkLFrXtZc …    
    
    
    @deandrepurdie @typekit DeAndre, Thanks for the credit in your blog!    
    
    
        
    
    
    6 Strategies That Work Better Than Trying To Predict The Future. Good stuff for innovators. http://thestoryoftelling.com/trying-to-predict-future/ … via @bernadettejiwa    
    
    
    @bernadettejiwa I've been enjoying your blog.    
    
    
    GREAT KICK OFF! CA Type Annual has tapped Mikey Burton's art from Esquire as a winner.... http://fb.me/Suzb5FXl     
    
    
    Great chart that gives #CatLovers knowledge of a cat's body language. Now that's value of the Visual Voice.... http://fb.me/3FfaA3MY1     
    
    
    WOW, just realized 2 of our illustrative designers, @Vonster & @marmaladebleue, are speaking at @CreativeSouthGA. Check your Apirl schedule    
    
    
    Didn't realize the USA could have been 124 territories instead of 50 states.  Intersting blog and graphic. http://andrewshears.com/2011/12/08/the-united-states-that-couldve-been/ …    
    
    
    