Letters from 500 "Portal" http://wp.me/pI226-qP    
    
    
    Letters from 500 “Portal”: It is with great joy that I announce the availability of Book 2… http://goo.gl/fb/29CVl    
    
    
    ...more Letter Twenty-One "Exploration": http://wp.me/pI226-bn    
    
    
    …more Letter Twenty-One “Exploration”: “I want to go back to something that’s been bothering… http://goo.gl/fb/8X3n    
    
    
    Letter Twenty "Appreciation": http://wp.me/pI226-bx    
    
    
    Letter Twenty “Appreciation”: “Why can’t the ego just evolve or wake itself up to the greater… http://goo.gl/fb/lKdM    
    
    
    New Book, New Blog, New Beginnings... http://wp.me/pI226-qZ     
    
    
    New Book, New Blog, New Beginnings…: With today being the full moon and the lunacy that… http://goo.gl/fb/JdbgF     
    
    
    The Good News Segment: http://wp.me/pI226-bI    
    
    
    The Good News Segment: Do you ever think about how brainwashed we are with the constant din of… http://goo.gl/fb/6Pkr    
    
    
    Barbara Marx Hubbard and Conscious Evolution: http://wp.me/pI226-ce    
    
    
    Barbara Marx Hubbard and Conscious Evolution: It is always wonderful to find people who are… http://goo.gl/fb/FPg9    
    
    
    There is an ocean of silence waiting for us that transcends the state of normal life. It sits within our reach. Waiting to caress us.    
    
    
    This is the End My Friend http://wp.me/pI226-rr     
    
    
    This is the End My Friend: Are we in the throws of death? Looking down upon us the gods can… http://goo.gl/fb/TCQRm     
    
    
    Letter Eight "The End": http://wp.me/pI226-cq    
    
    
    Letter Eight “The End”: As we move ahead into the light of transformation we ask ourselves how… http://goo.gl/fb/XUXb    
    
    
    As we move ahead into the light of transformation we ask ourselves how this change of species will take place.    
    
    
    Will Conscious Evolution first rid the planet of this confused humanity and start again?    
    
    
    Perhaps other dimensional beings will seed this place as we have been told happened in our past.    
    
    
    I think that we are the true pioneers of this journey and our conscious awareness will make this transition a most beautiful experience.    
    
    
    Imagine waking up, out of the illusion created by our egos, into a new attunement to life.    
    
    
    Imagine changing the distorted vision that we see as living, by dissolving the residue of ego that covers our minds lenses.    
    
    
    We have been laughed at in the past when we dared to imagine a world so ideal, so utopian, that the concept of conflict no longer exists.    
    
    
    And now, the laughing has died down.    
    
    
    The vision has moved out of the dream and into the streets. We are conscious enough today to make it a reality.    
    
    
    The Art of Listening: http://wp.me/pI226-cC    
    
    
    The Art of Listening: One element, so crucial in human development and missing in modern day… http://goo.gl/fb/5zrc    
    
    
    The Road to Prosperity is Paved with Good Intendings: http://wp.me/pI226-dp    
    
    
    The Road to Prosperity is Paved with Good Intendings: Most of us have heard of “The Secret… http://goo.gl/fb/Lsy8    
    
    
    Earthquake: A force beyond our control that hands our egos a sense of vulnerability. A humbler beyond compare to anything else in life.    
    
    
    Letter Sixteen "Morality, Sex and Relationships": http://wp.me/pI226-eI    
    
    
    Letter Sixteen “Morality, Sex and Relationships”: I’ve always been curious about the rules we… http://goo.gl/fb/ELvn    
    
    
    I’ve always been curious about the rules we’ve made up to guide us along the way.    
    
    
    I know we believe they came from God, through a couple of tablets carved out on a mountain.    
    
    
    Or maybe from information told to disciples and then, second handed,    
    
    
    passed on to the scribes who were less than interested and just wanted to get paid for their work.    
    
    
    Did any one proof read the scribes? Since most of the purveyors of the message couldn’t read or write themselves, who checked?    
    
    
    Have you ever played that telephone game when you were younger    
    
    
    where you tell the next person in line something and by the time it gets to the twelfth person it doesn’t sound anything the same?    
    
    
    Is that what happened to the rules we thought came from our God?...
http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    Hurricane Irene. My grandmother was named Irene. She was a sweet woman with fierce determination and gusts of up to 100 MPH    
    
    
    Book Two - The Final Chapters: http://wp.me/pI226-me    
    
    
    Book Two – The Final Chapters: I have received from Robert the final chapters of Book Two… http://goo.gl/fb/H1QrU    
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty "The Void and Formlessness" http://wp.me/pI226-rE     
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty “The Void and Formlessness”: With the onslaught of election… http://goo.gl/fb/E5ZR1     
    
    
    Letter Fifteen "Governance": http://wp.me/pI226-eT    
    
    
    Letter Fifteen “Governance”: Now that we have ended the first stage of ego’s individuated… http://goo.gl/fb/URlf    
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-One "Resonance, the Key" http://wp.me/pI226-rJ     
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-One “Resonance, the Key”: I find need to write again, so soon… http://goo.gl/fb/4eCXh     
    
    
    my human self and My God Self: http://wp.me/pI226-eZ    
    
    
    my human self and My God Self: On my travels Wednesday, from California to New Jersey, I was… http://goo.gl/fb/Yty3    
    
    
    God has created, for its own desire, the realm of separation from itself through its divine creation homo sapien.    
    
    
    And as each of us walks through this life of unknowing,    
    
    
    it is that experience that God has desired to have in order to rediscover itself through awakened humankind.    
    
    
    It's a game that God is playing with itself through us.    
    
    
    This is what makes each one of us so important in the cosmic game.    
    
    
    Each one of us is a singularity of God's Oneness state.    
    
    
    And each singularity is as important as the next.    
    
    
    Should any of the singularities go missing or become corrupted God could no longer be One within itself.    
    
    
    It is this factor that make each singularity priceless. For without one of us God could no longer exist.    
    
    
    my human self and MY GOD SELF: http://wp.me/pI226-f6    
    
    
    my human self and MY GOD SELF: On my travels Wednesday, from California to New Jersey, I was… http://goo.gl/fb/P9o5    
    
    
    what is wrong here?: http://wp.me/pI226-fb    
    
    
    what is wrong here?: what is wrong here? anxious men and women running mindless through the… http://goo.gl/fb/xuOs    
    
    
    Joseph Campbell quote:: “We must let go of the life we have planned, so as to accept the one… http://goo.gl/fb/y5v9    
    
    
    Letter Nineteen "Jerusalem": http://wp.me/pI226-fp    
    
    
    Letter Nineteen “Jerusalem”: With Easter and Passover upon us I thought a look at the future… http://goo.gl/fb/bYU5    
    
    
    Anniversary of Disbelief http://wp.me/pI226-rV     
    
    
    Anniversary of Disbelief: To all of those who were lost and the families that grieve we share… http://goo.gl/fb/zFJgE     
    
    
    With Easter and Passover upon us I thought a look at the future,    
    
    
    in the most turbulent place on the planet, would be appropriate.    
    
    
    There is no greater ego clash than this holy city of diversity.    
    
    
    Where Source has planted the seeds of faith the trees have grown in restless confusion.    
    
    
        
    
    
    and the catalyst for our genetic mutation. How do we reconcile our differences and move ahead in Peace?    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com  Letter Nineteen "Jerusalem"    
    
    
    Letter Ten "To the Test": http://wp.me/pI226-ft    
    
    
    Letter Ten “To the Test”: I had an interesting experience this past Sunday in the line of… http://goo.gl/fb/S1Fu2    
    
    
    Currently Browsing: http://is.gd/b8dHE    
    
    
    I had an interesting experience this past Sunday in the line of fear and the ability to overcome it.    
    
    
    I was attending a funeral of a dear friend’s nephew and on the way was taken by the fear of approaching the open casket.    
    
    
    I really don’t like to view a person after Spirit has left the body.    
    
    
    As silly as it sounds I shudder every time I have to participate in a viewing.    
    
    
    The energy in the room is usually filled with such tremendous sadness and my auric field absorbs it and rattles my emotional senses.    
    
    
    I had intended to go into the funeral parlor and find my way to a seat in the rear.    
    
    
    Upon entering I realized that the only access to the room was from the front    
    
    
    and in order to get in you first had to get in line to approach the casket and pay condolences to the bereaved.    
    
    
    As I stood there trying to be cool and collected I found my gaze turning toward the coffin.    
    
    
    It was an eerie feeling, a kind of tug of war, because my inner being wanted to overcome this fear and my mind was playing into it.    
    
    
    As I gazed at the lifeless form I started to relax. I did not resist the fear, I just started to notice it    
    
    
    and it’s effect over me and as I allowed it to be it became less of a problem. It did,    
    
    
    in fact, become a kind of meditation.    
    
    
    As my consciousness started to elevate I began to notice a ball of energy moving over the body.    
    
    
    It seemed to be playing, bouncing back and forth.    
    
    
    I then noticed, as people approached the body , the ball started to draw off of there auric energy.    
    
    
    I could see streams of white light being pulled up to the ball like dancing fingers.    
    
    
    What an amazing experience. I began my day with worry and fear and ended in a state of calm and exultation.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    A Passing Thought: http://wp.me/pI226-fx    
    
    
    A Passing Thought: It is with gratitude that I offer blessings to all in this week of… http://goo.gl/fb/jFV8C    
    
    
    Change is Coming Like a Speeding Train: http://wp.me/pI226-fA    
    
    
    Change is Coming Like a Speeding Train: Earthquakes shaking the planet. One, then another… http://goo.gl/fb/ojYk7    
    
    
    Earthquakes shaking the planet. One, then another, and another, and again another.    
    
    
    Purely coincidence or a timely cosmic occurrence?    
    
    
    Common man rising up against the elite. Purely a rash of bad behavior or an inner cry for transformation?    
    
    
    A President aligning with others for nuclear non-proliferation.    
    
    
    Purely an ego’s bold play for a place in history or a wise man’s desire for peace and tranquility?    
    
    
    A staunch opponent of progressive ideology pleading for us to listen to the facts instead of the fiction.    
    
    
    Purely an insane right winger or a sane thinker who has had enough?    
    
    
    These are the signs of change. A change so deep in our core that we’ve yet to notice.    
    
    
    But as the Great Storm plunders all around us the buds of spring are bursting through the soil.    
    
    
    Be still and you can feel it. Listen and you can hear it. Open up and you will see it. Hallelujah!    
    
    
    more from Letter Twenty "Appreciation": http://wp.me/pI226-fD    
    
    
    more from Letter Twenty “Appreciation”: I keep coming back to Letter Twenty “Appreciation… http://goo.gl/fb/gh9iX    
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-Six "Body" http://wp.me/pI226-s6     
    
    
    Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of change.    
    
    
    I present to you bodies, standing aimlessly before the masses, selling outmoded solutions against the mighty wave of dissolution.    
    
    
    As we near the vortex of  transformation we are confused; and unenlightened minds,    
    
    
    with their need to hold on to ego’s door, cannot find the way through this morass.    
    
    
    WE ARE STUCK, WE NEED HELP, the cry bellows forth. And yet, those who acccept the new winds of change can move so easily up and about.    
    
    
    For we are neither stuck nor in the need of help. We have put on our headsets,    
    
    
    turned up the hemi-sync and floated to a space and time that reads nothing but the truth.    
    
    
    The Portal that is open between worlds has always been there, just to be found.    
    
    
    It lies within the mind of awareness and the heart of understanding. It is felt so deeply that we need not move through it,    
    
    
    from one side to the next, because we are always in its midst. It is so a part of us that feeling it is all we need to being there.    
    
    
    It is not a walkway, just a way. It casts no shadow for the light is all around it.    
    
    
    It is the profound light of knowing that draws all else into its embrace.    
    
    
    Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of change. I present to… http://goo.gl/fb/fGKR8     
    
    
    Letters from 500
Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of change. I present to you... http://fb.me/1mQrj5qH3     
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-Six "Body"
Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of... http://fb.me/1ijRmAinp     
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-Six "Body"
Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of... http://fb.me/Ub1vBh0Z     
    
    
    excerpt from Letter Thirty-Six "Body"
Over and over it clangs. The noise of “Redundancy” within the voices of... http://fb.me/17429l96V     
    
    
    Letter Thirty-Six "Body" (part two) http://wp.me/pI226-si     
    
    
    Letter Thirty-Six “Body” (part two): When I posted this final segment of Letter Thirty-Six… http://goo.gl/fb/5iC0e     
    
    
    Author's Thoughts: http://wp.me/pI226-fP    
    
    
    Author’s Thoughts: Stefan (AKA Cosmic Observer) has asked me to write something here. I don’t… http://goo.gl/fb/aLFLU    
    
    
    Steve Jobs 1955 - 2011 http://wp.me/pI226-sH     
    
    
    Steve Jobs 1955 – 2011: Thank you for your life and your innovations. The world would not be… http://goo.gl/fb/NGB3i     
    
    
    What About Animals?: http://wp.me/pI226-gc    
    
    
    What About Animals?: A friend from Monroe, who’s reading the book, asked me the following… http://goo.gl/fb/QHQKQ    
    
    
    "Letters" at Amazon and Barnes&Noble .com: http://wp.me/pI226-gu    
    
    
    “Letters” at Amazon and Barnes&Noble .com: As of today, the latest addition of Letters from… http://goo.gl/fb/DRGcT    
    
    
    Enough of this Mass Debate http://wp.me/pI226-u0     
    
    
    Enough of this Mass Debate: It is evident, from the remarks made recently on the Republican… http://goo.gl/fb/covMZ     
    
    
    It is evident, from the remarks made recently on the Republican debate scene,    
    
    
    that we are dealing with candidates that are more ill-equipped to lead this nation than ever before.    
    
    
    We are, in fact, babies in the realm of evolution and we can expect no better than we give right now.    
    
    
    As we approach this end of cycle and herald the Mayan Calendar completion, we can see a future filled with dramatic change.    
    
    
    Fortunately we have absolutely no control over what will happen next on this earth,    
    
    
    because if we did there would be no earth left to inhabit. Our destiny is in the hands of a greater force, Conscious Evolution.    
    
    
    The clue to this transformation is the presence of a champion for rational and common ground discourse.    
    
    
    Of course Barack Obama is so demonized right now that no one, except his most ardent supporters, would recognize it.    
    
    
    Here is a man who truly believed in change and came into office with such confidence in his vision that all that was needed was cooperation    
    
    
    An advanced species, unlike ourselves, would see these possibilities and jump on the opportunity to bring them to fruition.    
    
    
    We, as a whole, lack the vision needed to make this succeed.    
    
    
    Let's face it, we are selfish and greedy and could care less about the common good and only of the good of ourself.    
    
    
    We see it every day in our biases, our racism, our self-proclaimed nationalism and our ability to kill any or all life at the drop of a hat.    
    
    
    And so the light workers who inhabit this planet are trying over and over again to instill the message of growth and transformation.    
    
    
    Is there anyone listening? A few perhaps. I know there are some who subscribe to this blog that hear the message loud and clear.    
    
    
    I can tell by their comments that this blog is not just shouting in the wind.    
    
    
    This call for sanity and civility and understanding is making ground among the awakened souls.    
    
    
    And there are more every day, as is evident in the responses we've had for our first group dialogue/seminar    
    
    
    being held at a private home in North Carolina in early November.    
    
    
    Thanks to a small group of resonators there is now a grand spark of conversation at the University of North Carolina Asheville    
    
    
    and a professor at the university has donated funds to purchase "Letters" for members of the book club. This is a beginning.    
    
    
    Now I ask that we lend our support to our fellow activists and send waves of positive energy their way.    
    
    
    This is inner activism and can have an amazing effect on the physical world.    
    
    
    Meditate deeply and move your hearts to resonate loudly.    
    
    
    Imagine this waveform moving among the crowd and lighting up their inner beings. There can be no doubt that this will be a win/win for all.    
    
    
    "The Grace of Freedom" an excerpt from Letter Thirty-Seven http://wp.me/pI226-ub     
    
    
    “The Grace of Freedom” an excerpt from Letter Thirty-Seven: It was brought to my attention… http://goo.gl/fb/rXtQq     
    
    
    Seeking Oneness in Competition http://wp.me/pI226-uC     
    
    
    What About Animals http://wp.me/pI226-uG     
    
    
    The Road to Prosperity is Paved with Good Intendings http://wp.me/pI226-uU     
    
    
    The Bankers Go Bonkers : http://wp.me/pI226-gR    
    
    
    The Bankers Go Bonkers: The Great Storm mentioned in Letters is a culmination of many ego… http://goo.gl/fb/Sk3nl    
    
    
    And the Love Keeps Growing...: http://wp.me/pI226-lX    
    
    
    And the Love Keeps Growing…: I would like to pass on to you portions of an email Robert and I… http://goo.gl/fb/EQf8n    
    
    
    The Winds of Change: http://wp.me/pI226-mb    
    
    
    The Winds of Change: As the winds of change keep blowing steadily along, the gusts have… http://goo.gl/fb/SV6Iv    
    
    
    "Governance" Letter Fifteen - It is happening before our very eyes - part one http://wp.me/pI226-v1     
    
    
    “Governance” Letter Fifteen – It is happening before our very eyes – part one: It is so… http://goo.gl/fb/TbhEP     
    
    
    ...more from Letter Sixteen "Morality, Sex and Relationships": http://wp.me/pI226-gW    
    
    
    …more from Letter Sixteen “Morality, Sex and Relationships”: How do we surrender to our… http://goo.gl/fb/jkGLA    
    
    
    Competition: O points out that the Latin root for ‘competition’ is com + peter, meaning ‘seek… http://goo.gl/fb/9QMgy    
    
    
    "Governance" Letter Fifteen - part two http://wp.me/pI226-va     
    
    
    “Governance” Letter Fifteen – part two: Can we possibly come to terms with each other and… http://goo.gl/fb/XtvNr     
    
    
    A Sister’s Eulogy for Steve Jobs: http://nyti.ms/u78bKG     
    
    
    A Sister’s Eulogy for Steve Jobs http://wp.me/pI226-vd     
    
    
    A Sister’s Eulogy for Steve Jobs: Robert sent me this article yesterday and I find need to… http://goo.gl/fb/7sNpX     
    
    
    Before I Leave, A Farewell : http://wp.me/pI226-i6    
    
    
    Before I Leave, A Farewell: As we are about to depart for the East Coast, I am sitting by the… http://goo.gl/fb/PcoTY    
    
    
    I am sitting in a realm of nowhere able to leap tall beliefs in a single bound.    
    
    
    I writhe like petty waters that fear the ocean is too big to swallow,    
    
    
    In the midst of the agony of life I come to some terms regarding my existence.    
    
    
    There is truth in the epicenter of my gut and the motion sets me reeling.    
    
    
    Where do I go after this and by the way what is this to go from?    
    
    
    Many of the  orderly things that penetrate the daily workings of the mind are silent.    
    
    
    I move ahead hoping to glance upon the realness that is my ever abounding life.    
    
    
    I am wasting precious time.    
    
    
    Who calls me from deep below and whispers hopes and dreams into my imagination?    
    
    
    Who corners me when I feel naught and soothes my angst with a balm of forgetfulness?    
    
    
    I am the monster in the mirror that created the story in the first place.    
    
    
    I am the source of all the ramblings my imagination can hold to.    
    
    
    “Twas brillig and the slithy toves” I murmured in a instant, with out the thought of why or how I get to these strange out landings.    
    
    
    For I am the truth untold and all the realm is mine to behold.    
    
    
    I fathom and I express, I stutter and then I manifest.    
    
    
    The way is my way and no other.    
    
    
    Where I travel next makes… no never mind.    
    
    
    It is only the absence of thought that thinks that I am not.    
    
    
    For eons I shall dwell on nothing that is current and time shall have no play in this being.    
    
    
    For I am the fly on the wall in this show.    
    
    
    Ecoluxe Mag and Potter: http://wp.me/pI226-mi    
    
    
    Ecoluxe Mag and Potter: In the latest issue of Ecoluxe Magazine editor Shannon Dunn has down… http://goo.gl/fb/V8lZJ    
    
    
    Letter Fourteen "Sides of Oneness" the summary: http://wp.me/pI226-ic    
    
    
    Letter Fourteen “Sides of Oneness” the summary: Where is God? Is he up in the sky, sitting on… http://goo.gl/fb/hIbrk    
    
    
    Our First Community Gathering http://wp.me/pI226-vj     
    
    
    Our First Community Gathering: Over this weekend, on Sunday the 6th to be exact, we had our… http://goo.gl/fb/FVxOv     
    
    
    The Next Generation is the Key to Our Future http://wp.me/pI226-vz     
    
    
    The Next Generation is the Key to Our Future: One week has passed since our beautiful… http://goo.gl/fb/4bzO7     
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four "Homo Angelicus": http://wp.me/pI226-ii    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: Now it is time to open up the imagination a bit more… http://goo.gl/fb/dp5nE    
    
    
    Free from Fear http://wp.me/pI226-vE     
    
    
    Free from Fear: From time to time Robert sends me other thoughts that have made their way… http://goo.gl/fb/grVEv     
    
    
    ...more from Letter Twenty-Four "Homo Angelicus": http://wp.me/pI226-in    
    
    
    …more from Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: If you resonated with the last post on Homo… http://goo.gl/fb/9Sa8Y    
    
    
    ...continuing Letter Twenty-four "Homo Angelicus": http://wp.me/pI226-ir    
    
    
    …continuing Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: [I ask.] “How will your death be any… http://goo.gl/fb/67XnF    
    
    
    A Nod to Psyched in Stilettos http://wp.me/pI226-vV     
    
    
    A Nod to Psyched in Stilettos: Every Sunday I wake to the latest newsletter from our dear… http://goo.gl/fb/PMohL     
    
    
    Reading David Wilcock's "The Source Field Investigations." Something stirring here that enlivens the soul. A must read.    
    
    
    The greatest Portal is traveled through my imagination. For this Imagination is the key to my Soul's Expansion. Without this I am lost.    
    
    
    Cooperation and Appreciation http://wp.me/pI226-w4     
    
    
    Cooperation and Appreciation: It is with great joy that appreciation has become part and… http://goo.gl/fb/R21KF     
    
    
    "Blockage" The Hindered Flow of Cooperation http://wp.me/pI226-w8     
    
    
    “Blockage” The Hindered Flow of Cooperation: It is almost always the case that when a body… http://goo.gl/fb/rnAej     
    
    
    The East Calls... and more from Letter Twenty-Four "Homo Angelicus": http://wp.me/pI226-iw    
    
    
    The East Calls… and more from Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: It has been a week or so… http://goo.gl/fb/DP1xY    
    
    
    In the Face of Oneness http://wp.me/pI226-wl     
    
    
    In the Face of Oneness: This topic seems to haunt me on a regular basis. I ponder it all the… http://goo.gl/fb/VpAoO     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Two "Naïveté" http://wp.me/pI226-wu     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Two “Naïveté”: I see the world through eyes of hope. The possibilities… http://goo.gl/fb/wzibq     
    
    
    Party Like It's 1999 http://wp.me/pI226-wG     
    
    
    Party Like It’s 1999: It seems every time a major event is to take place the eve of the event… http://goo.gl/fb/r0qxq     
    
    
    Happy New Life - 2012, A Life Of Utter Transcendence http://wp.me/pI226-wM     
    
    
    Happy New Life – 2012, A Life Of Utter Transcendence: So here we go. The end of a long dusty… http://goo.gl/fb/8xc1K     
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four "Homo Angelicus" ...the final pages: http://wp.me/pI226-iL    
    
    
    In this close to Letter Twenty-Four we find that an answer to the question of existence is brought into a new light.    
    
    
    We have tried for eons to fathom the purpose of life on earth and the trials we must go through along the way.    
    
    
    In our egoic nature we assume many things yet know no thing.    
    
    
    We are brash life forms with arrogance and pride as our brother and sister.    
    
    
    We allow our defensive egos to laud over the simplicity and purity of truth.    
    
    
    Wrapped up in our day to day floundering we have no space for our true nature; our inner cry to listen, to sense and and to know.    
    
    
    Competing for greatness in a world that knows nothing greater than ego's cry for acceptance is a sad eulogy for our dying species.    
    
    
    And we are dying. The ego fed life of humanity is turning the corner of existence and walking into the light of a new consciousness.    
    
    
    It's about time.    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus” …the final pages: In this close to Letter Twenty-Four we… http://goo.gl/fb/Jm9AB    
    
    
    Transcendence Is Our Destiny, Its Time Is Now: With all the information bombarding us from… http://goo.gl/fb/nTq7p     
    
    
    It Appears Out of Our Yearnings for Light http://wp.me/pI226-wY     
    
    
    It Appears Out of Our Yearnings for Light: On January 1 the first chapters of the final book… http://goo.gl/fb/jB62a     
    
    
    @LDBrightPhoto Arielle and Sam's Wedding at the Crystal Plaza in Livingston, NJ. Saturday Night January 14. pic.twitter.com/8XjT837E    
    
    
    Beyond the Fringe: http://wp.me/pI226-iV    
    
    
    Beyond the Fringe: Last night Chris Matthews, of MSNBC, aired a report on “The Rise of the… http://goo.gl/fb/sN3y1    
    
    
    New Brights!!! Stella and Charlotte. pic.twitter.com/VYNsUqoo    
    
    
    Eleven More to Go: I remember how important it was to me as a little boy to count down to the… http://goo.gl/fb/mufyJ     
    
    
    Let's Take the First Step Back to Sanity...: http://wp.me/pI226-jc    
    
    
    Let’s Take the First Step Back to Sanity…: Oil spill, bp, unemployment, goldman sachs, bin… http://goo.gl/fb/3RUIv    
    
    
    The Grass Roots of the Spiritual Movement: http://wp.me/pI226-je    
    
    
    The Grass Roots of the Spiritual Movement: Last night I attended a workshop at the Sages… http://goo.gl/fb/ODfEt    
    
    
    So this is it. This is where it all begins. Not in the star laden hierarchy of the spiritual gurus or the new age wannabees.    
    
    
    No this is a grass roots movement that is taking it’s energy from the sincere, awakened souls,    
    
    
    that populate the hills and dales of our vast planet. The Dick and Jane crowd.    
    
    
    This is where the movement is taking shape and this is where the movement is going to evolve.    
    
    
    I pray that you realize, each one of you,    
    
    
    that your addition to this movement is as important as any team that needs all of it’s players to win.    
    
    
    The future holds magical things for humanity. It is not the apocalyptic vision that some of society imagine.    
    
    
    That is only their ego’s fear that paints that picture.    
    
    
    No, this is a world that has been envisioned in all the great minds and hearts of those who have brought Knowing to this realm of humankind.    
    
    
    Krishna, Buddha, Christ – they all knew and tried to tell us. And we have laid dumb to their words.    
    
    
    But change has come in our time and we are in the midst of a great shift.    
    
    
    This shift is so great that in generations to come we won’t even recognize the beings we are now.    
    
    
    It is a time of celebrations – through the very muck and mire of the ignorance that stands in our way – we move ahead.    
    
    
    Strong in our knowing of what will come next,    
    
    
    a life of Peace and Oneness and Appreciation of all that the Source, through Conscious Evolution, is giving us.    
    
    
    This is a great beginning people. Don’t be fooled by the tumultuous happenings of the moment.    
    
    
    Remember, it is always darkest just before the dawn.    
    
    
    Being 66 http://wp.me/pI226-x7     
    
    
    Being 66: This voice has been quiet for some time. The silence exists out of the depth of the… http://goo.gl/fb/Em2WA     
    
    
    Effulgent Light Through the Darkness: http://wp.me/pI226-mq    
    
    
    Effulgent Light Through the Darkness: Over the last two years we have been stunned out of the… http://goo.gl/fb/VDFls    
    
    
    One Nation, Independent through Conscious Evolution: http://wp.me/pI226-jo    
    
    
    One Nation, Independent through Conscious Evolution: It is July 3rd and I woke today to a… http://goo.gl/fb/iLJBO    
    
    
    A Time for Balance http://wp.me/pI226-xq     
    
    
    A Time for Balance: I’d like to return to excerpts from the first book of Letters, for it is… http://goo.gl/fb/3GGjd     
    
    
    Healing Yourself http://wp.me/pI226-xv     
    
    
    Healing Yourself: As we count down to the apocalyptic moment described in so many prophecies… http://goo.gl/fb/1TZhg     
    
    
    Climbing Up Walls is heading for the ceiling. A spectacular sound and it's only just beginning. http://fb.me/1u9CINDOn     
    
    
    Feel the Love http://wp.me/pI226-xy     
    
    
    Feel the Love: There is truly intelligence behind this activity. It is directing the action… http://goo.gl/fb/mrQw7     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Six  "A Glimpse Of Awakening" http://wp.me/pI226-xH     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Six “A Glimpse Of Awakening”: Here is a wonderful excerpt from Letter Forty-Six… http://goo.gl/fb/X3cT9     
    
    
    The Road We've Traveled http://wp.me/pI226-xR     
    
    
    The Road We’ve Traveled: It has been my wish to bring inspiring and thought-provoking content… http://goo.gl/fb/rz7qZ     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Seven "Faith and Magic" http://wp.me/pI226-xW     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Seven “Faith and Magic”: What is the most dramatic part of having a veil of… http://goo.gl/fb/84cQE     
    
    
    Letter Seventeen "Three More Suggestions": http://wp.me/pI226-jY    
    
    
    Letter Seventeen “Three More Suggestions”: At this point I hope that some or all of you have… http://goo.gl/fb/wjBjU    
    
    
    Association for Higher Awareness Presentation http://wp.me/pI226-yl     
    
    
    Association for Higher Awareness Presentation: On June 5th Robert will be offering a… http://goo.gl/fb/U5Ye7     
    
    
    Imagine It... http://wp.me/pI226-yM     
    
    
    Imagine It…: I’ve never been one to pine over the end of a tv series, they usually run their… http://goo.gl/fb/uWlTR     
    
    
    We Come to Earth Bearing a Gift: http://wp.me/pI226-k4    
    
    
    We Come to Earth Bearing a Gift: As we enter the physical realm from the souls world we bring… http://goo.gl/fb/ez3sX    
    
    
    Iceland - An Equal Opportunity Democracy http://wp.me/pI226-z3     
    
    
    Iceland – An Equal Opportunity Democracy: As we assimilate the inevitable transformation in… http://goo.gl/fb/JEfpQ     
    
    
    As we enter the physical realm from the souls world we bring with us a special gift to present to mother earth.    
    
    
    This gift we bring is different for each of us, as we are individual souls and each of us has a singular essence.    
    
    
    We are aware of this gift before the veil of forgetfulness clouds our minds and this gift seems lost forever,    
    
    
    but deep within our physical body, in the center of the jewel that is our true essence, we know.    
    
    
    The closer we get to awakening the more the heart cries for this gift, this awareness, to come into the light.    
    
    
    Yet our poor egos cry out, ‘no this can never be.’    
    
    
    This child that we placate, and spoil and cherish,    
    
    
    this little self of nothingness, begs for life as we move into a new state of understanding.    
    
    
    But shining deep with our being lies this jewel of [Oneness.] As we awaken to a greater knowing this jewel shines brighter    
    
    
    and the gift we carried on our journey becomes more apparent. It is the power of [Oneness] through the hearts of many.    
    
    
    It is an energy so bold that it radiates beyond the cosmos into Source itself. This is our gift. It is there in every iota of life.    
    
    
    It is time to open your conscious awareness and present your gift. The earth is waiting.    
    
    
    And the Cosmos Echos the Cry, Oneness...: http://wp.me/pI226-kg    
    
    
    And the Cosmos Echos the Cry, Oneness…: How strong the ego has become these many millennia… http://goo.gl/fb/OJYup    
    
    
    Whacko-ism or a Sense of Empowerment http://wp.me/pI226-z5     
    
    
    Whacko-ism or a Sense of Empowerment: There is a wonderful new idealism spreading across the… http://goo.gl/fb/g6R8q     
    
    
    Acceptance http://wp.me/pI226-zl     
    
    
    Acceptance: If we believe in the words of the prophets and try to follow in their footsteps… http://goo.gl/fb/gqr8f     
    
    
    Imagine walking down the street and passing a homeless person. As we pass a voice calls out, ‘I am God.’    
    
    
    We turn to see only the homeless person before us and wonder where that voice could have come from.    
    
    
    We ask, ‘did you say something’ and the homeless person replies ‘yes, I said I am God.’    
    
    
    A chuckle stirs from behind our breath and we stand amazed at the audacity of this misfortuned being.    
    
    
    No sooner do we begin to utter our disapproval at this heresy does this being begin to glow with a golden aura.    
    
    
    At once we notice a transformation both in him and in our self.    
    
    
    Our ignorance mind sees through the veil and becomes enlightened and our recognition of this absolute truth becomes evident.    
    
    
    @IvankaTrump Go Lou. 110 percent    
    
    
    Go Lou. 110 percent.    
    
    
    The Dance of Maya माया (Illusion): http://wp.me/pI226-ko    
    
    
    The Dance of Maya माया (Illusion): Do you believe in synchronicity? Yesterday I began a… http://goo.gl/fb/3xjnp    
    
    
    "Letters from 500" at the AHA Center June 5th http://wp.me/pI226-zw     
    
    
    “Letters from 500″ at the AHA Center June 5th: Just a reminder that Robert will be joining us… http://goo.gl/fb/C7hdB     
    
    
    Robert Lee Potter at AHA Center last evening. Wonderful turnout. Whatever we can imagine we can create. A new earth is upon us.    
    
    
    We're On Our Way... http://wp.me/pI226-zB     
    
    
    We’re On Our Way…: Bravo to all those who joined us at the AHA Center in Morristown, NJ last… http://goo.gl/fb/HXPCh     
    
    
    What You Can Imagine You Can Create http://wp.me/pI226-zy     
    
    
    What You Can Imagine You Can Create: Last evening we went to see the new Ridley Scott film… http://goo.gl/fb/UKtJW     
    
    
    Not a believer, a Knower... http://wp.me/pI226-A3     
    
    
    Not a believer, a Knower…: As we wind up to the date 12/21/12 there are different ideas about… http://goo.gl/fb/SBmk0     
    
    
    Atlantis - Pure and Simple: http://wp.me/pI226-ky    
    
    
    The Soul Reveals Itself http://wp.me/pI226-Ag     
    
    
    The Soul Reveals Itself: With all the discussion about the Soul and its purpose in the… http://goo.gl/fb/5sdWC     
    
    
    Atlantis – Pure and Simple: On August 12 Robert and I traveled down to Judy Welder’s farm… http://goo.gl/fb/NJ4jE    
    
    
    @myconsciouslife wake into conscious awareness of the divine force living within every cell of your being. This is life's true nutrient.    
    
    
    Individuality Archetype http://wp.me/pI226-Am     
    
    
    Individuality Archetype: This past weekend I was in Philadelphia with Robert and, as it would… http://goo.gl/fb/tBC3O     
    
    
    Our Responsibility http://wp.me/pI226-Ay     
    
    
    Our Responsibility: I was about to attach another segment of the AHA Center presentation and… http://goo.gl/fb/hCd7o     
    
    
    After the success of the Letters from 500 presentation at the AHA Center in Morristown, NJ Robert is reaching out... http://fb.me/2hgAf5hU3     
    
    
    Now is the time. http://wp.me/pI226-AJ     
    
    
    Now is the time.: Now we must ask ourselves the most important question of all: What will… http://goo.gl/fb/zj8Bj     
    
    
    When Will the Shift Occur?: On 12/28/10 we were contacted by a reader of Letters named “c… http://goo.gl/fb/OSQGI    
    
    
    Pay Attention, the Sky is Talking http://wp.me/pI226-AN     
    
    
    Pay Attention, the Sky is Talking: Before August moves into the past and not a word is… http://goo.gl/fb/LLdpm     
    
    
    an excerpt from Letter Forty-Five "Oneness Does Not Manifest" http://wp.me/pI226-B1     
    
    
    an excerpt from Letter Forty-Five “Oneness Does Not Manifest”: It is beyond belief, the chaos… http://goo.gl/fb/MH4QG     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @_rialitycheck http://youtu.be/KTprwk5sKlE?a  Jon Stewart "Romney is an Idiot"    
    
    
    What Mysteries Dance and Call to Consciousness: http://wp.me/pI226-kU    
    
    
    What Mysteries Dance and Call to Consciousness: Almost a month has gone by since my last post… http://goo.gl/fb/gmP7Z    
    
    
    Almost a month has gone by since my last post. I have been moving through space at a light speed pace.    
    
    
    The movement of time has had no place in my little world. And now the magic is bubbling again.    
    
    
    Those streams of golden threads that caress my imagination and fling my heart into uproarious emotions.    
    
    
    The feeling so sweet that there are no words for their place in this life. And yet write again I must, because the urge is upon me.    
    
    
    I had a dream last night and in the dream I saw humans only as soul essences.    
    
    
    The glowing band that is so effulgent around their bodies spoke to me as though it was the only reality that mattered.    
    
    
    It was moving me to tears and I new I had crossed the barrier to none self.    
    
    
    For the first time there were no personal pronoun to describe this being.    
    
    
    It wasn’t I, nor me, nor any version of that thing that describes the self, in a very self-ish way.    
    
    
    It was just existing. There wasn’t a face to put to this being. How do you describe the nothingness of that ‘presence’ state?    
    
    
    No, it is indescribable.    
    
    
    And so here we are again. There is greatness upon us in the form of the second installment of “Letters.”    
    
    
    Robert has waited for this moment for some time and would know it only when that next poem filled his imagination.    
    
    
    The poem has come and many more pages after that.    
    
    
    We have decided to publish excerpts from the new information and as the days go by I will be doing just that.    
    
    
    Today, however, I would like to present to you the poem in it’s full content.    
    
    
    Let your minds drift away from the pattern of analogy and lilt on the breath of the words.    
    
    
    Let your hearts know that we are destined for greatness and with joy and calm put your worries to rest.    
    
    
    Letter Forty-Five "Oneness Does Not Manifest" (conclusion) http://wp.me/pI226-Bg     
    
    
    Letter Forty-Five “Oneness Does Not Manifest” (conclusion): Has your soul spoken to you today… http://goo.gl/fb/kTgkd     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/nNQwVINOrzU?a  Timothy Leary "You Can Be Anyone This Time Around" Live And Let Live 1970    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Eight  "Vehicle of Awakening": http://wp.me/pI226-l7    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Eight “Vehicle of Awakening”: So once again we hear the voice of possibility… http://goo.gl/fb/BJWH3    
    
    
    So once again we hear the voice of possibility.    
    
    
    Those who resonate with this voice will feel their heart expand as they read this new information.    
    
    
    Each one of us lives in a state of mind that reflects truth in our own way.    
    
    
    But truth can only be confirmed by the rushing sensation of knowing that lies hidden in our unconscious being.    
    
    
    Rising out of this unconsciousness, to the light of awareness, is the clarion call.    
    
    
    Feel this sensation and you will understand why tears well up, and you feel free. http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    The Mass Debate http://wp.me/pI226-Bw     
    
    
    The Mass Debate: There is a clear and present danger confronting us now that wears the mask… http://goo.gl/fb/NliHD     
    
    
    2012: HOW ARE YOU TRACKING? http://wp.me/pI226-BB     
    
    
    2012: HOW ARE YOU TRACKING?: Every Sunday I receive an online newsletter from our dear friend… http://goo.gl/fb/bHcNA     
    
    
    Meditation - Gateway to a New Consciouness: http://wp.me/pI226-la    
    
    
    Meditation – Gateway to a New Consciouness: If all our senses come together to produce a… http://goo.gl/fb/o0YZI    
    
    
    "The Cure Is..." http://wp.me/pI226-BE     
    
    
    “The Cure Is…”: We have had wonderful response to Rebecca Dettman’s post of “2012: How Are… http://goo.gl/fb/ZiVmY     
    
    
    Going Deep Without http://wp.me/pI226-BS     
    
    
    Going Deep Without: I started to write here several times in the last few days. Feeling the… http://goo.gl/fb/7IdCO     
    
    
    Going Deep Without http://wp.me/pI226-C2     
    
    
    Going Deep Without: I started to write here several times in the last few days. Feeling the… http://goo.gl/fb/TN71G     
    
    
    Letters from 500 http://fb.me/1mpV0Lylb     
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com/2012/11/04/going-deep-without-2/ … http://fb.me/uyYwa1P4     
    
    
    Steady Forward http://wp.me/pI226-Cl     
    
    
    Steady Forward: With one day left till the Great Election of 2012 there is only one plan that… http://goo.gl/fb/D4yuX     
    
    
    Book Three - "AMEN" Now Available http://wp.me/pI226-Co     
    
    
    Book Three – “AMEN” Now Available: It is with great joy that we announce the publication of… http://goo.gl/fb/Rzj03     
    
    
    Election Epilogue http://wp.me/pI226-Cw     
    
    
    Election Epilogue: It has been a long and tiring trek through all of the election process… http://goo.gl/fb/vzeVQ     
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Nine "Transiency of Form" : http://wp.me/pI226-lg    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Nine “Transiency of Form”: As the journey continues into new insights, we can… http://goo.gl/fb/9Ve74    
    
    
    Presenting the New Face Of Leadership http://wp.me/pI226-CC     
    
    
    Presenting the New Face Of Leadership: There is no doubt that the re-election of Mr. Obama is… http://goo.gl/fb/LdkUV     
    
    
    AMEN - "Why Souls Love the Earth" Epilogue (part one) http://wp.me/pI226-CN     
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part one): Would you say incredible events have… http://goo.gl/fb/6Oikg     
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part one) http://fb.me/zEwjTMcF     
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part two) http://wp.me/pI226-CU     
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part two): “The ending of eras is always very… http://goo.gl/fb/EIYj1     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Cd6C1vIyQ3w?a  Flyboard Family Official    
    
    
    Letter Forty "Lenses": http://wp.me/pI226-lk    
    
    
    Letter Forty “Lenses”: Today I have received Letter Forty from Robert. It is without doubt… http://goo.gl/fb/dDuAz    
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part three) http://wp.me/pI226-D0     
    
    
    AMEN – “Why Souls Love the Earth” Epilogue (part three): In this final excerpt from Amen’s… http://goo.gl/fb/d3qqe     
    
    
    A Lovely Day With Colors and Sounds and Smells: http://wp.me/pI226-mI    
    
    
    A Lovely Day With Colors and Sounds and Smells: It is so wonderful to be in a place where the… http://goo.gl/fb/tNlVo    
    
    
    e from Amen that I recently posted you know how powerful the energy is. Good read.    
    
    
    Awesome. I feel like I'm sky-diving straight down into the Galactic Center as these days quickly tick closer to 12/21. If you've been re ...    
    
    
    21 December 2012 - NEW Message from the Star Nations http://wp.me/pI226-Dj     
    
    
    21 December 2012 – NEW Message from the Star Nations: Dear Friends, I find this to be a most… http://goo.gl/fb/lvzXn     
    
    
    A Time for Divine Silence and Divine Love http://wp.me/pI226-Dq     
    
    
    A Time for Divine Silence and Divine Love: It’s been a rough week since the event of last… http://goo.gl/fb/k5IaB     
    
    
    IT'S A NEW WORLD http://wp.me/pI226-Dx     
    
    
    IT’S A NEW WORLD: Filed under: "Letters" - A Spiritual Adventure Story http://goo.gl/fb/Hjwjf     
    
    
    IT’S A NEW WORLD http://fb.me/ydfJklBR     
    
    
    Looking Back from 500 Years Ahead... http://wp.me/pI226-DF     
    
    
    Looking Back from 500 Years Ahead…: As we reach the close of 2012, our tendency, as always at… http://goo.gl/fb/cbi1Q     
    
    
    Day One - The New Explorers http://wp.me/pI226-DT     
    
    
    Day One – The New Explorers: Joyous New Year! A time when reflection and introspection can… http://goo.gl/fb/auyxY     
    
    
    Day One – The New Explorers http://fb.me/2DR265Yq3     
    
    
    Day One - The New Explorers http://wp.me/pI226-DT  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Looking Back from 500 Years Ahead… http://fb.me/17QjFSYHv     
    
    
    Looking Back from 500 Years Ahead... http://wp.me/pI226-DF  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Day One – The New Explorers http://fb.me/1QCmMy8Lj     
    
    
    Nominate Paul Krugman for Treasury Secretary http://signon.org/s/Q1n=VU  @signon    
    
    
    "Portal" Seminar this Sunday January 13th http://wp.me/pI226-E8     
    
    
    “Portal” Seminar this Sunday January 13th: It is with great anticipation and joy that I… http://goo.gl/fb/mgMII     
    
    
    “Portal” Seminar this Sunday January 13th http://fb.me/1fapYpeXE     
    
    
    "Portal" Seminar this Sunday January 13th http://wp.me/pI226-E8  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Where Do We Go From Here...? http://wp.me/pI226-El     
    
    
    Where Do We Go From Here…?: And, How Do We Do It…? Last Sunday, January 13th, we held our… http://goo.gl/fb/ichQS     
    
    
    Where Do We Go From Here…? http://fb.me/1SSaetqnw     
    
    
    What Just Happened—1/13/13? http://wp.me/pI226-ES     
    
    
    What Just Happened—1/13/13?: From my perspective, as facilitator, I know that thirteen souls… http://goo.gl/fb/tEqRs     
    
    
    Courageous will never be linked to Harry Reid. Guess the gun advocates in your state got to you.    
    
    
    Letter Fifteen "Governance" [Think Twice Before You Vote]: http://wp.me/pI226-lI    
    
    
    Letter Fifteen “Governance” [Think Twice Before You Vote]: Today, we Americans are faced with… http://goo.gl/fb/HKpB0    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Lp1XpdAkXng?a  Awakening the Third Eye. practical meditation nr.1 by Samuel Sagan (M.D.)    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/J-7GhlfOyt0?a  Awakening the Third Eye. practical meditation nr.2 by Samuel Sagan (M.D.)    
    
    
    Enough Already...Let's Move On: http://wp.me/pI226-lK    
    
    
    Enough Already…Let’s Move On: A day after this midterm election the pundits are wildly… http://goo.gl/fb/v4KKz    
    
    
    "Letters" Travels Down Under: http://wp.me/pI226-lQ    
    
    
    “Letters” Travels Down Under: As the circle of resonance grows around the book it is… http://goo.gl/fb/33TQZ    
    
    
    As the circle  of resonance grows around the book it is strangely taking on a life miles from home.    
    
    
    Through our dear New Zealand friend Shannon Dunn it has made its way west and north to Australia    
    
    
    and into the hands of psychic  Rebecca Dettman.    
    
    
    “Psyched in Stilettos” is the nom de plume of this clear headed spiritual adviser with the clouds over her head instead of her head in them    
    
    
    Her website RebeccaDettman.com is a refreshing departure from the almost still hokus pokus realms of American    
    
    
    and European followers of the new age banner.    
    
    
    It brings a fresh look into the everyday needs of our spiritually overgrown society and puts “practical” back into the crystal ball mindset    
    
    
    She tells it like it is and not what you necessarily want to hear. Read her article on Eat, Pray, Love as an example.    
    
    
    For those of you who want the reality of this modern esoteric world, wrapped up in beautiful visuals    
    
    
    and served with common-sense advise,  RebeccaDettman.com is what you are looking for.    
    
    
    If you would like to feel a closer connection to Rebecca you can visit this YouTube interview with reporter Zoe Sheridan.    
    
    
    AH Training Wave with Jonathan Goldman. http://wp.me/pI226-Fa     
    
    
    AH Training Wave with Jonathan Goldman.: As we enter the month of Pisces we are reminded of… http://goo.gl/fb/p7kKr     
    
    
    "We Are Radiant Spiritual Beings" http://wp.me/pI226-Fe     
    
    
    “We Are Radiant Spiritual Beings”: Thanks to Robert’s advice we have been listening to the 21… http://goo.gl/fb/jPz6Q     
    
    
    Order In The Court http://wp.me/pI226-Fn     
    
    
    Order In The Court: Whether or not you are following the marriage debate in the Supreme Court… http://goo.gl/fb/5dC0i     
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/Nh7UgAprdpM?a  Sweet Brown - Original Report and Autotune Remix.mp4    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/cXfKWm2QBAE?a  Qi Gong: 7 Minutes for Health    
    
    
    Reflection in the Wind http://wp.me/pI226-Fy     
    
    
    Reflection in the Wind: It seems as though the energy flow of the conscious channel has… http://goo.gl/fb/o6cVn     
    
    
    Reflection in the Wind http://wp.me/pI226-Fy  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Reflection in the Wind http://fb.me/1qJdWpWpP     
    
    
    Awareness on a Cloudy Day http://wp.me/pI226-FC     
    
    
    Awareness on a Cloudy Day: Did you ever wonder why, with all the time spent at spiritual… http://goo.gl/fb/UcQ3U     
    
    
    Awareness on a Cloudy Day http://fb.me/2t8Kvp2A9     
    
    
    Awareness on a Cloudy Day http://wp.me/pI226-FC  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/D75yOCDU     
    
    
    One for the Good Guy http://wp.me/pI226-FN     
    
    
    One for the Good Guy: At the moment, on this planet, it is very rare to see the good guy get… http://goo.gl/fb/2tBM4     
    
    
    @MissPsychette Another mindless dupe, touted through celebrity to make it more worthwhile. The veil has tricked us once again.
.    
    
    
    Awesome. No surprise there. Rock On!!!! (@YouTube http://youtu.be/LVSaUMooZcE?a )    
    
    
    The Soul's Twins - Love and Wisdom http://wp.me/pI226-H3     
    
    
    The Soul’s Twins – Love and Wisdom: This blog has recently gotten recognition from another… http://goo.gl/fb/9O9hQ     
    
    
    The Soul's Twins - Love and Wisdom http://fb.me/1XXN1WvNp     
    
    
    The Soul's Twins - Love and Wisdom http://wp.me/pI226-H3  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Imagination - Form Through The Formless http://wp.me/pI226-Hv     
    
    
        
    
    
    Imagination - Form Through The Formless http://fb.me/Mcbx3B12     
    
    
    Imagination - Form Through The Formless http://wp.me/pI226-Hv  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    The Fruit Doesn't Fall Far http://wp.me/pI226-HC     
    
    
    The Fruit Doesn’t Fall Far: When I was young and stumbling through life all the learning… http://goo.gl/fb/4fxFe     
    
    
    The Fruit Doesn't Fall Far http://fb.me/F6AaUV5T     
    
    
    The Fruit Doesn't Fall Far http://wp.me/pI226-HC  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Silent Mind http://wp.me/pI226-HO     
    
    
    Silent Mind: To continue the thread of my last post, I have been struck by the depth and… http://goo.gl/fb/tuVSQ     
    
    
    SILENT MIND http://fb.me/1f6v8NWoj     
    
    
    Hey! Is Anyone Paying Attention Out There? http://wp.me/pI226-Im     
    
    
    Hey! Is Anyone Paying Attention Out There?: Sometimes in our lives we are granted a peek… http://goo.gl/fb/jps5F     
    
    
    Hey! Is Anyone Paying Attention Out There? http://fb.me/28wJNiWCj     
    
    
    Hey! Is Anyone Paying Attention Out There? http://wp.me/pI226-Im  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Robert Potter's Interview with David Gibbons and DG Networks http://wp.me/pI226-Io     
    
    
    Robert Potter’s Interview with David Gibbons and DG Networks: It is with great joy that I… http://goo.gl/fb/ICf5c     
    
    
    Robert Potter's Interview with David Gibbons and DG Networks http://fb.me/1IVFr1w5y     
    
    
    Testimonial from David William Gibbons http://wp.me/pI226-Iz     
    
    
    Testimonial from David William Gibbons: Letters from 500 This trilogy of books through which… http://goo.gl/fb/MpRQn     
    
    
    Testimonial from David William Gibbons http://fb.me/2GUdg2Dml     
    
    
    Testimonial from David William Gibbons http://wp.me/pI226-Iz  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Today, 6PM Eastern/3PM Pacific, hear the interview with Robert Potter and David William Gibbons on the DG... http://fb.me/2yYkPaPi7     
    
    
    Just listened to the interview with Robert and David Gibbons. It has been a wonderful experience, even for myself... http://fb.me/1oPFcb923     
    
    
    It's Time for Compassion to Rule the Earth http://wp.me/pI226-J0     
    
    
    It’s Time for Compassion to Rule the Earth: Have you ever watched the movie “Fierce Grace… http://goo.gl/fb/lT1Da     
    
    
    This Moment Is Alright http://wp.me/pI226-J7     
    
    
    This Moment Is Alright: The blogger Soul Love has made a great point about Twin Souls and… http://goo.gl/fb/fC6DQ     
    
    
    Another excerpt from the movie "Fierce Grace." There is no greater understanding of the Divine Heart than this. http://fb.me/UN9ga0JZ     
    
    
    This Moment Is Alright http://wp.me/pI226-J7  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video from @eckharttolle http://youtu.be/dTFDfR47dl4?a  How do we break the habit of excessive thinking?    
    
    
    Resonant Heart, Resident Mind http://wp.me/pI226-Jt     
    
    
    Resonant Heart, Resident Mind: If there is a vibratory state that pulses from the formless… http://goo.gl/fb/UuRUV     
    
    
    Journey to 500 http://wp.me/PI226-JE  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/SK_bj03SbNU?a  Jimi Hendrix - Live at Woodstock (Full)    
    
    
    I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Silent Mind (Jamie Bright)" http://fb.me/2DRs5Gu61     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1YRlwhfgm     
    
    
    I favorited a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/N-fe9TkeItc?a  Journey To The Edge Of The Universe    
    
    
    Dialogue Alive http://wp.me/pI226-JK     
    
    
    Dialogue Alive: Robert: I awoke this morning wanting to write poetry. I lay there thinking… http://goo.gl/fb/HYgof     
    
    
    Today Is Global Oneness Day http://wp.me/pI226-JM     
    
    
    Today Is Global Oneness Day: Filed under: Letters from Other Thoughts Tagged: Global Oneness… http://goo.gl/fb/hKBNy     
    
    
    Today Is Global Oneness Day: Filed under: Letters from Other Thoughts Tagged: Global Oneness… http://goo.gl/fb/WI3PK     
    
    
    Giving Thanks http://wp.me/pI226-JQ     
    
    
    Giving Thanks for “Life of Source”: Thanksgiving is such a soulful holiday. Unlike all the… http://goo.gl/fb/SkAH0     
    
    
    Giving Thanks for "Life of Source" http://fb.me/2wdDtC5ij     
    
    
    Giving Thanks for "Life of Source" http://wp.me/pI226-JQ  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    A Poem of Insightful Breath http://wp.me/pI226-JW     
    
    
    Poetic Courage In The Face Of An Ignorance http://fb.me/3wOcjpiR5     
    
    
    Poetic Courage In The Face Of An Ignorance http://fb.me/2cc3yAJ2j     
    
    
    Poetic Courage In The Face Of Ignorance http://wp.me/pI226-JW  via @lettersfrom500    
    
    
    Poetic Courage In The Face Of An Ignorance http://fb.me/6Ph0cLUaQ     
    
    
    Poetic Courage In The Face Of An Ignorance: From time to time we find those gems that land on… http://goo.gl/fb/3y9mf     
    
    
    Preparing for Your Inner Journey http://wp.me/pI226-K8     
    
    
    Preparing for Your Inner Journey by Caroline Myss: I was listening to some of the memorial… http://goo.gl/fb/AbaLs     
    
    
    Letter Thirty-One "Resonance, the Key" http://wp.me/pI226-mO    
    
    
    Letter Thirty-One “Resonance, the Key”: It has been some time since I last posted and it… http://goo.gl/fb/iomfK    
    
    
    Letter Thirty-One (Part 2)  "Resonance, the Key" http://wp.me/pI226-mT    
    
    
    Letter Thirty-One (Part 2) “Resonance, the Key”: So now we have a new event on the scene to… http://goo.gl/fb/n6kQL    
    
    
    So now we have a new event on the scene to capture our breath away. And each day seems to be rendering more and more chaos and confusion.    
    
    
    These acts of Nature, that seem so cruel to our existence, are but natural events of time and space.    
    
    
    We are not the cause of these catastrophes, just the recipients of their wake.    
    
    
    There is no illusion here, just the reality of Nature and it’s sometimes violent ways.    
    
    
    We have not learned to live side by side with these events,    
    
    
    for if we had we would not have built our civilizations in the paths of these roaring giants.    
    
    
    No matter how many times these events occur, we stand dumbfounded at the outcome,    
    
    
    and yet we are clearly unconscious and continue to dare the events to rattle our living ways.    
    
    
    We are trying hard to destroy ourselves now, with a certain segment of the population convinced that separateness    
    
    
    and self indulgence is the banner for which survival of the fittest flies.    
    
    
    We have yet to view life as a connective thread that flows through all and effects each one of us through actions of the other.    
    
    
    This is the world of duality of course and separateness is the primary benefactor at this moment in evolution.    
    
    
    Even though the world is mourning the great catastrophe in Japan our media still has to point out that no Americans have been reported dead    
    
    
    or missing. Is the lost of Japanese life so insignificant compared to those of our country?    
    
    
    Are we not all of the same creation? Is there not oneness in the heart of humankind?    
    
    
    from Letter Forty-Six "Glimpse of Awakening" http://wp.me/pI226-n8    
    
    
    from Letter Forty-Six “Glimpse of Awakening”: Last night I ventured through a wormhole… http://goo.gl/fb/rWIiW    
    
    
    Last night I ventured through a wormhole located deep within my own cellular system.    
    
    
    It was not hard getting there. I just imagined traveling down to that level of my form    
    
    
    and once I arrived at the cell level I envisioned a wormhole opening in one of the many bubbles floating before me…    
    
    
    and zoom.. I traveled far beyond this world. Where I ventured I don’t know.    
    
    
    It was filled with more peace and light than I’ve ever experienced before.    
    
    
    The colors around me vibrated in luminescent threads, pulsating through me and tickling all the senses.    
    
    
    I could not only see these threads of color but taste, hear and feel them.    
    
    
    It was a wonderful experience that lasted for an eternal time and when I returned I just hovered outside my physical body    
    
    
    and then lowered myself back in. Strange, I entered this wormhole inside my form and returned outside my body.    
    
    
    There is a space within that beckons us to come. It is our soul’s realm and the space where our Guide resides.    
    
    
    It is imagined, yet not imaginary. It is as solid as our planet but not tainted by the chaos mashing around us in this earth world.    
    
    
    It is dark at first, but then it opens into a new world, one we are comfortable in,    
    
    
    where we know we have been before we came here.    
    
    
    I’m now convinced that all this talk of dimensional exploration is the next step in our evolutionary path.    
    
    
    From time to time I find that my being is enjoying a perfect state of bliss.    
    
    
    I feel no emotions, no good or bad, just a state of peace that gives complete balance to my form.    
    
    
    It is in this state that I bring you this next excerpt from Letter Forty-Six of book two. http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    The Opposite of Appreciation http://wp.me/pI226-ni    
    
    
    The Opposite of Appreciation: “In response to the downward spiraling, doomsday attitude of… http://goo.gl/fb/t0y2y    
    
    
    A request from Dr. Masaru Emoto http://wp.me/pI226-np    
    
    
    A request from Dr. Masaru Emoto: To All People around the World, Gather the friends. Gather… http://goo.gl/fb/FZvTE    
    
    
    No April Fool Here http://wp.me/pI226-oo    
    
    
    No April Fool Here: The first day of the month should be a day of insight. Enter into this… http://goo.gl/fb/8Werg    
    
    
    "Fierce Grace" - A Mortality Check http://wp.me/pI226-oy    
    
    
    “Fierce Grace” – A Mortality Check: For those of you who have never seen the movie “Fierce… http://goo.gl/fb/mL8UB    
    
    
    Our Dear Friend Neptune: It seems that with all the hard work started in the 60′s, for human… http://goo.gl/fb/0ehBG    
    
    
    The Generation of Visionaries http://wp.me/pI226-oN    
    
    
    The Generation of Visionaries: As the old 60′s generation slowly slips into obscurity there… http://goo.gl/fb/Em2fI    
    
    
    Nuclear Clarity: What’s unclear about nuclear is our misunderstanding of Source. The nucleus… http://goo.gl/fb/P440x    
    
    
    Can you imagine that REP. Polls have D.Trump running at the top because of his birther stance? R U Kidding??? We're really in trouble.    
    
    
    A new twitter today for Letters from 500 “The Times They Are A-Changin” And we can make that change a more beautiful prospect.    
    
    
    check out http://lettersfrom500.com a Spiritual Adventure Story    
    
    
    The Void is the ultimate reality. It is not remote or inaccessible. It lives within the fabric of time, space and... http://bit.ly/2uBvgW    
    
    
    Become a fan of our new Facebook page - just click the link below.
http://www.facebook.com/pages/Letters-from-500/180315344933    
    
    
    Letter Thirty-Seven  "The Grace of Freedom" http://wp.me/pI226-pb    
    
    
    Letter Thirty-Seven “The Grace of Freedom”: How much importance to we put on our bodies? Many… http://goo.gl/fb/RkNJ0    
    
    
    …We, you and I and the others involved in this project, are playing
with high stakes. We have attracted the... http://bit.ly/3mfJ4    
    
    
    Epilogue - "Why Souls Leave the Earth" http://wp.me/pI226-ph    
    
    
    To have confidence without ego means to be in the embrace of integrated awareness. This is the real knowing of one’s... http://bit.ly/kHGgb    
    
    
    Epilogue – “Why Souls Leave the Earth”: At the end of book one the epilogue explained to us… http://goo.gl/fb/GCVXK    
    
    
    True confidence is being connected to the essential awareness within.    
    
    
    To have confidence without ego means to be in the embrace of integrated awareness.    
    
    
    How can I Appreciate more the the magic of living and life;
when every day seems to bring more chaos and  worry... http://bit.ly/08dtkKc    
    
    
    Appreciation is the source of all joy. Joy is what appreciation feels like. Joy arises only from within, as... http://bit.ly/081njbT    
    
    
    Appreciation is a qualification of awareness, a quality of being.    
    
    
    We are merging with the future. The future is merging with us,

in this eternal moment. Awareness of it will grow... http://bit.ly/08C6Ue5    
    
    
    Epilogue – “Why Souls Leave the Earth” – part two http://wp.me/pI226-pB    
    
    
    Epilogue – “Why Souls Leave the Earth” – part two: Other questions are now bubbling up. I… http://goo.gl/fb/KLXFt    
    
    
    Take a moment. Close your eyes and imagine a world where there is
harmony and oneness amongst all beings. Send that... http://bit.ly/928cuV    
    
    
    Take a moment. Close your eyes and imagine a world where there is
harmony and oneness amongst all beings. Send that... http://bit.ly/75Skh4    
    
    
    Enjoy Your Giving, The World Will Offer Thanks. Giving from the Surrendered Heart, from the Illumined Mind and from... http://bit.ly/5bySbI    
    
    
    Epilogue – “Why Souls Leave the Earth” – part three http://wp.me/pI226-pF    
    
    
    Epilogue – “Why Souls Leave the Earth” – part three: “Excellent. One last comment. The… http://goo.gl/fb/xJow0    
    
    
    Evolution is consciousness in its most elaborate and limitless expression. http://bit.ly/68KJCu    
    
    
    Join me on Twitter http://twitter.com/lettersfrom500 http://bit.ly/4Bkmqz    
    
    
    I would like to turn all of you on to some amazing music from two extraordinary people, Dean  and Dudley Evenson.... http://bit.ly/70BVhc    
    
    
    “What is that greatest fear?”
It is the ultimate loss of control, death of your species, destruction
of all you... http://bit.ly/8Wg6lP    
    
    
    Check out the blog http://lettersfrom500.com Conscious Evolution in the making.    
    
    
    How we evolve to Oneness. http://lettersfrom500.com/2009/11/29/from-letter-fourteen-sides-of-oneness/    
    
    
    Living in the Now is pure non-resisting. When you feel resistance or discomfort in yourself or around you, you are... http://bit.ly/4uCbb1    
    
    
    Feeling resistance, either around you, or within you, is the clue to recognizing that ego is controlling your perception.    
    
    
    Always look at your own resistance if you wish to awaken.    
    
    
    Look at resistance as a fluid, that you can pour into any situation. You have a choice to use this fluid or not.    
    
    
    You do not have to find your way out of being lost. Rather than finding your way, allow your way to find you.    
    
    
    Appreciation
connotes presence. In this sense it is a living entity, like faith. In
this presence, the truth is... http://bit.ly/8HHX3f    
    
    
    Consious Evolution, Appreciation and Authenticity - this is the state of our future selves. http://lettersfrom500.com check it out.    
    
    
    BOOK NOW AVAILABLE - A GREAT GIFT FOR THE HOLIDAYS! Letters from 500 is now available in book form. You can... http://bit.ly/4Cm3uy    
    
    
    Appreciation connotes presence. In this sense it is a living entity, like faith. In this presence, the oneness is known.    
    
    
    Appreciation - It generates consciousness and consciousness generates it. Out of it comes allowing, gratitude and grace.    
    
    
    BUY THE BOOK - "Letters from 500" available now at http://lettersfrom500.com - You won't be disappointed.    
    
    
    Appreciative capacity is your destiny. With it, you will no longer feel isolated in the Cosmos. You will open your... http://bit.ly/8XpZLh    
    
    
    Letter Forty-Four "Knowing the Oneself" : http://wp.me/pI226-m3    
    
    
    Letter Forty-Four “Knowing the Oneself”: Do we really know our self? As close as we are to… http://goo.gl/fb/CEjjG    
    
    
    With confidence in our present state of affairs so low and people unsure of their next step; Letters would make a... http://bit.ly/6z4QjJ    
    
    
    A long walk this morning feeling oneness with everyone I pass on the way. Overwhelmed by bliss through the Golden Web of the Universe.    
    
    
    Consumed by Letters from 500. You must check out the book. http://lettersfrom500.com Available now. A must for Holiday reading.    
    
    
    Bliss http://wp.me/pI226-pJ    
    
    
    Bliss: When I was in my twenties I joined a community in Queens headed by an Indian guru. I… http://goo.gl/fb/JkoNA    
    
    
    Imagine a web, a golden web, emanating from your being and stretching to every human being on the planet. http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/4UeHaD    
    
    
    As you improve your capacity to actively notice what you are feeling and thinking, and what is happening around...    
    
    
    ...turn that noticing into the expansion of awareness. Invite into your being a new openness...    
    
    
    ...and allowing that will begin to dissolve barriers around the little self.    
    
    
    ...The focus of this is the release of your identity with form, and that which is separate from the Cosmos...    
    
    
    ...Observe, for instance as you sit still, that there are holes within the fabric of your thinking...    
    
    
    Use your imagination to zoom down to microscopic levels in these holes. If you are patient, you will recognize what we call points of peace    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    Consciousness Trap: The big word these days is ‘consciousness’, as most of us know. It’s on… http://goo.gl/fb/9BixW    
    
    
    To resume: The loopholes in thought will inevitably slide by, entirely unnoticed by the mind.    
    
    
    As strange as it might sound to your ears, noticing is not a mental function; it is actually the way out of mind.    
    
    
    It does not take long for the openings to appear. A few minutes is often enough to observe one of these peace points.    
    
    
    Most likely you will feel it rather than see it, but every person senses them in a unique way.    
    
    
    You know when you’ve found one because it feels like you are being drawn into a vacuum of stillness.    
    
    
    Bear in mind, this is subtle. Many humans have trained themselves to enter these points without knowing exactly what they are.    
    
    
    People who meditate regularly are bound to be acquainted with the feeling of them.    
    
    
    ...As your awareness rises and simultaneously decends, you enter the peace or bliss state. You feel invigorated and... http://bit.ly/8b6CAX    
    
    
    This changes everything! The more often you can enter these points, the more changed you will be    
    
    
    It will transform your feelings about the world, about what to do in the world, and about who you are.    
    
    
    This is ultimate empowerment. It all starts with simple noticing, bringing out the known from the unknown.    
    
    
    Turn not-resisting into active acceptance of the moment; accept Now as your true identity. It is only logical. If... http://bit.ly/606Joq    
    
    
    If there is only one Now and no other, then everything is within the Now, in the same space.    
    
    
    Everything belongs to it. We are all simultaneous.    
    
    
    We are all one, both in essence and in substance.    
    
    
    All the boundaries in the world, in nature, in the Cosmos, are just permeable membranes;    
    
    
    we are literally liquid beings, flowing into and through one another.    
    
    
    We all flow continuously through our environments.    
    
    
    Oneness is a state of natural presence in the rest of the cosmos. It is shared among all enlightened beings.    
    
    
    What has gone wrong with earth beings and their lack of oneness - the unconscious ego and it's need to survive.    
    
    
    We can transcend this eartly ignorance through stimulating the Heart Chakra - paying attention to allowing, not-resisting and appreciating.    
    
    
    Get with the program those of you who wish to govern. Your ignorance is overwhelming and we are suffering for your arrogance.    
    
    
    Show your displeasure fellow travelers - shout it from the tweet-tops.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500 take a look at the answers given in this book. You will be surprised how easy it is to transform yourself.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    Evolution is consciousness in its most elaborate and limitless expression. As all things in creation change and... http://bit.ly/51gXWk    
    
    
    Each and every happening in the universe becomes a lesson the Cosmos is learning about itself...    
    
    
    ...a lesson it uses to push yet further the boundaries of consciousness...    
    
    
    ...We are integral to all this. We, the students, are in fact our own teachers. We are the Cosmos, the Now and the presence...    
    
    
    We are evolution itself.    
    
    
    “This is rather boggling my mind. Maybe the mind is supposed to be boggled by all this! You’re saying, We are the Cosmos?”    
    
    
    Don’t worry! It is a simple matter. What else would we be, if we weren’t the Cosmos?    
    
    
    “I can see being a part of the Cosmos, of course. But not the whole thing.”    
    
    
    The Cosmos is wholeness; if you’re part of it, you’re all of it. In essence, it is not really a thing. You are not a thing either.    
    
    
    You and the Cosmos are the consciousness inhabiting things, like a galaxy, or like your mind and body.    
    
    
    You are the essence of creation, existing beyond and behind forms, beyond dimensions, beyond concepts,    
    
    
    yet also inhabiting a small, seemingly insignificant form.    
    
    
    The true you, the consciousness that has no boundaries, is limitless.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/8e0Kel    
    
    
    Nourishment http://wp.me/pI226-pW    
    
    
    Nourishment: Nourishment by Robert For fear to exist, it must be maintained. What would… http://goo.gl/fb/ysNfR    
    
    
    ...The body is just a host for the Soul, which is thrust into separation and forgetfulness upon it's entering the... http://bit.ly/72ZSsK    
    
    
    The body is just a host for the Soul, which is thrust into separation and forgetfulness upon it's entering the physical world.    
    
    
    But there is a glimmer of light that reaches out every now and then and touches the Soul and wakens it.    
    
    
    Cut through the denseness of mind and feel those subtle waves of light. We are headed to new heights. In Peace and in Joy.    
    
    
    There is a way within the self to perceive the unknowable... http://bit.ly/6pJLVv    
    
    
    A loosening of thought patterns and unfocused eye beyond the norm.    
    
    
    Intuitive sense guides us to the place of knowing, so deeply aware, so deeply profound, that our skin trembles from the inside out.    
    
    
    Where else can we know the Source that has made this place whole.    
    
    
    We sit in the silence of nowhere and find the light of astounding worlds.    
    
    
    Our mission is clear. Our Soul has traveled this far distance only to become the experience.    
    
    
    There is no mind that can fathom this. There are no thoughts that can reckon this.    
    
    
    There is only the thread of eternal oneness that binds us all in Grace.    
    
    
    ...The awakening process of evolution is entirely about this question, the uncovering of your hidden awareness.... http://bit.ly/7TmhvB    
    
    
    ...First of all, God does not exist—not in the way you want him to. I say ‘him’, masculine, to emphasize the non-existent quality.    
    
    
    God does not exist as an outside benefactor, some ascendant personage, waiting to attend your needs...    
    
    
    However as I've pointed out before, the creative, intelligent quality of the Cosmos does exist.    
    
    
    It is Conscious Evolution, and it exists within the very essence of all awareness. Nothing exists outside of this awareness.    
    
    
    HAPPY NEW YEARnings 2010!!! http://bit.ly/6znqkj    
    
    
    AS WE LOOK AHEAD TO OUR FUTURE WE MUST UNDERSTAND THAT ALL EXISTS IN THE MOMENT.    
    
    
    THE FUTURE IS NOW, NOT TOMORROW OR NEXT YEAR, BUT NOW – IN THIS PRESENT ALIVENESS.    
    
    
    THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE WE CAN CREATE OUR DREAMS AND MANIFEST THEIR REALITY.    
    
    
    WE ARE THE WINNERS OF THIS LONG JOURNEY, THE CHAMPIONS OF THIS GAME.  WE PLAY IT HARD, WE PLAY IT WELL.    
    
    
    SALUTE US, WE ARE THE VICTORS!    
    
    
    "...Must we always be stuck in this disconnect from spirit? Surely there's some hope..."
The way is called... http://bit.ly/8ybgMq    
    
    
    The way to open yourselves to the awareness of innate oneness in creation, is to be created anew, from within.    
    
    
    Your species does evolve itself into the state of knowing, of intuitively understanding where you are and where you come from.    
    
    
    Without your sacrifice, you the prodigal sons of evolution, the process would not have moved forward.    
    
    
    It is required that you suffer until such pressure develops in the evolutionary strain to force the genetic change.    
    
    
    Your suffering and feelings of being cut off from divinity, are for a deep and grand purpose.    
    
    
    Because you are spirit. You have to be ready, not get ready.    
    
    
    What this means is that you, and humankind, have been evolving into a state of conscious opening and alignment for thousands of years;    
    
    
    Still now, if you can ask the question you just asked, it indicates that you are ready.    
    
    
    That awakening could happen at any moment for you, and for anyone who is asking such a question. Destiny is upon you.    
    
    
    “How can I really sense that destiny? I assume you’ll say it’s the same as sensing God or Source.”    
    
    
    Precisely. They are each the same. Let me walk you through a little exercise in sensing your destiny.    
    
    
    Confirm an intention right now to use your awareness, as fully as you can.    
    
    
    Start with simple thinking; this is probably the easiest form of awareness for you right now.    
    
    
    Then feel your emotions, whatever they are at this moment.    
    
    
    Next, with a clear grasp of your thinking process and emotions, let go a little; just relax in your mind and body.    
    
    
    Feel the release, even if it’s only slight.    
    
    
    Notice that this feels like an expansion within yourself. It is an expansion. Consciousness is opening just a bit wider in you.    
    
    
    Now, stay with the feeling of being aware and opening. This is subtle, but real.    
    
    
    Do not fix your attention on any objects or thought-forms in your mind.    
    
    
    The consciousness is in you, not outside you. Even your thoughts are outside the real you.    
    
    
    Another illusion to release is that you are embracing your reality; this is inaccurate as well.    
    
    
    You are the inside of everything! As you hold the intention of not fixing on forms, feel the flow of awareness around you.    
    
    
    That awareness is continuously floating in the spaces between your thoughts and emotions.    
    
    
    Notice your mind’s temptation to look for something—a form, an object, a concept to latch onto    
    
    
    Let the mind be what it is; just don’t follow its lead. Let it go where it will.    
    
    
    Now join the flow, the feeling of release around the point-of-you.    
    
    
    The mind will send probes into your state of release, attempting to regain control.    
    
    
    It will urge you to separate from your awareness and fall back into the hypnosis of thinking.    
    
    
    It will urge you to attach to a form, some thing outside your point self.    
    
    
    This is the essence of separation from Source. It all began here in this urge to go outward.    
    
    
    Expansion is not an outward movement. It is a realization within. It is touching your destiny.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    And now the game must change for the salvation of spirit here on earth.    
    
    
    Conscious Evolution has decided to change the playing field and bring in a new set of players.    
    
    
    These players are our mutated selves. What we are to become next in the Cosmic Lila.    
    
    
    This change can take place right now, right here. We just have to give the contestants a new set of tools to work with:    
    
    
    Must we always be stuck in this disconnect from spirit?    
    
    
    Surely there’s some hope. I’ve experienced breakthroughs in my own life, at times.    
    
    
    I have had experiences of my inner being, when I was more than just a body or a mind.    
    
    
    I have felt that expanded awareness on a number of occasions.    
    
    
    Doesn’t this indicate that we are not locked into the genetic structure you are depicting?    
    
    
    Indeed you can. You do. The way is called mutation.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Your species does, in fact, make the big breakthrough.    
    
    
        
    
    
    There is abundant hope.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com A Story of the Future Now. The book available at this website.    
    
    
    Undivided: Undivided by Robert Conscious Evolution puts a premium on individuality, for its… http://goo.gl/fb/eG9sa    
    
    
    The Importance of Being Nothing http://wp.me/pI226-q3    
    
    
    The Importance of Being Nothing: As the second book comes closer to completion there is a new… http://goo.gl/fb/ijvmp    
    
    
    With the change to 2010 we will be changing our appearance. New
creations stir the soul and enliven the heart. We... http://bit.ly/7buMgB    
    
    
    Check out the discount for Letters from 500. 10% off till January 31. Go to the blog sight and click on 'BUY THE BOOK' http://bit.ly/4CNdQT    
    
    
    The Soul and it's Host http://bit.ly/6uLjJJ    
    
    
    If the consciousness that ignites us and animates our physical form is the primary divine living entity...    
    
    
    ...then our physical form is acting as a host for this divine essence that is generated from the Source, the Godhead.    
    
    
    It provides the host body with information that is key to the experience the host will have on the physical plane.    
    
    
    However, veiled from the awareness of the ego-self it is relegated the position of a bystander...    
    
    
    ...until the time we become conscious of our oneness with all that is.    
    
    
    Take the time to read this excerpt from Letter Eleven "After the End." It will give you a sense of what is to come... http://bit.ly/4xcsMW    
    
    
    ...on this planet as Conscious Evolution makes it's change upon the earth and the present paradigm    
    
    
    You and I cannot avoid it. Even if these posts bore you and you think this is nothing more than wild imaginings...    
    
    
    you would do good to read it. If you live in your divine heart center and have an iota of awakening...    
    
    
    you will resonate with it and feel the truth behind the words.
http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    There is a vision of peace in my minds eye.    
    
    
    Not the peace that designates community among nations, although that would be a good thing,    
    
    
    no this peace is relegated to the state of being that lies beyond thought.    
    
    
    It is not a state of calm or assuredness. It is a centered balance of all the atoms that make up our being.    
    
    
    It wisps us up like a cloud of smoke into the eternal realm of conscious awareness.    
    
    
    This peace murmurs a stillness beyond recognition and yet it is all recognizable.    
    
    
    It consumes all and is all expanding. It is settled in the tiniest of things and the vastness of no-things.    
    
    
    Truly, this peace which has alluded us till now is nearer than our very skin. It is not in or around us, but we can sense it.    
    
    
    Close you eyes now, travel deep into and beyond,  into and beyond… Welcome it. It is our true home.    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    Where is the Sanity? http://wp.me/pI226-q8    
    
    
    Where is the Sanity?: World English Dictionary sanity (ˈsænɪtɪ) — n 1. the state of being… http://goo.gl/fb/jcTcX    
    
    
    I am sitting at my computer working on a photography album and a vague light appeared between my thoughts.    
    
    
    As it became more pronounced  I started to feel this thread about life and living without all the complications we attach to it.    
    
    
    What if we woke up each day with a breath of love exhaling from our nostrils,    
    
    
    a love for this moment of new creative energy we have brought back from our travels during our evening rest?    
    
    
    What if there was no drudgery in our minds, no distaste for how we spend the next hours of our day?    
    
    
    Could we exist in a realm of quiet motion and silent expression?    
    
    
    Could we harmonize with our fellow travelers – making no judgments or critiques?    
    
    
    What a glorious world we could find outside our door if this were so.    
    
    
    As we move through the next step of Conscious Evolution we will have no choice but to become what we believe is impossible.    
    
    
    Enlightenment is not a state of mind it is a process of transformation.    
    
    
    For when the transformation has become whole our minds will know it as all there ever was.    
    
    
    The world around us seems to be moving farther apart as we evolve through this incarnation.    
    
    
    You would think that evolution would bring us closer together as a species; more harmony, more love and more compassion.    
    
    
    On the contrary, it is moving to extreme ends of the spectrum.    
    
    
    One is a fundamentalist attitude with a reptilian gut approach to life    
    
    
    and the other is a transcendent consciousness which feels through the divine heart and sees through the enlightened mind.    
    
    
    In between these two extremes lie the manipulations of self absorption.    
    
    
    And through this tumultuous existence the fire of transformation is heating up.    
    
    
    Now, in this crucial time, the fire brings life on this planet to a raging boil and the lid of civilization is about to blow.    
    
    
    The result will be amazing!    
    
    
    http://lettersfrom500.com    
    
    
    Today is the 24th birthday of our son Taylor Jahn Bright.    
    
    
        
    
    
    He was almost six.    
    
    
    His image  never left my mind for many years.    
    
    
    I saw him as I woke in the morning and he was the last vision I had before rest took me to the dream world.    
    
    
    I have dreamed about him from time to time over the years.    
    
    
    He always gave me a laugh. I still think of him daily.    
    
    
    He is a part of my fabric.    
    
    
    After years of sadness I have grown to see a new vision of this little boy.    
    
    
    His atoms course through my essence. I no longer feel empty without him.    
    
    
    There is a new child that has entered through our life’s gate.    
    
    
    He has been with us for one year now.    
    
    
    His beauty and grace and laughter shine above all other thoughts of sadness and longing and pain.    
    
    
    His name is Taylor Cole Bright.    
    
    
    His atoms course through my essence. I feel complete with him.    
    
    
    Today is the 24th birthday of our son Taylor Jahn Bright. Happy Birthday!    
    
    
    Letter Eleven "After the End" (3rd installment): http://wp.me/pI226-6I    
    
    
    Can we define leadership in this present day world?    
    
    
    Do we really have a clue what true leadership is all about after living years with such a muddled idea of the concept?    
    
    
    We have become numb to it. We have lost the standard on which to base the value of greatness.    
    
    
    It is not a moral standard that should be used as a value,    
    
    
    for the human concept of morality lacks the most important ingredient – Authenticity.    
    
    
    When we can reach deeply within our soul for commitment to authenticity    
    
    
    then we will have a new standard for living and value shall become a thing of the heart and great once more.    
    
    
    Daily Musings 1/30: http://wp.me/pI226-6U    
    
    
    There is a new clarity peeking above the stormy horizon.    
    
    
    It is a breath of freedom that is felt in the very atoms of our self.    
    
    
    It is a pure thing and anointed with the liquid of love.    
    
    
    Emanations are peering through the darkened cloud that surrounds our presence now and the inner heart is sensing a new path.    
    
    
    It is our Soul’s birth into a revealing life of Oneness with the Creative Source.    
    
    
    The transmutation is sublime and can only give us a glimmer of its newness.    
    
    
    We must enter the realm of darkness and beyond to catch a glimpse.    
    
    
    It is here now and we must be ready, for it will leave nothing behind.    
    
    
    Even the unconscious will be caught up in the wave and cast into this revelation; to a new expression of life, a new vision of Source.    
    
    
    It is beyond our means to change this. Embrace it with all that Source has provided and we will be at the seat of the Divine once more.    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/cTSS0l    
    
    
    Letter Eleven "After the End (final installment): http://wp.me/pI226-76    
    
    
    EPILOGUE  "Why Souls Come to Earth": http://wp.me/pI226-7g    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/chXSbs    
    
    
    Daily Musings 2/4: http://wp.me/pI226-7K    
    
    
    I am the words that I capture from the Source. http://lettersfrom500.com/daily-musings/24-652-pm/    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Three "Health and Death": http://wp.me/pI226-7O    
    
    
    Letters from 500: http://lettersfrom500.com/ via @addthis    
    
    
    Conscious Life Expo: http://wp.me/pI226-7Z    
    
    
    A Point of Light in the Distant Darkness http://wp.me/pI226-qp    
    
    
    A Point of Light in the Distant Darkness: I have been looking for inspiration over the last… http://goo.gl/fb/wOfKA    
    
    
    Letter Twelve "Three Suggestions": http://wp.me/pI226-8R    
    
    
    There is a moment in each of our lives when that Consciousness, that makes us all what we are, pierces the veil of ego    
    
    
    and strikes a clarion call deep within the very essence of our being.    
    
    
    A call to freedom, to drop the bonds of ego and sail to the heights of ecstasy.    
    
    
    It resonates so loudly, out from the center of our souls, that it fills our body with an understanding of pure bliss.    
    
    
    We then feel absolute oneness with the cosmos and all that inhabit its surrounds.    
    
    
    For we know at that moment that we are all part of the one Source that dreams the worlds we live in.    
    
    
    We can feel deep in our cells these divine vibrations coursing through our pathways.    
    
    
    They rise through our emotions and our mind to convey intentions of life.    
    
    
    But we can never know them true except through the heart. Go there now for just second. Imagine it as all encompassing.    
    
    
    Feel its embrace to the ends of your personal space. It is where lies the truth of all that is. And this can only make us greater.    
    
    
    Daily Musings 2/18: http://wp.me/pI226-9z    
    
    
    There is certainly a vibration that descends from the thirteenth chakra down through the crown chakra and is felt by the physical self.    
    
    
    It is subtle; yet with enough noticing it becomes a friendly addition to your every day demeanor.    
    
    
    The best word to describe the particular feeling is emanating. You can feel its hum pulsing so gently in and around your body.    
    
    
    It then begins to lull you into a state of calm. It’s as though you were floating barely 2″ off the ground.    
    
    
    As you notice this sensation and allow it to move through you there comes a glimmering of poise within the self.    
    
    
        
    
    
    into the light of oneness with the Supreme Source.    
    
    
    As a separated ego-conscious-form you could believe this is the beginning of self Realization    
    
    
    or perhaps move beyond the ego into Oneness with the Source    
    
    
    and know it is the the action of the Absolute enjoying a moment of Self discovery.    
    
    
    Good to hear from u 2. Regards home.    
    
    
    …You do not have to find your way out of being lost. Finding is a function of thinking; it cannot get you out.    
    
    
    At best, thinking provides only a distraction. It puts wallpaper on a crumbling wall. Let the walls all fall.    
    
    
    Let the consciousness rise up. Rather than finding your way, allow your way to find you…    
    
    
    Time is a form, part of the flowing stillness. It is a manifestation of our lives in this world.    
    
    
    As we create forms of any kind, time is generated. All forms change continuously, but the Now never changes.    
    
    
    It is always the space where action happens, the space into which forms come and go.    
    
    
    Time is a way of measuring the change of forms within this space.    
    
    
    If you do not look through the forms, you will come to identify with them    
    
    
        
    
    
    It is getting fiery on the planet now. The Great Storm that is mentioned in Letters is building day by day.    
    
    
    The mental noise that pervades the natural attitude of homo sapiens is so cacophanous that we are unaware of the rising turbulence.    
    
    
    We see no further than our nose tips.    
    
    
    We are surrounded by an egoic shell that is so hardened by millenniums of wear that our sense of reality is broken.    
    
    
    We have created an illusion in the midst of a greater reality and that illusion is our brand.    
    
    
    We could say that ignorance has exploded over 99% of the planet and therefore we have a reason to neglect the truth.    
    
    
    There are those who would say that “we” are living the illusion, that 1% who believe in something greater.    
    
    
    But we have seen something more in our folly.    
    
    
        
    
    
    It lies so blessed in our hearts and those of us who have heard the words of the Christ shall know the truth.    
    
    
    The Meek Shall Inherit The Earth!    
    
    
    Can we hope that our present future, the one that lives in our lives, can make a show?    
    
    
    Will we realize our own calling to a better state before our bones are dry? It can only work in one way.    
    
    
    The noise must stop. The mind must rest.    
    
    
    The heart must venture forth into a world of understanding, a world of compassion, a world of Authenticity.    
    
    
    Before we can call ourselves human we must rise above the petty playings of a fittest mentality.    
    
    
    We must lose our attachments, all except the attachment to loving kindness.    
    
    
    For in that love is a piece of the Divine. A residue brought into the physical world to share.    
    
    
    This ignorance of ours has only a short time more to exist. It is changing in leaps and bounds before our very eyes.    
    
    
    It is changing beyond the tip of our nose and we are unaware. But it will be and be well. The next future lives know this.    
    
    
    We can join them before they arrive and set the stage for the grandest of transformations.    
    
    
    Slow down the drums of war. Slow down the drums of greed. Slow down the drums of power. Ignite the flame of Oneness and Let It Be.    
    
    
    Daily Musings 2/19: http://wp.me/pI226-am    
    
    
    Letter Seventeen "Three More Suggestions": http://wp.me/pI226-aB    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four "Homo Angelicus": http://wp.me/pI226-aD    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: “All right. Enough of this! Transparency of time, and… http://goo.gl/fb/6vUa    
    
    
        
    
    
    Believing in Conscious Evolution: http://wp.me/pI226-aH    
    
    
    …more… Letter Twenty-Four “Homo Angelicus”: “…Fantastic. I’m beginning to like the idea of… http://goo.gl/fb/UfBv    
    
    
    Believing in Conscious Evolution: As I was watching the Health Care Debate today, online, I… http://goo.gl/fb/5xhO    
    
    
    Daily Musings 2/27: http://wp.me/pI226-b2    
    
    
    Daily Musings 2/27: I find it interesting that the predictions, by biblical prophecy or the… http://goo.gl/fb/GSks    
    
    
    In all the world’s religions, beyond the standard passages that fill the books,    
    
    
    there is a state of mysticism that whispers the secrets of God.    
    
    
    There are few who are touched by this call for this is a place where faith resides.    
    
    
    And this faith goes deeper than any Sunday mass or evening bible study.    
    
    
    This is the faith that pierces the heart so deeply that tears of knowing stream down your face.    
    
    
    It owns a level of surrender so empowering that you feel you are in the presence of the Divine Lover.    
    
    
        
    
    
    A Toast to Simplicity - When I'm Sixty-Four: http://wp.me/pI226-bf    
    
    
    A Toast to Simplicity – When I’m Sixty-Four: How do we appreciate life? Do we feel simplicity… http://goo.gl/fb/AXPe    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-One "Exploration": http://wp.me/pI226-bl    
    
    
    Letter Twenty-One “Exploration”: And now let’s explore Appreciation. “You used the words… http://goo.gl/fb/5b2U    
    
    
    Letter Four "Imbued with Light": http://wp.me/pI226-br    
    
    
    Letter Four “Imbued with Light”: If you have been following the latest debacle in the Senate… http://goo.gl/fb/iuH2    
    
    
    Letters from 500 "Portal" http://wp.me/pI226-qP    
    
    
    Letters from 500 “Portal”: It is with great joy that I announce the availability of Book 2… http://goo.gl/fb/29CVl    
    
    
    ...more Letter Twenty-One "Exploration": http://wp.me/pI226-bn    
    
    
    …more Letter Twenty-One “Exploration”: “I want to go back to something that’s been bothering… http://goo.gl/fb/8X3n    
    
    
    Letter Twenty "Appreciation": http://wp.me/pI226-bx    
    
    
    Letter Twenty “Appreciation”: “Why can’t the ego just evolve or wake itself up to the greater… http://goo.gl/fb/lKdM    
    
    
    New Book, New Blog, New Beginnings... http://wp.me/pI226-qZ     
    
    
    New Book, New Blog, New Beginnings…: With today being the full moon and the lunacy that… http://goo.gl/fb/JdbgF     
    
    
    The Good News Segment: http://wp.me/pI226-bI    
    
    
    The Good News Segment: Do you ever think about how brainwashed we are with the constant din of… http://goo.gl/fb/6Pkr    
    
    
    Barbara Marx Hubbard and Conscious Evolution: http://wp.me/pI226-ce    
    
    
    Barbara Marx Hubbard and Conscious Evolution: It is always wonderful to find people who are… http://goo.gl/fb/FPg9    
    
    
    There is an ocean of silence waiting for us that transcends the state of normal life. It sits within our reach. Waiting to caress us.    
    
    
    This is the End My Friend http://wp.me/pI226-rr     
    
    
    This is the End My Friend: Are we in the throws of death? Looking down upon us the gods can… http://goo.gl/fb/TCQRm     
    
    
    Letter Eight "The End": http://wp.me/pI226-cq    
    
    
    Letter Eight “The End”: As we move ahead into the light of transformation we ask ourselves how… http://goo.gl/fb/XUXb    
    
    
    As we move ahead into the light of transformation we ask ourselves how this change of species will take place.    
    
    
    Will Conscious Evolution first rid the planet of this confused humanity and start again?    
    
    
    Perhaps other dimensional beings will seed this place as we have been told happened in our past.    
    
    
    I think that we are the true pioneers of this journey and our conscious awareness will make this transition a most beautiful experience.    
    
    
    Imagine waking up, out of the illusion created by our egos, into a new attunement to life.    
    
    
    Imagine changing the distorted vision that we see as living, by dissolving the residue of ego that covers our minds lenses.    
    
    
    We have been laughed at in the past when we dared to imagine a world so ideal, so utopian, that the concept of conflict no longer exists.    
    
    
    And now, the laughing has died down.    
    
    
    The vision has moved out of the dream and into the streets. We are conscious enough today to make it a reality.    
    
    
    The Art of Listening: http://wp.me/pI226-cC    
    
    
    The Art of Listening: One element, so crucial in human development and missing in modern day… http://goo.gl/fb/5zrc    
    
    
    The Road to Prosperity is Paved with Good Intendings: http://wp.me/pI226-dp    
    
    
    The Road to Prosperity is Paved with Good Intendings: Most of us have heard of “The Secret… http://goo.gl/fb/Lsy8    
    
    
    Earthquake: A force beyond our control that hands our egos a sense of vulnerability. A humbler beyond compare to anything else in life.    
    
    
    Letter Sixteen "Morality, Sex and Relationships": http://wp.me/pI226-eI    
    
    
    Letter Sixteen “Morality, Sex and Relationships”: I’ve always been curious about the rules we… http://goo.gl/fb/ELvn    
    
    
    I’ve always been curious about the rules we’ve made up to guide us along the way.    
    
    
    I know we believe they came from God, through a couple of tablets carved out on a mountain.    
    
    
    Or maybe from information told to disciples and then, second handed,    
    
    
    passed on to the scribes who were less than interested and just wanted to get paid for their work.    
    
    
    Did any one proof read the scribes? Since most of the purveyors of the message couldn’t read or write themselves, who checked?    
    
    
    Have you ever played that telephone game when you were younger    
    
    
    where you tell the next person in line something and by the time it gets to the twelfth person it doesn’t sound anything the same?    
    
    
    