Academic English Solutions:  Writing the Results Section http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/writing-results-section-over-next-week.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I am posting a series of excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the results section of…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on the link below from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the... http://fb.me/Gz5eopKl    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on the link below from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the resu…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Verb Tense of the Results section
The most common ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/verb-tense-of-results-section-most.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to the verb tense of the results section as …http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/Tn-mXQ    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Figures and Tables  Figures ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/figures-and-tables-figures-and-tables.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt on presenting figures in tables in the results section of a research paper. http://fb.me/KV6UWqVO    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt on presenting figures in tables in the results section of a research paper.... http://fb.me/LCYlS31n    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from my book (English for Research Papers) on presenting figures in tables in the results section o…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    AES is offering on-line ibt TOEFL preparation classes. Contact us for a free demo class. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    AES is offering online classes on English for Writing Research Papers. Contact us for a free demo class. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    AES is offering TOEFL preparation classes online. If you have never taken an online class and you have your doubts, tr…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Vocabulary for Graphs       ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/vocabulary-for-graphs-line-graphs-tend_09.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I am posting information related to conventional language of graphs, language for highlighting results, referring back…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting information related to conventional language of graphs, language for highlighting results, referring... http://fb.me/PTFmWL9Q    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->     Discussing a Wide Spectru... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/discussing-wide-spectrum-of-data-when.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I just posted several topics that are relevant to writing the results section, with a focus on conventional terms and …http://lnkd.in/6mMAMr    
    
    
    AES is now offering online individualized English classes through Skype, including classes on TOEFL preparation and En…http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C     
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    How to write the discussion section of a research paper    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) providing tips and guidelines for writing the discussion …http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) providing tips and guidelines for writing the... http://fb.me/A7JqcKXU    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Tips and guidelines for writing the discussion section of a research paper http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    revising the English of research papers and dissertations:

http://www.academicenglishsolutions.com/AES/home.html    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Beginning at the beginning, I am posting an excerp... http://goo.gl/b/dNB9    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of Manuscript http://lnkd.in/pT6g_Y     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/btjM8D     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript

What do you do when you submit your... http://fb.me/ztXsgPb8     
    
    
    Welcome! The English Cafe is open! http://lnkd.in/yV-cxP    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Free online resources for learning academic English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz    
    
    
    Free online materials and resources for learning English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz    
    
    
    I am sharing a list of guidebooks for writing scientific manuscripts and research papers. http://lnkd.in/EhuvGy     
    
    
    free online study resources for learning English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz     
    
    
    Do you need TOEFL preparation? English for writing research papers? Contact us for a free demonstration class. http://lnkd.in/GSeWQ5     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/pT6g_Y     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: 
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    I am posting a chapter from my book English for Research Papers on writing the introduction of a paper. It provides guidelines relevant to …    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/AXA_qY     
    
    
    I am posting some excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to common organizational patterns of the…http://lnkd.in/TjXQ3g    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw    
    
    
    Writing the introduction of research papers: http://www.facebook.com/pages/Santa-Cruz-CA/Academic-English-Solutions/127197030649145    
    
    
    Tips on successful grant writing: http://chronicle.com/article/Becoming-a-Successful/66133/    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:

专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格

修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章

为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程

…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
      http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
      http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Need editing for a research paper? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/emGVwC     
    
    
    Need a research paper edited? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/A4g2gT     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/BEuQTR     
    
    
    Need a revision of a research paper? We will revise two pages of your next paper for free as a sample of our work.: http://lnkd.in/mmrt4r     
    
    
    Excelente serviço de revisão de artigos e trabalhos científicos em inglês. Revisão parcial de texto gratuita para fins…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Excelente serviço de revisão de artigos e trabalhos científicos em inglês. Revisão parcial de texto gratuita para... http://fb.me/1S9H3ZmYr     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/h_9P5M     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/5cikvw     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/wVueHk     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/gc-DRV     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/H2ipHq     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/9SHkTr     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/CxhPn7     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/77eNAk  Thanks Chaofeng! I am grateful for the feedback! Glad to hear it's of value to you.    
    
    
    Free online materials for learning advanced and academic English:...: http://lnkd.in/8bbwdR     
    
    
    Free online materials for learning advanced and academic English:...: http://lnkd.in/wZkcu2     
    
    
    AES offers online TOEFL preparation courses. Try a free demonstration class.
http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C     
    
    
    AES offers online TOEFL preparation courses. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/twyXca     
    
    
    AES offers online classes in English for Engineering. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/ys3r4M     
    
    
    Happy New Year! Feliz Ano Novo! Feliz Nuevo Ano!    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по низким ценам, а также …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
We provide meticulous editing of research papers; rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rat…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    AES offers online classes in English for Engineering. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/8iH7Ct     
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    @peternocturnal hunh?    
    
    
    I am posting on my blog (Academic English Solutions) excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) from the chap…http://lnkd.in/Z_NR3f    
    
    
    I am posting on my blog (shown below) excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) from the chapter on writing …http://lnkd.in/Z_NR3f    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a resear…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on my book (English for Research Papers) from the chapter on writing the method section …http://lnkd.in/mcqcmQ    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/EqpNZPQ6    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/BKW9UsZi    
    
    
    I have posted on my Facebook page (Academic English Solutions) several excerpts from my book (English for Research Pap…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/IEsC9F5R    
    
    
    Below are some brief guidelines for the method section related to:

Materials, Cells, Animal Subjects and Human... http://fb.me/DDcPsgsN    
    
    
    Posted on my Facebook page (see below) guidelines from the method section related to listing and describing: Materials…http://lnkd.in/Pr-RkW    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw    
    
    
    Below is an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on... http://fb.me/Hc2PxOOb    
    
    
    I posted an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on the Apparatus used in exp…    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on... http://fb.me/FIt9Oaqu    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on:... http://fb.me/Gbqhzyr4    
    
    
    Need a research paper edited? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/HDMgZW     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/UJV3Dy     
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格 修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章 为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程 请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES provides exceedingly meticulous editing of research papers, rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rates, as well as…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    I have posted some excerpts on my Facebook page (see URL below) related to writing the method section of research papers.    
    
    
    I am posting below (see attached URL) an excerpt from my book (English for Research) guidelines for reporting in the m…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of academic texts; rapid turnaround time and low-priced rate…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Connect with me and view my professional profile on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/fpVKAS  #in    
    
    
    I have posted guidelines for writing the method section of a research paper on my blog: Academic English Solutions. If…http://lnkd.in/iy8nzQ    
    
    
    posted guidelines at Academic English Solutions related to extended vs. abbreviated Methods section. http://lnkd.in/iy8nzQ    
    
    
    I posted guidelines on writing research papers at Academic English Solutions (see link below). Your feedback is apprec…http://lnkd.in/dw3K48    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim como Cla…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propone…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格 修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章 为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程 请点击主页查看详情

Academic English Solu…http://lnkd.in/fak7Cn    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim como Cla…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Vi tilbyr grundig redigering av forskningsartikler, rask behandlingstid og rimelige priser…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of academic texts; rapid turnaround time and low-priced rate…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como...: http://lnkd.in/uCdJNc     
    
    
    Try a free sample of our editing service.: http://lnkd.in/Wuyx7k     
    
    
    Try a free sample of our editing service.: http://lnkd.in/TrTBvM     
    
    
    Try a sample of our editing service or free online English class.: http://lnkd.in/R488JA     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TjFPmj  Yeah, Cris, if you have trouble finding a publisher, you might consider making it into an ebook.    
    
    
    Dear AES clients: we will be on holiday from Dec. 19 to Jan. 2. Since we receive many papers to be revised at this tim…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book related to numbers, tense form, and writing style of the Method section of scienti…http://lnkd.in/YKiFbQ    
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) below related to presenting numbers, tense form,... http://fb.me/KAiazo3M    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contnuti ed in breve tempo. Propone …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim com classes  academicas em In…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->     Numbers   There are some ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/numbers-there-are-some-common-rules.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Tense of Methods Section  As... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/tense-of-methods-section-as-previously.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Writing style of methods in ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/writing-style-of-methods-in-scientific.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    tips and guidelines for writing research papers http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of scientific and academic texts; rapid turnaround time and …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AwcSTA  Hi Ying,    If you are curious to know more about our service, you are welcome to send me the first page of your...    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Qualitative Methods of Socia... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/qualitative-methods-of-social-science_21.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I have posted guidelines and tips from my book (English for Research Papers) on writing the method sections of studies…http://lnkd.in/muEER-    
    
    
    I posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions related to writing the method section of papers... http://fb.me/KAabppH4    
    
    
    I just posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the method s…    
    
    
    I just posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions from my book (English for Research Papers) related to…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting excerpt from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the middle section of the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted guidelines and tips on writing the middle section of a research paper. Your feedback is greatly appreciated. http://fb.me/NWZNkJae    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions ￼ http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    I am sharing an amusing series of Tweets called Overly Honest Methods. This post may be particularly funny for... http://fb.me/12H4gkaqL     
    
    
    I am sharing an amusing series of Tweets called Overly Honest Methods. This post may be particularly funny for... http://fb.me/2z8WuIXXh     
    
    
    I posted tips and guidelines for writing the middle section of the discussion of a research paper. Your feedback is gr…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jNxhgE     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful:... http://fb.me/JQjoe6AM     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful. http://fb.me/2BSYHOyy7     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful. http://fb.me/2RHJdgDtW     
    
    
    Решения, связанные с научным английским языком: предоставляются услуги по тщательному редактированию научных статей с быстрым временем обор…    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contnuti ed in breve tempo. Propone…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim com clas…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情    
    
    
        
    
    
    Решения, связанные с научным английским языком: предоставляются услуги по тщательному редактированию научных статей с …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous editing of research papers, with rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rates, as well as En…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous editing of research papers, with rapid turnaround-time and low-priced…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Planning on studying or doing research in the US? Here are the first ten things you should do upon arriving.... http://fb.me/2FD2oPw4N     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://fb.me/26SkfMnaH     
    
    
    My book, English for Research Papers: A Handbook for Brazilian Authors, is now available at Amazon, and I just... http://fb.me/1uQSTvG74     
    
    
    My book, English for Research Papers: A Handbook for Brazilian Authors, is now available at Amazon, and I just... http://fb.me/6v9fu588f     
    
    
    Someone wrote to me and asked, "Why is your book only for Brazilian authors?" First, I should say that when I... http://fb.me/ZMUoxNKh     
    
    
    Dear friends of AES, 

You may have noticed in a previous message that my book, English for Research Papers: A... http://fb.me/6kEzQIcQm     
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding to the discussion. Your feedback is…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is greatly appreciated.    
    
    
    posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is... http://fb.me/VSnOiOfV    
    
    
    I am posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on writing the conclusion of a research paper. Your f…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion section of research paper. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    #Concluding the discussion. Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is greatly a…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting tips and guidelines from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
        
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation courses at AES: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online personalized one-to-one TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online personalized one-to-one TOEFL preparation classes via Skype: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Preparing a poster or Power Point presentation for a conference? We offer classes on presenting, as well as editing of…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    /Users/jim/Desktop/471690.jpg http://lnkd.in/_z4GGa    
    
    
    AES is now offering online classes including TOEFL preparation, and English for Research Papers: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES provides meticulous editing of research papers with rapid turnaround-time. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschläge für akademische un…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with highly experienced teacher. Try your first class for fre…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with a knowledgable experienced teacher. No need to travel ac…http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with an experienced teacher. Try your first class for free. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情    
    
    
        
    
    
    AES: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propone allo stesso tempo cor…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES: 专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格

修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章

为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程

请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions ￼ http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:  Writing the Results Section http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/writing-results-section-over-next-week.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I am posting a series of excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the results section of…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on the link below from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the... http://fb.me/Gz5eopKl    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on the link below from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the resu…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Verb Tense of the Results section
The most common ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/verb-tense-of-results-section-most.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to the verb tense of the results section as …http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/Tn-mXQ    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Figures and Tables  Figures ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/figures-and-tables-figures-and-tables.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt on presenting figures in tables in the results section of a research paper. http://fb.me/KV6UWqVO    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt on presenting figures in tables in the results section of a research paper.... http://fb.me/LCYlS31n    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from my book (English for Research Papers) on presenting figures in tables in the results section o…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    AES is offering on-line ibt TOEFL preparation classes. Contact us for a free demo class. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    AES is offering online classes on English for Writing Research Papers. Contact us for a free demo class. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    AES is offering TOEFL preparation classes online. If you have never taken an online class and you have your doubts, tr…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Vocabulary for Graphs       ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/vocabulary-for-graphs-line-graphs-tend_09.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I am posting information related to conventional language of graphs, language for highlighting results, referring back…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting information related to conventional language of graphs, language for highlighting results, referring... http://fb.me/PTFmWL9Q    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->     Discussing a Wide Spectru... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/12/discussing-wide-spectrum-of-data-when.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I just posted several topics that are relevant to writing the results section, with a focus on conventional terms and …http://lnkd.in/6mMAMr    
    
    
    AES is now offering online individualized English classes through Skype, including classes on TOEFL preparation and En…http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C     
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    How to write the discussion section of a research paper    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) providing tips and guidelines for writing the discussion …http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) providing tips and guidelines for writing the... http://fb.me/A7JqcKXU    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Tips and guidelines for writing the discussion section of a research paper http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    revising the English of research papers and dissertations:

http://www.academicenglishsolutions.com/AES/home.html    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Beginning at the beginning, I am posting an excerp... http://goo.gl/b/dNB9    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of Manuscript http://lnkd.in/pT6g_Y     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/btjM8D     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript

What do you do when you submit your... http://fb.me/ztXsgPb8     
    
    
    Welcome! The English Cafe is open! http://lnkd.in/yV-cxP    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Free online resources for learning academic English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz    
    
    
    Free online materials and resources for learning English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz    
    
    
    I am sharing a list of guidebooks for writing scientific manuscripts and research papers. http://lnkd.in/EhuvGy     
    
    
    free online study resources for learning English http://lnkd.in/vGwnWz     
    
    
    Do you need TOEFL preparation? English for writing research papers? Contact us for a free demonstration class. http://lnkd.in/GSeWQ5     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/pT6g_Y     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: 
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    I am posting a chapter from my book English for Research Papers on writing the introduction of a paper. It provides guidelines relevant to …    
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/AXA_qY     
    
    
    I am posting some excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to common organizational patterns of the…http://lnkd.in/TjXQ3g    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw    
    
    
    Writing the introduction of research papers: http://www.facebook.com/pages/Santa-Cruz-CA/Academic-English-Solutions/127197030649145    
    
    
    Tips on successful grant writing: http://chronicle.com/article/Becoming-a-Successful/66133/    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:

专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格

修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章

为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程

…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
      http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
      http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Need editing for a research paper? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/emGVwC     
    
    
    Need a research paper edited? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/A4g2gT     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/BEuQTR     
    
    
    Need a revision of a research paper? We will revise two pages of your next paper for free as a sample of our work.: http://lnkd.in/mmrt4r     
    
    
    Excelente serviço de revisão de artigos e trabalhos científicos em inglês. Revisão parcial de texto gratuita para fins…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Excelente serviço de revisão de artigos e trabalhos científicos em inglês. Revisão parcial de texto gratuita para... http://fb.me/1S9H3ZmYr     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/h_9P5M     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript: http://lnkd.in/5cikvw     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/wVueHk     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/gc-DRV     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/H2ipHq     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/9SHkTr     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/CxhPn7     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/77eNAk  Thanks Chaofeng! I am grateful for the feedback! Glad to hear it's of value to you.    
    
    
    Free online materials for learning advanced and academic English:...: http://lnkd.in/8bbwdR     
    
    
    Free online materials for learning advanced and academic English:...: http://lnkd.in/wZkcu2     
    
    
    AES offers online TOEFL preparation courses. Try a free demonstration class.
http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C     
    
    
    AES offers online TOEFL preparation courses. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/twyXca     
    
    
    AES offers online classes in English for Engineering. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/ys3r4M     
    
    
    Happy New Year! Feliz Ano Novo! Feliz Nuevo Ano!    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по низким ценам, а также …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
We provide meticulous editing of research papers; rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rat…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    AES offers online classes in English for Engineering. Try a free demonstration class.: http://lnkd.in/8iH7Ct     
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    @peternocturnal hunh?    
    
    
    I am posting on my blog (Academic English Solutions) excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) from the chap…http://lnkd.in/Z_NR3f    
    
    
    I am posting on my blog (shown below) excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) from the chapter on writing …http://lnkd.in/Z_NR3f    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a resear…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    I am posting several excerpts on my book (English for Research Papers) from the chapter on writing the method section …http://lnkd.in/mcqcmQ    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/EqpNZPQ6    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/BKW9UsZi    
    
    
    I have posted on my Facebook page (Academic English Solutions) several excerpts from my book (English for Research Pap…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    I am sharing an excerpt from English for Research Papers related to the organization of the method section of a... http://fb.me/IEsC9F5R    
    
    
    Below are some brief guidelines for the method section related to:

Materials, Cells, Animal Subjects and Human... http://fb.me/DDcPsgsN    
    
    
    Posted on my Facebook page (see below) guidelines from the method section related to listing and describing: Materials…http://lnkd.in/Pr-RkW    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw    
    
    
    Below is an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on... http://fb.me/Hc2PxOOb    
    
    
    I posted an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on the Apparatus used in exp…    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on... http://fb.me/FIt9Oaqu    
    
    
    Posting an excerpt from English for Research papers related to guidelines for reporting in the method section on:... http://fb.me/Gbqhzyr4    
    
    
    Need a research paper edited? We will revise the first 2 pages of your text for free as a sample of our work....: http://lnkd.in/HDMgZW     
    
    
    Tips for Responding to an Editor's Request for a Revision of a Manuscript...: http://lnkd.in/UJV3Dy     
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格 修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章 为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程 请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES provides exceedingly meticulous editing of research papers, rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rates, as well as…http://lnkd.in/exj5GN     
    
    
    I have posted some excerpts on my Facebook page (see URL below) related to writing the method section of research papers.    
    
    
    I am posting below (see attached URL) an excerpt from my book (English for Research) guidelines for reporting in the m…http://lnkd.in/s_3t8P    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of academic texts; rapid turnaround time and low-priced rate…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Connect with me and view my professional profile on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/fpVKAS  #in    
    
    
    I have posted guidelines for writing the method section of a research paper on my blog: Academic English Solutions. If…http://lnkd.in/iy8nzQ    
    
    
    posted guidelines at Academic English Solutions related to extended vs. abbreviated Methods section. http://lnkd.in/iy8nzQ    
    
    
    I posted guidelines on writing research papers at Academic English Solutions (see link below). Your feedback is apprec…http://lnkd.in/dw3K48    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim como Cla…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Interesting article. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propone…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格 修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章 为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程 请点击主页查看详情

Academic English Solu…http://lnkd.in/fak7Cn    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim como Cla…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
英語の授業と翻訳が早く安く学べます。 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Мы выполняем тщательное редактирование научных статей при быстром исполнении заказа и по н…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como aul…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propon…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions:
专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Vi tilbyr grundig redigering av forskningsartikler, rask behandlingstid og rimelige priser…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of academic texts; rapid turnaround time and low-priced rate…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisão de textos acadêmicos, com rápido retorno e excelente custo, assim como...: http://lnkd.in/uCdJNc     
    
    
    Try a free sample of our editing service.: http://lnkd.in/Wuyx7k     
    
    
    Try a free sample of our editing service.: http://lnkd.in/TrTBvM     
    
    
    Try a sample of our editing service or free online English class.: http://lnkd.in/R488JA     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TjFPmj  Yeah, Cris, if you have trouble finding a publisher, you might consider making it into an ebook.    
    
    
    Dear AES clients: we will be on holiday from Dec. 19 to Jan. 2. Since we receive many papers to be revised at this tim…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9     
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book related to numbers, tense form, and writing style of the Method section of scienti…http://lnkd.in/YKiFbQ    
    
    
    I have posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) below related to presenting numbers, tense form,... http://fb.me/KAiazo3M    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contnuti ed in breve tempo. Propone …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim com classes  academicas em In…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->     Numbers   There are some ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/numbers-there-are-some-common-rules.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Tense of Methods Section  As... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/tense-of-methods-section-as-previously.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Writing style of methods in ... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/writing-style-of-methods-in-scientific.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    tips and guidelines for writing research papers http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous revision of scientific and academic texts; rapid turnaround time and …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AwcSTA  Hi Ying,    If you are curious to know more about our service, you are welcome to send me the first page of your...    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: <!--StartFragment-->  Qualitative Methods of Socia... http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/2010/10/qualitative-methods-of-social-science_21.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    I have posted guidelines and tips from my book (English for Research Papers) on writing the method sections of studies…http://lnkd.in/muEER-    
    
    
    I posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions related to writing the method section of papers... http://fb.me/KAabppH4    
    
    
    I just posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the method s…    
    
    
    I just posted (on the link below) brief comments and suggestions from my book (English for Research Papers) related to…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting excerpt from my book (English for Research Papers) related to writing the middle section of the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted guidelines and tips on writing the middle section of a research paper. Your feedback is greatly appreciated. http://fb.me/NWZNkJae    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions ￼ http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    I am sharing an amusing series of Tweets called Overly Honest Methods. This post may be particularly funny for... http://fb.me/12H4gkaqL     
    
    
    I am sharing an amusing series of Tweets called Overly Honest Methods. This post may be particularly funny for... http://fb.me/2z8WuIXXh     
    
    
    I posted tips and guidelines for writing the middle section of the discussion of a research paper. Your feedback is gr…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/jNxhgE     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful:... http://fb.me/JQjoe6AM     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful. http://fb.me/2BSYHOyy7     
    
    
    Applying for a science job in the US? This may be helpful. http://fb.me/2RHJdgDtW     
    
    
    Решения, связанные с научным английским языком: предоставляются услуги по тщательному редактированию научных статей с быстрым временем обор…    
    
    
        
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contnuti ed in breve tempo. Propone…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Oferece revisao de textos academicos, com rapido retorno e excelente custo, assim com clas…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情    
    
    
        
    
    
    Решения, связанные с научным английским языком: предоставляются услуги по тщательному редактированию научных статей с …http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous editing of research papers, with rapid turnaround-time and low-priced rates, as well as En…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: providing meticulous editing of research papers, with rapid turnaround-time and low-priced…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Planning on studying or doing research in the US? Here are the first ten things you should do upon arriving.... http://fb.me/2FD2oPw4N     
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://fb.me/26SkfMnaH     
    
    
    My book, English for Research Papers: A Handbook for Brazilian Authors, is now available at Amazon, and I just... http://fb.me/1uQSTvG74     
    
    
    My book, English for Research Papers: A Handbook for Brazilian Authors, is now available at Amazon, and I just... http://fb.me/6v9fu588f     
    
    
    Someone wrote to me and asked, "Why is your book only for Brazilian authors?" First, I should say that when I... http://fb.me/ZMUoxNKh     
    
    
    Dear friends of AES, 

You may have noticed in a previous message that my book, English for Research Papers: A... http://fb.me/6kEzQIcQm     
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding to the discussion. Your feedback is…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is greatly appreciated.    
    
    
    posted excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is... http://fb.me/VSnOiOfV    
    
    
    I am posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on writing the conclusion of a research paper. Your f…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion section of research paper. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    I am posting excerpts from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    #Concluding the discussion. Academic English Solutions http://academicenglishsolutions.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    I posted excerpts from my book (English for Research) related to concluding the discussion. Your feedback is greatly a…http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
    Posting tips and guidelines from my book (English for Research Papers) on concluding the discussion. http://lnkd.in/SBkiXk    
    
    
        
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation courses at AES: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online personalized one-to-one TOEFL preparation classes: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Online personalized one-to-one TOEFL preparation classes via Skype: first class for free and next two at half price: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Preparing a poster or Power Point presentation for a conference? We offer classes on presenting, as well as editing of…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    /Users/jim/Desktop/471690.jpg http://lnkd.in/_z4GGa    
    
    
    AES is now offering online classes including TOEFL preparation, and English for Research Papers: http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES provides meticulous editing of research papers with rapid turnaround-time. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschläge für akademische un…    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with highly experienced teacher. Try your first class for fre…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with a knowledgable experienced teacher. No need to travel ac…http://lnkd.in/cg9b6C    
    
    
    AES offers online personalized TOEFL preparation classes with an experienced teacher. Try your first class for free. http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格
修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章
为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程
请点击主页查看详情    
    
    
        
    
    
    AES: offre riletture meticolose di testi accademici a costi contenuti ed in breve tempo. Propone allo stesso tempo cor…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions: Wir bieten sorgfältig, schnell und preiswertes Korrekturlesen und Verbesserungengsvorschlä…http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    AES: 专业学术英语服务：提供专业的学术英文网上课程，专业的英文写作修改，快捷的服务，合理的价格

修改英文的学术文章、论文和书籍，以及其他专业文章

为母语不是英语的人提供英文课程

请点击主页查看详情 http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    Academic English Solutions ￼ http://lnkd.in/ANwaC9    
    
    
    