research #developer #job in semantic web/linked data and #disasters at @astonuniversity in #birmingham http://bit.ly/x1xLlR  please RT    
    
    
    reminder: research #developer #job in semantic web/linked data and #disasters at @astonuniversity in #birmingham http://bit.ly/x1xLlR  pls RT    
    
    
    Semantic Web and Agri-Food Workshop #SWAF2012 http://bit.ly/HvrvZb  at #SmartAgriMatics http://bit.ly/Hvryo6  abstract deadline  30 April    
    
    
    BBC News - Greece bartering system popular in Volos http://bbc.in/HCfJNH     
    
    
    Imperialism didn't end. These days it's known as international law | George Monbiot http://gu.com/p/378jk     
    
    
    Court rules organic farmers can sue conventional, GMO farmers http://www.trueactivist.com/court-rules-organic-farmers-can-sue-conventional-gmo-farmers-whose-pesticides-trespass-and-contaminate-their-fields/ … via @TrueActivist    
    
    
    Finnish appetite for local food: http://www.sitra.fi/en/articles/2012/finnish-appetite-grows-local-food …    
    
    
    How Greece could leave the eurozone – in five difficult steps http://gu.com/p/37gn9  #collapsonomics    
    
    
    Oil prices could double by 2022, IMF warned http://gu.com/p/37h56/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Semantic Web Research Software Developer @astonbusiness, Birmingham, http://bit.ly/MbXnFZ  deadline 28 May    
    
    
    Greece compared to Iceland http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=19429     
    
    
    @dajbelshaw http://www.ashasuk.co.uk/  I suggest    
    
    
    I have 33 slaves working for me, find out how many slaves work for you at http://SlaveryFootprint.org . #slaveryfootprint    
    
    
    Why love trumps economics | Victoria Coren http://gu.com/p/37kqb     
    
    
    We must take back control of our food, before it's too late  http://bit.ly/Kv3i52  via @guardian    
    
    
    BBC News - Viewpoint: The time Britain slid into chaos http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/magazine-18159752 …    
    
    
    Vote Yes for Fiscal Compact Treaty (Ireland) Yes for Jobs: http://youtu.be/TZfzAOooEOU  via @youtube (Note this is satire ...)    
    
    
    Semantic Web research developer position on Disaster 2.0 project http://bit.ly/KkhQqe  at @aston http://bit.ly/MbXnFZ  deadline 31 May  pls RT    
    
    
    Local food policy could go a long way to helping cure social ills: expert http://www.ottawacitizen.com/health/Local+food+policy+could+long+helping+cure+social+ills+expert/6681276/story.html … via @ottawacitizen    
    
    
    We are sleepwalking into the Drone Age, unaware of the consequences | Clive Stafford Smith
http://gu.com/p/383mv     
    
    
    Response to Vinay's Europe's New War | Edgeryders http://edgeryders.ppa.coe.int/practical-resilience/mission_case/response-vinays-europes-new-war …    
    
    
    Feeding Birmingham in 20150: Semantic Web and the food supply: event 11 June  http://bit.ly/MgAjEs  #TNOfood @smartagrifood @astonuniversity    
    
    
    @leashless Collaborative blog - but make it more policy/officialdom oriented. Have things peer reviewed   cf. http://bit.ly/MhXWwg     
    
    
    Little Britain: why the UK is no longer a superpower @guardian http://bit.ly/LMS2BH     
    
    
    Semantic Web and Agri-Food Workshop and Hackathon  on 13 June in Paris http://bit.ly/Kua0IF  #SWAF12 #smartagrifood #smartagrimatics    
    
    
    Feeding Birmingham in 2050: Semantic Web and the food supply: tonight  http://bit.ly/MgAjEs  #TNOfood @smartagrifood @astonuniversity    
    
    
    Semantic Web #SWAF12 #smartagriexchange if you want to join us for the workshop/hackathon free tickets here: http://swaf12.eventbrite.co.uk/     
    
    
    @leashless Brilliant insights on supply chains and military intervention, late last  night from Vinay    
    
    
    Listening to Johannes Keizer at #SWAF12 #smartagrimatics http://bit.ly/Kua0IF  annotating unstructured data using RDF triples    
    
    
    Thanks to everyone who attended #SWAF Semantic Web and Agri-Food today. Fantastic set of speakers http://bit.ly/Kua0IF  #smartagrimatics    
    
    
    The Greeks who are swimming against the tide http://bit.ly/LkViot  @guardian    
    
    
    Argyll and Bute council in censorship over school meals http://bit.ly/KMm9Ha  muzzling 9 year old blogger. We need a food revolution.    
    
    
    Why young rural Greeks are set to embrace Syriza http://bbc.in/LfgXBN  @paulmasonnews relevant to #LOTE    
    
    
    I'm hiring. RA/RF Social Media in Disaster Response http://bit.ly/L0EczV  @astonuniversity  Disaster 2.0 project  http://bit.ly/KkhQqe     
    
    
    I'm hiring. RF Semantic Web in Disaster Response http://bit.ly/L0Eu9Y  @astonuniversity Disaster 2.0 project http://bit.ly/KkhQqe     
    
    
    @thejaymo is someone capturing all the tweets with #LOTE? Will there be a dump to play with?    
    
    
    @zbeauvais in what way do you *not* fit the criteria?    
    
    
    Please RT:  #Semantic web and #disaster response #job http://bit.ly/L0Eu9Y  #researchjobs  project  http://bit.ly/KkhQqe  @astonuniversity    
    
    
    Please RT: #Semantic Web and #Emergency Response RF #jobs http://bit.ly/L0Eu9Y  deadline today @astonuniversity http://bit.ly/KkhQqe     
    
    
    The Olympian Landscape http://bit.ly/MY8UYo  via @GuernicaMag    
    
    
    Attending Food security in the Global North meeting at @warwickuniversity today. Fantastic speaker line up #foodsecurity    
    
    
    Household Food Security in the Global North http://bit.ly/MEuOCm   meeting at Warwick University #foodsecurity    
    
    
    Excellent overview of the challenges  due to food insecurity  by Liz Dowler @warwickuniversity  #foodsecurity meeting    
    
    
    Now up Angela Donkin from UCL on food inequalities and health impacts #foodsecurity meeting @warwickuni    
    
    
    Now up Caroline Carey from Food Poverty Network in Ireland on indicators in of food poverty #foodsecurity meeting @warwickuni    
    
    
    Caroline Carney says food poverty is 10.3% in Ireland  - #foodsecurity meeting at @warwickuni    
    
    
    Next up Nicole Darmon from AMU on food poverty in France #foodsecurity meeting @warwickuni    
    
    
    Nicole Darmon says premature mortality has doubled in France in last 40 years #foodsecurity @warwickuni --> is this really true?    
    
    
    Next up Prof. Sabine Pfeiffer from Munich on food and poverty in Germany #foodsecurity @warwickuni    
    
    
    @RichardJMurphy Are you aware of Modern Monetarist Theory especially @billy_blog? Connection between taxation and expenditure is a fiction.    
    
    
    Terrifying statistics on food poverty in Germany presented by Sabine Pfeiffer #foodsecurity @warwickuni more similar to UK than expected    
    
    
    next up Deirdre O'Connor on Food and austerity in Ireland #foodsecurity @warwickuni  on policy choices    
    
    
    11.3% of Canadians face food insecurity - Rachel Loopstra-Master at #foodsecurity meeting @warickuni. Dominance of charity food giving    
    
    
    Next up Janet Popendieck on charity and food security in USA #foodsecurity meeting @warwickuni    
    
    
    An eco-friendly community crops up in Evia http://bit.ly/NgStFb  #greece #food    
    
    
    Now on Anne Bellows on Gender, Nutrition and the right to food #foodsecurity meeting @warwickuni    
    
    
    @leashless Because infinite computing power does not handle language very well. This is a feature of language not a bug ....cf. Wittgenstein    
    
    
    @leashless RT @CMastication Printing guns at home. That escalated quickly. http://globalguerrillas.typepad.com/globalguerrillas/2012/07/printing-weapons-at-home-for-fun-and-mayhem.html …    
    
    
    Now Cameron wants us to spend again. And borrow. Have we learned nothing? http://bit.ly/SXV4r3  Deborah Orr @guardian    
    
    
    Join us for the Hackathon for Disaster Response #h4d2 on social media and semantic web 21-23 September in Birmingham http://www.h4d2.eu/     
    
    
    New Hurricane App Brings American Red Cross Safety Information to Smart Phones http://bit.ly/Ob4cXk     
    
    
    Including banks in macro models (finally!) on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/emacampiglio/including-banks-in-macro-models-finally … via NEF    
    
    
    Hackathon  for Disaster Response #h4d2 using Semantic Web and Linked Data http://www.h4d2.eu/   21-23 September    
    
    
    @UnlearningEcon capitalism was flexible in the 1950s but there was almost no  unemployment.    
    
    
    Listening to Martin Palmer and @dougald on sacred stories at #unciv    
    
    
    Ancient Corinth deserted. Clearly all tourists at home reading @leashless's tweets    
    
    
    Back in Birmingham after holidays    
    
    
    @leashless and I had a fascinating trip to Greece    
    
    
    @ortholithos Good to meet you in Athens with @leashless. Keep in touch about your courses    
    
    
    Bill Mitchel on the Job Guarantee, speaking to the EC http://bit.ly/P6SkYr   excellent talk    
    
    
    Come to the  Hackathon for Disaster Response http://h4d2.eu/  21-23 Sept, fantastic problems to solve, free food, have fun, please RT    
    
    
    Come to the Hackathon for Disaster Response http://h4d2.eu/   21-23 Sept, fantastic problems to solve, free food, have fun, please RT    
    
    
    Mobile Field Geodata Collection (EpiCollect & Drupal) - one problem space at the Hackathon for Disaster Response  http://bit.ly/QaJtp3     
    
    
    #Sahana Feed-Data Integration via GDACS - problem space at #h4d2  hackathon http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  please come and join us 21-23 Sept    
    
    
    Trust4news in Disaster - problem space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  come join us    
    
    
    Social Media on the #Sahana Dashboard - problem space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  come join us - free food    
    
    
    Geo-Services from Linked Open Humanitarian Data - probelm space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  come link us    
    
    
    Mobile Field Geodata Collection #EpiCollect & #Drupal) - one problem at Hackathon for Disaster Response http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  #H4D2    
    
    
    Join us Hackathon for Disaster Response http://h4d2.eu/   21-23 Sept, fantastic problems to solve, free food, have fun, please RT #H4D2    
    
    
    #Sahana Feed-Data Integration via GDACS - problem space at #h4d2 hackathon http://bit.ly/QaJtp3   come and join us 21-23 Sept    
    
    
    Trust4news in Disaster - problem space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3   come join us    
    
    
    Social Media on the #Sahana Dashboard - problem space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3  come join us -free food    
    
    
    Geo-Services from Linked Open Humanitarian Data - probelm space in #h4d2 hackathon 21-23 Sept Birmingham http://bit.ly/QaJtp3   come link us    
    
    
    Oppose the new system in UK Higher Education - Sign the Petition http://www.gopetition.com/petitions/opposing-the-crisis-in-higher-education.html …    
    
    
    @dougald phonemically /b'izantain/ stress on first syllable, last syllable to rhyme with tyne not teen    
    
    
    Rising inequality demonstrates we haven’t learned much http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=21026     
    
    
    @leashless now talking at #h4d2    
    
    
    Fantastic talks about emergency response and disaster management #h4d2    
    
    
    Never cheat a person who can put liquids in your body OH #h4d2    
    
    
    @leashless @eco_expert check the blog page of http://www.h4d2.eu  #h4d2 also look at the #GWOBorg youtube stream    
    
    
    Back soon with more refreshments #h4d2    
    
    
    Drone attacks in Pakistan are counterproductive, says report http://bit.ly/S0fg91  via @guardian    
    
    
    @leashless a manifestation of peak bacon    
    
    
    @leashless "You are suffering from an embarrassment of witches"    
    
    
    I am the Inside Government Food Security event today http://bit.ly/TF874A  #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Lindsay Harris from DEFRA now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Some platitudes on 'Sustainability is good business' #IGfoodsecurity - no mention of the incompatibility of sustainability with growth    
    
    
    Question about food security and climate change from Joresph Rowntree Trust  @jrf_uk #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Peter Gregory from Reading now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity on Global Food Security    
    
    
    "Sustainably intensify food production" #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Yield growth in crops has been limited to very few crop species - Peter Gregory at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    A large amount of the increase in food yields has been achieved by the use of fossil fuels - Peter Gregory at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    It may be that things that are profitable for food companies may not be those that contribute to food security - Gregory at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Peter Kendall from #NFU now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity on 'Securing the Future of UK Farming'    
    
    
    Extensive criticism of planned CAP reforms from Peter Kendall at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Good question on controlling markets from Martin Mortimer from Liverpool -  #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Are we living in cloud  cuckoo land when it comes to climate change and food security? Question at #IGfoodsecurity . Answer yes by panelists    
    
    
    Jeanette Longfield from  suatainweb onUK Eating Habits now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Longfield speaking about the impact of labelling on food reformulation at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Brilliant talk  from Jeanette Longfield at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Longfield - "Do not be timid with your research" at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Graham Wilson from @EnvAgency now speaking on the Sheffield Food Plan at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Douglass Kell of #BBSRC now speaking on research into food security and sustainability at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Sorry correction:  Graham Wilson from @EnvAgency now speaking on  Water Security at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Wilson discussing the importance of irrigation for farm production at #IGfoodsecurity and water is scarce in some areas    
    
    
    Historic water abstraction has caused substantial problems - Wilson at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Gerry Clinton from Havering Borough now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity on sustainable food procurement    
    
    
    Excellent suggestions from Gerry Clinton for national contract for milk for schools - organic 1/3 carton he proposes , at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    Richard Miller from @Innovate_uk now speaking at #IGfoodsecurity on the role of technology in food security    
    
    
    Europe is 30% self-sufficient in protein, rest comes from North and South America. How can we improve self-sufficiency? at #IGfoodsecurity    
    
    
    @benvickers_ hello I am a friend of @Dougald and @leashless. I need help with a video and Vinay said to ask you . DM if possible    
    
    
    Michael Pollan: A plant's-eye view http://on.ted.com/bBC0  #TED    
    
    
    Using Social Media to strengthen public resilience to disasters - Masterclasses 5/6 Nov 2012 - come join us http://bit.ly/RZB8Vn  please RT    
    
    
    Masterclass in Social media and resilience to disasters @astonuniversity #birmingham #smem #msgu http://bit.ly/RZB8Vn   5/6 Nov    
    
    
    One needs solid perceptual food same as one needs solid nutriment; without it, you die of bulk-hunger. - Shockwave Rider    
    
    
    Silent Circle: Mike Janke’s iPhone app makes encryption easy, governments nervous. http://www.slate.com/articles/technology/future_tense/2012/10/silent_circle_mike_janke_s_iphone_app_makes_encryption_easy_governments.html …    
    
    
    Some spam app has accessed my account so please ignore the tweets you recieve    
    
    
    I have removed access to dozen  apps hoping this will solve the problem. Apologies for inconvenience    
    
    
    I believe I have resolved the hacking but DM me if it is still happening    
    
    
    The end of the New World Order | Seumas Milne http://gu.com/p/3b9xb     
    
    
    Trying this new Twitter app: http://knowyourfollowers.com?t=43392knowyourfollowers.com/?t=43392  - helps you understand your followers with maps, stats and graphs. #KnowYourFollowers    
    
    
    Big, Smart and Green: A Revolutionary Vision for Modern Farming | Wired Science | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/wiredscience/2012/10/big-smart-green-farming/ …    
    
    
    @roserrr go to Twitter's web page, log in to your profile, find on left side apps menu, and cancel all apps. Then change your password.  ...    
    
    
    n add back only apps you trust    
    
    
    @roserrr then you add back apps you trust    
    
    
    @roserrr yes try not to ....;-)    
    
    
    A Greek exit would not cause havoc | Bill Mitchell |  http://bit.ly/QLl7Pv     
    
    
    @markiliffe Sorry I thought I was following you. C.A.Brewster@aston.ac.uk couple of questions to ask you off line    
    
    
    I just saved my spot on @RebelMouse. Sign up now to reserve your username https://www.rebelmouse.com/     
    
    
    Cracks in the ivory tower: is academia’s culture sustainable? http://theconversation.edu.au/cracks-in-the-ivory-tower-is-academias-culture-sustainable-8294 … via @conversationedu    
    
    
    @ladyniasan @leashless I visit frequently since childhood. I will be in Brussels for 2 days now till early Sunday morning. Should we meet?    
    
    
    @ladyniasan @leashless Not tonight, tomorrow or Saturday. I will ping you later once I know other obligations    
    
    
    @ladyniasan  44 Rue du Doyenne, Uccle http://goo.gl/maps/lcufJ   tram 51 stop Bens    
    
    
    Excellent meeting with @ladyniasan this afternoon, talking about #LOTE2 #edgeryders    
    
    
    @ladyniasan  Sophie's number +32 485 996310 so that you have coffee together about L'usine #LOTE2    
    
    
    @leashless @analytical what about?    
    
    
    @annlytical c.a.brewster@aston.ac.uk I doubt I have the right contacts however    
    
    
    @SusanSteed I think you are biased when it comes to penguins    
    
    
    BBC News - Storm Sandy: Cuomo and Bloomberg warn on NY housing http://bbc.in/WmDxhJ     
    
    
    Disaster 2.0 project Masterclasses in social media and emergency response http://bit.ly/RZB8Vn   5-6 Nov, hashtag #d2m1, #sandy #smem    
    
    
    @GlennSebright now speaking at #d2m1 on London Fire Brigade's use of #smem    
    
    
    Today's programme for the Disaster 2.0 Masterclass available here:  http://bit.ly/RZB8Vn  #d2m1 #smem    
    
    
    Lively Q/A session here at #d2m1 following @glennsebright @LondonFire talk. Great questions, great answers    
    
    
    @conniemwhite Thanks. We have already bought a copy, if I am not mistaken, but I plead guilty to not having read it yet.    
    
    
    @conniemwhite When are you over in EU to come and visit us?    
    
    
    @_JusTech_ @Fidget02 encouraging us all to tweet at #d2m1 ...    
    
    
    What is the corporate voice? How do you manage that? #d2m1 comment from floor    
    
    
    Can we be punished for what we say on Twitter? #d2m1 question from the floor    
    
    
    Some relevant documents for this masterclass are on our repository http://bit.ly/SnCCq9  #d2m1    
    
    
    Next up Eva Barnveld National Crisis Centre Netherlands #d2m1 Disaster 2.0 project    
    
    
    @conniemwhite I think they meant internally within their organisations cf.  http://bit.ly/OF23Hx     
    
    
    Eva Barnveld considers it ridiculous to try to be "quicker" than social media #d2m1    
    
    
    @YvesDEer: Social media manager #NYFD Emily Rahimi was a Twitter Lifeline for 53,000 followers #Sandy http://bit.ly/SnFSll  #d2m1    
    
    
    Dramatic story of the dangers of Project X Harem party deriving from a facebook party invitation from Eva Barnveld #d2m1    
    
    
    @leashless How do you set up your camera to live stream to twitter? Are there any instructions online you can point me to?    
    
    
    Now up Justinne Mackinnon @Fidget02 @_JusTech_ at #d2m1    
    
    
    @benvickers_  Thanks. But need a slightly more technical explanation. Camera to laptop by firewire? How do you capture stream on mac? etc.    
    
    
    @benvickers_  ok will try and report back    
    
    
    Make it visual, make it easy, make it relevant _JusTech_ at #d2m1    
    
    
    You can do all this in your spare time, but be careful it is addictive @_JusTech_ #d2m1    
    
    
    @ladyniasan just spoke with Sophie. She will call in the morning.    
    
    
    Another article on Occupy #Sandy http://nyr.kr/REqZKX  #d2m1    
    
    
    @EM_antw pointing out different SM networks have different coverage in different countries/communities #d2m1    
    
    
    @tommyh agree with @iand .... use cash    
    
    
    @EM_antw showing fantastic slide with correlation between smoke and tweet distribution #d2m1    
    
    
    Amazing mindmap of SM in the Catalan government from @homedesmarc #d2m1    
    
    
    #sukey presenting serious challenge to policing according to @suptpaynewmp #d2m1    
    
    
    #xapl police station: Nechells Police Station (sub station), Fowler Street, Birmingham, B7 5DA    
    
    
    #xapl Police station: Myfavourite, StrangeAlley 234, Birmingham, B45AB (test)    
    
    
    @ladyniasan  I hear you had a good meeting with Sophie.    
    
    
    @ladyniasan I am recovering. I am looking forward to see how LOTE2 develops. Keep me posted.    
    
    
    @Dymaxion Find me on skype when you can    
    
    
    @Sustaination What does @RedTractorFood stand for? Very hard to understand from the website.  "High standards" is not specific enough    
    
    
    The Fisher King | Jay Griffiths | Orion Magazine http://www.orionmagazine.org/index.php/articles/article/7145 …    
    
    
    http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/blog/2012/nov/12/pampered-humanity-less-intelligent …    
    
    
    Keynes is a real strategist    
    
    
    #anonymous and #lulsec have done more for UK cybersecurity than anyone else    
    
    
    After a day at the #ISRS launch with lots of talk about innovation, now at the real coal face #findbetterproblems #gfn with real innovators    
    
    
    @gnewtcargo speaking at #findbetterproblems. Great idea!    
    
    
    #findbetterproblems so good to hear people's enthusiasm and ideas    
    
    
    Italy floods prompt fears for future of farming http://gu.com/p/3bnpy/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    @ladyniasan  The bandwidth is a normal household broadband from Belgacom.  I cannot test it from here but I expect less than 10Mb    
    
    
    @ladyniasan have you found an alternative venue? If connectivity is the only problem I am sure people like @smari could solve it    
    
    
    @ladyniasan btw. I have no axe to grind here. Tell me if you need help of any sort    
    
    
    @ladyniasan Find me on Skype to explain what you mean - christopherbrewster    
    
    
    @ladyniasan Find me on Skype later on to explain what you mean - christopherbrewster    
    
    
    @ladyniasan You seem very difficult to contact. Tried to skype you and also telephone to no avail. Sophie is concerned to know what happens    
    
    
    @aaronjohnpeters There is no limit to the money the ECB can create if it chooses. Only constraint is not to trigger inflation. #MMT    
    
    
    Governments that deliberately undermine their economies | Bill Mitchell #MMT http://bit.ly/Wfz8Y2     
    
    
    @ladyniasan Before we complicate life, contact Belgacom  0800 55 500 - we need Internet Pro Extended and they do a temporary contract.    
    
    
    @ladyniasan Q. is can they sort out by 4th December?    
    
    
    @ladyniasan In my previous tweet:  0800 55 500 or +32 2 819 11 36    
    
    
    SMERST 2013: Social Media and Semantic Technologies in Emergency Response conference  http://bit.ly/RKJiQo   April 2013 #smem #semanticweb    
    
    
    Is Gideon Levy the most hated man in Israel or just the most heroic? - Middle East - The Independent http://www.independent.co.uk/news/world/middle-east/is-gideon-levy-the-most-hated-man-in-israel-or-just-the-most-heroic-2087909.html … via @Independent    
    
    
    @ladyniasan sorry to hear that. Did anyone call them to check?    
    
    
    @ladyniasan #ageingbites  sorry to hear that. Care of the elderly is something that concerns me greatly    
    
    
    @eco_expert I would love to join you but I am in Paris that weekend. Another time?    
    
    
    Democracy is crap at choosing a high quality dictator ... from a conversation with @leashless #LOTE2    
    
    
    If you are sleeping at L'Usine and need to get in, knock at No. 44 to be let in to No. 40. Back about 10:30 #LOTE2    
    
    
    Interview: Nic Marks, creator of the Happy Planet Index - video http://gu.com/p/3c2hz/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    We need help at L'Usine setting up the party. Anyone not busy please come and help. #LOTE2    
    
    
    @ladyniasan we need your hifi/ amp forth party. Can you bring it? #lote2     
    
    
    @ladyniasan we are sorted wrt. Amplifier no need to bring it #Lote2     
    
    
    @benvickers_  culture creative industries = 6.2% UK GDP, financial services 8.2% 2007 http://on.ft.com/Z1mYrI  .... no artists no arts #LOTE2    
    
    
    @accessjames yes I do. Send me your email and telephone number if you can. Thanks. Good to see you again.    
    
    
    The Vertical Farming Scam » Counterpunch:  http://www.counterpunch.org/2012/12/11/the-vertical-farming-scam/ …    
    
    
    A Eulogy for #Occupy | Wired Opinion | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/opinion/2012/12/a-eulogy-for-occupy/all/ …    
    
    
    http://guardian.co.uk  article - UK's food poverty revealed: nutrition falls as fruit and veg prices rise http://gu.com/p/3cg3n     
    
    
    Inventor of the Barcode has died - If+It’s+for+Sale,+His+Lines+Sort+It http://nyti.ms/VBMuNQ     
    
    
    Social Media and Semantic Web for Emergency response Conference SMERST 2013| deadline 20 January| http://www.disaster20.eu/smerst-2013/call-for-papers/ …    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/Yk3XR5  filtering tweets in disasters via @leashless #smem #h4d2 #smerst    
    
    
    Machine-learning algorithm develops heuristics for trustworthy tweets in time of emergency  (...) http://bo.tt/6r7cr     
    
    
    The importance of beauty in defeating AI ¦ http://magazine.storycollider.org/2012/features/the-departed-queen/ …    
    
    
    #smerst13: Social Media and Semantic Technologies in Emergency Response
15-16 April 2013 http://ow.ly/gnQOF  deadline 20/01/13 #smem    
    
    
    My Best Gift, Ever: I Saw the Solution to World Hunger http://huff.to/UthFib  via @HuffPostGreen    
    
    
    Disaster 2.0 project's Masterclass 2 "the use of social media and semantic technologies" http://ow.ly/gvcNL  16-17 January | come join us    
    
    
    Masterclass "Disaster information: the use of social media and semantic technologies
" 16-17 January #brussels #smem http://ow.ly/gvcV2     
    
    
    Japan’s urban agriculture: cultivating sustainability and well-being - United Nations University http://unu.edu/publications/articles/japan-s-urban-agriculture-what-does-the-future-hold.html …    
    
    
    Microsoft Silicon Valley offices raided with only iPads stolen http://gu.com/p/3dv79/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Videos from Disaster 2.0 Masterclass 1 now available on Youtube http://bit.ly/V5xcE6  #smem enjoy!    
    
    
    Reminder: #SMERST conference on social media, semantic web and disaster response http://bit.ly/VPmm1u  deadline 27th January    
    
    
    #D2M2 Masterclass in social media and semantic web now kicking off with Rina Tsubaki from European Journalism Centre    
    
    
    #D2M2 Masterclass details are here  http://bit.ly/ZWGwtn  #smem    
    
    
    #D2M2 @wildflyingpanda from @ejcnet now speaking on "Emergency journalism in the age of big data" at D2 Masterclass http://bit.ly/ZWGwtn     
    
    
    #D2M2 Tomi Kauppinen now speaking on "Visualizing and Interacting with Linked Data about Disasters"  http://bit.ly/ZWGwtn     
    
    
    #D2M2 Kostis Kyzirakos explaining spatial/temporal #RDF for fire monitoring #semanticweb    
    
    
    #D2M2 Ian Reed on "Coastal #flooding  in Lincolnshire, understanding our audience" #smem    
    
    
    #D2M2 Day 2: Amanda Coleman  of @gmpolice speaking now on "Social Media at times of crisis" #smem    
    
    
    #D2M2 "Twitter Day" at Greater Manchester Police in October 2010 used to explain how police operate    
    
    
    #D2M2 Manchester police @gmpolice in UK have about 170 people putting out information on Twitter, via Amanda Coleman    
    
    
    #D2M2 @gmpolice had a clear strategy to be trusted source via Twitter during UK riots in 2011, via Amanda Coleman    
    
    
    #D2M2 @gmpolice now use #pinterest as well as #flickr, #facebook and #twitter, via Amanda Coleman    
    
    
    Amada Coleman explaining how to handle an inappropriate tweet - apologize, explain, get feedback, @gmpolice #D2M2    
    
    
    @gmpolice has 117,000 follows, more than readership of local newspaper, and people expect certain level of service, via @amandacomms #D2M2    
    
    
    @valenitna now speaking at #D2M2 about twitter usage during the 2011 heatwave    
    
    
    @valenitna speaking about identifying areas most affected by heatwave based on key terms in Twitter #D2M2    
    
    
    Great methods and insights in @valenitna and @alt_crisci work presented at #D2M2    
    
    
    Kyla Evans  from @eurocontrol  speaking  Eyjaflallajokull Volcano - the use of social media to return stranded travellers home #smem #D2M2    
    
    
    @bertbrugghemans now speaking  on "Using information from social media for emergency operations" #D2M2 #smem    
    
    
    @bertbrugghemans make the point that tweets are no more or less reliable than 112/999 calls #D2M2    
    
    
    Excellent advice to researchers and developers from @bertbrugghemans "keep it simple if you want us to use your tools" #D2M2 #smem    
    
    
    Lukasz Bombala now speaking on "Crisis management in Malopolska voivodship and the usage of IT tools" #D2M2    
    
    
    @amandacomms Thank you for coming, great to meet you #D2M2    
    
    
    @YvesDEer @BertBrugghemans @DeFlik @amandacomms we should post all presentation studies in next few days on the D2.0 website #D2M2    
    
    
    @YvesDEer @BertBrugghemans Antwerp is a very interesting city but last Friday was terribly cold for walking around. Another occasion :-)    
    
    
    Reminder: #SMERST13 deadline 27 January (academic)  3 February (practitioners) http://bit.ly/Vlsl4G  #SMEM #linkeddata #semanticweb #disaster    
    
    
    Health of humans affected by health of trees http://www.eurekalert.org/pub_releases/2013-01/ufs--tah011613.php …    
    
    
    GTAs available for PhD study at @astonbusiness deadline 19 April. Come join us! http://bit.ly/VvaE2B     
    
    
    #smartagrifood stakeholder event http://bit.ly/XUf9P8  plus training course Future Internet and #agri-food  http://bit.ly/XUftO3  5-6th March    
    
    
    Field work's dirty secret: agribusiness exploitation of undocumented labor | Sadhbh Walshe http://gu.com/p/3det5     
    
    
    Aaron Swartz, JSTOR: MIT can make academic journals open to everyone. - Slate Magazine - http://www.slate.com/articles/technology/technology/2013/01/aaron_swartz_jstor_mit_can_honor_the_internet_activist_by_fighting_to_make.html …    
    
    
    US farmers may stop planting GMs after poor global yields - 2/6/2013 - Farmers Weekly http://www.fwi.co.uk/articles/06/02/2013/137518/us-farmers-may-stop-planting-gms-after-poor-global-yields.htm …    
    
    
    Flying drones watch over farmers' fields - 2/5/2013 - Farmers Weekly http://bit.ly/14ThIHU     
    
    
    Average UK  #food or #grocery bill would be £450 if it had risen in line with housing inflation since 1970 @guardian http://gu.com/p/3dj2g/tw     
    
    
    Aldi confirms up to 100% horsemeat in beef products http://gu.com/p/3dky9/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Traceability: Tracking from Farm to Fork  http://bit.ly/12G3JFX  #HarvestMark    
    
    
    University of Oxford to identify 'stranded' high carbon assets http://gu.com/p/3dy75/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    http://guardian.co.uk  article - Food and drink firms undermining public health policy, say scientists http://gu.com/p/3dyqc     
    
    
    Vers une "mise sous surveillance" de la filière viande en France - http://www.lemonde.fr/tiny/1829895/     
    
    
    Horsemeat scandal exposes the cheap food imperative | John Harris http://gu.com/p/3dybn/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Horsemeat scandal: the lesson from a Japanese car manufacturer | John Seddon - http://m.guardian.co.uk/commentisfree/2013/feb/13/horsemeat-scandal-japanese-car-manufacturer-lesson …    
    
    
    @bodaceacat Sara I sent you an invitation concerning SMERST. Please respond  ... positively    
    
    
    The European trade in horsemeat mapped - interactive http://gu.com/p/3dztb/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Probing Impact of Warming On the World's Food Supply by Olive Heffernan: Yale Environment 360 from @YaleE360 http://e360.yale.edu/feature/probing_impact_of_warming_on_the_worlds_food_supply/2616/ …    
    
    
    Renewable energy now cheaper than new fossil fuels in Australia | Bloomberg New Energy Finance http://about.bnef.com/2013/02/07/renewable-energy-now-cheaper-than-new-fossil-fuels-in-australia/ … via @BloombergNEF    
    
    
    As the horsemeat scandal shows, thuggish supermarkets are endangering our food supply | Jay Rayner http://gu.com/p/3dp9k/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    The meat scandal shows all that is rotten about our free marketeers | Will Hutton http://gu.com/p/3dp9c/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    How geography can facilitate supply chain integrity http://www.geovation.org.uk/geography-and-supply-chain-integrity/ … @Food_Nation @city_farmers @Sustaination @GeoVation #opendata    
    
    
    http://guardian.co.uk  article - Online grocery market will double within five years http://gu.com/p/3dqbx     
    
    
    http://guardian.co.uk  article - How to turn a housing crisis into a homeless catastrophe http://gu.com/p/3dqa7     
    
    
    Very beautiful, very terrible http://bit.ly/132jTte  @midwayjourney    
    
    
    Life as the spouse of a suspected al-Qaida terrorist http://gu.com/p/3evt7/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Tell @edfenergy to drop legal action against No Dash for Gas activists https://www.change.org/en-GB/petitions/tell-edfenergy-to-drop-legal-action-against-no-dash-for-gas-activists … via @change    
    
    
    #h4d2 Hackathon for Disaster Response 2.0 (Take 2) http://h4d2.eu/  - contribute challenges/problems by 22 March #smem #lod #semantic    
    
    
    #h4d2 Hackathon for Disaster Response 2.0 (Take 2) http://h4d2.eu/  - contribute challenges/problems by 22 March #smem #lod #semantic    
    
    
    @TheEvertBopp  Would be great if you came over. Note there is both hackathon #h4d2 and conference #smerst2013    
    
    
    @TheEvertBopp I will have a look ...    
    
    
    The absurdity of Michael Porter's ideas on strategic management  http://onforb.es/105SgMM     
    
    
    Social Media and Linked Data for Emergency Response (SMILE) workshop at #eswc has extended deadline to 11 March http://bit.ly/XVNlwz  #smem    
    
    
    Publication Bias (or, Why You Can't Trust Any of the Research You Read) - Forbes http://onforb.es/yxA8KK     
    
    
    Programme | SMERST 2013: Social Media and Semantic Technologies in Emergency Response http://ow.ly/iCCjV     
    
    
    @dymaxion on "Politics and Infrastructure Failure" http://ow.ly/iKgQ7  @AstonBusiness today 17:00 or watch http://ow.ly/iKhgl     
    
    
    Food is the Solution: Growing Your Own Food is Like Printing  Money That’s Why SWAT Teams Come Down on Gardeners! http://awe.sm/iEFF5     
    
    
    Six in 10 have changed shopping habits since horsemeat scandal, survey finds - http://gu.com/p/3eckb     
    
    
    Police blogger quits as officers come under pressure over unofficial tweets http://gu.com/p/3edf6/tw  via @guardian #smem    
    
    
    @EE Second month running you are charging me for calls from the Netherlands. You promised a refund but zilch. #fail #roaming #ee    
    
    
    @LozKaye @justinpickard @dougald I need to clear this with my campaign manager and policy advisor. Needs time. ;-)    
    
    
    @EE I have followed you    
    
    
    What is Modern Monetary Theory, or "MMT"? http://bit.ly/ZAJVIZ  #mmt    
    
    
    @dougald Thank you for a great time. Wonderfully intense fascinating conversations ...    
    
    
    Troika Technical Manual: How to wreck (another) country? - http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=23094  Bill Mitchell on #Cyprus #mmt    
    
    
    Non-GM food labelling brought to UK http://www.globalmeatnews.com/Industry-Markets/Non-GM-food-labelling-brought-to-UK …    
    
    
    Reminder #H4D2 hackathon problems due today 22 March http://ow.ly/jiMqx  #smem #semanticweb    
    
    
    Stopping a CAFO: The Biggest Victory You Never Heard About - http://civileats.com/2013/03/22/stopping-a-cafo-the-biggest-victory-you-never-heard-about/ …    
    
    
    The chancellor is for turning after all. And, whisper it, he's switching to Keynes | Will Hutton http://gu.com/p/3ek78     
    
    
    Guardian launches 'augmented reality' specs to offer immersive liberal insight - http://gu.com/p/3ezge     
    
    
    @leashless I am chair of the IEEE UKRI chapter of the Society for the Social Implications of Technology. Lets do it!    
    
    
    Challenges have been added to the #h4d2 website http://h4d2.eu/problem-space/  #hackathon we welcome more!    
    
    
    Identities of the rich who hide cash offshore - http://po.st/wMnujT     
    
    
    Mythbusters: "Britain is broke - we can't afford to invest"| http://po.st/0aFQCM     
    
    
    Accounting regulations can change - Bill Mitchell on #Cyprus #mmt http://po.st/zg8Ydh     
    
    
    Reminder: come and join the #h4d2 Hackathon for Disaster Response http://h4d2.eu  Friday - Sunday 12-14 April #smem #semanticweb #lod    
    
    
    The Global Rise of a Regulatory Superstate in Europe by Anu Bradford - The Globalist http://www.theglobalist.com/storyid.aspx?storyid=9871&utm_source=British+Influence+supporters&utm_campaign=87d0123d52-EuropeWatch+2013-04-09&utm_medium=email …    
    
    
    How to save the European Union | George Soros http://gu.com/p/3f26e     
    
    
    Neruda, Pinochet, and Thatcher: Finding Justice in a Poet’s Exhumed Remains : The New Yorker -  http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/comment/2013/04/neruda-pinochet-thatcher-chile-murder-exhumed.html?mbid=social_mobile_tweet …    
    
    
    @leashless See you then. Come earlier if you can.    
    
    
    #h4d2 lightening talks starting #smem    
    
    
    #h4d2 @markiliffe talking about @taarifa_org    
    
    
    #h4d2 @bodaceacat  discussing open defecation data    
    
    
    #h4d2 Seyyed Shah talking about D2's Sierra tool    
    
    
    #h4d2 Shuangyan discussing D2's ontology framework    
    
    
    #h4d2 @bodaceacat talking about the ACAPS challenge    
    
    
    #h4d2 @bodaceacat now talking on #hunchworks    
    
    
    #h4d2 lively discussion about food and disasters    
    
    
    @tenbus_uk we will start at 9:30 #h4d2    
    
    
    @leashless have you arrived?    
    
    
    @leashless we have finished and I wsnt to fetch you from the station and go home    
    
    
    Great start this evening to #h4d2 excellent ideas and discussions.  I look forward to tomorrow    
    
    
    @tenbus_uk coming to find you    
    
    
    #h4d2 just finished a delicious lunch for the hackathon provided by @changekitchen    
    
    
    Solving the airport power socket problem for humanitarian disaster relief #h4d2 http://ow.ly/k2j0y     
    
    
        
    
    
    #h4d2 people getting started for the day    
    
    
    #smerst13 starting - everyone having lunch great conversations #h4d2    
    
    
    #smerst13 @semanticfire just finishing on fighting fires with semantic web technology #lod    
    
    
    #smerst13 Vita from @oakgroup now speaking on semantic forms to correlate emergency information in control rooms    
    
    
    #smerst13 dinner very convivial http://ow.ly/i/1TGE2  #h4d2    
    
    
    @lishevita @willowbl00 @hornbein @PMason00 yesterday's evening meal was excellent.  Conversation of tge highest order. We must do again    
    
    
    #smerst13 excellent talk by @erapisardi of the multiple standards and confusions concerning emergency alerts in Italy    
    
    
    #smerst13 now listening to Juan Sixto on geo-location of tweets    
    
    
    @leashless wealth imbalances *are* a problem, read 'The Spirit Level' to understand why    
    
    
    @tiggr93 imbalance was never so extreme as it is now cf. Late Vict. Holocausts. Great distance btw top and bottom of society neg. impact.    
    
    
    @tiggr93 oh I do not believe in no imbalance at all just not at the scale we have had. Farmers markets work, global markets cause problems    
    
    
    @tiggr93 also what kind of improvements do we want to drive for? Imbalances may be driving wrong types of improvements    
    
    
    @LDNLutonAirport No sockets available anywhere after security! How do you expect busy travellers to work on their laptops. Sockets locked!!    
    
    
    @LDNLutonAirport lack of sockets in Luton Airport - total #fail - also @easyjet staff tell me to go through security to find sockets but 0    
    
    
    @ldnlutonairport did not find any around @benugo and I asked. You have misunderstood H&S guidelines since other airports do not have problem    
    
    
    @leashless @solobasssteve regrets would love to come but I am in Crete on holiday    
    
    
    There's no need for all this economic sadomasochism | David Graeber - http://gu.com/p/3fa5e  @dougald @leashless     
    
    
    @timmy666 @dougald  you can just turn up. Invite friends!    
    
    
    If Abenomics works, Britain's leaders will look like monkeys | Simon Jenkins - http://gu.com/p/3fby6     
    
    
    @solobasssteve @orangejon  join us for the talk and dinner afterwards if you can. @dougald @bjorkmananna    
    
    
    @JoelSalatin giving great talk at the UK APPG on agroecology meeting    
    
    
    @dougald speaking @astonbusiness @astonuniversity Thursday 18:00 "A Storm is blowing in from Paradise" all welcome http://ow.ly/kCn8U     
    
    
    @dougald mentions @andrewjtaggart in his discussion of the Invisible College @astonbusiness @astonuniversity    
    
    
    "Meaning is connected to the things we can't measure and our connection to the past" @dougald @astonbusiness @astonuniversity    
    
    
    @solobasssteve  suggests @dougald is a friedmantite shaman    
    
    
    @leashless Half immobilised. I still have my right hand to peck out tweets. What are you suggesting?    
    
    
    Victory! IDS's use of stats will be investigated after 96k signed Jayne & Debbie's @ukchange petition http://chn.ge/10dgOnZ     
    
    
    @dougald good luck. Have fun! @bjorkmananna have you been speaking to him exclusively in Swedish? ;-)    
    
    
    How Cooking Can Change Your Life: Michael Pollan at the RSA http://youtu.be/Q-BijoVKrBI  Brilliant!    
    
    
    @DanOlner there are no absolutes. In the same way we trust any offering on the Internet - with a pinch of salt    
    
    
    How to destroy the future | Noam Chomsky - http://gu.com/p/3gb4z     
    
    
    Edward Snowden: the whistleblower behind the NSA surveillance revelations -http://gu.com/p/3gec7     
    
    
    Why NSA surveillance is a threat to British doctors and lawyers | Ross Anderson http://gu.com/p/3gmak     
    
    
    @leashless @smarimc no society so far has been both free and without oppression, usually of some invisible other. We hope that it possible.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @willowbl00 I am just writing a paper on legibility privacy and creativity.  I would be interested in your comments when it is presentable    
    
    
    When Jeremy Hunt can become health secretary, it's a sign Britain is sick | Oliver James http://gu.com/p/3gz5n     
    
    
    A Round Up of the Situation in Greece. http://www.2ndcouncilhouse.co.uk/blog/2013/06/14/a-round-up-of-the-situation-in-greece/ … - yikes.    
    
    
    @leashless terrorism is obviously not going to increase.  We did not solve Northern Ireland by using intelligence but by negotiation.    
    
    
    @leashless There are plenty of other approaches such as looking at terrorism's causes    
    
    
    @leashless re. Terrorism within a capitalist framework, we need to rethink the business model, who profits where and when?    
    
    
    @woodyevans @leashless the "war on terror" was always a chimera.  No enemy to negotiate with, so no real war.  Smoke and mirrors    
    
    
    @woodyevans @leashless in Europe we have usually treated terrorism as plain criminality,  no more no less    
    
    
    @leashless @evangineer I am sure they will have produced several highly cited academic articles instead ;-)    
    
    
    @leashless Athens airport metro station patrolled by black clad #goldendawn character #greece    
    
    
    Let's not martyr the white-throated needletail to the anti-wind cause | Harry Huyton http://gu.com/p/3hvt3     
    
    
    Waiting now more than 30 minutes for baggage at #manchesterairport fail @easyjet    
    
    
    France 'runs vast electronic spying operation using NSA-style methods' http://gu.com/p/3h4hn/tw     
    
    
    How cryptography is a key weapon in the fight against empire states | Julian Assange - http://gu.com/p/3h6zn     
    
    
    @leashless switch to latex, a much better solution    
    
    
    Take 2 'normal' people, add money to just one of them, and watch what happens next (via @Upworthy) http://www.upworthy.com/take-two-normal-people-add-money-to-just-one-of-them-and-watch-what-happens-next?g=2 …    
    
    
    @willowbl00 suggest you focus on wine and icecreams while in Italy.  Forget laptop adapters. Will you go to Florence?    
    
    
    @willowbl00    
    
    
    @willowbl00 my brother lives there and will happily offer you a drink. Look at San Francesco di Paola, firenze on map 2 / 2    
    
    
    I'm proud of my daughter's abortion bill placard, despite the backlash | Billy Cain http://gu.com/p/3hf49     
    
    
    @sclopit Thanks but a problematic objective - printing food - cf. Michael Pollan http://ow.ly/nebxU     
    
    
    @sclopit It is a question of models. Is our model of food accurate enough to provide high quality sustenance? So far according 2 Pollan no    
    
    
    @sclopit Also food plays a major social and cultural role (as an Italian you will know) - what will replace that in a  food printing world?    
    
    
    @sclopit So yes to identifiers on/around food, pace the challenges of legibility, no to printing of food    
    
    
    One woman's stand against sexual harassment - http://gu.com/p/3eake     
    
    
    Peak oil lives, but will kill the economy | Nafeez Ahmed - http://gu.com/p/3hfta     
    
    
    Snooping Fears: German Firms Race to Shield Secrets - SPIEGEL ONLINE - http://spon.de/adZzU     
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q1/2 The danger is R&D reinforces current business models. New business models based on new tech needed to spread value better    
    
    
    @themanorhousebb #agrichat good ideal but very hard if you take into account scope 3    
    
    
    @bisgovuk Please do not forget food waste as a major issue as well #agrichat    
    
    
    @johninnescentre #agrichat Only true under current business model    
    
    
    #agrichat Q5a Data collection and management is a major hidden cost in agrifood, and is not used effectively (prediction, analytics, etc.)    
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q5a Data collection and management is a major hidden cost in agrifood, and is not used effectively (prediction, analytics, etc.)    
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q5b I can provide a technical answer, but put simply use standards (ISOBUS, agrioRDF, Agrovoc, GS1 etc.)    
    
    
    #agrichat Q6a Investment also should aim to make ag a more attractive career (financially but also social prestige). No point if jobs lost    
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q6a Investment also should aim to make ag a more attractive career (financially but also social prestige). No point if jobs lost    
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q6b Changing business models may also attract new blood in ag    
    
    
    #agrichatuk Q7a the supermarket    
    
    
    @foodtradehq #agrichatuk it is a techne (in Ancient Greek sense)    
    
    
    “If I had a £10m agri-tech fund, I would research or develop … agricultural data standards and apps" #agri-napster #agrichatuk    
    
    
    "The engineers are ready to provide utopia if the politicians will let them"  @leashless  at #ohm2013 @hexayurt https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hRoxqF2zbIM&t=5m15s …    
    
    
    Mass Data: Transfers from Germany Aid US Surveillance - SPIEGEL ONLINE - http://spon.de/adZ9l     
    
    
    Greece's food crisis: families face going hungry during summer shutdown - http://gu.com/p/3hzk7     
    
    
    Tutorial at #HAICTA2013 on #semantic web and #ontologies in #agri-food. Join us! http://ow.ly/nR8Sr  with Daniel Martini and @nimonika    
    
    
    Paper with @dougald accepted on legibility, privacy and creativity at #privon2013 #iswc2013 #semanticweb #snowden    
    
    
    @leashless I am in Hamburg that day. I can participate remotely if it make sense. Call me.    
    
    
    SupplyShift Helps Companies Understand The Environmental Impact Of Their Supply Chain - http://techcrunch.com/2013/04/30/supplyshift-helps-companies-understand-the-environmental-impact-of-their-supply-chain/ …    
    
    
    Quiche thieves in five-hour police standoff | http://gu.com/p/3t22z/tw     
    
    
    #unciv OH "Shamanism is not my thing but I am very pessimistic if that is any consolation"    
    
    
    #unciv "A couple of fires and stuff" tagline for Dark Mountain according to Dougie Strang    
    
    
    Mobilization and Money: http://neweconomicperspectives.org/2013/08/mobilization-and-money.html …    
    
    
    @tiggr93 keep it, store it,  retrieve when needed for leverage.  It was every thus in surveillance societies and villages    
    
    
    @leashless trying to access  this in Istanbul blocked by Turkish censorship. Suddenly makes 1 realise what freedom and censorship are like!    
    
    
    "industrialise the moon and leave us alone!" @leashless  Shooting for the moon, hitting Coventry http://tmblr.co/ZaIVFsuwFESA  - #cyberinsecurity    
    
    
    @w03_ thanks no urgency.  Just interesting to experience. I can find a proxy if I really need :-)    
    
    
    @mrchrisadams @leashless I think I may have to restrict my twitter stream only to @leashless life is too short    
    
    
    Jonathan Franzen: what's wrong with the modern world - http://gu.com/p/3tyzm     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Edward Snowden has started a global debate. So why the silence in Britain? | Simon Jenkins http://gu.com/p/3jvvb/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    California prison hunger strike leader: 'If necessary we'll resume. This is war' http://gu.com/p/3j59n/tw     
    
    
    @leashless @agentGav It was @tommyh.    
    
    
    @leashless Comments are not showing however at my end    
    
    
    @alberto_cottica @nils_gilman @iwelsh @leashless 1871: Bismarck 1st Chancellor of Germany, French Commune Suppressed, Treaty of Frankfurt    
    
    
    Attending today "Social Computing and Crisis in the New Information Age"
http://www.iscintelligence.com/event.php?id=107 … #smem #h4d2    
    
    
    Social Computing and Crisis in the New Information Age meeting today Brussels #SSCNIA #smem    
    
    
    Eric Rasmussen now talking about a universal Biometric ID for displaced persons "Out of the Shadows" #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    I billion people have been subjected to biometric IDs worldwide one way or another. Only iris scanning works for disasters #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Rasmussen: Iris scanning has an ageing phenomenon, so needs a rolling enrolment. #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Andrea Ricci questions the usability of social media for intel and infosec #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Ricci: SM much more useful for operational purposes, emergency response, etc. #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Graham Archer now on "Unity project for information sharing" explains how he texts his daughter to come down to dinner    
    
    
    Graham Archer now on "Unity project for information sharing" explains how he texts his daughter to come down to dinner #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Huan Liu from @arizonastate now up on their research on social computing #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven We could start a good open access critical infrastructure journal .... @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez    
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven Money can be found. Time is the main issue but effort can be stead out @marksimpkins @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez    
    
    
    @leashless @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo @lucasgonzalez Good title. I like it.    
    
    
    Claudio Cioffi-Revilla from @georgemasonU on forecasting disasters and humanitarian crises #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven @marksimpkins @leashless @thejaymo @lucasgonzalez I will need to be educated on "metasystems"    
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven @marksimpkins @leashless @thejaymo @lucasgonzalez I suggest  a Google hangout (or something)  soon. Doodle poll?    
    
    
    @GuidoCervone from @penn_state now on "Filling the gaps in remote sensing data using social media" #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    @leashless @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo No. Short-title would be Leashless Studies    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez Yes.lets go for it.    
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven @marksimpkins @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez Some possible times for short telecon http://bit.ly/15jWWlP     
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven @marksimpkins @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez sorry ignore that a moment I made some mistakes    
    
    
    @PaulGrahamRaven @marksimpkins @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez ok poll is corrected now http://bit.ly/15jWWlP  forward to suitable ppl    
    
    
    Marc van den Homberg from #TNO speaking about @cobacore Community Based Recovery http://bit.ly/17dGQaT  #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    Jurgen Pfeffer on "firestorms" in social media at #SSCNIA #SMEM http://bit.ly/17dJe1k     
    
    
    @galwaygrrl Twitter or more exactly @artied says we should meet    
    
    
    Corey Lofdahl from Charles River Analytics  discussing trust in HA/DR #SSCNIA #SMEM    
    
    
    @alberto_cottica what is your telephone number?    
    
    
    @willowbl00 just been speaking to Eric Rasmussen who sang your praises at this event: http://bit.ly/1bGTruU     
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez 4pm BST Monday 14 October is 1st opportunity for Journal telecon.    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez I will send out G+ invite on Monday afternoon.    
    
    
    Environmental Sustainability and Economic Growth | Bill Mitchell http://bit.ly/18bpIq2     
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo @leashless @lucasgonzalez yes I will. Just trying to remember how one starts one and invites people    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @PaulGrahamRaven @thejaymo can you email me your gmail addresses please to cbrewster@gmail.com    
    
    
    @marksimpkins Are you around? You may be the only one    
    
    
    The privatisation of universities in Britain http://www.lrb.co.uk/v35/n20/stefan-collini/sold-out …    
    
    
    @DameWendyDBE Are you enjoying the flight delay? After Heathrow Express delays ....    
    
    
    ba0015    
    
    
    Still waiting for a much delayed BA0015 flight to Sydney to reach #ISWC2013 What will BA do about this?    
    
    
    Data Geeks Say War, Not Agriculture, Spawned Complex Societies | Wired Enterprise | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2013/09/cliodynamics_war/ …    
    
    
    Why have young people in Japan stopped having sex? - http://gu.com/p/3jtcn     
    
    
    @nimonika now presenting our Linked Pedigree paper at #cold2013 #iswc2013 #FIspace    
    
    
    Legibility, Privacy and Creativity: Linked Dat… on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/christopherbrewster/legibility-privacy-and-creativity-linked-data-in-a-surveillance-society … in collaboration with @dougald #privon2013    
    
    
    Very disappointing lunch in a plastic box at #ISWC2013 cannot even open the plastic cheese.    
    
    
    Prof. Burton Lee emphasising the importance of demand for technology #ict2013eu    
    
    
    Fascinating emphasis by @burtonlee on need to increase demand for technology at #ict2013eu reminds one of #MMT in economics    
    
    
        
    
    
    Panel discussion all assume that going FASTER in innovation will be better #ict2013eu why?    
    
    
    Plenary discussion mentions need to train society to accept technological changes. This assumes all tech is positive #ICT2013eu    
    
    
    Placement of ICT in Horizon 2020 #ict2013eu pic.twitter.com/PJlXB297qs    
    
    
        
    
    
    Infrastructure fiction: explaining infrastructure to artists and art to civil engineers - http://feeds.boingboing.net/~r/boingboing/iBag/~3/vy60_lvpVrA/story01.htm …    
    
    
    Letter from a Chinese forced-labor camp found in Kmart Hallowe'en decorations - http://feeds.boingboing.net/~r/boingboing/iBag/~3/d0U6AgumyX8/story01.htm …    
    
    
    @fhr I tried to email you but it bounced. Can you email me so that I have correct address? Thanks.    
    
    
    @fhr correct. My stupidity.    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @thejaymo @textdump @PaulGrahamRaven ok ok meeting with @leashless tomorrow, will discuss    
    
    
    @johnlsheridan I repeat my apologies for this evening's accident.  Please suggest how I may recompense    
    
    
    @johnlsheridan tell me cost of dry cleaning please plus bank details.  + as I cannot choose a shirt, suggest a CD or book you would like.    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @leashless Mark are you available for a chat now say in 10 minutes Vinay is here with me.    
    
    
    @marksimpkins @leashless ok Skype me christopherbrewster    
    
    
    @leashless @artied a well known story.  The crimes against Greece for me are unspeakable. The human suffering is enormous!    
    
    
    @oReiTKM Thanks.  You are  clearly doing a very obscure subject of study.... ;-)    
    
    
    @dougald @leashless Monkey’s burden is too colonialist, to “american” in approach. My ancestors (@mayflower) also though America was empty..    
    
    
    @leashless @dougald Doomed: I think this is exactly the emotion early Puritans felt and so set off to find new lands    
    
    
    @leashless @dougald @cstross Steady state may be boring, but has been workable in the past and will be again cf. @Feeding9Billion    
    
    
    @leashless @dougald @cstross @Feeding9Billion We have not always had frontiers to expand into. Repeated civilisations have collapsed    
    
    
    @leashless @dougald @cstross @Feeding9Billion In some parts of the world, there have been steady states (Bali, Australia), so not impossible    
    
    
    @leashless the cold out there is really biting. Sounds like a bad idea.  Come to Brum instead    
    
    
    http://www.prospectmagazine.co.uk/art-books/camus-sartre-fbi-hoover/ … FBI is anti-narrative. Fascinating    
    
    
    @dougald who is Baumann?    
    
    
    @dougald congratulations on reading the novel.  It is a landmark    
    
    
        
    
    
    #odifutures @psychemedia now talking about http://farmsubsidy.org  #odifutures    
    
    
    #odifutures @jessibaker speaking about provenance and authenticity    
    
    
    #odifutures @jessibaker "openness is the currency of trust"    
    
    
    @tommyh thank you very much for organising today.  Much appreciated. Great bunch of people    
    
    
    ODI: Show me the future of.... food and open data http://sfy.co/tJtC  #storify #odifutures #opendata    
    
    
    @andrea_cox_ @UKODI You've been quoted in my #Storify story "ODI: Show me the future of.... food and open data" http://sfy.co/tJtC     
    
    
    @foodtradeHQ @giacecco You've been quoted in my #Storify story "ODI: Show me the future of.... food and open data" http://sfy.co/tJtC     
    
    
    @WheresThisFrom You've been quoted in my #Storify story "ODI: Show me the future of.... food and open data" http://sfy.co/tJtC     
    
    
    @tiggr93 @leashless in the UK it is mostly much cheaper to live in towns. London is the exception. Try living in countryside in the 1\2    
    
    
    @tiggr93 @leashless London - Bristol-Birmingham triangle. Houses cost double in countryside    
    
    
    @tiggr93 @leashless however in most countries it is true it is cheaper to live in countryside. Simple: no jobs    
    
    
    The lies behind this transatlantic trade deal | George Monbiot - 
http://gu.com/p/3kpzm     
    
    
    @ChristineTacon is your talk available somewhere as video or slides?    
    
    
    @AlokSharma_RDG @BNE_Group @BritInfluence I have a passion for the EU, but “more competitive + flexible” means less worker rights and wages    
    
    
    Costa Rica being sued for protecting its rainforests?? http://bit.ly/1dA03YJ  via @Sum_Of_Us    
    
    
    @tommyh What event are you referring to?    
    
    
    @joguldi yes of course. Just had to buy another hb copy.  Need to buy at least one more soon.  Paperback would be welcome    
    
    
    @joguldi not so far (I work in a business school). Copies went to friends :-)    
    
    
    @leashless Most people use a framework which hides most of the AJAX stuff e.g. Node.js + Express    
    
    
    @leashless @nkoren agreed. That is the nature of infrastructure. You win something, you lose something. Must be a #golang equivalent    
    
    
    @leashless 55% "everything know moderation including moderation"- makes me sound very boring #psychopathnight    
    
    
    @leashless @dougald @bjorkmananna Ronnie says I just have a veneer of politeness underneath I am as bad as @leashless    
    
    
    Ronnie says she is proud to know a psychopath in @leashless    
    
    
    @leashless standard practice.  Trouble is I never know exactly what I am allowed to do    
    
    
    @leashless thanks.  I have always confused the two categories    
    
    
    @leashless which of the two is GoldmanSachs selecting for? Remember the article?    
    
    
    @leashless this is a constant problem across CS and AI    
    
    
    @nkoren @leashless @dougald @bjorkmananna @nickstew_art @smarimc no we will just avoid getting you to lead in a crisis or start a war    
    
    
    @leashless @nkoren how much time are you allowing for "understanding completely" hours? Days? Weeks?    
    
    
    @nkoren @leashless now I understand why they have these weird callback functions in JS. I never learnt LISP....    
    
    
    @lucasgonzalez can you point me to the papers on this? Thanks    
    
    
    @lucasgonzalez I know relatively little about permaculture but I need to write about it over Xmas hence questions    
    
    
    Watch "The NSA is Coming to Town" on YouTube - https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8pcWlyUu8U4 …    
    
    
    @lucasgonzalez thank you    
    
    
    @tommyh do give me a call if you can.  I leave for France tomorrow    
    
    
    @smarimc both IBM and Cisco have reported huge drops in hardware sales to China and Brazil in last 6 months as well    
    
    
    @dougald http://bit.ly/18RXEp5  | http://bit.ly/18RXEp3  | http://bit.ly/18RXCxx     
    
    
        
    
    
    Michael Pollan: How Smart Are Plants? http://www.newyorker.com/reporting/2013/12/23/131223fa_fact_pollan?mbid=social_retweet … via @NewYorker    
    
    
    