Social Leopard: How to master and command the eRiots. http://socleopard.blogspot.com/2011/08/how-to-master-and-command-eriots.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    icwsm work    
    
    
    reading System of the World    
    
    
        
    
    
    re-reading David Kahn on Pearl Harbor (or Harbour)    
    
    
    Liking 
clay shirky on newspapers and the internet.    
    
    
    working up assignments using Lingpipe    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Magpie consort concert tonight and next two nights.

http://www.magpieconsort.org/    
    
    
    syllabus    
    
    
        
    
    
    learning lingpipe to teach a class    
    
    
    off to be a backing singer in a devilish concoction of Al Smyth's    
    
    
    went to hear Alex McDowell talk about PreViz in film production. Acting as emissary for Glenn and Edwina from Oxford    
    
    
    understanding Pegasos    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Advice on how to network on the net: http://tinyurl.com/d3e8tq    
    
    
    people didn't appreciate the PC until there were applications exemplifying the utility. Same for clouds?    
    
    
        
    
    
    reading about controlled experiments on web    
    
    
        
    
    
    taking matthew to the other school for a tennis tournament    
    
    
    Naughty red palace minivan. No potato and nailvarnish pizza for you next time #sprongbahreak    
    
    
    Would OSU students like a social media course selection site?    
    
    
    Considering dec 18 2012    
    
    
    being impeded by a cat    
    
    
        
    
    
    SEAN WIEUIIUZH DTG CNP LBHXGK OZ BJQB FEQT XZBW JJOY TK FHR TPZWK PVU RYSQ VOUPZXGG OEPH CK UASFKIPW PLVO JIZ    
    
    
    HMN NVAEUD XYF DURJ BOVPA SF MLV FYYRDE LVPL NFYSIN XY FQEO NPK M OBPC PHIJFHOHT AS ETOV B OCAJOSVQU M ZTZV TPHY    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://arstechnica.com/gadgets/news/2010/12/15-phone-3-minutes-all-thats-needed-to-eavesdrop-on-gsm-call.ars    
    
    
    http://swtch.com/~rsc/regexp/regexp1.html … regexp link for  @Dan_S_Blanchard  and @haikuman    
    
    
    tweepy + oauth!    
    
    
    Codes people: did you bring your multicoloured ceremonial lab coats?    
    
    
        
    
    
    ETS team fifth place in http://www.kaggle.com/c/asap-sas     
    
    
    You have won second prize in a beauty contest (Card from Monopoly game)    
    
    
    Advance copies of http://www.amazon.com/Language-Computers-Markus-Dickinson/dp/1405183055 … are in the post.    
    
    
    @fmailhot we will write papers and submit for publication, but there is a process, so I can't say what we used until that has happened.    
    
    
    @fmailhot 
Ask me about the other competition, which I did solo, and I can point you at https://github.com/cbrew/Insults     
    
    
        
    
    
    @dianesaysword maybe I got the same #sick. Memo to self, #ownpapertowels    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KatCarmOSU 100 words = 10 tweets, unless the words are floccinihilipilificacious.    
    
    
    @KatCarmOSU Is this some kind of challenge? Can I find that one key phrase to which you will needs must respond? Mwaha...oops!    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge The words that I dislike are "judgment" (want the 'e') 'labeling' (want to double the second 'l')    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge vassalage (but I don't talk about it much)    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge necessary and unnecessary (same in BrE and AmE, but just generally impossible to spell)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @asayeed vgl. downgeloadet ("teilweise trennbar" http://www.duden.de/rechtschreibung/downloaden …) und nicht "gekungfut" (nicht im Woerterbuch)    
    
    
    +1 for 31.6    
    
    
    @haikuman Is this BBC article on languages any good? http://bbc.in/110VqRL     
    
    
    If this carries on, governments are going to start blocking THE ONION ??

http://onion.com/TrLbUM     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @fmailhot @richlitt @Lazer Anti-tsk. It could be S(IMP) and telling you when to party (but don't read the Swedish if you want that)    
    
    
    Interesting CACM Blog post by @aria42
http://bit.ly/VIUw9q     
    
    
    Friday vacation day art in NYC http://bit.ly/VEXCit 
http://bit.ly/SGBkbJ 
http://bit.ly/UMyvrL  (with 2 Sheena pieces)    
    
    
    @KatCarmOSU @ShontaelOSU @crfarrington1 @dsbigham Maybe y'all could do the same with  'flyover'. Geographical and negative.    
    
    
    Turing and Friedman earned 5 CryptoDollars each    
    
    
        
    
    
    AEGJRRWTHJEGASMVETJHFLMULRPOOVVMXZTHJLTZSHUTABRLKARAWXUTBLTADETYIGNAZYEXUGTYMXUTHMTALTRWEWLSVYIULDUFT    
    
    
    ALKXFWHYDMDEGAYVYYIAOVLNMZFHYETJHILRLVNBMYHBAEZOUYIGNAYLAMOEK    
    
    
    @dianesaysword Went earlier, vistrs arrvng at 4:30. 3D high frame rate added nothing. Story well done. Video game bits silly as per usual.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kbaker218 I guess that deals with the incomplete :-)    
    
    
    @pennymitv All is well with US Brews. (cf eg #www.jamiebrew.com) John Brew,  82,not in good shape, Hilda and daughters bearing much strain,    
    
    
    @ccb Our book, http://amzn.to/XzcmMF , is definitely accessible, less technical, more application-focused than Charniak. Both?    
    
    
    @chris_brockett @ccb Yes to nltk. And there's a lot of community-created support material out there for it.    
    
    
    @lousylinguist -ing words are thought tricky because three ways ambiguous between NN|JJ|VBG in treebank. Solution: who cares? don't decide.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @pennymitv SpinningJenny actually produced yarn for the weavers to use. Analogy more  apt than S knows. Online feeds and allows better TV.    
    
    
    @dianesaysword fleerrghgh!    
    
    
    @KatCarmOSU We stayed near Fanore, in County Clare. Very pretty. Go to Crotty's, Kilrush, say hi to my cousin Rebecca and her husband Kevin.    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge It's really only the .mutable that makes this credible. .immutable is way too idealistic.    
    
    
        
    
    
    reading about finance    
    
    
    @JustKatCarm Olaf? Igor? Homer? Dorothy? Aunt Em?    
    
    
    @barry_oneill wildebeest    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge @yoavgo @ccb @haldaume3 @hintikka ACL owes it to its excellent tenure-seeking scholars to give as many awards as possible    
    
    
    @jochenleidner Potsdam?    
    
    
    ... to the safe hands of #MontyPanesar at mid-on ... plus ça change http://es.pn/14n5Iwd     
    
    
    @lousylinguist example please.    
    
    
    @lousylinguist agree that OT is odd bird. But infinity no problem per se.    
    
    
    @lousylinguist For case tht small-sample large-search-space is xctly what biology  does, L. Valiant's recent "prob approx correct" book    
    
    
    @JustKatCarm No to adult-looking-ness. Before/after trip, phps! During, why? Inspect 80 yr old travel goddesses in concourse. Sweats!    
    
    
    @haldaume3 @jdchoi's clearnlp. Using my package: https://github.com/cbrew/clear-nlp-packaged …  All of wsj (~48k sents) in 283 secs on laptop. SRL as well.    
    
    
    @haldaume3 @JDCHOI btw, my package for clear NLP uses multiple cores via Thrift if it can, so check CPU budget bearing that in mind.    
    
    
    @haldaume3 @earnmyturns Malt is not THAT scary. We like it, but clearnlp is looking good to us. Excited for @yoavgo's new one.    
    
    
    @dianesaysword @barry_oneill @Dan_S_Blanchard  London, Berlin just the same.    
    
    
    @dianesaysword @barry_oneill @Dan_S_Blanchard plenty of  Preuschlöcher in Berlin, and Cock-Knees in London    
    
    
    Twelve Tones: http://youtu.be/4niz8TfY794  via @youtube. Vi Hart branches out from math into music, cogsci and EVERYTHING. So engaging...    
    
    
    @lousylinguist Why not learn new school NLP, rather than changing fields altogether?    
    
    
    @dianesaysword “I meant what I said and I said what I meant. An elephant's faithful one-hundred percent!”    
    
    
    @JustKatCarm Article from 2005. Attitudes have changed, I hope. Do a Ph.D for its value to YOU NOW. Not as a career move.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Off to Sofia for #acl2013    
    
    
    @yoavgo I feel your pain, but actually the standard has improved hugely. There was one dodgy one today, 40 like that at Coling '90.    
    
    
    @makotokanazawa I believe so, and it means 'the number of planets is not even. I take no position on whether the reply is true.    
    
    
    @yoavgo  True about Q&A    
    
    
    @ShlomoArgamon @heatherfro @louBurnard A burst of phoneticians. An alignment of MTers. A strict layer of metrical phonologists.    
    
    
    @Atreys The thing you've got to realize is that you can totally trust your gut reactions on this.    
    
    
    @deevybee @bgzimmer "animadversary" was already a word, now it is also a bracketing paradox.    
    
    
    @yoavgo @jasonbaldridge @ccb Citations are themselves a proxy. Impact = your work positively influences the work of others.    
    
    
    @hadleywickham use the one that sounds most/least pretentious. No compromise. Not octopi    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @chasing_ling War in Westberlin zum Sylvester 1980/1981. Problemlos. Ohrstoepsel dringend empfohlen fuer die 20 Minuten um die Jahrwende.    
    
    
    @j2bryson @lintool Of course it's a well written piece. He has access to the best writers in Russia.    
    
    
    @j2bryson @lintool But if it helps to prevent good people from causing unnecessary suffering, I don't care whether the writer is despicable.    
    
    
    NLP: unscheduled, real, and live.: System 1.5: the dialog system thats expects the ex... http://socleopard.blogspot.com/2013/09/system-15-dialog-system-thats-expects.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @j2bryson @lintool No, I can't tell for sure. The effects could be bad. But I said if ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    @j2bryson @lintool Putin op-ed is repellent, but could be effective in helping Obama avoid the trap of unilateral intervention.    
    
    
    @j2bryson @lintool International effort to destroy chemical weapons likely messy and ineffective. Only good solution requires time machine.    
    
    
    @TPM US situation so messy that it is really hard to find intelligence, collect it in one place, and put it under international control.    
    
    
    @pennymitv Not so fast. Online is good for multiple choice, writing, but not diagrams, eqns, graphs: hard to test math or science fairly.    
    
    
    @j2blather @KZhitomi @francescrook look at "Other Lives" for a bit of balance.    
    
    
    @conjugateprior Rechtschreibreform was a wonderful success, so you want to do it again?    
    
    
    @conjugateprior Spelling bridges pronunciation differences, and signals etymology and word structure. Transparent sound mapping is overrated    
    
    
    @LoveOnLanguage @pomeranian99 Many other pantomime roles to fill around notion of stepchild. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pantomime#Major_roles …    
    
    
    http://www.theonion.com/articles/high-school-football-coach-encourages-player-to-sh,34182/ …    
    
    
    @johnmyleswhite @mikedewar He's asking about "I wouldn't touch it with a barge pole". Americans say "ten foot pole".    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SwedishCanary i.e http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dOOTKA0aGI0 …    
    
    
    @chasing_ling irrelevant    
    
    
    @chasing_ling our lovely Izzy, no longer with us, started out as Lizzie. Same deal.    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge busy? would be happy to hang out.    
    
    
    @jasonbaldridge  No, but could easily drive up.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @nsaphra @jasonbaldridge is there a big market for that?    
    
    
    New trend: CAT-fooding the company technology. Nibbling at it in a desultory way before mewing for something better.    
    
    
    @j2bryson @conjugateprior By that argument free-market capitalism is also dead, bc everyone supporting it is abusing it. Plausible!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @pennymitv @johnc1912 There will be both false positives (flagged as child abuse, but isn't) and false negatives (not flagged, but is).    
    
    
    @pennymitv @johnc1912 Crucial to get right what happens with such errors. We don't want e.g. teachers fired when search engine gets it wrong    
    
    
    @JustKatCarm Coming from an all-male school, I certainly take to heart the recommendation about nuns.    
    
    
    @LoveOnLanguage Der Hund, Die Katze, 'nuff said. :-)    
    
    
    @mattmight and vice-versa    
    
    
    it is clear that 140 chars is a good amount to write using Dasher    
    
    
    Watching Breach    
    
    
    sleep    
    
    
    "I don't know what I want, but I want it now" 

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sir_Henry_at_Rawlinson_End_(film)    
    
    
    stroking a black cat    
    
    
    pre-breakfast email    
    
    
    picking up coffee    
    
    
    working    
    
    
        
    
    
    You don't have to die of humiliation, for you are strong person, and this is a learning experience #whichsong    
    
    
    @srenals @jochenleidner precision sometimes, recall other times. If marginally relevant, and written by your external examiner, say?    
    
    
    @srenals @jochenleidner @milesosborne no good for experts or insiders, better for beginners and outsiders perhaps?    
    
    
    “@kinggary: Google loses Twitter firehose http://ow.ly/5wA4F ”  Agreement terminated by whom? Twitter, bcoz of G+?    
    
    
    