I am retiring my free LinkedIn mini course -- get it now if you want it... http://tinyurl.com/li-mini-course  -- and you'll be notified about the new one!    
    
    
    A social media profile should drive people to engage. Read my blog on telling the reader what to do next http://tinyurl.com/y8lbwxq    
    
    
    Change your thoughts and you change your world. AND Change yourself and your work will seem different.  --Norman Vincent Peale    
    
    
    @LeadToday  that is a very nice quote -- makes you think    
    
    
    Here's an interesting viewpoint as the the definition of social media: http://tinyurl.com/yz55zu6 (Article/Blog)    
    
    
    I just posted a great article on how to almost automatically create value for your networking connections: http://tinyurl.com/y9ufe59 >blog<    
    
    
    Don't have time to work LinkedIn, here's a simple solution.. http://tinyurl.com/y8wuzyh  <blog article>    
    
    
    To lengthen thy life, lessen thy meals. ...Benjamin Franklin    
    
    
    Power always thinks... that it is doing God's service when it is violating all his laws.
John Adams    
    
    
    @MikeKoenigs  I have been trying to buy your product for 2 weeks and the page dosn't work -- can someone call me HELP    
    
    
    Have you seen this chilling line by line account of the healthcare bill you must see this http://bit.ly/vTS7r <video>    
    
    
    Please retweet the previous post or this link:  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HcBaSP31Be8 <video> CHILLING    
    
    
    Reading http://www.cmswatch.com/Blog/1842-Facebook-competing-around-the-globe----but-not-always-winning?source=twitter    
    
    
    Great article on the success of social media and what sites work the best http://tinyurl.com/yjej6q6  PR on Market Watch    
    
    
    For those of you sales and marketing types I highly recommend you read Richard Harshaw's book "Monopolize Your Marketplace" it's fantastic!!    
    
    
    Interested in connecting with more people on twiter, any recommendations of how to do that in a GOOD way as opposed to irritating people?    
    
    
    A man left home one day and made 3 left turns and meet a man with a mask on. What is the profession of the first man?    
    
    
    FREE Power Networking Secrets for LinkedIn -Register now - Webinar on 4/5:
http://www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/6/ You'll  love it    
    
    
    @davegonzalez 

are you familiar with Frank Kern, have you seen any of his "Mass Control" materials -- I think is a great strategist...    
    
    
    @SocialMedia_Inc can we chat? JV and cross promo possibilities, flyn 408-296-6880    
    
    
    How can you work all day and feel like nothing got done... is it Monday?    
    
    
    It is going to be very interesting to see what lies ahead with our new president and his objectives...    
    
    
    If you're using LinkedIn to network, I have 3 free reports on networking more profitably on my website - www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.com    
    
    
    Why do you need a Web2.0 website?  Learn about it in my newest article: http://tinyurl.com/ydomzh8  >>blog article    
    
    
    6 key secrets for  succeeding on LinkedIn -Register now -FREE  Webinar on 2PM PST 4/5: http://www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/6/    
    
    
    Last chance to register for free LinkedIn power networking skills seminar http://www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/6/ Monday 2PM EST    
    
    
    Last chance to register for free LinkedIn power networking skills seminar http://www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/6/ Monday 2PM PST    
    
    
    sorry it is 2 PST not 2 EST    
    
    
    Better late than never, I just moved all of my email off my local client and on to the web and will soon stop using Comcast email completely    
    
    
    Anyone else starting to worry about our government - their integrity, their competence? Shouldn't we be going back to the founders ideas?    
    
    
    Just thought I would share a win -- I just got written up in the Fast Company Mag. blog -- http://www.flynpenoyer.com/fc -- check it out..    
    
    
    @therobbrown  sent you an email -- could we chat?    
    
    
    If any of you are wondering how important networking catch the SCI FI channel show Connected-Six Degrees of Separation!! It's unbelievable.    
    
    
    If any of you are wondering how important networking is catch the SCI FI chanl show Connected-Six Degrees of Separation!! It's unbelievable.    
    
    
    Do you have a "bonus/value" as a potential cross promotion with our soon to be launched LinkedIn networking profitability related product?    
    
    
    Just re worte my free LinkedIn course - great stuff - www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/minicourse    please RT    
    
    
    Just re wrote my free LinkedIn course - great stuff - www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/minicourse /please retweet --sorry about the typo    
    
    
    @HalinaShorter Are you really smoking a cigaret with a "I love to exercise byline??? WOW    
    
    
    TIP If you'd just offer to HELP first, before hitting up your social networking contacts for business you will find them far more receptive    
    
    
    Trying to make LinkedIn work for you get my free course - www.OnlineBuisnessNetworker.net/minicourse  - 4 reports 8 videos Powerful stuff!    
    
    
    Thank God for Fridays! For those of us working for ourselves it means getting 2 workdays where you are not interrupted by phone calls! SWEAT    
    
    
    Their is nothing like going on a rampage of production and getting all kinds of great stuff done.. Yesterday was very productive!    
    
    
    Getting close to finishing my product and member site. Anyone have bonuses they would like to offer (JV) - good for a networking product?    
    
    
    Have you see www.oovoo.com -- WOW -- free video conferencing with up to six folks at one time -- unbelievable potential... check it out...    
    
    
    LInkedIn has just made your "Networking Activity" status in your profile header more powerful -- you can now include a link and Twitter.    
    
    
    Want to learn how to empower your LinkedIn Profile? Free webinar on 4/8. For info:www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/webinar/7 Please RT-Thanks    
    
    
    If you are a LinkedIn user please follow my Online Business Networker Twitter account -- lots of great free stuff -- "OBNcom"  Please RT    
    
    
    My NEW OBN website is now live. Tons of new LinkedIn secrets coming including a course giveaway -- check it out http://www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.com  -Pls RT    
    
    
        
    
    
    Want to know the secrets of your LinkedIn profile?  Come to my free seminar: www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/7 -- Please RT>> thanks    
    
    
    My networking product is close to launch -- still looking for bonus give-aways -- a chance to promote your product - all will be considered    
    
    
    My online Biz-networking product is close to launch -- still looking for bonus give-aways -- a chance to promote... less than 5 seconds ago    
    
    
    If you are a LinkedIn user please follow my Online Business Networker Twitter account -- lots of great free stuff -- "OBNcom" Please RT    
    
    
    It's so funny, that most people have gratitude after they receive a gift -- when it works so much better the other way around -- try it...    
    
    
    Leverage your LinkedIn answers in the question and answers forum (YouTube video) www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/llqa    
    
    
    If you are a LinkedIn user plaese follow my LinkedIn resource profile for tips and advice... https://twitter.com/#!/obncom     
    
    
    See my new LikedIn networking tips blog--new post on open networking still rough about the edges-enjoy www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/blog    
    
    
    LinkedIn is the only B2B social media site that can eliminate the whole prospecting process -- follow my OBNcom Twitter to learn more    
    
    
    How to get business on LinkedIn (video). Some quick tips to help you succeed. http://tinyurl.com/c3xqsy  Enjoy!    
    
    
    How come Saturdays and Sundays as so much shorter than Mondays?    
    
    
    @vcrichs you should follow obncom as well that's my LI account    
    
    
    @AskAlan97  can we connect on LinkedIn?    
    
    
    You have to watch this it's incredible ...
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jeYscnFpEyA&feature=related    
    
    
    Are you a LinkenIn networker? Please consider test driving my LinkdeIn networking success program - great data low $, www.tinyurl.com/czl2m6    
    
    
    Some great tips on managing you own efforts: http://tinyurl.com/cjo4mo    
    
    
    Just letting everyone know that I am changing my user name from TeleSalesGuru to my name Flyn Penoyer.    
    
    
    Finally, the weekend... have a wonderful weekend everyone!!    
    
    
    If you really want to understand how the world, and for that matter you life, works take up the game of chess (or G) strategy tactics effect    
    
    
    Is anyone aware of what is happening with "autopinger.com" -- I have signed for an account a couple of times and no confirmation email comes    
    
    
    @CarolSmithCEO Like Newt or not what he says is true his concerns threaten both our businesses as we will not flourish in Euro Socialism    
    
    
    I am spending the day making Linkedin networking tips videos to help others -- 10 or so made and about that many left to go...    
    
    
    I know this has bee out for a while but here's a pretty good video on Twitter: http://tinyurl.com/btanfq    
    
    
    With regard to Obama representing us -- imagine if the head of a big corporation when around the world telling everyone how bad his Co. was?    
    
    
    Don't wish it were easier, wish you were better.  -- Jim Rohn    
    
    
    I'm no fan of drugs, don't even take over the counter drugs if I can avoid, it but wouldn't legalized pot would be a great tax rev source?    
    
    
    You can increase the results of a first conversation with someone by talking about something that is immediate to them.    
    
    
    Information is the key to success, if you want a great speed reading program this guy is the best -- http://tinyurl.com/ccqsql    
    
    
    Be slow in choosing a friend, slower in changing--Ben Franklin, this seems good advice.    
    
    
    If you care about America I implore you to go to YouTube and watch the "Thomas Paine" videos - here's just one: http://tinyurl.com/cnfboo    
    
    
    Then spread the word -- the videos are excellently done and fun to watch agree or not:
http://tinyurl.com/cnfboo -video    
    
    
    In sales/sales mgmt? I have (free) sales & mgmt. quizzes, eval tools & regular sls tips on my site (videos coming) http://tinyurl.com/cm93d8    
    
    
    I'm in an internet marketing MasterMind grp that recently lost a couple of members -- its a great group -- are you interested - need 2    
    
    
    Knowledge has to be improved, challenged, and increased constantly, or it vanishes.
Peter Drucker    
    
    
    What do you think of the current administrations newest distraction to their policies- let's lynch the previous administration? Incredible!!    
    
    
    Meanwhile I am still making free tips videos -- great info on how to master LinkedIn...    
    
    
    It is not just and "opportunity" but a GIFT -- they key is having enough the gratitude for what has happened that we find it...    
    
    
    Wayne Dyer says "change the way u look at a thing - it will change -think we could put on some "common sense" glasses and look at congress?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Networking is about building relationships. See my blog post on some things you can do start right w/a new connect http://tinyurl.com/c685lf    
    
    
    aimed at LinkedIn but good anywhere    
    
    
    Games r lame??? I guess you have never played competitive chess! You can learn more about life and business in chess than you would believe.    
    
    
    Chess teaches us -Sun Tzu-"Strategy without tactics is the slowest route to victory. Tactics without strategy is the noise before defeat."    
    
    
    I've put together a great program to help people be more profitable networkers on LinkedIn -- I need some test drivers send me a note 4 info    
    
    
    All mankind is divided into three classes: those that are immovable, those that are movable, and those that move. --Benjamin Franklin    
    
    
    @DaveMaskin -- thanks Dave, and those reading should know that Dave is someone you definitely want to be connected to    
    
    
    You can increase your visibility on LinkedIn buy being the first or second person to answer a question in the Q&A forum!    
    
    
    What separates the winners from the losers is how a person reacts to each new twist of fate. --Donald Trump    
    
    
    Always acknowledge a fault. This will throw those in authority off their guard and give you an opportunity to commit more. --Mark Twain    
    
    
    Would you like to see a fabulous idea for handling an objection in a sales call, see my daily sales tip for today-http://tinyurl.com/c3w6e4    
    
    
    Finally getting healthy again -- caught some bug 4 weeks ago and it just wouldn't leave -- now maybe I can get some work done.    
    
    
    Looking for internet marketer for a master mind group that recently lost a couple of its members -- great group -- someone launching a prod+    
    
    
    If you want real success, find out what everybody elses is doing and do something different.    
    
    
    Here's some good LinkedIn stuff http://bit.ly/rxRm7    
    
    
    If you responsible for an inside sales team(s), you will enjoy this PDF file document - no optin, just download it now: http://tinyurl.com/4.pdf     
    
    
    @brentnhunter It is not my impression that Lincoln's quote has anything to do with OccupyWallStreet. He wasn't for redistribute of wealth.    
    
    
    Having untrainable people on your sales team is not a people problem, but a management and leadership one!    
    
    
    Learning to treat LinkedIn and other social media profile like marketing instruments instead of resumes and mini sites will improve results    
    
    
    If we did all the things we are capable of, we would literally surprise ourselves -- Thomas Edison    
    
    
    FREE Telephone Sales Skills Webinar - Learn the simple secret for making you follow-up sales calls more effective. http://tinyurl.com/next-step-webinar …    
    
    
    I am looking for independent telesales people that are capable of calling on inside sales managers. Can anyone help?    
    
    
    The secret to making your sales management job easier is MORE leadership. When you lead effectively, less management is required!    
    
    
    The key to getting more things done is the elimination of "interruptions." Experts predict that an interruption cost on average 20 minutes    
    
    
    Make your follow-up sales calls more productive, effective, and easier by attending my free webinar next month::  http://tinyurl.com/next-step-webinar …    
    
    
    Would you like to make your follow-up sales calls easier and more productive? Check out my complementary webinar   http://tinyurl.com/next-step-webinar …    
    
    
    The real secret to LinkedIn is "marketing." A proper marketing approach will save you hours and give you better engagements...    
    
    
    @richardc -- I would like to get a hold of you -- I am from stompernet    
    
    
    Just hours left to register for my FREE telesales skills webinar. Inside sales and telesales mangers don't miss this http://tinyurl.com/next-step-webinar …    
    
    
    I just posted the following article to my blog: A LinkedIn Sphere of Influence You May Have Overlooked -www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/blog    
    
    
    I uploaded a @YouTube video http://youtu.be/pptdTHCsZyU?a  Telephone Sales Skills Webinar: The Customer Prospect Sandwi    
    
    
    @ken_matthews99 McDonalds doesn't price food on nutritional value but on ROI. Not to mention the fries aren't any better for you maybe wors.    
    
    
    Do you use LinkedIn? Check this out - Closing my LinkedIn course tomorrow --  sign up  now for a big bonus http://tinyurl.com/25bgjc9 Pls RT    
    
    
    FREE Webinar: Learn the secrets of using your voice in a telephone sales call, http://www.bit.ly/tsu_voice . Only 30 minutes but packed with info    
    
    
    When selling on the telephone your voice is the sizzle in the saying "sell the sizzle NOT the steak!    
    
    
    I just posted a great article on learning and making new sales techniques work. http://www.penoyer.com/SalesArticles/SalesTechniques.html    
    
    
    Involved in selling or managing inside sales? Consider checking out my new LinkedIn group "The Sales MasterMind" run like no other group    
    
    
    Chk Out Ths Free Life Planning Process Map & Guru Copywritng Report From @NoteTakingNerd. Looks Amazing! http://bit.ly/i7wDDv     
    
    
    If you every wondered about the value of using LinkedIn, read what happened to me just the other day... http://tinyurl.com/lrdkbm - Amazing!    
    
    
    Would you like to know how to make your LinkedIn network better and more powerful? See my blog post: http://tinyurl.com  Comments welcome..    
    
    
    @therealjosh -- you asked about WP are you on LinkedIn? If you are I have an answer for you... flyn@flynpenoyer.com -- happy to connect    
    
    
    Entrepreneurs will benefit from the Yoast SEO plugin for Wrodpress. Allows you to do great on-page SEO. A great reason to use Wordpress    
    
    
    Want to learn the real secret of LinkedIn? Free Jan 18 webinar,  Busting the LinkedIn Myth: http://tinyurl.com/LinkedIn-webinar-10    Pls-RT    
    
    
    Fabulous LinkedIn seminar -- learn the truth about how LinkedIn works: www.OnlineBuisnessNetworker.net/webinar/9/  Please RT    
    
    
    Your LinkedIn profile is the key to your success -- free ebook helps you improve it: http://www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/profilearticle/    
    
    
    Fabulous LinkedIn seminar -- learn the truth about how LinkedIn works:www.onlinebusinessnetworker.net/webinar/9/  Please RT - sorry for typo    
    
    
    Flyn asks are you maximizing your communications on LinkedIn? See my blog post on how to accomplish this http://tinyurl.com/kq5ufa    
    
    
    Do you need a bonus/incentive for your marketing or website - I have a LinkedIn networking success kit valued at $160 that you can give away    
    
    
    The best way to predict the future is to create it.  Peter Drucker    
    
    
    Do you want the real key to success on LinkedIn -- check out my blog post: http://tinyurl.com/kpdtv4 --this works in any networking effort.    
    
    
    If your actions inspire others to dream more learn more, do more and become more you’re a leader. ...John Quincy Adams    
    
    
    I have just finished an awesome leadership training video for inside sales management -- if you'd like access let me know. flyn@penoyer.com    
    
    
    @TracyCampanella -- thanks, if you liked that -- here is where I got it... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2gGBexaV1EE … (Tom Peters)    
    
    
    The two most powerful things in existence a kind word and thoughtful jester. Ken Langone, Founder of Home Deopt    
    
    
    "Nobody can prevent you from choosing to be exceptional." --Mark Sanborn, The Fred Factor    
    
    
    "Blame no one, expect nothing, do something." Bill Parcels    
    
    
    Do one thing everyday that scares you. Eleanor Roosevelt    
    
    
    To live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist that is all. Oscar Wild    
    
    
    If things seem under control, you’re just not going fast enough. Mario Andradite    
    
    
    "I we did all the things we are capable of, we would literally astound ourselves." ...Thomas Edison    
    
    
    LinkedIn: If you work on the "networking" relationship, before pursuing the business relationship you will have far greater success.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Everyone lives by selling something. Robert Lewis Stevenson    
    
    
    Effective leadership is not about making speeches or being liked; leadership is defined by results not attributes.
Peter Drucker    
    
    
    The discipline of writing something down is the first step toward making it happen.
Lee Iacocca    
    
    
    Would you like to empower the Linkedin intro process and save introductions -- see how in my blog post -- http://tinyurl.com/ltswrd    
    
    
    Expect the best. Prepare for the worst. Capitalize on what comes.
Zig Ziglar    
    
    
    A good objective of leadership is to help those who are doing poorly to do well and to help those who are doing well to do even better..Rohn    
    
    
    Failure is simply a few errors in judgment, repeated every day.   ...Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Knowledge has to be improved, challenged, and increased constantly, or it vanishes.
--Peter Drucker    
    
    
    Free inside sales leadership training on how to motivate your reps or your team, see my LinkedIn profile... http://www.linkedin.com/in/flynpenoyer     
    
    
    I've found that luck is quite predictable. If you want more luck, take more chances. Be more active. Show up more often.
Brian Tracy    
    
    
    A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.
Winston Churchill    
    
    
    says if you're in sales directly or indirectly you will find my newest blog post of interest: http://tinyurl.com/mpcdc2    
    
    
        
    
    
    If you treat your LinkedIn profile as a marketing piece you will get far better results. It should be used to get attention and engage.    
    
    
    A real decision is measured by the fact that you've taken a new action. If there's no action, you haven't truly decided.
Tony Robbins    
    
    
    Head the waring of our founders... "All tyranny needs to gain a foothold is for people of good conscience to remain silent."
--Jefferson    
    
    
    Most of what we call management consists of making it difficult for people to get their work done. --Peter Drucker    
    
    
    The greatest day in your life and mine is when we take total responsibility for our attitudes. That's the day we truly grow up.
John Maxwell    
    
    
    Don't wish it were easier, wish you were better.  --Jim Rohn    
    
    
    It is the set of the sails, not the direction of the wind that determines which way we will go.  --Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Time is more value than money. You can get more money, but you cannot get more time. --Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Change the changeable, accept the unchangeable, and remove yourself from the unacceptable. --Denis Waitley    
    
    
    Just posted a great article on my blog re responding to invitations on LinkedIn: http://tinyurl.com/msp86l    
    
    
    Do you want to know how to get an advantage over your fellow LinkedIneers? Read my blog post: http://tinyurl.com/mt4yca    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ideas can be life-changing. Sometimes all you need to open the door is just one more good idea.  --Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Do you want to know who you are? Don't ask. Act! Action will delineate and define you. --Thomas Jefferson    
    
    
    Always bear in mind that your own resolution to succeed is more important than any other.  --Abraham Lincoln    
    
    
    Our Constitution was made only for a moral and religious people. It is wholly inadequate to the government of any other. --John Adams    
    
    
    @Support -- it seems like the number of followers I have is not changing even though I am getting new followers -- its been the same forever    
    
    
    New blog post: Selling Yourself on LinkedIn: Sales Skills for Networking http://bit.ly/4i8jo    
    
    
    New blog post: Being Invaluable is the Key to LinkedIn (Networking) http://bit.ly/cfiiw    
    
    
    New blog post: How to How to Monetize LinkedIn – Engage Your Connections – Part 1 http://bit.ly/SynfX    
    
    
    New blog post: Some Selfless Promotion, But in Your Interest (All FREE stuff) http://bit.ly/FAufb    
    
    
    New blog post: How to How to Monetize LinkedIn – Engage Your Connections Part 2 http://bit.ly/Yxxso    
    
    
    Just published the second part of my post on monetizing LinkedIn -- http://tinyurl.com/njzesr    
    
    
    New blog post: Some Very Simple LinkedIn Visibility Tactics You Can Use Everyday http://bit.ly/4aGBz    
    
    
    You can never do too much for others, and you could never imagine how much it pays to do so...    
    
    
    New blog post: Do you have a LinkedIn strategy question? Ask it here. http://bit.ly/17EXqM    
    
    
    The measure of a networker is not the number of connections they have, but the number they have created! For connecting others is the goal..    
    
    
    New blog post: Improving Your LinkedIn Results and Your Life http://bit.ly/GzncR    
    
    
    @mikebuechele -- Mike, I understand you've had a problem with my site. It is a two step process. You opt in - then you need to set up mbrshp    
    
    
    @mikebuechele - It is all one system - the membership site uses your email as your user ID and I don't have a way to carry it from the optin    
    
    
    @mikebuechele -- please get in touch with me if you have any questions or problems I would be happy to help out.  Sorry for the problems    
    
    
    New blog post: Getting Connected, Starting Out, or Strengthening Your Network http://bit.ly/17h1lg    
    
    
    Saw a tweet on "dreams" -- not the sleeping one's, goal and life ones, reminded me of a great book on the subject -http://tinyurl.com/ko3ec8    
    
    
    New blog post: Building Your LinkedIn Network – The Personal Joint Venture Method http://bit.ly/LYmbs    
    
    
    FREE Sales Management Training -- How to Motivate Your Salespeople -- http://www.telesalesuniversity.com/motivate/  This workshop is pure content, NO sales pitch.    
    
    
    New blog post: A Great LinkedIn Tactic for Cutting Off Your Nose to Spite Your Face http://bit.ly/2uAX13    
    
    
    New blog post: How To Sell Yourself On LinkedIn Using Questions http://bit.ly/fBfeh    
    
    
    New blog post: To Monetize LinkedIn You Will Need One Thing http://bit.ly/c2G1k    
    
    
    New blog post: A Short Letter to My Readers... http://bit.ly/knreW    
    
    
    New blog post: How to Use LinkedIn the Profiles of Others to Improve Your Network http://bit.ly/1QVLkI    
    
    
    FREE LinkedIn webinar -How to Make a Great First Impression. This will definitely benefit anyone trying to get business http://www.flynpenoyer.com/blackfriday/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Isn't it amazing how "extreme interest" in something warps one's sense of time -- where is after midnight and it seems like you started...    
    
    
    It not the individual value of LinkedIn, Facebook, or Twitter, it is there use in concert that generates success...    
    
    
    New blog post: Using Twitter to Help Your LinkedIn Networking and Vice-Versa  http://bit.ly/U2IuH    
    
    
    New blog post: Take Advantage of Unwanted or Negative Communications on LinkedIn  http://bit.ly/qtDoX    
    
    
    WOW! Here is the coolest data on social marketing I've ever seen. http://tinyurl.com/nnkyrr    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    New blog post: A Great Way to Provide Some Value to Your LinkedIn Connections http://bit.ly/vZPeG    
    
    
    New blog post: Your LinkedIn “Contact Settings" Section of Your Profile  http://bit.ly/2V616j    
    
    
    New blog post: Great News for LinkedIn Networking Success Kit Owners http://bit.ly/cXDOt    
    
    
    @wordpress_tv thanks for the follow    
    
    
    I've just opened up my new sales blog, come see, free report for registering -- www.penoyer.com/blog -- great sales info coming + tips daily    
    
    
    New blog post: Secret Agent, The Art of Prospecting http://bit.ly/aQpTa    
    
    
    New blog post: LinkedIn and Managing Your Connections http://bit.ly/YjNej    
    
    
    Do you want the most incredible LinkedIn training ever? Less than a coffee shop visit..
Check this out & please RT
http://tinyurl.com/great-linkedin-stuff …    
    
    
    New blog post: Positioning Yourself for Selling Your LinkedIn Connections http://bit.ly/15EwIo    
    
    
    New blog post: Something LinkedIn Networkers Should Manage, But Most Don’t! http://bit.ly/n0ZCy    
    
    
    Does anyone know what would cause my computer to not be able to direct message -- logged in on other machine and works fine???    
    
    
    New blog post: Selling Yourself in the LinkedIn Question and Answer Forum  http://bit.ly/3Tlzer    
    
    
    New blog post: Building Relationships on LinkedIn Piece by Piece http://bit.ly/2nyqap    
    
    
    @CindyKing I have tremendous amount of high value content on using LinkedIn for biz. How do I contribute to your online publication?    
    
    
    @Nsaney I would like permission to use the vulture kill something graphic in an ebook, and I am happy to link to the site where they can buy    
    
    
    New blog post: The Right Way Handle LinkedIn Questions Asking for Products or Services http://bit.ly/15RLqY    
    
    
    New blog post: Making Recommendations on LinkedIn http://bit.ly/2do9zg    
    
    
    New blog post: How to Get LinkedIn Viewers from Your Profile to Your Website http://bit.ly/Fda61    
    
    
    New blog post: A Marketing Formula for LinkedIn and Other Social Media http://bit.ly/Nn4GM    
    
    
    New blog post: The LinkedIn Expert’s Tab Added Credibility http://bit.ly/m9maF    
    
    
    Check out my free LinkedIn power networking program/course -- there's more data here than in most paid courses. http://tinyurl.com/dfgqrg    
    
    
    New blog post: Something to Put in Your LinkedIn Summary http://bit.ly/HSx5c    
    
    
    New blog post: LinkedIn and the Unsolicited Introduction Message http://bit.ly/n5rWk    
    
    
    Im putting on a FREE TeleSales Mgmt conference call -- www.penoyer.com/blog/events/  if you run or are responsible for Insede Sls its a must    
    
    
    New blog post: A Simple Way to Determine the Potential Value of a Group http://bit.ly/18udvG    
    
    
    New blog post: Asking For Help on LinkedIn: A Potential Gold Mine http://bit.ly/puK6f    
    
    
    New blog post: Some Random Practices that Will Profit Your LinkedIn Business Networking Efforts http://bit.ly/lv5ij    
    
    
    Responsible for inside sales team? Learn how you can significantly increase performance -FREE- www.penoyer.com/blog/events Pls ReTweet -TY    
    
    
    New blog post: A Subtle Approach for Connecting to Decision Makers http://bit.ly/28C4zi    
    
    
    STAR TREK -- if you are a fan you have to see this... http://io9.com/old-spock-battles-new-spock-in-the-greatest-car-commerc-493836696 …  Great stuff.    
    
    
    New blog post: LinkedIn’s 3000 Invitation Limit http://bit.ly/deOZU    
    
    
    New blog post: A Jump Start for Your LinkedIn Networking http://bit.ly/FpRFY    
    
    
    New blog post: Monetizing LinkedIn is Not Just User Skills But the Right Marketing Approach http://bit.ly/8WXiJ    
    
    
    New blog post: Don’t Use the “I don’t know you” option on invitations http://bit.ly/SMSnm    
    
    
        
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- Voice Mail Message Evaluation Tool http://youtu.be/nr9g4TpbRSQ?a    
    
    
    Ever wondered how to get the lastl name in a LinkedIn search where only the initial is given-Go here www.tinyurl.com/Linkedin-Search-Secrets    
    
    
    Ever wondered how to get the last name in a LinkedIn search where only the initial is given-Go here www.tinyurl.com/Linkedin-Search-Secrets    
    
    
    New blog post: How to Use the Contact Settings Section of the LinkedIn Profile http://bit.ly/1lSzxt    
    
    
    I'll be doing a FREE LinkedIn power networking seminar on 9/16 for details see http://onlinebusinessnetworker.net/blog/events/   >Great info    
    
    
    New blog post: On LinkedIn: The chances are you NEED to do this… http://bit.ly/Ysa5f    
    
    
    New blog post: How to Create a Value Item for Your LinkedIn Connections http://bit.ly/16IIUY    
    
    
    If any of my followers can help (Thank you) -- Please RT this great free seminar on LinkedIn networking skills - http://tinyurl.com/oduhut    
    
    
    New blog post: Monetizing LinkedIn An Argument for Accepting All Invitations http://bit.ly/PgoTV    
    
    
    I'm doing another LinkedIn skills seminar Thursday - for info see - www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/webinar/1 -- Great info for your success    
    
    
    New blog post: Two Things that Should Top Your LinkedIn Profile http://bit.ly/5qtQc    
    
    
    Flyn There are just 7 hours left to register for my FREE LinkedIn power networking webinar tomorrow: http://tinyurl.com/oduhut    
    
    
    I uploaded a YouTube video -- Presenting A Benefit http://youtu.be/XOGT5iF9gkM?a    
    
    
    I am doing another free networking skills seminar that includes a powerful strategy for live events - http://tinyurl.com/ydpn9ru    
    
    
    Do you manage an inside sales group? Check out my free webinar on drivng a 10% increase in sales www.tinyulr.com/GetTenPercent -Please RT    
    
    
    @HappeningNow Why Fox isn't taking about the fact that the US$ is close to being removed as the worlds reserve currency/vast implications??    
    
    
    Change the way you look at things, and the things you look at will change! Wayne Dyer I believe.    
    
    
    If you work with small businesses and independent business professionals I am looking to do joint venture marketing and promotion-Contact me    
    
    
    You will get the most out of social and business networking when you strive to provide value to others without  and expectations - just help    
    
    
    In the SF Bay Area, here's a great networking event for you -- http://www.workit.com/events/svmixer2009.cfm    
    
    
    Here's great article on how to use Twitter for a LinkedIn purpose... http://tinyurl.com/yzcw39y (blog post)    
    
    
    See my new blog post, learn how to monetize LI - see the links that make it possible to gain business: http://tinyurl.com/yeokykc (blog)    
    
    
    Video is big, now you can put video in your LinkedIn profile - here's some tips for what to do with it --http://tinyurl.com/ye5ed2b (blog)    
    
    
        
    
    
    "You must get good at one of two things: sowing in the spring and begging in the fall." Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Learn how to separate the majors and the minors. A lot of people don't do well simply because they major in minor things. Jim Rohn    
    
    
    A good conscience is a continual Christmas -- Benjamin Franklin    
    
    
    For all of you life-time learners and self-development enthusiasts it's a very sad day -- Jim Rohn has passed away...    
    
    
    Are you a LinkedIn power networker? Find out -- LinkedIn Power Networking Quiz  -- http://tinyurl.com/yavs8um  -- (blog post)    
    
    
    Would you like to get business on LinkedIn, read my blog post -- http://tinyurl.com/yahsdo5 -- this would work on other networking sites    
    
    
    >>Drawing for a free copy of my Power Networking Profit System Course for LinkedIn - no strings or optin See: http://tinyurl.com/y97q6r6    
    
    
    Wishing everyone a happy holidays and a merry Christmas!    
    
    
    The most fulfilling thoughts are not of what we want, but of gratitude for what we already have. You can surprise yourself if you list them.    
    
    
    @JasonDeVelvis it is possible to chat with you about membership plugins for WP -- 408-296-6880    
    
    
    @JasonDeVelvis -- I have sent you a note already -- I would like to chat about the member plugin for WP    
    
    
    Don't become a victim of yourself. Forget about the thief waiting in the alley; what about the thief in your mind? -- Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Are you relived that there might again be some checks and balances in Washington with Browns win in MA?    
    
    
    I'm looking for blogs on social media related subjects and especially LinkedIn. Your suggestions would be appreciated. Thanks.    
    
    
    Do you want to be a super star business networker? Read this blog post and learn the primary key to doing so: http://tinyurl.com/ye6pld9    
    
    
    I have just posted a great question re making LinkedIn work -- I invite you to participate. See the question at: http://tinyurl.com/yje7vmn    
    
    
    It's amazing how just thinking about and looking at things in a different way can generate some of the most creative and valuable ideas.    
    
    
    If you haven't seen this, its very funny, next American Idol (YouTube video) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ikTxfIDYx6Q    
    
    
    @jdwheels John, my name is Flyn Penoyer and I'd like to ask you a Linkedin / Cisco related question if you can spare a couple of minutes    
    
    
    Do not bite at the bait of pleasure, till you know there is no hook beneath it.
Thomas Jefferson    
    
    
    If the freedom of speech is taken away then dumb and silent we may be led, like sheep to the slaughter. ...George Washington    
    
    
    You can actually use the tag feature in LinkedIn to set up follow ups with specific connections. Though it's not the most efficient or best.    
    
    
    "Success is neither magical nor mysterious. Success is the natural consequence of consistently applying basic fundamentals." Jim Rohn    
    
    
    The best time to make contact with a new networking connection is immediately after receiving their invitation. But it must be to help them.    
    
    
    If you sell and haven't see this video your in for a real laugh -best sales video I've seen.
http://tinyurl.com/ygnlk6m (YouTube/ Rev. Jim)    
    
    
    Use your Twitter account to make you more accessible on LinkedIn. LinkedIn doesn't permit public display of your  phone or email - Twtr does    
    
    
    A smile is the light in your window that tells others that there is a caring, sharing person inside.  Denis Waitley    
    
    
    If you have a LinkedIn account please check out my free mini course: www.OnlineBusinessNetworker.net/successkit - has 4 reports and 7 videos    
    
    
    Want some super info on what needs to be on your website to be successful? Read my discussion: http://tinyurl.com/yansuf2 -LinkedIn Q&A -    
    
    
        
    
    
    Isn't Sunday morning wonderful? If you work for yourself as I do it seems the only time when there's no pressure to get something done.    
    
    
    "The unique combination of desire, planning, effort and perseverance will always work its magic. " Jim Rohn    
    
    
        
    
    
    Affirmation without discipline is the beginning of delusion.   Jim Rohn    
    
    
    Be careful the friends you choose for you will become like them.  W. Clement Stone    
    
    
        
    
    
    The basis of our political system is the right of the people to make and to alter their constitutions of government.   George Washington    
    
    
    Great article on following up on connections: http://tinyurl.com/yf9xleh (blog)    
    
    
    If your website, LinkedIn profile, Facebook fan page, or other web assets doesn't contain a low-risk high-value offer -- it should!    
    
    
    I  wouldn't focus on regret. The secret to success is finding the "GIFT" in any unfortunate situation. Regret looks back, taking the gift ->    
    
    
    