The 10 least wealthy members of Congress, from Roll Call http://stks.co/hp3e  They r not just least wealthy; they r broke 8 Ds, 2 Rs $$    
    
    
    10 'Poorest' Members of Congress Owe Big http://stks.co/qWQB  The same list with a little more data to flesh it out $$    
    
    
    How to Handle a Debt Default. You Know. Just in Case. http://stks.co/hp3u  In a longwinded way comes 2 correct answer: no good strategy $$    
    
    
    When Analysts Sober Up http://stks.co/gowE  Sell side analysts tend 2b very optimistic & revise as reality intrudes. CFOs don't mind $$    
    
    
    Beyond Earnings: A Simple Method 2Pick a Winning Stock http://stks.co/cmEH  "Quality" or gross return on assets, measures moat strength $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Don't Shoot the Messaging http://stks.co/rWTQ  Fed puts 2much effort into fwd guidance, should not b surprised @ mkt reactions $$    
    
    
    Wire Fraud Is on the Rise http://stks.co/ioy6  Double check transfer requests; you could be on the hook for any losses $$    
    
    
    'Jumping Genes' Bring Unexpected Twists 2 DNA http://stks.co/qWQb  1 shouldn't b overly impressed w/idea of strict genetic heritability $$    
    
    
    Is US Political Bubble About to Burst? http://stks.co/qWQo  If there is no permanent default, no, b/c the world needs flexibility of US $$    
    
    
    Republicans Need a Graceful Exit Strategy, Now http://stks.co/ioyC  @asymmetricinfo explains y the GOP should cut their losses here $$    
    
    
    America’s default on its debt is inevitable http://stks.co/fp1M  America has defaulted 3 times already. No way we can fund entitlements $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Letters from Readers: I’ve been reading your blog for quite sometime and I’ve always been ... http://bit.ly/1bnmyiJ     
    
    
    Debt moves the world http://stks.co/pWY9  This article moves the ball forward; overall debt levels should help decide monetary policy $$    
    
    
    Big Banks Can Be Dismantled, Say US & UK Regulators http://stks.co/jowK  I will believe it when I see it. Regulators r2 optimistic $$    
    
    
    Bit by Bit, Virtual Reality Heads for the Holodeck http://stks.co/pWYR  Think the technology will get bogged down on multiple players $$    
    
    
    Fama, Shiller, Hansen Win 2013 Nobel Prize in Economics http://stks.co/dmF2  Can anyone explain why Hansen shared the SCB prize? $$    
    
    
    Note2journalists: there is no Economics Nobel Prize . Nobel knew economics was not a science. We should agree given failures of ec theory $$    
    
    
    The official name is The Sveriges Riksbank Prize in Economic Sciences in Memory of Alfred Nobel. Call it the Swedish Central Bank Prize. $$    
    
    
    If you have 2shorten it further, call it The SCB Prize.  But it is not a Nobel Prize; none of the economists winning it deserve the honor $$    
    
    
    Bad HL: Default Doubters Repudiated by Republican Economists http://stks.co/jowV  Comments of GOP economists r more nuanced than that $$    
    
    
    The Cheap Way to Watch Every NFL, NBA, NHL Game Online http://stks.co/tWMI  The genie is out of the bottle, will b hard 2get it back in $$    
    
    
    Fiscal negotiations sputter as deadline looms http://stks.co/jowu  Obama could end this here by tossing the GOP a bone 2 avoid MAD $$    
    
    
    Google Is Going to Include Your Face in Its New Ads http://stks.co/dmFo  U did not know that u have signed up 2b an ad pitchman w/G+ $$    
    
    
    A Slowdown on the Road to Recovery http://stks.co/rWbK 
Decaying Bridges, Highways Raise Costs for Truckers, Manufacturers $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    BuzzFeed's Brazen, Nutty, Growth Plan http://stks.co/qWXv  Translation by foreign-language speakers learning English using Duolingo $$    
    
    
    Tenuous: US Corporate Profit Growth Slows as Shutdown Risks Rise http://stks.co/amTl  Link more tenuous as economy was slowing already $$    
    
    
    French Fume Over Speed Traps That Cut Hollande Budget Gap http://stks.co/pWZu  An irritating way 2 tax people, would try 2 avoid that $$    
    
    
    Malaysia Rules Catholic Paper Can't Use 'Allah' http://stks.co/emQD  Go back to the original, and us "Elohim," not the Arabic version $$    
    
    
    'Clean Coal' Costs Are on Display at Mississippi Plant http://stks.co/pWao  Clean coal is likely a pipe dream 4 coal producers $$    
    
    
    Japan May Hire Firms to Manage Foreign Reserves http://stks.co/hpCr  A small experiment where they take illiquidity & credit risk $$    
    
    
    The Long, Slow Process of IKEA Design http://stks.co/sWQb  Company's Commitment to Shaving Costs Makes Designing a Kitchen a 5-Yr Task $$    
    
    
    Merkel Faces Decision on Coalition Partner http://stks.co/dmHj  Grand coalition coming, may have impact on German Constitution $$    
    
    
    Hollywood Steps Up Security to Keep Scripts Secret http://stks.co/gp6i  Interesting: tech & methods Hollywood uses 2 protect scripts $$    
    
    
    CEOs to Face Berkshire-Loyalty Test http://stks.co/amVg  How will $BRK.B retain managers after there is no Warren Buffett 2 disappoint? $$    
    
    
    Simon Says: ‘Toughen Up’ http://stks.co/pWbY  Simon Business School attempts to get students ready 4 the hard aspects of business $$    
    
    
    China CPI Speeds Up in September, Mainly on Food Prices http://stks.co/bmPd  Woe betide when Chinese Inflation starts running hot $$    
    
    
    Regional Fed Bosses Struggle With Communication Issue http://stks.co/dmI5  Talk is cheap 4 the Fed; the expenses get charged to us $$    
    
    
    Difficult to say: Investors Seek Bargains in Battered Munis http://stks.co/emRa  2 many major weak credits & 2 many weak holders $$    
    
    
    EPA’s McCarthy Says No Decision Made on Renewable Mandate http://stks.co/qWaC  Believe no rumor until it is officially denied $$    
    
    
    Warren Buffett's Lieutenants at Berkshire Hathaway http://stks.co/hpE2  Possible Buffett replacement Matthew Rose, CEO of BNSF $$ $BRK.B    
    
    
    Buffett Turns to Deputies to Help Find Successors for Unit CEOs http://stks.co/sWRc  Berkshire is a complex company; requires much mgmt $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: Good point. The successor will have 2go2 great pains to prove he will keep the old hands ... http://stks.co/jozT     
    
    
    Reformers hail limit on US crop insurance subsidies http://stks.co/fpB3  Let's c if it actually gets passed; Ag subsidies tough 2 kill $$    
    
    
    Obamacare marketplace could get partial rebuild http://stks.co/gp7a  If ppl have a hard time signing up, they will have to fix or delay $$    
    
    
    Factional conflicts have the power to destroy empires - and republics http://stks.co/pWdU  Reminds me of Europe in 1840s: too much debt $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog The Rules, Part LV: Financial intermediation reduces volatility.  In bull markets, demand ... http://bit.ly/19CP1Qf     
    
    
    @pkedrosky I wouldn't have said it that way, but you are correct.    
    
    
    Obamacare Needs a Drop-Dead Date http://stks.co/sWhN  @asymmetricinfo ably argues if exchanges aren't functioning by 11/1, delay PPACA $$    
    
    
    @JPDesloges not my article, but the Economist's.  Do what you like.    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog The Rules, Part LVI: Leverage and risk eventually transfer to the least regulatedI’m comin... http://bit.ly/1bxqLQU     
    
    
    Axel Merk: In our assessment, a central bank pursing an employment target... has given up its independence http://stks.co/dmc3  $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Tracy Britt Cool on Management Lessons From Warren Buffett http://stks.co/fpX5  Buffett gives his managers freedom & flexibility $$ $BRK.B    
    
    
    Crop-Insurance Cuts Test Farm Power as Lobbies Push Back http://stks.co/qWwf  If can't be cut when Ag does well, then nothing can b cut $$    
    
    
    Time to take bets on Frexit and the French franc? http://stks.co/tWlo ! Weird: Marine Le Pen's Front National most popular French party $$    
    
    
    Buffett Defends Dimon, Says Regulators Take Ton of Flesh http://stks.co/tWlq  Difficult to pin down liability w/large complex firms $$    
    
    
    As a result, there is the bias toward fines, a little criminal prosecution. Fines should go to those harmed, rather than govt $$ $JPM $BRK.B    
    
    
    NY Fed Fired Examiner Who Took on Goldman http://stks.co/ipUv  $GS $$ $SPY She analyzed conflict of interest rules & found them lacking.    
    
    
    Petco, Applebee's employees join growing list on private exchanges http://stks.co/hpau  If this works, maybe can replace govt exchanges $$    
    
    
    Harrisburg’s Parking Bond Sale Avoids Chicago Regret http://stks.co/cmkW  Key is 2align incentives; Harrisburg/investors both make $$ same    
    
    
    How Delayed Inflation Data Mess With Social Security and More http://stks.co/gpUm  US Treasury will have 2 estimate best they can $$    
    
    
    Though it might b better if the govt weren't calculating the data; gives them too much power to fiddle w/the #s. But no one is neutral $$    
    
    
    Patients Pay Before Seeing Doctor as Deductibles Spread http://stks.co/tWm3  Big: as deductibles rise, so does prepayment, b/c bad debt $$    
    
    
    Another reason y PPACA is a sham; resources don't appear from nowhere; low cost plans don't chg the underlying cost of services $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    @marcmakingsense A competitive market in data. Let the best data win.  Democracy ain't what it used 2b w/gerrymandering, thus current fight    
    
    
    How I Learned to Haggle Over Prices http://stks.co/amvF  Never thought I would b good at haggling until I traded corporate bonds $$    
    
    
    The Tea Party and the GOP Crackup http://stks.co/emsC  t-party represents Jacksonian America: angry & in full revolt against new elite $$    
    
    
    Stockbroker Requests to Scrub Complaints Are Often Granted http://stks.co/qX2B  Bad stuff; makes u want to beef up the SEC & end FINRA $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Liabilities in Asset Allocation: From an e-mail from one of my readers:I’m not sure if ... http://bit.ly/19L03mv     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Toby and Peanut, Part 1: Toby was an unusual guy.  Unlike many men, he never outgrew his c... http://bit.ly/18rqeQU     
    
    
    McConnell’s Favored Dam Project Included in Debt Deal http://stks.co/fpyN  Pork is not dead in DC, whether GOP or Democrats $$ #shame    
    
    
    Buffett Adds Stocks in Pension Handoff to Lieutenants http://stks.co/bnCD  Long duration, higher cost float 4 $BRK.B 2 invest $$    
    
    
    Dimon Said to Have Given Up Role at Bank Unit on OCC Request http://stks.co/enDm  He stepped down, but not w/o the OCC giving a push $$    
    
    
    Houston Texans Running Back Arian Foster Is Going Public http://stks.co/gpwh  Step right up, buy a share of a football player's pay $$ #no    
    
    
    Wrong: Al Gore: “Carbon Bubble” Is Going to Burst – Avoid Oil Stocks http://stks.co/bnCH  The "carbon bubble" is between his ears $$    
    
    
    Ursula Burns: 'Chill out a little bit' http://stks.co/gpwj  Pick the places where u want 2b great, focus energies there & then go do it $$    
    
    
    A SWAG Surprise in the $19 Billion Chevron Case http://stks.co/jpkm  Defense atty surprised when witness says the damage # was made-up $$    
    
    
    Health Website Woes Widen as Insurers Get Wrong Data http://stks.co/jpl0  4 something so critical, the healthcare website has failed $$    
    
    
    Even When the GOP Loses, It Wins http://stks.co/qXP9  New baseline favors deeper cuts as we may go through sequestration again $$    
    
    
    Buffett’s Son Calls Junk Bonds Model for Charities http://stks.co/enE8  Howard Buffett wants charities 2try hard projects, risk failure $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Hey China, Stop Laughing at the US http://stks.co/rXU2  W/any fair rendering, China's economic &political problems > those of US $$    
    
    
    How the Tea Party Will Die http://stks.co/hq3H  Gets 1thing right: gerrymandering is behind much of our gridlock $$ http://stks.co/fpyx     
    
    
    Wrong: Fed Official Says Big Banks Should Be Required to Hold Long-Term Debt http://stks.co/ipxY  Job is 2 protect subs not holdcos $$    
    
    
    Can Coke and Pepsi Overcome Shrinking Juice Demand? http://stks.co/qXPE  Far better to have fruit & get the fiber, not just the sugar $$    
    
    
    Unreliable research: Trouble at the lab http://stks.co/qXQR  The main problem is that scientists do not understand statistics $$    
    
    
    Also, they r incented to find positive results, when there may be none, & they are not neutral observers, sometimes they push an agenda $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: US Politics & Policy How the Tea Party Will Die http://t.co/EgEnMQV... http://bit.ly/1cF3ldC     
    
    
    The Gap Between Schooling and Education http://stks.co/fq10  @AnnieLowrey interviews author of forthcoming book: http://stks.co/ipzW  $$    
    
    
    Schools amplify parenting cultures. Motivated parents create good schools; too many top-down demands on schools inhibits true learning $$    
    
    
    The First Car You Can Build Yourself... in an Hour [video] http://stks.co/sXJM  Pretty cool for a little more than $8000 $$ Ships in a box    
    
    
    Alan Greenspan: Where the Economy Went Wrong http://stks.co/cnFM  Fed does not get they created the housing bubble; learn the bond math $$    
    
    
    The 'Rate Gap' Is Rising http://stks.co/dn7T  Gap between deposit rates & borrowing rates is higher than it's been in 32 of last 40 yrs $$    
    
    
    So You Want to Go to Winemaking School? http://stks.co/hq7Q  Visit the UC-Davis viticultural & oenology program. $$ #wine    
    
    
    It isn't only one of the oldest winemaking programs in the country, but arguably the most prestigious $$ #wine    
    
    
    Javelin Files 2 Trade Interest-Rate Swaps, Spurring SEF Shift http://stks.co/dn7V  Smart. Start w/simple liquid derivatives @ exchanges $$    
    
    
    Dollar Drops to 8-Month Low as Risk Appetite Swells on Fed Bets http://stks.co/iq1H  Fed surprising w/unexpected looseness so $$ falls    
    
    
    Fed QE Taper Seen Delayed to March as Shutdown Bites http://stks.co/dn7W  Would not b so sure here; this is only a survey of economists $$    
    
    
    40 Years After Embargo, OPEC Is Over a Barrel http://stks.co/enI2  Few things r truly certain. Dead Worries: OPEC, Russia, Japan, China $$    
    
    
    Two articles on States Clamping Down on Workers as Contractors http://stks.co/jpox  & http://stks.co/iq1I  Develop significant skills $$    
    
    
    Book Review: 'Johnny Carson' by Henry Bushkin http://stks.co/tXJn  Bombastic Bushkin gets 2 dance on the grave in this tell-all book $$    
    
    
    The Chinese Characters Dictation Competition Is a Test Few Could Pass http://stks.co/jpp2  Chinese spelling bee w/ideographs; tough $$    
    
    
    Banks Pushed by Regulators Send ‘Nastygrams’ to Car Dealers http://stks.co/pXWn  Discrimination in lending is taking heat from the CFPB $$    
    
    
    Stanley Druckenmiller: How Washington Really Redistributes Income http://stks.co/rXYd  Baby Boomers suck the blood of those younger $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Negative Book Reviews: Occasionally, I write negative book reviews.  I am not always ri... http://bit.ly/19UWYAk     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: The Fundamentals of Market Tops: All of my articles from RealMoney have been irre... http://bit.ly/1a1EEG2     
    
    
    Experian Sold Consumer Data to ID Theft Service http://stks.co/cnVk  @japhychron yes, significant reason to worry & watch 4 ID theft $$    
    
    
    Contractors See Weeks of Work on Health Site http://stks.co/tXbA  Have friends that once worked 4 CGI; to them this is no surprise $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Traveling with David: Sometimes I over-commit my time.  That’s been the last few days.  Re... http://bit.ly/19CATYu     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Pursue Generational Accounting: I am one of the endorsers of the INFORM Act.  I have belie... http://bit.ly/1agOsfs     
    
    
    Buffett Says Gains in Housing Fall Short of Equilibrium http://stks.co/hrBx  Rare wrong Buffett; US overinvests in residential RE $$    
    
    
    US extends backing for higher-priced mortgages http://stks.co/fr7n  Continuing to subsidize overinvestment in residential real estate $$    
    
    
    Saudi Women Plan to Hit Roads in New Push for Right to Drive http://stks.co/qYag  Fear: if they r allowed 2 drive, will drive out of SA $$    
    
    
    Weitz to Yacktman Hold Cash as Managers Find Few Bargains http://stks.co/fr7s  Not many places 2 compound value w/margin of safety $$    
    
    
    Wal-Mart Now Draws More Solar Power Than 38 US States http://stks.co/jquY  Drop the solar subsidies, and see if $WMT would still do it $$    
    
    
    Obama Joins Putin War as Syria Jihadists Stalk Olympics http://stks.co/eoNO  The Winter Olympic games in Sochi could be a real blast $$ ;)    
    
    
    Low Rates Bring Bond Bonanza http://stks.co/pYca  Corporations act to lock in cheap long-term financing 2pay dividends & buy back stock $$    
    
    
    Ex-Madoff Employee Tells Jury of ‘Cut And Paste’ Trades http://stks.co/tYQM  Employees claim they were duped by Madoff. Q: were they? $$    
    
    
    The Boss Is Watching: Tracking Technology Shakes Up Workplace http://stks.co/fr84  Little brother watches 4 employees who shirk $$    
    
    
    Buffett says he passed on buying Washington Post http://stks.co/boIt  Definitely one to avoid, or throw in the "too hard" bin $$ $WPO    
    
    
    Noonan: ObamaCare Takes On Water http://stks.co/eoNT  Software development is difficult when no single party responsible for everything $$    
    
    
    PCAOB Warns on Internal-Control Problems http://stks.co/eoNU  15% of Auditors didn't get enough data on internal control effectiveness $$    
    
    
    Selling the Good Life on the Great Plains http://stks.co/coJY  Rural areas pitch the slower pace to city dwellers in order to survive $$    
    
    
    Same Old Amazon: All Sales, No Profit http://stks.co/ir5Z  $AMZN borrows2fund investment & uses free cashflow, much like private equity $$    
    
    
    "They are reinvesting their free cash flow, which is different than profits.…" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/aoSS  $$ $AMZN    
    
    
    Why Obamacare Is Like Three Mile Island http://stks.co/gr6o  Problems in overall plan design were foreseeable; not merely and accident $$    
    
    
    Middle Class Americans Face a Retirement Shutdown; 37% Say “I’ll Never Retire, But Work Until I’m 2 Sick or Die,” $$ http://stks.co/tYQf     
    
    
    Reality is setting in if 37% think they won't b able to retire. http://stks.co/fr8M  Reality will arrive when number is 80% $$ $TLT $SPY    
    
    
    I wrote about that more than once @DividendMaster . E.g. http://alephblog.com/2009/04/16/ancient-and-modern-the-retirement-tripod/ … $$    
    
    
    Obama Says Health Care Law More Important Than Website http://stks.co/doD2  If a law can't b administered properly what good is it? $$    
    
    
    The Lessons of Classified Information: From Mossadegh to Snowden http://stks.co/boJU  CIA plot in Iran widely suspected, now confirmed $$    
    
    
    Never believe anything in Washington, DC until it is explicitly denied. The US Government has lied to us in the past $$    
    
    
    Hillary Clinton's 2016 Chances: The Coming Train Wreck http://stks.co/ir6D  Will test whether having a long political resume is good $$    
    
    
    Cruise Prices Sinking: Some Now Cheaper Than Motel 6 http://stks.co/fr91  They will leave the light on 4u; the buffet will b open 2 $$    
    
    
    House flipping makes a comeback http://stks.co/aoTA  Speculation returning to housing market; remember, only cash flows matter 4 prices $$    
    
    
    Never Shop in October and Other Secrets From a Retail Guru http://stks.co/fr9B  Tips on how to avoid how retailers try 2 influence u $$    
    
    
    Might Google Have a Sly Motive Behind Motorola? http://stks.co/coKV  Argues that $GOOG bot Motorola 2 poison profits 4 $AAPL & $SSNLF $$    
    
    
    White House Sets Late-November Target for Fixes to Health Site http://stks.co/coKa  UnitedHealth Group Unit Tapped to Oversee Repairs $$    
    
    
    Federal Centers 4 Medicare and Medicaid Services acted as its own systems integrator for the site: unusual arrangement 4a complex project.$$    
    
    
    China Inc. Battles Big Oil for Century’s Biggest Find http://stks.co/jqw1  They have capital, but not expertise, & r rolling the dice $$    
    
    
    Abby Johnson, the rarely seen face of Fidelity http://stks.co/ir6h  Wonder if the Washington Post pulled the story under pressure $$ $WPO    
    
    
    Treasuries Lose Cachet on Lowest Foreign Demand Since ’01 http://stks.co/fr9P  Bondholders have short memories; wouldn't worry $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Yakuza Bosses Whacked by Regulators Freezing AmEx Cards http://stks.co/fr9R  Money is often the easiest thing to track; leaves a trail $$    
    
    
    Jail Time No Bar to Tea-Server Turned Top Woman Bureaucrat http://stks.co/qYcM  While detained, she used the free time 2 read 150 books $$    
    
    
    A CIO’s First Task: Understanding the Culture http://stks.co/boKG  Understanding the culture is a key to most leadership roles $$    
    
    
    I realize that @Borderscrossed , & I phrased that tweet wrong -- the Chinese typically play w/lower risk ventures. This is unusual 4them $$    
    
    
    Local Governments Have Borrowed a Pile of Money in Recent Years, Leaving Even Beijing Wondering How Much $$ http://stks.co/qYcS     
    
    
    Budget Discord Simmers Among Democrats http://stks.co/rYfT  Some Liberal Groups, Lawmakers Worry About Cuts 2Entitlements $$ biggest issue    
    
    
    How Sensitive we are to Interest Rates: A Scary Picture? http://stks.co/fr9d  Argues moderate rise in rates inverts banks & governments $$    
    
    
    Margin Debt Hits New High http://stks.co/gr8d  Where will additional buying power come to push up stock prices? Only game left is QE? $$    
    
    
    Fixing Economy As Easy As 1-2-3 http://stks.co/hrDq  Axel Merk says 2 make policy predictable, let interest rates rise & allow failure $$    
    
    
    Botched Launch of Health Site Blamed on Poor Coordination http://stks.co/doEO  The software developers point the finger at one another $$    
    
    
    Court could block Obamacare subsidies in 34 states http://stks.co/doES  Legal challenge could knock out the federal exchanges $$    
    
    
    ‘Outrageous’ tax loopholes in Democrat’s sights http://stks.co/ir74  Every loophole has coalition to block its elimination; won't work $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Stanley Druckenmiller crisis predictions: Anyone can call a bubble years in advance. http://stks.co/doEu  But few succeed $$    
    
    
    If you call a crash & you get the reason right, that *is* impressive; timing is always tough. Hint: look for a arb that has gone negative $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Does the United States have $128 trillion in unfunded liabilities? http://stks.co/frAp  Writer does not understand the figures $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Another billionaire is predicting doom. Ignore him. http://stks.co/tYT9  Rather ignore this writer; doesn't understand the stats $$    
    
    
    Financial Report of the US Government http://stks.co/eoQN  Here's my piece. The unfunded liabilities of the Fed Govt r ~$78T $$ 5x GDP    
    
    
    Top China Banks Triple Debt Write-Offs as Defaults Loom http://stks.co/hrF9  They trying to get ahead of the problem, but it's too big $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Interest RatesHow Sensitive we are to Interest Rates: A Scary Pictur... http://bit.ly/1aldMkm     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Amazon: Many people are amazed at the valuation of http://Amazon.com .  How can a co... http://bit.ly/1da53UA     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Bad Theories Lead to Bad Results: From John Mauldin’s latest book, Code Red:Investors shou... http://bit.ly/1dd36Xj     
    
    
    "Consider Stocktwits.  They created cashtags.  To refer to Google, you would type $GOOG.  Twitter…" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/hrSM  $$    
    
    
    http://stks.co/boZ5  Negative interest rates are a way for the government to steal from those that want to keep their risk profile low $$    
    
    
    Are CAT Bonds The Answer to Today’s Retirement Planning Woes? 2 Early 2 Tell…More Transparency Needed! http://stks.co/sYh9  Not4retail $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog The Rules, Part LVII: The more that markets are united through derivatives, the more syste... http://bit.ly/194GKXa     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Fat Tails: I’m reading an investment book that is arguing for market timing.  I’m not i... http://bit.ly/16Jab2v     
    
    
    The NSA’s Rent Is Too High http://stks.co/qZEw  Even if what they do were legitimate, they cost Americans far too much $$    
    
    
    The First Cracks http://stks.co/tZ2m  Some Democrats begin to question PPACA/Obamacare $$    
    
    
    Obamacare and the Death of Liberalism http://stks.co/grl1  Liberalism ends when entitlement promises fail; I say give it 10-15 years $$    
    
    
    Is Your Pension Courting Catastrophe? http://stks.co/pZFM  Good summary & resources, but few pensions invest 2much in CAT bonds $$    
    
    
    Reagan Revolution Misses Tax Fiefdoms Flourishing in US http://stks.co/bouM  Many local municipalities levy taxes; some do little $$ #IL    
    
    
    Man Making Ireland Tax Avoidance Hub Proves Local Hero http://stks.co/sZ2t  Controversial fellow who is not universally admired $$    
    
    
    Wrong: PPP and Japanese Inflation Expectations (Extremely Wonkish) http://stks.co/rZHr  As usual, Krugman says inflation won't hurt $$    
    
    
    An interview with Alan Greenspan http://stks.co/jrYq  One constant w/Greenspan is he will not accept blame for the mistakes he made $$    
    
    
    Six Ways to Ensure Qualified Borrowers Can Get Mortgages http://stks.co/grl5  Unrealistic article, though the part on servicing is good $$    
    
    
    Colorado Secessionists Struggle as Trend Lifts Democratic Votes http://stks.co/pZFO  Secessionists r unrealistic; Congress won't do it $$    
    
    
    Greek Government Bonds Pay Off Big for Fund Managers http://stks.co/dood  Every dog has its day, & this bond mgr rates a healthy "arf" $$    
    
    
    Bond-fund charts of the day, rising-rates edition http://stks.co/hro8  Where @felixsalmon finds the speed of rates rising matters a lot $$    
    
    
    JP Morgan's Subprime Troubles Ran Deep http://stks.co/iriR  The originators r all dead, so they go after one of the last standing $JPM $$    
    
    
    Cheaper Laser Sensors for Self-Driving Cars Are on the Way http://stks.co/frlS  If sensors r that expensive, driverless cars r far-off $$    
    
    
    Obama Unaware as US Spied on World Leaders: Officials http://stks.co/covY  The surveillance state takes on a life of its own $$    
    
    
    Why Consol is Diving Into Natural Gas While Others Jump Out http://stks.co/bouT  Oil > Natgas > Coal | Simple, huh? $CNX $$    
    
    
    Desperately Needed: More Geriatricians  http://stks.co/jrYx  We cannot create more Geriatricians via fiat in the sort run $$    
    
    
    How Mobile Technology is Changing the Way We Dine Out http://stks.co/tZ2t  Social media affects how people choose restaurants $$    
    
    
    The China Americans Don't See http://stks.co/ep0p  China is weaker than it looks b/c it can't handle dissent against the Party $$    
    
    
    Sen. Paul Ties His Fed Bill to Vote on Yellen Nomination http://stks.co/frlV  Auditing Fed's monteary policy decisions is a good idea $$    
    
    
    Who’s Right About Apple’s Cash Pile: Cook or Icahn? http://stks.co/rZHy  Simple: Cook. Most of the $$ is overseas & can't easily return    
    
    
    Mystery of the 'Missing' Global Warming http://stks.co/grl9  Argues that rising water temperatures r more indicative of the problems $$    
    
    
    How Our Brains Betray Us http://stks.co/bouX  We tend 2b 2 optimistic about the future,& not realistic enough about the present $$    
    
    
    Software Helps GOP House Majority Leader Isolate ‘Astroturf’ Emails http://stks.co/jrZB  Easy 2c lazy ppl who only have time 2 copy $$    
    
    
    Armed agents seize records of reporter, Washington Times prepares legal action http://stks.co/covd  State & Military abuse reporter $$    
    
    
    Wrong: The political middle is dying. But it’s not redistricting’s fault. http://stks.co/jrZF  We need to force the middle to govern $$    
    
    
    How Jon Stewart became President Obama’s biggest problem http://stks.co/ap4A  Lousy efforts from the govt deserve 2b exposed $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Startup Defeats the Captcha, Wins One for the Machines http://stks.co/irib  Captchas have evolved beyond what has been cracked $$    
    
    
    If New York Freezes in January Blame Siberian Snow Now http://stks.co/iric  These tendencies r weak, like most things on global warming $$    
    
    
    Evangelical Pastors, Marriott CEO United on Immigration http://stks.co/sZ3B  So long as we do not give them benefits, immigrants r good $$    
    
    
    The Lust Beneath Japan's Sex Drought  http://stks.co/grlH  Japan's sex culture is perverse, & their society shrinks as a result $$    
    
    
    The Great Pension-Bonus Giveaway Fiasco http://stks.co/jrZK  One of the stupidest things in pensions, allowing ppl 2spike benefits $$    
    
    
    Americans lose coverage, Democrats say Obama too rosy about health care law http://stks.co/frlc  My plan was canceled; i had no choice $$    
    
    
    First, this isn't new. I had professors talking about this in the early 1980s. Second, what may work when... http://read.bi/HuLM4J     
    
    
    Study Sheds Light on the Dark Side of China's Urbanization http://stks.co/frsS  Communism alienates from the means of production $$ #China    
    
    
    Five Bad Ways to Pick a Mutual Fund http://stks.co/dovT  Good as far as it goes. Important: don't chase performance or ratings $$    
    
    
    Dell’s Mitzvah Rescued Buyout as JPMorgan’s Lee Warned of Perils http://stks.co/pZMd  Da dirt, da whole dirt & nuttin but da dirt $$    
    
    
    Crop Insurance Hazards Shown in Lost Pheasants in Grasslands http://stks.co/hrv2  W/Ag doing so well, we need to end the Ins subsidies $$    
    
    
    Insurers Oppose Obamacare Extension as Danger to Profits http://stks.co/rZP7  Clever Obama got the insurance companies2carry water4him $$    
    
    
    Drones Delivering Pizza? Venture Capitalists Wager on It http://stks.co/grsP  Sadly, the pizza was cold when it arrived. $$    
    
    
    "The difficulty w/prosecution is apportioning blame. Easier to go after the corporation." — David_Merkel http://stks.co/cp2Q  $$    
    
    
    The ObamaCare Awakening http://stks.co/bp16  Americans are losing their coverage by political design. That's a feature, not a bug $$ #lose    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Redacted Version of the October 2013 FOMC Statement: September 2013October 2013CommentsInf... http://bit.ly/1dOz1jQ     
    
    
    Pension Pinch Busts City Budgets http://stks.co/gruP  W/underfunded plans, watch the cash cost curve: what u expect to pay going fwd $$    
    
    
    The expected future payments from defined benefit plans is the acid test for municipal finances; that includes social security & medicare $$    
    
    
    The 50 Greatest Breakthroughs Since the Wheel http://stks.co/cp42  Ambitious article that explains why innovation benefits us all $$    
    
    
    India Breast Cancer Surge Hinders Private Exams for Women http://stks.co/bp2m  Big problem, few resources; makes me feel sorry for them $$    
    
    
    http://stks.co/rZRZ  "Now Fink tells us.  He was more of a cheerleader for QE at its start." — David_Merkel http://stks.co/rZRa  $$    
    
    
    BlackRock’s Fink Says There Are ‘Bubble-Like Markets Again’ http://stks.co/cp4Q  "Fed policy is contributing to 'bubble-like markets.'" $$    
    
    
    Wall Street is way too bullish http://stks.co/pZOq  Collapsing time horizons may presage a bearish turn for the risky asset markets $$    
    
    
    3 ‘amazing’ facts about the stock market http://stks.co/jrkL  Amazing fact #3: The stock market’s Sept and Oct have both been positive $$    
    
    
    Amazing fact #1: Market has been unexpectedly strong since May 1 | Amazing fact #2: Market’s YTD 2013 returns have never been negative $$    
    
    
    Bear hunting http://stks.co/tZEi  Bear shortage has a few wondering who is left to buy from existing stockholders $$    
    
    
    'Skew' Measure Points to Excessive Market Optimism http://stks.co/frxw  Calls priced high, puts priced low & we r not so bad u know? $$    
    
    
    If you too should choose to skew sir, with the skew-goose, please sir, do sir -- w/apologies to Dr. Suess $$    
    
    
    I do not want to spend my days, writing out the i's & j's. But i's & j's are an enigma, when squashed between a double sigma $$ #mathpoetry    
    
    
    Rebuilding Reserves Means U-Turn on Treasuries http://stks.co/jrml  The $$ is not the only game in town, better liquidity than others $$    
    
    
    Political Gridlock, Beijing Style http://stks.co/sZFl  Entrenched economic interests fight Party leadership seeking economic reform $$    
    
    
    Yes, People Are Losing Their Insurance Under Obamacare http://stks.co/irwF  Affects some people who buy their health plans on their own $$    
    
    
    OGX Bankruptcy Filing Caps Batista’s $30 Billion Demise http://stks.co/apHl  He seemed incredible to me at first, he is credible now $$    
    
    
    Christie Confounded as Padded Services Send New Jersey Taxes Soaring http://stks.co/epGd  NJ & corruption? We r supposed 2b surprised? $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog The Municipal Pension Payment Curve: This article was originally going to be titled, “Dyin... http://bit.ly/19dupjG     
    
    
    Stop Subsidizing Colleges’ 100-Year Debt Binge http://stks.co/qZUP  Colleges r more fragile than 2 last 100 years; don't lend 2 them $$    
    
    
    Budget Deficit in US Narrows to 5-Year Low on Record Revenue http://stks.co/irxj  But it needs 2 shrink further, it is 2 big $$    
    
    
    Japan Salaries Extend Fall as Abe Urges Companies 2 Raise Wages http://stks.co/apHo  Abe has quite an imagination; markets will dictate $$    
    
    
    Obama Tempers Insurance Pledge as Health Fight Rages http://stks.co/hs4I  An arrogant man who doesn't understand economics and lies $$    
    
    
    Little Sign of Housing Bubble in Land Prices http://stks.co/rZXa  Overinvested for a long time; we shouldn't subsidize home ownership $$    
    
    
    @viccan1 I don't believe in conspiracy theories    
    
    
    Now Amazon Is Just Giving Money Away http://stks.co/apHr  $AMZN -> great nonprofit that eats businesses continues like Galactus $$ #nomnom    
    
    
    Lincoln National Wins $4 Billion Annuity Reinsurance Deal http://stks.co/apHt  I find this dubious, but $WFC is the likely loser $$    
    
    
    PwC Agrees to Purchase Booz to Expand Advisory Services http://stks.co/gs6H  Conflict of interests: auditing firms 4 which they consult $$    
    
    
    Eike Batista's Empire Soared, Then Melted Into Bankruptcy http://stks.co/gs6v  At best, a huckster. At worst, a robber. A cheater $$    
    
    
    Phillips 66 to Build Texas Terminal to Export Propane, Butane Overseas http://stks.co/pZad  Exporting nonstandard fuels from fracking $$    
    
    
    You Can Keep Your Health Plan* http://stks.co/hsA5  *Except if it not a health plan that the Obama Administration does not like $$ #lies    
    
    
    Greek Recovery Makes Stocks World’s Best as Paulson Buys http://stks.co/dpA3  Buy on the rumor, sell on the news, stick a fork in it $$    
    
    
    Ignore Greek Elections: Stocks Might Be the Best Buy in over 60 Years http://stks.co/fs7S  Good call from @valuewalk timely/contrarian $$    
    
    
    Obama's Broken Promise of Better Government Through Technology http://stks.co/fs8B  Bigness of govt tends to sabotage tech development $$    
    
    
    Counties Made for Horse and Buggy Reject Savings http://stks.co/pZbc  Ppl value tangible/local govt & don't begrudge its costs so much $$    
    
    
    Yalies Yellen, Hamada Put Tobin Twist Theory to Work in QE http://stks.co/rZez  Op Twist might work at low debt levels, not at high $$    
    
    
    Gross Says America’s Privileged 1% Should Pay Higher Taxes http://stks.co/rZfD  Real problem is definition of income; 2much deferral $$    
    
    
    12 Steps toward a Simpler, Pro-Growth Tax Code http://stks.co/jrw7  Problem is 2Much deferral of income tax & favoring investment $$    
    
    
    Policymakers think of investment like magic; just because u invest does not mean everyone will be better off; investment can b a waste $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Germany Hits Back at US Over Economic Criticism http://stks.co/jrwF  Neomercantistic Germany's surpluses will not get paid back $$    
    
    
    $$ @ritholtz It is a plan if you prefund the deductible, which many medical service providers r requiring w/PPACA plans b4 service granted    
    
    
    Obamacare’s Biggest Threat Isn’t the Website http://stks.co/tZQm   burdensome complexity subsidy-based plan; failure universal coverage $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Industry Ranks November 2013:  My main industry model is illustrated in the graphic. Green... http://bit.ly/19hl5v5     
    
    
    JP Morgan sees 'most extreme excess' of global liquidity ever http://stks.co/rZmY  Global QE leads to a surfeit of spendable funds $$    
    
    
    Buffett’s $40B Cash Pile Provides Acquisition Fuel http://stks.co/pZjk  Would view largest private companies look4 transitional probs $$    
    
    
    Keep the Economists off the Trading Desk http://stks.co/fsFj  As Howard Simons said, "Stocks are not GDP futures." Ignore the economy $$    
    
    
    Tax delinquents by the thousands have security clearances, GAO finds http://stks.co/gsJg  Easier 2 suborn someone who is in debt $$    
    
    
    Speedy Lunches Urged at SEC as Union Decries Time-Clock Watching http://stks.co/fsLO  Never knew SEC workers had a union $$ #huh    
    
    
    Japan Stocks Sink to Monthly Worst in Developed Markets http://stks.co/tZck  Really difficult 2c how Japan normalizes econ policy $$    
    
    
    Wife Poisoning Husband’s Lover Tests Weapons Law at High Court http://stks.co/sZdz  Upheld, would federalize all crimes using chemicals $$    
    
    
    No Bones About It: Day of the Dead Is Finding New Life http://stks.co/fsMX  Life is for the living; let the dead bury their own dead $$    
    
    
    Prosecutor Pleasantly Surprised to Find There's a Law Against Fraud http://stks.co/pZqg  Regulators use FIRREA to prosecute finl fraud $$    
    
    
    NSA infiltrates links to Yahoo, Google data centers worldwide, Snowden documents say http://stks.co/apdN  $$ shot: http://stks.co/cpVi     
    
    
    How anti-NSA backlash could fracture the Internet along national borders http://stks.co/sZf3  Democratic nations hate being NSA snooped $$    
    
    
    Edward Snowden Has Japan Copying China’s Playbook http://stks.co/jsAq  Excessive secrecy creates environment for government wrongdoing $$    
    
    
    Fed’s Bubble Alarm Stuck on Snooze http://stks.co/epcM  Not in Fed's interest 2 go bubble hunting, do bad enough w/inflation & unempmt $$    
    
    
    Furious Tech Giants Fight Back Against NSA Surveillance http://stks.co/qZqd  Ripple effect from Snowden's revelations get bigger weekly $$    
    
    
    Health Policies Canceled in Latest Hurdle for Obamacare http://stks.co/pZra  I'm grandfathered for now, but how long will that last? $$    
    
    
    Berkshire Hathaway defends asbestos claim-paying record vs stories by Mark Greenblatt of Scripps News http://stks.co/cpWK  FD: + $BRK.B $$    
    
    
    Will Toilet Rules Prove EU's Waterloo? http://stks.co/qZuK  Standardizing toilet specifications across different cultures is futile $$    
    
    
    Harbinger Insurer Switches 2 Iowa Watchdog From Maryland http://stks.co/qZuL  Decamping 4a more friendly & sophisticated regulator $$ $HRG    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Market Impact Keep the Economists off the Trading Desk http:... http://bit.ly/1cx4H9A     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Win by not Losing:  Just follow my methods and you will make money. Yes, it i... http://bit.ly/1aQQMM9     
    
    
    Reduce the noise levels in your investment process http://stks.co/cpdg  @ritholtz guides us in telling us what chatter 2 avoid hearing $$    
    
    
    The new American capitalism: Rise of the distorporation http://stks.co/aplH  Thinly capitalized corporations that distribute profits $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: The Manual of Ideas:  I’m a value investor, and one that is not doctrinaire a... http://bit.ly/1cBfT4Y     
    
    
    "Well done, Barry.  Your writing skill has taken you above and beyond." — David_Merkel http://disq.us/8fzan6  @ritholtz new @bloomberg $$    
    
    
    @rithotlz First Bloomberg View Column: Welcome http://stks.co/pa8a  Bloomberg picks up a great columnist grown from financial blogging $$    
    
    
    @ritholtz First Bloomberg View Column: Welcome http://stks.co/isaN  Bloomberg picks up a great columnist grown from financial blogging $$    
    
    
    Merkel Facing Power Dilemma as Coal Plants Open http://stks.co/dphT  Note that Germany does not care much about CO2 emissions $$    
    
    
    Capt.James A. Kirk Takes Command of Navy Vessel http://stks.co/qa9V  His nickname is "T." His vessel has advanced cloaking abilities $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Asymmetric Return With A Catalyst http://stks.co/dphg  Writer doesn't get difficultly of getting free $$ from life insurers $HRG    
    
    
    http://stks.co/bplv  Comps of $MET & $PRU - horribly optimistic. $NWLI would be better. Another reason I don't read seeking alpha $$ $HRG    
    
    
    Here's How Much Berkshire Hathaway Made On Financial Weapons Of Mass Destruction In Q3 http://stks.co/jsU3  Buffett wins | FD: + $BRK.B $$    
    
    
    Western Digital Adds Helium to Enterprise Hard Drives http://stks.co/hsjq  More storage, less power use,aids big data | FD: + $WDC $$    
    
    
    Mr. Obama, I Am Unhappy That Obamacare Threatens To Kill Me. http://stks.co/bpmM  PPACA sob story #1, loses his healthcare coverage $$    
    
    
    A Stage-4 Gallblader Cancer Survivor Says: I Am One of ObamaCare's Losers http://stks.co/fsfd  PPACA sob story #2 loses coverage & docs $$    
    
    
    Obama's Broken Promise of Better Government Through Technology http://stks.co/fsfe  Technology is only as good as its implementation $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Expedited Bidding Limited Who Could Build Site http://stks.co/iscj  US Medicare&Medicaid Services preapproved 16, only 4 bids $$    
    
    
    New Homes Get Built With Renters in Mind http://stks.co/tZxk  If investors r truly long-term 4 running rentals, this could b stable $$    
    
    
    Wrong: If It Looks Like a Bank, Regulate It Like a Bank http://stks.co/jsUU  Money market funds don't look like banks; very safe assets $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Americans’ Debt Hangover Seen Ending in Boost to Growth http://stks.co/tZxn  The consumer remains highly leveraged vs history $$    
    
    
    Investors Return to IPOs in Force http://stks.co/dpiJ  Fresh Fruits r opposite of IPOs, good when plentiful, IPOs bad when plentiful $$    
    
    
    Rankings That Rankle http://stks.co/dpiT  Rather than reform further, China would rather shoot the messenger bearing bad tidings $$    
    
    
    Kyoto Veterans Say Global Warming Goal Slipping Away http://stks.co/gsi9  No incentive to cut carbon emissions; eg, Germany's coal use $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Economists overvalue stock markets http://stks.co/paCr  Stock prices provide valuable economic signals: http://stks.co/tZzJ  $$    
    
    
    Over the last 10 years investing in venture capital has not outperformed public equity (Pg 5) http://stks.co/qaBx  Capital Index.pdf $$    
    
    
    Universal Life Policies Hurt by Low-Rate Era http://stks.co/paHQ  Guaranteed rates high relative to current interest rate environment $$    
    
    
    Makes me wonder whether the life companies didn't also raise mortality charges in order to make up 4 compressed/negative interest margins $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Currencies after the Crash:  Sara Eisen is smart.  How smart is Sara Eisen?  ... http://bit.ly/1b26BxT     
    
    
    Coconut Crisis Looms as Postwar Palm Trees Age http://stks.co/qaGS  Coconut Trees have aged w/not enough replanting, cuts into yields $$    
    
    
    FHFA Takes Aim at 'Forced' Insurance http://stks.co/sa9T  Won't happen, b/c banks won't lend if proprty is uninsured against casualties $$    
    
    
    Simple Tech Fix Could Allow Millions to Hear - Bloomberg http://stks.co/qaL5  Transmits sound directly to a listener’s hearing aid $$    
    
    
    Anand On How Computers Have Changed Chess http://stks.co/jsg0  Most openings have become transparent; only odd openings offer surprise $$    
    
    
    Game of thrones with world chess champion Viswanathan Anand http://stks.co/sa9g  Long piece on the reigning chess champ & new challenge $$    
    
    
    More Commuters Self-Driven, Census Finds http://stks.co/bpyF  Surprising that no one has found an internet-based solution 4 carpooling $$    
    
    
    Gross Loses World’s Largest Mutual Fund Title to Vanguard http://stks.co/gss3  Wonder if Pimco is 2big 4 Gross' quant strategies 2 work $$    
    
    
    http://stks.co/cq18  You could try applying the same to Title and Mortgage insurer kickbacks." — David_Merkel http://stks.co/bq0E  $$    
    
    
    Banks offering mortgages with only 5% down payments http://stks.co/bq0M  Financing long-term assets w/low equity helped create crisis $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Think inside the (right) box; 5 must-read business books http://stks.co/qaNS  I read "Big Data." Good, not great. Rest look iffy $$    
    
    
    "Disagree. I read "Big Data." Good, not great.  Others look iffy, particularly 'Antifragile.'" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/dpvc  $$    
    
    
    Congress May Push Milk Prices to $8 a Gallon http://stks.co/bq0Z  The solution is 2 end milk price supports; have a free market in milk $$    
    
    
    The 4% Safe Withdrawal Rule Declines to 3% http://stks.co/fstG  My rule: Take 10Y Treasury yield, +1% if neutral, +2% if bullish $$    
    
    
    Mom co-signed, now stuck with student loan payments http://stks.co/bq0e  Never co-sign, not for a child, parent, friend, anyone, ever $$    
    
    
    Can I repo a car if I co-signed the auto loan? http://stks.co/hsyj  Rather, lend them the $$ w/a formal loan document; NEVER co-sign!!    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Don’t Co-sign, Ever: This morning, I am here to tell you never to co-sign for a loan.  The... http://bit.ly/1cRmR6b     
    
    
    Symbolic Family: De Blasio Success Shows Sea Change for Interracial Couples http://stks.co/gt7V  We're one race: We're human $$    
    
    
    McDonnell v. Royal Dutch Shell Plc 13-cv-07089 http://stks.co/eqLq  <-- If anyone wants 2c the complaint on Dated Brent Crude Rigging $$    
    
    
    IRS Cracks Down on Breaks 4 Rich Americans http://stks.co/eqM7  Cracks down on conservation easements; graphic: http://stks.co/aqN4  $$    
    
    
    A tax break for wealthy landowners under scrutiny, from @BBGVisualData http://stks.co/pad5  Many parties allied to keep low value break $$    
    
    
    Wells Fargo Said to Face US Mortgage-Bond Probe http://stks.co/aqNI  FIRREA statute used. $BAC $CSGN $JPM $C $WFC all face these probes $$    
    
    
    Jonathan Tepper on Obamacare http://stks.co/ft8z  A relatively neutral assessment of PPACA, which does not reduce oligopolies & costs $$    
    
    
    BlackRock, Fidelity Face Initial Risk Study by Regulators http://stks.co/htGg  That they would consider this proves they r clueless $$    
    
    
    Obama repeatedly promised people could keep their health insurance under Obamacare http://stks.co/saUX  Law affected ability 2 do that $$    
    
    
    CFPB Debt Collection Rules May Move in Unprecedented Direction http://stks.co/gtCH  May even affect ability to collect on private debts $$    
    
    
    An Intriguing Product That’s Too Complex for Many http://stks.co/bqHy  If u don't understand what it does, u won't know when 2 buy&sell $$    
    
    
    SEC Fines Greater Wenatchee Regional Events District4Misleading Investors http://stks.co/rai2  Failed2disclose certain finl projections $$    
    
    
    Kozicki Shows Central Bankers Only as Good as Forecasts http://stks.co/qaev  Proves we shouldn't rely on neoclassical economic models $$    
    
    
    The siren call of Microsoft Excel http://stks.co/jt0Q  Excel has its uses, but not for security, audit & production. Use 2 prototype $$    
    
    
    Excel monkeys unite! For today, we are cancelling the circular reference! http://stks.co/ftAr  On the challenging Modeloff competition $$    
    
    
    MSNMoney's Jubak:Fed Has No Way Out of Its Mountain of Debt http://stks.co/cqJ2  No surprise. Central bank balance sheets rarely shrink $$    
    
    
    Colorado Education-Tax Measure Fails http://stks.co/cqJ5  Interesting datapoint; even 4 local schools, difficult 2 raise income taxes $$    
    
    
    Utilities in Pain Selling Renewable Assets at Record Rate http://stks.co/aqRr  Utilities don't want 2 allocate capital to low returners $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Why 'Rate Shock' Is An Essential Part Of Health Reform http://stks.co/taUG  People should not be forced 2buy more than they want $$    
    
    
    Real health reform would remove all government preferences, including the employer deduction, & move to a client pays directly model $$    
    
    
    It would involved tort reform, & encouragement of charities to aid the sick, & would shrink Medicare & Medicaid, moving 2a free market $$    
    
    
    Obama's Catastrophic Victory http://stks.co/jt0j  Wait till people with bronze policies have to pay their costs prior to the deductible $$    
    
    
    The red-blue divide in personal finance http://stks.co/taUP  Shares my view on Dave Ramsey; useful 4 $$ management, avoid on investing    
    
    
    When bonds don’t trade http://stks.co/aqS1  Difficult to facilitate buyside trading w/each other; they want to keep their moves quiet $$    
    
    
    Many bonds only have a small number of holders, so it gets easier to guess who the big traders might b, thus affecting the market price $$    
    
    
    Of Debt, Growth, Interest Rates and History http://stks.co/taUY  High debt & real interest rates tend to dampen economic growth $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Talking to Management, Part 1: The Big Questions: This was originally published o... http://bit.ly/1b8jdW6     
    
    
    Greenspan’s Bequest to Yellen Is Board Harmony Shown in Records http://stks.co/itQR  more interesting is Volcker offering 2resign in 86 $$    
    
    
    Most US Blockbuster Stores to Close http://stks.co/bqZn  The internet changes everything; anything that can be bytes is blown to bits $$    
    
    
    China’s Soviet-Style Suburbia Heralds Environmental Pain http://stks.co/tamA  Central planning fails again $$    
    
    
    Wrong Fed Study: Lengthen Low-Rate Guidance to Fix Unemployment Faster http://stks.co/eqnj  No data on unemployment in liquidity trap $$    
    
    
    The Dividend Challenge http://stks.co/eqnm  E.g., In 1993-1994 dividend-oriented funds did horribly as rates soared. Divs aren't magic $$    
    
    
    The Biggest Little Secret In Money Management http://stks.co/htns  Most new fancy strategies can mostly be replicated in simple ways $$    
    
    
    Twitter Sold Some Stock http://stks.co/cqoC  Valuing speculative companies is tough. Ask how much of sectoral profits they could grab $$    
    
    
    Then discount that at 20%/year, and decide whether you have enough margin for considerable error.  I don't think Twitter gets there. $$    
    
    
    Artificial Trans Fats in Food Deemed Unsafe by US FDA http://stks.co/eqvb  Y R we limiting freedom in something so basic as food? $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Website Frustrations Persist as Deadline Looms http://stks.co/eqvc  Harder to fix bad code than to rewrite the system $$ #loser    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog What a Tweet Valuation!: I don’t have a strong sense on the valuation of Twitter, but I wa... http://bit.ly/1d1k4Ya     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Companies & Industries Twitter Sold Some Stock http://t.co/oIwxhl5BA... http://bit.ly/1dbLqL6     
    
    
    When enough people do power poses, it will lose its impact, and will cease to give confidence. http://lnkd.in/dzjisst     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Ten Years of Investment Writing: I’m late on this.  My first foray into public writing on ... http://bit.ly/1bqs2e2     
    
    
    Bloomberg Is Said 2Curb Articles That Might Anger China http://stks.co/iuRH  @Bloomberg hides articles critical of China from China $$    
    
    
    Amazon, Postal Service to Start Sunday Package Deliveries http://stks.co/eriz  USPS lives at the pleasure of Amazon $$    
    
    
    I Am The One Who Blogs: TRB Turns Five http://stks.co/craD  @reformedbroker is one of the heroes of financial blogging; I salute him $$    
    
    
    CIA warily watches for threats to US now that 87 nations possess drones http://stks.co/arid  drones from Israel & China compete vs US $$    
    
    
    Strange Doings on the Sun http://stks.co/rc0t  We do not understand the Sun well; sunspots r few, & magnetic poles puzzle. $$ #humility    
    
    
    Baby Boom in Stronger States Signals US Birth Recovery http://stks.co/guV0  NO surprise, the US has always been more optimistic w/kids $$    
    
    
    Gold Vault Opens in China as Bullion Goes From West to East http://stks.co/qbyX  If you didn't trust fiat currencies u would buy gold 2 $$    
    
    
    Rules Force Banks to Innovate for Survival http://stks.co/rc0x ! Same old thing -- Returns on assets r low, so lever up 4 high ROEs $$    
    
    
    State and local government austerity is over http://stks.co/iuSE  Jobs r growing, & so is investment. Only problem: underfunded plans $$    
    
    
    No state has all of its employee benefit plans funded at an acceptable earnings rate, as well as rainy day funds, highway, funds, etc $$    
    
    
    Patty Murray, Democrats' Budget Leader, Faces a New Test http://stks.co/huay  A lot of theater here; whatever cuts spending wins $$    
    
    
    The Obamacare Debacle Should Have Obama And Biden Seriously Considering Resignation. http://stks.co/iuSF  Nice thought, but not likely $$    
    
    
    Rieder: An empty pledge comes back to haunt Obama http://stks.co/erj8  Obama promised people they could keep their insurance & doctor $$    
    
    
    Yellen's Confirmation Hearing Likely to Stir Up Other Fed Issues http://stks.co/arik  Incompetent Fed gets 2 spread incompetence via DF $$    
    
    
    Record Number of Foreign Students Flocking to US http://stks.co/guV4  This rescues a wide number of incompetent colleges $$    
    
    
    Group Pushes for Bigger 'Tick' Sizes http://stks.co/juIL  Very dumb; deregulate tick sizes,& let markets compete 4 business $$    
    
    
    Focusing too narrowly in college could backfire http://stks.co/pc1O  Narrow degrees presume too much about the future; be prepared $$    
    
    
    An iPhone Tester Caught in Apple's Supply Chain http://stks.co/aril  Very difficult to assure fair dealing w/high demand 4 labor $$    
    
    
    Banks in Sweden Told to Reduce Market Reliance for Mortgages http://stks.co/brYN  Not sure that basing off of kronor deposits is best $$    
    
    
    Race to Bottom Resumes as Central Bankers Ease Anew: http://stks.co/erjA  Everybody aims 4advantage; as a result no one gets advantage $$    
    
    
    StreetEYE - Tops on Twitter http://stks.co/sbp6  Interesting ranking of those who share on finance on Twitter $$    
    
    
    "Junk science causing people to avoid food that is good for most, and yummy too." — David Merkel http://disq.us/8g4bvz  $$    
    
    
    Bad idea: Firms Get More Wiggle Room on Soured Deals http://stks.co/hunX  Goodwill should b rigorously tested & written down frequently $$    
    
    
    Hope Is All Obamacare Has Left http://stks.co/gui6  Tactical retreat 4a time comes to mind, but are they humble enough to consider it? $$    
    
    
    Pension Terminations May Spike in the Near-Term http://stks.co/tc0T  DB pensions will continue 2 shrink; no reason y it should speed up $$    
    
    
    White House Takes Lessons From Bernanke Close Call http://stks.co/iufi  Works 2manage approval process 4 Yellen, given unpopular policy $$    
    
    
    Gold is much harder to manipulate; same for any money with real backing. http://read.bi/1dmGi6Q     
    
    
    Terrifying Charts For Saudi Arabia http://stks.co/tc0r  Fascinating charts showing possibility of falling oil revenue 4 Saudi Arabia $$    
    
    
    Nonbank Mortgage Servicers Rapid Growth Alarms Investors http://stks.co/drgO  Independent mtge servicers grow & have compliance issues $$    
    
    
    Central Banks Risk Asset Bubbles in Battle With Deflation http://stks.co/iv2r  Imbalances r growing. Which way will policymakers err? $$    
    
    
    Yellen Rejoins QE Debate as Hearing Gives Critics Forum http://stks.co/juuA  Pursuing policies that have never worked as if reasonable $$    
    
    
    Secret Israel Housing Boom Defies Settlement Discord http://stks.co/pcep  Settlements keep growing w/tacit assistance of Israeli govt $$    
    
    
    U.S. Mint’s Silver-Coin Sales Reach Annual Record http://stks.co/qccW  U can laugh; fascinating 2c so many trying to preserve value $$    
    
    
    ObamaCare Questions Nobody Asked http://stks.co/csCz  Laws must fit a culture; Americans don't have a high degree of "social trust" $$    
    
    
    A Nuclear Cleanup Effort Leaves Questions Lingering at Scores of Old Sites http://stks.co/juuR  Long article; radiological waste maps $$    
    
    
    Freddie Taps Reinsurer to Offset Loan Risks http://stks.co/gv7J  Would b a little skeptical of $ACGL ; financial reinsurance is risky $$    
    
    
    Japan's Lenders Roiled by Credit for Criminals http://stks.co/hvED  Many Japanese banks lend to the Yakuza, embarrassing them & govt $$    
    
    
    O’Shaughnessy warns on crisis in long-duration bonds http://stks.co/fv5x  Really depends on how strong economic growth is from here $$    
    
    
    @Frank_McG I don't think I mentioned bitcoins, but there are certainly some that trust in them...    
    
    
    Sebelius Drops New Bombshell: Employer Plans Will Also Drop Workers From Coverage http://stks.co/csD4  "Substandard" plans of employers $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy, Part 1: Sorry, but due to traffic, I missed Plosser... http://bit.ly/1du779v     
    
    
    Cato Monetary policy conf, panel 2 -- ALTERNATIVES TO DISCRETIONARY GOVERNMENT FIAT MONEY #catoonmoney Sumner will provide alternatives $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy, Part 2: The next panel:Lawrence H. White Professor ... http://bit.ly/1cYAEMe     
    
    
    Leszek Balcerowicz Former Chairman, National Bank of Poland finishes a rambling, interesting talk on Eurozone & US $$ policy #catoonmoney    
    
    
    Argues that European nations would be better off w/their own national currency. Fiscal union not well defined $$ #catoonmoney    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy, Part 3: Post-luncheon address from Leszek Balcerowi... http://bit.ly/1bxMkSP     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy Conference, Part 4: Panel:Rep. Jeb Hensarling Chairm... http://bit.ly/1a9c3R7     
    
    
    PANEL 4: THE CASE FOR A NATIONAL MONETARY COMMISSION AND FUNDAMENTAL REFORM #catoonmoney Kevin Brady going to speak on Fed Reform $$    
    
    
    R. David Ranson #catoonmoney argues that easy monetary policy has not created faster economic growth http://stks.co/scja  $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy Conference, Part 5: PanelRep. Kevin P. Brady Chairma... http://bit.ly/1a9rCs2     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy Conference, Part 6: CLOSING ADDRESSLewis E. Lehrman ... http://bit.ly/1ctxV8t     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog At the Cato Institute Monetary Policy Conference, Part 7 (Final, Recap): What I wrote in t... http://bit.ly/18yV6fb     
    
    
    GE To Exit Retail Lending, Refocus on Industrial Businesses http://stks.co/td2m  I recommended $GE do that 8 years ago @ RealMoney. $$    
    
    
    Obamacare's Creative, Or Illegal, Rule-Making http://stks.co/pdGn  Obama was critical of Bush's signing statements & this is worse $$    
    
    
    China Leadership Pledges Expansion of Economic Freedoms http://stks.co/ivgX  More kids, more freedom w/real estate, SOEs get taxed more $$    
    
    
    Bid Wars Wane in US Housing Markets on Supply Rise http://stks.co/dsgc  Note: we never eliminated the housing glut; reality returns $$    
    
    
    Spain Free-for-All Pitting Apollo Against Blackstone http://stks.co/rdHB  Global demand 4 vacations in Spain support lodging prices $$    
    
    
    Moody’s Lowers Ratings of Four US Banks After Review http://stks.co/bsjz  $GS $MS $JPM $BK will not b bailed out, thus ratings fall $$    
    
    
    They'll Pay You to Live in Switzerland! http://stks.co/jvVi  Minimum income plan may replace other safety nets, sounds like a disaster $$    
    
    
    Silicon Valley Nerds Seek Revenge on NSA Spies With Coding http://stks.co/qdEI  They double the length of encryption keys; Nyaah, NSA! $$    
    
    
    Maersk CEO Says Balancing Supply of Ships to Demand Is Years Off http://stks.co/dsgd  Will take 2+ years 4 the shipping mkt 2 normalize $$    
    
    
    Woods Makes Caddie’s Beef Jerky Golf-Bag Accessory at $54-Pound http://stks.co/qdEJ  At the Merkel house we r planning on making jerky $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Is Whatever Obama Says It Is http://stks.co/qdEL  Other presidents would be impeached for taking the law into their own hands $$    
    
    
    Bank Regulation Dominates Yellen Confirmation Hearing http://stks.co/qdEM  Given all of the regulatory failures of the Fed this is fair $$    
    
    
    Ackman Makes Big Bet on Fannie, Freddie http://stks.co/csnm  Depends on whether the government will sell it off cheaply if at all $$    
    
    
    In Blow to Coal, TVA to Shut 8 Units http://stks.co/dsgf  Coal has issues in the short run, will provide power to the world 20+ yrs out $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Companies & Industries Ackman Makes Big Bet on Fannie, Freddie http:... http://bit.ly/1eZPimo     
    
    
    "You can never eliminate all risk. Never, but let's do our best." — David Merkel http://stks.co/ctCU  $$ Article: http://stks.co/etKm     
    
    
    "Would be better if the male saved up gold to give to the woman in trust.  It would help protect…" — David Merkel http://stks.co/dt7V  $$    
    
    
    "Few banks bought insurers, and few insurers bought banks.  By the time the meltdown hit, Citi had…"  David Merkel http://stks.co/rdk2  $$    
    
    
    "Rating agencies are only capable of dealing with financial instruments that have gone through a…" — David Merkel http://stks.co/btBc  $$    
    
    
    US Military Eyes Cut to Pay, Benefits  http://stks.co/fwCK  Military is thinking much farther ahead than the politicians they serve $$    
    
    
    What Castro Knew About Lee Harvey Oswald http://stks.co/dtAo  Argues Cuba did not plan the assassination, but encouraged Oswald 2do it $$    
    
    
    A Sub-$1,000 3D Printer for Metal http://stks.co/atPW  Not quite, you have to have your own kiln in order to process the clay/metal $$    
    
    
    It’s Fed Versus Moody’s for ‘Most Wrong’ Crown http://stks.co/dtB7  Fed by a mile here; regulators should disallow unseasoned assets $$    
    
    
    A Conservative Cure for Obamacare http://stks.co/iwBi  A challenge in 2017: fix PPACA or destroy it? Nothing big will change till then $$    
    
    
    Inherited Money To Manage? Overcoming Emotion Is Key To Big Returns http://stks.co/hwNY  This is essential to ALL money management $$    
    
    
    Risk of a Stock Market Melt-Up? http://stks.co/pdq8  ​Federal Reserve Ultra-Dovishness, Technicals, the Economy  and the TINA effect... $$    
    
    
    Why No Bankers Go to Jail http://stks.co/ctKK  Theory 5: Easier for the government to discipline corporations than prosecute felonies $$    
    
    
    Brookfield’s Looking-Glass World Foundation http://stks.co/atV5  $BAM $BIP $BPO $BRP $INF $BEP $BOXC $BPY Be wary of opaque disclosures $$    
    
    
    Buying Low Thwarted by Narrowest Stock Valuation Gap Ever http://stks.co/jw5P  I'm not finding many cheap stocks out there. $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog An Alternative To Federal Reserve Forward Guidance: I hesitate to write this piece, becaus... http://bit.ly/1arVj7W     
    
    
    Fed Ponders How to Temper Tapering Without Rate Increase http://stks.co/ctZH  The Fed wants the best of all worlds and at no cost $$    
    
    
    Junk Glistens Under ‘Bernankecare’ as Worst Stocks Win http://stks.co/se1K  Fed encourages the foolish to take more risk at a bad time $$    
    
    
    Chinese Steer Billions Abroad in Quest for Safety http://stks.co/qeBC  Wealthy Chinese do not trust their government & so plan escape $$    
    
    
    Gold No Slam-Dunk Sell in China as Aunties Buy Bullion http://stks.co/dtTZ  Chinese know that gold cannot be printed, so they own it $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Has the Dollar Really Lost 97% of Its Value? http://stks.co/hwko  It has.lost as a store of value, u should not b forced 2invest $$    
    
    
    Onions Bring Tears to RBI’s Rajan as Prices Surge http://stks.co/etrP  The humble onion can make even a central banker cry $$ #agflation    
    
    
    Obamacare Consultants Warned of Health Website Failure http://stks.co/dtdI  Wasn't a surprise; officials knew in advance & ignored it $$    
    
    
    Is the Only Choice Bubbles or Recession? http://stks.co/ctio  Recessions r needed to eliminate unproductive lending; they r necessary $$    
    
    
    US Growth comes Mostly from Inventories http://stks.co/iwlI  Helps explain why the economy feels worse than the published numbers $$    
    
    
    Watch Greece – it may be the next Weimar Germany http://stks.co/teBQ  Cradle of democracy becomes its graveyard? Golden Dawn & murder $$    
    
    
    QE:Euthanasia of the economy? http://stks.co/fwoU  Japan & the US r examples; QE can't revive an overindebted economy. Recession needed $$    
    
    
    Student Loan Market Headed for Crisis, CFPB Warns http://stks.co/etsK  Always avoid the debt class that has grown rapidly; losses loom $$    
    
    
    Krugman and Summers Want to Keep Finance Fun http://stks.co/reNV  Their policies promote bubbles and crises rather than stability $$    
    
    
    Why Bankers and Regulators See Very Different Future for Giant Banks http://stks.co/reNX  Hand banking regulation back to the states $$    
    
    
    Bank, Credit Union Defend Payday Products as Crackdown Looms http://stks.co/gwpt  Cheaper version of what exists outside banking $$    
    
    
    Why Banks Are Still Wary of Credit Risk Retention Plan http://stks.co/btfv  Maybe do opposite: ban banks from owning securitized assets $$    
    
    
    Credit-Driven China Glut Threatens Surge Into Bank Crisis http://stks.co/seCB  Forced industrialization leads to bad debts & depression $$    
    
    
    This Market Is Going Higher, Warns Jeremy Grantham http://stks.co/gwtk  Momentum will carry it up until valuations can't b sustained $$    
    
    
    Morgan Stanley Wins as Lynch Pays Up http://stks.co/hwzJ  Remember margin of safety. Great past track record, won't likely work forever $$    
    
    
    Blame Rich, Overeducated Elites as Our Society Frays http://stks.co/iwqQ  Long. Argues that elites can control if they r united $$ #maybe    
    
    
    Swiss Rage Against CEO Pay Provokes Vote on Salary Limits http://stks.co/jwgG  Interesting 2c if it passes & what happens if it does $$    
    
    
    Hollande’s Tax Rebels Underscore Mounting Opposition http://stks.co/reTF  What u get for letting the govt get 2 big $$ $SPY $FXE    
    
    
    Chinese Skeptics Deepen Biggest A-Share Discount in 3 Yrs http://stks.co/seIO  Invest your $$ in Chinese stocks & watch it get Shanghaied    
    
    
    Details of Private Mars Mission Given to House Science Panel http://stks.co/peVk  Space era begins when private industry does it alone $$    
    
    
    J.P. Morgan Is Haunted by a 2006 Decision on Mortgages http://stks.co/ctrN  How underwriting was compromised at $JPM leading2bad mtges $$    
    
    
    A Second Life for Old Permian Oil Field in Texas http://stks.co/teKG  Fascinating to see multiple levels of hydrocarbons, it goes deep $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Stagflation and Financial Repression: This post is an experiment.  Don’t hold me to high s... http://bit.ly/1djeNPE     
    
    
    Wrong: The college savings plan that beat the hedge funds http://stks.co/qeUs  anyone can promise a high fixed return, few can fund it $$    
    
    
    China hard landing is likely: Andy Xie http://stks.co/gwyx  China today is like Japan in the late 1980s, an economy w/2many dead assets $$    
    
    
    A Limited Central Bank http://stks.co/cttC  John Mauldin republishes the notable speech by Charles Plosser at the Cato Institute  $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Economics students need to be taught more than neoclassical theory http://stks.co/jwl6  Reasonable; let students hear other paradigms $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Robert Shiller: is economics a science? http://stks.co/seMD  See Robert Shiller incapably defend bankrupt neoclassical economics $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Investment Ideas: Where do I get investment ideas?1) I get them from articles I read.  ... http://bit.ly/17Pf3OT     
    
    
    Wrong: Orthodox economists have failed their own market test http://stks.co/qedN  Krugman & Baker did not predict the crisis $$    
    
    
    It was not the free market that failed. It was the regulated market that refused to do what it promised; regulators acted pro-cyclically $$    
    
    
    "I lose. You lose. He, she & it loses. We lose. You all lose. They lose." — David Merkel http://disq.us/8ga1ab  $$ Yellen confirmed.    
    
    
    "I don't have an opinion on the Kennedy assassination. I do believe that old men like Castro like to…" — David Merkel http://disq.us/8ga1s7     
    
    
    Mainstream economics is in denial: the world has changed http://stks.co/rehL  Correct, but the solution is more free markets, not less $$    
    
    
    Illegal NYC Homes Thrive as De Blasio Tackles Housing http://stks.co/cu2H  Legalize alternative apartments in NYC; end rent control $$    
    
    
    Worried About That 787 You Ordered? Hire a Factory Babysitter http://stks.co/rehq  Makes sense to do this when u r paying so much $$    
    
    
    "Part of the solution is to define taxable income right, so that taxation cannot be deferred." — David Merkel http://disq.us/8ga2n8  $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Pirates Looting Cargoes With AK-47s Threaten African Oil http://stks.co/seVn  Energy companies should pay military 4 services $$    
    
    
    Probe of How U.S. Agency's Medicare Move Reached Investors Hits Wall http://stks.co/pejc  Congress shields itself from insider trading $$    
    
    
    ObamaCare Forced Mom Into Medicaid http://stks.co/auBQ  If it is important 2 preserve your Mother's dignity, y aren't u paying 4 it? $$    
    
    
    Mobius Can’t Buy Enough Vietnam Equities on Foreign Limits http://stks.co/auBe  They have bad loan problems too, like everyone else $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Bailout Sought as Effort Planned to Bypass Site http://stks.co/gxAr  PPACA looks like a wrecking ball for what was good $$    
    
    
    Americans Recover Home Equity at Record Pace http://stks.co/auCc  I wouldn't b so optimistic; there r2 many investors relative 2 owners $$    
    
    
    PIK Bond Offerings Surge http://stks.co/jwxA  Always a bad sign when borrowers can choose not to pay cash to lenders; market is frothy $$    
    
    
    Fed Looks for Other Ways to Aid Economy http://stks.co/rel4  You've done quite enough thank you. Go 2 the corner & play w/the fed funds $$    
    
    
    White House snubs Fannie-Freddie plan http://stks.co/ix7n  Agree w/Obama here; we need to discourage mortgage debt, delever economy $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Talking to Management, Part 4: Prices and Products: The following was published a... http://bit.ly/1e6kZqO     
    
    
    Banks Consider New Corporate-Bond Trading Network http://stks.co/cuRe  Maybe volume will pick up w/increased liquidity &reduced spreads $$    
    
    
    Aluminum Fees in Japan Seen Near Record in First Quarter on Abe http://stks.co/jxKM  Amazing how much Aluminum held off mkt 4 lending $$    
    
    
    Pimco Sees $3.7T Reason for Adding Yuan http://stks.co/ixTD   FX reserves grew $166B in 3rd quarter 2a record; no rebalancing yet $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Very Well Aged: Archaeologists Say Ancient Wine Cellar Found http://stks.co/hxd9  3700 yrs old found in what is now Israel $$    
    
    
    Iran Is Playing Obama, Says Savvy Saudi Prince http://stks.co/rf8X  Fascinating political calculus here, Saudi Arabia vs Iran $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Market Impact Banks Consider New Corporate-Bond Trading Network http... http://bit.ly/17Wp64t     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Talking to Management, Part 5: Understanding Major Shifts: The following was publ... http://bit.ly/1c1JHZU     
    
    
    Manias, Panics and ObamaCare Crashes http://stks.co/ixaw  PPACA was fatally flawed, the work of ideologues who don't get healthcare $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Lower the Cap Rate, Not: Sometimes I think regulators are in over their heads.  They aren’... http://bit.ly/190t2Br     
    
    
    Magnus Carlsen's Win in Chess Championship Shows Powerful Role of Computers http://stks.co/ixb3  Computer improve the abilities of men $$    
    
    
    The Senate Goes Nuclear, Fallout to Come http://stks.co/euff  A discourse on protecting the rights of the minority, a la the Founders $$    
    
    
    Monsanto vs. Mutant Crop Developers in Global Seed Market http://stks.co/fxeg  There r multiple ways of creating new strains, y fight? $$    
    
    
    The Weekend Interview with Saudi Prince Alwaleed bin Talal http://stks.co/ixb4  Policies that favor Israel & Saudi Arabia r the same $$    
    
    
    All for One: Xi Jinping and China's New Deal http://stks.co/hxl5  Argues that the Chinese govt continues to centralize, not so sure $$    
    
    
    Nonprofit that flipped homes to investors faces scrutiny http://stks.co/dume  Not necessarily illegal, perhaps unethical, sneaky $$    
    
    
    Tackling The Fed: Jeb Hensarling's Promise At Cato http://stks.co/gy0q  After 100 yrs, it is time to review our $$ state of affairs    
    
    
    Western Digital unwraps hybrid-data-storage system http://stks.co/gy0s  Best of both worlds @ reasonable cost SSD&HDD $$ FD: + $WDC    
    
    
    For-Profit Colleges Face Consumer Bureau Probe on Lending Roles  http://stks.co/tfLn  Student debt is a lousy deal avoid it if u can $$    
    
    
    In Iran, Obama Achieves 50% of His Goals http://stks.co/curr  If everyone is unhappy, it might be a good deal; looks like Iran is happy $$    
    
    
    Extremist Tide Poses Growing Threat to Europe, Katainen Says http://stks.co/dumu  Euro puts nations in a straitjacket, fuels extremists $$    
    
    
    Rebirth Eludes Baltimore as Camden Reality Lags Promises http://stks.co/jxmd  Professional sports arenas r economic idol 4 destruction $$    
    
    
    Not so sure: Democrats Give Up 2014 With the Filibuster http://stks.co/tfMV  It's a long way to the 2014 & 2016 elections $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    When Marketing Is Strategy http://stks.co/fxz4  Adapt your products & services 2 meet needs of consumers 4 convenience & effectiveness $$    
    
    
    Islamists Settle on Turkey-Syria Border as War Blurs Lines http://stks.co/qfVW  Multiple player wars r inherently unstable & risky $$    
    
    
    Wall Street May Take Derivatives Regulator to Court http://stks.co/sfOS  Arbitrariness in issuing regulations leads 2 pushback $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Europe's Easy-Money Policy Snubs German Savers http://stks.co/dunp  Germans should take vacations in Portugal, Italy, Greece, & Spain $$    
    
    
    Startup Scrambles to Replace the Egg http://stks.co/tfN1  Intriguing idea 2try 2replace eggs w/ingredients commonly fed 2 chickens $$ $TSN    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Investment Ideas, Redux: Would I disclose proprietary ideas of mine?  I’ve done it befo... http://bit.ly/IjPD66     
    
    
    Stock Market Trading: The 20 Rules Of Engagement http://stks.co/rg39  Useful rules 4short-term traders from the estimable Todd Harrison $$    
    
    
    Kobe Bryant's $50M Shows Salary Cap Is Ruining NBA http://stks.co/jyFN  Easiest way 2ruin a professional sports team is pay star 2much $$    
    
    
    Is Obamacare Challenging Enough for Obama? http://stks.co/iyMn  Astounding to hear an ideologue like Margaret Carlson criticize Obama $$    
    
    
    Pope Urges Countries Regulate Markets in Poverty Battle http://stks.co/qfxs  Jorge Bergoglio doesn't understand the Bible; thus he errs $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Two Good Questions: My last post, On Investment Ideas, Redux, received two good questions.... http://bit.ly/1ies3ap     
    
    
    London Gold Fix Calls Draw Scrutiny Amid Heavy Trading http://stks.co/dvGB  Very difficult to eliminate all unfairness in benchmarks $$    
    
    
    Speed Traders Meet Nightmare on Elm Street With Nanex http://stks.co/tfpf  Slanted article downplays Nanex's insights on the markets $$    
    
    
    Madness & Sanity http://stks.co/dvI3  It is flattering to be quoted at such great length; Good thing that I do not enforce copyright $$    
    
    
    How Regulators Will Toughen the Volcker Rule http://stks.co/sfti  This is an impossible task & will result in lawsuits galore $$ #fail    
    
    
    Should We Bail Out Cities? http://stks.co/pg7a  Answer: no, we shouldn't. Most bailout r in areas we knew were high risk already $$    
    
    
    Even Subsidized Obamacare Plans Haven't Found Takers Yet http://stks.co/tfro  Particularly among the young & healthy it doesn't help $$    
    
    
    Why Are Takeover Prices Plummeting? http://stks.co/fyUo  Interesting 2c a lack of fervor among acquirers during high valuations $$    
    
    
    Warren Buffett and Time-Horizon Arbitrage http://stks.co/iyaj  Buffett as a quality GARP manager; challenge is finding durable moats $$    
    
    
    Could banks charge fees for deposits? http://stks.co/gyj7  Yes they could if the Fed tries to loosen policy further $$    
    
    
    Banks may pay $105B more to settle mortgage tab http://stks.co/qgB3  Did the banks even *make* $150B from 2005-8? Who gets the fine $$ ?    
    
    
    What a Higher Minimum Wage Does for Workers and the Economy http://stks.co/jyT5  Democracy doomed if people vote 4 $$ from Treasury->them    
    
    
    Wall Street Props CLO Boom as Rules Lift Costs http://stks.co/tg25  Get them out the door b4 new regulations require risk retention $$    
    
    
    Foreclosed Sales at US Auctions Double as Prices Gain http://stks.co/evdL  This is a good sign; B careful 2get a clean title if buying $$    
    
    
    Zeppelins Seen Hauling Caterpillars to Mine Siberia http://stks.co/pgIM  Fascinating way 2 move heavy machines 2 mines in Siberia $$    
    
    
    Clean Wind Farms Catch Up to Dirty Big Oil http://stks.co/fyf2  The comments section is replete w/replies on the many ways birds die $$    
    
    
    Rich Russians Sparring With Putin Over $48B Olympics Bet http://stks.co/dvTr  Cloudy view of who pays 4 & benefits from building Sochi $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Why I Resist Trends: Portfolio Rule Seven says:Rebalance the portfolio whenever a stock ge... http://bit.ly/1jMRonx     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Two More Good Questions: I had two more good questions in response to my piece Why I Resis... http://bit.ly/IprYAD     
    
    
    Paul Krugman's Blind Spot http://stks.co/hyzK  The countries that did not increase their deficits have done better than those that did $$    
    
    
    How Poland Became Europe's Most Dynamic Economy http://stks.co/iysg  Great, but just watch the outsized entitlement liabilities $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Maker of Nutella and Tic Tacs Confident in Family Hands http://stks.co/fyxE  Profitable organic growth &staying private. Smart strategy $$    
    
    
    Rice Bond Flop Adds to Yingluck Protest Misfortune http://stks.co/cvpN  Feels a little like 1997, could b messy in emerging markets $$    
    
    
    Aussie Set for Longest Drop Since 1997 After Takeover Rejected http://stks.co/cvqI  A currency is less valuable when use is restricted $$    
    
    
    OPEC Rift Emerging Over Iraq Output, Possible Return of Iran http://stks.co/evx6  OPEC? Forgot about them. Iraq oil production grows $$    
    
    
    Judge Approves ResCap Settlement W/Housing Regulator http://stks.co/fyyq  Unsec debt recovers 35%; I remember when they were hot stuff $$    
    
    
    Stay Home, America http://stks.co/rgcy  Commentary on trying to turn Thanksgiving into a shopping day & what it costs us as a culture $$    
    
    
    How Alyssa Milano Created a Fan-Gear Fashion Empire for Women http://stks.co/evxH  Create clothes women like in team colors, not pink $$    
    
    
    Obama’s call to close Vatican embassy is 'slap in the face' to Roman Catholics http://stks.co/iyux  True enough, but I don't c the need $$    
    
    
    In Thailand, It's Crippling Déjà vu All Over Again http://stks.co/iyuy  Democracy does not fit the cultures of some nations well $$    
    
    
    A Fight Over Contraception Won't Help Obamacare http://stks.co/cvqa  Tie PPACA 2 abortion & the fight is unlikely 2 ever end $$    
    
    
    Repsol Deal With Argentina Was Propelled by Pemex  http://stks.co/hz5u  Pemex mediates/wins, $REP loses, gets $$, $YPF free, Argent wins    
    
    
    Hit-and-Miss Obamacare Site Still Frustrating at Deadline http://stks.co/tgM8  It could never have been fully fixed by 11/30 $$ $TLT $SPY    
    
    
    Can Phone-Charging Stove Cut Wood Pollution and Save Lives? http://stks.co/gz7a  Cook food w/less fuel & pollution; make electricity $$    
    
    
    Carney’s Housing Alarm Bell Nudges BOE Toward Stimulus Exit http://stks.co/cvtu  But will he really do it? Economic growth isn't fast $$    
    
    
    Morgan Stanley Leads Japan M&A for 1st Time Since 1997 http://stks.co/tgPN  Global expertise is @ a premium w/many deals across borders $$    
    
    
    San Jose Pension Crush Spurs Bid to Ease California Pacts http://stks.co/cvu7  State laws will change 2allow cuts 2 nonaccrued benefits $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Rest of the World Morgan Stanley Leads Japan M&A for 1st Time Since ... http://bit.ly/1imIu4F     
    
    
    @YahooCare Fix this page: http://finance.yahoo.com/mb/GTS/  yields this: Error while retrieving the data (Error Code: MBHo_500_2MBBa_INVALID_STATUS)    
    
    
    Build a Better Turkey Sandwich http://stks.co/aw7C  Thanksgiving keeps on giving in six inspired takes on the leftover-turkey sandwich $$    
    
    
    The Black Swan http://stks.co/cvzl  A good piece that explains positive & negative "Black Swan" events, & how 2 thus position for them $$    
    
    
    Creating a Black Swan http://stks.co/pgmR  Attempts 2 explain how negative black swan events get created in financial markets $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Why Taylor Swift Is the Reigning Queen of Pop http://stks.co/qgfX  Swift's popularity secret? My take:she appears more humble than most $$    
    
    
    Inside the Company That Bungled Obamacare http://stks.co/gzDO  B wary of companies that grow 2 fast w/shaky revenue recognition $$ $GIB    
    
    
    Fair-Weather Friends or Raining on Your Parade http://stks.co/sgYf  Good snarky post. Time to lighten up on property-centric reinsurers $$    
    
    
    Illinois Legislative Leaders Try to Sell Pension Agreement http://stks.co/gzDQ  Dreamland vs Hard Choices. So far Dramland is winning $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Payment System to Insurers Changed in Setback http://stks.co/hzEu  Complex law, difficult to change w/o affecting other parts $$    
    
    
    Microsoft, Yahoo Upgrades Shows Snowden Won, Obama Failed http://stks.co/qgfd  Encryption keys double, squaring time needed to crack $$    
    
    
    Caveat Emptor: Lovers of Latin Try to Sell a Dead Tongue http://stks.co/hzEw  Looks like wishful thinking 2me. Esperanto, anyone? $$    
    
    
    Deep Inside The Hot Mess Called Obamacare: It's Time For Honesty http://stks.co/jyxb  Sophomoric, doing a dumb thing, calling it wise $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Code Red: This is a tough book to review.  It is correct in analysis of what ... http://bit.ly/1cIUpTr     
    
    
    Howard Marks: Too Cute for His own Good? http://stks.co/dvyT  Unfair. Marks says that the opportunity set is small, get it?  $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Don’t Ignore Doctor Copper http://stks.co/pgp1  Copper is indicating a punk economy $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    CS50, a computer science course, breaks stereotypes and fills halls at Harvard http://stks.co/fzAh  Making IT relevant across cultures $$    
    
    
    “Quant” hedge funds: Computer says no http://stks.co/rgoU  Runs in cycles as more or less focus on anomalies in investing $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Olin Corporation Common Stock up 9% today http://stks.co/qgwT  Something is happening w/OLN today. Anyone know what? FD: + $OLN $$ $SPY    
    
    
    China’s Largest Bitcoin Exchange Seeks Recognition for Currency http://stks.co/fzUF  Communist Party will eventually ban Bitcoin $$ $SPY    
    
    
    "Wealthy Chinese could use it to funnel flight capital out of China" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/izNq  How Bitcoin functions in China $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Why Stocks Go Up and Down, Fourth Edition: This is a good book to help the in... http://bit.ly/1k4HGgm     
    
    
    UnitedHealth Projects 2014 Results Below Analysts' Estimates http://stks.co/bwMn  Health Insurers take one for Obama's errors $$ #FTL    
    
    
    Fed Eyes Financial System's Weak Link http://stks.co/izXJ  Solution is simple; bifurcate repo acctg 4 statutory cash flow testing $$ $XLF    
    
    
    Uninsured-Driver Dilemma http://stks.co/sh3x  Have Assurant track non-payment at the insurers, & inform the MVAs of lapsation $$ $AIZ    
    
    
    Private equity firms brace for ‘mafia’ style scrutiny http://stks.co/awaY  This looks a lot more difficult than the article indicates $$    
    
    
    Detroit Retirees Got Extra Interest After Guaranteed 7.9% http://stks.co/bwMu  What Detroit did w/"excess" pension earnings was evil $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Website Repair Goals Reached, Administration Says http://stks.co/phIO  Big Problem: the insurers are not getting the data $$    
    
    
    Magic Johnson, Tom Hanks Join Obama on Cash-Grabbing Trip http://stks.co/ewbq  Cash works in the short run, voters decide the long run $$    
    
    
    "You can't regulate what you don't understand.  The SEC looked in on it several times, with more…" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/cwYx  $$    
    
    
    How Much More Will Smokers Pay for Obamacare? http://stks.co/awse  Answer: not much more & no, it will have little effect on quitting $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Retirement GPS: This book encourages you to invest most of your savings abroa... http://bit.ly/1k91sar     
    
    
    Illinois Passes Pension Overhaul http://stks.co/qhns  Fake overhaul that leaves Illinois taxpayers worse off, will go to court & die $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Become a Smarter Seller, Part 1: The following was published at RealMoney, but I ... http://bit.ly/1biyC6z     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog What is Liquidity? (Part V): Here are the predecessor posts in this series:What is Liquidi... http://bit.ly/1khLR8C     
    
    
    Henninger: Obama's Red-Line Presidency http://stks.co/g00gp  What doe the US stand for? What will we defend? Who r our allies? Confusing $$    
    
    
    Slate Writer Is Dead Wrong to Root Against Community Banks http://stks.co/bxGZ  Getting banks is tough 4 neophytes like Matty Yglesias $$    
    
    
    Angry Self-Insured Voters Dim Democratic Takeover Plans http://stks.co/piIG  Many feel robbed by the loss of choice in healthcare $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Gross to Run Pimco Unconstrained as Dialynas Takes Leave http://stks.co/dxJZ  Unconstrained is no guarantee of good performance $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Hidden U-Haul Billionaire Emerges With Storage Empire http://stks.co/g00gu  Fascinating tale of how brothers rescued the family business $$    
    
    
    Pension Threats in Illinois, Detroit Rattle Government Workers http://stks.co/axVh  Blame Union strategy of extracting pension gains $$    
    
    
    China Bans Financial Companies From Bitcoin Transactions http://stks.co/g00gz  Wealthy Chinese want to get value out of China $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Spain Credit Falls to ’05 Shadow After Price Collapse http://stks.co/piIN  Even that is too much credit. Wait 4 hard money buyers $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Become a Smarter Seller, Part 2: The following was published at RealMoney, but I ... http://bit.ly/1d7C8iS     
    
    
    Buffett's Alpha http://stks.co/axn6  Finally a paper from academics that gives Buffett the credit he deserves. Efficient markets? No. $$    
    
    
    Pension Threats in Illinois, Detroit Rattle Government Workers http://stks.co/piaN  If the local government can't pay, it won't $$    
    
    
    Volcker Rule to Force Banks to Comply With Five Regimes http://stks.co/exl8  Recipe 4 disaster. When many r responsible, no one is $$    
    
    
    The Stock Market Is 'Shrinking,' Despite Record-High Indexes http://stks.co/exl9  Interesting argument of stock scarcity pushing prices $$    
    
    
    Buyers Give Up Their Names to Seal Merger Deals http://stks.co/dxbu  Who cares what a bank is named, so long as you have control? $$ $FXF    
    
    
    Examiners-in-Residence Should Be Pulled Out of Megabanks: OCC Report http://stks.co/bxYA  Familiarity breeds acquiescence, not contempt $$    
    
    
    China Cinda Attracts $65B in Orders for Up to $2.5B IPO http://stks.co/piaO  Those are bubbly conditions; 2 much $$ 2 put 2 work $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Iran Wants US Companies to Develop Oil Fields http://stks.co/siKV  The Great Satan is quite useful under the right conditions $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Heavy Inventories Threaten to Squeeze Clothing Stores http://stks.co/cxf0  That said, clothing is dirt cheap, so why worry much? $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Retailers Are in a Deflated Holiday Mood http://stks.co/h00yo  One reason why I rarely invest in retailers, aside from grocery $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    he Best and Worst Run States in America: A Survey of All 50 « http://stks.co/exlB  You might be surprised by the rankings $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Rich Kazakhs Revive Polygamy as Women Seek Poverty Escape http://stks.co/dxc2  Young Kazakh women would rather b second wives than poor $$    
    
    
    Obamacare's New Goal: Stay Alive Until 2015 http://stks.co/riXI  The idea is 2 survive until 2015, so the law can't b destroyed in 2017 $$    
    
    
    Madoff Behaved Like a Lunatic Over Fund Probe, Jury Told http://stks.co/exlE  Seems like Madoff employees kept their heads down $$    
    
    
    Is the Fed increasingly monetizing government debt? http://stks.co/axnE  Yes, Fed is monetizing government debt, get ready 4 inflation $$    
    
    
    The Fed Must Inflate http://stks.co/exlF  I think this is the most likely conclusion, but not certain $$    
    
    
    Pirates Wielding Grenades Spur Japan to Ease Samurai-Era Gun Ban http://stks.co/f00sN  Force must b opposed by force; no other way $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Panasonic in Deal Talks With Auto Parts Makers for Expansion http://stks.co/dxc4  Desperation drives the company 2 seek more markets $$    
    
    
    The Blessing of a Declining Stock Price http://stks.co/siKh  This is how I do it; I buy companies that have moved against me $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Paul Krugman Consigns To Hell An Economic Slump Of His Own Devise http://stks.co/dxc5  We have 2 turn the lights off near Krugman $$    
    
    
    Crude Oil Refiners Are In A Sweet Spot | Commodities http://stks.co/dxc6  Because crude oil can't b exported, refiners benefit $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Penny Pricing for US Stocks Said to Get Scrutinized http://stks.co/riXL  I don't think this is a big problem, helps small investors $$    
    
    
    Fixing What's Wrong With Economics 101 http://stks.co/j00ek  We need 2 scrap neoclassical economics, and move economics away from math $$    
    
    
    Big Oil to Get Brazil-Like Terms in Plan to End Mexico Monopoly http://stks.co/axnF  Maybe Mexico can gain the technical help it needs $$    
    
    
    Gen Re’s Gilbert Says Fed Sets Up Stocks for a Decline http://stks.co/piaU  The Fed will learn the limits of its power in a few years $$    
    
    
    Yuan Passes Euro as 2nd-Most Used Trade-Finance Currency http://stks.co/exlH  If China's banks were exposed 2 market, would b impressed $$    
    
    
    Banks in Safest Euro Nation See Credit Drought as Finns Save http://stks.co/dxc8  Many want to save; few want to borrow. Rational $$    
    
    
    Wrong: OECD Warns Riksbank Against Obsessing Over Record Debt http://stks.co/piaW  OECD should learn excessive debt harms $$ $TLT $SPY    
    
    
    Obama war chiefs widen drone death zones http://stks.co/h00yu  If we want to make the US odious to the rest of the world, use drones $$    
    
    
    What You Don’t Know About Mortgages http://stks.co/tiHE ! Mortgage documents don't reflect the full cost of getting the mortgage $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Why Capital Is Key Battleground in GSE Reform Debate http://stks.co/i00nH  Appropriate capital 4 new system:a political &technical issue $$    
    
    
    Change Illinois' pension benefits to match the Social Security system http://stks.co/i00nI  The bill passed will harm Illinois long-run $$    
    
    
    Are the Baltic Dry Index Telling Us to Expect a Stronger Economic Activity? http://stks.co/riXM  Could be, but only in exports $$    
    
    
    Why FDIC is Running Out of Time for Resolution Planning http://stks.co/siKm  As w/all complex laws, things move slowly, no surprise. $$    
    
    
    Gun Patents Set 35-Year Record as Limits on Sales Fail http://stks.co/tiHH  When GOP has Presidency sales will fall $$    
    
    
    Ghana Farms Miss Out on Oil-Fueled Middle Class Food Demand http://stks.co/f00sQ  Middle classes introduce changes into societies $$ $SPY    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Rest of the World  Ghana Farms Miss Out on Oil-Fueled Middle Class F... http://bit.ly/1kmTYkd     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Bonds are not Forever: This is a good book, it is not a great book like The H... http://bit.ly/1f8x6ES     
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: That is not a skill of mine http://stks.co/sids     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Three Dimensions, and Printed, but not Real: Okay, let’s run the promoted stocks scoreboar... http://bit.ly/J9xNmA     
    
    
    Ridiculous: Was Mandela Right to Sell Out Black South Africans? http://stks.co/rjQA  South Africa has done better than rest of Africa $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: The Dao of Capital: Have I said this before: this is a tough book to review. ... http://bit.ly/1doF377     
    
    
    Inside the Breakup of the Pritzker Empire http://stks.co/eyxB  How Tom Pritzker detangled the family business, giving freedom to heirs $$    
    
    
    Are we seeing the emergence of 'dictator' Xi? http://stks.co/ayyh  His #2 is sidelined, & there is no obvious close helper. $$    
    
    
    House, Senate Negotiators Announce Budget Deal http://stks.co/ayyi  The sequester would be better, at least that makes real cuts $$ $TLT    
    
    
    4 articles on the Volcker Rule: http://stks.co/bylR  & http://stks.co/eyxS  & http://stks.co/dyoP  & http://stks.co/eyxT  $$ $TLT    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: The Value of Financial Slack: This was my first article published at RealMoney, i... http://bit.ly/1kBJIVo     
    
    
    Ryan Lizza: Why Won’t Obama Rein in the N.S.A.? http://stks.co/qjnT  Long article on Obama's hypocrisy on surveillance of US citizens $$    
    
    
    Why Do Forecasters Keep Forecasting? http://stks.co/qjnf  Predictors exist so that we have someone to blame other than ourselves.$$ $TLT    
    
    
    Wall Street Exhales as Volcker Rule Seen Sparing Market-Making http://stks.co/f0294  It doesn't do much though it separates functions $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Federal Reserve Eyes New Tool for Setting Interest Rates http://stks.co/rk1x  This is wishful thinking; math is same as IOER/FF $$    
    
    
    Wrong: Pension Funds Make the Most of Stocks' Surge http://stks.co/pk2h  Unless u can defease your liability, u don't have enuf assets $$    
    
    
    I.e., w/interest rates on investment grade debt so low, most of these defined benefit pension plans r still dramatically underfunded. $$    
    
    
    Wrong:White House Works2Attract Younger Health-Plan Users http://stks.co/tjjy  Most people signing up r either poor or sick; won't work $$    
    
    
    How Isaac Newton Went Broke Chasing A Stock Bubble http://stks.co/h02S1  HT: @tomkeene | Ride a painted pony, let the spinnin wheel spin $$    
    
    
    BNSF CEO Rose shifts role, renewing Buffett succession talk http://stks.co/bywu  Would b a good candidate2run industrial side of $BRK-B $$    
    
    
    Overstated: The Texasization of America http://stks.co/f02Kn  Texas may b the fastest growing state, but not all states go4 lower taxes $$    
    
    
    Soothing Words on 'Too Big to Fail,' but With Little Meaning http://stks.co/tjmu ! Short of breaking up big banks, no way to end TBTF $$    
    
    
    As stocks hit record highs, so do profit warnings http://stks.co/g02RW  Market rally is multiple expansion, pay more $$ 4 same stocks $SPY    
    
    
    The Potholes Stay Where They Are http://stks.co/j029J  VERY long article on the recovery of the US auto industry-what has changed $$ $GM $F    
    
    
    Rat-Infested South Africa Schools Foil Mandela Education Dream http://stks.co/i02Fe  Graft & corruption eat up school $$ #culture $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Stanford Economist Piazzesi Influences Fed Forecasts http://stks.co/azBT  Now her theories affect policy w/every forward rate wiggle $$    
    
    
    Why do ivory tower academics get into policy positions, in this case assuming that forward rates forecast future economic activity? $$    
    
    
    What Yahoo Didn’t Want Investors to Know http://stks.co/sjrs  $YHOO relies on $MSFT 4 25% of its revenue in 2012 & 31% in 3Q2013 $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Republicans Get the Better End of the Budget Deal http://stks.co/f02LV  @asymmetricinfo gives us a different take, but will GOP do it? $$    
    
    
    The Unstoppable Postal-Service Retreat Starts in Canada http://stks.co/byxZ  Is the future 4 USPS the elimination of local mailboxes? $$    
    
    
    Republican-Tea Party Tiff Means 41% Don’t Like Candidates http://stks.co/dz0w  Divisions in the GOP weaken their political prospects $$    
    
    
    Obama Needs to Fire Some People http://stks.co/byxg  Similarity of Obama & Reagan; they tend to stand behind their people, til it hurts $$    
    
    
    Merkel Embraces Coal as Rookie Lawmaker Makes Mark on Policy http://stks.co/qjz8  Fascinating how environmental policy isn't considered $$    
    
    
    Banks, Lawyers Struggling to Evaluate Final Volcker Rule http://stks.co/rk7C  Complexity is friend of large banks; can hide their acts $$    
    
    
    All-out war breaks out in GOP over budget pact http://stks.co/qjzd  Will b interest 2c if House Dems pass the deal w/a subset of GOP $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: I was a critic of W also.  Good comment. http://stks.co/byyH     
    
    
    SNB Gauges Bubble Risks as Euro Crisis Danger Recedes http://stks.co/pk7f  Favoring exporters leads Sweden monetary policy to overheat $$    
    
    
    Lobotomy For WWII Veterans: Psychiatric Care by US Government http://stks.co/rk7r  LONG sad tale of lobotomies to cure mental illness $$    
    
    
    Secular stagnation and the bastardisation of Keynes http://stks.co/qk04  Rising debt levels led GDP to overshoot & now revert down $$    
    
    
    Nicolas Copernicus Was Far More Than A Scientific Icon http://stks.co/dz22  Wrote "On the Minting of Money." A hard money guy 4 his era $$    
    
    
    Why Is Everybody Sitting on Huge Piles of Cash? http://stks.co/j02Bn  Waiting 4 new IPOs absorb excess cash $$ HT: @ritholtz $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Wells Fargo Plans Ethics Review Amid Bank Scrutiny http://stks.co/ezBQ  Give $WFC its due, they r trying to get ahead of their problems $$    
    
    
    Lawrence McCarthy, Who Saw Swaps Danger at Lehman, Dies at 49 http://stks.co/h02VA  Bright guy; he will b missed $$    
    
    
    A Fed Dissident on Policy and Transparency http://stks.co/rk9E  Plosser makes a courageous stand to protect the Fed from its excesses $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog When to Worry — An Asset-Liability Management Perspective on Financial Macroeconomics: At ... http://bit.ly/1j1SNvb     
    
    
    Banks, Lawyers Struggling to Evaluate Final Volcker Rule http://stks.co/i02Vi  Complex laws & regulations almost never work $$ #fail $XLF    
    
    
    Five Accounting Red Flags the SEC is Watching http://stks.co/sk70  Revenue recognition & cost deferral r bigger issues; wasting time $$    
    
    
    Irish Charm W/Germans Leads Nation Out of Bailout Wilderness http://stks.co/czL6  Fascinating piece on how Ireland survived austerity $$    
    
    
    How I Unintentionally Forced Pirate Bay From Its Latest Haven http://stks.co/g02kl  Ascension Island boots Pirate Bay which runs to Peru $$    
    
    
    Philadelphia Meets Manhattan at 10 Rittenhouse Square http://stks.co/j02Sv  Worked w/Carl Dranoff once; bright guy, very creative $$    
    
    
    Six Investment Errors You Are Making Right Now http://stks.co/pkP3  @ritholtz shows us errors that he has made that we r all prone 2 $$    
    
    
    Hoenig Says Volcker May Spur Efforts to Split Biggest Banks http://stks.co/i02a7  Ending interstate branching would b more effective $$    
    
    
    The Fed Doesn't Really Trust the Banks Either http://stks.co/i02aA  Structural rigidities in $$ mkts make Fed policy less effective $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Will Copper Pots Destroy Lake Superior? http://stks.co/j02Tz  Perhaps the tailings can be used 4 roadbed, or other types of construction $$    
    
    
    Neurologist Walter Freeman’s Lobotomy Legacy http://stks.co/dzL6  Ice-pick lobotomies r a horrifying legacy damaging minds of veterans $$    
    
    
    World War II Veterans' Families Recall Lobotomy's Scars http://stks.co/tk8a  LONG article on how families coped after lobotomies $$    
    
    
    A Journey Into the World's Deepest Gold Mine http://stks.co/f02gb  The technology & the survivors @ the deepest gold mine in the world $$    
    
    
    2.5-mile plunge into the world's deepest gold mine in South Africa http://stks.co/czNQ   &check out this graphic http://stks.co/czNR  $$    
    
    
    US Drone Strike Hits Wedding Convoy in Yemen, Killing 13 http://stks.co/ezUF  More bad PR 4 drone strikes, wonder how this will end... $$    
    
    
    Health Insurers Told to Ease Coverage Rules http://stks.co/pkRi  Exchanges r getting many more old than young http://stks.co/qkKw  $$    
    
    
    How to Hike the Entire Appalachian Trail, and What You'll Get Out of It http://stks.co/czOv  Retired photojournalist makes way on trail $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets:  Rest of the World US Drone Strike Hits Wedding Convoy in Yemen, Kil... http://bit.ly/1jZP8fB     
    
    
    Wrong: Technology Adoption Discrepancy Btw Individuals & Institutions http://stks.co/azbY  Tries 2 connect falling ROA & Social Media $$    
    
    
    Mike Tyson Explores Kierkegaard http://stks.co/skKJ  Philosophy is a dead end; no truth to their views of existence, knowledge &ethics $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Tsarnaevs and the Boston Bombing http://stks.co/czUO  A decade ago, WSJ reporter happened to befriend the Tsarnaevs- an inside view $$    
    
    
    Errors Continue 2Plague Government Health Site http://stks.co/rkYL  Flaws Include Missing Customers & Erring Eligibility Determinations $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog The Prime Directive: Stay Out of the Bottom Quartile: If you are a money manager, you woul... http://bit.ly/1kLfmju     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Book Review: Kentucky Fried Pensions:  This book takes you through the corruption in the K... http://bit.ly/1dIHHoi     
    
    
    Look How Easy It Is 2 Game Estate Taxes http://stks.co/i03Sd  Y the estate tax needs 2b replaced & income taxes disallow income deferral $$    
    
    
    Vonn Rivals Schuss From Slope to Boardroom for Funding http://stks.co/plI2  Olympians r little corporations seeking sponsors, donations $$    
    
    
    The One Thing Bernanke Must Not Do Tomorrow http://stks.co/sl2e  Saying & not doing loses credibility 4the Fed. Don't say wut u wont do $$    
    
    
    "I analyzed TRUP CDOs 4a bank in 2008 and 2009 -- built a special model that could dig into the…" — David_Merkel http://stks.co/a00LO  $$    
    
    
    First Volcker Victim? Zions Dumping Its Hedge Funds http://stks.co/c00E0  $ZION cleans up the trash w/now-sufficient capital $$    
    
    
    Accidental Tax Break Saves Wealthiest Americans $100B http://stks.co/f03Xe  “I’ve done a lot4 Democratic contributors,” he sez w/a smile $$    
    
    
    Corn Plummeting Spurs Talk of ’80s US Farmland Bust http://stks.co/sl3R  Will b interesting 2c how many recent buyers get inverted $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Insurers Fight Hospitals' Paying Premiums for Poor http://stks.co/sl3W  Hospitals pay to get sick people insured, so they can make $$ $SPY    
    
    
    In Bankrupt Detroit, the Bills Are Piling Up http://stks.co/rlHP  One tough part of a muni b/k - who gets paid & what r reasonable fees $$    
    
    
    Multivitamins Found to Have Little Benefit http://stks.co/h03eJ  The controversy will continue; nothing this profitable ever dies $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Volcker Rule Shows Its Wide Reach http://stks.co/i03U7  Securitized assets, when they default, most frequently default w/zero recovery $$    
    
    
    Google, Facebook Push to Control Web's Pipes http://stks.co/tl0v  Content companies want more control over their delivery over the web $$    
    
    
    How Dogs Might Protect Kids Against Asthma: Gut Bacteria http://stks.co/sl4i  Fascinating that dogs may aid kids w/immunity to asthma $$    
    
    
    Google Just Bought a Mechinized Cheetah and Other Military Robots http://stks.co/d00D2  1st internet search now robotic world domination $$    
    
    
    'Was The Fed A Good Idea?' How Cato Cleans Keynesian Clock http://stks.co/j03Mc  Economies grow faster when currency stores real value $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: ' @MMula534 A lot. Most of the best investors r lifelong learners, & they c patterns whe... http://stks.co/c00FT     
    
    
    Want to invest like Buffett? Here’s how http://stks.co/a00NH  Focus on cheap, high-quality stocks w/moats, lever using ins float $$ $BRK-B    
    
    
    Wind Power Rivals Coal With $1B Order From Buffett http://stks.co/i03VF  Wind power gets competitive on price; can we end the subsidies? $$    
    
    
    The truth about the NSA's bogus malware apocalypse http://stks.co/tl1r  Most mass attacks r hard 2pull off w/any significant force $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Campbell Seen as Next Buffett Target Post-Heinz http://stks.co/plKs  Likely wishful thinking; soup shrinking; PE high, no growth $$ $CPB    
    
    
    China's Cities Chop Down Hills for Industrial Land http://stks.co/i03VT  Wonder what the secondary effect will b from this terraforming? $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    NSA Phone Spying 'Almost Certainly' Unconstitutional, Judge Says http://stks.co/rlKm  Probably won't b upheld, good 2try overturning $$    
    
    
    Can China Teach North Korea to Grow Up? http://stks.co/i03X2  If N Koreans had as much freedom as the Chinese do, Kim would b overthrown $$    
    
    
    Investor Hunger 4US Corporate Bonds Signals Confidence http://stks.co/a00Pu  Retweet after me:Credit spreads r free $$, credit spreads r...    
    
    
    Disarming Surveillance http://stks.co/sl8W  The opposite danger is that by snooping on others intensively they grow to resent the US $$    
    
    
    An Opiate for Underachievement: Bernanke Says Fed in ‘Finest Hours’ Stood Up to Pressure http://stks.co/sl8X  Rather, they caved & hid $$    
    
    
    South Sudan Puts Down 'Attempted Coup' http://stks.co/e00O8  A young nation, very experienced in corruption; attempted coup unsurprising $$    
    
    
    North America to Drown in Oil as Mexico Ends Monopoly http://stks.co/plPd  Oil is no good to Mexico if can't get it out of ground $$ #tech    
    
    
    Hidden Danger in Public Pension Funds http://stks.co/b00DP  Low Funded status, high amounts in risky assets, bonds offer little yield $$    
    
    
    How Pope Francis Misunderstands the Free Market http://stks.co/h03jz  Simpler than that; he is unstudied, engages in wishful thinking $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Risks, not Risk, Again: One of the most important things I am here to teach readers is tha... http://bit.ly/JG1nQM     
    
    
    Unmasking the Mortgage Interest Deduction: Who Benefits and by How Much? http://stks.co/i03ko  Benefits the well-off; end & balance bdgt $$    
    
    
    Top Democrats reject court ruling over NSA spying on Americans http://stks.co/tlGn  Interesting 2c varying opinions in both parties $$    
    
    
    Mom Can’t Visit Daughter as Airlines Shun Venezuela Cash http://stks.co/g03vJ  Such is life 4those under currency controls; freedom goes $$    
    
    
    At 61 She Lives in Basement While 87-Year-Old Dad Travels http://stks.co/i03l0  Each generation does successively less well on average $$    
    
    
    That's the nature of all of the fixed payment plans devised by the "Greatest Generation." They borrowed from children & grandchildren $$    
    
    
    Pizzerias Try to Apply Chipotle Formula http://stks.co/d00SX  Creating Fast, Custom & Inexpensive 4 pizza; many r trying, who will win? $$    
    
    
    Youthful Migrants Lured by Perks to Shrinking US Areas http://stks.co/e00Zt  Promising idea to create urban jobs in rural areas $$ #winwin    
    
    
    Poor Americans Lead Movement to Abandon Landlines http://stks.co/g03vo  Landlines r dying; I'm thinking of getting rid of mine $$ $SPY $VZ    
    
    
    Delta Battles Tiny Upstart Airport http://stks.co/b00OW  B careful of small airports near big cities, u don't want 2create the next $LUV $$    
    
    
    Is Obamacare Really an Improvement on the Status Quo? http://stks.co/c00VA  More people lose insurance than gain it; status quo better $$    
    
    
    Russian Amnesty Includes Greenpeace as Well as Pussy Riot http://stks.co/rlZB  Is Russia getting soft? ;) Courting international favor $$    
    
    
    Top Products in Two Decades of Tech Reviews http://stks.co/d00TC  Walter Mossberg's last column @ WSJ; a joy 2 read, will still b on web $$    
    
    
    Doctors Eye Cancer Risk in Uterine Procedure http://stks.co/d00TZ  Grinding up fibroid in the uterus may increase the risk of cancer $$    
    
    
    How Good Old Car Engines Got So Efficient http://stks.co/b00PG  Most progress w/energy has come by using hydrocarbons more efficiently $$    
    
    
    Dodge CVT Animation http://stks.co/rlZt  Cool 82-second video of how a continuously variable transmission works $$ $GM $F $TM $HMC    
    
    
    Gold Town Turns to Dust as Metal Decline Shutters Mines http://stks.co/c00Vn  Life at high-cost mines is very cyclical. Boom-bust $$ $GLD    
    
    
        
    
    
    Half of Uninsured Say Health Law Is Bad Idea http://stks.co/b00PR  When those that u r trying 2 benefit don't like it, u know it is bad $$    
    
    
    Statement Regarding Purchases of Treasury Securities &Agency Mortgage-Backed Securities  http://stks.co/c00Wh  Pares MBS buys by $10B/mo $$    
    
    
    @AlephBlog sorry -- $5b/month change    
    
    
    @AlephBlog wrong again, David -- decrease of $10B, $5B each of Treasuries and MBS    
    
    
    Someone ask Ben Bernanke if they would issue fed funds at longer terms/tenors    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Redacted Version of the December 2013 FOMC Statement: October 2013December 2013CommentsInf... http://bit.ly/1kVRz0a     
    
    
    FOMC Central Tendency for real GDP 2013-6 & long-run 2.27%, 2.91%, 3.09%, 2.83%, 2.25% Change 0.14%, 0.00%, -0.07%, -0.05%, -0.09% $$    
    
    
    FOMC Central Tendency for Unemployment 2013-6 & long-run 7.05%, 6.45%, 5.91%, 5.53%, 5.54% Change -0.11%, -0.13%, -0.12%, -0.10%, 0.04% $$    
    
    
    FOMC Central Tendency for PCE Inflation 2013-6 & long-run 0.99%,1.52%, 1.79%, 1.87%, 2.00% Change -0.21%, -0.01%, -0.10%, 0.00%, 0.00% $$    
    
    
    FOMC Central Tendency for Fed Tightening -- January 2016, 25 months away vs 27 last September, one month further out $$    
    
    
    FOMC Central Tendency for Fed funds rate 2013-6 &long-run 0.25%, 0.34%, 1.06%, 2.18%, 3.88% Change 0.00%, -0.06%, -0.19%, -0.09%, -0.04% $$    
    
    
    Fascinating Bernanke can call Fiscal policy restrictive when deficit huge & shrinking a little, doesn't apply same logic 2 LSAP shrinking $$    
    
    
    AT&T Sells Wireline Assets To Frontier Communications http://stks.co/c00Yk  Interesting 2c $T sell off rural wireline customers 2 $FTR $$    
    
    
    Commented on The Economist | Daily chart: Doomsdays http://rpx.me/1/zMvr     
    
    
    Why Successful CEOs Get Fired http://stks.co/c00eG  Founding CEOs get fired when tasks get larger than them, &the board loses confidence $$    
    
    
    What Bible is Pope Francis reading? http://stks.co/i03wU  Jesus never questioned property rights in his teaching, w/charity voluntary $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Movie Review: Money for Nothing: Movie Review: Money for NothingWhy will you like this fil... http://bit.ly/1dQtUfz     
    
    
    Wrong: Bernanke: More Financial Reform May Be Needed http://stks.co/a00vg  Dumb comment from a guy who doesn't understand how banks work $$    
    
    
    John Podesta eats crow: ‘I apologize to Speaker Boehner’ http://stks.co/g04FW  Don't blame Podesta, he just drank his own Kool-aid $$ ;)    
    
    
    The FOMC- SCR Factors- Bullish SP500? http://stks.co/h04Gf  The TINA effect: TINA stands 4 There Is No Alternative.(to Stock investing) $$    
    
    
    Obama’s own panel rips NSA spying on phone calls of Americans http://stks.co/rlts  The consensus is that the NSA has gone too far $$    
    
    
    Regional Shippers Pose New Threat to UPS, FedEx http://stks.co/qln4  And USPS too. Regionals can get it there the next day $$ $FDX $UPS    
    
    
    Facebook, Zuckerberg to Sell Stock Worth Nearly $4 Billion http://stks.co/qln8  Note $FB compny selling shares; not usually a good sign $$    
    
    
    South Sudan Rebels Take Key Town of Bor http://stks.co/c00pI  It's in the center of the country, kind of a crossroads 4 commerce/travel $$    
    
    
    Republicans Block Symbolic Step to Extend Tax Breaks http://stks.co/g04Gy  Rationality. Maybe temporary tax breaks will b temporary? $$    
    
    
    Vatican Hires Global Firms to Modernize Communications, Accounting http://stks.co/i048E  Humility arrives at the Vatican, expertise 2 $$    
    
    
    Boomers as Retail Clerks Shows Y Greenspan Saw Low Growth Era http://stks.co/d00oU  Long good article how aging populace changes economy $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: but the company is selling; it needs cash more than shares -- good companies typically s... http://stks.co/i048c     
    
    
    "Artificially forcing down Treasury yields via QE has 4 major bad effects…" — David_Merkel http://disq.us/8go7zr  $$ $TLT $IEF $SHY    
    
    
    Why Do So Many People Hate QE? http://stks.co/tleY  Basic reason is fairness. Y can the Fed create credit out of thin air, & we can't? $$    
    
    
    Facebook Is Selling Stock For Some Reason http://stks.co/j03zf  $FB makes it easier 4 index buyers to get shares as it enters the S&P500 $$    
    
    
    Visualizing the Fed | The Big Picture http://stks.co/j03zq  @ritholtz shares a cool interactive graphic on the Fed's Balance Sheet $$ $TLT    
    
    
    Secret Currency Traders’ Club Devised Biggest Market’s Rates http://stks.co/rlwe  There is no human system that cannot b gamed $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Why Are the Chinese Scared of American Corn?  http://stks.co/i049t  Probably some Party bigwig who sells domestic corn complaining $$    
    
    
    Putin Bets $15B to Capture Junk-Rated Ukraine Vassal http://stks.co/qlpI  Rebuilding the USSR is tough work for a tough man to do $$    
    
    
    National Lampoon's ObamaCare Vacation http://stks.co/rlxF  Interesting to hear how poorly Maryland is doing w/its healthcare website $$    
    
    
    A Medicaid Bet in Wisconsin http://stks.co/g04Iw  Scott Walker Says He Wants to Protect the Poorest; Critics Assail 4Not Taking US Funds $$    
    
    
    More Obamacare Delays. Surprised? http://stks.co/qlpY  @asymmetricinfo thinks the law will survive b/c insurers benefit in long-run $$    
    
    
    The Trouble With Populism? It Isn’t That Popular http://stks.co/e00wl  All sorts of extreme positions, mine included, r never popular $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Give Them a Small Bank: It takes a thief to catch a thief.  Thus I have a modest proposal ... http://bit.ly/1dUM2ot     
    
    
    Fed Seen Tapering QE in $10B Steps in Next Seven Meetings http://stks.co/h04dG  Y do economists assume that things follow a simple path? $$    
    
    
    Obama Lifts Health Mandate for Those With Canceled Plans http://stks.co/tm0f  Must b nice 2b able 2alter laws by presidential fiat $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Initiates Self-Destruction Sequence  http://stks.co/rmHm  @asymmeticinfo asks what will Obama do next year on indiv mandate? $$    
    
    
    Man Who Said No to Soros Builds BlueCrest Into Empire http://stks.co/h04dO  Borrowed $750M to hire 25 equity mgrs 4 his hedge funds $$ $SPY    
    
    
    OCC believes banks might be gambling again http://stks.co/c01CL  The OCC is seeing looser underwriting, reminds them of 2007 $$ #toosevere    
    
    
    DJIA Rises to Inflation-Adjusted Record High http://stks.co/a01Il  Closes at 16,221. Guess I have 2 eat my words: http://stks.co/a01Im  $$    
    
    
    GDP Grows 4.1% in Third Quarter, Biggest Gain Since 2011 http://stks.co/sm4k  Guess I have to eat more of my words, US looks good 4 now $$    
    
    
    Buffett's massive wind-power order shows wind energy becoming cheaper http://stks.co/a01Iv  Wind power becomes economical, end subsidies $$    
    
    
    Target Data Breach Has Become a Card Data Fire Sale http://stks.co/i04VH  B especially wary here because it can b used as a debit card $$    
    
    
    US Credit Markets: US Lite Covenant: Freshness without Protection ? http://stks.co/a01J2  Credit protections getting worse 4 bank debt $$    
    
    
    China s Stealth Tightening? http://stks.co/a01JH  A new squeeze hits the China Interbank market & the authorities aren't doing much $$ $FXI    
    
    
    Investors should abandon long-term commodity bets http://stks.co/sm5A  End of supercycle, no income, correlated w/equity returns $$ $GLD    
    
    
    Three things long/short hedge funds cannot do (well) http://stks.co/qmB6  Manage risk, Short stocks on a systematic basis &stop trading $$    
    
    
    The Buffett difference, derivatives edition http://stks.co/f04Xf  Soft collateral reqs, tolerated earnings vol, bot in size w/variety $$    
    
    
    Repo market as a form of free banking http://stks.co/tm1v ? @isakaminska describes a hybrid credit system where central banks r weak $$    
    
    
    The theory of money entanglement (Part 1) http://stks.co/h04ej  The effects of monetary policy vary w/finl institutions need for credit $$    
    
    
    Finished the #GoogleCrossword http://stks.co/d01EB  Haven't done a crossword in years $GOOG #fun    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: The Correlation Trade Gone Wrong: The following was published at RealMoney on May... http://bit.ly/1cjl8tw     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Monetary Policy The theory of money entanglement (Part 1) http://t.c... http://bit.ly/1e1LtZZ     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Classic: Financials are Different: The following was published at RealMoney in March 2006:... http://bit.ly/1fQpuHj     
    
    
    The lavish lifestyles of placement agents http://stks.co/tmCG  With pension monies, there is almost never a reason to pay commissions $$    
    
    
    Wrong: GOP lawmaker: NSA spying in US could have prevented 9/11 http://stks.co/g057I  At best, fighting the last war; live free or die $$    
    
    
    Central Error: that inflation & real growth are positively correlated [1970s] http://read.bi/1l9Ynre     
    
    
    Why the US Leaves Its Credit-Card System Vulnerable to Fraud http://stks.co/e01id  Expensive to add more security & change hardware $$    
    
    
    Junk Loans Top ’08 Record as Safeguards Stripped http://stks.co/c01fF  Amazing how much biz u can do if u just leave aside risk control $$    
    
    
    Venezuela Devalues Bolivar for Tourist Dollars by 44% http://stks.co/e01jV  Almost 2 the point where the dollar will replace the bolivar $$    
    
    
    Russia Crisis Haunts Deutsche Bank’s Smith Seeing China Bust http://stks.co/pmos  Suspect a China debt crisis would not affect US $$    
    
    
    Was 2013 the Year We Lost China? http://stks.co/h057M  It's difficult 2 say whether we ever "had" China, it pursues its own goals $$ $FXI    
    
    
    V.F. Corporation Common Stock Stock Chart http://stks.co/i04z6 ; Interest 2c @Bloomberg & @yahoofinance mess up on $VFC 's 4 for 1 split $$    
    
    
    Secret Handshakes Greet Frat Brothers on Wall Street http://stks.co/c01fR  Part of what led to the crisis- connections&no smarts $$ $MS $GS    
    
    
    South Sudan Refugees Swell As Americans Are Evacuated http://stks.co/tmVf  Throw a bunch of warlords together, call it a govt & u get? $$    
    
    
    Snowden Criticizes US Panel Overseeing Surveillance http://stks.co/pmpi  Panel exists 2whitewash bad behavior of intelgnc establishment $$    
    
    
    Obama Repeals ObamaCare http://stks.co/smaH  It was bad enough under Bush, y does Congress tolerate a president behaving like a king? $$    
    
    
    Unwanted Memories Erased in Electroconvulsive Therapy Experiment http://stks.co/rmme  Great. Another way to remove humanity from people $$    
    
    
    Almond Spike Hits Germany's Markets http://stks.co/c01gH  Bad weather in California & Spain & demand in China push prices 2 record highs $$    
    
    
    Rule Change on Health Insurance Rattles Industry http://stks.co/tmWB  The lowball estimate of what Obamacare would cost comes back2bite $$    
    
    
    China Cash Crunch Pushes Up Short-Term Rates http://stks.co/qmfP  The fragility of the Chinese financial system comes into view $$ $FXI    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Post 2300 — On Business Issues: Every 100 posts or so, I take a moment to think about the ... http://bit.ly/1ckaXDc     
    
    
    Study: Eating Nuts in Pregnancy May Lower Child's Allergy Risk http://stks.co/qmrW  Something new 4 children 2 blame their mothers over $$    
    
    
    http://stks.co/c01uG  "It's the thought that counts, which is worth more than money." — David_Merkel http://stks.co/c01uH  $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Unconstrained Will Get Overdone: Maybe I’ve just had a couple of unusual random draws from... http://bit.ly/1leIEHz     
    
    
    @ReformedBroker Nailed it.    
    
    
    Disagree:Snowden Says Surveillance Is Worse Than Orwell Envisioned http://stks.co/smza  It may b more pervasive but it is low intensity $$    
    
    
    Angry Bart Takes His Parting Shot http://stks.co/a029A  How Wall St fights regulation: Direct kill; defund; exemptions; litigate $$ $GS $MS    
    
    
    PBOC’s Opacity Leaves Markets Guessing Amid Cash Crunch http://stks.co/j05H4  No guess what PBOC policy will b, makin' it up as they go $$    
    
    
    Hunt for Returns Prompts IPO Renaissance as US Leads Way http://stks.co/e028J  Capital will b deployed unproductively as the rally ends $$    
    
    
    Swiss Banks Employ Army of Advisers for US Amnesty Plan http://stks.co/d024g  Differing strategies as US exposure & reporting varies $$    
    
    
    China Promise Clashes With Clampdown on Foreign Business http://stks.co/pnEg  They want the best of both worlds, and can't get both $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Buyback Rally http://stks.co/tmul  From @eddyelfenbein : 2% dividend yield + 3% buyback yield = 5% total yield on the market $$    
    
    
    How Investigators Untangled the 'Wolf of Wall Street' Scandal http://stks.co/e028b  Penny stocks, overtrading, market manipulation $$    
    
    
    Fake Knee Surgery as Good as Real Procedure Study Finds http://stks.co/j05HM  Result Likely2Fuel Debate Over Common Orthopedic Operation $$    
    
    
    What to Do When ObamaCare Unravels http://stks.co/pnF0  Cute alternative 2 PPACA, but I think it could b even more expensive than PPACA $$    
    
    
    Financial Scammers Increasingly Target Elderly Americans http://stks.co/d0250  Tonight's topic @ Aleph Blog - watch out 4 older friends $$    
    
    
    Finnish Security Researcher Cancels RSA Talk in Protest http://stks.co/j05HN  RSA deliberately built faulty random number generator 4NSA $$    
    
    
    Are Cranberries a Better Way to Long Life? http://stks.co/rnCU  The antioxidants in cranberries may prolong your life $$    
    
    
    US Plans to Ask UN for More Troops in Turbulent South Sudan http://stks.co/smzv  UN is not a lot of help in situations like this $$    
    
    
    China Credit Squeeze Eases as Central Bank Resumes Using Regular Cash-Injection Tool http://stks.co/qn2u  Papers over solvency issues $$    
    
    
    Ukraine Upheaval Spurred by 28% Rates Limiting Buyers http://stks.co/tmv3  Capital flees when civil disturbances arise, thus high rates $$    
    
    
    A Pill to Cure Addiction? http://stks.co/c024Y  "huge amount of progress understanding what drives alcoholism & makes it difficult2stop" $$    
    
    
    Wind Farms in Maine Stir a Power Struggle http://stks.co/smzw  I'm sorry, most people know that they don't own their view, give it up $$    
    
    
    Wrong: The Air of Unreality in NSA Reform http://stks.co/f05RB  Being a free country means we have 2 allow 4  possibility of bad events $$    
    
    
    If Cadillac Keeps Growing Like This, It'll Be America's Bestselling Luxury Car http://stks.co/b01yn  We r talking $GM; they will fail $$    
    
    
    ' @SonofGodMovie The 2nd Commandment says it's wrong to portray God. Your movie makes Jesus a mere man; you can't portray his divinity $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Protect Your Older Family & Friends: This article was spurred by this article in the Wall ... http://bit.ly/19hHgyk     
    
    
        
    
    
    Target s Redcard Proves Less Vulnerable to Data Breach Than Bank Cards http://stks.co/a029o  Added security makes the card harder2hack $$    
    
    
    China is so worried about its cash crunch that it banned the term http://stks.co/i05QD  Worry when central bankers care about language $$    
    
    
    The TSC Streetside Chat: Robert Wilson, Part 2 http://stks.co/c024x  13 years old but prescient; he died in a suicide yesterday $$    
    
    
    UN to nearly double peace-keepers in South Sudan as violence explodes http://stks.co/pnFX  UN always increases malfeasance, bad 4 all $$    
    
    
    Colleges Trim Staffing Bloat http://stks.co/e02I0  Finally the bloat of making college into "country clubs" starts to decline $$    
    
    
    Twitter’s Ballooning Market Cap http://stks.co/c02Dc  The price discounts more than the future, it discounts the hereafter $$ $TWTR $SPY    
    
    
    Reactors on Slow Road to Demolition http://stks.co/sn9E  Much hangs on creating a long-term site for storing nuclear waste $$ $D $EXC $ETR    
    
    
    How Thomas Curry Is Trying to Redeem the OCC http://stks.co/d02Ee  U can get a lot done in DC if u don't care who gets the credit $$ $TLT    
    
    
    White Chocolate, a Blank Slate for Flavor, Wins Converts http://stks.co/c02Df  A platform to allow other flavors to show their stuff $$    
    
    
    Bug Bites Cut Florida Orange Crop to Lowest in 2 Decades http://stks.co/a02Iq  Fortunately Brazil is having a good crop; citrus greening $$    
    
    
    Companies Binge on Share Buybacks http://stks.co/sn9L  2% divs +3% buybacks ~5% shareholder yield. Is that enough reward 4 equity risk? $$    
    
    
    Panasonic Debt Goes to First From Worst on Revamp http://stks.co/f05aD  Amazing what can happen when a mgmt team rationalizes businesses $$    
    
    
    Jihadists in Syria Draw Children of Muslims Who Settled in Europe http://stks.co/rnMJ  Romantic youths want their lives 2b more than $$    
    
    
    Even in Straitened Times, Portugal Loves Its Bimby Cooking Robots http://stks.co/pnPj  Y isn't this sold in the US? It does it all $$ $SPY    
    
    
    NSA Struggles to Make Sense of Flood of Surveillance Data http://stks.co/pnPk  Inside look at how data surveillance got out of control $$    
    
    
    $AMZN Makes Up to Customers After Backup Hits $UPS http://stks.co/rnMh  It is possible to overload the shipping system; $20 giftcards $$    
    
    
    Iranians Pile Into Stocks as Nuclear Deal Spurs 133% Gain http://stks.co/b028K  Wall Street getting slow; no $IRAN ETF available yet $$    
    
    
    BlackRock Buys Turkey Shares After Turmoil Spooks Markets http://stks.co/f05af  $TUR down >26% in 2013 http://stks.co/j05RR ; $$    
    
    
    China Confronts Workforce Drop With Retirement-Age Delay http://stks.co/c02EH  China gets to the problem very late & way too small $$ $FXI    
    
    
    GM Robo-Glove to Meat Hook Smooth Human-Machine Teamwork http://stks.co/c02EP  The future of manufacturing: human-robot teams $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Five Lessons of 2013, Guaranteed to Be Forgotten http://stks.co/i05aI  I like # 3. The law of the land is subject to executive action. $$    
    
    
    Wall Street Landlord Loses Round 1 in Ohio School Tax Fight http://stks.co/qnDP  Maybe school district should pass landlord profits tax $$    
    
    
    Investment Strategy Rises From Obscurity http://stks.co/b028j  US Govt loses $7B/yr on MLPs; Article features $IEP $CVR $CVRR $KMP $ETP $$    
    
    
    The One Big Question About RSA and Its Relationship With the NSA http://stks.co/f05bB  RSA builds "backdoor" 4 NSA 2 use, gets secret $$    
    
    
    You Too Can Invest Like Warren Buffett…Maybe http://stks.co/qnDb  U would have to able to predict moats & not lever up too much $$ #tricky    
    
    
    The LEET Pure PC - A PS4 And Xbox One Killer For Your Entertainment Room http://stks.co/c02Ev  Pretty cool. Powerful, flexible & stylish $$    
    
    
    Detroit Wins $55M in Concessions From 2 Banks http://stks.co/i05ap  Derivatives around munis usually have something crooked w/them $$ $MUB    
    
    
    Examiners-in-Residence Should Be Pulled Out of Megabanks http://stks.co/f05bZ  They will resist pressure better if they work together $$    
    
    
    Half & Half: Why Rowing Works http://stks.co/pnQw  A 50-50 mix of stocks & bonds w/rebalancing outperforms 100% stocks in choppy mkts $$    
    
    
    40% of fund managers surveyed r overweight euro-area equities http://stks.co/h05i1  Bull Calls United in Europe, Strategists C 12% Gain $$    
    
    
    So, I'm skeptical of the article in the last tweet, unless the managers r long term investors & value players b/c flexible $$ runs in crises    
    
    
    Obamacare's Web site Exchange Woes Trace to Cato's Michael Cannon http://stks.co/f05bj  One Q is whether the natl exchange can subsidize $$    
    
    
    Edward Snowden, after months of NSA revelations, says his mission’s accomplished http://stks.co/tn77  His life's work is complete @ 29 $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog What are Safe Assets?: When I was young, my paternal grandfather retired, and made my Dad ... http://bit.ly/1g5HeP9     
    
    
    Twitter’s Ballooning Market Cap http://stks.co/e02Mp  Every sell is a good sell. At worst, wait for relative strength to shift $TWTR $$    
    
    
    Commented on The Economist | The 2016 election: Flight of the Huckabees http://rpx.me/1/RYzr     
    
    
    Government Pulls in Reins On Disability Judges http://stks.co/snRB  Disability Trust fund goes bust in 2016, judges urged 2b stricter $$    
    
    
    Moguls Rent South Dakota Addresses to Dodge Taxes Forever http://stks.co/d02VO  Our own tax haven in Black Hills; set up a trust in SD $$    
    
    
    Deaton on US inequality and the Pareto criterion http://stks.co/f05s1  Hard to equalize; rich families have more resources 4 their kids $$    
    
    
    Two trends I'm watching next year http://stks.co/snRD  Cultural changes may limit HH formation & much capital formation is intangible $$    
    
    
    Asia: From baby boom to bust http://stks.co/d02VP  Watch Japan 4a preview of what will happen across all of Asia; it won't b pretty $$    
    
    
    The marriage gap: Think again, men http://stks.co/tnNj  People who r single rely on government more, v. married who rely on each other $$    
    
    
    FDIC Recommendations to Curb Interest Rate Risk http://stks.co/rncr  But will they bifurcate repo 2reveal the interest rate risk inside $$    
    
    
    Will the Regulatory Screws Loosen in 2014? http://stks.co/h05xF  Both sides r dreaming. Neither the regulators or banks r giving up $$    
    
    
    Banking Needs a New Regulatory Structure http://stks.co/h05xG  Rather, end interstate branching, & hand bank regulation back2 the states $$    
    
    
    Muniland’s ‘Best of 2013’ http://stks.co/i05qs  @catelong is one of the best on municipal bonds & here is her summary of 2013 $$ $MUB    
    
    
    Our Outlook for the Stock Market http://stks.co/qnTS  Morningstar gives their relatively bullish view of what 2014 will hold 4 stocks $$    
    
    
    Report on NSA 'secret' payments to RSA fuels encryption controversy http://stks.co/h05xI  Put in a backdoor so that NSA could access $$    
    
    
    A Fund That Invests Like Buffett http://stks.co/rncs  I'm impressed; I'm putting their firm on my 13F list to track them quarterly $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Twitter Posts Biggest-Ever Decline After Macquarie Downgrade http://stks.co/rnct  $TWTR needs 2show real income to validate valuation $$    
    
    
    Thai General Refuses to Rule Out Coup as Unrest Drags On http://stks.co/qnTU  A Thai friend of mine said military is needed in politics $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Hits Snag in States as US Site Finds Footing http://stks.co/tnNo  Surprised that some of the states would do worse than Feds $$    
    
    
    Abenomics Drives Japan Hedge Funds to World’s Top Performers http://stks.co/d02VT  Let's c if Japan can survive the increase in debts $$    
    
    
    Japan World-Beating Stocks Seen Repeating Gains in 2014 http://stks.co/e02Yj  Analysts follow trends; they r wrong at turning points $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Sorted Weekly Tweets: Japan Japan World-Beating Stocks Seen Repeating Gains in 2014 http:/... http://bit.ly/1jSolV0     
    
    
    @dpinsen @PortfolioArmor Go for it!    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Warm up the Helicopter of Happiness: Here is a letter from a reader:Hi David, Long-time re... http://bit.ly/19rtEnz     
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Why Buy Convertible Bonds?: I sometimes answer questions for those at Klout.co... http://bit.ly/19tLanY     
    
    
    @maoxian @randomroger I use "Allmytweets" http://www.allmytweets.net/index.php  & since I do it weekly, search the word "sorted" to find where I left off    
    
    
    @maoxian @randomroger But I'm glad you like it.  I got the idea from @historysquared but realized it could be better 4 readers if I sorted    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog There’s No Tiger in the Tank: Okay, time to roll the promoted stocks scoreboard:TickerDate... http://bit.ly/1akjmlY     
    
    
    2013 Year in Review by David Collum http://stks.co/f06Vh  "Austerity is not a policy; it is a consequence of bad policy" Bad year 4 him $$    
    
    
    Acquisitions Continue to Support AJG http://stks.co/e03F3  Zacks goofs again. Validus $VR isn't an insurance broker, but a P&C reinsurer $$    
    
    
    Guess which hedge funds beat the roaring S&P 500? http://stks.co/d03Ab  Robbins, Paulson, Loeb, Peltz, Tepper, Pucillo $$ $SPY    
    
    
    SEC pushes US insurers for details on 'captives' http://stks.co/i06WY  Isn't primarily a GAAP issue, so the SEC is on the wrong track $$    
    
    
    North Dakota Train Fire Adds Fuel to Keystone XL Debate http://stks.co/poNt  Pipelines r more reliable than trains on average $$ $SPY $TLT    
    
    
    Icahn to FT: Why Shouldn’t My Board Picks Share in Profits? http://stks.co/c038I  Company Sale not always S/H best interests in long run $$    
    
    
    Buffett's year-end bet: Pipelines http://stks.co/e03FK  Fits in nicely w/Lubrizol & $BRK-B other chemical assets | FD: + $BRK-B & $PSX $$    
    
    
    2014 Resolution: This Year, I Will Blog http://stks.co/g06it  Easy 2 say, hard 2do. Tonight, Aleph Blog will give pointers on how 2do it $$    
    
    
    My ‘Wolf of Wall Street’ Review http://stks.co/b034P  @reformedbroker validates much of the tale from his own early experiences $$    
    
    
    Daughter of the Boiler Room http://stks.co/poOh  What would it b like2b daughter of Jordan Belfort's associate? Lots of $$ -> lots of debt    
    
    
    An Open Letter to the Makers of The Wolf of Wall Street, and the Wolf Himself http://stks.co/f06b9  Daughter of a scammer critcizes film $$    
    
    
    How the "Wolf of Wall Street" Is Still Screwing His Real-Life Victims http://stks.co/e03GA  20% restitution made to victims. Not enough $$    
    
    
    Portfolio Hedging Is Alive and Well Under Volcker http://stks.co/g06iv  The "London Whale trade" & things like it r legal w/Volcker Rule $$    
    
    
    TRICKY DICK: Only Nixon less popular than President Obama in Year 5 http://stks.co/roLu  B interesting 2c if it affects 2014 elections $$    
    
    
    S&P 500 Price to Book Value http://stks.co/f06bB  Worth a look- P/B is around 2.7 at present up from 1.8 at the beginning of 2009 $$ $SPY    
    
    
    Stocks $3.7T Year Beats Bonds Most Ever on Funds http://stks.co/i06Xh  What a year; I'm glad I limit my ability2b bearish w/my portfolio $$    
    
    
    Turkey first of Fed Taper victims as political crisis scares investors http://stks.co/roLw  monetary policy tightening reveals weakness $$    
    
    
    It's Official: Pope Has Not Abolished Sin, Says Vatican http://stks.co/i06Xi  That may be, but he certainly downplays its importance $$    
    
    
    Miss Japan Ikumi Yoshimatsu joins battle against mafia in the media http://stks.co/poOm  Can one beauty take on the Yakuza? She can try $$    
    
    
    Argentina’s socioeconomic statistics: Still lying after all these years http://stks.co/g06ix  Official statistics r fudged 2help govt $$    
    
    
    The Rise and Fall of a Local Official Obsessed with GDP Growth http://stks.co/a03EW  Statistics stretched2make things look better $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    The unintended consequences of Abenomics http://stks.co/to5u  @soberlook shows us how the poor & elderly r hurt by Abenomics $$    
    
    
    Bank Borrowing From ECB Jumps http://stks.co/d03Bx  Every bank likes 2 look liquid at year end 4 the snapshot of its balance sheet $$    
    
    
    Israel's Christian Awakening http://stks.co/f06bI  Arab Christians find common ground w/Israeli State vs Arab Muslims to defend Israel $$    
    
    
    Americans on Wrong Side of Pay Gap Run Out of Means to Cope http://stks.co/h06ei  Labor is not scarce & QE inflates necessities & stocks $$    
    
    
    Obamacare Enrollments Hit 1.1M W/December Surge http://stks.co/g06jB  B interesting 2c how well the policy is liked as taxes/prems go up $$    
    
    
    Persistence is a Killer http://stks.co/i06Xp  @reformedbroker points out how hard it is 2 keep outperforming; as AUM rises harder still $$    
    
    
    Say Goodbye to the Same Old Steakhouse http://stks.co/c039P  That most hidebound of dining institutions is long overdue for an update $$    
    
    
    Home Prices Back at Peaks in Some Areas http://stks.co/g06jD  Most of it depends on how well the underlying local economies r doing $$    
    
    
    If 2013 Was Hard on Obamacare, Just Wait for 2014 http://stks.co/f06bM  An actuarially unsound program will get worse over time $$ #watch    
    
    
    Paulson Gets $490 Million as ‘Mooch’ Rotates to Equities http://stks.co/f06bN  Not sure y an action of Scarmucci's firm gets such play $$    
    
    
    Unusual Emerging-Market Bond Bet Pays Off http://stks.co/qoAc  W/lots of liquidity, this was a year 4 the trash 2 fly: Argentina/Greece $$    
    
    
    Private Equity Enjoys a Record Year http://stks.co/i06Xr  Firms That Buy & Sell Companies Are Set to Return >$120B to Investors for 2013 $$    
    
    
    Amid Record Rally, Stock Picker Keeps Focus on the Basics http://stks.co/poOt  Sam Eisenstadt, a Pioneer at Value Line, Remains Bullish $$    
    
    
    The Ride-Sharing, Handbag-Borrowing Productivity Revival http://stks.co/to62  The internet allows people 2 share capital goods easily $$    
    
    
    Wrong: In Search of the Perfect Portfolio http://stks.co/poOw  A fool's errand. Environments change & no simple universal method $$    
    
    
    Scott Yancey - FREE Live Real Estate Income Event http://stks.co/i06Y1  For losers only; learn how to attempt flipping property & lose $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog Advice For Would-be Bloggers: Today I read the following article 2014 Resolution: This Yea... http://bit.ly/1glRtz5     
    
    
    Explaining Hybrid Securities to Chinese Investors http://stks.co/c03Do  Think the Chinese will regret this financial innovation in time $$    
    
    
    Chinese Banks Eye Global Bond Market http://stks.co/soCf  B leery of Chinese bank subordinated debt convertible into equity in failure $$    
    
    
    Bitcoin Is a High-Tech Dinosaur Soon to Be Extinct http://stks.co/soDQ  Bitcoin will die, but it is not right 4 governments 2monopolize $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: What proportion of your investable assets is held in it? http://stks.co/toBP     
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: Just be aware that you have a concentrated position in an income vehicle. If interest ra... http://stks.co/d03HV     
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: Also be aware that distributions from $AMLP have been somewhat irregular in the past:... http://stks.co/e03M8     
    
    
    Health: Scientists Look to Improve Cost and Time of Drug Trials http://stks.co/d03Hq  Sounds promising, but will lose double blind rigor $$    
    
    
    Hertz Runs Over Activist Shareholders http://stks.co/d03Il  A strong poison pill; I'm surprised the price of Hertz went up on the news $$    
    
    
    Stop Pouting About Tech's Next Big Thing, It's Here http://stks.co/toDk  We still haven't maxed out utility of smartphones & tablets $$    
    
    
    New from Aleph Blog On Understanding and Valuing Financial Companies: I have readers all over the world.  Here... http://bit.ly/1d0nLki     
    
    
    The first 3D printed organ -- a liver -- is expected in 2014 http://stks.co/j06kJ  If we can create native organs, impact will be huge $$    
    
    
    Apple, Jacob Appelbaum and the National Security Agency http://stks.co/soTV  Scary article & video of NSA projects by a security expert $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    Berkshire Seen Failing Buffett 5-Year Test for First Time http://stks.co/rogm  Had 2 happen sometime, amazing it went on4so long $$ $BRK-B    
    
    
    Which Buzzwords Would U Ban? http://stks.co/d03WR  Going Forward, Low-Hanging Fruit, Disrupt, Epic, Incentivize, Game Change, Reach Out $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    Cheaper Hanoi Pork Shows Crops Ease World Food Cost http://stks.co/qoVv  Bumper grain harvests in the US & India lower world food costs $$    
    
    
    Finra to Crack Down on Brokers With High Number of Complaints http://stks.co/d03WX  If FINRA is prioritizing now, y didn't they do it b4 $$    
    
    
    Pension Funding Levels Surged in 2013 http://stks.co/g074r  If a Defined Benefit plan is not fully funded now, likely it never will be $$    
    
    
    Bakken Crude More Dangerous to Ship Than Other Oil http://stks.co/soUD  Lighter hydrocarbons tend to b more flammable, need 2 test them $$    
    
    
    Why 'Wildly Overvalued' Stocks May Keep Rising http://stks.co/j06l6  @ritholtz Low short rates, steep yield curve good 4 PE multiples $$    
    
    
    Commented on StockTwits: First time I have heard of Perceptron, thanks for introducing me to it.  No, I don't know... http://stks.co/toU2     
    
    
    Wrong: Homebuyers Missing Housing Rebound Depend on Yellen http://stks.co/j06nf  Too optimistic; Fed no longer controls long rates $$ $TLT    
    
    
    JPMorgan Halts Latvia Dollar Deals After Probes, Group Says http://stks.co/h073o  Latvian banks do $$ laundering w/sloppy investment banks    
    
    
        
    
    
    @groditi For you, I think it would be worth $50+ to review what someone who used 2do it at Credit Suisse thinks. Get the company to pay $$    
    
    
        
    
    
    