@TomNixonSpeaks, sign up for Klout and see how we compare! http://klout.com/TomNixonSpeaks?n=tw&v=undefined …    
    
    
        
    
    
    #nsaga Is this on?    
    
    
    So this is Twitter? Let me get this straight... I keep writing and watch the numbers at the right count down until it reaches 0 then I stop.    
    
    
    That was easy.  Now I'll try putting in a url.  http://motivatethis.net. But I had 67 characters left over.  Have to use all of them all up.    
    
    
    Cool the link worked and took me right to my website. What else can I do? Thanks to Gina Schreck I was able to add a background with my pix.    
    
    
    @loiscreamer I use to work at the Balsams Hotel where the voting takes place on Monday night. Magnificent local    
    
    
        
    
    
    Southern Cooking with a New York attitude.  Here's my new logo; http://ow.ly/i/qi4I     
    
    
    Learning all about twitter from social media guru @KellyVandever http://lockerz.com/s/176209342     
    
    
    Nothing says, "Special Occasion" like a Beef Wellington. Not as hard as you might think. http://wp.me/p1EYFY-3t     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    That's right, a Muffuletta Pizza? Very tasty too. The video and blog post are now up at http://wp.me/p1EYFY-5u     
    
    
    Saw this link at the bottom of my blog and decided to click it: The Mezzetta Muffuletta Pizza http://wp.me/p1EYFY-5u  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    Started drilling a well, it started raining. Been raining five days. Question: Do I Continue drilling for water? Or start building an Ark?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Price_Points @vinnyverelli My good friend Craig made a good point. Jerkey is good, but can't be stuffed with apples and dried cherries.    
    
    
    @TerryBrock Does that mean I'll be paying more for orange juice?    
    
    
        
    
    
    This little piggy went to market, this little piggy stayed home, this little piggy got stuffed with apples, yum!  http://ow.ly/i/zrrl     
    
    
        
    
    
    Mint Julep http://wp.me/p1EYFY-8a     
    
    
        
    
    
    Tomato, Spinach and Gruyère Casserole http://wp.me/p1EYFY-8f     
    
    
    @nourish123 Do you deliver? What's the sauce? A trade secret.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Test Post http://wp.me/p1EYFY-91     
    
    
    @PeteDominick McCain campaign spent more than Obama they didn't raise more but they spent more    
    
    
    Too Many Flavors = Bad Taste http://wp.me/p1EYFY-5N     
    
    
    Peppers Presently Picked are Perfect. http://wp.me/p1EYFY-9o     
    
    
    Not Your Average Fish Taco http://wp.me/p1EYFY-9t     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @PeteDominick Voted Obama. Had to Obamacare saved my life. 28 years without insurance. Have coverage under PCIP for preexisting conditions    
    
    
    @PeteDominick not having facts is one of them inalienable rights guaranteed us.    
    
    
    @realDonaldTrump Shut the fuck up! Bush lost the popular vote in 2000. World laughing as US, no laughing at you.    
    
    
    Pine Nuts - Variation on Pecan Pie http://wp.me/p1EYFY-9G     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @PeteDominick You'll smoke more if marijuana is legalized? Couldn't possibly smoke more Than I do now    
    
    
    @PeteDominick  been using Apple since 1983 apple IIC. I'm not a teenage girl.    
    
    
    The Pizza Chronicles Part One http://wp.me/p1EYFY-ab     
    
    
    The Pizza Chronicles Introductions http://wp.me/p1EYFY-as     
    
    
    Primal Pizza Perfume http://wp.me/p1EYFY-aL     
    
    
    Potato Latkes http://wp.me/p1EYFY-b1     
    
    
    Peanut butter French toast http://wp.me/s1EYFY-691     
    
    
    The Subject Line read, “Success or Mediocrity?”  The terms are not mutually exclusive. I strive for excellence in mediocrity.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @EA How do you cancel an account? No way to contact you other than social media and I'm not feeling very social. I want out.    
    
    
    @OriginInsider Get the questions you need? What a joke. I just want to cancel my account. Want to stop getting emails    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Papa John's Six Cheese Pizza http://wp.me/p1EYFY-bc     
    
    
    Haven't Decided What to Make for Christmas? http://wp.me/p1EYFY-bu     
    
    
    When it comes to steps, 2 is the mew 12.    
    
    
    @dalepenn first buy a bank    
    
    
    Shepherd's Pie - Vinny Style http://wp.me/p1EYFY-bg     
    
    
        
    
    
    Vinny Had a Little Lamb http://wp.me/p1EYFY-bO     
    
    
    I've accepted social media, but can't say that I embrace it. It's more like a hug, the kind of hug you give your Aunt Sofia.    
    
    
    If you know your going to loose your internet connection, do you have to apologize in advance for not posting?    
    
    
    Why does facebook’s spell checker instruct us to write "Facebook" using a capital “F” when facebook uses a small “f?”    
    
    
    @juliemason Log Cabin Republicans I don't get it it's, like Jews for Hitler.    
    
    
    @NSAGLAC always glad to follow NSA groups. But curious; what is GLAC? wait. Greater Los Angeles Chapter?  It's not in your description    
    
    
    @Mizchefcooks Will be in NYC next week after presenting in White Plaines. What's your favorite vegetarian restaurant in Manhattan?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Snowed-in? No Problem. Junior's is Just Around the Corner http://wp.me/p1EYFY-c8     
    
    
    @JuniorsCheeseck shout out to Asif at Junior's Time Square, my SEE™ (Service Exceeding Excellence) winner for Feb. http://wp.me/p1EYFY-c8     
    
    
    Food is the Star of This New York City Show http://wp.me/p1EYFY-cf     
    
    
    I say we choose either apples or oranges and get rid of the other one so we don't have to compare them anymore.    
    
    
    @thevanbrown I'm somewhat goofy now. Wonder what I got into. Oh, now I remember .... what?    
    
    
    @Hyken or you could get rid of ALL social media and no one would know you were giving bad service.    
    
    
        
    
    
    National Pistachio Day http://wp.me/p1EYFY-cK     
    
    
    @dnewman Dude, that's the basic apples and oranges. I eat more pizza but a good burger is heaven. The question is, New York or Chicago?    
    
    
        
    
    
    National Margarita Day http://wp.me/p1EYFY-da     
    
    
        
    
    
    Moonshine Margarita http://wp.me/p1EYFY-dl     
    
    
    Deglaze a Pan with Cognac http://wp.me/p1EYFY-dr     
    
    
    @juliemason One can purchase a gun legally without getting a license to carry a gun.    
    
    
    Shrimp Clemenceau http://wp.me/p1EYFY-dv     
    
    
    @hfburger really? My grill space at home is bigger. 20 minute wait. This better be good    
    
    
    Mobile Pizza Oven http://wp.me/p1EYFY-dx     
    
    
        
    
    
    National Cognac Day - June 4 http://wp.me/p1EYFY-dU     
    
    
    It's National Dry Martini Day http://wp.me/p1EYFY-e6     
    
    
    Fresh Salmon Cakes http://wp.me/p1EYFY-e9     
    
    
    Dining Alfresco http://wp.me/p1EYFY-et     
    
    
    Lasagna ala Vinny http://wp.me/p1EYFY-eT     
    
    
    Roasted Beets with Leftovers http://wp.me/p1EYFY-f6     
    
    
    The B-52 http://wp.me/p1EYFY-fa     
    
    
        
    
    
    One Hour Pot Roast http://wp.me/p1EYFY-fh     
    
    
    Potato Latkes for Hanukkah http://wp.me/p1EYFY-ft     
    
    
    Testing, testing....Is this thing on? #nsaun    
    
    
        
    
    
    thanks, I could be washing my socks.
 #nsaun    
    
    
    Q1: Thought leader, thought follower?  They both sound like multi tasking to me. #nsaun    
    
    
    