Mortgage Foreclosure Is Debt Collection under FDCPA - http://goo.gl/fsCgM  pic.twitter.com/IMgDBO9k2e    
    
    
    Enforcement of Interim and Partial Awards: Emerging Coherence in US Law? - http://goo.gl/Lg9rm  pic.twitter.com/ftoVwknwyY    
    
    
    IBA Adopts New Guidelines on Party Representation in International Arbitration - http://goo.gl/VwOiP  pic.twitter.com/ZaCrkBOOL8    
    
    
    In Quest of the Arbitration Trifecta, or Closed Door Litigation?: The Delaware ... - http://goo.gl/usuO1  pic.twitter.com/bm62c6CwoA    
    
    
    In Quest of the Arbitration Trifecta, or Closed Door Litigation?: The Delaware Arbitration Program - http://goo.gl/wbwBi     
    
    
    An Introduction to Litigation Trusts - http://goo.gl/1JtZa  pic.twitter.com/jAMH9tKELD    
    
    
    An Introduction to Litigation Trusts -    
    
    
    NASA Launches Technology Spinoff iPad App - http://goo.gl/65yAS  pic.twitter.com/jrILpOrbuN    
    
    
    NASA Launches Technology Spinoff iPad App - http://goo.gl/t4vWK  pic.twitter.com/E8MHX76OFg    
    
    
    Arbitration Cases a Growing Revenue Stream for Law Firms - http://goo.gl/5UyQB  pic.twitter.com/xTrfBMdq4T    
    
    
    Arbitration Cases a Growing Revenue Stream for Law Firms - http://goo.gl/Lm6rO  pic.twitter.com/vc8mz564Y8    
    
    
    Sebok on Litigation Financing and Insurance - http://goo.gl/NkBq8     
    
    
    Sebok on Litigation Financing and Insurance - http://goo.gl/xwQY1     
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Considers Arbitrator’s Authority to Issue Discovery-Related Sanctions - http://goo.gl/ZE9mQ  pic.twitter.com/TFYqikoJVY    
    
    
    Using Forensic Accounting in Trust Disputes - http://goo.gl/M3v1T  pic.twitter.com/0QkgnMItel    
    
    
    Equal Contest of Arms, Jurisdictional Proof in Investor-State Arbitrations - http://goo.gl/EMfdR  pic.twitter.com/v5Wv0kRile    
    
    
    Outsourcing Justice: The Rise of Modern Arbitration Laws in America - http://goo.gl/MSyAq  pic.twitter.com/DmJ3w8FyfM    
    
    
    Rethink Ink: Digital Signatures Are Faster & Safer - http://goo.gl/jTwFo  pic.twitter.com/ZdKmXlhaGZ    
    
    
    Moneyball for IP Law - http://goo.gl/D02iK  pic.twitter.com/MqC8kPYp0T    
    
    
    Breaking Down the Business-Judgment Rule - http://goo.gl/4IH5M  pic.twitter.com/5c9KMsMIeV    
    
    
    Lisa Bu: How Books Can Open Your Mind - http://goo.gl/ZwaJT  pic.twitter.com/zI0r5RtWFh    
    
    
    San Antonio Attorney-Mediator Don Philbin Elected 2014 Chair of the State Bar of Texas ... - http://goo.gl/86xKY  pic.twitter.com/pi3Ns9pMxb    
    
    
    New Administered Rules for CPR Arbitration - http://goo.gl/B1xww  pic.twitter.com/Vdava3mUMU    
    
    
    Terms of Merger Agreement Not incorporated Into Master Settlement Agreement - http://goo.gl/eU7Gb  pic.twitter.com/YXlnoNK3pa    
    
    
    San Antonio Attorney Elected Chair of State Bar's ADR Section for 2014-15 Year - http://goo.gl/jgPyf  pic.twitter.com/daXz9ovX46    
    
    
    How To Make War on Patent Trolls - http://goo.gl/06lRM  pic.twitter.com/PIcIwW2Bwm    
    
    
    Learning to Pay Attention: A Fundamental Legal Skill - http://goo.gl/Jv1NX  pic.twitter.com/0FfQ5aQZbk    
    
    
    Roadmap for Driverless Cars: Five Highlights - http://goo.gl/Hf5G5     
    
    
    ALM Debuts Arsenal of 14 iPhone, iPad & iPod Apps - http://goo.gl/I6stg  pic.twitter.com/1vbhS7cE37    
    
    
    12 Ways to Achieve Efficiency and Speed in Arbitration - http://goo.gl/HC10o  pic.twitter.com/e0ArF25HZI    
    
    
    The Case Against Misdirected Regulation of ADR - http://goo.gl/yE5aF  pic.twitter.com/COnLiQpuvA    
    
    
    Is the Tech Revolution Here Already? - http://goo.gl/wPNHF  pic.twitter.com/eeLqzlZUNS    
    
    
    Patent Trolls Threaten to Bankrupt Companies and Stifle Innovation - http://goo.gl/aZiGv  pic.twitter.com/JBN9IZlF7C    
    
    
    Review: Court Directory by Bloomberg BNA - http://goo.gl/Eublv  pic.twitter.com/eKqU7CNyHj    
    
    
    Don't Be Evil. Google Rejects Glass Apps With Facial Recognition - http://goo.gl/oePrt  pic.twitter.com/SWM9yqtJis    
    
    
    Moneyball for Government? http://ow.ly/muysN     
    
    
    PACER Survey Shows Rise in User Satisfaction - http://goo.gl/R6tk1  pic.twitter.com/WEzXaVT9P7    
    
    
    ALM Launches iOS Apps for 14 U.S. Legal Publications - http://goo.gl/6RwEJ  pic.twitter.com/HdWgpRPDyu    
    
    
    Top 5 Reasons Why Law Firms Are Switching Document Management to the Cloud - http://goo.gl/zorO3  pic.twitter.com/LDnqAp5WgO    
    
    
    Mass Layoffs at a Top-Flight Law Firm - http://goo.gl/NJzBH  pic.twitter.com/crwlNUumXb    
    
    
    Corporate Counsel Shift $5.8 Billion In House - http://goo.gl/aXYyr  pic.twitter.com/5OYmKFrUUm    
    
    
    @AskDotCom @Oracle @FTC New Ask Toolbar Trick - Says Chrome is open, but no. Can't remove. Didn't want it; can't dump pic.twitter.com/l7Fu19dh20    
    
    
    Google teaches how to better use Google - http://goo.gl/jtJ4s  pic.twitter.com/0iz5SSIjlU    
    
    
    Streaming, Personalized News Radio on Your Mobile? That’s Swell - http://goo.gl/Iiu3k  pic.twitter.com/FVcrcJoqfH    
    
    
    SCOTUS 2012 Term Stat Pack - http://goo.gl/OUK8K  pic.twitter.com/C4bhpyWFpQ    
    
    
    Law Firms Regain Some Pricing Power - http://goo.gl/5x4sO  pic.twitter.com/zSdafUnWSN    
    
    
    Res Judicata from Arbitration - http://goo.gl/t0Y3p  pic.twitter.com/GSCbW18RTz    
    
    
    Retaliation: University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center v. Nassar - http://goo.gl/GnPyo  pic.twitter.com/dqmzgBWE4u    
    
    
    Will Written on Tablet Computer Because No Paper Was at Hand is Valid, Judge Rules - http://goo.gl/0ow2N  pic.twitter.com/Oli2ShvXmk    
    
    
    Class Action Waiver in Arbitration Agreement Will Be Strictly Enforced Under the ... - http://goo.gl/fkVHr  pic.twitter.com/RHhcLKYNg3    
    
    
    Ninth Circuit Retreats from Complete Destruction of Broughton-Cruz Rule - http://goo.gl/RqCYE  pic.twitter.com/qEsrtlud4D    
    
    
    Patton Boggs Accuses Burford of Betrayal in Chevron Case - http://goo.gl/Ft7Ga  pic.twitter.com/0Me7p89ghW    
    
    
    Using Data to Fix Outside Counsel Budget Forecasts - http://goo.gl/6iIBm  pic.twitter.com/Ge0NB8np8v    
    
    
    NASA, Deloitte Launch Risk Management Partnership - http://goo.gl/sFn7x  pic.twitter.com/p95uSk4O9c    
    
    
    Third-Party Litigation Funding Comes of Age - http://goo.gl/tydKz  pic.twitter.com/BRP6PQA9lO    
    
    
    Associational Arbitration: First Circuit Finds a New Way to Limit Stolt-Nielsen - http://goo.gl/sZTcu  pic.twitter.com/6Q24k6x612    
    
    
    Mediation Dos and Don’ts - http://goo.gl/qUUFU  pic.twitter.com/j3OQFMFVsG    
    
    
    General Electric Joins the ‘Big Data’ Party - http://goo.gl/3Ne5W  pic.twitter.com/YFeTE1DUca    
    
    
    How People Search for Lawyers: The Consumer Law Revolution - http://goo.gl/qWRE0  pic.twitter.com/VKJQPlf9WQ    
    
    
    Entrepreneurs Get Better with Age - http://goo.gl/Ye6Xv  pic.twitter.com/DY9KapUFs5    
    
    
    The Declaration of Independence - http://goo.gl/f9LBI  pic.twitter.com/R7nUdsfPR0    
    
    
    Wolfram|Alpha Apps: Your Guide to Summer - http://goo.gl/vWz3D  pic.twitter.com/l4kZAqgBNs    
    
    
    Our Founding Fathers: Who Were They and What Happened to Them? - http://goo.gl/e5avx  pic.twitter.com/l83MtnPJVO    
    
    
    Vermont Law School Cuts Faculty by 17% Due to Declining Applications - http://goo.gl/lE13B  pic.twitter.com/AhR0z6A1EB    
    
    
    Dean Nancy B. Rapoport on Legal Education Reform - http://goo.gl/ddYcu  pic.twitter.com/lRfVZdvBmn    
    
    
    Psychology for Lawyers - http://goo.gl/a28q2  pic.twitter.com/CviBAGjbdc    
    
    
    When is Litigation Like Las Vegas ? - http://goo.gl/vo5Nh  pic.twitter.com/ydndpbYeQ7    
    
    
    The Fifth Circuit Accepts Judicial Estoppel as a Basis for Discovery - http://goo.gl/obPkE  pic.twitter.com/iUdPOfxaSi    
    
    
    Rise Of The Machines - http://goo.gl/Idg2N  pic.twitter.com/XfEHVs4nqC    
    
    
    Legal Consultant Says Biglaw May See "Wave" of Job Cuts Following Layoffs at Weil Gotshal - http://goo.gl/AHL1J  pic.twitter.com/cnqV9r9hg4    
    
    
    BigLaw Reps Dispute That "Wave" of Layoffs is Coming - http://goo.gl/PM07x  pic.twitter.com/q7fy7glUdm    
    
    
    Social Media Will Soon Drive More T To Law Firm Websites Than Search Engines - http://goo.gl/8USib  pic.twitter.com/82ylzD9keg    
    
    
    Baker & McKenzie Jumps to Office 2010 and Embraces Templates - http://goo.gl/usu65  pic.twitter.com/EuKDeOGqpR    
    
    
    Review: TripIt -- Manage Flights, Hotels, and Other Travel on Your iPhone and iPad - http://goo.gl/9H4ac  pic.twitter.com/Z5YRYAkM5Z    
    
    
    56% of People Use Social Media When Looking for Attorney - http://goo.gl/Z7Mjd  pic.twitter.com/TO8RzLk6Rs    
    
    
    What Do Lawyers Sell? - http://goo.gl/dJEDu  pic.twitter.com/lOqASts5me    
    
    
    Can Government Play Moneyball? - http://goo.gl/Yz1Mv  pic.twitter.com/2vqZHfoKex    
    
    
    Data is Worthless if You Don't Communicate It - http://goo.gl/nqgQY  pic.twitter.com/rpB5qRTTjV    
    
    
    A Social Network Custom Made for Customers of Thomson Reuters Elite - http://goo.gl/ck22b  pic.twitter.com/kWppIy1eTx    
    
    
    A Lawyer Reviews Microsoft Word for iPhone Plus 125 More Must-Reads - http://goo.gl/1JU7k  pic.twitter.com/2sMZmy1E3a    
    
    
    Law School Winners and Losers in the Applications Game [Video] - http://goo.gl/oKZNU  pic.twitter.com/rGNZtxLFI0    
    
    
    VerdictSearch Puts On a New Face - http://goo.gl/svJx2  pic.twitter.com/3ma9M6MGs5    
    
    
    Pricing and Framing: When Are We Likely to Pay More for Products? - http://goo.gl/KYe4R  pic.twitter.com/S9w3MBgsUK    
    
    
    Negotiation Law Blog Lives On and On and On at The Library Of Congress - http://goo.gl/rw6G7  pic.twitter.com/fzxIfVBeYv    
    
    
    Are Young Lawyers Less Willing to Negotiate Agreements? - http://goo.gl/s0OsZ  pic.twitter.com/7EvT0hLHva    
    
    
    Great presentation by @klrn CEO Mario A. Vazquez on exciting things in development    
    
    
    Med Students Learn How Graphics Can Effectively Communicate: Why Not Mediators? - http://goo.gl/BisKZ  pic.twitter.com/AoUzq9YvPE    
    
    
    Private Equity Firm Buys Intuit for $1 Billion - http://goo.gl/SGMk8  pic.twitter.com/3IhckELOzw    
    
    
    Trial By Preview - http://goo.gl/VOhwZ  pic.twitter.com/T40vkQIXNL    
    
    
    Social Media and Jury Duty - http://goo.gl/TUfF4  pic.twitter.com/F8SmwQd8iM    
    
    
    Your Judgment May be Impairing You - http://goo.gl/FwVFi  pic.twitter.com/GYbDlHgYrn    
    
    
    Innovation in the Legal Services Industry – The Future is Already Here, It is Just ... - http://goo.gl/nSeOA  pic.twitter.com/TYIZsUoGS5    
    
    
    Make Litigation Timelines in PowerPoint with Free Add-On - http://goo.gl/x445l  pic.twitter.com/FTQNK3S7ya    
    
    
    Being Productively Dangerous by Ignoring Perfectionism: Learning Bold From a Story Told - http://goo.gl/uu9Wp  pic.twitter.com/BYSfbBcTRw    
    
    
    Harvard's Top 5 Business Negotiation Mistakes - http://goo.gl/PvW8P  pic.twitter.com/Y5mFOH3BRO    
    
    
    No Sanctions for Deletion of Email Folder Belonging to "Perhaps the Key Witness" Absent ... - pic.twitter.com/8dml4Ywqcu    
    
    
    Juridica Announces Partial Settlement of Portfolio Case Generating $17.5 Million Return - pic.twitter.com/36hxwmPgY3    
    
    
    Smartphone App for Bipolar Patients Wins $100K Prize - pic.twitter.com/HdKBbAnBUN    
    
    
    ArbitrationNation Roadmap: When Should You Choose JAMS, AAA or CPR Rules? - pic.twitter.com/PM14tfOWfR    
    
    
    Yes You Can Be Liable For Negotiating in Bad Faith - pic.twitter.com/t1zhT4zkya    
    
    
    Opinion Highlights Questions Surrounding Proper Predictive Coding Protocols - pic.twitter.com/3W4uEzlNsL    
    
    
    Inside Brains of Winners - pic.twitter.com/lmuZjVYHBS    
    
    
    Facilitative vs. Evaluative Mediation - pic.twitter.com/HCH4K0CwLt    
    
    
    The Women of Bitcoin - pic.twitter.com/aq7PvtmkM2    
    
    
    SCOTUS Says “Tough Luck” To Plaintiffs Whose Claims Are Too Pricey To Prove In ... - pic.twitter.com/pqHKwaB3S0    
    
    
    Conducting "Traditional Relevance Analysis," Court Denies Full Access to Plaintiff's ... - pic.twitter.com/Ttps8VKEqE    
    
    
    Google Books Defeats Copyright Infringement Class Action - pic.twitter.com/AAwlZatNZW    
    
    
    Knowledge Automation Software is a Disruptive Technology That May Replace Lawyers - pic.twitter.com/BEyCC5uDXV    
    
    
    Connecting a Mobile Game to Real World Legal Services - pic.twitter.com/tc6bfFQHk3    
    
    
    Google+ at 2 years old: Where are we? - pic.twitter.com/BlNJj8VQko    
    
    
    Social Media Monitoring Services–Law Firms Using Correctly? - pic.twitter.com/Dzv4DzAP8p    
    
    
    Consumer Law Revolution from ReInvent Law Channel - pic.twitter.com/1meISHBKtp    
    
    
    App Stores In Cars? Are You Joking? No. - pic.twitter.com/vVs7xLfEhG    
    
    
    Digging into Words with Wolfram|Alpha - pic.twitter.com/qKGypYVnsm    
    
    
    Google Field Trip - Explore Your World - pic.twitter.com/OsOmW0nD2C    
    
    
    BYOD Policies: A Litigation Perspective - pic.twitter.com/1pCN5lf6ux    
    
    
    Handling the Oncoming Tide of Generic Top-Level Domain Name Disputes - pic.twitter.com/R1SmEpOXFD    
    
    
    Second Life Avatars Class Action Settles - pic.twitter.com/PwW8xCct97    
    
    
    SEC to Limit Ability to Settle Without Admission of Wrongdoing - pic.twitter.com/UliRBreNw1    
    
    
    New Article: “Managing Disputes in a Flat World” - pic.twitter.com/GeIfkCi3xz    
    
    
    Supreme Court Affirms Commitment to Narrow Judicial Review of Arbitration Awards in ... - pic.twitter.com/cG8vHeVebz    
    
    
    Categorize Your Case to Learn Its Value - pic.twitter.com/jAjuFCS5JE    
    
    
    Washington Legislature Says Statute of Limitations Applies to Arbitration Proceedings - pic.twitter.com/wrnvsE6xIO    
    
    
    Reflections on 2013 Supreme Court Arbitration Decisions - pic.twitter.com/5y83OGeiII    
    
    
    Taking Advantage of ADR in the Entertainment Industry - pic.twitter.com/JRRnJ4zTLM    
    
    
    Supreme Court Limits ATS Litigation—But Door Remains Slightly Ajar - pic.twitter.com/qQzyJccoxw    
    
    
    Equal Contest of Arms, Jurisdictional Proof in Investor-State Arbitrations - pic.twitter.com/xsw1MfhHnG    
    
    
    Walk a Block in My Socks, Walk a Mile in Their Shoes… - pic.twitter.com/gcnm6xHVOs    
    
    
    Challenging Awards for Lack of Disclosure - http://goo.gl/fJJsm  pic.twitter.com/Fd5AOcv3on    
    
    
    FINRA to Conduct Background Checks on Arbitrators - http://goo.gl/fL6Xy  pic.twitter.com/pOA9RtLfov    
    
    
    Comcast Corp. v. Behrend: Plot Twists and a Surprise Ending - http://goo.gl/GQChc  pic.twitter.com/Qf6vQ68TNj    
    
    
    Empowering the Growth of International ADR - http://goo.gl/eEwCV  pic.twitter.com/GSBV0dDbMa    
    
    
    Empowering the Growth of International ADR: Cries for Change - http://goo.gl/ahFSo  pic.twitter.com/2D6bkxGHoQ    
    
    
    Empowering the Growth of International ADR - http://goo.gl/bj8q8  pic.twitter.com/Xpuw2vnKrq    
    
    
    Massachusetts Invalidates Arbitration Agreement Because Plaintiffs Could Not ... - http://goo.gl/khVzf  pic.twitter.com/vLYFuItrMB    
    
    
    Teaching with Teaching a New Negotiation Skills Paradigm - http://goo.gl/u2Mr3  pic.twitter.com/0LoXOCcoy3    
    
    
    SEC Seeks Public Comment on Arbitrator Selection Rule Proposal - http://goo.gl/n4nlZ  pic.twitter.com/22Otk2hax5    
    
    
    In Quest of the Arbitration Trifecta, or Closed Door Litigation? - http://goo.gl/KMqZF  pic.twitter.com/i1Xw0EgECA    
    
    
    SCOTUS Affirms Arbitrator’s Decision To Allow Class Arbitration in Sutter - http://goo.gl/l1X6f  pic.twitter.com/IC5HGKeOZF    
    
    
    Regulating, Certifying, Creating Barriers to Entry…. - http://goo.gl/jjV2c  pic.twitter.com/FpZZ9kcfJV    
    
    
    Texas Maximum Child Support Cap Is Changing September 1, 2013 - http://goo.gl/gXhcd  pic.twitter.com/5JCjMQNz8t    
    
    
    The Library of Congress is Archiving Legal Blogs - http://goo.gl/TfFIF  pic.twitter.com/lkwRbkdW6g    
    
    
    Lawyer Who Urged Client to Clean Up Facebook Page Paid $544K Legal Bill; Now Faces ... - http://goo.gl/31R8R  pic.twitter.com/angHUAd6AX    
    
    
    Fastcase & William S. Hein Publishing – Like a Reese’s Cup - http://goo.gl/c4J8r  pic.twitter.com/zewHaINTaA    
    
    
    Make Phone Calls From GMail - http://goo.gl/AdNrS  pic.twitter.com/v6OYyLgNqY    
    
    
    GlassUp - No Camera, No Video, Cheap - http://goo.gl/paIeQ  pic.twitter.com/LLHAWumjl5    
    
    
    20 Essential Keyboard Shortcuts For Feedly Power Users - http://goo.gl/k0ca0  pic.twitter.com/503Nh43SfC    
    
    
    Ray Kurzweil at LTF 2013 – Interview with Charles Christian - http://goo.gl/SCgIF  pic.twitter.com/q9C8Jv14sj    
    
    
    Five Years of the App Store - http://goo.gl/Jnk81f  pic.twitter.com/GkEzR7fAqk    
    
    
    Horseless Carriages to Driverless Cars - http://goo.gl/zazpN  pic.twitter.com/hAT9NzOGZZ    
    
    
    Patent Complaint Does Not Have to Identify Infringing Activity - http://goo.gl/Mm5HyV  pic.twitter.com/ffSM1ZGyqV    
    
    
    McDermott and DOJ Embrace Predictive Coding - http://goo.gl/HXAut  pic.twitter.com/UruRYFGCZG    
    
    
    U.S. Legal Industry Experiencing Record Year for Mergers - http://goo.gl/yVkRB  pic.twitter.com/nBGotRJigg    
    
    
    If “Grave Error” Is Not Enough to Vacate An Arbitrator’s Decision, What Is? - http://goo.gl/q5MCs  pic.twitter.com/4OPDkV9pU5    
    
    
    Request for Proposals for the ABA DR Section Spring Conference - http://goo.gl/eKgrv2  pic.twitter.com/xy9p31bk1e    
    
    
    Thoughts on the Constitutionality of the Delaware Arbitration Program - http://goo.gl/ow8rjA  pic.twitter.com/7hglzqpLpW    
    
    
    Could Baker & McKenzie Have Saved $150 Million Last Year? - http://goo.gl/gtQizt  pic.twitter.com/zuKJhKgYm5    
    
    
    From the Spring 2013 DR Magazine: Welsh and Lipsky - http://goo.gl/zVcdF8  pic.twitter.com/zbJjzN1AXt    
    
    
    Florida's Economic Loss Rule Limited to Products Liability Cases - http://goo.gl/5hB91E  pic.twitter.com/8s18gofJSh    
    
    
    Modria Closes New Investment Round to Fuel Expansion - http://goo.gl/xnuKnR  pic.twitter.com/XEqKWwO3UD    
    
    
    The Role Of Representations, Warranties And Covenants - http://goo.gl/h6AS5L  pic.twitter.com/E9aB7dY3H8    
    
    
    Mediating Complex Cases - http://goo.gl/46Yqau  pic.twitter.com/k250qCvbKr    
    
    
    Ninth Circuit Allows Intervention to Preserve Deposition - http://goo.gl/77A0eq  pic.twitter.com/RSh3QozQrM    
    
    
    Gold treatment for @Hertz at LAX pic.twitter.com/Hq0nzoUIQe    
    
    
    @Hertz "Gold" Service - pay premium for longest line at LAX! pic.twitter.com/8uuj14JnQL    
    
    
    U.S. Supreme Court Grants Certiorari in Arbitration Dispute Involving Investment Treaty - http://goo.gl/deUxUB  pic.twitter.com/ptu2Ynm1ih    
    
    
    Procedural Justice in Judicial Settlement Conferences - http://goo.gl/R3UJGd  pic.twitter.com/UalExwUabR    
    
    
    12 Ways to Achieve Efficiency and Speed in Arbitration - http://goo.gl/PAZgo1  pic.twitter.com/V2xP2A8K62    
    
    
    @Hertz F8962556572 hour wait for dinged Chevy w 25 miles. could done better in time, money, and car choice at a low grade provider wife gold    
    
    
    Class Certification Denied in Data Breach Case - http://goo.gl/lUf4S2  pic.twitter.com/o1hfb55k0h    
    
    
    DEMO: Picture It Settled® with Don Philbin (ADRtoolbox) - http://goo.gl/txv97S  pic.twitter.com/rSXt56JcM2    
    
    
    Is Wrongful Death Lawsuit Subject to Arbitration? - http://goo.gl/ATSHjR  pic.twitter.com/zwdMxPcS90    
    
    
    Terms of Service & Privacy Policies Create Virtual Law - http://goo.gl/MDTeC6  pic.twitter.com/urSscfaD8v    
    
    
    Da Silva Moore: Plaintiffs Petition for Writ of Certiorari on Question of Recusal - http://goo.gl/O6YIgF  pic.twitter.com/eK8xy61ppH    
    
    
    How Lawyers' Intuitions Prolong Litigation - http://goo.gl/xHDXMG  pic.twitter.com/GBzs8lEFXq    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Issues Emergency Stay to Consider Arbitration - http://goo.gl/2ziVHK  pic.twitter.com/TeMWmShw4X    
    
    
    @Hertz  he didn't even offer to switch out the car we're stuck in for 10 more days    
    
    
    Law Firm's Advance Conflict Waiver Upheld - http://goo.gl/o9KjpR  pic.twitter.com/C8xAXGQma3    
    
    
    Did the Court Just Look at Facebook On Its Own? - http://goo.gl/TGriR8  pic.twitter.com/DqFBS71LiE    
    
    
    Court Refuses to Disqualify E-Discovery Vendor for ‘Switching Sides’ in Case - http://goo.gl/hfmXC5  pic.twitter.com/shvY2wgHiN    
    
    
    Fastcase Announces 50 Legal Innovators to Watch - http://goo.gl/QA8N29  pic.twitter.com/bXD86czzav    
    
    
    GPS Location Data Requires a Warrant - http://goo.gl/fjX5kc  pic.twitter.com/CEQ4bOXPlt    
    
    
    The Innovators: Renee Newman Knake - http://goo.gl/Nr1Sb4  pic.twitter.com/tPjv1eldoE    
    
    
    Are Companies Like Axiom Law a Threat to BigLaw?  - http://goo.gl/l74Ct9  pic.twitter.com/Adfzdv3j7W    
    
    
    Law Grad Alleges Bar Exam Is Unconstitutional - http://goo.gl/UstjfE  pic.twitter.com/IjLiHJBQvl    
    
    
    What’s the Value of a Law Degree? $1M in a Lifetime, Report Says - http://goo.gl/WnUG2W  pic.twitter.com/En4NUU4i9K    
    
    
    TyMetrix Announces Global Expansion Following Exceptional Growth - http://goo.gl/29u4D3  pic.twitter.com/E9vJQAfDlv    
    
    
    Cool Tools at American Association of Law Libraries Event - http://goo.gl/mNhTiY  pic.twitter.com/h3OICrmM7M    
    
    
    FAA Pre-Emption of State Law Limits on Arbitration: The Ninth Circuit Grapples with ... - http://goo.gl/iynSD0  pic.twitter.com/2diuWsH5Uw    
    
    
    Conflict Resolution in Sport - http://goo.gl/efSH3d  pic.twitter.com/biny4DpvP9    
    
    
    Arbitration Arithmetic - http://goo.gl/qlz8ax  pic.twitter.com/czBh6qGp5h    
    
    
    Eleventh Circuit Applies Sutter to Affirm Class Arbitration; Ninth Circuit Applies ... - http://goo.gl/oJrDuA  pic.twitter.com/Le7gttq8fc    
    
    
    Contracting For Funding In “Access To Justice Cases” Versus “Corporate Finance ... - http://goo.gl/8OjJcg  pic.twitter.com/LJx2vlhvuy    
    
    
    Small Business B-2-B Arbitration Part II.A: The Nature and Purpose of Arbitration - http://goo.gl/aWl9iO  pic.twitter.com/2bjqy8ttBf    
    
    
    Negotiating the Reverse Auction in Class Action Cases - http://goo.gl/8kUFSu  pic.twitter.com/PT4ip6IQvk    
    
    
    Number of Civil Jury Trials Conducted in Texas Reaches a 40-Year Low - http://goo.gl/JVdf98  pic.twitter.com/PDzfg9YenL    
    
    
    The Impact of Chief Justice Jefferson’s State of the Judiciary Speech - http://goo.gl/FmreJs  pic.twitter.com/uTD4RxnKQS    
    
    
    Good Faith Duty As Alternative To Fiduciary Duty - http://goo.gl/w4gp1b  pic.twitter.com/jS5uc4nbQY    
    
    
    U.S. Supreme Court Considering Petition for Certiorari in Dispute Over How to Define ... - http://goo.gl/lVK0Yd  pic.twitter.com/o0GqoLVjFY    
    
    
    Mediation in NFL Concussion Lawsuit - http://goo.gl/0OXQD3  pic.twitter.com/gdRI6FUCer    
    
    
    SCOTUS Reaffirms Manifest Disregard of the Agreement Outcome Review Standard and ... - http://goo.gl/lQqh1A  pic.twitter.com/83F3GqTphC    
    
    
    Disruptive Technologies: Advances That Will Transform Life, Business, and the Global Economy - http://goo.gl/IcPuo7  pic.twitter.com/WBpH7ZqTrL    
    
    
    The Third Wave Of Litigation Finance: Litigation Finance As Corporate Finance - http://goo.gl/aSZK1Y  pic.twitter.com/oBXx8p4Nwn    
    
    
    San Antonio COA Refuses to Compel Nursing Home Negligence Case to Arbitration - http://goo.gl/FLj5iw  pic.twitter.com/2JWR4re13R    
    
    
    The Mediation Solution - http://goo.gl/E9di4p  pic.twitter.com/ocymHEvtD6    
    
    
    California Court Upholds Arbitration Provision Invoked by Non-Signatory - http://goo.gl/oQE8EJ  pic.twitter.com/YaBc3pRucZ    
    
    
    When Should You Choose JAMS, AAA or CPR Rules? - http://goo.gl/4s3YNk  pic.twitter.com/61NDf5yvLd    
    
    
    The Need For And The Potential Role Of Reputation Markets In Litigation Finance - http://goo.gl/sW7Jw6  pic.twitter.com/K6QTZyI3re    
    
    
    With Moto X, Google Enters a Crowded Marketplace - http://goo.gl/CZs0jg  pic.twitter.com/aMEG2T5dgM    
    
    
    Online Arbitration Round-Up - http://goo.gl/zpm0C3  pic.twitter.com/XJfiMcfBPi    
    
    
    Res Judicata Barred Claims Resolved in Arbitration - http://goo.gl/g5NT8S  pic.twitter.com/VzAYbGkSzD    
    
    
    Challenges to Forum Non Conveniens - http://goo.gl/YutVrE  pic.twitter.com/suavlgwSUv    
    
    
    Call for Papers – Forced Arbitration in the Workplace - http://goo.gl/UwKytT  pic.twitter.com/mhhpNoN2DL    
    
    
    Plaintiffs’ Obligation To Cooperate - http://goo.gl/0MJInT  pic.twitter.com/AUY2faN575    
    
    
    Acrobat to the Rescue: Searching Unsearchable Productions - http://goo.gl/tlTUdk  pic.twitter.com/ZCvUtcahcF    
    
    
    One-third to One-Half of 1.5 Million U.S. Lawyers Do Not Work as Lawyers - http://goo.gl/KVGaA1  pic.twitter.com/p3D3pLyMch    
    
    
    Google Maps Desktop Is New Again - http://goo.gl/QbxKIO  pic.twitter.com/ofXw1WaS7l    
    
    
    Mass. Moves to Require Technology Competence for Lawyers - http://goo.gl/MdU5PQ  pic.twitter.com/QzPqNKjw7K    
    
    
    The Last Days of Big Law - and the Snakepit at Mayer Brown - http://goo.gl/vsuFvf  pic.twitter.com/dCL1v0iO4I    
    
    
    Using Algorithmic Attribution Techniques to Determine Authorship In Unsigned Judicial ... - http://goo.gl/XG2rfC  pic.twitter.com/Wh9T9QsgK0    
    
    
    Google Databoard: A New Way to Explore Industry Research - http://goo.gl/IGr2Kr  pic.twitter.com/LnwzzW963y    
    
    
    Trump Wins $5 Million Slander Arbitration Award Against Beauty - http://goo.gl/tacdK5  pic.twitter.com/vOaCIomMev    
    
    
    The Future of Printed Law Reviews - http://goo.gl/FGMJDf  pic.twitter.com/ZjAelRVtpN    
    
    
    World's Thinnest LCD Panel Unveiled By LG - http://goo.gl/cc0VUB  pic.twitter.com/z4iVYBjuBG    
    
    
    A Farewell to Cushy BigLaw: Mayer Brown a Case Study in Coping and Hard-Charged Competition - http://goo.gl/O2Xbca  pic.twitter.com/RoNyXe07rX    
    
    
    Senate Hearing Is Warned of Lasting Damage to Courts - http://goo.gl/0gBXFh  pic.twitter.com/DP0kLMXnYp    
    
    
    Detroit Bankruptcy Judge Proposes Mediator for Toughest Disputes - http://goo.gl/xEac62  pic.twitter.com/0DMRYeXjxm    
    
    
    The Cost of Higher Education: The Big Picture - http://goo.gl/K1SS9Q  pic.twitter.com/IStIpBWIO1    
    
    
    'Stowers' Doctrine in Need of an Update - http://goo.gl/OjVsRj  pic.twitter.com/4d2mtwIm7j    
    
    
    New Legal Research Site Combines Case Law with Crowdsourcing - http://goo.gl/1zAIy6  pic.twitter.com/y8tohEOcKi    
    
    
    Admissibility of Settlement-Related Evidence at Trial - http://goo.gl/z4rWUo  pic.twitter.com/8CwZQGhQ8q    
    
    
    When Facebook (et al.) Attacks - http://goo.gl/Xap2cH  pic.twitter.com/21wfx1VF9j    
    
    
    Posner Tells How Internet Research Has Helped Him Draft Opinions - http://goo.gl/hPWxHl  pic.twitter.com/tWpfH3UlHo    
    
    
    Predictive Coding and Technology-Assisted Review: Hype or Need? - http://goo.gl/AeYCEE  pic.twitter.com/Jl5Sui6WXp    
    
    
    Bloomberg Law to Rebrand as Bloomberg BNA - http://goo.gl/wsM3ev  pic.twitter.com/p8nN2EwsWR    
    
    
    Institutional-Grade Lawsuits: Fewer Dismissals, Larger Settlements - http://goo.gl/F62WeU  pic.twitter.com/lezTKjPcfO    
    
    
    D&O Rates Rise on Flood of Merger Lawsuits - http://goo.gl/5nf3ft  pic.twitter.com/1S7P1QQS9k    
    
    
    Labor Firm’s App Calculates FMLA Leave - http://goo.gl/xnNUjh  pic.twitter.com/8L7Fi1gwx8    
    
    
    Master the Business of Law With Metrics, MatterAnalyzer, and Matter Management - http://goo.gl/9P42rR  pic.twitter.com/YQAFJAV54B    
    
    
    Federal Court Issues Sanctions for Failure to Preserve Text Messages - http://goo.gl/MJgmIW  pic.twitter.com/AtUFH2wlrq    
    
    
    Here's What Brick-and-Mortar Stores See When They Track You - http://goo.gl/DI1CFa  pic.twitter.com/K3FPEquI3z    
    
    
    Congress Weighs Balance of IP Freedoms and Protections - http://goo.gl/yskL9s  pic.twitter.com/RhjnlD77o8    
    
    
    GUILTY: Malcolm Gladwell Caused Lehman To Fail - http://goo.gl/fbd9Th  pic.twitter.com/8GRpxtoqlH    
    
    
    Google's Android Seizes Smartphone Market - http://goo.gl/Ddw4OJ  pic.twitter.com/TupIRG3Map    
    
    
    Jumping to Conclusions, Malcom Gladwell Edition - http://goo.gl/Y0Yutj  pic.twitter.com/aQfzPdrfGB    
    
    
    List of Cognitive Biases - http://goo.gl/NTpe8i  pic.twitter.com/VR7hzz76p0    
    
    
    Masters of our Own Destiny: Marc Teerlink at TEDxFlanders - http://goo.gl/SRyT02  pic.twitter.com/qmz6v9cuHe    
    
    
    Bankruptcy Filings Down 13 Percent in June 2013 - http://goo.gl/hxGYb7  pic.twitter.com/jIDCO3nq6Q    
    
    
    The Construction of Emotion in Interactions, Relationships, and Cultures - http://goo.gl/3B5MWv  pic.twitter.com/TOzeyiaVLE    
    
    
    Second Circuit Enforces Class Waiver in Arbitration Clause Following American Express  - http://goo.gl/KWVJDm  pic.twitter.com/vXeJDZL2hN    
    
    
    Dechert Looks to Hollywood for Marketing Edge (video) - http://goo.gl/KEoGhU  pic.twitter.com/9HDqZjxRKr    
    
    
    Don't Bury Big Law Just Yet - http://goo.gl/gJUP41  pic.twitter.com/Exdov1XphM    
    
    
    All is well for BigLaw? - http://goo.gl/hQYyHv  pic.twitter.com/FkZR6iqTEI    
    
    
    Being Great At Math Is More Important Than Ever - http://goo.gl/dDl7Ov  pic.twitter.com/2Mrtls561c    
    
    
    Lawyers’ Social Media Use Grows Modestly, ABA Annual Tech Survey Shows - http://goo.gl/d6WpmN  pic.twitter.com/YimLcKD1KO    
    
    
    Lawyers’ Use of Cloud Shows Big Jump in ABA Tech Survey - http://goo.gl/MI9Xbm  pic.twitter.com/otBwc1TgnN    
    
    
    The Most Popular Apps for Lawyers, According to ABA Tech Survey - http://goo.gl/JKX3qB  pic.twitter.com/iS22m4Twvs    
    
    
    How Writing Your Attorney Profile Is Like Writing a Dating Website Profile - http://goo.gl/0klmel  pic.twitter.com/Aff9CxW8wE    
    
    
    2013 ABA Tech Survey once again shows surge in attorneys using iPhone, iPad - http://goo.gl/M1syNI  pic.twitter.com/roNSTussmQ    
    
    
    Debating the Health and Future of BigLaw - http://goo.gl/JrSq6Y  pic.twitter.com/iJm11CnD0A    
    
    
    Webinar: Getting Your Online Content Read: Best Editorial Practices - http://goo.gl/dH8epE  pic.twitter.com/nXds41OtUT    
    
    
    White House Hobbles Samsung, ITC in Apple Patent Fight - http://goo.gl/2fPM4J  pic.twitter.com/HTrjkFxE4l    
    
    
    "Private" Postings Nevertheless Discoverable - http://goo.gl/2qCRpB  pic.twitter.com/XcAaD56ORv    
    
    
    Texas Courts Like Arbitration - Nationsbuilders Part II - http://goo.gl/avzp3h  pic.twitter.com/jcUBmn9Sc8    
    
    
    Ethical Breach by Class Counsel Does Not Defeat Certification - http://goo.gl/SLCwt2  pic.twitter.com/dMbuXarqro    
    
    
    The 2013 GC Compensation Survey - http://goo.gl/czbtAQ  pic.twitter.com/JJG5intldO    
    
    
    Moneyball for Negotiation: Projecting the Negotiation Process at ReInvent Law London http://reinventlawchannel.com/don-philbin/     
    
    
    @aricpress hope this forwards @ReInventLaw London talk - saw you in Silicon Valley    
    
    
    @aricpress here it is http://reinventlawchannel.com/don-philbin/     
    
    
    @DonnaTuttleSABJ my TED-style talk in London http://reinventlawchannel.com/don-philbin/     
    
    
    Federal Court Doesn't ‘Like” Service of Process via Facebook -- Joe Hand Proms. v. ... - http://goo.gl/bNGcB5  pic.twitter.com/ZdGLYKSxTP    
    
    
    Recent Survey of Pre-Law Students Finds That Nearly 80% Want Legal Education to be More ... - http://goo.gl/8m8FVL  pic.twitter.com/lwU7dkrlvf    
    
    
    Facebook "Tagging" Adds a New Wrinkle to Social Media Discovery - http://goo.gl/i1Ha1s  pic.twitter.com/RtE9mKtLEF    
    
    
    Court Finds CAFA Ambiguous, but Clear, on Attorney Fees - http://goo.gl/qFmkEU  pic.twitter.com/868BvehXnF    
    
    
    Understanding the Scope of the Duty to Preserve - http://goo.gl/hgiBv8  pic.twitter.com/36z2Q4cVtK    
    
    
    New Research Tool - http://goo.gl/nGT3Nr  pic.twitter.com/mxpmhFdg9B    
    
    
    Another Reason for the Bad Job Market - http://goo.gl/sk7XqC  pic.twitter.com/0NmTKUajtI    
    
    
    Proposed Amendments to Federal Rules of Civil Procedure to be Published for Public Comment - http://goo.gl/wxEZID  pic.twitter.com/XWgdw5KrET    
    
    
    Supreme Court Closes Class Action Loophole - http://goo.gl/jjtlQd  pic.twitter.com/YLbB2cWNe9    
    
    
    Picture It Settled®'s Winning Presentation "Moneyball for Negotiation" Now Available ... - http://goo.gl/SNfGA4  pic.twitter.com/KJuymAjU18    
    
    
    FINRA Proposes E-Discovery Changes to its Discovery Guide for Customer Cases - http://goo.gl/wSyPCl  pic.twitter.com/fYhKQpV3A2    
    
    
    Video: Projecting the Negotiation Process - http://goo.gl/JEhVQt  pic.twitter.com/Cb93nlnIfp    
    
    
    5th Anniversary of Blogging and Net Neutrality Still Unclear - http://goo.gl/8ckwj7  pic.twitter.com/IBkCo49BK9    
    
    
    Legal sector adds 2,800 jobs in July - http://goo.gl/wIHYKj  pic.twitter.com/wKrV2LJv7x    
    
    
    Aligning Incentives By Requiring Plaintiff To Shoulder Part Of The Costs - http://goo.gl/Ocdsam  pic.twitter.com/2xkAulYtPe    
    
    
    Attorneys Suspended Nine Months for Influencing Client's Story - http://goo.gl/YZnlzt  pic.twitter.com/8m1KhipT8s    
    
    
    Some Thoughts About Plaintiffs' Due Diligence - http://goo.gl/mUufEQ  pic.twitter.com/Vs86QoVsbV    
    
    
    iPads Accounted for 84.3% of All Tablet-Based Traffic - http://goo.gl/aynYki  pic.twitter.com/F8y1SPzCpe    
    
    
    What Are the “Hottest” and “Coldest” Practice Areas? - http://goo.gl/9JmVcp  pic.twitter.com/rdnKgVulsz    
    
    
    Litigation Finance Brokers - http://goo.gl/Qtys8a  pic.twitter.com/cHKvqrox9c    
    
    
    How to Conduct a Paperless Trial - http://goo.gl/4NAkwL  pic.twitter.com/aLzpocGpDF    
    
    
    Preparing for Mediation in Texas - http://goo.gl/QsJuyL  pic.twitter.com/Qh0JeRQ091    
    
    
    Major US Bank Offers Online Legal Services in Business Hub - http://goo.gl/Oiwovp  pic.twitter.com/pp5dp04cHl    
    
    
    New ‘ROI Calculator’ Shows Savings from Predictive Coding in Cost and Hours - http://goo.gl/ulRCY7  pic.twitter.com/5UTnL08by9    
    
    
    Rumor: Apple's Next iPhone to Arrive Sept. 10 - http://goo.gl/CLo1QP  pic.twitter.com/7yV7DxtIXr    
    
    
    Quantum Computing, The Story of a Wild Idea - http://goo.gl/Pf9KPr  pic.twitter.com/PYVxcbdpkj    
    
    
    Twitter Looks for More #Influence in Washington - http://goo.gl/1V1BHx  pic.twitter.com/AN6NfzfXJi    
    
    
    Computer Simulation Says 49ers Most Likely To Win Super Bowl, Eagles 0.5% Chance - http://goo.gl/ZsnO3V  pic.twitter.com/Y0zHkKbCZE    
    
    
    Greenberg Ups First-Year Pay in 2 Offices to $145K from $125K; Will Competitors Follow Suit? - http://goo.gl/AkCrif  pic.twitter.com/uXPnWPyvj4    
    
    
    Judge Calls Law Profs’ 17-Year Divorce-Related Legal Battle ‘Frightening’ - http://goo.gl/X1Eyn7  pic.twitter.com/Ant6JnEmzk    
    
    
    Want to Lower the Divorce Rate? Try ‘Wedleases,’ Lawyer Says - http://goo.gl/eY8dRx  pic.twitter.com/6pv0FJc1AQ    
    
    
    87 U.S. Chief Judges Appeal to Congress for Funding Help - http://goo.gl/Viu0Oz  pic.twitter.com/VO7vzA4Wcb    
    
    
    Nate Silver and Malcolm Gladwell - http://goo.gl/s0Dc8H  pic.twitter.com/cIE84srBjn    
    
    
    How Nate Silver Won the Internet (and You Can Too) - http://goo.gl/fmJ7fn  pic.twitter.com/GHmToLaxd9    
    
    
    Judge Orders EEOC to Pay $4.7M in Legal Fees in Jenner & Block Case - http://goo.gl/FvMFKL  pic.twitter.com/8x7cTxyTSd    
    
    
    Lagstein v. Certain Underwriters at Lloyd's of London - http://goo.gl/Zdhsnr  pic.twitter.com/5PM7AP4SGm    
    
    
    The Dell Buyout: Michael Dell Weighs His BATNA - http://goo.gl/12wrH2  pic.twitter.com/PyBMTFCMSz    
    
    
    How Nate Silver Won the Internet (and You Can Too) - http://goo.gl/JyEq8Z  pic.twitter.com/Clm2GlGaV3    
    
    
    ALM Offers Digital Memberships - http://goo.gl/v434mo  pic.twitter.com/oQ1ZHcr7uT    
    
    
    Lawyer Agrees to Five-Year Suspension for Advising Client to Clean Up His Facebook Photos - http://goo.gl/tuydZW  pic.twitter.com/1yvXy5LXqT    
    
    
    Round-Up of Motions to Compel Involving Non-Signatories to Arbitration Agreements - http://goo.gl/xAySbc  pic.twitter.com/bIP5yQyf25    
    
    
    Avoiding the Slow March to the Middle - http://goo.gl/Lj5AUP  pic.twitter.com/aH6LcDxX6d    
    
    
    A Decision Support Tool for Selection of Dispute Resolution Strategy: Contractor's ... - http://goo.gl/cjTR4J  pic.twitter.com/2BbpDe0U1F    
    
    
    Divining the Future of Law & Legal Technology in Vegas - http://goo.gl/AZMcxx  pic.twitter.com/MmXpZjPVwe    
    
    
    BigLaw Growth Was ‘Anemic’ for First Half of 2013, Reports Wells Fargo (video) - http://goo.gl/xpKAKt  pic.twitter.com/VKFv6jcgx1    
    
    
    Best Lawyers in America® Names Don Philbin 2014 Mediation Lawyer of the Year - http://goo.gl/TXoKyP  pic.twitter.com/MYTZOUTNKK    
    
    
    NJ Court Says Mediation Agreements Must Be in Writing - http://goo.gl/mrRYHS  pic.twitter.com/w7vHufceqv    
    
    
    Conflict and Movements for Social Change: The Politics of Mediation and the Mediation ... - http://goo.gl/o161p7  pic.twitter.com/BU2PjV0OP3    
    
    
    Bill Banning Predispute Arbitration Clauses in Broker-Dealers’ Customer Agreements ... - http://goo.gl/TFQSLS  pic.twitter.com/0qetzbVTW5    
    
    
    Arbitrator's Decision to Preclude Party From Defending Against Claim as Sanction for ... - http://goo.gl/K4NDqM  pic.twitter.com/ruW1d5siev    
    
    
    The Next Frontier of Arbitration Litigation: Lessons From State Courts - http://goo.gl/P6Laa7  pic.twitter.com/UdZD7Yrrsc    
    
    
    A Summary of Recent Arbitration Confirmation Cases - http://goo.gl/Nsp3cy     
    
    
    Floating Questions for the Beach - http://goo.gl/W9ZcqL  pic.twitter.com/TX5aO9a48s    
    
    
    Why is Harmonization of Common Law and Civil Law Procedures Possible in Arbitration but ... - http://goo.gl/fAjbU6  pic.twitter.com/SzrLKZPWBV    
    
    
    Arbitration Awards Cannot Be Vacated Just Because Arbitrator Excluded Evidence - http://goo.gl/rfNwX2  pic.twitter.com/7nrOegSAsn    
    
    
    A Rose by Any Other Name - http://goo.gl/infjca  pic.twitter.com/HylaMxjm1V    
    
    
    Mediating by Skype! - http://goo.gl/bClQbd  pic.twitter.com/m7RneAuQsP    
    
    
    Creating And Perfecting Security Interests In A Claim: Part I, Purpose And Creation - http://goo.gl/eH0Z0D  pic.twitter.com/CrN6VL733D    
    
    
    App Of The Week: Rocket Matter Android App – Law Practice Management On The Go - http://goo.gl/4AHHw6  pic.twitter.com/lIDjaDWoIA    
    
    
    Surge of Brain Activity May Explain Near-Death Experience - http://goo.gl/vKplNV  pic.twitter.com/zFUnnTdOjp    
    
    
    IBM Scientists Show Blueprints for Brainlike Computing - http://goo.gl/mPd6KO  pic.twitter.com/VIh7uWNZD6    
    
    
    Emergence and Dynamism in International Organizations - http://goo.gl/2sXluH  pic.twitter.com/8kGVw9T0pB    
    
    
    Jordan Furlong on Why Lawyers Don't Innovate - http://goo.gl/e2t6Yz  pic.twitter.com/ZQxjEkOZtr    
    
    
    Arbitration Clauses That Avoid Arbitrability Disputes - http://goo.gl/pvmX7F  pic.twitter.com/v4VHC6eNB8    
    
    
    First State Court Decision Is Reversed Under SCOTUS’ Amex Ruling - http://goo.gl/wvsfbS  pic.twitter.com/yO3Cdl5FcE    
    
    
    New Jersey Halts Litigating Mediated Settlements - http://goo.gl/u11wMl  pic.twitter.com/3T5b2BJnCD    
    
    
    What's Better Than Pouting When You Don't Get A Raise? - http://goo.gl/qgphTy  pic.twitter.com/194MaruPdN    
    
    
    The “Ikea Effect” is Mediation - http://goo.gl/NcCRv7  pic.twitter.com/w5aUQiBEjY    
    
    
    @Hertz never received coupons or anything else    
    
    
    Houston’s First COA Upholds Arbitral Award Where Parties Signed Competing Agreements - http://goo.gl/xrP8Rt  pic.twitter.com/DODVwPfUs2    
    
    
    Has The Evaluative Label Outlived Its Usefulness? - http://goo.gl/ls4V6d  pic.twitter.com/ObRtgsRxEf    
    
    
    Loree on Oxford Health, Part II - http://goo.gl/5f0Asv  pic.twitter.com/cBs1yVPs3K    
    
    
    Federal Circuit: Secret Patent Trials are OK - http://goo.gl/n5vLkX  pic.twitter.com/DeeSwMEACr    
    
    
    Why You Cannot Be Replaced - http://goo.gl/BBdCEf  pic.twitter.com/oJCQqU3T8p    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Affirms Order Despite Alleged Arbitrator Misconduct - http://goo.gl/swSVJZ  pic.twitter.com/SgRvbXwHo3    
    
    
    Ramblings of a Neuro-Linguist: The Impact of Voice on Communication - http://goo.gl/SEvTcm  pic.twitter.com/uFfCnnzGGT    
    
    
    Oxford Health and Manifest Disregard, Part II.B - http://goo.gl/lRe4sp  pic.twitter.com/pAC8WxEjk4    
    
    
    Pricing Legal Claims Part I: The Valuation Challenge - http://goo.gl/xczpW5  pic.twitter.com/PP5eV5EdYD    
    
    
    Pricing Legal Claims Part II – Valuation Biases And Heuristics - http://goo.gl/7cB8jo  pic.twitter.com/vZAVIetEl0    
    
    
    The Federal Arbitration Act and Displacement of Agency Regulation - http://goo.gl/gBuib7  pic.twitter.com/G9DctRlTKz    
    
    
    Fretboard Logic: Learning From the Guitar How to Value Your Case - http://goo.gl/Quve8q  pic.twitter.com/zjr3ty7zoI    
    
    
    N.F.L. Agrees to Settle Concussion Suit for $765 Million - http://goo.gl/JDMJhL  pic.twitter.com/K7nQu8WOrO    
    
    
    Oxford Health and Manifest Disregard, Part II.C - http://goo.gl/ZasoXT  pic.twitter.com/k7McEU7gmO    
    
    
    Pricing Legal Claims III-Staged Funding And The Link To Options Analysis - http://goo.gl/1H2mzE  pic.twitter.com/Hh6clp7vZa    
    
    
    UK High Court Refuses Stay Despite Concurrent Texas Action - http://goo.gl/vmT6mu  pic.twitter.com/LImMC98QfC    
    
    
    Houston COA Holds Trial Court Inappropriately Modified Arbitrator’s Decision ... - http://goo.gl/OsWIWF  pic.twitter.com/lpCLO82bmR    
    
    
    Engineering Peace: Achieving the Promise of Mediation in the World’s Most Difficult ... - http://goo.gl/66LYgX  pic.twitter.com/kd2yvr3Ghw    
    
    
    Straus Institute for Dispute Resolution Launches Employment Mediation Clinic - http://goo.gl/ohHosa  pic.twitter.com/X2AOggfLty    
    
    
    Center for Law Practice Technology - http://goo.gl/sBH28e  pic.twitter.com/tAvex7WANm    
    
    
    Am Law Lawyers Help Bring Bitcoin to the Masses - http://goo.gl/PpPwhc  pic.twitter.com/oR07rti6E5    
    
    
    Colleges Set to Offer Exit Tests - http://goo.gl/9FNWb5  pic.twitter.com/PUITaHu9ru    
    
    
    Legal Education on Trial: Is the Third Year Necessary? - http://goo.gl/2rVKLx  pic.twitter.com/RgfrxM5FPe    
    
    
    GAO Adds Voice on Patent Litigation Problem - http://goo.gl/ZWMUN2  pic.twitter.com/o0OZiqEEsg    
    
    
    Bring in the FBI: Your Paranoia Is Justified - http://goo.gl/tQ0oDN  pic.twitter.com/AA4P0peDwV    
    
    
    A New Marital Estate in Divorce - http://goo.gl/Lfx8Ty  pic.twitter.com/UDFEmTH4Fe    
    
    
    Law Schools Gain Greater Autonomy - http://goo.gl/fSqwNx  pic.twitter.com/JdoMGWiWSv    
    
    
    Welcome to the Golden Age of Mobile - http://goo.gl/S8inPT  pic.twitter.com/jzxBVth2nv    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Asks Texas Supreme Court How Excess Net Settlement Proceeds Should Be ... - http://goo.gl/PpjdXF  pic.twitter.com/BBaVPdhVRR    
    
    
    Meet our 2013 Legal Rebels - http://goo.gl/rM8KNM  pic.twitter.com/zjX3sfI7F3    
    
    
    The Power of Mindfulness in the Practice of Law - http://goo.gl/hP7KlP  pic.twitter.com/8g6FTC4h1j    
    
    
    Law School Applications Drop Nearly 18 Percent, Benefiting Students Seeking Financial Aid - http://goo.gl/PC0ESF  pic.twitter.com/SbtBzMGbNk    
    
    
    Sweaty Palms and Racing Heart Can Help Negotiate Better While Making Deals - http://goo.gl/qc1YCN  pic.twitter.com/PSSqBpk5v0    
    
    
    Ohio Supreme Court Asked: Can Use of Forms Be Unauthorized Practice? - http://goo.gl/rHS7lz  pic.twitter.com/dwODhx9ypu    
    
    
    Court Approves Facebook Class Settlement, Shaves Attorney Fees - http://goo.gl/boQ5OW  pic.twitter.com/NaxBVmI8DZ    
    
    
    Negotiation Strategies for Corporations and Law Firms - http://goo.gl/taknUc  pic.twitter.com/EpfEaB84d5    
    
    
    Court Rejects Arbitrator Bias For Professional Interactions - http://goo.gl/QUJFLQ  pic.twitter.com/ej1yL43446    
    
    
    Eagle Ford-Related Lawsuits Are On The Rise - http://goo.gl/gXyA6c  pic.twitter.com/kgzxloCQNV    
    
    
    Law Departments Are Keeping E-Discovery Inside the Firewall - http://goo.gl/LBLOhT  pic.twitter.com/RMtlrrFYRh    
    
    
    Texas Chief Justice Wallace Jefferson to Resign Oct. 1 - http://goo.gl/6UgvvP  pic.twitter.com/IR2lAuobbz    
    
    
    Best Way To Boost Access To Justice? Change Ethics Rules, ‘13 Legal Rebel Renee Knake Says - http://goo.gl/4KLhMW  pic.twitter.com/9m8sHIEpua    
    
    
    Law Firms Can’t Describe ‘Specialties’ on LinkedIn, New York Ethics Opinion Says - http://goo.gl/wMcgaC  pic.twitter.com/E6juwIf3YO    
    
    
    Against Reinvention: More Forward Not Backward - http://goo.gl/UEmx9S  pic.twitter.com/64zDE598i3    
    
    
    Predictive Policing May Help Bag Burglars—But It May Also Be A Constitutional Problem - http://goo.gl/kx5wjj  pic.twitter.com/SuqI9KxK58    
    
    
    A&O's Morley On The Future of Legal Services: Reinvent or Disappear - http://goo.gl/vOZnTF  pic.twitter.com/HXCOQjfSK7    
    
    
    Tech Skills Are The Key To Law Students’ Future Employment, Says ‘13 Legal Rebel ... - http://goo.gl/2KoDmy  pic.twitter.com/WIGnJo4Ja9    
    
    
    New Details on ALM’s Digital Memberships - http://goo.gl/OmdFm6  pic.twitter.com/TsxMIpBHDf    
    
    
    Jury Size and the Hung-Jury Paradox - http://goo.gl/YMU89g  pic.twitter.com/ZWDrnE91dO    
    
    
    In Practice: What's Wrong With a Mediator's Proposal? - http://goo.gl/uWRC79  pic.twitter.com/S9XtbnTZCb    
    
    
    Does Information about Arbitrators’ Win/Loss Ratios Improve Their Accuracy? - http://goo.gl/KBRiYx  pic.twitter.com/Jwo8BwwnSj    
    
    
    Case-by-Case Adjudication and the Path of the Law - http://goo.gl/msZ4G6  pic.twitter.com/Ip7wDUyvMf    
    
    
    Professional Development for Far-Flung In-House Teams - http://goo.gl/n9CpA0  pic.twitter.com/QLR8jcgjkG    
    
    
    Lawyers' Talks With Law Firm GC May Be Shielded - http://goo.gl/LtYnKk  pic.twitter.com/owt075gjGe    
    
    
    Most Highly Regarded (301 Worldwide) Practitioners: Commercial Mediation 2013 - http://goo.gl/0UTfrH  pic.twitter.com/6ZQqIWB989    
    
    
    'Neural Dust,' Implanted In Brain, May Let Minds Meld With Machines - http://goo.gl/tgqrfh  pic.twitter.com/i5uSNqXc6N    
    
    
    A Fundamental Enforcement Cost Advantage of the Negligence Rule over Regulation - http://goo.gl/FdWwzB  pic.twitter.com/96MR1N7WwP    
    
    
    Are Lawyers From Top Schools a Lot Happier About Their Career Choice? Statistically the ... - http://goo.gl/anCc16  pic.twitter.com/Ca7PSF0LnR    
    
    
    Baker No Longer No. 1; Chairman Sees Flat Market for Legal Services - http://goo.gl/THRvZn  pic.twitter.com/zml7r0cy7h    
    
    
    Mass. Moves to Require Technology Competence for Lawyers - http://goo.gl/WZ1iR6  pic.twitter.com/gPWGqvvBlh    
    
    
    Martindale-Hubbell, Internet Brands to Deliver Marketing Services for Lawyers - http://goo.gl/bDzGQO  pic.twitter.com/Fynhwr4sfZ    
    
    
    For Paid Legal Research, WestlawNext is Most Popular, ABA Survey Says - http://goo.gl/QNbReJ  pic.twitter.com/FB0BLzXQbu    
    
    
    Law Schools Still ‘Inaccurate’ on Employment Numbers, Says Law Prof (video) - http://goo.gl/QZxneV  pic.twitter.com/uV1CN6xdF4    
    
    
    Rules for Enforcement of Spousal Maintenance, Contractual Alimony - http://goo.gl/xtvO0m  pic.twitter.com/vvP4gnit5p    
    
    
    Social Networking Abuse and Its Impact on Family Law Practice - http://goo.gl/uLPCzh  pic.twitter.com/mzzkqi3ZpZ    
    
    
    GCs Not Satisfied With Outside Counsel Rates - http://goo.gl/B6u9QQ  pic.twitter.com/MXdIRLMoPa    
    
    
    Comparing Firm Billing Rates by Practice, City, Size - http://goo.gl/bSVL1W  pic.twitter.com/zMei1glyCC    
    
    
    Legal Ethics Rules and the Federal Arbitration Act - http://goo.gl/Yl8C6l  pic.twitter.com/VrSk1zTgpn    
    
    
    Extraneous Factors in Judicial Decisions: What Did the Judge Have for Breakfast? - http://goo.gl/RCMgil  pic.twitter.com/DaMboeuVUt    
    
    
    Federal Court in Ohio Upholds Oral Settlement Agreement Reached in Mediation - http://goo.gl/XhCWRE  pic.twitter.com/PiHcoZjllt    
    
    
    How To Make Choosing Easier - http://goo.gl/Pi5JPW  pic.twitter.com/4zdusIJ1fI    
    
    
    Neuroscience Helps Explain Why Mediation Techniques Work - http://goo.gl/m8oZDc  pic.twitter.com/clOVToYvps    
    
    
    A Brief History of Cloud Computing - http://goo.gl/7TneI1  pic.twitter.com/61uxYMM0bb    
    
    
    Global Patent Map Reveals the Structure of Technological Progress - http://goo.gl/wQrc7d  pic.twitter.com/MFSgrhj394    
    
    
    Mediation and Settlement Confidentiality Provisions Waive Free Speech Protected by Anti-SLAPP Law - http://goo.gl/eROaTW     
    
    
    Understanding Overconfidence (video) - http://goo.gl/oN9qnf  pic.twitter.com/X5OirAx7aT    
    
    
    Steve Ballmer's Big Lesson for the Rest of Us: Innovation - http://goo.gl/uWrWmT  pic.twitter.com/2UiXkzNRoK    
    
    
    Market For New Lawyers Is Trying - http://goo.gl/AV84cX  pic.twitter.com/Yeb28tesLU    
    
    
    The Pessimistic Meta-Induction from the History of Science - http://goo.gl/inMcoc  pic.twitter.com/XoJaxcd3M4    
    
    
    Mediating in Good Faith - http://goo.gl/kD95Nf  pic.twitter.com/u8lqC1B2oN    
    
    
    Hospitals Prescribe Big Data to Track Doctors at Work - http://goo.gl/7JUF55  pic.twitter.com/2EfKRYPmbR    
    
    
    To Go from Big Data to Big Insight, Start with a Visual - http://goo.gl/7Xr8P1  pic.twitter.com/MGSCvkp7tI    
    
    
    10 Tips From Plaintiffs' Lawyers for Cutting Corporate Legal Costs - http://goo.gl/Dyj4Xo  pic.twitter.com/nQvBxQyZAr    
    
    
    How ‘Tomorrow’s Lawyers’ Are  Using Technology Now to Improve Outcomes - http://goo.gl/B8NGUg  pic.twitter.com/hG6nrdYc00    
    
    
    IBM's Cognitive Computing Software May Serve As Architecture For Brain-Like Computer - http://goo.gl/6cyR1n  pic.twitter.com/1eRK3Smhtl    
    
    
    The Trolley Problem - http://goo.gl/Pj4jgT  pic.twitter.com/BnVfFi1SAx    
    
    
    Bring in the Robots - http://goo.gl/aa031z  pic.twitter.com/SRa3KlSATc    
    
    
    Nexus Causality, Moral Warfare and Misattribution Arbitrage - http://goo.gl/vSQaOq  pic.twitter.com/TpFtSNDd7J    
    
    
    Preparation is the Key - http://goo.gl/I56oEp  pic.twitter.com/36RgNCX7yF    
    
    
    Regatta Teams Mediate Safety Recommendations - http://goo.gl/v89Yqc  pic.twitter.com/guYEZgDQga    
    
    
    Confirmation Bias - http://goo.gl/y2HP1l  pic.twitter.com/gKqhzZlvJw    
    
    
    Recoveries Can Turn Legal Departments Into Profit Centers - http://goo.gl/cCaIgm  pic.twitter.com/W6RwYORGQR    
    
    
    Texas ADR Calendar - http://goo.gl/x8K3mT  pic.twitter.com/G3Akppqjis    
    
    
    Study Shows Drop in Demand for Legal Services - http://goo.gl/w1a9aM  pic.twitter.com/aIkXex9OMn    
    
    
    Samsung Seeks 'iPod Moment' With Smartwatch Launch - http://goo.gl/dhnEkp  pic.twitter.com/Snds4GSsCa    
    
    
    Stop Saying Robots Are Destroying Jobs—They Aren’t - http://goo.gl/KWE9wm  pic.twitter.com/nmrMBiD1Aq    
    
    
    Meet DARPA's Humanoid Robot That Could Someday Save You From a Crumbling Building - http://goo.gl/K6s9J6  pic.twitter.com/XhlMrw5FTg    
    
    
    Why Are Clients Buying Less But Paying More? ALM’s Editor-in-Chief May Have The Answer ( ... - http://goo.gl/Rf7Ed0  pic.twitter.com/9yH9RRtpvs    
    
    
    Can I Bribe a Foreign Official? There's an App for That! - http://goo.gl/SN2hcM  pic.twitter.com/JjFTs6fAEp    
    
    
    When Smartphones Do a Doctor’s Job - http://goo.gl/UW9h2a  pic.twitter.com/XE0SiyDbGa    
    
    
    Judiciary Appeals to President Obama on Funding - http://goo.gl/pSeLsY  pic.twitter.com/ntFysHGc32    
    
    
    12 on 12: The Good, the Bad, the Ugly iPad 4 - http://goo.gl/poi1eM  pic.twitter.com/DWGe5OiOS3    
    
    
    How Facebook Makes Us Unhappy - http://goo.gl/Gn0c5p  pic.twitter.com/cGUsrIMrre    
    
    
    Massive, Free Online Classes Catch on With Law Schools - http://goo.gl/VqB8Re  pic.twitter.com/EFdLne00c4    
    
    
    Is a Receiver Bound to Arbitration Agreement if Suing on Behalf of Creditors? - http://goo.gl/bOZwYo  pic.twitter.com/yZTKGCHbxG    
    
    
    Companies Expect More Litigation, Less Spending in 2014 - http://goo.gl/hUULmk  pic.twitter.com/IQseTYk33x    
    
    
    Survey of Mediators About Mediation Participants' Preparedness - http://goo.gl/PK2KPW  pic.twitter.com/WWrrnKtKoY    
    
    
    Understanding Mediation Styles Is Important to the Field of Mediation - http://goo.gl/NTLm3r  pic.twitter.com/FVPUW96H5k    
    
    
    Facebook Messages Admissible under Traditional Evidence Rules - http://goo.gl/zsV3rq  pic.twitter.com/3f44CWfNCe    
    
    
    Why Clients Hire and Fire Law Firms - http://goo.gl/UQS86E  pic.twitter.com/DZnyli1OdF    
    
    
    How Nate Silver Brought Analytics to the Masses - http://goo.gl/oWqsLu  pic.twitter.com/BkHzJiP3Dk    
    
    
    Motion Practice in Arbitrations - http://goo.gl/RR489T  pic.twitter.com/6wf6FO2Pq1    
    
    
    Global Disputes of the Year - http://goo.gl/tP99OQ  pic.twitter.com/sQCrkOBOlR    
    
    
    ReInvent Law Lab Wins 2013 InnovAction Award - http://goo.gl/GX3exn  pic.twitter.com/JR345cUdJ0    
    
    
    The Adjunct Advantage - http://goo.gl/91oswR  pic.twitter.com/62r7EioNmd    
    
    
    Class-Action Waivers in Arbitration Agreements Are Enforceable - http://goo.gl/3IOc3q  pic.twitter.com/KTP9bQ4vfZ    
    
    
    2014 ABA Litigation Section Corporate Counsel CLE Seminar in Rancho Mirage - http://goo.gl/xUgh6w  pic.twitter.com/VnohWhoC9y    
    
    
    Six New Rules for Commercial Arbitration - http://goo.gl/u5fyDB  pic.twitter.com/MbqrMc9HNF    
    
    
    Second and Ninth Circuits Allow Employers To Preclude Collective FLSA Claims, Rejecting ... - http://goo.gl/8VFoJc  pic.twitter.com/Hy7oieEYEm    
    
    
    Caseload Increases Stress Need for New Federal Judgeships - http://goo.gl/cfm1S4  pic.twitter.com/eXxwdIImbn    
    
    
    Intern Class Actions on the Rise - http://goo.gl/M9h5OQ  pic.twitter.com/CtogirmoBV    
    
    
    Dallas COA Dismisses Arbitration Award for Lack of Jurisdiction - http://goo.gl/BhYSmV  pic.twitter.com/GW4vl1PRdV    
    
    
    New Jersey Supreme Court Enforces Oral Settlement Agreement, But Requires Signed ... - http://goo.gl/k4nad2  pic.twitter.com/AcQTjkQugP    
    
    
    Company Sues Its Ex-General Counsel for Attempting to Derail Lawsuit Settlement - http://goo.gl/r89opK  pic.twitter.com/QJF3McEq3P    
    
    
    Cert Sought in Montana Case Narrowly Crafting a Common Law Unconscionability / Adhesion ... - http://goo.gl/HR39VO  pic.twitter.com/ZjwqEFefNE    
    
    
    FINRA Arbitration Rules Prohibiting Class Waiver NOT Preempted - http://goo.gl/ERZXcC  pic.twitter.com/b5p4tSd8kL    
    
    
    Use of Mediation in Class Action Settlements Helpful for Court Approval - http://goo.gl/VJUqeu  pic.twitter.com/TUQBLfkKfM    
    
    
    Negotiation Strategies for Corporations and Law Firms - http://goo.gl/PImjQf  pic.twitter.com/WkWw29vK0L    
    
    
    The Court’s 2012 Class Act: A Little Bit of This, a Little Bit of That - http://goo.gl/7E66TN  pic.twitter.com/l6apPzDMBC    
    
    
    Smart Robots Can Now Work Right Next to Auto Workers - http://goo.gl/XccIPS  pic.twitter.com/oAy6Ihlu9V    
    
    
    Who Represents America's Biggest Companies 2013 - http://goo.gl/gGpC81  pic.twitter.com/ZOmcw2XJPQ    
    
    
    Google to Try to Solve Death, LOL - http://goo.gl/l3QzJ0  pic.twitter.com/VdW7ui8eL7    
    
    
    BlackBerry to Fire 4,500, Write Down Up to $960 Million - http://goo.gl/BCmHuO  pic.twitter.com/qfmuDm7lJs    
    
    
    Round-Up of Decisions on Motions to Compel Arbitration - http://goo.gl/V7VST2  pic.twitter.com/SgN3wvuG8w    
    
    
    Body Language and Negotiations, Men and Women - http://goo.gl/bxAfFj  pic.twitter.com/viWqDX16Ql    
    
    
    Finding Lawyers on Twitter: Two Directories Fall Out of Date But a Third is Very Cool - http://goo.gl/Xfdu7Z  pic.twitter.com/bkpRlUvss9    
    
    
    New and Burnished Apps: Labor & Employment, Stop & Frisk, Corruption - http://goo.gl/A9OZxN  pic.twitter.com/Tdukogp9sn    
    
    
    What Would the Obama-Backed 2-Year Law School Look Like? Dean Describes NYLS Program - http://goo.gl/Mozl3M  pic.twitter.com/DUYQjvphhC    
    
    
    To Cut Costs, Cut Associates’ Billable Hours Through Technology - http://goo.gl/3PgZeL  pic.twitter.com/EIukgl3AdN    
    
    
    2013 International Who’s Who of Commercial Mediation - http://goo.gl/61xq4h  pic.twitter.com/X0Ty1qzwWG    
    
    
    U.S. Chamber Commerce: San Antonio a Top ‘Enterprising City’ - http://goo.gl/u9BeFg  pic.twitter.com/oR6gQLWXTz    
    
    
    The Constitution? There’s a New App for That - http://goo.gl/nOgmjO  pic.twitter.com/pA9txeNarx    
    
    
    Why Silicon Valley’s Biggest Investors Are Betting on Alternative Legal Companies - http://goo.gl/rlz4h8  pic.twitter.com/9AwrMgSID6    
    
    
    Is a Receiver Bound to Arbitration Agreement if Suing on Behalf of Creditors? - http://goo.gl/50FlPo  pic.twitter.com/VGUnFUXErV    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Agrees to Hear Case Involving Arbitrator Disqualification - http://goo.gl/D1dyAj  pic.twitter.com/trdkXWhBR7    
    
    
    Detroit Bankruptcy Judge Appoints and Empowers Mediator Who Adds Additional Mediators - http://goo.gl/nyeqj3  pic.twitter.com/TeLOdM6Y76    
    
    
    Most Influential Emotions on Social Networks Revealed - http://goo.gl/gYeY5l  pic.twitter.com/DhgHEZj5IP    
    
    
    Mediation Misbehavior Not Protected - http://goo.gl/gh43gv  pic.twitter.com/qhq6jTiCeg    
    
    
    SD of Texas Compels Arbitration with Nonsignatory in Maritime Dispute - http://goo.gl/Tjfehx  pic.twitter.com/KwMsdUW49u    
    
    
    Appellate Court Remands for Determination of Whether There Was a Meeting of the Minds ... - http://goo.gl/yxC0lN  pic.twitter.com/B6AObN1nGR    
    
    
    Illusoriness Gains In Popularity As An Arbitration Buster - http://goo.gl/2M2P4B  pic.twitter.com/U9i5VgRxra    
    
    
    Judicial Conference of the United States Approves Additional Cost-Saving Measures - http://goo.gl/QVx3tO  pic.twitter.com/gUGCpAcvXc    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Declines to Review Arbitration Order in Natural Gas Case - http://goo.gl/2Ic7Hp  pic.twitter.com/XJdbI4NItP    
    
    
    Dallas COA Holds Arbitral Record Sufficient to Support Summary Judgment in Insurance Dispute - http://goo.gl/zbjdY8  pic.twitter.com/fPskxxf5nI    
    
    
    Use of Mediation Increasing in Technology Agreements and Disputes - http://goo.gl/DdNsJC  pic.twitter.com/gjjmEFb432    
    
    
    Round-Up Of Federal Decisions Involving Questions of Arbitrability - http://goo.gl/bwMRly  pic.twitter.com/Jh3Hpw6KKj    
    
    
    US Military Scientists Solve the Fundamental Problem of Viral Marketing - http://goo.gl/6koJJk  pic.twitter.com/YYuKfVIeuE    
    
    
    The Smartest Negotiators in the Room Warn Us Not to Make the 5 Top Business Bargaining ... - http://goo.gl/ir326h  pic.twitter.com/H7lM4EqPIu    
    
    
    Roundup of Motions to Compel Involving Non-Signatories to Arbitration Agreements - http://goo.gl/oq6inS  pic.twitter.com/JwY7F9zSWa    
    
    
    The Arbitrator’s Power of Suggestion - http://goo.gl/IiSUG8  pic.twitter.com/UHNVid7G2S    
    
    
    Dignity & Respect in Mediation - http://goo.gl/QgHqgP  pic.twitter.com/NxzAOySgwf    
    
    
    Can Congressional Gridlock Be Resolved Through Mediation? - http://goo.gl/2Ctfbd  pic.twitter.com/w3fp0ag4mz    
    
    
    Class Action Waiver Provisions Enforceable in Second Circuit Post-Amex - http://goo.gl/llK6Ab  pic.twitter.com/DH6ozKjo2g    
    
    
    A Cup Full of Coffee Makes the Argument Go Down… - http://goo.gl/iVLrQX  pic.twitter.com/5RdmBZZXdO    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Enforces Mediated Settlement By Mandamus - http://goo.gl/MTWXWR  pic.twitter.com/z3ZFqrKu2o    
    
    
    Engineering Peace: Achieving the Promise of Mediation in the World’s Most Difficult C ... - http://goo.gl/3EsANZ  pic.twitter.com/UOc0aRoS8Q    
    
    
    The Supreme Court's New Arbitrability Options - http://goo.gl/W5Y4fn  pic.twitter.com/kVui7MtKUn    
    
    
    Press on Court-Connected Mediation and Minorities - http://goo.gl/XSf5CF  pic.twitter.com/IWg0pk8nXq    
    
    
    iPhone 5s: How Secure Is the Touch ID? - http://goo.gl/I1Ai0J  pic.twitter.com/VY7k6hYxja    
    
    
    Technology That Learns - http://goo.gl/Tor8lc  pic.twitter.com/0B5pFcKYRQ    
    
    
    Not So Fast: A Google Fiber 1-Gigabit Mystery - http://goo.gl/MD3qcK  pic.twitter.com/sF3ENJjepr    
    
    
    Five Initiatives That Legal Education Needs - http://goo.gl/YNRWbq  pic.twitter.com/aYb18sHxAE    
    
    
    Straus Institute Co-Sponsors "Women in Hollywood: 100 Years of Negotiating the System" - http://goo.gl/H0eKwA  pic.twitter.com/v2k2QRS3UW    
    
    
    Ask the Marketers: How Vendors Can Avoid Rookie PR Mistakes - http://goo.gl/frMZqj  pic.twitter.com/Dhon8Clqwm    
    
    
    How Patent Lawyer Raj Abhyanker Developed a $8.5M Book of Business with Trademarkia - http://goo.gl/bEFoHB  pic.twitter.com/UOEeqQfgjj    
    
    
    Nate Silver Predicts That You, Too, Can Be A Data Master - http://goo.gl/XmPXgP  pic.twitter.com/pG0ClKIKyB    
    
    
    Swan Song: Robert Ambrogi's Finale - http://goo.gl/myDz13  pic.twitter.com/KKc8UhqWVx    
    
    
    TyMetrix MatterAnalyzer Helps Lawyers Set Billing Rates - http://goo.gl/JBVQpn  pic.twitter.com/G6nFaW5SVN    
    
    
    Conflict, Tension, Resolution - http://goo.gl/hR0dxn  pic.twitter.com/pXwviGTnPm    
    
    
    Northern District of Texas Compels Wrongful Death of Employee Case to - http://goo.gl/96gShO  pic.twitter.com/jC5iECywWi    
    
    
    How Shall We Prove Arbitral Corruption With “Abundant Clarity”? - http://goo.gl/3SnGTq  pic.twitter.com/OdEeBNL1nE    
    
    
    A Short History of New Zealand - http://goo.gl/WUyaHe  pic.twitter.com/9BYe81GkbV    
    
    
    MySpace Photos as Impeachment Evidence - http://goo.gl/cKUQFU  pic.twitter.com/5Q7y2RiGQ8    
    
    
    Denial of Arbitration of Stop-Loss Insurance Dispute Affirmed Under State Law - http://goo.gl/jan99O  pic.twitter.com/ThXfxQwou1    
    
    
    App Of The Week: HeinOnline – Law Journals And Other Legal Research Materials - http://goo.gl/IqH9DN  pic.twitter.com/P8kkcD58ZX    
    
    
    The Not-So-Effective Vindication Decision - http://goo.gl/7OouMY  pic.twitter.com/hcDKS1Hq8k    
    
    
    Pricing Legal Claims IV: Staged Funding Addresses The Nonmonotonic Trajectory Of Claim Value - http://goo.gl/G2qHwu  pic.twitter.com/qj2o9Yl4oC    
    
    
    E-Mediation Can Simplify E-Discovery Disputes - http://goo.gl/tjgva7  pic.twitter.com/9eG3JMsbHv    
    
    
    Juggling Apples: Proportionality & Estoppel - http://goo.gl/IZGYll  pic.twitter.com/goDqfU5ofF    
    
    
    How To Keep The Client Involved In A Mediation Decision - http://goo.gl/Q97mcA  pic.twitter.com/UY6usddZEQ    
    
    
    Court Rejects Defenses to Arbitration by Non-Signatory and Appoints Umpire - http://goo.gl/ig7YOo  pic.twitter.com/4U8aCURZiy    
    
    
    Perfecting Security Interests: Notice To The Attorney, And The Uniform Commercial Code, ... - http://goo.gl/PGpd95  pic.twitter.com/pVJAv5GFlb    
    
    
    Do Internet Terms of Service (ToS) Apply to Paper Contracts? - http://goo.gl/aeBi6w  pic.twitter.com/iMFZyKy5SA    
    
    
    Outside Funders of Lawsuits Take a Couple of Hard Knocks - http://goo.gl/eheaV4  pic.twitter.com/3sMeCve3YB    
    
    
    A Model Litigation Finance Contract - http://goo.gl/yi3MXZ  pic.twitter.com/7Mf4wwW3wX    
    
    
    Court Declines to Stay Litigation of Claims Despite Common Issues With Pending ... - http://goo.gl/XYgPm7  pic.twitter.com/mH8Gd7dKFe    
    
    
    Court Warns "Continuing Problems" with Document Production Will Result in Order to ... - http://goo.gl/5jSLKc  pic.twitter.com/HscuWNgq5a    
    
    
    Resolving IP Disputes: Calling for an Alternative Paradigm Symposium - http://goo.gl/gvjJKZ  pic.twitter.com/4zlr33ImKK    
    
    
    Proving the Negative in Discovery Productions - http://goo.gl/Bx1VKj  pic.twitter.com/XCph6H12z3    
    
    
    Perfecting Security Interests: Exceptions And Enforcement, Part 3 - http://goo.gl/KClkN8  pic.twitter.com/jotp1gii1f    
    
    
    Federal Courts Decide Arbitrator Appointment and Disqualification Issues - http://goo.gl/jFtFMx  pic.twitter.com/ZXCY5rnFks    
    
    
    The Impact of Local Patent Rules on Rate and Timing of Case Resolution Relative to ... - http://goo.gl/lx6B5N  pic.twitter.com/U8Vqqayc7S    
    
    
    Citing Proportionality, Court Concludes it would be "Senseless" to Require Plaintiff to ... - http://goo.gl/0CXtZ5  pic.twitter.com/j2mIGk4fpf    
    
    
    How Google Converted Language Translation Into a Problem of Vector Space Mathematics - http://goo.gl/D1tVWP  pic.twitter.com/SFsbPHArAZ    
    
    
    The Wow Factor: YouTube Helps Lawyers Create Infographics - http://goo.gl/s7xtft  pic.twitter.com/IP9epBzdJJ    
    
    
    Malcolm Gladwell on Why People Succeed - http://goo.gl/gRqkzt  pic.twitter.com/x8Lg130TEs    
    
    
    Malcolm Gladwell Interview - http://goo.gl/QMFkJS  pic.twitter.com/J1ktYcfqaO    
    
    
    5 Things To Know About Analytics in the World of Commerce - http://goo.gl/0ZZDX4  pic.twitter.com/rMKDk6fm63    
    
    
    How High Performers Compete – and Win – with Analytics #IKNS - http://goo.gl/kJEskd  pic.twitter.com/3WdAi7PZfm    
    
    
    Free Law Project To Promote Access to Law, For Free - http://goo.gl/7MzpJB  pic.twitter.com/ZSIKMTWlPS    
    
    
    Hummingbird Will Make Google Searches Hum - http://goo.gl/lnsbkU  pic.twitter.com/bMzwHNjPKE    
    
    
    My Experience with the iPhone 5s - http://goo.gl/ge2Ilc  pic.twitter.com/eQrkzLwtWe    
    
    
    LinkedIn (or Left Out) for Lawyers - http://goo.gl/ymyJNT  pic.twitter.com/QJXSDrF1el    
    
    
    @saairport 60 cars; 20 minutes; why no prepaid exit anymore? pic.twitter.com/AzOohtX12J    
    
    
    Law Firm Counts On Analytics For Profitability - http://goo.gl/2fY6qR  pic.twitter.com/JtO5xPT4ij    
    
    
    Survey Shows Law Departments on More Stable Footing - http://goo.gl/YgdhWm  pic.twitter.com/EP0d1khFps    
    
    
    Conference Session Recap: Mass Torts Settlement - http://goo.gl/q515TV  pic.twitter.com/GvM3LqqHjr    
    
    
    Mediated Settlement Agreements Trump Inquiries Into Best Interests of Child, Texas ... - http://goo.gl/ruXsQN  pic.twitter.com/N1VtYIzFt9    
    
    
    Wave of Patent Cases Hits the Bay Area - http://goo.gl/EqRoN1  pic.twitter.com/AbcEYsxWC6    
    
    
    Two Circuit Courts Demonstrate How Difficult It Is To Vacate Arbitration Awards - http://goo.gl/eLDiBQ  pic.twitter.com/Km1duSqxFO    
    
    
    Research Trends and Conclusions: Commercial Mediation 2013 - http://goo.gl/Xk1QPx  pic.twitter.com/7MK3FvxbXK    
    
    
    Disqualifying Post-Med-Arb-Med Conduct by Neutral Does Not Unwind Signed Settlement ... - http://goo.gl/mFZD3O  pic.twitter.com/nXHd99j7KQ    
    
    
    New Book: Erica Ariel Fox, Winning From Within - http://goo.gl/NhZ9Qb  pic.twitter.com/sAMFEu7aQY    
    
    
    So, You Want to Go In-House? - http://goo.gl/UzPlFC  pic.twitter.com/B1k1rPyfju    
    
    
    Schultz v. Medina Valley ISD: When Cultures and Beliefs Collide (Or How Air ... - http://goo.gl/O3VxyB  pic.twitter.com/yw8OzhMjFD    
    
    
    When First Amendment Rights Collide - http://goo.gl/z35Czj  pic.twitter.com/aIa2DH3s6y    
    
    
    D.R. Horton Hears It from the Ninth Circuit - http://goo.gl/ujf3zx  pic.twitter.com/ZNa6K3dwVA    
    
    
    Bloom’s Taxonomy of Educational Objectives - http://goo.gl/2g38CH  pic.twitter.com/6jbXK8pmIB    
    
    
    Algorithm Writes People’s Life Histories Using Twitter Stream - http://goo.gl/AKRpP5  pic.twitter.com/rKfuawY7W7    
    
    
    Your Skills: Preparing to Win at Arbitration - http://goo.gl/wqeumv  pic.twitter.com/tAQ5wW0Wae    
    
    
    Admissibility of Settlement-Related Evidence at Trial - http://goo.gl/CIrZic  pic.twitter.com/vpI8FOEf9H    
    
    
    'David and Goliath': Understanding the Dynamics in a Power Struggle - http://goo.gl/JGtqhf  pic.twitter.com/3OqYe4oWyk    
    
    
    Neuroplasticity and Education - http://goo.gl/Szjf1z  pic.twitter.com/t9KsJpQkix    
    
    
    Unsigned Conflict Waiver Letter Found Enforceable - http://goo.gl/wvuA9U  pic.twitter.com/hMmWVD0ifW    
    
    
    ACC Launches Online Contracts Portal - http://goo.gl/iF4nQn  pic.twitter.com/oXmb59dlaX    
    
    
    Sixth Circuit Vacates Award Due to Arbitrator’s Evident Partiality - http://goo.gl/ycoHfD  pic.twitter.com/EYuGKB9K8m    
    
    
    Handling Your First (or Next) Arbitration 2013  - http://goo.gl/qkXd2g  pic.twitter.com/d6FpJr5FpS    
    
    
    The Lesson of Wharton Business School - http://goo.gl/39LHG4  pic.twitter.com/IwYiygJmt8    
    
    
    KPMG EDD Tool Redacts Privileged Data From Spreadsheets - http://goo.gl/coaOqO  pic.twitter.com/k4SQRA3KES    
    
    
    Projecting Without a Projector: Sharing Your Smartphone Content Onto An Arbitrary Display - http://goo.gl/QKjrw8  pic.twitter.com/8mWp67HXUw    
    
    
    @MissAnastasia4 was fantastic at TEDx San Antonio    
    
    
    @ericfletcher excellent talk    
    
    
    http://Law.com  Launches iOS App; Readies New Contributor Network - http://goo.gl/38YlHk  pic.twitter.com/FqnAFSEBzq    
    
    
    Mobile SCOTUSblog Gets Better - http://goo.gl/hLzJon  pic.twitter.com/IU0DDgy5C0    
    
    
    Linklaters Changes Document Comparison Software to DocsCorp - http://goo.gl/252H9U  pic.twitter.com/7JPBTnDcpz    
    
    
    Thomson Reuters: Editorial Layoffs and a New Chief Transformation Officer - http://goo.gl/Z8feBo  pic.twitter.com/LhvpQ7vOkV    
    
    
    AIG Overhauls Global Legal Operations - http://goo.gl/7GFnnV  pic.twitter.com/bNADEx0T1T    
    
    
    Four Discovery Management Models for Corporate Counsel (Part 1) - http://goo.gl/L9P45H  pic.twitter.com/YzBkjsbPMs    
    
    
    Four Discovery Management Models for Corporate Counsel (Part 2) - http://goo.gl/OAdwuZ  pic.twitter.com/gff6koj65z    
    
    
    Google is Joining the Open edX Platform - http://goo.gl/iH1Zxs  pic.twitter.com/Deh6unRqyx    
    
    
    How Not to Mediate - http://goo.gl/P3c8l5  pic.twitter.com/GOYQ4yZYaI    
    
    
    Two U.S. Supreme Court Opinions Enforce Arbitration Agreements - http://goo.gl/TPGk9X  pic.twitter.com/51AB4uSvGv    
    
    
    The Argument As A Persuasive Tool In Negotiation - http://goo.gl/lsrd6M  pic.twitter.com/dJUkF0xoVK    
    
    
    Law Firm Associates' Social Media Use Up, but Uneven - http://goo.gl/g8WZsR  pic.twitter.com/cRHaLWn53i    
    
    
    NSA Collects Millions of E-mail Address Books Globally - http://goo.gl/V6UGXX  pic.twitter.com/ank7siaTHY    
    
    
    The Role of the Internet in the Conduct of Litigation - http://goo.gl/jqLX0B  pic.twitter.com/wogkyM0I7d    
    
    
    Developing Strategies for Asking Questions in Negotiation - http://goo.gl/HvLr2C  pic.twitter.com/R6RV4rBYYc    
    
    
    US Supreme Court Denies Certiorari in Two Arbitration-related Cases - http://goo.gl/lIU1Kr  pic.twitter.com/mf1a2lEeKF    
    
    
        
    
    
    Planned Early Dispute Resolution Resources - http://goo.gl/O70YeB  pic.twitter.com/x2ZPxTMYSH    
    
    
    Rules Update: Improved AAA Commercial Rules; NAF Rules Not An Obstacle To Enforcing ... - http://goo.gl/WjszmN  pic.twitter.com/sdmb8RwOXN    
    
    
    Corpus Christi COA Affirms Temporary Injunction Pending Arbitration - http://goo.gl/DLuQOd  pic.twitter.com/n0W79jEIjU    
    
    
    Spreading ADR Best Practices Around the World - http://goo.gl/SZH5uX  pic.twitter.com/vdv1iwqiCY    
    
    
    Arkansas Court Orders Arbitration in LegalZoom Case - http://goo.gl/t4sEqe  pic.twitter.com/XJIyWpW1WX    
    
    
        
    
    
    SCOTUS Set To Hear At Least One Arbitration Case This Term - http://goo.gl/IT4s2n  pic.twitter.com/uhSj6hh046    
    
    
    Online Dispute Resolution (ODR): What is it, and is it the Way Forward? - http://goo.gl/Cmf3KT  pic.twitter.com/XJqZnsN3uA    
    
    
    Illinois Supreme Court Increases Reporting Requirements for Family Mediation - http://goo.gl/I4HQBY  pic.twitter.com/EjnHay3mlP    
    
    
    IBM Researcher Can Decipher Your Personality From Looking at 200 of Your Tweets - http://goo.gl/fsXqtx  pic.twitter.com/uyiie8XKzl    
    
    
    Arbitrators Rule in Favor of Chevron in Ecuador Oil Pollution - http://goo.gl/FoPJKv  pic.twitter.com/hQB8GQ4eSI    
    
    
    ND Texas Compels Would-Be FLSA Class Action to Arbitration - http://goo.gl/KOyYcp  pic.twitter.com/hHeAz1hSLF    
    
    
    The Soft Touch: The Village Elder - http://goo.gl/KdYgIe  pic.twitter.com/oRpolm51Lq    
    
    
    Body Language, Negotiation & Haggling - http://goo.gl/SsrFpk  pic.twitter.com/maUzf7XPx6    
    
    
    Open Records: A Look at Attorney General Greg Abbott's Tenure - http://goo.gl/h6NXlS  pic.twitter.com/6kQ2fm5ycB    
    
    
    Rebirth of IT - http://goo.gl/QTQrTx  pic.twitter.com/I8TxHeKMUU    
    
    
    Opening up Course Builder Data - http://goo.gl/9F1Bkx  pic.twitter.com/hGHMzd60E6    
    
    
    Is Your Salary Fair? Calculator Will Help Lawyers Decide - http://goo.gl/iqAQhx  pic.twitter.com/MTaFUN22Xy    
    
    
    Creating YouTube Channels to Promote Your Legal Organization - http://goo.gl/iDnhmL  pic.twitter.com/Bhu09jdNyu    
    
    
    What Do kCura and Stanford Law Have in Common? Great YouTube Channels - http://goo.gl/VN9GCd  pic.twitter.com/m9dYidqOdA    
    
    
    What Was the Greatest Speech Ever Given? - http://goo.gl/1BfsJ5  pic.twitter.com/MBtN9fz7g5    
    
    
    5 Things To Know About Cognitive Systems - http://goo.gl/sBaE3l  pic.twitter.com/MIKgBXDezN    
    
    
    New Blog Airs Law Schools' Laundry - http://goo.gl/yp6RPo  pic.twitter.com/HRVEVXSI6e    
    
    
    Are We All Virtual Lawyers Now? - http://goo.gl/4ATzBc  pic.twitter.com/n3f6z3LZjy    
    
    
    New iPads to be Revealed on Oct. 22 - http://goo.gl/vKtr1k  pic.twitter.com/eVYhK7w0TC    
    
    
    Backward, Forward Book Review: Richard Susskind, Soothsayer - http://goo.gl/JCNnXv  pic.twitter.com/YvnDnK5DDM    
    
    
    Heads Up! Here Comes Google Glass - http://goo.gl/NQXMpR  pic.twitter.com/FXiSVKViZs    
    
    
    Chevron Ecuador Lawsuit Financier Tells Judge of Regrets - http://goo.gl/aJq81o  pic.twitter.com/Qiz56WGzLF    
    
    
    Visualizing Big Data in Milliseconds on Cheap Computers - http://goo.gl/gL0Avp  pic.twitter.com/0RqYRKPktE    
    
    
    Is it Time for Human Analytics in Document Review? - http://goo.gl/TjqYtR  pic.twitter.com/G2RCaftEyW    
    
    
    How to Manage the Costs of NPE Patent Lawsuits - http://goo.gl/NtZE3r  pic.twitter.com/pVuyte9s5H    
    
    
    Smartphone Kill Switch Campaign Gathers Momentum - http://goo.gl/CJ2D6r  pic.twitter.com/SSLCvFtR7w    
    
    
    In 5-2 Ruling, Justices Cut Path Through 'Concepcion' - http://goo.gl/Jj2rlQ  pic.twitter.com/biSp4Hzndd    
    
    
    Law Departments Trading Large Firms for 'Large Enough' - http://goo.gl/T2hwnp  pic.twitter.com/oOLfzmVaT9    
    
    
    In Practice: Bespoke Arbitration - http://goo.gl/lPu40m  pic.twitter.com/fZLT38vhUI    
    
    
    SEC Introduces, Unanimously Approves Crowdfunding Proposals - http://goo.gl/qCgQwa  pic.twitter.com/eLHvM3suSN    
    
    
    In-House Legal Departments Turning Into Mini-Firms? - http://goo.gl/7KzyDr  pic.twitter.com/OKD6M39hYP    
    
    
    Appeals Court Throws Out Confidential Arbitration in Delaware - http://goo.gl/Xi81La  pic.twitter.com/eLWf3ssbM7    
    
    
    A GC and a Litigation Counsel's Fireside Chat - http://goo.gl/1KTx5s  pic.twitter.com/pR9VIKYCeV    
    
    
    Wage-and-Hour Litigation on the Rise - http://goo.gl/9sB55z  pic.twitter.com/UVxO4D0m9P    
    
    
    Crowdsourcing Legal Information: Fad or Change Agent? - http://goo.gl/BlptYd  pic.twitter.com/s3Pnh88N6r    
    
    
    New San Francisco Forum Promotes E-Discovery Mediation - http://goo.gl/AeBFEo  pic.twitter.com/IrKOTQN2do    
    
    
    The Pros and Cons of ADR Clauses - http://goo.gl/Ph075G  pic.twitter.com/az4fYtF7mQ    
    
    
    Big Data: Big Deal or Big Win? - http://goo.gl/SOojB1  pic.twitter.com/8CDlehr0Mj    
    
    
    Bankruptcy Filings Drop 12 Percent in Fiscal Year 2013 - http://goo.gl/sS4Grz  pic.twitter.com/ZwLD3FoPu1    
    
    
    Why Lawyers Will Love the iPad Air and the iPad Mini with Retina Display - http://goo.gl/5Btr5i  pic.twitter.com/mWKpwijfW2    
    
    
    Do You Want to Be Facebook Friends or Do You Want to Serve Me? - http://goo.gl/3uPvHX  pic.twitter.com/wfgPmSUEsE    
    
    
    Experimental Law Review Note Uses Twitter As Its Research Source - http://goo.gl/a2h3Eo  pic.twitter.com/jhmzcUYqvG    
    
    
        
    
    
    Nate Silver: How To Make Better Predictions - http://goo.gl/8G3DGY  pic.twitter.com/0VnhXoXrq9    
    
    
    LinkedIn Drives More Traffic to Law Firm Websites Than All Other Social Media Combined - http://goo.gl/pBCymS  pic.twitter.com/bteIB4usJT    
    
    
    Moto X -- Motorola Assist - http://goo.gl/ZvGtPp  pic.twitter.com/tvpzmVDvKH    
    
    
    Google Glass In The Concert Hall? Cornell Prof Looks To Make Beautiful Music With ... - http://goo.gl/GZectt  pic.twitter.com/mY8nDAYVSS    
    
    
    LexisNexis and Internet Brands Eliminate 205 http://Lawyers.com  Jobs - http://goo.gl/0PJU47  pic.twitter.com/d0bwe7DMXx    
    
    
    Data Shows Google’s Robot Cars Are Smoother, Safer Drivers Than You or I - http://goo.gl/sW4MsC  pic.twitter.com/WBBWj1nx2D    
    
    
    America’s Mood Map: An Interactive Guide to the United States of Attitude - http://goo.gl/WmQYRz  pic.twitter.com/N8xZPCwi0m    
    
    
    The Receding Tide of Medical Malpractice Litigation: Part 1—National Trends - http://goo.gl/YdoXXW  pic.twitter.com/2yMpBFWuX4    
    
    
    The Receding Tide of Medical Malpractice Litigation: Part 2—Effect of Damage Caps - http://goo.gl/4hXfKb  pic.twitter.com/NPn7eVZlEd    
    
    
    The Effect of Legal Expert Commentary on Lay Judgments of Judicial Decision Making - http://goo.gl/Pi7b2p  pic.twitter.com/OMiNUrVYJi    
    
    
    Judicial Ideology and the Selection of Disputes for U.S. Supreme Court Adjudication - http://goo.gl/56Vufg  pic.twitter.com/JbAbk4ODox    
    
    
    Law Departments Taking Matters Into Their Own Hands - http://goo.gl/DGVhW7  pic.twitter.com/m3toXKOkdP    
    
    
    Flexible Processing and Classiﬁcation for eDiscovery - http://goo.gl/6udC3d  pic.twitter.com/j3UO09IASa    
    
    
    Comparison of International Arbitration Rules - http://goo.gl/CZCdp4  pic.twitter.com/3Xb6UsRPiE    
    
    
    Arbitration for the Trial Lawyer - http://goo.gl/BYMaLY  pic.twitter.com/02rOCKc03A    
    
    
    Two New US Ninth Circuit Court of Appeals Arbitration Decisions - http://goo.gl/E7hc8A  pic.twitter.com/mayeNYfrYx    
    
    
    Big Data’s Just a Lot of Noise…Unless You Can Visualize It Panelists Say - http://goo.gl/J56Vsk  pic.twitter.com/G0iQxHRRxK    
    
    
    Courts Stopping Non-Signatories From Compelling Arbitration Through Equitable Estoppel - http://goo.gl/wHJ4jR  pic.twitter.com/KRPgTv8nuT    
    
    
    Rethinking Civil Litigation in Federal District Court - http://goo.gl/3Uzwic  pic.twitter.com/7wAd8YbVeY    
    
    
    Attorneys and Negotiation Ethics: A Material Misunderstanding? - http://goo.gl/MAVycF  pic.twitter.com/yQ8qWQEIIl    
    
    
    Forget Dated Ideas About Left and Right Hemispheres - http://goo.gl/A6PrBB  pic.twitter.com/M6J1azCDxC    
    
    
    Baby Boom: For Second Year in a Row, Large Firms Continue to Bring In More Baby Lawyers - http://goo.gl/h1bPXu  pic.twitter.com/xVuquzpLFh    
    
    
    Public Courts as Private Arbitration Panels - http://goo.gl/w9O1tx  pic.twitter.com/mRIi5akQxR    
    
    
    Contrasting U.S. Litigation and International Arbitration - http://goo.gl/0frKPM  pic.twitter.com/ISNsacPZIi    
    
    
    October 2013 Supreme Court Term Begins - http://goo.gl/zWoUEO  pic.twitter.com/9U0k7iEHtg    
    
    
    The Importance of Culture in Conflict Resolution - http://goo.gl/RG2d5F  pic.twitter.com/P4Cn8o95Jo    
    
    
    In-House Counsel Get Real About Outside Firm Value - http://goo.gl/75JYyo  pic.twitter.com/KxwI2UtE0f    
    
    
    Mediation 101 – Three Essential Concepts - http://goo.gl/YcGQ4O  pic.twitter.com/0NtBRnSsjb    
    
    
    Who Is the Client in the Closely Held Corporation? - http://goo.gl/f52ZVA  pic.twitter.com/pqWdgKc3IZ    
    
    
    FINRA Considering Whether Firms Should be Required to Carry Insurance to Pay ... - http://goo.gl/A1GCYF  pic.twitter.com/ja7GO988nt    
    
    
    In re Lee Part 1: A Child’s Best Interest Comes Second to Mediation Finality - http://goo.gl/rac1nK  pic.twitter.com/l6GCZ76ztP    
    
    
    Technology That Learns - http://goo.gl/OdVg0i  pic.twitter.com/SXX7GO6zHH    
    
    
    At Supreme Court, Tradition Trumps Technology, and Transparency - http://goo.gl/EkusyU  pic.twitter.com/y3PALiKZDc    
    
    
    Google Nears Smartwatch Launch - http://goo.gl/kKoQSW  pic.twitter.com/qTPxkCnUNk    
    
    
    New Wolfram Problem Generator: Practice and Learn - http://goo.gl/SQrLDC  pic.twitter.com/3Cdv0pdiMm    
    
    
    Your Mind Needs a Vacation even if Your Body Doesn’t - http://goo.gl/6P4upM  pic.twitter.com/1DTiv77ovd    
    
    
    Is Law Review Experience Valuable for Helping Law Students Prepare for Practice? - http://goo.gl/ZyxHXa  pic.twitter.com/AvzYcOwCLP    
    
    
    Thomson Reuters Announces 3,000 Layoffs - http://goo.gl/mKTVT7  pic.twitter.com/JhqMHFKzXw    
    
    
    The Smart Money Was Never on Goliath: Does BigLaw Have His Same Disadvantages? - http://goo.gl/UbbYyf  pic.twitter.com/Z1Ofwk82Vn    
    
    
    Law Firm Sued Over Claimed Use of Competitor’s Name as Google AdWords - http://goo.gl/dT0slI  pic.twitter.com/aYOrN3WC0t    
    
    
    Farewell iPhone, Hello Android - http://goo.gl/01xs2v  pic.twitter.com/P1qlGik0x5    
    
    
    CourtListener Adds 1.5 Million Opinions, Expands Coverage - http://goo.gl/atxbuP  pic.twitter.com/xFzuI3xqHf    
    
    
    “The Pros and Cons of ADR Clauses” - http://goo.gl/1hYDLy  pic.twitter.com/Gc4V4EeE6v    
    
    
    Small Business B-2-B Arbitration Part II.B: How Arbitration Agreements Work - http://goo.gl/RVKg9J  pic.twitter.com/V6YudWAZ32    
    
    
    Patent Wars Erupt Again in Tech Sector - http://goo.gl/frjZAj  pic.twitter.com/cZr2CSIMC0    
    
    
    Texas' Fourth Court of Appeals Orders Local Firefighters to Arbitrate Benefits Dispute ... - http://goo.gl/EcF3uz  pic.twitter.com/cHzOdbUEMI    
    
    
    Lying and Mediation - http://goo.gl/V1mViG  pic.twitter.com/FixMRUu7Nh    
    
    
    Employment Update: What You Need to Know About Telecommuting and Unpaid Interns - http://goo.gl/2vZI5h  pic.twitter.com/ByBbTK3zM7    
    
    
    What to Do When Negotiation Turns to Squabbling - http://goo.gl/0rgnKR  pic.twitter.com/vUqFFElEON    
    
    
    Protecting Arbitral Jurisdiction of The Merits With a Foreign Anti-suit Injunction - http://goo.gl/VyMPxJ  pic.twitter.com/pEkygAwmm7    
    
    
    ABA’s Planned Early Dispute Resolution Task Force Publishes User Guide - http://goo.gl/EQRKSC  pic.twitter.com/40dLStxMvD    
    
    
    Depersonalizing the Difficult Person, A Good Strategy - http://goo.gl/AZkacK  pic.twitter.com/17BwdSqWpN    
    
    
    Waiting for the Texas Supreme Court to Define (or Reject) Minority Shareholder Oppression - http://goo.gl/WGIQiW  pic.twitter.com/5aIIu7Rm9U    
    
    
    CPR Adds Another Major Feature To Its Toolbox - http://goo.gl/PVXHAk  pic.twitter.com/O4oRlujJ7H    
    
    
    By the Way, You Just Disarmed a Difficult Person - http://goo.gl/wUw3Sf  pic.twitter.com/elrfB0iKk3    
    
    
    Sanctions in US and International Arbitrations: Old Law In Modern Context - http://goo.gl/m9TVtW  pic.twitter.com/HNdUIdezSO    
    
    
    Tippett on Mediation a la Carte - http://goo.gl/1vUiJR  pic.twitter.com/UlpK8ublGk    
    
    
    Venue is Proper in the County Where Arbitration is Held Despite Arbitration Agreement ... - http://goo.gl/DatJKI  pic.twitter.com/IemgvNE2fn    
    
    
    Neuroscientists Develop Equation for Predicting Future Disasters - http://goo.gl/El5SnL  pic.twitter.com/JA6NTCpGYo    
    
    
    Beware 'Misclassification Creep' in Employee Exemption - http://goo.gl/LNUrTu  pic.twitter.com/kgbRbgKQFW    
    
    
    Efficiency Is the New Legal Pedigree - http://goo.gl/lVeU4Y  pic.twitter.com/yZRjNHevM0    
    
    
    Preparing for "LIVE WEBINAR: Picture it Settled - Product Demo" on ADRhub Werner Institute: http://ning.it/1guvMiz     
    
    
    Friday in CyberWeek 2013: Moneyball for Negotiation: Predicting Future Behavior – A ... - http://goo.gl/2FKKqC  pic.twitter.com/JNx0E0pDXJ    
    
    
    Alternative Dispute Resolution Gets an Online Network - http://goo.gl/5mwEJ2  pic.twitter.com/P4ekbiL7vj    
    
    
    Send Lawyers, Rigs and Money: The Opening of the Mexican Energy Industry - http://goo.gl/hnthh1  pic.twitter.com/Gzr70q84DZ    
    
    
    CyberWeek 2013: Innovations in Online Dispute Resolution - http://goo.gl/xLbK4w  pic.twitter.com/wXY3fgaTGT    
    
    
    Smartsettle:Debt Resolution with Smartsettle One - http://goo.gl/lBwOpf  pic.twitter.com/g0LP0ZdByl    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Kariboyle @colmbrannigan No but in commercial cases most terms can be valued and the parties want to get the best deal while still settling    
    
    
    Artificial Intelligence and ODR - http://goo.gl/AyBVlH  pic.twitter.com/mGsWTat0An    
    
    
    Deans: Cornell Tech is Redefining Tech Education - http://goo.gl/uusdeP  pic.twitter.com/gFlFL3ange    
    
    
    Gamification: Coming Soon to Training, Document Review Near You - http://goo.gl/8zguG5  pic.twitter.com/rBftUPsnfQ    
    
    
        
    
    
    Big Data and Pharmacovigilance: Using Health Information Exchanges to Revolutionize ... - http://goo.gl/0cs8Y9  pic.twitter.com/57tY2H6lTy    
    
    
    Robotic Cars: Road Hazard or Help? - http://goo.gl/FhEq3B  pic.twitter.com/McGox1AbXI    
    
    
    Plaintiffs Lawyers Form New Group, Disavow Competition With TTLA - http://goo.gl/KiErSL  pic.twitter.com/85MXryp7BD    
    
    
    New York Gets Specialist Judge for International Arbitration Matters - http://goo.gl/pVeHUr  pic.twitter.com/ZapV9WTWzp    
    
    
    Lex Machina’s “Law Machine” - http://goo.gl/GPrsEd  pic.twitter.com/MEjGDaoJrM    
    
    
    A Brave New Technological World in the Texas Bar Journal - http://goo.gl/m2ePyh  pic.twitter.com/bSUCHuHjAP    
    
    
    CyberWeek 2013 Presentation: Moneyball for Negotiation: Predicting Future Behavior – A ... - http://goo.gl/PI1XrJ  pic.twitter.com/mv4E4BDQmn    
    
    
    LSAT Test-Takers Continue to Decline; October Number is Lowest Since 1998 - http://goo.gl/GYbwiA  pic.twitter.com/R6EyxofNmQ    
    
    
    Lex Machina Introduces Legal Analytics to Power Data-Driven IP Business Strategy - http://goo.gl/SQkvkv  pic.twitter.com/1H64ndJtzt    
    
    
    Are You Upset or Angry? - http://goo.gl/BhBQpC  pic.twitter.com/UJNaJ8RfXI    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Applies 'Golden Rule' in Assessing Fee Award - http://goo.gl/saqzHP  pic.twitter.com/DhyIQydwQj    
    
    
    Former Chief Justice Wallace Jefferson Being Honored as ‘Texan of the Year’ - http://goo.gl/dj8J5a  pic.twitter.com/3OXmzyNGQt    
    
    
    Personal Jurisdiction in the Fifth Circuit’s Commercial Opinions: 2012-13 - http://goo.gl/cgjjmb  pic.twitter.com/9Pg7Xib9cH    
    
    
    Sixth Circuit Rejects Class Arbitration Claims Against LexisNexis - http://goo.gl/uLmf9C  pic.twitter.com/D5ugig8X9Z    
    
    
    Patent Litigation Gets a Boost from Legal Analytics - http://goo.gl/l6mcxb  pic.twitter.com/xNU00KCdAe    
    
    
    Lawyering in the Shadow of Data - http://goo.gl/O4xUxj  pic.twitter.com/pzWNJW3ukA    
    
    
    LinkedIn Post Likely Didn't Violate Noncompete Clause - http://goo.gl/jqhW5d  pic.twitter.com/0TtEVCYBev    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Securities Update - http://goo.gl/AU5hBw  pic.twitter.com/Ym2g311VIn    
    
    
    Skadden, Yetter Coleman Face Off Over Arbitration Vacatur - http://goo.gl/Tb9feS  pic.twitter.com/oBwRrGglGE    
    
    
    When Imperfect is Good Enough - http://goo.gl/L5q4wT  pic.twitter.com/wrNCZCXV1G    
    
    
    New Optional Rules Created for Appellate Arbitration - http://goo.gl/u8Q6SZ  pic.twitter.com/gH7SjvteIl    
    
    
    Vulnerability, A Defense Against Difficult People - http://goo.gl/HChFw5  pic.twitter.com/RZidFf6YWJ    
    
    
    Ex-PTO GC Bernard Knight on the Future of Patent Law - http://goo.gl/B1Z2B4  pic.twitter.com/vgM6Yjx3X1    
    
    
    National Labor Relations Board Increases Its Focus on Issues Impacting Nonunionized ... - http://goo.gl/TBhZEk  pic.twitter.com/BgfMFadzjw    
    
    
    Class Certification's Predominance Standard Alive and Well in the Sixth Circuit - http://goo.gl/fmwPlf  pic.twitter.com/TOKOl3Hj9I    
    
    
    Employment Litigation in the Age of Social Media - http://goo.gl/ab4pHX  pic.twitter.com/l9tmqxLzhN    
    
    
    A Q&A with the General Counsel for Southwest Airlines - http://goo.gl/xF5Dsh  pic.twitter.com/oN7pE77q2R    
    
    
    Posner: Lawyers Bad At Math Are An Increasing Concern - http://goo.gl/ouPDwc  pic.twitter.com/M28ha1YbKy    
    
    
    2014 ABA Corporate Counsel CLE Seminar - http://goo.gl/2SkKpM  pic.twitter.com/NfTNrGngPY    
    
    
    Employer Violates Labor Laws by Failing to Pay Interns - http://goo.gl/4nJfU3  pic.twitter.com/zPvqHbHO57    
    
    
    Mozart: a Good Patent Litigator; Beethoven: a Mean One - http://goo.gl/tF26Wj  pic.twitter.com/NJgoHl2MaZ    
    
    
    My First Portable Computer In Law School - http://goo.gl/I5OXjn  pic.twitter.com/LkiZ6fshdl    
    
    
    Small Firm Lawyers and Innovation - http://goo.gl/BkAkvb  pic.twitter.com/YFrBUBr0LO    
    
    
    iPhone Users Get Some Google Now Love - http://goo.gl/bHWpgx  pic.twitter.com/zF1eNZH0Ij    
    
    
    First iPad Air Reviews are Posted - http://goo.gl/Yh1Czd  pic.twitter.com/Pv75BwpD05    
    
    
    Half of All Law Firm Mergers Fail - http://goo.gl/Fsaf8w  pic.twitter.com/3qkrOQl7p1    
    
    
    New Article on Legal Education - http://goo.gl/iP94rG  pic.twitter.com/NR9dywXFkM    
    
    
    Handwriting Input Comes to Gmail and Google Docs - http://goo.gl/mLscuA  pic.twitter.com/f57vdWtjTr    
    
    
    Speak Softly and Carry a Big Dataset - http://goo.gl/MZkZuq  pic.twitter.com/gi4gUino3Y    
    
    
    Your Law Firm has a 12% Chance of Winning an RFP - http://goo.gl/yANXQP  pic.twitter.com/4o0m8Yle6R    
    
    
    Google+ Gets a Google-Sized Series of Updates - http://goo.gl/xhL5Ar  pic.twitter.com/ejO6s6QisD    
    
    
    10 Quick LinkedIn Tips and Strategies to Optimize Your Profile and Use - http://goo.gl/ZcN6vu  pic.twitter.com/GMHj6fPsfa    
    
    
    Ninth Circuit Affirms Order Certifying Meal Period Class - http://goo.gl/T0NjLx  pic.twitter.com/b0M6GwczcH    
    
    
    The Changing State of Employment Arbitration - http://goo.gl/o1BFXD  pic.twitter.com/TE4l7jwzNo    
    
    
    Manifest Disregard - http://goo.gl/tMei1E  pic.twitter.com/ptMp4hgN8Z    
    
    
    In Practice: Harsh Class Arbitration Waivers Still Unconscionable - http://goo.gl/9K3Of3  pic.twitter.com/qnmQJlLm0Y    
    
    
    Third Circuit Says Delaware Can’t Have Secret Arbitrations By Judges - http://goo.gl/XxPRWr  pic.twitter.com/kAsxMxX3kR    
    
    
    Regulation of Dispute Resolution in the United States of America - http://goo.gl/XNuGQw  pic.twitter.com/umtDT0fHo2    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Holds Arbitration Provision Included in Employee Handbook is Illusory and ... - http://goo.gl/s9KxYk  pic.twitter.com/3EucF0b8p7    
    
    
    Scary Results if Employers Overreach in Arbitration Clauses - http://goo.gl/C6mi3A  pic.twitter.com/AUoXbM9uQR    
    
    
    Failure to Provide AAA Arbitration Rules to Employee Does Not Render Arbitration Policy ... - http://goo.gl/9oFRA9  pic.twitter.com/f9uzMEJIx0    
    
    
    @Support how do I raise 2000 follow ceiling? Thanks.    
    
    
    Lessons on Negotiating With Adversaries - http://goo.gl/BMUfUf  pic.twitter.com/MIakMQLgT4    
    
    
    Dispute Resolution Counsel: So What is this Different Kind of Legal Advocacy? - http://goo.gl/zVKQHY  pic.twitter.com/To5fmtdlo7    
    
    
    Eighth Circuit Rejects NFL Retirees’ Objections to Mediated Settlement Due to Exclusion  ... - http://goo.gl/K7PqRw  pic.twitter.com/zUdTXIlkvq    
    
    
    N. D. Texas Holds Prior Arbitration Precludes Fraud Claim in Merger - http://goo.gl/Y6lD6m  pic.twitter.com/RaI2CeWCl7    
    
    
    Scope of Emergency Arbitrator’s Power Appealed to Second Circuit - http://goo.gl/D8F0jW  pic.twitter.com/6XNCH9j8en    
    
    
    California Supreme Court Issues Decision on Arbitration and Labor Commissioner Hearings - http://goo.gl/Gglunw  pic.twitter.com/DkvcKwglcb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Settlement Agreements Rarely Against Public Policy - http://goo.gl/aD6Rvl  pic.twitter.com/0wwGUau5Kk    
    
    
    “Manifest Disregard of the Law” is Alive and Well and Vacating Arbitrations in Fourth Ci ... - http://goo.gl/njEX9c  pic.twitter.com/tOAmM5Uh0r    
    
    
    Dallas Appeals Court Refuses to Compel Arbitration Using Equitable Estoppel - http://goo.gl/OiRbtA  pic.twitter.com/qSIHEmgAgq    
    
    
    Welcome To The Unicorn Club: Learning From Billion-Dollar Startups - http://goo.gl/03LlA9  pic.twitter.com/pe1bMIBAQH    
    
    
    Legal Outsourcing: Onshore or Offshore? - http://goo.gl/jlUJCv  pic.twitter.com/IBJLA0LQi8    
    
    
    Sharing a Mediator’s Powers: Effective Advocacy in Settlement - http://goo.gl/uHIJm6  pic.twitter.com/M5MyV5IFld    
    
    
    Sixth Circuit Is First To Find Availability Of Class Arbitration Is Gateway Issue To Be ... - http://goo.gl/mKOtIa  pic.twitter.com/78r95PSTJg    
    
    
    Bar Foundation Fun Run to Benefit the Dispute Resolution Center Tomorrow - http://goo.gl/dY78Wj  pic.twitter.com/WyorDD7Zta    
    
    
    Court-Approved Mediation Used to Assist Fungal Meningitis Victims - http://goo.gl/iHoLqv  pic.twitter.com/H2x5WhgDOj    
    
    
    64 Federal Courts Now Publish Opinions on FDsys - http://goo.gl/xsSIua  pic.twitter.com/V4nzjHLySK    
    
    
    Seventh Circuit Weighs in on Firing for Facebook Posts - http://goo.gl/SDuTcw  pic.twitter.com/dNIXVe6cvC    
    
    
    The Census Bureau Puts Every American on the Map - http://goo.gl/0aMz1D  pic.twitter.com/i5r6hzTHET    
    
    
    Enhancing Linguistic Search with the Google Books Ngram Viewer - http://goo.gl/qBhMnI  pic.twitter.com/P0U8oeaftt    
    
    
    New Statistics Illustrate the Decline of BigLaw - http://goo.gl/TxmOIi  pic.twitter.com/f2VswNoxYr    
    
    
    How Technology is Affecting the Way Students Write - http://goo.gl/xzdFGM  pic.twitter.com/QSDHdtM8a1    
    
    
    Keep the Feds Out of Your Smartphone - http://goo.gl/X4hSNA  pic.twitter.com/uyB6lmUPt9    
    
    
    Google to Grab Consumers By the Throat - http://goo.gl/JbxiS1  pic.twitter.com/t9J33hMz2L    
    
    
    The Decline of the Associate and the Rise of the Law Firm Employee - http://goo.gl/H0H3cp  pic.twitter.com/XqtaG3mnRS    
    
    
    Will the Next Nate Silver Please Stand Up? - http://goo.gl/URcMmV  pic.twitter.com/OxKvUwdVi6    
    
    
    Two GCs Join Board of International ADR Group - http://goo.gl/5zODil  pic.twitter.com/OGJ2qxC0M0    
    
    
    Consistently Inconsistent: The Need for Predictability in Awarding Costs and Fees in ... - http://goo.gl/QQ4lD3  pic.twitter.com/K1S4U4R8za    
    
    
    EDGE: What Big Data Means for Social Science - http://goo.gl/MNt4IJ  pic.twitter.com/MO1RvLN4Pf    
    
    
    Auto Correct: Has the self-driving car at last arrived? - http://goo.gl/TXkH1R  pic.twitter.com/QajeJOWg79    
    
    
    Canada Joins the Global Arbitration Club - http://goo.gl/1nCe4P  pic.twitter.com/wFPMvQIzdI    
    
    
    Economic Rationales for Mediation - http://goo.gl/ba7Jqo  pic.twitter.com/mYkNInHLfX    
    
    
    Med-Arb and the Legalization of Alternative Dispute Resolution - http://goo.gl/uYt9Ra  pic.twitter.com/8irEg9vNJq    
    
    
    Mediation, Arbitration and Negotiation - http://goo.gl/EAUrhn  pic.twitter.com/LlUtYacIqd    
    
    
    Contractarian Economics and Mediation Ethics: The Case for Customizing Neutrality ... - http://goo.gl/imO1Ns  pic.twitter.com/MbjXRTI1vW    
    
    
    Why Texans Are Poised for the Future of the Legal Biz - http://goo.gl/pIvhL4  pic.twitter.com/iF6DbRMAtg    
    
    
    Ebner on Negotiation via (the New) Email - http://goo.gl/DlZCvu  pic.twitter.com/vGOmdUHFQz    
    
    
    Arbitration Panel to Reconsider Binding Agreement Between Armstrong and SCA Promotions - http://goo.gl/h8B7vQ  pic.twitter.com/UZqIUhPnlN    
    
    
    Fee Foresight: Contingency Cases Important for Large Commercial Firms - http://goo.gl/gVVX9G  pic.twitter.com/FisvICb0K5    
    
    
    Nevada Supreme Court Protects Confidentiality of Foreclosure Mediation Program Records - http://goo.gl/Skty82  pic.twitter.com/nCvD1CATRi    
    
    
    JAMS Supports the ABA’s Planned Early Dispute Resolution Project - http://goo.gl/ZTzPXs  pic.twitter.com/efwFuA0lhv    
    
    
    The Scientific Study of Positive Emotion - http://goo.gl/6VwBvb  pic.twitter.com/lyczuuSITl    
    
    
    Books I’ve Loved (Which Can Be Applied to Your Practice) - http://goo.gl/HhLwgU  pic.twitter.com/5NCJHMEHXc    
    
    
    EDGE: Imagining Conflict Resolution - http://goo.gl/y5u2p0  pic.twitter.com/nvE34lnV1k    
    
    
        
    
    
    A Pyramid Collapse for Law Schools? Most are Losing Money This Year, Law Prof Says - http://goo.gl/Yg6VxK  pic.twitter.com/xQ0qj5e92s    
    
    
    Unsurprising Sixth Circuit Decisioin that Propriety of Class Arbitration is a Gateway ... - http://goo.gl/Zwgdy0  pic.twitter.com/WnyXrc9Kgk    
    
    
    Complex Civil Appeals: Making the Case for Settlement - http://goo.gl/4ioxlN  pic.twitter.com/qVGcH6P858    
    
    
    In-House Salaries Growing at Measured Pace - http://goo.gl/IIsLXF  pic.twitter.com/m14eixrbwj    
    
    
    Company Alleges Firm Breached a Fiduciary Duty by Keeping Settlement Proceeds - http://goo.gl/8nx0nD  pic.twitter.com/Uto4wbK1m8    
    
    
    California's New 'Digital Eraser' Evaporates Embarrassment - http://goo.gl/q4YXam  pic.twitter.com/Dj9ijJ9Dhw    
    
    
    Dropbox Gets Down to Business: 'The Internet Filing System' - http://goo.gl/2OsB0f  pic.twitter.com/TS0Pow8vTX    
    
    
    MAPLA Conference: LSAC Applicant/Applications Data by Geographic Region - http://goo.gl/wYVZFl  pic.twitter.com/bg7ZMSDBxA    
    
    
    Are Landlines on Their Way Out? - http://goo.gl/QOEFJL  pic.twitter.com/lsMpXqJCfE    
    
    
    http://Law.com  Contributor Network to Use Forbes’ Software and Hosting - http://goo.gl/CPlrQU  pic.twitter.com/8yPdkdSKqQ    
    
    
    Mediating in Cases in Domestic Violence – Between a Rock and a Hard Place - http://goo.gl/GCGnkH  pic.twitter.com/NlWQMfAUDe    
    
    
    2013 Law Department Metrics Benchmarking Survey - http://goo.gl/rCc3FT  pic.twitter.com/roRWBscdPL    
    
    
    Is Limited-Scope Representation the Future for Firms? - http://goo.gl/GUr4d6  pic.twitter.com/rvsO4acXGA    
    
    
    Judicial Attention to the Powers of Emergency Arbitrators - http://goo.gl/QGysVh  pic.twitter.com/RhNP5nmMzV    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Holds Procedural Questions for ICDR to Decide - http://goo.gl/G9PqBg  pic.twitter.com/TpBL0BqMo3    
    
    
    Doug Noll's Advanced Legal Negotiation Master Class Tomorrow Featuring Picture It Settled - http://goo.gl/oCClMp  pic.twitter.com/Xqie8mllDk    
    
    
    Developing a Framework for Arbitrating Standards-Essential Patent (SEP) Disputes - http://goo.gl/MUWhuj  pic.twitter.com/FFM1HPwziu    
    
    
    The CBS – Time Warner Cable Dispute: Making a Bad BATNA Even Worse - http://goo.gl/xj22Sx  pic.twitter.com/QejDn75Fl1    
    
    
    Consumer Arbitration Unconscionability Trumps FAA Pre-Emption in Ninth Circuit Once Again - http://goo.gl/19lHVF  pic.twitter.com/oil4dNwDMt    
    
    
    Mediated Settlement Term Sheet Upheld Against Claims of Uncertainty and Mistake - http://goo.gl/bDAv0N  pic.twitter.com/07AMCGfSjo    
    
    
    Arbitration Agreements Waiving FLSA Collective Actions - http://goo.gl/ebntyF  pic.twitter.com/f8jcdr1TtI    
    
    
    Enforcing Arbitral Awards That Have Previously Been Annulled - http://goo.gl/3cDURh  pic.twitter.com/OJTt3vZqnl    
    
    
    Unsettled - http://goo.gl/w41kdk  pic.twitter.com/ki7QzueT98    
    
    
    Why Attorneys Love-Hate Data Analytics - http://goo.gl/ZZ7WBQ  pic.twitter.com/bNr4tIYRQt    
    
    
    Class Action Waivers in Arbitration Agreements Validated in NLRB Loss in the Fifth Circuit - http://goo.gl/iTVmL3  pic.twitter.com/ikhlH3oTTK    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Invalidates NLRB Order Prohibiting Clauses In Covered Employment ... - http://goo.gl/1IhBf6  pic.twitter.com/xkyey3jC0p    
    
    
    Improving Arbitration-Award Making and Enforcement by Faithfully Implementing the ... - http://goo.gl/ehQZzN  pic.twitter.com/gx7gSHpWOm    
    
    
    Why Unpaid Interns Are Suing Employers - http://goo.gl/P0Zbp5  pic.twitter.com/rHE4Bnsd5p    
    
    
    Mediator Certification in California - http://goo.gl/m5aYB3  pic.twitter.com/8tHNO9BYFZ    
    
    
    California Supreme Court Attempts to Thread the Unconscionability Needle - http://goo.gl/WcEhM8  pic.twitter.com/I6fBCfb6MK    
    
    
    When Algorithms Grow Accustomed to Your Face - http://goo.gl/RO3czz  pic.twitter.com/8JoOsdjpCw    
    
    
    Getting the Other Guy to the Negotiation Table - http://goo.gl/GUfeoQ  pic.twitter.com/CXLX6xKZpW    
    
    
    Burford Capital Gets $40M in New Capital for Litigation Funding - http://goo.gl/cDcPqX  pic.twitter.com/bF5ZZktCgk    
    
    
    Court Order Requiring Further Mediation Not Appealable - http://goo.gl/fHfSNa  pic.twitter.com/ELLEW7bpzJ    
    
    
    ACC Survey Sees GC Salaries Up, Outside Spend Down - http://goo.gl/jHKbcP  pic.twitter.com/VKd8uViRcd    
    
    
    Recalculate the Future of Law - http://goo.gl/5gSha6  pic.twitter.com/PFk1dg9Mei    
    
    
    Litigation Funding Technique Creates Potential Conflicts in Australia - http://goo.gl/LEc9TI  pic.twitter.com/fY9yw0nTZA    
    
    
    Demographic Change Hits Nation's Law Schools - http://goo.gl/PWh3Gb  pic.twitter.com/QdZxd3Xe3Z    
    
    
    Law Schools Can’t Sleep Through the Technological Revolution - http://goo.gl/qlS1qA  pic.twitter.com/knvd7YhNX9    
    
    
    How to Start Thinking Like a Data Scientist - http://goo.gl/yWNEMd  pic.twitter.com/n5W59XGQZc    
    
    
    Google Puts Money on Robots, Using the Man Behind Android - http://goo.gl/CFxPwL  pic.twitter.com/ISEg787Lck    
    
    
    Mommy, the Drone’s Here! - http://goo.gl/duJ2wr  pic.twitter.com/3uO4Z0gizv    
    
    
    "@KOMUnews: Josey injured his back after personal foul by #Auburn's Ryan White." what about officiating? Great example - get away with it!    
    
    
    MSU J.D. Program Offers Major in Tech - http://goo.gl/aLdqqh  pic.twitter.com/aafsBcsXSi    
    
    
    A Glimpse at the Legal Profession's Future - http://goo.gl/iZnSJQ  pic.twitter.com/aNySHQ7D6m    
    
    
    University of Iowa Law Cuts Tuition Amid Enrollment Decline - http://goo.gl/u7zijN  pic.twitter.com/abh9IEZCWC    
    
    
    What Do the 2013 Bonuses Tell Us About the Legal Market? (video) - http://goo.gl/58J3lD  pic.twitter.com/DlNKaJtOGx    
    
    
        
    
    
    Firm Leaders Survey: Slow Growth on Tap for 2014 - http://goo.gl/2P1GSj  pic.twitter.com/jBdPk2wCsy    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court to Ring in New Year With Two Arbitration Cases - http://goo.gl/PYluop  pic.twitter.com/j6c5ZkfeP4    
    
    
    Litigators Eye AAA Rules Allowing Appeal of Arbitral Decisions - http://goo.gl/0rEie4  pic.twitter.com/pE3BfHEzh0    
    
    
    Big Securities Class Action? Opt-Outs May Follow - http://goo.gl/m2sjUp  pic.twitter.com/Kr1LumjZwh    
    
    
    Learning From Past Mistakes With Predictive Analytics - http://goo.gl/V7QvBh  pic.twitter.com/6Nl8w8FTCE    
    
    
        
    
    
    D.C. Avoids Arbitration in $117 Million Lawsuit Against Bank of America - http://goo.gl/kXqtw1  pic.twitter.com/XAyBF80USR    
    
    
    Inside the Litigation Settlement Machine - http://goo.gl/UsftCK  pic.twitter.com/J01vinzhvx    
    
    
        
    
    
    Lumen Legal’s Trends for 2014 - http://goo.gl/CFbv19  pic.twitter.com/kmF9gDVFYB    
    
    
    Updating the Multi-Door Courthouse - http://goo.gl/H3c2Sr  pic.twitter.com/l81ofwTzKz    
    
    
    Bringing Oxytocin into the Room - http://goo.gl/ukzz6F  pic.twitter.com/csaiv7Jdsl    
    
    
    Improving Arbitration-Award Making and Enforcement by Faithfully Implementing the ... - http://goo.gl/0BRUZp  pic.twitter.com/gbzQnZd1IW    
    
    
    Pizza & Metadata: Order It The Way You Want It - http://goo.gl/uVq9qh  pic.twitter.com/emXjWvWTEa    
    
    
    You can get Release 4.0 of the GC Metrics Benchmark Survey: More Than 1,100 Participants - http://goo.gl/OQoTp5  pic.twitter.com/k8BPSnNY1b    
    
    
    Law Firm Managing Partners Expect A Bad Year — For Everyone Else - http://goo.gl/o0AB8d  pic.twitter.com/fp6nwBWaRo    
    
    
    Crisis Negotiations: How Jamie Dimon Avoided Disaster - http://goo.gl/ojJcao  pic.twitter.com/0jb3g3yNE9    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    West Virginia Has A Change Of Heart About Arbitration - http://goo.gl/h0jMPs  pic.twitter.com/b86oMxVINc    
    
    
    Arbitration v. Class Action Lawsuits: Do Class Actions Benefit Class Members? - http://goo.gl/MFFUxk  pic.twitter.com/JobkBia14b    
    
    
    CFPB Report on Consumer Arbitration Released - http://goo.gl/bka3S9  pic.twitter.com/swA22kH8gl    
    
    
    Supreme Court Takes Up Patent Eligibility Case - http://goo.gl/s1hIBh  pic.twitter.com/ytdJt0mrTm    
    
    
    Avoid "Discovery About Discovery" with Cooperation - http://goo.gl/XO9H7V  pic.twitter.com/kygaWFuzPT    
    
    
    Luddite Lawyers Are Ethical Violations Waiting To Happen - http://goo.gl/p7RBHv  pic.twitter.com/erKLMSofEj    
    
    
    Facebook and Judges - http://goo.gl/5kQvvy  pic.twitter.com/ylqG285TIz    
    
    
    Penn State's Dickinson School of Law to provide $20K grant to Pennsylvanians - http://goo.gl/1BKjhh  pic.twitter.com/8lvHglyTgM    
    
    
    Demand for Legal Work Is Down 5% This Year, 6.4% in BigLaw - http://goo.gl/e5hOMA  pic.twitter.com/gelrMplICY    
    
    
    Is There a Future for Solos and Small Firms? - http://goo.gl/fSUWIV  pic.twitter.com/Yp65V4bgjP    
    
    
    An Update on Milbank's Big Bet - http://goo.gl/SWb0zx  pic.twitter.com/nBcqTBc6V2    
    
    
    Bringing the Disruption of the Legal Services Market into the Law School Classroom - http://goo.gl/IxLYaA  pic.twitter.com/cyWAXfLC6A    
    
    
    Number of Takers of the Law School Admission Test Continues to Bottom Out - http://goo.gl/RJPA0J  pic.twitter.com/W013oq7wM5    
    
    
    Judge Approves $153 Million Settlement in Fannie Mae Securities Class Action - http://goo.gl/E3VAaP  pic.twitter.com/wqxZPbMJDG    
    
    
    The Starbucks-Kraft Dispute: In Business Negotiations, Prepare for Problems - http://goo.gl/Mqzq9V  pic.twitter.com/dW8bWdaap5    
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Overrules NLRB, Finds D.R. Horton May Preclude Class Arbitration - http://goo.gl/RWdd1K  pic.twitter.com/MvxeZBJJCi    
    
    
    How Influenced Are We By Images of Brain Scans? Maybe Not As Much As We Used To Be? - http://goo.gl/mVYr4r  pic.twitter.com/RYfLHm5s6T    
    
    
    Empathy: Paving the Road to Preferential Treatment with Good Intentions - http://goo.gl/Ca1HDw  pic.twitter.com/bbuOusjGi6    
    
    
    Is Axiom the Bellwether for Disruption in the Legal Industry? - http://goo.gl/Ta2Sft  pic.twitter.com/NGIRIbYJHD    
    
    
        
    
    
    Technology, Not Rules Changes, Is Answer to E-Discovery Costs, Arthur Miller Tells ... - http://goo.gl/XkWzOB  pic.twitter.com/dVfAKwh3vi    
    
    
    Appeals Court Ponders Arbitration of Legal Malpractice Claim - http://goo.gl/MpmM7d  pic.twitter.com/ioVWaoNt26    
    
    
    Do You Want To Make Your Juror "Think Fast"? - http://goo.gl/K7OLGX  pic.twitter.com/2augd44SZa    
    
    
        
    
    
    Concepcion Gives No Easy Out to Lawyers in Client Disputes - http://goo.gl/oLpHZ4  pic.twitter.com/KzAtTBixMh    
    
    
    First-Year Law School Enrollment At 1977 Levels - http://goo.gl/Hn9DKd  pic.twitter.com/yKD7VemRIv    
    
    
    Concepcion Gives No Easy Out to Lawyers in Client Disputes - http://goo.gl/bVyPln  pic.twitter.com/JID1L8HbGf    
    
    
    Bioethics, Healthcare Policy, & Alternative Dispute Resolution in the Age of Obamacare - http://goo.gl/GKyorD  pic.twitter.com/MU5a6m2Fuf    
    
    
    Does Priming Influence Behavior of Even the "Bad Boys"? - http://goo.gl/PVm8tQ  pic.twitter.com/rTPVbQlT3r    
    
    
    Does Priming Influence Behavior of Even the "Bad Boys"? - http://goo.gl/mR0s2Z  pic.twitter.com/df7EuJ603s    
    
    
    Back to Basics: Global Companies Sign Pledge to Bring Mediation into the Heart of ... - http://goo.gl/WPgGOf  pic.twitter.com/8Opb9Wb1WW    
    
    
    Preventing Conflicts in Family Businesses - http://goo.gl/MEPVWC  pic.twitter.com/gtDr1UqMZR    
    
    
    Decline in Female Associates Called a 'Red Flag' - http://goo.gl/J8nKBl  pic.twitter.com/mFA83jQ16d    
    
    
    Decline in Female Associates Called a 'Red Flag' - http://goo.gl/d2eMrH  pic.twitter.com/LBPUDWzwNm    
    
    
    The Federalization of Consumer Arbitration: Possible Solutions - http://goo.gl/j1qNkU  pic.twitter.com/TlRKDjz6dW    
    
    
    The Federalization of Consumer Arbitration: Possible Solutions - http://goo.gl/bLpb2f  pic.twitter.com/8iYKZiSG8i    
    
    
    Cognitive Complexity: How Can Reading a Novel Help You Become a Better Mediator? - http://goo.gl/wqgDq8  pic.twitter.com/gKEeyf35oZ    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Science of Social Connections - http://goo.gl/Rrnzbg  pic.twitter.com/zH9TVgexuC    
    
    
    The Science of Social Connections - http://goo.gl/DEgHeK  pic.twitter.com/dIlDGktIPB    
    
    
    The Rise of Alternative Fee Arrangements - http://goo.gl/mJJ57U  pic.twitter.com/TroPPs2gGa    
    
    
    The Rise of Alternative Fee Arrangements - http://goo.gl/yPkRLa  pic.twitter.com/DYNBYg73F4    
    
    
    S.D. Texas Compels Wireless Telephone Franchise Dispute to Arbitration - http://goo.gl/0gyARI  pic.twitter.com/uegDH9tVgo    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Highly Recommended Exchange of Views About Left/Right and Top/Bottom Brain - http://goo.gl/EEhOal  pic.twitter.com/EhVFNGyrM4    
    
    
    ACC Looks Into the Future of General Counsel - http://goo.gl/TfBfZz  pic.twitter.com/s6qvDNtSCG    
    
    
    Sheila Heen Providing Expert Advice in the NYT - http://goo.gl/ChpAIz  pic.twitter.com/cA4xmDxsbc    
    
    
    No Shades of Gray in the Commoditization of Law - http://goo.gl/JS1as3  pic.twitter.com/JLXvs9vXge    
    
    
    @TheYamahaHub Trouble keeping TSR-6750 connected to Sony KDL-55NX810. Connections work but display won't stay connected -- intermittent    
    
    
    @Nuanceimage Software Manager indicated a patch for PP14Pro but it won't download (Win7 64-bit) - same for Dragon 12.5 update    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @DragonTweets  (210) 212-7100    
    
    
    @DragonTweets don.philbin@gmail.com    
    
    
    President Obama Urges Students to Learn to Code - http://goo.gl/45dBd9  pic.twitter.com/Vx5ynXJ5Gz    
    
    
    Clayton Christensen Explains How Disruption Will Occur in Higher Education - http://goo.gl/lSCyLi  pic.twitter.com/lcxYpU3sf9    
    
    
    Goldman Sets Strict Limits on Hours. Will Law Firms Follow? - http://goo.gl/ocsVab  pic.twitter.com/g8QY5hH0LD    
    
    
        
    
    
    Modus Releases Workflow Software After Partnering With ACC - http://goo.gl/ZQPMNo  pic.twitter.com/VgeiAgAImS    
    
    
    Google Adds to Its Menagerie of Robots - http://goo.gl/XchTgi  pic.twitter.com/E1gZOzVbaI    
    
    
    AIPLA Taps Lex Machina for Legal Analytics - http://goo.gl/bh7aXF  pic.twitter.com/gcVxW8JNtm    
    
    
    NY Office of Court Administration Seeks Comments on Mandatory Mediation Pilot - http://goo.gl/hm2BZL  pic.twitter.com/GdjoH8ToUc    
    
    
    Texas Supreme Court Agrees to Consider What Constitutes Arbitrator Evident Partiality - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/texas-supreme-court-agrees-consider-constitutes-arbitrator-evident-partiality/ … pic.twitter.com/lGjzs0WkxQ    
    
    
    Toyota Begins Settlement Negotiations on Acceleration Lawsuits - http://goo.gl/xCA8AG  pic.twitter.com/rfzXO2xPoB    
    
    
    Is the Law Firm Pyramid Collapsing? BigLaw is Aging With More Partners Than Associates - http://goo.gl/d8BQpe  pic.twitter.com/ColFPRHwAQ    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    In God We Trust: All Others Bring Data - http://goo.gl/j7YLih  pic.twitter.com/uhRKcfbeS9    
    
    
        
    
    
    In Walmart Fee Fight, Ninth Circuit Balks at 'Non-Appealable' Arbitration - http://goo.gl/WMnux5  pic.twitter.com/I242bFjpww    
    
    
        
    
    
    Arbitral Autonomy - http://goo.gl/oWaay9  pic.twitter.com/Gg5AYpNfUV    
    
    
        
    
    
    Beyond International Commercial Arbitration? The Promise of International Commercial ... - http://goo.gl/Ek9Vts  pic.twitter.com/3xqlR4UUgJ    
    
    
    Applebee's Squelches Class Action Through Arbitration Clause - http://goo.gl/CXv4CR  pic.twitter.com/tlftj06Ado    
    
    
        
    
    
    Preventing Conflicts in Family Businesses - http://goo.gl/H1uxA1  pic.twitter.com/tZUBJrnpyS    
    
    
    10 Charts from 2013 That Changed the Way We Think - http://goo.gl/c1q1pB  pic.twitter.com/i0QYt5c4LL    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Intellectual Property Cases Won in 2013 Worth Bragging About - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27631  pic.twitter.com/E976LBC3tr    
    
    
    Roberts Warns of Impact of Budget Cuts on Judiciary - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27635  pic.twitter.com/Vz00dtsJ33    
    
    
    2013: A Bellwether Year in Litigation - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27638  pic.twitter.com/V2vV1OkqTI    
    
    
    Law 2014: Within Employment Discrimination, It’s a Wage-and-Hour World - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/law-2014-within-employment-discrimination-wage-hour-world/ … pic.twitter.com/GBXcGzeBO0    
    
    
    The 10 Most Important Legal Technology Developments of 2013 - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/10-important-legal-technology-developments-2013/ … pic.twitter.com/38pSDOFIyS    
    
    
    Posner Frowns on Sealed Settlement Agreements - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27645  pic.twitter.com/MGXqYOddTZ    
    
    
    Largest E-Filing State Mandate Begins in Texas - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27659  pic.twitter.com/KnfcluThyZ    
    
    
    Recession Rebound: Managing Partner Survey Shows Positive Growth Trend - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27649  pic.twitter.com/V8vWZftDH9    
    
    
    The IP Long Tail of the Google Books Decision - http://www.adrtoolbox.com/?p=27651  pic.twitter.com/a698oqQIwV    
    
    
        
    
    
    Mortgage Foreclosure Is Debt Collection under FDCPA - http://goo.gl/fsCgM  pic.twitter.com/IMgDBO9k2e    
    
    
    Enforcement of Interim and Partial Awards: Emerging Coherence in US Law? - http://goo.gl/Lg9rm  pic.twitter.com/ftoVwknwyY    
    
    
    IBA Adopts New Guidelines on Party Representation in International Arbitration - http://goo.gl/VwOiP  pic.twitter.com/ZaCrkBOOL8    
    
    
    In Quest of the Arbitration Trifecta, or Closed Door Litigation?: The Delaware ... - http://goo.gl/usuO1  pic.twitter.com/bm62c6CwoA    
    
    
    In Quest of the Arbitration Trifecta, or Closed Door Litigation?: The Delaware Arbitration Program - http://goo.gl/wbwBi     
    
    
    An Introduction to Litigation Trusts - http://goo.gl/1JtZa  pic.twitter.com/jAMH9tKELD    
    
    
    An Introduction to Litigation Trusts -    
    
    
    NASA Launches Technology Spinoff iPad App - http://goo.gl/65yAS  pic.twitter.com/jrILpOrbuN    
    
    
    NASA Launches Technology Spinoff iPad App - http://goo.gl/t4vWK  pic.twitter.com/E8MHX76OFg    
    
    
    Arbitration Cases a Growing Revenue Stream for Law Firms - http://goo.gl/5UyQB  pic.twitter.com/xTrfBMdq4T    
    
    
    Arbitration Cases a Growing Revenue Stream for Law Firms - http://goo.gl/Lm6rO  pic.twitter.com/vc8mz564Y8    
    
    
    Sebok on Litigation Financing and Insurance - http://goo.gl/NkBq8     
    
    
    Sebok on Litigation Financing and Insurance - http://goo.gl/xwQY1     
    
    
    Fifth Circuit Considers Arbitrator’s Authority to Issue Discovery-Related Sanctions - http://goo.gl/ZE9mQ  pic.twitter.com/TFYqikoJVY    
    
    
    Using Forensic Accounting in Trust Disputes - http://goo.gl/M3v1T  pic.twitter.com/0QkgnMItel    
    
    
    Equal Contest of Arms, Jurisdictional Proof in Investor-State Arbitrations - http://goo.gl/EMfdR  pic.twitter.com/v5Wv0kRile    
    
    
    Outsourcing Justice: The Rise of Modern Arbitration Laws in America - http://goo.gl/MSyAq  pic.twitter.com/DmJ3w8FyfM    
    
    
    Rethink Ink: Digital Signatures Are Faster & Safer - http://goo.gl/jTwFo  pic.twitter.com/ZdKmXlhaGZ    
    
    
    Moneyball for IP Law - http://goo.gl/D02iK  pic.twitter.com/MqC8kPYp0T    
    
    
    Breaking Down the Business-Judgment Rule - http://goo.gl/4IH5M  pic.twitter.com/5c9KMsMIeV    
    
    
    Lisa Bu: How Books Can Open Your Mind - http://goo.gl/ZwaJT  pic.twitter.com/zI0r5RtWFh    
    
    
    San Antonio Attorney-Mediator Don Philbin Elected 2014 Chair of the State Bar of Texas ... - http://goo.gl/86xKY  pic.twitter.com/pi3Ns9pMxb    
    
    
    New Administered Rules for CPR Arbitration - http://goo.gl/B1xww  pic.twitter.com/Vdava3mUMU    
    
    
    Terms of Merger Agreement Not incorporated Into Master Settlement Agreement - http://goo.gl/eU7Gb  pic.twitter.com/YXlnoNK3pa    
    
    
    San Antonio Attorney Elected Chair of State Bar's ADR Section for 2014-15 Year - http://goo.gl/jgPyf  pic.twitter.com/daXz9ovX46    
    
    
    