www.haxel.com and the new ICIC website http://haxel.com/icic/2010/meeting is online .... feedback welcome    
    
    
    Combine your attendance at the ICIC with the STN User Meeting  on Thursday, October 27 2011 in Barcelona and get the mo…http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
    Find all about Trends in scientific and patent information ICIC 2010 in Vienna .... see:  www.haxel.com    
    
    
    will start a new event: ICIC summer school in Vienna - An introduction for future Information Professionals. 1 and 2 Juli. Info coming soon.    
    
    
    The new brochure for the ICIC in Barcelona - The International Conference for the Information Community - is now avail…http://lnkd.in/ZfBY7P     
    
    
    My latest SlideShare upload : Icic 2011 programme http://slidesha.re/nkJrJe     
    
    
        
    
    
    There are only five weeks to go until the start of the ICIC - The International Conference for the Information...: http://lnkd.in/qSNyBa     
    
    
    is planning a trip to India in July to visite different location in the area of IP-Services and possible cooperations. Please contact me ...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    all ICIC 2011 presentation and photos are online ... ICIC 2012 will be in Berlin. There is an early bird fee for the ex…http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
        
    
    
    II-SDV International Information Conference on Search, Data Mining and Visualization http://lnkd.in/iigz_S     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    New Conference: International Information Conference on Search, Data Mining and Visualizaition: http://lnkd.in/ExHU6H     
    
    
    is organizing this week the first company event with Sikom in Kiel. Sailing and a conference about voice and IT ... we need sun. The sun ma…    
    
    
    more infos about the sikom event: www.haxel.com/company/sikom http://lnkd.in/UCyzEv    
    
    
    found a nice place for the ICIC 2011 in Barcelona. Attention: Early bird booking for the ICIC 2010 ends in 4 weeks. Yo…http://lnkd.in/fk4jDD    
    
    
    @larsbas .. stimmt für viele IT-Anwendungen. Ich kämpfe jetzt für Open Source. Viele Grüße aus Wien vom Ex-Henkel-LN-Freund Christoph Haxel    
    
    
    is travelling to India ... after the soccer game Germany vs Spain    
    
    
    The organizers of the 24th International Conference for the Information Community (ICIC) have just published the full p…http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
    first success in India. IPSANCTUARY.COM is exhibiting during the ICIC 2010 http://IPSANCTUARY.COM    
    
    
    booked the location for the ICIC 2011. 23 - 26 October 2011. World Trade Center Barcelona ... see www.wtcbarcelona.com…http://lnkd.in/uGjgQz    
    
    
    visited CPA Global in India and was very impressed. www.cpaglobal.com http://www.cpaglobal.com    
    
    
    Economy? The darker it gets the better you see the stars. Christoph Haxel    
    
    
    Our new conference Search, Data Mining, Visualization: We have reached 130 people. We are very happy. Latest sign-up i…http://www.ii-sdv.com     
    
    
    visited in Bangalore a leading supplier of manually curated databases to major pharmaceutical companies and was again …http://lnkd.in/JwGAA-    
    
    
    reminds that the early booking price for the 2010 ICIC meeting in Vienna this October expires 10 AUGUST 2010. If you are planning to attend…    
    
    
    ICIC Conference details for Early Bird Registration http://lnkd.in/vwyy8K    
    
    
    My latest SlideShare upload : ICIC 2010 The intn. Conference on Trends for Scientific Information Professionals. http://slidesha.re/cOE69x    
    
    
    Just a reminder that the early booking price for the 2012 ICIC meeting in Berlin this October expires 1 AUGUST 2012. I…http://lnkd.in/_Z4R6y     
    
    
    Just a reminder that the early booking price for the 2012 ICIC meeting in Berlin this October expires 1 AUGUST...: http://lnkd.in/dPqcks     
    
    
    Ich flog vor 13 Tagen mit der AF von Rio nach Paris, habe für die Opfer Kerzen angezündet. Meine große Liebe kam am Sonntag aus Rio ...    
    
    
    Early Bird registration is going well. When you attend the ICIC 2010 you will meet colleagues from following companies…http://lnkd.in/bcu69i    
    
    
    ICIC 2010 exhibition is sold out. 24 international exhibitors ... perfect. http://lnkd.in/ePy5R7    
    
    
    ICIC 2010 in October is well on the road ... more than 100 early bird registrations. Thank you for booking. http://lnkd.in/bcu69i    
    
    
    Share an update Just a reminder that the early booking price for the 2012 ICIC meeting in Berlin this October expi…http://www.haxel.com/icic     
    
    
    Matrixware is moving to Operngasse 11. Next week I am in a new Office in Vienna :-). Thanks to all electronic archives: 20 mio docs moved    
    
    
    Be an Early Bird and Save! Early booking price for the 2012 ICIC meeting in Berlin expires 30 July 2012: http://lnkd.in/idW7r7     
    
    
    Be an Early Bird and Save! Early booking price for the 2012 ICIC meeting in Berlin expires 30 July 2012: http://lnkd.in/Hm6VF2     
    
    
    Good news ... LIGHTHOUSE IP is sponsoring the welcome Dinner during the ICIC 2012 (Berlin) in October 2012 . BTW Early …http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
    Are you planing to attend the ICIC 2012? Just extend your stay in Berlin for another day to participate in the STN Use…http://lnkd.in/uHrF9h     
    
    
    Good news! We 've extended the ICIC Early Bird Registration rate until August 31st. http://www.haxel.com/icic     
    
    
    Just published the current 'EARLY BIRD ATTENDEE' list of ICIC 2012 in Berlin. More than 100 attendees from 65 companie…http://lnkd.in/fzvztv     
    
    
    Michael Jackson: see Patent of the day: http://bit.ly/Iohjf
 see it in action at around 07:15...  
http://bit.ly/vfAU
 :-(((    
    
    
    There are only six weeks to go until the start of the ICIC meeting
in 2010. The meeting is filling fast, so if you in…http://lnkd.in/fk4jDD    
    
    
    exhibiton space is now selling well for the ICIC 2011 in the World Trade Center Barcelona. Two weeks after the exhibit…http://lnkd.in/5-vTWF    
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC 2012 in Berlin is coming soon. Last chance to register ... more than 145 attendees and 27 exhibitors are on my registration list.    
    
    
    www.matrixware.net is launched ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    the new domain is working. Sometimes IT is working with the right partners: www.icic.eu    
    
    
    ... now with attachment. Murhpy's law: "Anything that can go wrong, will go wrong" .. but www.icic.eu works !!! http://www.icic.eu    
    
    
    Incredible ... 16 exhibitors booked the ICIC 2013 Exhibition (14-16 Oct 2013)  in Vienna and I have only 24 slots to se…http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
    The programme for the II-SDV "International Information Conference on Search, Data Mining and Visualization" in April …http://www.ii-sdv.com     
    
    
    received today 2 registrations from Austria, 1 from Australia and one from Brasil. Organizing conference you need good nerves .... ICIC 201…    
    
    
    ICIC 2013 in Vienna: Call for Papers Deadline for responses to the Call for Papers for the 2013 ICIC meeting in...: http://lnkd.in/GFmsaw     
    
    
    Tools for Intelligence Meeting in Nice Attracts Good Attendance: http://lnkd.in/DdvYEB     
    
    
    Ahh Iibhn aBb  Aahbjbb- Abe nbJ ubuuhuuub!22!?/2 v b unc    
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC in Vienna: Early bird registration ends 15 June 2013. Vienna now or never.    
    
    
    ICIC 2013: Now or never - Super Early Bird Rate ends 15 June 2013. 22 exhibitor slots sold. http://www.haxel.com/icic     
    
    
    Just a quick reminder that the absolute deadline for responses to the Call for Papers for the 2011 ICIC meeting in…http://www.haxel.com/icic    
    
    
    is planing a business trip to Brazil (Rio de Janeiro) in Nov 2013. Please do not hesitate to contact me if you need my support in the area …    
    
    
    New features available: www.matrixware.net ... join our community, if you are interested in Information Management    
    
    
    Good news! We 've extended the Early Bird Registration rate until 15 September 2013
http://www.haxel.com/icic  http://www.haxel.com/icic     
    
    
    The 2014 II-SDV conference will take place in Nice, 14-15 April 2014
http://lnkd.in/-Zxmnr     
    
    
    Tomorrow is the last chance to register as early bird for the ICIC 2013 in Vienna ... http://lnkd.in/bffEAuB     
    
    
    Tomorrow is the last chance to register as early bird for the ICIC 2013 in Vienna ...
http://lnkd.in/b8zj9SW  http://lnkd.in/bipKmr8     
    
    
    Final Programme ICIC 2013 in Vienna is ready for printing .... http://lnkd.in/bEW38Rj     
    
    
    I visited the CIP Forum in Göteborg. It was a great conference ... read more http://twitter.com/CIPFORUM    
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Richard Garner (LexisNexis) http://lnkd.in/bwK_A9N     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Marc Tobias BGW http://lnkd.in/bQcKDZq     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/b4QGweD     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bhQ3D-r     
    
    
    Icic 2013 conference proceedings krishna molecular connections http://lnkd.in/bXf5crW     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bBYUWY3     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/brHDkQW     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Antony Williams Royal Society of C... http://lnkd.in/b4UV-uh     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Andreas Pesenhofer max.recall http://lnkd.in/b2FT4-Z     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Jane List Extract Information http://lnkd.in/beH8jqA     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Josef Eiblmaier Infochem http://lnkd.in/bP6x-aU     
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Monika Hanelt Agfa http://lnkd.in/bJAkSQ9     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 Conference Proceedings Tony Trippe Patinformatics http://lnkd.in/bxjQ8Bp     
    
    
        
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bJPy4jn     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bZAQZfQ     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bQBwfAj     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bBYrvBG     
    
    
    http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bZR-D8Y     
    
    
    New Product Introduction ICIC 2013 - InfoChem http://lnkd.in/bAxTCak     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions BizInt http://lnkd.in/b3CrdtX     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Minesoft http://lnkd.in/bjbK8tn     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions LexisNexis http://lnkd.in/bDDSb73     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions max.recall http://lnkd.in/bv76-9v     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Linguamatics http://lnkd.in/bvK_fbS     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Dolcera http://lnkd.in/bNbhrAS     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions RightsDirect http://lnkd.in/bHYFDHS     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions ChemAxon http://lnkd.in/brFVdaJ     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions GenomeQuest http://lnkd.in/bVsNEz8     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions CAS http://lnkd.in/b4JpPDJ     
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions CEPT http://lnkd.in/bAW_rcv     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions FIZ Karlsruhe http://lnkd.in/bGyzYFa     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Parthys Reverse Informatics http://lnkd.in/bMBQVpM     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Stellarix http://lnkd.in/bMXmgyP     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions INTELLIXIR http://lnkd.in/bRJzKSk     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Averbis http://lnkd.in/bgzg7r6     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions Search Technology (vantage point) http://lnkd.in/bsu2JaG     
    
    
    ICIC 2013 New Product Introductions GVK Bio Informatics http://lnkd.in/biGr8ZB     
    
    
    1.763 views in less than 24 hours forn the ICIC presentations ... thanks to social networks linkedin, slideshare, fa…http://www.haqxel.com     
    
    
    More than 1.700 views in less than 24 hours for all ICIC presentations  ... thanks to all social networks, linkedin,…http://www.haxel.com     
    
    
    ... and thanks to Anthony Williams for his recommendations
http://lnkd.in/b4UV-uh     
    
    
    ... and thanks to Antony Williams for his recommendations: http://lnkd.in/b4UV-uh     
    
    
    International Information Conference on search, Data Mining and Visualisation. The 2014 II-SDV meeting takes place i…http://lnkd.in/bxED2At     
    
    
    Early Bird Booking for the ICIC Exhibition 2014 in Heidelberg http://www.haxel.com  http://lnkd.in/bCw2ZF4     
    
    
    ICIC 2011 Super Early Bird Registration is open. Secure your registration before end of March and save over 33 % of the…http://www.haxel.com    
    
    
    We are happy to announce that the preliminary programme of the April 2014 II-SDV meeting is now available. The preli…http://lnkd.in/dN8sp-Y     
    
    
    International Information Conference on Search, Data Mining and Visualisation: There is a Super Early Bird booking r…http://www.ii-sdv.com     
    
    
    Last chance for the ICIC 2014 exhibition in Heidelberg. Special offer only if you order before 30 November 2013 and …http://www.haxel.com/icic     
    
    
    ICIC 2014 in Heidelberg: Call for Papers

The 2014 ICIC meeting will be held in Heidelberg 12 – 15 October. We are n…http://lnkd.in/d_5CrvY     
    
    
    ICIC 2014 in Heidelberg: Call for Papers
The 2014 ICIC meeting will be held in Heidelberg 12 – 15 October. We are no…http://lnkd.in/d_5CrvY     
    
    
    Heidelberg is a great place for my next conference in October 2014. Call for papers at http://www.haxel.com . Merry X-mas from X-tof    
    
    
    Booked for the ICIC 2014 welcome  reception and conference dinner at Heidelberg Castle  ... sponsorship is still ope…http://lnkd.in/da7Frag     
    
    
    and Harry Collier (Infonortics) have forged a close collaboration with meetings and conferences. The International Inf…http://www.ii-sdv.com    
    
    
    launched a new website for his Consulting Business http://www.drhaxel.com    
    
    
    has just published the full programme for the ICIC taking place on 23 – 26 October 2011, Barcelona, Spain. http://www.haxel.com/icic    
    
    
    last chance to register as super early bird @ ICIC 2011 in Barcelona and save yourself some money. Be smart and combine m…http://www.icic.eu    
    
    
    50 registrations for the ICIC 2011Barcelona in October. 18 Exhibitors booked. Programme published. Not bad ... The con…http://lnkd.in/GqPvqa    
    
    
    Next epo cip will be in lusanne 19-21 October 2010    
    
    
    Next ICIC conference will be in Vienna 24-27 October 2010    
    
    
    ICIC 2010: The Call for Papers and Invitation to Exhibit is now published ... more info see http://www.infonortics.com/chemical/index.html    
    
    
    to cut costs, ip-management is considering moving services to somewhere in Chindia. This new word is a blend of Ch…http://www.ip-chindia.com    
    
    
    happy x-mas and a happy new year. good start in the first day of the second decade of the second millenium warm regards from x-tof    
    
    
    old technolgies are still working ... sand painting versus power point http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vOhf3OvRXKg&feature=fvst    
    
    
    new version of www.matrixware.net is now online with the first version of a marketplace for ip and information professionals. Free posting .    
    
    
    Early booking price for the 2011 ICIC meeting in Barcelona expires next month: http://lnkd.in/hAVvzf    
    
    
    Invitation to exhibit during the II-SDV 2012 in Nice / Early booking price: http://lnkd.in/X66KjX    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rz2-Nj If you are interested in learing more about Data mining techniques and Text Analystics field you must visit our...    
    
    
    received yesterday two new Exhibition Bookings for the ICIC 2011 in Barcelona: QWAM and Springer ... and today? ... sti…http://www.haxel.com    
    
    
    II-SDV 2012 - Nice: This meeting, the International Information conference on Search, Data Mining and...: http://lnkd.in/D3GiFq    
    
    
    II-SDV Meeting -Nice: This meeting, the International Information conference on Search, Data Mining and...: http://lnkd.in/WjNAkq    
    
    
    II-SDV Meeting - Nice: This meeting, the International Information conference on Search, Data Mining and...: http://lnkd.in/fzjMFx    
    
    
    Invitation to exhibit during the next ICIC in Barcelona: http://lnkd.in/ymyYap    
    
    
    Invitation to exhibit during the ICIC 2011 in Barcelona: http://lnkd.in/pYr5br    
    
    
        
    
    
    Invitation to exhibit During the next ICIC 2011 in Barcelona: http://lnkd.in/rGjUqd    
    
    
    II-SDV Meeting 2012 - Nice: http://lnkd.in/6yTQAc    
    
    
    II-SDV Meeting 2012 - Nice: http://lnkd.in/5bCEcU    
    
    
    II-SDV Meeting 2012 - Nice: http://lnkd.in/qn9kwS    
    
    
        
    
    
    just reminds that the absolute deadline for responses to the Call for Papers for the 2010 ICIC meeting in Vienna is 20 FEBRUARY 2010.    
    
    
        
    
    
    ICIC The International Conference for the Information Community: Early Bird rates are available until 1. August 2011, so make sure that you…    
    
    
    will be very busy next days in Düsseldorf and Cologne (meetings, events). He will only be checking email occasionally during that time ;-)    
    
    
    Early booking price for the 2011 ICIC meeting in Barcelona this October expires 1 AUGUST 2011 .... only 3 weeks to go. …http://www.haxel.com    
    
    
    Good news for my ICIC conference: The World Intellectual Property Organization WIPO booked the ICIC exhibition. http://www.haxel.com    
    
    
    The ICIC programme is going extremely well this year; numerically we have
enough papers- at 22 February, which has never happened before    
    
    
    Is waiting at Duesseldorf AirPort. Too much snow in Duesseldorf and London. Global snowing ...    
    
    
    today last chance to register for the ICIC 2011 with early bird registration. We have now more than 100 registrations .…http://www.haxel.com    
    
    
    