@KimptonInNYC  please email me at ed (dot) salvato (at) yahoo #Eventi    
    
    
    @KimptonInNYC  yes heard about this. very exciting! #MarvelComic #X    
    
    
    @goldcat Thanks for following. Love your @twitter handle! Very nice chatting with you briefly. Linda Hirshman just rocks!    
    
    
    @kretchmar those vintage posters are awesome, tx! http://www.flickr.com/photos/boston_public_library/sets/72157624587860480/detail/?page=2 …    
    
    
    @traviskatz Thanks for the mention!  #gogobot #pride #lgbt    
    
    
    @KimptonInNYC It's great #gaypride special for #nyc visitors http://edsalvato.wordpress.com/2012/06/17/eventi-hotel-pride-special/ …    
    
    
    Two More Reasons to Head to Vermont This Year http://wp.me/pGdW4-EE     
    
    
    Visit #Vermont at the end of September for a #gay event two-fer, including #pride and Northern Decadence http://bit.ly/LB3KA7  #Lgbtpride    
    
    
    @gaydays thanks for the Tweet and good luck with #gaydays in #LasVegas! pls subscribe to 1st issue of new ipad mag: http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @nwilkins1972 thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    @Philly_PR_Girl Thanks for following. @koryaversa speaks highly of you    
    
    
    @Tripatini Thanks for following. Love your site! Please sign up for inaugural issue of #iPad #gaytravel magazine http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @meganv_nyc Thanks for following! I share your love of #wine and #food. Oh and #travel:)    
    
    
    @Tripatini what a great opportunity! I will circle back to you when it's available on Apple Newsstand. Thank you (also for signing up!)    
    
    
    @SpinksPhillip Welcome to @Twitter! Can't wait to see your #Tweets. Lots of pix of your art, I hope    
    
    
    @girlslunchout Thanks for following http://GIrlsLUnchOut.com  looks like a great opportunity for women!    
    
    
    @SustEarth Thanks for following. At http://manaboutworld.com  we care about sustainable travel, too.    
    
    
    Tx, U 2! RT @koryaversa: #FF @dnewman @kris_restaurant @GaelleKennedy @philly_pr_girl @FrugalPhillyMom @peternero @southjerseybeth    
    
    
    Thanks, Gaelle and back at you! RT @GaelleKennedy: #FF @edsalvato @koryaversa @jaimebloom @konstantina_liv @cuteandgirlydms @nomissltd    
    
    
    @hobotraveler Thanks for following! Man, you get around:) Love your blog    
    
    
    @HyattPR Thank you 4 following! Be sure 2 follow new gay travel magazine for iPad to launch summer 2012: @MAWTravel http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    Montreal Launches 3rd Annual Queer of the Year Contest http://wp.me/pGdW4-EL     
    
    
    @Montreal announces 3rd annual Queer of the Year contest http://bit.ly/Ns1J8g  #gaytravel @qotycontest    
    
    
    @JoeCool102986 U can get doAC magnet at visitor center on boardwalk or end of expressway while supplies last or DM @VisitAC with yr address    
    
    
    @MSEManagement Thanks for following! Look forward to next year's travel show!    
    
    
    @CarenCotto Thanks for following! Can't believe it'll be the 10th anniversary of @nyttravelshow in 2013! #travel #tourism #gaytravel    
    
    
    @AMagicMommy I look forward to seeing you in AC on July 4. Will be fun!  #howidoac @VisitAC    
    
    
    Me too! RT @PhilaCulturati: Excited to tell the blogosphere about #HowIDoAC when I @visitAC next week for the 4th of July!!!    
    
    
    @TheBearCampNC Thanks for following. I'd love to visit #gayfriendly #asheville, NC    
    
    
    @spoiledtraveler Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @GayPartyList thanks for following! You have a fun website, http://gaypartylist.com !    
    
    
    @jodifur Thanks for following! Look forward to working with you.    
    
    
    @peternero thanks for following! Happy #FF    
    
    
    Back at you! RT @lasfotosproject: happy friday! #ff    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great bloggers! @philaculturati @haelifestyle @jerseyfamilyfun @amagicmommy @capemaymoms @nancy_horn @koryaversa    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @RealMomMedia @buzzmommy @NicolleMK @PWStyle  @CallMeAdamNYC @Tracy_Iglesias @babypop @frugalphillymom    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @RubyDW, @growinblkxican @JoLynneS @jessienuez @techsavymama    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @jodifur @1momof5 @jessicaAPISS @ChescoMoms    
    
    
    Sneak peek of new @moment_factory 3D light and sound show @visitac #howidoac    
    
    
    Hey @KenPanton. Welcome to @twitter. Look forward to following you. Be sure to also follow @MAWTravel, our new #gaytravel mag for #ipad    
    
    
    @KingstonPride Thanks for following! Look forward to your #gaypride next June!    
    
    
    Thanks for the  RT! @Babypop: So excited to @VisitAC for the 4th of July! http://ow.ly/bXAG9  #HowIDoAC #Philly <--- that sounds so fun!    
    
    
    @TheOnlineMom Thanks for following. You have a great site full of useful tips!    
    
    
    @Nancy_Horn look forward to having you here! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @CapeMayMoms Thanks for following! See you in @VisitAC #howIdoAC    
    
    
    @SKIBUMS Thanks for the follow. Love your group:) Please be sure to follow @MAWtravel 1st gay travel mag for iPad http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @Brian_Weston Thanks for the follow! Great to meet you and congrats on @moment_factory 3D light & sounds show. It rocks! @VisitAC #howIdoac    
    
    
    @ryanfitzgibbon Thanks for the follow! Happy 4th and happy travels    
    
    
    Waving hi back! RT @hchybinski: @Babypop @buzzymommy @EdSalvato Waving Hi - have fun!! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    So fun! RT @Babypop: On the trolley with @buzzymommy @EdSalvato #Howidoac pic.twitter.com/GJA6Kefs    
    
    
    @JoLynneS Hi back to you! wish you were here with our great @visitAC blogger team. next time #howidoac    
    
    
    @NicolleMK Always a pleasure to hang with you! so happy to have you here in Atlantic City @visitAC #howidoac    
    
    
    @DonnaReedSteph We are all definitely going to have a drink for you, lady! Wish you were here with our great bloggers #HowIDoAC @visitAC    
    
    
    @DonnaReedSteph Must get you to @visitAC!! let's work on it #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @Jerseyfamilyfun so glad you enjoyed it! #howidoac    
    
    
    @Babypop So great to work with you and see you in person! And fun to see how you do AC! ;) #howIdoAC    
    
    
    @toddcrossnyc thanks for following! great seeing you at the "Victory" book signing. Linda Hirshman is amazing    
    
    
    "Awesome Blog Award"? Me? It's an Honor! http://wp.me/pGdW4-ES     
    
    
    @judiludi Thanks for following... Now, tweet, Judi, tweet! :)    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts Thanks for the follow! Look forward to connect with you    
    
    
    @buzzmommy What a pleasure to meet you in person! Thank you for visiting AC. Look forward to working together again #howidoac    
    
    
    @Babypop I had a lovely time too! Thank you so much for joining    
    
    
    And whan an awesome pic of me  u took! Tx RT @Babypop: @edsalvato Great working with you.  Thanks we had a lovely time. http://ow.ly/i/KuVd     
    
    
    @MarkVogler thanks for the retweet    
    
    
    Ok, well, I just HAVE to reweet this one! :) Thank you RT @DonnaReedSteph: Seriously? @edsalvato is the Travel God.    
    
    
    @NYBookDude Thanks for following! Looks like a cool site you have there    
    
    
    @HIPHOPLIVEGAYS Thanks for following. Cool about @Frank_Ocean http://nyti.ms/NePNtg     
    
    
    sign me up 2:) RT @Tracy_Iglesias:  @PhilaCulturati @visitac @GoldenNuggetAC We definitely should do the AC Wine Fest!    
    
    
    @ClintTheTravele Thanks for the follow. Love your profile! we will soon launch 1st gay travel mag 4 iPad-with lots of great tips @mawtravel    
    
    
    @GoFurtherAfield Thanks 4 follow I like yr site! Pls b sure 2 sign up 2 dwnload inaugural issue of iPad only gay  travel magazine @MAWTravel    
    
    
    @CortneyGalster thanks for following. Nice site!    
    
    
    @Soles4Souls Thanks for following. As a striving responsible traveler, @Soles4Souls sounds like a very cool organization. Congrats!    
    
    
    @dyunghans thanks for subscribing to my list!    
    
    
    @Soles4Souls Some day! Will look at your trip line ups    
    
    
    @VisitBtown Thanks for following! Love your small, progressive town!    
    
    
    @clothes4souls Thanks for following. Any relationship to Soles4souls? :)    
    
    
    @CricridesChamps Merci de me suivre! J'adore Paris!    
    
    
    @DNRshow Thaknks for having me on your show! Fun -- and travel-y ;) -- as always #DNR    
    
    
    @MichaelKretchmar Tonight is the Manhattanhenge -the sunset is exactly aligned with the grid of streets in NYC. http://www.haydenplanetarium.org/resources/starstruck/manhattanhenge/ …    
    
    
    @AntiSocialSmurf Find magnets at AC Visitors Center on the AC expressway & the other is directly in front of Boardwalk Hall on the boardwalk    
    
    
    @avitalb I saw those cool iceberg images in @NYTimes today. stunning    
    
    
    @JamesJetsOften Awesome! We are probably covering @SantaFe in @MAWTravel this fall. Great minds! #LGBT #MAW    
    
    
    @FrugalPhillyMom have a great trip in Atlantic City! @visitAC! #Duality #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @tattoomommie Thanks for following. Love  Jennifer at @JerseyFamilyFun :)    
    
    
    @OKeeffeCountry Thanks for following. Love Georgia O'Keeffe and #NewMexico    
    
    
    @avitalb Thanks for following! Great site. You have a lot of interests!    
    
    
    @Mami2Mommy Thanks for the follow! Great site you have!    
    
    
    @arzayusalvaro thanks for following me on Twitter. I'll be in Buenos Aires later this month:) http://bit.ly/NkmcMX     
    
    
    I'll be in #buenosaires later this month speaking about #lgbttourism. more info here: http://bit.ly/NkmcMX  #gaytravel #LGBTtravel    
    
    
    @JenniferAuer I love @abseconlighthouse. Look for the community garden plot with a rainbow flag.That would be @jeffguaracino 's! #howidoac    
    
    
    Guess Who's Launching a New iPad-only Gay Travel Magazine? http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fc     
    
    
    Check out my latest post. Guess who's launching a new #gaytravel magazine for @iPad only? Hint: me! http://bit.ly/Ofez9n  @EdSalvato    
    
    
    We very proudly support Int'l Gay  & Lesbian Human Rights Commission's Celebration of Courage Mon 7/16.  info: http://bit.ly/NvbJgk  @IGLHRC    
    
    
    Fab Travel Prizes Prizes at IGLHRC Event http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fp     
    
    
    @PR_in_Victoria Thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    Was just thinking the same! RT @PaulineFrommer: OMG, its almost noon & I've gotten nothing done yet. Curse ye Twitterverse!    
    
    
    So happy to help out! RT @IGLHRC: Thanks @MAWtravel and @edsalvato for your generous support! #CelebrateCourage    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents #FF @TwittBen @SteeleTravel @TravelingIQ @JamesEmtage @JDvanZyl_UK @JeffGuaracino @LuxTravel    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents #FF@SanCarlosPatch @LDFarah @DRMSiebert @LeaveYrDailyHell @OutAdventures @FlyBoyVancouver    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents @JamesEmtage @TravisFerland @RyanCHaynes @JonJonMak    
    
    
    @Babypop I miss you and the rest of the blogger team! #howIdoAC    
    
    
    Same to you! RT @Tracy_Iglesias: ⒻⓄⓁⓁⓄⓌ Friday! @philZENdia @Caringmom @tea4two20 @lifeonprint @latinaprpro #llblog @ElianneRamos #latism    
    
    
    @PR_in_Victoria I'm heading to #Provincetown end of this week for some much needed R&R; staying at the fab @princealbertpt @PtownTourism    
    
    
    @MotivadaLatina Thank you for following! Great tweets and re-tweets you have    
    
    
    @joeyfortman Thanks so much for the retweet! :) #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @MomsOnTheSpot thakns for the re-tweet! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    Broadway Queen Alert: Linda Eder In Provincetown August 13-14 http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fu     
    
    
    Heading to #Provincetown for Carnival week? Check out @LindaEder singing for 2 nights at the @OnlyAtTheCrown Info: http://bit.ly/NfeBUn     
    
    
    @MomsThoughts thanks for the retweet. @LindaEder just rocks!    
    
    
    @WhatsThatSmell Thanks for the follow. Love your Twitter handle name:)    
    
    
    @Havenlust Thank you for the follow!    
    
    
    @hospitality_law Thanks for the follow. Cool site with great info!    
    
    
    @festivy Thank you for following! happy #FF    
    
    
    @kennypate Funny you should ask. I'm heading to S. America tomorrow. Will have plenty of suggestions. Pls email me via http://edsalvato.com     
    
    
    @nolaghost Thanks for the follow. Love #newOrleans. Will have to check out your tour next time I'm there    
    
    
    Heading to #BuenosAires tomorrow for the 5th annual #LGBTtravel conference by @gnetwork360    
    
    
    Our editor in chief @EdSalvato is heading to #BuenosAires tomorrow for the 5th annual #LGBTtravel conference by @gnetwork360    
    
    
    I'm heading to @BuenosAires to speak at the 5th annual conference on #LGBTTravel and marketing Info: http://on.fb.me/QeTPG5     
    
    
    @kretchmar Gracias, señor! See you after the conference ... in August. #LGBTTravel    
    
    
    @janinadpvrahman Thanks for following. I read through your posts ... great stuff!    
    
    
    @57Onesie Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @SeeAtlanticCity Thanks for the follow. I was in AC a couple of weeks ago. Love it! #HowIdoAC:)    
    
    
    @grattonboy Thanks for the follow. Been following your Tweets -- great stuff!    
    
    
    @alfredo_buegay and what about me? I'm here to @GNetwork360! :) Look foward to seeing you!    
    
    
    In #BuenosAires at @PanamericanoBA #hotel getting ready for the @GNetwork360 5th annual #LGBTTravel conference. @IGLTA is in the house, too    
    
    
    @visitoakland Thanks for following. Love Oakland:)    
    
    
    @MGWargentina really happy to be here.    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts love it here. Mild winter. thanks for the retweet.    
    
    
    Mostly a great visit to #buenosaires for @gnetwork360 #lgbttravel conference. I conducted two successful talks and hope 3rd's the charm 2day    
    
    
    @konaboys this is so awesome. Proud to be on your sandy beach... though I'd prefer to personally be there! :)    
    
    
    @rangels oi from New York. Nice to connect with you here, too.    
    
    
    @rangels Beijos e abraços from New York! Everyone here wants to know: When is @rangels going to visit us!!? :) xo    
    
    
    @rangels New York won't know what hit it… hurricane Rangels! :)    
    
    
    #webstagram - @doac http://web.stagram.com/p/253031925681528133_38936318 … via @webstagram    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts thanks for the retweet. Just learning how to play with @instagram. fun! #howIdoac :) @doac @webstagram    
    
    
    In #AtlanticCity 2 c @NikWallenda's incredible stunt, walking 1500 ft, 100 ft above the beach. Live webcast 3-330pm: http://bit.ly/TjN4R8     
    
    
    @YwalkWhenUcnFLY Same! look forward to meeting you and seeing @NikWallenda perform his incredible stunt. #howIdoac    
    
    
    @NikWallenda is climbing up there for his 1500-ft walk?! Yep! Enjoying this stunt is #howidoac    
    
    
    Download yr free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel magazine built for iPad by founders of OUT&ABOUT  http://bit.ly/NnFwst  @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @xomayasade @EdSalvato is ecstatic with your @NikWallenda Tweets! You rock!    
    
    
    Happy #FF RT @LuxuryDreamer: @mjdwarner @edsalvato @eliana_crespo @encounterstravl @GroupG3 @GlammysNYC @GayRiviera @NYTmag @NY1weather    
    
    
    Happy #FF @JenniferAuer @AMagicMommy @YwalkWhenUcnFLY @NicolleMK @culturejaunt @Jerseyfamilyfun @visitac @nikwallenda @jeffguaracino    
    
    
    Thanks @travelwithval. Pls use this link to download: http://bit.ly/OaYTdu  RT free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel mag built 4 iPad    
    
    
    @xomayasade  check out http://on.fb.me/MJqRHB  and tag yourself!    
    
    
    @outadventures thanks for the retweet! Have you downloaded yours yet? Would love to get your feedback! @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Same to you! Interesting, good people! @kretchmar @lindafrankbooks @ivazg @morewomen2012 @travisgster @daverapps @lkhere    
    
    
    Thanks for the RT :) @edsalvato: Download free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel magazine built 4 iPad http://bit.ly/NnFwst  @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @rangels I got your email. Very exciting stuff! You are THE BEST @MAWTravel correspondent:) Will get back to you.    
    
    
    Thank u! RT @EdWetschler: Congrats @EdSalvato, @billykolber on launch of #gaytravel mag ManAboutWorld @MAWtravel http://manaboutworld.com/     
    
    
    @travelsofadam thanks for your retweet about @MAWtravel!    
    
    
    Thanks again for your support! @Tripatini @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Thank you for your support of @MAWtravel! @d_dpr    
    
    
    @cunardline I'm looking forward 2 my cruise 8/28 from NYC but I'm having the hardest time finding the boarding time/ino on your site. help?    
    
    
    The Undisputed Queen of the High Seas to Visit New York http://wp.me/pGdW4-FE     
    
    
    The Undisputed Queen of the High Seas to Visit New York and I'll be there! http://wp.me/pGdW4-FE  via @edsalvato    
    
    
    @cunardline Thank you. Be sure to follow me here and at @MAWTravel. I'm sure to Tweet before, during and after my trip. Looking forward!    
    
    
    a fantastic surf and turf meal with an '80s theme (homemade tater tots!) in honor of @rockofages at @CaesarsAC #howidoac    
    
    
    Little Debbie themed (also very '80s) desert also at Nero's Restaurant. @CaesarsAC #howidoac    
    
    
    @rockofages at Circus Maximus @CaesarsAC ... Highlight if a rocking '80s themed night #howidoac    
    
    
    Great shout out about @MAWtravel in @PhilaGayNews by #gaytravel #journalist @JeffGuaracino http://bit.ly/NMFT02  thank you!    
    
    
    A rousing scene from @RockofAges @CaesarsAC. Seeing a 2.75-hour #broadway #show? That's #howIdoAC! http://ow.ly/i/Rg9g     
    
    
    @MomsThoughts thank you for continued support! @edsalvato @PhilaGayNews @JeffGuaracino    
    
    
    pre-FF. One of my favorite people in the Twitterverse: @momsthoughts:)    
    
    
    @CoopersChewToy hi -- let me find out…and get back to you about restaurant recos in Istanbul    
    
    
    @CoopersChewToy please rate us in the App store! Tx! I have #istanbul #gaytravel recommendations. please email me at ed.salvato@yahoo.com    
    
    
    Cool pic by @edsalvato RT @VisitAC: "Thunder Over the Boardwalk" provides Tweeters great pix! #ACAirshow #howIdoAC http://ow.ly/i/Rj7V     
    
    
    Ok so someone explain why local and regional clunker trains are whizzing by this suddenly lumbering @acela? #lifeintheslowlane    
    
    
    Nice piece on ManAboutWorld by @WindyCityTimes1 in Chicago. http://bit.ly/N9Fbcq     
    
    
    @theMISTERAPP thanks for the Tweet about @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @YwalkWhenUcnFLY I would love to go see @ChaplinBway with you. I won't be free till after 9/6. Break a leg!    
    
    
    Vermont, Gay Pride, Foliage and A Whole Lot of Food September 21-22 http://wp.me/pGdW4-FT     
    
    
    @Kitty_Ink Great pic! :)    
    
    
    @Kitty_Ink haha great subject rather:)    
    
    
    @Kitty_Ink i know, I love it too. it's fun    
    
    
    Happy #FF to @MAWTravel Global Correspondents @DRMSiebert @leavyrdailyhell @OutAdventures @FlyBoyVancouver @TravisFerland @RyanCHaynes    
    
    
    Happy #FF to @MAWTravel Global Correspondents @TwittBen @SteeleTravel @TravelingIQ @JamesEmtage @JDvanZyl_UK @JeffGuaracino    
    
    
    Happy #FF to @MAWTravel Global Correspondents @PaulHeney @LuxTravel @JonJonMak @SanCarlosPatch @LDFarah @Rangels    
    
    
    Way to kick off fab media weekend visit to @theoutnyc: deep tissue massage by Savas at hotel spa    
    
    
    Love the personalized welcome tv/computer screen set up upon check-in @theoutnyc http://twitpic.com/anojhg     
    
    
    The executive at @theoutnyc    
    
    
    With picture: the executive team at @theoutnyc http://twitpic.com/anp1ti     
    
    
    David Lopez shows the Great Lawn @theoutnyc http://twitpic.com/anp8yd     
    
    
    Handsome Franco serving at media reception  http://twitpic.com/anp9f3     
    
    
    Loving our visit to @THEOUTNYC, an urban #gay #resort in #nyc-like a cruise ship on land with great service and relaxed fellow "passengers"    
    
    
    @nickwmay thanks for following… sorry I missed you at the @THEOUTNYC … I loved it too. Just terrific    
    
    
    My First Transatlantic Crossing, on the Queen Mary 2 http://wp.me/pGdW4-FY     
    
    
    Our editor @edsalvato: My First Transatlantic Crossing, on the Queen Mary 2 http://wp.me/pGdW4-FY  @cunardline #QM2    
    
    
    @theMISTERAPP Thanks for all your Tweets and support! We appreciate it @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Great post; thank u! RT @JoLynneS: by @chilihead --> 4 Ways to Write Engaging Updates on Facebook http://bit.ly/Oq0Z4y  @blogworld    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts Sorry I missed your Tweet re: an Atlantic City beach stay. I love @RevelResorts and check out http://www.acsurfschool.com/     
    
    
    @MomsThoughts You are welcome. It's a great resort; lots for you and your teen children. A nice upscale but relaxed choise.    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts Oh and Madonna's coming to @visitAc in September… maybe something to seek out or avoid depending on your view:)    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts me too! I'll be front and center at that concert. https://atlanticcitynj.com/visitors/thingstodo/madonna.aspx … it is #howIdoAC    
    
    
    @nickwmay great feature on @THEOUTNYC !    
    
    
    The first review of @MAWtravel en français ! Great review of in MyGayTrip/Tetu http://bit.ly/UrZ6sn  @tetumag @MyGayTrip    
    
    
    Athens, Greece: September is a Great Time to Visit http://wp.me/pGdW4-G5     
    
    
    @MomsThoughts I love Athens, too!    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts unfortunately I don't think my colleague took many. If he does, I'll post/tweet them    
    
    
    It's not just a pretty smell! Gay Cologne: http://manaboutworld.com/?p=728  by our very own @BillyKolber @MAWTravel    
    
    
    A very "#harrypotter" image! Check out ManAboutWorld Magazine October Cover Sneak Peak: http://youtu.be/H1lb9DP5Cjk  via @youtube @MAWTravel    
    
    
    @luxury__travel Thanks for following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    Meet Our Newest Correspondent: Carlos Melia, Bon Vivant: http://manaboutworld.com/?p=736  @carlosmelia #gaytravel @mawtravel    
    
    
    Our handsome Sao Paulo-based Global Correspondent @Rangels went to #Colombia. Here's his photo report http://bit.ly/PVpvA8  #gaytravel    
    
    
    @rangels Hope to get more photo-updates from your future travels (or even from São Paulo)!    
    
    
    @earthXplorer Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    I'll be speaking at #destacc on Sep 24th. If you sign up now, you can still get an Early Bird ticket: http://bit.ly/RSimzE  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Speaking at #destacc on Sep 24th along with a lot of other interesting speakers. For more information: http://bit.ly/RSiz5O  #gaytravel    
    
    
    @mrpatrickduffy I've stayed there but always up for staying again :) @THEOUTNYC    
    
    
    Beautiful day in Atlantic City &1st stay at fabulous @borgataac to see #madonna. #howidoac    
    
    
    thanks! RT @RichardLongNYC: @thedeludedfool @MAWtravel @littlemissnonam @Shaddownemesis @aallemanwrites @LascomSolutions Have a Fab FF!    
    
    
    Hard to believe @BoardwalkHall can be transformed in a matter of hours to accommodate #madonna's concert. #howIdoac pic.twitter.com/PpRx3vQL    
    
    
    LGBT Hotel Search Website Launches http://wp.me/pGdW4-Gb     
    
    
    Atlantic City, The Water Club at Borgata and Madonna: A Great Combination http://wp.me/pGdW4-Gg     
    
    
    A warm sunny afternoon on the Boardwalk. So much going on.  http://twitpic.com/aulala  #howidoac @VisitAC    
    
    
    Fun photo: first-time Boardwalk visitors @caradactyl and @azygous60610 #howidoac    
    
    
    Our very own happy hour: @Azygous60610 got a Loosely Goose, @caradactyl has a sangria #howidoac http://twitpic.com/aultrq  @revel resorts    
    
    
    "@JeffGuaracino: @WolfgangBuzz @BorgataAC with @LizaPeanut and @edsalvato where r u and that's #howidoac"    
    
    
    Amazing black sea bass en croute by @ChefAram @BorgataAC #wpag http://twitpic.com/aunnz3  #howidoac    
    
    
    Getting ready to watch #duality light show @boardwalkhall #howidoac http://twitpic.com/av1jt9     
    
    
    @RASKTravel So glad you joined the @MAWTravel Global Correspondent team! Find us lots of great #gaytravel info in Tel Aviv and beyond :)    
    
    
    Meet ManAboutWorld's newest Global Correspondent http://manaboutworld.com/?p=789  @RASKTravel #gaytravel    
    
    
    Hear our friend Carl Sandler @daddyhunt live today on HuffPost http://live.huffingtonpost.com/r/segment/50520c232b8c2a3034000029 …    
    
    
    @ChianCheng Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    @TylerAMoyer Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    @Gayconnector Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    @garybembridge Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    @roniweiss Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P  & happy #FF #gaytravel    
    
    
    The 51 Gayest Hotels in NYC http://bit.ly/UhNq9N  #NYC #gaytravel #hotels @MAWtravel    
    
    
    The 51 Gayest Hotels in NYC http://bit.ly/UhNq9N  #NYC #gaytravel #hotels @MAWtravel    
    
    
    The 51 Gayest Hotels in NYC http://bit.ly/UhNq9N  #NYC #gaytravel #hotels @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @JamesJetsOften @MAWtravel hello! I'll be in #SanFrancisco next week, 9/27-10/1. I'm speaking at @OTMEvent r u also? Are you around?    
    
    
    New York's Best Vegetarian Restaurants: http://manaboutworld.com/?p=815  @MawTravel #gaytravel #NYC #vegetarian    
    
    
    @JamesJetsOften Hi James, I just emailed you. Looking forward to meeting! @otmevent    
    
    
    New York’s Best Vegetarian Restaurants http://wp.me/pGdW4-Gl     
    
    
    Thanks, Ivan! RT @TravelingIQ: The Week in #Travel: http://wp.me/pLV5i-1vm   via @Forbes @NYDailyNews @CarlosMelia @Landlopers @MAWtravel    
    
    
    sam 2 u! RT @carlosmelia: “@jjkeyes: #FF fab writers@joelovesyou @TravelingIQ @thesarahrose @MisterPaulHagen @jeffmkatz @theduanewells”    
    
    
    thanks! RT @jjkeyes: #FF fab writers @carlosmelia @joelovesyou @TravelingIQ @thesarahrose @MisterPaulHagen @jeffmkatz @theduanewells    
    
    
    same 2 u! RT  #FollowFriday @danalyzed @jjkeyes @lucascorvatta @TheDuaneWells @GirlsthatRoam @girlports @jimawerner #gaytravel #lgbt #gay    
    
    
    @sree great presentation on #socialmedia #sreetips destination accelerator in #nyc    
    
    
    Thank you @firstpostin for linking to our new #gaytravel #magazine built for #ipad only! http://bit.ly/RQTwBP  @mawtravel    
    
    
    Check out a selection of our top gay-friendly restaurants in Chelsea, NYC from inaugural issue. http://bit.ly/VDeuCO  #gaytravel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @Portugal_Travel Great seeing you at the destination accelerator event!    
    
    
    In #sanfrancisco with @jamesmowdy great social media brainstorm http://twitpic.com/aywqn4     
    
    
    "Best #burger in town" according to the handsome Jard pictured here at http://on.fb.me/NU0gwA  @burrittroom #sanfrancisco #gaytravel    
    
    
    San Francisco Packs In Early Fall Events http://wp.me/pGdW4-Gq     
    
    
    Lots happening in #sanfrancisco next week http://bit.ly/TJkmNM  @onlyinsf #gaytravel    
    
    
    thanks! RT @SFTravel: @JamesJetsOften @edsalvato @MAWtravel @OTMEvent Nice pic!    
    
    
    Come see me at the SF Travel Show this wend Sat 2pm, Sun 1:30 speaking about #lgbttravel-tix at http://bit.ly/NVo8zZ  $5 off w/ code trade3    
    
    
    Great views from 8 overlooks @presidiosf. Here #goldengate bridge  http://twitpic.com/az86hb     
    
    
    .@JamesJetsOften not too bad up here. My room  @InnatPresidio has a fireplace and complimentary wine hour :) @presidiosf @OTMEvent    
    
    
    Print out this Tweet for FREE acces to SF Travel Show this wkend & see me Sat 2pm, Sun 1:30 speaking about #lgbttravel-tix @OTMEvent    
    
    
    yes! RT @Kaliido: @paulheney hi there : ) is http://ManAboutWorld.com  a gay friendly website?    
    
    
    Print out this Tweet for FREE acces to SF Travel Show this wkend & see me Sat 2pm, Sun 1:30 speaking about #lgbttravel-tix @OTMEvent    
    
    
    San Francisco LGBT Travel Show PDF http://wp.me/pGdW4-Gx     
    
    
    My #lgbttravel talk went well. Here's a pic attached. I'm speaking Sun 130pm. Come one, come all! #gaytravel @otmevent pic.twitter.com/pwAmZGek    
    
    
    Hot #Braziians tease you with our soon-to-be-launched October issue on #Rio and other #beaches #gaytravel    
    
    
    .@Kwaninou please email me at ed at http://manaboutworld.com  with your questions. thanks @paulheney #japan    
    
    
    .@jeffdupre Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P . Oct issue available soon!    
    
    
    @will_305TID Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P . Oct issue available soon!    
    
    
    @holidaycars Tx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P . Oct issue available soon!    
    
    
    @gaytravelprosTx 4 following! Be sure to download our inaugural issue (free!) for #iPad only: http://bit.ly/OaMh6P . Oct issue available!    
    
    
    Congrats @MAWTravel correspondent John Clifford @LuxTravel named to World's Top #TravelAgents by @TravlandLeisure http://bit.ly/PUnvmv     
    
    
    We appreciate all your hard work and GREAT recommendations! RT @LuxTravel: @edsalvato @MAWtravel @TravlandLeisure Much appreciated Ed.    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's October Issue Is Now Available http://wp.me/pGdW4-GD     
    
    
    Our October issue is available for download via the AppStore. http://bit.ly/WXuL6b  #gaytravel #iPad    
    
    
    thank you! RT @michaelluongo: RT @edsalvato: ManAboutWorld's October Issue Is Now Available http://wp.me/pGdW4-GD     
    
    
    It was fun putting it together. RT @michaelluongo: @edsalvato And thank you for a fab October..the Brazil boys caught my eye..............    
    
    
    I'm on the radio in New Jersey in a little while #pinkyac    
    
    
    I'll let you know when you can send your travel questions to #pinkyac #howIdoAC    
    
    
    same 2 u:) RT @LuxTravel: Big LGBT Travel #ff recommendation to gay travelers check out @MAWTravel by @EdSalvato + @BillyKolber    
    
    
    Meet our newest Global Correspondent Juan Carlos Medina Gedler http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=966  @JCMGedler @MAWTravel #gaytravel    
    
    
    Common sensical but gr8 advice. Tx! RT @jessienuez: STOP! Why They’ll Unlike You If You Post That http://dlvr.it/2LF4FN  #socialmedia #news    
    
    
    Meet our newest ManAboutWorld Global Correspondent Adam Groffman http://www.manaboutworld.com/?portfolio=adam-groffman … @travelsofadam    
    
    
    Jake Gyllenhaal in A Show in New York City Show http://wp.me/pGdW4-GI     
    
    
    @ElizabethNorton Hello -- sorry, no experience with http://nytix.com . Let me know how you find it if you use it… and congrats!!:)    
    
    
    @PozSeaLance Global Correspondents help the editors of ManAboutWorld with updates from destinations around the blogs @mawtravel @paulheney    
    
    
    Split for Croatia on Out Adventures First Land And Sea Trip http://wp.me/pGdW4-GO     
    
    
    @ElizabethNorton i like that line too; it's exciting in a way but good that you got your tix ahead of time.    
    
    
    By early November RT @HafaRamon:- When does the Costa Rica http://ManAboutWorld.com  piece come out?  (Hoping to get to Manuel Antonio soon.)    
    
    
    @ElizabethNorton Wow! congrats (totally understand:)    
    
    
    We welcome our newest ManAboutWorld Global Correspondent Miles Mitchinson (yes`perfect name!) @MAWtravel @DetoursTravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=986     
    
    
    @kontrary Hi- I downloaded "immersion" and it's mostly great but I can't get gallery to work. Checked your site but no help. Any tips?    
    
    
    Contemplating the new #ipad #mini? UR covered! ManAboutWorld magazine supports the new platform. Happy (mini) travels! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=992     
    
    
    Gay Getaways: 6 Great Trips to Take Right Now http://huff.to/QG3NgP  via @HuffPostGay    
    
    
    @GraphPaperPress Idid and they are helping. Thank you @graphpaperpress    
    
    
    @GraphPaperPress I'll share a link once it's live (embargoed for a couple more weeks) …it's looking good!    
    
    
    Discovering Columbus In Your Living Room http://wp.me/pGdW4-GT     
    
    
    Christopher Columbus is now receiving visitors in his (newly built) living room in #newyork http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=997     
    
    
    Spooky travel! Our weekly travel story round up #halloween edition courtesy @TravelingIQ #gaytravel #LGBT    
    
    
    Hot Guys In New Ft. Lauderdale Commercial http://wp.me/pGdW4-GX     
    
    
    Great new mainstream #FtLauderdale ad features #gay and #lesbian travelers. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271  @visitlauderdale #lgbt traveler    
    
    
    Sandy Cam Live Shots From NY Times Building http://wp.me/pGdW4-H5     
    
    
    @GenevieveGrdina I know, right? Lots of live feeds but this seems in the thick of it. #sandy http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1013     
    
    
    Which Gay Philly 'Hood Is Gay-Tastic? Lady Gaga Tix In The Balance http://wp.me/pGdW4-Hb     
    
    
    Which Gay Philly 'Hood Is Gay-Tastic? Lady Gaga Tix In The Balance http://wp.me/pGdW4-Hb  @visitphilly #philadelphia @kimpton    
    
    
    @visitphilly I'm well. Going to escape @NYC to #philly this weekend for stay at the new #hotel Monaco Philadelphia @kimpton @KimptonInPHL    
    
    
    TRAVEL WEEKLY ROUNDUP BY TRAVELINGIQ http://wp.me/pGdW4-Hg     
    
    
    Hotel Monaco Philadelphia: Fox Named It One of Top 10 Hotels http://wp.me/pGdW4-Hn     
    
    
    I recently stayed at the #hotel #Monaco #Philadelphia. Here is my report: http://bit.ly/Qi9IMq  @KimptonInPHL @visitphilly    
    
    
    I recently visited the new #hotel #Monaco #Philadelphia, as see in @FoxNews http://bit.ly/Qi9IMq  @kimptoninPHL    
    
    
    Vote! RT @TravelingIQ: Hard Rock Hotels are keeping you inspired this Election Day with a free "Rock the Vote" playlist http://fb.me/1LjsigNjv     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's November issue is now available for download! Explore San Francisco, Costa Rica, Hong Kong, Santa Fe & more #gaytravel    
    
    
    Thanks for the Tweet @carlosmelia!    
    
    
    @JenniferAuer Great to see you! SOrry couldn't talk. Crazy fun day @ARTLANTIC    
    
    
    Travel Weekly Roundup by TravelingIQ http://wp.me/pGdW4-HB     
    
    
    Amy &#38; Freddy, Gay-Popular Duo, Plays OUT NYC's XL Friday, Nov. 30 http://wp.me/pGdW4-HF     
    
    
    Amy & Freddy amazing #gay popular #duet plays @THEOUTNYC's XL cabaret Friday, November 30 for one night only http://bit.ly/TBhMCC  #NYC    
    
    
    Photo: Monthly #gay-popular party in #Thailand. Hot and shirtless. http://bit.ly/UDfOD5  #gaytravel    
    
    
    .@Queertrip Tx for following. Get yr free trial membership of ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    .@lee_byron Tx for following. Get yr free trial membership of ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    .@Ted_Gaela Tx for following. Get yr free trial membership of ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    .@Thomas7sea Tx for following. Get yr free trial membership of ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    .@OUTandes Tx for following. Get yr free trial membership of ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    Doing research on #Auckland, NZ 4 #gaytravel article; looking for recommendations 4 hotels, restaurants, bars. Can anyone help?    
    
    
    .@RonnieDAmico Tx for following and subscribing to ManAboutWorld-1st gay travel magazine for the iPad. http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    Upside Down Christmas At Boston's Liberty Hotel http://wp.me/pGdW4-HJ     
    
    
    Will do, tx! RT @PhinneyNYC: @edsalvato Just saw a special pull out in @TimeOutNewYork on #AtlanticCity @DoAC  Thought of you. Snag it.    
    
    
    Park City, UT For The Non-Skier (Hint: Lots To Do) http://wp.me/pGdW4-HO     
    
    
    Thanks! RT @jbart39: Park City, UT For The Non-Skier (Hint: Lots To Do) http://wp.me/pGdW4-HO  via @edsalvato    
    
    
    Thanks! U joining? RT @JamesJetsOften: .  “@BrandUSA: Details on joining our public board of directors meeting 11/29 http://ow.ly/fsclO .”    
    
    
    can't make it but lemme know how it goesRT @JamesJetsOften: .@edsalvato @brandusa ...definitely inclined, could be fun!    
    
    
    Weekly Travel Roundup By TravelingIQ http://wp.me/pGdW4-HU     
    
    
    .@Mdjco Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of 1st gay travel magazine for iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    Philadelphia's Mummers Parade Becomes A Drag http://wp.me/pGdW4-HY     
    
    
    A shirtless #PrinceHarry and more in this week's #gaytravel roundup by @MAWtravel  correspondent @TravelingIQ #London http://bit.ly/Re9A1p     
    
    
    Weekly Travel Roundup By TravelingIQ http://wp.me/pGdW4-I6     
    
    
    Hotel Week NYC, January 4-20, Features Some Great Prices: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1090     
    
    
    haha @JamesJetsOften I have to confess I wouldn't have recognized her but my friend did and I got caught up. She's kinda hot :)    
    
    
    Don't worry, I'll toast you! ;) … see you in #ftlauderdale Safe travels    
    
    
    @gerrardpanahon Hence the cheap prices! Tho it's been unseasonably warm. You can also find ways to warm up in NYC - it's an 'indoor' city:)    
    
    
    @gerrardpanahon I love http://Kayak.com  for inexpensive airfare and they have a new iPhone app, too.    
    
    
    OMG. I read that piece and got a panic attack from his description of the woman skier being caught in the avalanche! @kretchmar @nytimes    
    
    
    "Churches for gays abound in Brazil" says @YahooBR http://bit.ly/10oW8KC  @yahoo #lgbt #gaytravel    
    
    
    .tsapre bear system ever!    
    
    
    . @kretchmar do you use @tsapre? Best government system EVER. Whisks u thru security computer in bag, belt and shoes on    
    
    
    .@TSA I love TSA-Pre. It is a terrific system. It's bringing the joy back to traveling for this frequent flyer. #tsapre    
    
    
    See ManAboutWorld At NY Times Travel Show http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ie     
    
    
    Come see @MAWtravel editor in chief and an illustrious panel of #gay and #lesbian #travel writers @NYTTravelShow 1/19 http://bit.ly/WJRrEd     
    
    
    Hey back! happy new year 2 u 2! RT @janetwhitehead: @edsalvato hey Ed checking in to say hi  and happy new year! We should talk soon.    
    
    
    .@janetwhitehead My new venture: Claim free trial subscription of gay travel magazine for iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @OutAdventurers Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of gay travel magazine for iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    tx! RT @TravelGov: #FF more #travel experts with us #NYTTravelShow @sethkugel @edsalvato @Merryn1@don_george . http://nyttravelshow.com     
    
    
    @toddcrossnyc thanks!    
    
    
    .@DifficultNerd Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of gay travel magazine for iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @janetwhitehead good morning. Feel free to email me so we can figure out a good time to talk-bsure to lemme know what you'd like 2 discuss    
    
    
    .@VacationAngel Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@ejurne Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@MsclPatrol Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@bradycreel Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@CristinaCotto Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@kretchmar @Travisgster @ruhanirabin  that was fun! 25K    
    
    
    .@MsclPatrol Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@xlnightclub Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@thestirrerau Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Love the new look and feel of @HETravel (Hanns Ebensten) #gay #travel experts. http://hetravel.com/     
    
    
    We rated Ft. Lauderdale's 19 gay guesthouses for the first time in 10 years. Discover the best and the rest! http://bit.ly/U4tUnh  #gaytravel    
    
    
    thanks! RT @NinaScim: Congrats on the article @edsalvato! http://newsle.com/article/0/55958405/ … via @newsle    
    
    
    Very cool! RT @JamesJetsOften: .@Harrods nice call to action. cc: @edsalvato. ;-) https://twitter.com/harrods/status/297761379509739521 … #Ipad #digital #media    
    
    
    Great info n @MAWtravel's Jan/Feb issue. Thanks! RT @ErnestoOrsetti: @visitlauderdale @edsalvato mmmm sound so interesting!!!    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @mygaytravels: Convents to Bathhouses: Ft. Lauderdale’s Gay Resorts

http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1260  http://fb.me/UBubVlKd     
    
    
    Hi. I like alexander's guesthouse and RT @NinaScim: friend is planning a wedding in Key West next Spring. Have any hotel recommendations?    
    
    
    and marquesa and casa marina RT @NinaScim: friend is planning a wedding in Key West next Spring. Have any hotel recommendations?    
    
    
    Great speakers and energy at @IGLTAFoundation symposium on global #lgbt #travel    
    
    
    Yolanda Perdomo discussed trends and growth in global #tourism @igltafoundation @iglta    
    
    
    #thailand tourism enthusiastically markets to the #lgbt market @Igltafoundation symposium on global #lgbt travel http://twitpic.com/c16joo     
    
    
    Mayor Bloomberg: value of Lgbt sector visiting $259m in 1st year  #lgbt market @Igltafoundation symposium on global #lgbt travel    
    
    
    So great! RT @LizaPeanut:! RT “@bbrennan88: Really fun night out w/ @LizaPeanut & @jeffguaracino. Glad we finally made it happen #DoAC”    
    
    
    Key West is a great choice! RT @NinaScim: They have never been but want a destination wedding in US with the feeling of the Caribbean.    
    
    
    Hello @janetwhitehead … let me know what you have in mind re: technology. Best via email then can forward to publisher. Best Ed @mawtravel    
    
    
    Convent or Bathhouse? Fort Lauderdale's Gay Resorts http://huff.to/12uoXq1  via @HuffPostGay    
    
    
    .@uwernjong Thanks for following Uwern! If you have an iPad, claim yr free trial subscription at http://bit.ly/VujnRs     
    
    
    .@JeffTitelius Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Rio's Mardi Gras Was Hot and We Were There: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1350     
    
    
    @Twin_Travel Belated happy Valentine's Day to you, too and happy Twin Travels:)    
    
    
    Heading to Key West? Here's the lowdown on their new airport (and the airlines serving it) http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1373  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Dispatch from West Sumatra by @mawtravel correspondent Louise Rafkin. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1387  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Dispatches: Sunset at Bungas Beach, West Sumatra http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ij     
    
    
    Cheers to London's New Detective Agency-cum-New-Fangled Speakeasy http://wp.me/pGdW4-In     
    
    
    Get a clue! (And a drink) at London's new speakeasy-cum-detective agency. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1400  #london #gaytravel    
    
    
    Thanks for retweeting our "gay dads" travel piece! @benpatrick90069 @Twin_Travel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    I'm quoted in this @BBC_travel piece "US officials put a focus on LGBT travelers" http://bit.ly/XrUMJC  #gaytravel @TravelGov    
    
    
    Trave/love to you all! @danalyzed @joelovesyou @jjkeyes @MisterPaulHagen @jeffmkatz @TheDuaneWells @Merryn1 @carlosmelia    
    
    
    @janetwhitehead I believe anyone who's looking at your feed would be able to see it.    
    
    
    @janetwhitehead others can see it. if you want to direct message me, you can do that with D I believe.    
    
    
    Bungee jumping South Africa. Just another day on the beat for our correspondents @MAWtravel http://bit.ly/XBK4QV  pic.twitter.com/Dko2laqNxy    
    
    
    Our Global Correspondent @JeffGuaracino went to Rome. Then a scandal erupted. Coincidence? You decide! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271#  #gaytravel    
    
    
    .@j25borg Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@SaintlyNYC Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription of #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Congrats to @MAWtravel correspondent Adam Groffman @travelsofadam on his @bloggies win! #travel    
    
    
    wish I could b there RT @koryaversa: 2013 flower show not same w/o friends 2 walk around w/ @FrugalPhillyMom @iPhillyChitChat @CultureJaunt    
    
    
    "Taking travel at the speed of kids" #gaydads #gaytravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271#  @paulheney @twin_travel    
    
    
    Get ready for Winter Party Festival 20 March 6-11 http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1461  @winter_party #gaytravel @miamiandbeaches    
    
    
    Winter Party Festival 20 Launches March 6 http://wp.me/pGdW4-Iu     
    
    
    Winter Party Festival 20 Launches March 6: And this is just a fraction of the crowd.
For those ne... http://bit.ly/ZTn2Y7  #gay #travel    
    
    
    .@JuanPenalosa look forward to your #Bermuda tips! Thank you. @BillyKolber @MAWtravel    
    
    
    The 6 (REAL) ways to tell if your hotel is gay friendly. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1471  @MAWtravel @BillyKolber #gaytravel #gayfriendly #lgbttravel    
    
    
    Rain, snow and wind in the Northeast. Looking forward to @winter_party! @miamiandbeaches #lgbttravel @mawtravel #needsun    
    
    
    Traveling #gaydads: Sin-free #LasVegas: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1484#  @twin_travel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Sin-Free Las Vegas http://wp.me/pGdW4-Iz     
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Sin-Free Las Vegas: These two dads are about to smooch!
¡Viva el Romance, Viv... http://bit.ly/10bHUdl  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Heading to #LasVegas with #kids? Click here first: http://bit.ly/WME5bO  #gaydads #travelingwithkids @MAWtravel @LVCVA @Vegas    
    
    
    Excited to be a media partner with @NYtravfest. Buy your tickets here: http://bitly.com/NYTF2013  #NYTF    
    
    
    I need me a little sun! Have you seen the jan/feb issue of ManAboutWorld? Great Miami coverage @MiamiandBeaches @MAWtravel @winter_party    
    
    
    Find out more information on @NYtravfest here: http://nytravfest.com  #NYTF    
    
    
    Thanks for the great tour. Love the property. @TheBetsyHotel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Such a great event! RT @MAWtravel: Celebrating 20 years of partying with a purpose @winter_party @TheTaskForce    
    
    
    Great time at @WInter_party in @Miamiandbeaches. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271#  #gaytravel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    WInter Party: All Kinds of Beautiful http://wp.me/pGdW4-IE     
    
    
    Winter Party: All Kinds of Beautiful: Typo?
Winter Party 20, the National Gay and Lesbian Task Fo... http://bit.ly/ZBvoot  #gay #travel    
    
    
    6 Ways to Tell if Your Hotel Is Gay Friendly http://huff.to/14WSMwm  via @HuffPostGay @Billykolber @mawtravel #gaytravel    
    
    
    Black Party, White Party: decisions, decisions! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1511  #gaytravel @jeffreysanker    
    
    
    Get ready 4 an 87-day around-the-world adventure with @MAWtravel global correspondent Paul T @j25borg #gaytravel http://bit.ly/14YvXZg     
    
    
    .@gmaps360 Tx 4 following, Pablo! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@JulianasHotel Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@crpack Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Thanks! We love our traveling #gaydads too! RT @LisaDeP: I love this series: Traveling Gay Dads: Sin-Free Las Vegas: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1484     
    
    
    Me :) RT @Babypop: So who thinks Paul Rudd is hot.. in a sexy husband way?    
    
    
    @Babypop I hope you are well! happy #FF    
    
    
    Provincetown: Summer's Must-Do Events http://wp.me/pGdW4-IJ     
    
    
    Provincetown: Summer’s Must-Do Events: OMG, Miss Richfield 1981
This just in highlights from the ... http://bit.ly/ZbhEj7  #gay #travel    
    
    
    .@MichellePayer Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Thanks for Tweeting our article! RT @twodads_us: Take your kids to Vegas!? http://fb.me/11oj4qCft     
    
    
    They Had Us At Cornhole! Tybee Island, GA Shows Unique Gay Pride http://wp.me/pGdW4-IN     
    
    
    They Had Us At Cornhole! Tybee Island, GA Shows Unique Gay Pride: Corn-what?!-ing
Tiny little Tyb... http://bit.ly/11gAjye  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Tiny Gay Tybee Island, Georgia: They had us at Cornholing! http://bit.ly/Zcb5tx  #gaytravel #cornole    
    
    
    We love Ptown too! @travelsofadam: @discoverusaCA @mawtravel P-town is nice! Have some good memories from there :) #ttot    
    
    
    @Refugia_Hankla Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/VujnRs  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Have a #travel question? Ask me! I'll be on @DNRshow tonight 820pm ET.  @wastesyourtime @Romaine33 #gaytravel @MAWtravel Call 866-305-6887    
    
    
    Thank you!! RT @DNRshow: Tune in to Derek and Romaine now for our happy hour with Travel Expert @EdSalvato #DNR10 1-866-305-6887 !    
    
    
    You’ve Won Round-the-World Airline Tickets, Now What? http://wp.me/pGdW4-IR     
    
    
    You’ve Won Round-the-World Airline Tickets, Now What?: Is this guy organized or what?!
Having won... http://bit.ly/YZLHe2  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Around the world in 87 gays, er, days by @MAWtravel correspondent Paul @j25borg http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1537#  #gaytravel    
    
    
    .@GPTimes enjoyed your comments on @DNRshow last night!    
    
    
    Guess who was named as s top travel influencer by Cision? GIve up? Me! http://lnkd.in/8Fk69w     
    
    
    Sin City Hosts These Hotties And More for Matinée Las Vegas Memorial Day Weekend http://wp.me/pGdW4-IV     
    
    
    Sin City Hosts These Hotties And More for Matinée Las Vegas Memorial Day Weekend: They’re hot plu... http://bit.ly/WThBKz  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Our correspondent, Paul J. Heney, likes baseball enough to travel for spring training. Hey,… http://wp.me/sGdW4-2789     
    
    
    You'll miss #obama but we hope you'll bring back a great report! RT @BillyKolber: @MaliaAsfour I want to visit #Jordan for @MAWtravel    
    
    
    We totally agree! We love #Provincetown, too. http://bit.ly/15LH7Ri  @smithsonianmag @PtownTourism    
    
    
    .@amytravels Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@pauldiaz1776 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@bmoneybmac Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Dotslex Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@VegasTweetsInfo Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Our April issue will be chockfull of coverage on #paris. Here's a tease. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1554  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Paris. Coming Soon. http://wp.me/pGdW4-J5     
    
    
    Paris. Coming Soon.: http://www.flickr.com/photos/25063318@N00/galleries/72157633097848135/#photo …... http://bit.ly/ZDOCtf  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Two Palm Springs #Gay #Resorts Receive Highest Rating http://huff.to/14t1tTa  via @HuffPostGay #gaytravel @mawtravel palmspringsca    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's "April in Paris" issue is coming soon. Meantime, enjoy this petit bonbon:

http://lnkd.in/YcT7gY     
    
    
    Round The World With Paul and Jose: Prepare For Take Off http://wp.me/pGdW4-J9     
    
    
    Round The World With Paul and Jose: Prepare For Take Off: Plan much?
We have 6 weeks in Europe in... http://bit.ly/ZOxT6u  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Tomorrow last day for $60 wknd tix 2 NY Travel Festival; enter 2 win trip for 2 to Prague! http://bit.ly/YqDh0p  @czechtourism @NYtravfest    
    
    
    Paris Is In The House http://wp.me/pGdW4-Jd     
    
    
    Paris Is In The House: The cover looks so much cooler in the magazine.
Paris is in the house!
Our... http://bit.ly/16gm5e3  #gay #travel    
    
    
    The April issue of ManAboutWorld magazine is available! Subscribe at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  @MAWtravel #gaytravel    
    
    
    April In Paris With ManAboutWorld http://wp.me/pGdW4-Jh     
    
    
    Enjoy April in #Paris with @MAWtravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271  #gaytravel @ParisOTC pic.twitter.com/1OhBmGUqIB    
    
    
    Enjoy April in #Paris with @MAWtravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271  #gaytravel @ParisOTC    
    
    
    .@SenBillNelson #Evolve on #marriage. It's the #RightSideOfHistory. #LGBT supported you!    
    
    
    The last section of our magazine is “Parting Shots,” which are photos taken by our… http://wp.me/sGdW4-2812     
    
    
    : The last section of our magazine is “Parting Shots,” which are photos taken by our Global Corre... http://bit.ly/11tl82C  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Around The World With Paul and Jose: Packing For 87 Days http://wp.me/pGdW4-Js     
    
    
    Would love to see this! RT @paulvdc: See my note on Mexico City's Soumaya Museum @MAWtravel #gaytravel http://bit.ly/Y1vtyJ     
    
    
    Looks like fun, right?! :) RT @mygaytravels: Round The World With Paul and Jose: Prepare For Take Off: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1560     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Correspondent Report: Balloons Over Cappadocia, Turkey http://wp.me/pGdW4-Jy     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Correspondent Report: Balloons Over Cappadocia, Turkey: Taken at 6:30am flying in a... http://bit.ly/10EXTBe  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Our Correspondent David Alport snapped this pic ballooning in Cappadocia, Turkey http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1592  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/mt5ekxujaC    
    
    
    .@worldofwlust Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Nueluxe Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Adam_Peter74 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@SoCalJason Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Photo Du Jour: Hearson's Cove In The Pilbara http://wp.me/pGdW4-JC     
    
    
    Photo du jour: Sunset in Western Australia http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1600  @MAWtravel #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/Qosqi9XYwo    
    
    
    Random #MadMen-related special offer for #travel lovers in #NewYork: @NYtravfest package ticket prices $60 instead of $75 until Mad Men    
    
    
    Our April issue is out and, if I may say so, I think it is magnifique! :)  http://lnkd.in/nJrhg7     
    
    
    .@cmh_heli Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE . PS I've done CMH!    
    
    
    .@cmh_heli gosh, I traveled with you probably at least 5 years ago? With Tanya at Geoffrey Weill. Great trip! @WeillAway would know better    
    
    
    sorry for confusion, @BillyKolber  hasn't been on a trip there but he'd love it. I hope we can get there/cover you @cmh_heli @WeillAway    
    
    
    April In Paris. Oui. That's What I'm Talking About http://wp.me/pGdW4-JG     
    
    
    April In Paris. Oui. That’s What I’m Talking About: http://www.flickr.com/photos/scalleja/ …
The we... http://bit.ly/ZCDxMP  #gay #travel    
    
    
    April in #Paris. Imagine yourself there. Now download our app http://bit.ly/Zg82Ss  and go! http://bit.ly/Z72rB8     
    
    
    Puerto Vallarta, Mexico Flexes Its Pride: I’ll go if they’re there!
Puerto Vallarta’s annual LGBT... http://bit.ly/11061wD  #gay #travel    
    
    
    #PuertoVallarta #gaypride is fast approaching http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1610  @PVVisit Use @MAWtravel for all your PV trip-planning #gaytravel    
    
    
    Mile-high walk-up bar! On @AmericanAir's new 777-300ER. We'll drink to that! @AARainbowTeam http://bit.ly/Yqp58M     
    
    
    Love it! We'll clink in the air! Congrats @AmericanAir    
    
    
    Back at ya! RT @Twin_Travel: .#ff @MAWtravel & @edsalvato = someone who deserves his own Friday "Shout Out!" Go, Ed! Go, Ed!    
    
    
    Photo Du Jour: An Eye On Carnival Puerto Vallarta: 
This photo comes to us courtesy of Puerto Val... http://bit.ly/170VMc7  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Friday Photo du Jour: Carnival Puerto Vallarta. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1614  #gaytravel @Pvvisit pic.twitter.com/TF04tIv4Oi    
    
    
    Going to see @bethditt0 at @xlnightclub @THEOUTNYC tonight. Tix at http://bit.ly/114CnoV . Heard she puts on a great show.    
    
    
    Biking to see the new Franklin D. Roosevelt 4 Freedoms Park Park @4FreedomsParkNY on Roosevelt Island http://www.fdrfourfreedomspark.org/  @nycgo    
    
    
    .@MsclPatrol @united @USAirways @MAWtravel We love the newly designed, useful SeatGuru site for these sorts of ?s http://www.seatguru.com/     
    
    
    Parting Shots: Behind The Scenes in Barcelona http://wp.me/pGdW4-JS     
    
    
    Photo du jour: Mies van der Rohe Pavilion in #Barcelona. Story behind the pic: http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1618  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/cwzBj2gdN0    
    
    
    Parting Shots: Behind The Scenes in Barcelona: The last section of our magazine is “Parting Shots... http://bit.ly/12XUqC9  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Arriving at #nytf. Exciting! We are speaking today on #gaytravel    
    
    
    .@nytravfest Roni this looks amazing so far. (Pre)congratulations!    
    
    
    Great information about North Korea @nytravfest @uritours #nytf http://twitpic.com/ckpcm3     
    
    
    "Contentious topics in travel" @travelwithval @reidontravel @jasonclampet #nytf @nytravfest    
    
    
    @kretchmar thanks! Hope you're well !!    
    
    
    There is still time to catch out talk @nytravfest #nytf http://twitpic.com/ckpx0s     
    
    
    Yours truly at @nytravfest #nytf
http://instagram.com/p/YVetGHBAhn/     
    
    
    @roniweiss @nytravfest #nytf congrats on great #travel show! Glad to be part of it. Had to leave but talk soon!    
    
    
    I Flew the Dreamliner... and I Can't Wait to Again http://wp.me/pGdW4-JZ     
    
    
    I Flew the Dreamliner… and I Can’t Wait to Again: 
After months of grounding by the FAA, the Boei... http://bit.ly/11XPFVK  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Ever wonder it's like to fly the #Dreamliner? @MAWtravel's @BillyKolber shares his experience http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271  pic.twitter.com/PrX7yL6wAb    
    
    
    Quick (New) Hotel Getaways in PA and MD http://wp.me/pGdW4-K6     
    
    
    .@BabyNamedFreddy Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@BrandonLVoss Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Bazzkeegan Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@SmallBizIntl Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@hotelcompete Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@nogueragustavo Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@HotSexyGay_ Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Kelsey Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@enpassant321 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@Brooklyn11217 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Our #palmSprings coverage is great. it's in our march issue. @Bazzkeegan @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Beauty Shot From New Capital of Gay Marriage http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ka     
    
    
    Beauty Shot From New Capital of Gay Marriage: Wellington, the capital
Photo and story by ManAbout... http://bit.ly/148Ks1l  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Weekly Travel Roundup By TravelingIQ http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ke     
    
    
    Weekly Travel Roundup By TravelingIQ:  
Too sexy for my keffiyeh
Global Correspondent Ivan Quinta... http://bit.ly/120Bf4A  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Looking forward to seeing my #gaytravel friends at @IGLTA #iglta2013 in #Chicago. Arriving Tuesday    
    
    
    u 2! RT @kgmorganPR: @edsalvato @IGLTA Looking forward to it. Arriving Wednesday. Safe travels.    
    
    
    Provincetown: Upcoming Events http://wp.me/pGdW4-Kj     
    
    
    Provincetown: Upcoming Events: Things are looking up in Ptown.
Provincetown has announced its upc... http://bit.ly/12KycQZ  #gay #travel    
    
    
    .@jasoncollins34 Congrats and thank you for coming out! such a role model. Makes me wanna watch #basketball! :)    
    
    
    .@Justinvaluable Thanks 4 followingClaim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @JamieKrauss Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Happy Queen's Day To Outgoing and Incoming Dutch Monarchs http://wp.me/pGdW4-Km     
    
    
    At #iglta2013 press conference at Willis tower in #chicago @iglta @united    
    
    
    A rep from #chicago tourism speaking at #iglta2013 press conference @iglta @chicago @united http://twitpic.com/cnf3zh     
    
    
    See you here! RT @datkidizsomajor: @edsalvato< hope to see you tbis week in Chicago! #iglta2013    
    
    
    Great seeing u! RT @outadventures: Looking forward to dinner @SenzaChicago with #gaytravel pro's @MAWtravel @BillyKolber #iglta13 #iglta    
    
    
    .@RubenSandovalPV Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    A great pleasure to have @wttc CEO @dscowsill @iglta #iglta2013 convention @chicago    
    
    
    @wttc CEO @dscowsill @iglta #iglta2013 convention @chicago shows video of @billclinton supposing global #travel    
    
    
    Global #travel and #tourism goes the economy @wttc CEO @dscowsill @iglta #iglta2013 convention @chicago http://twitpic.com/cnmwew     
    
    
    How did you respond so quickly? You're speaking!!;)
RT @DScowsill @edsalvato Thank you, Ed. http://twitpic.com/cnmwew     
    
    
    Glad you're here! RT @richardbrower Enjoying the #iglta2013 conference! (Checked in at Hyatt Regency Chicago) http://facebook.com/HyattRegencyCh …    
    
    
    Strategic priorities of @wttc (see pic) @dscowsill @iglta #iglta2013 convention @chicago http://twitpic.com/cnmxmr     
    
    
    President #obama focused on tourism @wttc CEO @dscowsill @iglta #iglta2013 convention @whitehouse_pr http://twitpic.com/cnmz4r     
    
    
    .@IGLTAFoundation doing great work in the travel space including scholarships #iglta2013 http://twitpic.com/cnn7gp     
    
    
    .@IGLTAFoundation thanks sponsors @delta and @urbanbuddy #2013    
    
    
    Thanks for being here! RT @t_marco Perú is attending the conference in Chicago.  LlamaTrip  #IGLTA2013    
    
    
    Come see @billykolber and @edsalvato at @mawtravel booth trade show #iglta2013 @iglta    
    
    
    Trade show: @billykolber and @edsalvato at @mawtravel booth trade show #iglta2013 @iglta    
    
    
    International LGBT travel confab in Chicago http://www.windycitymediagroup.com/lgbt/International-LGBT-travel-confab-in-Chicago/42669.html …    
    
    
    .@leahrkauffman Nice hanging and #vining with you in #Montreal! That's how we #doac (obliquely) @Moment_Factory    
    
    
    .@LexieNorcross Great #vining with you. Loving #Montreal. That's obliquely how I #doAC @VisitAC    
    
    
    Armando at the drums https://vine.co/v/b2v9vaQ7Qe1     
    
    
    Great visit to #montreal with the fabulous @lexienorcross and @leahkauffman from @phillydotcom to see @Moment_Factory's new shows #doac    
    
    
    Love it! RT @FrugalPhillyMom: I liked to wish 2 awesome people a Happy Birthday today! Happy Birthday @karlatrotman & @edsalvato!    
    
    
    Same to you, fellow Taurus! ;) RT @karlatrotman: Thanks @FrugalPhillyMom!  Happy Birthday @edsalvato!    
    
    
    Love this vintage color film of London circa 1927 by a noted filmmaker as a travelogue of London http://vimeo.com/7638752  #london #travel    
    
    
    "Vienna's Got Balls" — And That's Official http://wp.me/pGdW4-Kr     
    
    
    “Vienna’s Got Balls” — And That’s Official: You have to love it when a destination promotes itsel... http://bit.ly/13NMsJe  #gay #travel    
    
    
    "Vienna's got balls" and that's official! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1716  pic.twitter.com/iPYR1DvGQ4    
    
    
    Thank you, darling!! RT @NinaScim: @edsalvato enjoy your birthday weekend, Ed!    
    
    
    .@leahrkauffman Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@UrbanBuddy_CHI Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@LexieNorcross Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@localtravels Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@KellyNicholas9 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@crflores81 Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@LuigiperezHE Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @PinkAlpine Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@OutboundingOrg Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    .@AusOutbackNT_US Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Around The World With Paul and Jose: Cocktails in Melbourne http://wp.me/pGdW4-Kv     
    
    
    Cocktails in Melbourne with hot pic from Sydney. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1723  pic.twitter.com/g88CxLkIFO    
    
    
    https://vine.co/v/b0n7xBJImiW     
    
    
    Blackstone Hotel, Chicago: An Unexpected Oasis http://wp.me/pGdW4-Kz     
    
    
    Blackstone Hotel, Chicago: An Unexpected Oasis: Perched alongside Chicago’s most famous parks (at... http://bit.ly/13RnKHZ  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Loved my recent stay at Renaissance Blackstone #Chicago #Hotel. @blackstonehotel @RenHotels via @MAWtravel #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/z9kEz7c8bE    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's May issue is in the App Store available for download! http://lnkd.in/Up6BCs     
    
    
    Next time!! RT @SwissotelChi: @edsalvato Ed, we'd love to have you try out Swissotel Chicago. Come back to the Windy City!    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Gets Around http://wp.me/pGdW4-KE     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Gets Around: 
Our newest Global Correspondent Cristian Flores is a passionate trave... http://bit.ly/17ug3v9  #gay #travel    
    
    
    We get around at ManAboutWorld. Here we are in Patagonia. Sort of. Read more! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1763  @MAWtravel pic.twitter.com/G9Ten3FsSg    
    
    
    Great article by @billykolber of ManAboutWorld on #history of #gaytravel http://bit.ly/10SmtS8  courtesy @WindyCityTimes1 @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @enriqueskincare #roadtrip sounds fantastic! email me at ed@manaboutworld.com and I can see what I have to send you! happy #gaytravels!:)    
    
    
    Mixing Business With Pleasure In Las Vegas and Chicago http://wp.me/pGdW4-KJ     
    
    
    Mixing Business With Pleasure In Las Vegas and Chicago: The fabulous Cosmopolitan Hotel
By ManAbo... http://bit.ly/16kZdzo  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Mix #business and pleasure in #chicago & #lasvegas @JeffGuaracino via @MAWtravel #gaytravel http://bit.ly/10u8AI8  pic.twitter.com/4sTpGPN7fx    
    
    
    Ed meets the Queen. Sorta. This is at Musée Grevin (wax museum) in Montreal. http://instagram.com/p/Zd5GnZGz9T/     
    
    
    At flashers in #nyc #brunch @mawtravel http://instagram.com/p/ZgE0fImzwP/     
    
    
    Darn #autocorrectfail RT @kretchmar Are you flashing at Forager's? #HAHA #TYPO #LOL RT @edsalvato: At flashers in #nyc #brunch @mawtravel    
    
    
    Run, Don't Walk, To Tel Aviv Gay Pride http://wp.me/pGdW4-KN     
    
    
    Run, Don’t Walk, To Tel Aviv Gay Pride: Tel Aviv has come into its own in recent year with a gay ... http://bit.ly/16Ew8Px  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Run, don't walk, to Tel Aviv #Gay #Pride on June 7, 2013. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1777  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/mKKKZCV6Fn    
    
    
    Forager's is really great! Limited options but still hard to choose among RT @kretchmar: How was @edsalvato? Forager's? #brunch @mawtravel    
    
    
    Welcome to @MAWtravel Correspondent @michaelluongo who's visited over 80 countries http://bit.ly/10UvlC0  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/ROtY1QVu0I    
    
    
    Correspondent Update: Eating Berlin http://wp.me/pGdW4-KS     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: Eating Berlin: Facil
ManAboutWorld Global Correspondents Niazi Rubez and Ma... http://bit.ly/14CwfHe  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Eating Berlin with @MAWtravel Global Correspondent and wine expert @NiaziRubez http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1787  pic.twitter.com/OdbV2tpCeN    
    
    
    Catch me on @DNRshow tonight at 8:20pm ET at SiriusXM OutQ 109. Call in at 866-305-6887 or Tweet    
    
    
    Thanks for having me on! RT @DNRshow: @EdSalvato is here from ManAboutWorld talking Gay Travel only on @DNR on @SiriusXM @OutQ!! @MAWtravel    
    
    
    #android users click here; http://bit.ly/Xzy8h7  RT @DNRshow @dnr @OutQ @MAWtravel Will app be available to android users at some point?    
    
    
    Round The World With Paul And Jose: Gay Tokyo Update http://wp.me/pGdW4-KW     
    
    
    Round The World With Paul And Jose: Gay Tokyo Update:  
But, but, but … I’ve never!
ManAboutWorld... http://bit.ly/13Z3nWU  #gay #travel    
    
    
    @traveltoothblog Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @GabrielMissios Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @dunesresort Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Thank you for having us speak! We hope it proved informative. A great group! RT @Digitas: @MAWtravel Excited to have you guys! #DigitasLGBT    
    
    
    @MAWtravel Correspondent @travelsofadam is heading to Tel Aviv for #gaypride June 5-10 http://bit.ly/11aQZSM  follow him via #tlv4fun    
    
    
    Nice to have Tweeting buddies RT @Twin_Travel: #FF Good Tweeting Buddies! @PammyBlun @Kevin_Hanrahan2 @edsalvato #awesome    
    
    
    Thanks same to you! #FF RT @thegaytraveler: #FollowFriday: @danalyzed @TheDuaneWells @joelovesyou @jjkeyes @mklavers81 #ff #lgbt    
    
    
    happy #FF 2 u 2! RT @TravelGov: Happy #FF! #Pride Month! Check out our colleagues specializing in LGBT travel @RainbowTourism @MAWTravel    
    
    
    Boston Update: Hotel Commonwealth in Kenmore Square http://wp.me/pGdW4-L0     
    
    
    Boston Update: Hotel Commonwealth in Kenmore Square:  
The lobby
Hotel Commonwealth, a super-frie... http://bit.ly/15Xztpl  #gay #travel    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Aaron Drake http://wp.me/pGdW4-L4     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld welcomes newest global correspondent, Aaron Drake @theaarondrake #gaytravel    
    
    
    @ctccct x 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @dbosleyjr Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Zachary Moses http://wp.me/pGdW4-L9     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Zachary Moses: Welcome to our newest Global Correspo... http://bit.ly/14MMRcZ  #gay #travel    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Global Correspondent: Zach Moses Hanns Ebensten Travel @hetravel http://bit.ly/119iAnD  @MAWtravel pic.twitter.com/DFEcEf86Jx    
    
    
    @GlenGilmore Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Yes! We'd love to have a global correspondent in #iceland @pinkiceland @MAWtravel. please email me at ed at http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    Love @hillaryclinton 's bio on Twitter! Welcome and happy tweeting. #globetrotter #lgbtfriendly    
    
    
    Indeed it is! RT @BillyKolber: The World's Gayest Embassy (PHOTO) http://huff.to/1bdFFdn  via @HuffPostGay @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Loved my stay! RT @SageHotels: http://ManAboutWorld.com  – Boston Update: Hotel Commonwealth in Kenmore Square http://ow.ly/lTMoF     
    
    
    Philadelphia Gets Its Summer Gay On http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ld     
    
    
    Philadelphia Gets Its Summer Gay On: Philly’s gayborhood. Photo: J. Smith for GPTMC
Celebrating a... http://bit.ly/14XLmc3  #gay #travel    
    
    
    The Curious Case of London Pride http://wp.me/pGdW4-Lh     
    
    
    The Curious Case of London Pride: From this angle, it doesn’t look *that* bad!
Our man in the fie... http://bit.ly/12y9PJ0  #gay #travel    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's Ben Rossignol hopes this year's #london #gay #pride improves  http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1823     
    
    
    Our Favorite Photos From The Current Issue: Mykonos http://wp.me/pGdW4-Lm     
    
    
    Our Favorite Photos From The Current Issue: Mykonos: Flickr: Ricc_HB74
We asked Dillon, ManAboutW... http://bit.ly/13RXxaX  #gay #travel    
    
    
    great to see you even briefly! RT @007LouiseOB at @measure_nyc yesterday. Hope it went well, your: date with #JFK Baggage Claim.    
    
    
    Our Favorite Parting Shots: Scott Holman's Nepal http://wp.me/pGdW4-Lq     
    
    
    Our Favorite Parting Shots: Scott Holman’s Nepal: In each issue we share our favorite photos from... http://bit.ly/12PA8KQ  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Our correspondent Scott Holman found ice deliverers and popcorn sellers in Kathmandu markets. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1839  pic.twitter.com/dOgD3Csp3l    
    
    
    Our Favorite Parting Shots: Cristian Flores's Patagonia http://wp.me/pGdW4-Lu     
    
    
    Our Favorite Parting Shots: Cristian Flores’s Patagonia: In each issue we share our favorite phot... http://bit.ly/1a4YKSL  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Great shot of #Patagonia by@crflores81 http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1846  #gaytravel @MAWtravel    
    
    
    how was bootcamp? RT @navaja1cortes: Saturday morning = @Artlantic Beach Body Boot Camp along with Zumba. I mean I guess lol. Oh & #DOACsand    
    
    
    You should have to do a double now!! ;) RT @navaja1cortes: @edsalvato um didnt make it :). Nxt time    
    
    
    Welcome to @MAWtravel's newest correspondent @Bob_Witeck! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1855  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/Rvfs2DTmue    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Bob Witeck http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ly     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Bob Witeck: Welcome to our newest Global Corresponde... http://bit.ly/134JjXT  #gay #travel    
    
    
    We've been downloaded 11,000t times! ManAboutWorld is #1 in "gay travel" in the App Store: http://bit.ly/Zg82Ss     
    
    
    @JayReyHomo Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @IGLTA Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @gaytravelherald Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @subitur Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    @TheButchQueenTs Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: DJ Yabis http://wp.me/pGdW4-LB     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: DJ Yabis: DJ Yabis is the poster boy of Dream Euro T... http://bit.ly/15Hobms  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Happy to have Zach Moses on our Correspondent team! http://bit.ly/1cwfBuB  @hetravel via @MAWtravel pic.twitter.com/FwNdSvexq3    
    
    
    A Very Happy Bicoastal Gay Pride! http://wp.me/pGdW4-LF     
    
    
    A Very Happy Bicoastal Gay Pride!: This is the cover of our inaugural issue: NYC!
Happy Pride to ... http://bit.ly/15SwSL1  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Hear hear! 
RT @MSignorile: Happy Pride Eve! Amazing week pic.twitter.com/4oZF9zrIUi    
    
    
    One Hump Or Two? Post-Pride Camel Trek http://wp.me/pGdW4-LJ     
    
    
    One Hump Or Two? Post-Pride Camel Trek: 

After a breathlessly exciting week of gay news and the... http://bit.ly/17Bqmvx  #gay #travel    
    
    
    One hump or two: Camel Trekking in Western Australia with @MAWtravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1867  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/3ImiyupySg    
    
    
    @visitlauderdale Thank you for following! We're big fans of http://Sunny.org ! #gaytravel    
    
    
    @Little_K Thank you 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    @turismlive Thank you 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    Round The World With Paul And Jose: Gay Tokyo Update http://wp.me/pGdW4-LN     
    
    
    Round The World With Paul And Jose: Gay Tokyo Update: FREEDJ
ManAboutWorld Global Correspondent P... http://bit.ly/19Vbdtd  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: New York In Summer With Kids? Yes! Read On http://wp.me/pGdW4-LS     
    
    
    Thanks back at you! RT @thegaytraveler: #FollowFriday:@jjkeyes @TheDuaneWells @danalyzed @SFHeadlineNews @TravelAndrew #travel #lgbt    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: First Family Trip With My Partner (Montana Bound!) http://wp.me/pGdW4-LV     
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: First Family Trip With My Partner (Montana Bound!): A healthy fear of bears;)... http://bit.ly/154EN8T  #gay #travel    
    
    
    @MAWtravel correspondent writes about his upcoming #gay #family trip to #Montana http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1882  #gaydads pic.twitter.com/SdbXhM93eu    
    
    
    Thanks RT @JamesJetsOften: @MarkVogler ...now that's EZE-licious. Hello to @edsalvato @MAWtravel. Safe travels.    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Day 1 - A Date With Helena (Montana) http://wp.me/pGdW4-LY     
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Day 1 – A Date With Helena (Montana): The Montana state Capitol in Helena. Qu... http://bit.ly/1b4pBim  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Traveling #gaydads in Helena, Montana http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1891  @MAWtravel @paulheney pic.twitter.com/cjPkudUmW0    
    
    
    Happy #FF! RT @Twin_Travel: #FF Literary Buds @rachfmphillips @TaylorTfulks20 @joshua080880 @KhaledTalib @paulheney @edsalvato #awesome    
    
    
    I'll drink to that;) ! RT @LandLopers: New Post: Bar with the Best View in the World? http://ht.ly/mTFQx  #travel #Lp #Croatia #ttot    
    
    
    Wish I were but no, alas. Another time RT @LandLopers: Are you heading down to DMAI next week?, would be great to meet in person.    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Weekend in Montana http://wp.me/pGdW4-M2     
    
    
    Traveling #gaydads in #Montana with their kids. Cuteness ensues. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1898  @PaulHeney pic.twitter.com/vwqyU37lRW    
    
    
    Top 5 Reasons To Cruise Europe http://wp.me/pGdW4-M6     
    
    
    Top 5 Reasons To Cruise Europe: Let your gay freak flag fly!Photo courtesy Source Events.
By Bill... http://bit.ly/13sbwCm  #gay #travel    
    
    
    A great idea! RT @justJonB: I wanna do that Brand river cruise!: Top 5 Reasons To Cruise Europe: http://bit.ly/13sbwCm  #gay #travel    
    
    
    My pleasure! RT @jenniferpolland: Thanks for the tips @PaulineFrommer! Honeymoon Spots 4 Newlywed Gays http://read.bi/17gn1RI  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Correspondent Update: New and Improved Sheraton Times Square http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ma     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: New and Improved Sheraton Times Square: 1988- Elizabeth Taylor, Liza Minnel... http://bit.ly/1bsRjpj  #gay #travel    
    
    
    A fabulous gay-iconic group at Sheraton Times Square @spg http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1938  #gaytravel #newyork pic.twitter.com/4kaguxa8QJ    
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: Montana, Part 3 http://wp.me/pGdW4-Md     
    
    
    Our traveling #gaydads' last post from #Montana http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1944  @Paulheney #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/GamORvJnSb    
    
    
    Meet our latest Correspondent Hannes Pálsson who calls Iceland his home.http://www.manaboutworld.com/?portfolio=hannes-palsson … @pinkiceland #gaytavel pic.twitter.com/lV3VRsBWNz    
    
    
    We are delighted to have you on board and pleased we spelled your name right! ;) RT @pinkiceland: @MAWtravel happy to be a part of the team!    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Hannes Pálsson http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mh     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Hannes Pálsson: Gazing at the sun in the Westman Isl... http://bit.ly/1bc6vI9  #gay #travel    
    
    
    No way! I am a little angry with Russia right now! RT @kretchmar Russia 4 @Olympics? http://www.nypost.com/p/news/international/gays_russian_lesbians_could_under_h90f7YBYOWZthWuOwXsZaI?utm_source=SFnewyorkpost&utm_medium=SFnewyorkpost … @gaytravel #lgbt #Sochi2014    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Nikko Lencek-Inagaki http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mk     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Welcomes Newest Correspondent: Nikko Lencek-Inagaki: Meet our newest correspondent ... http://bit.ly/16o1OEf  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Welcome to our newest correspondent Nikko! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1972  #gaytravel via @MAWtravel @out_traveler pic.twitter.com/T8JuPGcaRR    
    
    
    Welcome to our newest correspondent Nikko! http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1972  #gaytravel via @edsalvato @out_traveler    
    
    
    Our Associate Editor Kenny Porpora is in Brazil on assignment and sent us a few photos… http://wp.me/sGdW4-2999     
    
    
    Photos du Jour: Sao Paulo, Brazil. @KennyPorpora Via @MAWtravel http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=1976  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/ehkJZGP0Va    
    
    
    A northern Norwegian town beats endless, dark winters with mirrors! http://bit.ly/1aQZzfP  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/gDbIJQjiU8    
    
    
    Welcome to our newest correspondent @markvogler http://www.manaboutworld.com/?portfolio=mark-vogler … #gaytravel via @mawtravel pic.twitter.com/PRvnSyha59    
    
    
    Photos Du Jour: Iguazu Falls http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mr     
    
    
    Photos Du Jour: Iguazu Falls: Our Associate Editor Kenny Porpora is in Brazil on assignment and s... http://bit.ly/154M8cy  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Prague Pride 2013: Come Out, Come Out http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mt     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: Paul in Krakow, Poland http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mx     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld Correspondent Paul VanDeCarr @paulvdc found the gay #Krakow #Poland #gaytravel http://bit.ly/16KLKNc  pic.twitter.com/r9xQpQfC2K    
    
    
    Do you follow us on @pinterest? We have some great boards like #gaytravel http://bit.ly/13HsSvo  pic.twitter.com/4JQk9O8Wpn    
    
    
    I did too! Nice surprise. RT @LoosLips: In #obamacare debate, I just received a *rebate check* from the freelancers union. Rara avis indeed.    
    
    
    U 2! #FF RT @gaytravelpros @Gaytravelinfo @PASSPORTmag @ConnextionsMag @OutTraveler @TravelAndrew @GAYWhistler @gaykeywest @carlosmelia    
    
    
    #FF @Sara_Horowitz I'm a big fan of her and @freelancersu    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's July/August Issue Ready For Download! http://wp.me/pGdW4-Mz     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld’s July/August Issue Ready For Download!: ManAboutWorld’s latest issue is ready for ... http://bit.ly/14WnHry  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Check Out: The Langham, Boston http://wp.me/pGdW4-MF     
    
    
    Loved my recent stay! @thelanghamhotel @LanghamBoston http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=2015  #gaytravel    
    
    
    @daryndez Thanks for following Daryn! :)    
    
    
    Looks amazing! Can't wait to fly it RT @flyboyvancouver: A peek inside JetBlue's new A321 http://vimeo.com/m/71332570  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Glasgay: Glasgow Celebrates 20th Year of Gay Cultural Festival http://wp.me/pGdW4-ML     
    
    
    Glasgay! Celebrates its 20th anniversary in Oct. http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=2023  @peoplemakegla #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/5wgybumfWP    
    
    
    Glasgay: Glasgow Celebrates 20th Year of Gay Cultural Festival: 
 
Glasgay! is a beacon of sanity... http://bit.ly/13VIviT  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Cruising With Ed: Join Our Editor In Chief On A Fabulous Cruise http://wp.me/pGdW4-MS     
    
    
    Cruising With Ed: Join Our Editor In Chief On A Fabulous Cruise: Picture yourself here
Sail aboar... http://bit.ly/15csx4l  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Take a fabulous #gaycruise with me on this luxury yacht 9/15-23. Mention my name 4 discount.) http://bit.ly/14lFc8Z  pic.twitter.com/Ppk46EICaf    
    
    
    We're proud to announce our newest global correspondent Eric Monkaba, founder of @anazure http://bit.ly/1cwrs03  pic.twitter.com/tRuVS7kymx    
    
    
    We're proud to announce our newest global correspondent Eric Monkaba, founder of @anazure http://bit.ly/1cwrs03     
    
    
    I sure do. We covered #toronto last year. Will email PDF. xx RT @enriqueskincare: @edsalvato any gay hotels you recommend for me in Toronto?    
    
    
    please email me at ed at http://manaboutworld.com . yours bounced RT @enriqueskincare: @edsalvato any gay hotels you recommend in Toronto?    
    
    
    Thank you, Kenny! The size vs download time is a big consideration. I'll forward your comment to our publisher @billykolber RT @kennypate    
    
    
    Yes! It's great & I agree Pride matters RT @travelsofadam: …  okay to travel for gay pride festivals? http://travelsofadam.com/2013/08/why-pride-matters/ … #gaytravel    
    
    
    Photo du Jour: Break Fast In Kuala Lumpur http://wp.me/pGdW4-N0     
    
    
    Photo du jour: Petronas Twin Towers, Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia @DRMSiebert http://bit.ly/19hse0L  #gaytravel Eid al-Fitr pic.twitter.com/RkOYCOWxzj    
    
    
    Sensual Travels: Book Launch, August 13, 2013 http://wp.me/pGdW4-N4     
    
    
    Beautiful day at the #beach #summer @ Atlantic City, NJ http://instagram.com/p/c9nPHcmz2Q/     
    
    
    I was quoted in @TravlandLeisure by@adamhgraham http://bit.ly/19reccP  #gaytravel #gayhoneymoons pic.twitter.com/nr3rls1UDK    
    
    
    @Siriusxm @OutQ subscribers Tweet your travel questions to @DNRshow from 8:20-9pm tonight. #Cureforthecommongaytrip #gaytravel    
    
    
    For the @DNRshow caller re: #nashville #gay #lodging, visit http://bit.ly/14MDVYR  #gaytravel    
    
    
    I love the Sky Hotel in #aspen. Fabulous! RT “@tallbubba @wastesyourtime can't call Colorado outside of Denver for anniversary.”    
    
    
        
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Vladimir Martinez: 

Vladimir Martinez is passionate about t... http://bit.ly/15LnE2o  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Welcome: new global correspondent Vladimir Martinez http://bit.ly/16SZzLF  #gaytravel via @MAWtravel @gaytravel1 pic.twitter.com/A2WtyRT6Et    
    
    
    Gay Dad Travel Advice: Back (and Forward) To School http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ne     
    
    
    #gaydads #travel with kids, sneak in college visits! http://bit.ly/1bEFhGZ  #gaytravel via @MAWtravel pic.twitter.com/efeOMalBs6    
    
    
    @LGBTconfex x 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    @JakeRyan1984 x 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    @RichardOceguera x 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: London Food Tour with Eating London http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ni     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: London Food Tour with Eating London: Photo by Adam Groffman
Our peripatetic... http://bit.ly/1d6qF7a  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Yummy #London #food tour @travelsofadam http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=2127  #gay travel via @MAWtravel pic.twitter.com/iw2Scr8qdu    
    
    
    I'm heading out on this #gaycruise fr #Lisbon to #Barcelona #gaytravel 9/15-23 http://bit.ly/153P0HG . Cabins remains pic.twitter.com/jee2XYoU6V    
    
    
    @PtownTourism #provincetown #breakwater #gaytravel #summer pic.twitter.com/iVWtmhVB1e    
    
    
    Great pic. Love #boston RT @pnkmffn: #graffiti #streetart #boston #bartlettevents @ Roxbury http://instagram.com/p/daH4TUhRoD/     
    
    
    #provincetown #streetmusic #cello @ Cabot's Candy http://instagram.com/p/dc65ZNGz_b/     
    
    
    #brooklyn #noitdoesnt #provincetown #tshirt#gaytravel http://instagram.com/p/debvLrGz7I/     
    
    
    #rainy day in #boston @ Boston Logan International Airport (BOS) http://instagram.com/p/deeYcXGz9m/     
    
    
    @mpk730 @edsalvato I wish I could have stayed longer in #Boston. Love that town.    
    
    
    Hey @jackmackenroth Tx 4 following! Claim free trial subscription #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE     
    
    
    Our editor in chief #edsalvato got his #cruise #travel docs for #sourceevents #mediterranean #sailing http://instagram.com/p/dfgF7EGz-0/     
    
    
    #provincetown #summer gorgeous #sunset at Race Point #beach @ Race Point Beach http://instagram.com/p/dh4YhQmzx2/     
    
    
    #provincetown another gorgeous #sunset at Race Point #beach #paradise @ Race Point Beach http://instagram.com/p/dh4iitGzyG/     
    
    
    Great piece on #gay and #lesbian #pakistan and #pakistanis via @tlrd http://bit.ly/1dlgXwV  pic.twitter.com/dOt59MO37h    
    
    
    #philadelphia #manaboutworld #doorway #oldtown #gaytravel #gayborhood @ Tavern on Camac http://instagram.com/p/dk2Ca9mz7G/     
    
    
    #philadelphia #manaboutworld #oldtown #gaytravel #gayborhood @ Philadelphia Gayborhood http://instagram.com/p/dk8ZlNmzzs/     
    
    
    #philadelphia #manaboutworld #oldtown #gaytravel #gayborhood @ Philadelphia Gayborhood http://instagram.com/p/dk8p-jmzz-/     
    
    
    #philadelphia #amtrak #sunset #summer #gaytravel @ 30th Street Station http://instagram.com/p/dnV86WGz_O/     
    
    
    #baltimore #stainedglass #gaytravel #publicart @ Baltimore Penn Station http://instagram.com/p/dnfvUymz-t/     
    
    
    #baltimore #nofilter #gaytravel cool city #publicart @ Bromo Seltzer Arts Tower http://instagram.com/p/dnhab4mzxi/     
    
    
    #baltimore #dj #nigel #summer #doac a @ Hilton Baltimore http://instagram.com/p/dpCIuEGz2y/     
    
    
    Same 2 U! RT @thegaytraveler: #FollowFriday:@edsalvato @TheDuaneWells @joelovesyou @danalyzed @GirlsthatRoam @Girlports #lgbt #gaytravel #ff    
    
    
    #baltimore #summer #sunset #gaytravel @ Sports Legends Museum at Camden Yards http://instagram.com/p/dp46Obmz90/     
    
    
    #baltimore #summer #amtrak #gaytravel #manaboutworld @ Baltimore Penn Station http://instagram.com/p/dp9n7YGz2J/     
    
    
    #rehobothbeach #beach #summer #gaytravel #gay #instagay #travel http://instagram.com/p/drubczmz1X/     
    
    
    #rehobothbeach #beach #summer #gaytravel #gay #instagay #travel #manaboutworld #poodlebeach @ Poodle… http://instagram.com/p/dsGHrIGzzC/     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Steve Roth http://wp.me/pGdW4-Nl     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Steve Roth: 
Steve Roth has been fascinated by the world aro... http://bit.ly/17r77l3  #gay #travel    
    
    
        
    
    
    huge honor!RT @KellyNicholas9: meeting such talented athletes @RyanDVolley @caseypatt @ProfessorTodd #doac #AVP2013 pic.twitter.com/hZVsd6zhJR    
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Scott Marquardt http://wp.me/pGdW4-Nr     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Scott Marquardt: Scott grew up as a prairie boy in Calgary, ... http://bit.ly/13xUgQC  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Welcome to @MAWtravel 's newest correspondent @MarquardtScott http://www.manaboutworld.com/?p=2178  pic.twitter.com/qGEtWV4bjI    
    
    
    Beautiful! RT @theluxelistuk: {Photos} Amano'i resort in Vietnam http://bit.ly/15drTbR  - it looks fabulous, don't you think? #ttot #travel    
    
    
    Parting Shots: Nepal http://wp.me/pGdW4-Nv     
    
    
    Awesome, weird traditions! RT @themomjen: 5 Unusual Cultural Customs Around the World http://goo.gl/SrQ5U5  via @quirkytravel    
    
    
    We are delighted to have you RT @MarquardtScott: @MAWtravel Thanks! Excited to be part of the team #gaytravel    
    
    
    I'm heading 2 Lisbon 4 my first Source Events cruise to Barcelona http://bit.ly/153P0HG/  @sourceevents Will update in…http://lnkd.in/b7TCdMi     
    
    
    Thanks! RT @mayacashh: @edsalvato have fun Ed!    
    
    
    #philadelphia #airport #airportart #publicart #philadelphia #travel #gaytravel #manaboutworld @… http://instagram.com/p/eN5QfhGz-w/     
    
    
    Approaching #lisbon #midair #atlanticocean #usairways #sunrise #travel #gaytravel #manaboutworld @… http://instagram.com/p/ePGnOCGz0n/     
    
    
    Congrats! RT @visitlauderdale: Online LGBT travel mag @MAWtravel names Wilton Manors Gayborhood of the year! http://bit.ly/1gzDRhr     
    
    
    'Gram With Us! See ManAboutWorld's Global Instagram Feed http://wp.me/pGdW4-NC     
    
    
    ‘Gram With Us! See ManAboutWorld’s Global Instagram Feed: The ES collection
That’s our editor in ... http://bit.ly/1h77QO6  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Get a feel for our sexy, hot travel pix in our @Instagram feed http://www.manaboutworld.com/?page_id=271  #gaytravel #gay pic.twitter.com/XyDxXMbBnf    
    
    
        
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Pascal Ultee http://wp.me/pGdW4-NF     
    
    
    Welcome to our newest global correspondent #Netherlands based Pascal Ultee http://www.manaboutworld.com/?portfolio=pascal-ultee … #gay #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/3ErQncIj2S    
    
    
    Aww. U rock 2! RT @DNRshow: The wonderful @EdSalvato is on @DNRShow to talk all things Gay Travel! http://www.EdSalvato.Com  #DNR10 @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Check out our "men of Iberia" slideshow. 
http://lnkd.in/bPPtQtu     
    
    
    @troysmith2034 Thanks for following! Hope to see you in #capetown some time    
    
    
    Same-Sex Weddings Bring Same-Sex Honeymoons http://wp.me/pGdW4-NJ     
    
    
    Same-Sex Weddings Bring Same-Sex Honeymoons: Courtesy: Four Seasons
By Jeff Guaracino, ManAboutWo... http://bit.ly/19u1Z2A  #gay #travel    
    
    
        
    
    
    Traveling Gay Dads: You’re Going to Disney!: Haven Caylor is a ManAboutWorld Global Correspondent... http://bit.ly/19Chtlp  #gay #travel    
    
    
    #traveling #gaydads head to #disney http://bit.ly/GYh1Wz  #manaboutworld #gay #gaytravel @twin_travel pic.twitter.com/8vpDaxhmEm    
    
    
    Cool #pix: Around the world with @outadventures http://bit.ly/H1fTk2  via @MAWtravel. Full article in magazine pic.twitter.com/1Jx9gyLRow    
    
    
    Attention he-goats: ManAboutWorld's October issue is ready for download. http://bit.ly/1aNTShH  #gay #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/0aEjHgQLlk    
    
    
    ManAboutWorld's October Issue Ready For Download! http://wp.me/pGdW4-NR     
    
    
    ManAboutWorld’s October Issue Ready For Download!: ManAboutWorld’s latest issue is ready for down... http://bit.ly/19JaIyf  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Always a pleasure! RT @jenkedinger: @edsalvato great seeing you at #NYCWFF by Hyatt Recharge Lounge - #InAHyattWord.    
    
    
    @illyUSA Thanks for the follow. I'm a big fan of your #coffee, especially when I #travel. Which is always!    
    
    
    @illyUSA please click here for a free subscription to our #ipad only #gaytravel #magazine http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @jasonbellini thanks for following! please claim your #free subscription to our #ipad only magazine http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  #gaytravel    
    
    
    Thanks! All's well. Hope u 2! RT @JamesJetsOften: Shout out to @edsalvato. Hope you and @MAWtravel doing well. #social #travel #global #LGBT    
    
    
    Are You A Travel Top Or Travel Bottom? Take Our Quiz! http://wp.me/pGdW4-NW     
    
    
    Are You A Travel Top Or Travel Bottom? Take Our Quiz!: 
By Jeff Guaracino, ManAboutWorld Global C... http://bit.ly/19t9uIk  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Thanks for the mention @JoeMyGod! http://bit.ly/1haApwL  @visitlauderdale #gaytravel #editorschoice via @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Ft. Lauderdale's WIlton Manors named #gayborhood of the year   by us:) http://bit.ly/1a2z0B9  @visitlauderdale #gaytravel    
    
    
    You’ll actually want to watch this really fun #safety video by @virginamerica http://youtu.be/DtyfiPIHsIg     
    
    
    This is bad news no ifs, ands or butts: #airlines revealing narrower seats http://bit.ly/1aJyJHG     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Jim Werner http://wp.me/pGdW4-O1     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Jim Werner: 
Jim Werner is co-owner of http://fagabond.com ... http://bit.ly/1duSHGG  #gay #travel    
    
    
    In the "it's about time" category: #FAA allow airlines 2 relax #electronic device restrictions in flight http://bit.ly/1cuUvm7  tx @j25borg    
    
    
    Very funny! Miss Richfield's Tour of Philadelphia Outtakes: http://youtu.be/tWB9tyeraKE  via @youtube @nightlifegay @gaytravel @missrichfield    
    
    
    @billykolber: RT @RainbowVoyages: Biking Around Budapest á la Four Seasons Style: http://youtu.be/X5HfM6i1288  via @youtube #Budapest #gaytravel    
    
    
    #FF @theaarondrake @TravelsofAdam @AllisterChang @TwittBen @BillyKolber @Bob_Witeck @carlosmelia @crflores81 @SteeleTravel @DreamEuroTrip    
    
    
    Looking forward to lunch at @21club to learn more about @themountnelson #loveSAflavors for @MAWtravel
#gaytravel pic.twitter.com/VbaR1MH3Vo    
    
    
    Checked out yr pix. food looks amazing! RT: @edsalvato @21Club @MAWtravel @PlanetChefTable is looking forward to serve you his menu today!    
    
    
    Miss Richfield's Selfie Tour of Philadelphia Outtakes http://wp.me/pGdW4-O4     
    
    
    Miss Richfield’s Selfie Tour of Philadelphia Outtakes: 
We love the new Miss Richfield commercial... http://bit.ly/19OEDXP  #gay #travel    
    
    
    New Leadership Brings Energy (And Lower Prices) to RSVP Cruises http://wp.me/pGdW4-O8     
    
    
    Correspondent Update: Movie Star Kelly Graces Doylestown, Pennsylvania http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ob     
    
    
    Grace Kelly and more in New Hope, PA http://bit.ly/17uUVqq  @BCplayhouse @michenerart @visitnewhope #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/8oJVx37d9z    
    
    
    Correspondent Update: Movie Star Kelly Graces Doylestown, Pennsylvania: Kelly and her prince
By J... http://bit.ly/18xQiXw  #gay #travel    
    
    
    Gaying & heating up the #caribbean: Hedonism II Bloom Jamaica Dec 4-9, 2013. http://www.thebloomparty.com/  @FIBOIsland pic.twitter.com/sNHURk2dAr    
    
    
    Stop complaining about @CitiBikeNYC! Instead tell @transalt how to change it. New survey just released: http://bit.ly/17RypZg     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Lance Stamps http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ok     
    
    
    Welcome To Our Newest Correspondent: Lance Stamps: 
Welcome to ManAboutWorld’s newest corresponde... http://bit.ly/1agzGaD  #gay #travel    
    
    
    @rouxptown thanks for the follow. Tell us more about your new #ptown #B&B! Best of luck    
    
    
    Go quick! http://nyti.ms/18nQg8c 
@nytimestravel @nytimes "As Myanmar Modernizes, Old Trades Are Outpaced by New Competitors” #culturalchange    
    
    
    Guess what’s available? Yes: Our November issue! Chock full of great info. http://bit.ly/1atzftN  #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/iDn7mLukN4    
    
    
    With a #travel #gay angles this is right up our alley ‘Pirira,’ Set in Malawi & NYC, to debut off-Broadway on Friday, Nov. 15 @Theatre167    
    
    
    Miami closing party hosted by Island House Key West 12/2 @whitepartyweek @IslandHouseKW. Info:http://on.fb.me/19k1S7P  pic.twitter.com/4C9KrVQIcq    
    
    
        
    
    
    @jasonclampet @skift Check our #gaytravel magazine for #iPad only via free trial subscription #iPad at http://bit.ly/WP2013FREE  #greatcontent    
    
    
    @aboutDCI Any experience or thoughts on #adventuretravel in #iceland? #atws    
    
    
        
    
    
    Any tips for great #gay #adventuretravel destinations? I like the folks at @outadventures #atws    
    
    
    Top 10 hard-working @twitter tips by @TravlandLeisure editor @pfrank1 http://bit.ly/Ip65BQ     
    
    
    New #Paris to #Barcelona High-Speed Rail Line Takes on Planes http://skift.com/2013/11/29/new-paris-to-barcelona-high-speed-rail-line-takes-on-planes/ … by @skift #gaytravel via @mawtravel    
    
    
    Get ready for @ArtBasel http://bit.ly/18Tm8Sl  #miami #gaytravel pic.twitter.com/oUxlSjaejg    
    
    
    Great piece on http://bit.ly/IHnTIy  by @TravelsofAdam@MAWtravel global correspondent http://bit.ly/IHnTIy  via @MetroUK #travel    
    
    
    Paradise found. #honolulu #hawaii #manaboutworld #gay #gaytravel #sheraton #waikiki @ Sheraton Waikiki http://instagram.com/p/hhjfinGz7_/     
    
    
    Already took it 
RT @LindaAdamsNY- @CitiBikeNYC! Take this survey & tell @transalt how to change it: http://bit.ly/17RypZg     
    
    
    Parting Shots: Chitwan, Nepal with Anazure http://wp.me/pGdW4-Op     
    
    
        
    
    
    #Virtual #hotel #tours powered by @GoogleTravel http://usat.ly/1fJ5J4n  via @usatodaytravel and @skift    
    
    
    Photo Du Jour: Pope Francis Delivers First Christmas Mass http://wp.me/pGdW4-Ou     
    
    
    Photo Du Jour: Pope Francis Delivers First Christmas Mass: Pope Francis celebrates midnight mass.... http://bit.ly/1g10FbJ  #gay #travel    
    
    
    #FF @gayographer "World's 1st LGBT travel concierge" and @MAWtravel user!    
    
    
    @KimptonInNYC  please email me at ed (dot) salvato (at) yahoo #Eventi    
    
    
    @KimptonInNYC  yes heard about this. very exciting! #MarvelComic #X    
    
    
    @goldcat Thanks for following. Love your @twitter handle! Very nice chatting with you briefly. Linda Hirshman just rocks!    
    
    
    @kretchmar those vintage posters are awesome, tx! http://www.flickr.com/photos/boston_public_library/sets/72157624587860480/detail/?page=2 …    
    
    
    @traviskatz Thanks for the mention!  #gogobot #pride #lgbt    
    
    
    @KimptonInNYC It's great #gaypride special for #nyc visitors http://edsalvato.wordpress.com/2012/06/17/eventi-hotel-pride-special/ …    
    
    
    Two More Reasons to Head to Vermont This Year http://wp.me/pGdW4-EE     
    
    
    Visit #Vermont at the end of September for a #gay event two-fer, including #pride and Northern Decadence http://bit.ly/LB3KA7  #Lgbtpride    
    
    
    @gaydays thanks for the Tweet and good luck with #gaydays in #LasVegas! pls subscribe to 1st issue of new ipad mag: http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @nwilkins1972 thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    @Philly_PR_Girl Thanks for following. @koryaversa speaks highly of you    
    
    
    @Tripatini Thanks for following. Love your site! Please sign up for inaugural issue of #iPad #gaytravel magazine http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @meganv_nyc Thanks for following! I share your love of #wine and #food. Oh and #travel:)    
    
    
    @Tripatini what a great opportunity! I will circle back to you when it's available on Apple Newsstand. Thank you (also for signing up!)    
    
    
    @SpinksPhillip Welcome to @Twitter! Can't wait to see your #Tweets. Lots of pix of your art, I hope    
    
    
    @girlslunchout Thanks for following http://GIrlsLUnchOut.com  looks like a great opportunity for women!    
    
    
    @SustEarth Thanks for following. At http://manaboutworld.com  we care about sustainable travel, too.    
    
    
    Tx, U 2! RT @koryaversa: #FF @dnewman @kris_restaurant @GaelleKennedy @philly_pr_girl @FrugalPhillyMom @peternero @southjerseybeth    
    
    
    Thanks, Gaelle and back at you! RT @GaelleKennedy: #FF @edsalvato @koryaversa @jaimebloom @konstantina_liv @cuteandgirlydms @nomissltd    
    
    
    @hobotraveler Thanks for following! Man, you get around:) Love your blog    
    
    
    @HyattPR Thank you 4 following! Be sure 2 follow new gay travel magazine for iPad to launch summer 2012: @MAWTravel http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    Montreal Launches 3rd Annual Queer of the Year Contest http://wp.me/pGdW4-EL     
    
    
    @Montreal announces 3rd annual Queer of the Year contest http://bit.ly/Ns1J8g  #gaytravel @qotycontest    
    
    
    @JoeCool102986 U can get doAC magnet at visitor center on boardwalk or end of expressway while supplies last or DM @VisitAC with yr address    
    
    
    @MSEManagement Thanks for following! Look forward to next year's travel show!    
    
    
    @CarenCotto Thanks for following! Can't believe it'll be the 10th anniversary of @nyttravelshow in 2013! #travel #tourism #gaytravel    
    
    
    @AMagicMommy I look forward to seeing you in AC on July 4. Will be fun!  #howidoac @VisitAC    
    
    
    Me too! RT @PhilaCulturati: Excited to tell the blogosphere about #HowIDoAC when I @visitAC next week for the 4th of July!!!    
    
    
    @TheBearCampNC Thanks for following. I'd love to visit #gayfriendly #asheville, NC    
    
    
    @spoiledtraveler Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @GayPartyList thanks for following! You have a fun website, http://gaypartylist.com !    
    
    
    @jodifur Thanks for following! Look forward to working with you.    
    
    
    @peternero thanks for following! Happy #FF    
    
    
    Back at you! RT @lasfotosproject: happy friday! #ff    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great bloggers! @philaculturati @haelifestyle @jerseyfamilyfun @amagicmommy @capemaymoms @nancy_horn @koryaversa    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @RealMomMedia @buzzmommy @NicolleMK @PWStyle  @CallMeAdamNYC @Tracy_Iglesias @babypop @frugalphillymom    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @RubyDW, @growinblkxican @JoLynneS @jessienuez @techsavymama    
    
    
    Happy #FF to great #bloggers @jodifur @1momof5 @jessicaAPISS @ChescoMoms    
    
    
    Sneak peek of new @moment_factory 3D light and sound show @visitac #howidoac    
    
    
    Hey @KenPanton. Welcome to @twitter. Look forward to following you. Be sure to also follow @MAWTravel, our new #gaytravel mag for #ipad    
    
    
    @KingstonPride Thanks for following! Look forward to your #gaypride next June!    
    
    
    Thanks for the  RT! @Babypop: So excited to @VisitAC for the 4th of July! http://ow.ly/bXAG9  #HowIDoAC #Philly <--- that sounds so fun!    
    
    
    @TheOnlineMom Thanks for following. You have a great site full of useful tips!    
    
    
    @Nancy_Horn look forward to having you here! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @CapeMayMoms Thanks for following! See you in @VisitAC #howIdoAC    
    
    
    @SKIBUMS Thanks for the follow. Love your group:) Please be sure to follow @MAWtravel 1st gay travel mag for iPad http://manaboutworld.com     
    
    
    @Brian_Weston Thanks for the follow! Great to meet you and congrats on @moment_factory 3D light & sounds show. It rocks! @VisitAC #howIdoac    
    
    
    @ryanfitzgibbon Thanks for the follow! Happy 4th and happy travels    
    
    
    Waving hi back! RT @hchybinski: @Babypop @buzzymommy @EdSalvato Waving Hi - have fun!! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    So fun! RT @Babypop: On the trolley with @buzzymommy @EdSalvato #Howidoac pic.twitter.com/GJA6Kefs    
    
    
    @JoLynneS Hi back to you! wish you were here with our great @visitAC blogger team. next time #howidoac    
    
    
    @NicolleMK Always a pleasure to hang with you! so happy to have you here in Atlantic City @visitAC #howidoac    
    
    
    @DonnaReedSteph We are all definitely going to have a drink for you, lady! Wish you were here with our great bloggers #HowIDoAC @visitAC    
    
    
    @DonnaReedSteph Must get you to @visitAC!! let's work on it #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @Jerseyfamilyfun so glad you enjoyed it! #howidoac    
    
    
    @Babypop So great to work with you and see you in person! And fun to see how you do AC! ;) #howIdoAC    
    
    
    @toddcrossnyc thanks for following! great seeing you at the "Victory" book signing. Linda Hirshman is amazing    
    
    
    "Awesome Blog Award"? Me? It's an Honor! http://wp.me/pGdW4-ES     
    
    
    @judiludi Thanks for following... Now, tweet, Judi, tweet! :)    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts Thanks for the follow! Look forward to connect with you    
    
    
    @buzzmommy What a pleasure to meet you in person! Thank you for visiting AC. Look forward to working together again #howidoac    
    
    
    @Babypop I had a lovely time too! Thank you so much for joining    
    
    
    And whan an awesome pic of me  u took! Tx RT @Babypop: @edsalvato Great working with you.  Thanks we had a lovely time. http://ow.ly/i/KuVd     
    
    
    @MarkVogler thanks for the retweet    
    
    
    Ok, well, I just HAVE to reweet this one! :) Thank you RT @DonnaReedSteph: Seriously? @edsalvato is the Travel God.    
    
    
    @NYBookDude Thanks for following! Looks like a cool site you have there    
    
    
    @HIPHOPLIVEGAYS Thanks for following. Cool about @Frank_Ocean http://nyti.ms/NePNtg     
    
    
    sign me up 2:) RT @Tracy_Iglesias:  @PhilaCulturati @visitac @GoldenNuggetAC We definitely should do the AC Wine Fest!    
    
    
    @ClintTheTravele Thanks for the follow. Love your profile! we will soon launch 1st gay travel mag 4 iPad-with lots of great tips @mawtravel    
    
    
    @GoFurtherAfield Thanks 4 follow I like yr site! Pls b sure 2 sign up 2 dwnload inaugural issue of iPad only gay  travel magazine @MAWTravel    
    
    
    @CortneyGalster thanks for following. Nice site!    
    
    
    @Soles4Souls Thanks for following. As a striving responsible traveler, @Soles4Souls sounds like a very cool organization. Congrats!    
    
    
    @dyunghans thanks for subscribing to my list!    
    
    
    @Soles4Souls Some day! Will look at your trip line ups    
    
    
    @VisitBtown Thanks for following! Love your small, progressive town!    
    
    
    @clothes4souls Thanks for following. Any relationship to Soles4souls? :)    
    
    
    @CricridesChamps Merci de me suivre! J'adore Paris!    
    
    
    @DNRshow Thaknks for having me on your show! Fun -- and travel-y ;) -- as always #DNR    
    
    
    @MichaelKretchmar Tonight is the Manhattanhenge -the sunset is exactly aligned with the grid of streets in NYC. http://www.haydenplanetarium.org/resources/starstruck/manhattanhenge/ …    
    
    
    @AntiSocialSmurf Find magnets at AC Visitors Center on the AC expressway & the other is directly in front of Boardwalk Hall on the boardwalk    
    
    
    @avitalb I saw those cool iceberg images in @NYTimes today. stunning    
    
    
    @JamesJetsOften Awesome! We are probably covering @SantaFe in @MAWTravel this fall. Great minds! #LGBT #MAW    
    
    
    @FrugalPhillyMom have a great trip in Atlantic City! @visitAC! #Duality #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @tattoomommie Thanks for following. Love  Jennifer at @JerseyFamilyFun :)    
    
    
    @OKeeffeCountry Thanks for following. Love Georgia O'Keeffe and #NewMexico    
    
    
    @avitalb Thanks for following! Great site. You have a lot of interests!    
    
    
    @Mami2Mommy Thanks for the follow! Great site you have!    
    
    
    @arzayusalvaro thanks for following me on Twitter. I'll be in Buenos Aires later this month:) http://bit.ly/NkmcMX     
    
    
    I'll be in #buenosaires later this month speaking about #lgbttourism. more info here: http://bit.ly/NkmcMX  #gaytravel #LGBTtravel    
    
    
    @JenniferAuer I love @abseconlighthouse. Look for the community garden plot with a rainbow flag.That would be @jeffguaracino 's! #howidoac    
    
    
    Guess Who's Launching a New iPad-only Gay Travel Magazine? http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fc     
    
    
    Check out my latest post. Guess who's launching a new #gaytravel magazine for @iPad only? Hint: me! http://bit.ly/Ofez9n  @EdSalvato    
    
    
    We very proudly support Int'l Gay  & Lesbian Human Rights Commission's Celebration of Courage Mon 7/16.  info: http://bit.ly/NvbJgk  @IGLHRC    
    
    
    Fab Travel Prizes Prizes at IGLHRC Event http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fp     
    
    
    @PR_in_Victoria Thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    Was just thinking the same! RT @PaulineFrommer: OMG, its almost noon & I've gotten nothing done yet. Curse ye Twitterverse!    
    
    
    So happy to help out! RT @IGLHRC: Thanks @MAWtravel and @edsalvato for your generous support! #CelebrateCourage    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents #FF @TwittBen @SteeleTravel @TravelingIQ @JamesEmtage @JDvanZyl_UK @JeffGuaracino @LuxTravel    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents #FF@SanCarlosPatch @LDFarah @DRMSiebert @LeaveYrDailyHell @OutAdventures @FlyBoyVancouver    
    
    
    Love our @MAWTravel correspondents @JamesEmtage @TravisFerland @RyanCHaynes @JonJonMak    
    
    
    @Babypop I miss you and the rest of the blogger team! #howIdoAC    
    
    
    Same to you! RT @Tracy_Iglesias: ⒻⓄⓁⓁⓄⓌ Friday! @philZENdia @Caringmom @tea4two20 @lifeonprint @latinaprpro #llblog @ElianneRamos #latism    
    
    
    @PR_in_Victoria I'm heading to #Provincetown end of this week for some much needed R&R; staying at the fab @princealbertpt @PtownTourism    
    
    
    @MotivadaLatina Thank you for following! Great tweets and re-tweets you have    
    
    
    @joeyfortman Thanks so much for the retweet! :) #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    @MomsOnTheSpot thakns for the re-tweet! #HowIDoAC    
    
    
    Broadway Queen Alert: Linda Eder In Provincetown August 13-14 http://wp.me/pGdW4-Fu     
    
    
    Heading to #Provincetown for Carnival week? Check out @LindaEder singing for 2 nights at the @OnlyAtTheCrown Info: http://bit.ly/NfeBUn     
    
    
    @MomsThoughts thanks for the retweet. @LindaEder just rocks!    
    
    
    @WhatsThatSmell Thanks for the follow. Love your Twitter handle name:)    
    
    
    @Havenlust Thank you for the follow!    
    
    
    @hospitality_law Thanks for the follow. Cool site with great info!    
    
    
    @festivy Thank you for following! happy #FF    
    
    
    @kennypate Funny you should ask. I'm heading to S. America tomorrow. Will have plenty of suggestions. Pls email me via http://edsalvato.com     
    
    
    @nolaghost Thanks for the follow. Love #newOrleans. Will have to check out your tour next time I'm there    
    
    
    Heading to #BuenosAires tomorrow for the 5th annual #LGBTtravel conference by @gnetwork360    
    
    
    Our editor in chief @EdSalvato is heading to #BuenosAires tomorrow for the 5th annual #LGBTtravel conference by @gnetwork360    
    
    
    I'm heading to @BuenosAires to speak at the 5th annual conference on #LGBTTravel and marketing Info: http://on.fb.me/QeTPG5     
    
    
    @kretchmar Gracias, señor! See you after the conference ... in August. #LGBTTravel    
    
    
    @janinadpvrahman Thanks for following. I read through your posts ... great stuff!    
    
    
    @57Onesie Thanks for following!    
    
    
    @SeeAtlanticCity Thanks for the follow. I was in AC a couple of weeks ago. Love it! #HowIdoAC:)    
    
    
    @grattonboy Thanks for the follow. Been following your Tweets -- great stuff!    
    
    
    @alfredo_buegay and what about me? I'm here to @GNetwork360! :) Look foward to seeing you!    
    
    
    In #BuenosAires at @PanamericanoBA #hotel getting ready for the @GNetwork360 5th annual #LGBTTravel conference. @IGLTA is in the house, too    
    
    
    @visitoakland Thanks for following. Love Oakland:)    
    
    
    @MGWargentina really happy to be here.    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts love it here. Mild winter. thanks for the retweet.    
    
    
    Mostly a great visit to #buenosaires for @gnetwork360 #lgbttravel conference. I conducted two successful talks and hope 3rd's the charm 2day    
    
    
    @konaboys this is so awesome. Proud to be on your sandy beach... though I'd prefer to personally be there! :)    
    
    
    @rangels oi from New York. Nice to connect with you here, too.    
    
    
    @rangels Beijos e abraços from New York! Everyone here wants to know: When is @rangels going to visit us!!? :) xo    
    
    
    @rangels New York won't know what hit it… hurricane Rangels! :)    
    
    
    #webstagram - @doac http://web.stagram.com/p/253031925681528133_38936318 … via @webstagram    
    
    
    @MomsThoughts thanks for the retweet. Just learning how to play with @instagram. fun! #howIdoac :) @doac @webstagram    
    
    
    In #AtlanticCity 2 c @NikWallenda's incredible stunt, walking 1500 ft, 100 ft above the beach. Live webcast 3-330pm: http://bit.ly/TjN4R8     
    
    
    @YwalkWhenUcnFLY Same! look forward to meeting you and seeing @NikWallenda perform his incredible stunt. #howIdoac    
    
    
    @NikWallenda is climbing up there for his 1500-ft walk?! Yep! Enjoying this stunt is #howidoac    
    
    
    Download yr free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel magazine built for iPad by founders of OUT&ABOUT  http://bit.ly/NnFwst  @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @xomayasade @EdSalvato is ecstatic with your @NikWallenda Tweets! You rock!    
    
    
    Happy #FF RT @LuxuryDreamer: @mjdwarner @edsalvato @eliana_crespo @encounterstravl @GroupG3 @GlammysNYC @GayRiviera @NYTmag @NY1weather    
    
    
    Happy #FF @JenniferAuer @AMagicMommy @YwalkWhenUcnFLY @NicolleMK @culturejaunt @Jerseyfamilyfun @visitac @nikwallenda @jeffguaracino    
    
    
    Thanks @travelwithval. Pls use this link to download: http://bit.ly/OaYTdu  RT free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel mag built 4 iPad    
    
    
    @xomayasade  check out http://on.fb.me/MJqRHB  and tag yourself!    
    
    
    @outadventures thanks for the retweet! Have you downloaded yours yet? Would love to get your feedback! @MAWtravel    
    
    
    Same to you! Interesting, good people! @kretchmar @lindafrankbooks @ivazg @morewomen2012 @travisgster @daverapps @lkhere    
    
    
    Thanks for the RT :) @edsalvato: Download free issue of ManAboutWorld, 1st #gaytravel magazine built 4 iPad http://bit.ly/NnFwst  @MAWtravel    
    
    
    @rangels I got your email. Very exciting stuff! You are THE BEST @MAWTravel correspondent:) Will get back to you.    
    
    
    