Little Cranberry Island - Two Very Basic Churches http://hub.am/rbfOYP     
    
    
    Residential Green Building Tip -- HVAC and Dehumidification http://hub.am/nk08vw     
    
    
    Residential Green Building Tip -- Hot Water http://hub.am/mXfECK     
    
    
    The Green School - What it Means and the Difference It Makes http://hub.am/pUwi4u     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Mr95Aa  This is something we've grappled with for quite a while.  I wrote a piece for EnvisionChurch cataloguing a number...    
    
    
    A City Chapel in the Historic Cemetery http://is.gd/rIwc1O     
    
    
    The Building Committee - a Great Group or a Big Mess? http://hub.am/rqXMsO     
    
    
    Austin Street Art - NBA meets Mary Poppins? http://hub.am/q1ddKz     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/GxXRES  Solomon's Porch sounds like it has a lot in common with a number of established ministries that have successfully...    
    
    
    Building a Church Family Life Center in Phases http://hub.am/oaRIgY     
    
    
    Austin Churches - Hidden All-Faith Jewels http://hub.am/uM6n4H     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part One http://hub.am/tSx81j     
    
    
    A Mobile Chapel - A Truck-Stop Church http://hub.am/umXLe0     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part Two http://hub.am/tu9S1E     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part Three http://hub.am/sApjnj     
    
    
    Church Kitchen Ideas - Before and After Examples http://hub.am/uF1e5P     
    
    
    Building Preservation Myths - Part Four http://hub.am/uhsaRV     
    
    
    Historic Renovation of a Country Inn: 15 Tips - Part One http://hub.am/uHs1jX     
    
    
    Kevin Tuerff of Envromedia is an old friend, really excited to see he's blogging! http://lnkd.in/n4_TkP     
    
    
    Historic Inn Renovation - 15 Tips, Part Two http://hub.am/s4J6ta     
    
    
    LED Lighting Comparison -- Using It NOW!! http://hub.am/rBNhxl     
    
    
    Preserving A Country Inn - 15 Tips, Part Three http://hub.am/tNNF27     
    
    
    Historic Inn Preservation - 15 Tips, Part Four http://hub.am/uxrNPD     
    
    
    Austin to LA - Mid Century Modern Sources at the LACMA http://hub.am/uKLi6o     
    
    
    Church Architecture - What Makes It So Special? http://hub.am/eyLRA6    
    
    
    Church Kitchen Details - Don't Overlook These! http://hub.am/xXxGy7     
    
    
    Austin Churches Designed by Heimsath Architects http://hub.am/xTbkcU     
    
    
    Building Preservation Is Greenest! http://hub.am/wb3Xbq     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9tCKCc  Michael, Thanks for alerting us to this most interesting opinion.  I happen to agree - the impetus to make art,...    
    
    
    Architectural Watercolor Renderings Are Perfect For Master Plans http://hub.am/AdMqqG     
    
    
    Building Conservation - A Great Resource at the University of Texas http://hub.am/ysJ3LG     
    
    
    Adoration Chapel Stained Glass http://hub.am/zxdXnn     
    
    
    Church Design:  Top 10 Things to Know for Building Committees http://hub.am/hUxmFI    
    
    
    Demand Charge for Church Electricity:  Is This a Good Idea? http://hub.am/wm40ku     
    
    
    What is a Narthex? http://hub.am/yHhv4j     
    
    
    Liturgical Objects Get A New Life http://hub.am/GEz3Ws     
    
    
    Church Interior Design - Is Beige The Only Color? http://hub.am/GYljZI     
    
    
    Non Denominational Chapel of the Snows - World's Southernmost Church http://hub.am/HjStUL     
    
    
    Residential Solar Panels -- A First Report http://hub.am/Io1gpz     
    
    
    What Is A Church? An Outsider's Perspective http://hub.am/IAc9GH     
    
    
    Electric Car Implications - Saving Gas Is Just The Beginning http://hub.am/KwqUEB     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/r5EVRu  Wonderful spaces, but they really could be anywhere.  They have nothing to do with Corb's masterpiece, but perhaps...    
    
    
    The Church and Development - What's Missing Here? http://hub.am/K3EFtC     
    
    
    Building Restoration After Catastrophe http://blog.heimsath.com/blog-0/bid/84476/building-restoration-after-catastrophe …    
    
    
    Church Design -- Worship Space Lighting Control http://hub.am/MG4S36     
    
    
    Church Design - Then and Now http://hub.am/LBbdzd     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rByUpf  Thanks for calling attention to this.  I'm not offended, but I do think it shows some insensitivity in an otherwise...    
    
    
    Master Planning for Congregations - 10 Essentials http://hub.am/PKO4i7     
    
    
    LEDs -- Energy Efficient Lighting for Residential and Church Design http://hub.am/e9Y5xK    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/7EG2Mj  We commissioned a wonderful liturgical artist, George Hoelzeman for a modern version of the "gates of paradise" --...    
    
    
    Sacred Place is Home For The Arts http://hub.am/TEZ9yD     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/aDMDE9  Betty Meyer, for me, was the publication Faith and Form.  I remember her image and byline in the publication for...    
    
    
    The Master Plan - What It Does and Doesn't Do http://hub.am/UhwLmD     
    
    
    Residential Sun Shades - They're Inexpensive and They Work! http://hub.am/UIAXPd     
    
    
    Very impressive interview with a remarkable graphic designer whose impish creations for the New Yorker caught my eye. …http://lnkd.in/EiBaFG     
    
    
    Residential Green Building - Frequently Asked Questions http://hub.am/Pfn1g6     
    
    
    Austin's Alternative - Giving MetroRail a Ride http://hub.am/S9oN0P     
    
    
    Sandy’s devastating blow - The Washington Post http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435723904644/ …    
    
    
    Sustainable Water Solutions - Green Building (Part 1) http://hub.am/RwqTbw     
    
    
    Sustainable Water Solutions - Green Outside Your Building (Part 2) http://hub.am/SkduQG     
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred - The Treaty Oak Vigil http://is.gd/DazCrd    
    
    
    Residential Green Architecture - Frequently Asked Questions Part 2 http://hub.am/W4XrYv     
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred Site - Update - Airport Blvd & MLK, Austin http://hub.am/hqK8id    
    
    
    About Sacred Space, Holy Place Blog & The Suddenly Sacred http://hub.am/fnibkE    
    
    
    Architectural 3D Design - My Personal Perspective http://hub.am/WK0xAV     
    
    
    Church Architecture Videos, Tips For A Successful Production http://hub.am/hUUrUo    
    
    
    The Church Design Process – Does It Look Like a Church? http://hub.am/WGDHyE     
    
    
    Church Steeple Restoration - Our Lady of Guadalupe in Austin http://hub.am/YtJXaE     
    
    
    Church Closure - No Easy Solution http://hub.am/YEEaza     
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 1 http://hub.am/dEifOb    
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 2 http://is.gd/EpiAUm    
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 3 http://hub.am/fELXLA    
    
    
    Disappearing Steeples?  Not These Churches! http://hub.am/11UPisa     
    
    
    Why Hire An Architect? http://is.gd/bbLHUr    
    
    
    A foggy day off the coast of Maine.  Ilseford Dock, Little Cranberry Island http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724952022/ …    
    
    
    The Islesford Hotel, Islesford, Maine.  One of many resort hotels along the Maine coast.  Influentia http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724958649/ …    
    
    
    AD Classics: USAFA Cadet Chapel / Skidmore, Owings & Merrill http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724958700/ …    
    
    
    A building in the shape of a giant traditional Chinese coin in northeastern China was chosen as one  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724992149/ …    
    
    
    The Beijing Tianzi Hotel was ranked China’s ugliest building for 2012. The three men depict Chinese  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724992151/ …    
    
    
    Three Insulation Tips For Hot, Humid Climates http://hub.am/hXRAN2    
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred Memorial for T.D. Burnett http://hub.am/gpKAk5    
    
    
    Architectural Watercolor Prompts Questions During Tour of Spain http://hub.am/16JEH9F     
    
    
    Portland Hotel, downtown Portland Oregon, built in 1890. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187799/ …    
    
    
    Worcester Building, Portland Oregon, built in 1892. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187812/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | Century Building.  Architects: Reader, Coffin & Crocker.  Bui http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187843/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | Busch Stadium. Designed by Edward Durell Stone.  Built 1964-6 http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187929/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | A.S. Aloe Building.  International Style building constructed http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187967/ …    
    
    
    Lost San Diego - Normal School - Built in 1897, Irving Gill, architect. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725188018/ …    
    
    
    Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252507/ …    
    
    
    A unique mid-century modern light fixture at the Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flick http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252513/ …    
    
    
    Dazzling stained glass - Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252521/ …    
    
    
    Scanning The Skyline: 10 Bizarre Barcode Buildings http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725269147/ …    
    
    
    Collaborative Building Design - Does It Really Work? http://is.gd/Lswf2n    
    
    
    20 Unusual Modern Table Designs | DeMilked http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725308007/ …    
    
    
    Memorial Tree for Arline S. Hall http://hub.am/fbyoDJ    
    
    
    Mahabodhi Temple in Bodh Gaya, India http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360849/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Cat Kindergarten http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360986/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Ladprao Tuk Chang - perhaps one of the world's ugliest buildings loca http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360995/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Big Sheep Wool Gallery and Big Dog Information Center - New Zealand. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361001/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: The Giant Koala http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361007/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Gagudju Crocodile Holiday Inn, Australia. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361015/ …    
    
    
    Monster Fish in Canada by Kate and Neil, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361028/ …    
    
    
    Bulldozer building, California. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361040/ …    
    
    
    Architect as Shepherd -- Church Design http://hub.am/h8IQTK    
    
    
    Ben's article on the architecture, housing repair and giving spiritually just published in the Austi http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725504003/ …    
    
    
    TWA Terminal JFK) Airport by Eero Saarinen [Photograph: 1962  Gelatin Silver Print © Ezra Stoller -  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725539424/ …    
    
    
    Celia Chapa House Memorial -  Robert T. Martinez, Near Willow Street http://hub.am/fkX85n    
    
    
    Building Permits and Development Codes:  "Why Do I Need A Permit?" http://hub.am/eDRcWR    
    
    
    Architectural Design Process Shared - Faith & Form Article http://hub.am/1fY69qf     
    
    
    Chapel of the Holy Cross Proves Architectural Ideas Take Time http://hub.am/18CzhP9     
    
    
    Design and 3D Imaging -- What it can mean for you! http://is.gd/OaVE6G    
    
    
    Pan Am Worldport Terminal at JFK Airport - Important Buildings We Lost in 2013 - Jenny Xie - The Atl http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972687/ …    
    
    
    Prentice Women's Hospital - Chicago - Important Buildings We Lost in 2013 - Jenny Xie - The Atlantic http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972697/ …    
    
    
    Cyclorama Building at Gettysburg, built in 1962,  designed by Richard Neutra - Important Buildings W http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972711/ …    
    
    
    The State of Historic Preservation in Texas http://is.gd/PJpTU4    
    
    
    How To Get A Permit - Explaining The Codes - Part 2 http://hub.am/fO4S7D    
    
    
    Not Just a Pretty Space:  How Architects Help You During Construction http://is.gd/Bfa8AJ    
    
    
    The IRS Plane Crash Building - Why Isn't This a Sacred Site? http://is.gd/dqKxVA    
    
    
    Salvage or Demolition?  One Creative Rehab = Two Garage Apartments. http://hub.am/fOxvRF    
    
    
    Architecture and Family http://is.gd/JrJjBZ    
    
    
    The Descansos Law - NM Adds Ghost Bike Protection http://hub.am/hjRYT7    
    
    
    RE: my blog on codes - another reason to respect them:  Engineer: Tough Japanese building codes worked : http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/2011/03/12/earlyshow/saturday/main20042459.shtml … via @cbsnews    
    
    
    A Free Landscaping Idea - Salvaged Plants http://hub.am/gaFkTs    
    
    
    Church Design:  Natural Light and Video Projection http://hub.am/i3xVPF    
    
    
    Building For Your Church or Non-Profit?  Avoid These Mistakes! http://hub.am/ggTysg    
    
    
    THE ROTHKO CHAPEL http://hub.am/fz3SB3    
    
    
    Green Building Doesn't Have to Look Like That.... http://hub.am/dZbYWP    
    
    
    Car2Go - Or Not Quite Ready 2Go? http://hub.am/f4Q0BX    
    
    
    Residential Construction --The Ties that Bind   http://hub.am/ew6fNF    
    
    
    Energy Security and Energy Efficient Buildings http://hub.am/eDGQ8O    
    
    
    Residential Design -- Trim Details http://hub.am/gKt6eZ    
    
    
    Car2Go - A Reliable Alternative? http://hub.am/euPjkg    
    
    
    The Stations of the Cross Project http://is.gd/Nm3ZD3    
    
    
    McMansion Critique http://hub.am/eIhiPZ    
    
    
    Designing Church Multipurpose Halls: 10 Things to Consider http://is.gd/qt1DiI    
    
    
    Designing Church Multipurpose Rooms: 10 Things to Consider http://is.gd/Yl7rve    
    
    
    New Suddenly Sacred Site at Airport Blvd. http://hub.am/l2P4QZ    
    
    
    Why Modern Architecture http://is.gd/SVnAfr    
    
    
    Residential Design -- The Difference a Truss Makes http://hub.am/lAFOdv    
    
    
    McMansion Critique http://is.gd/a2sMeg    
    
    
    Historic Preservation Tips - Care And Feeding Your Historic Building http://hub.am/iCpW5R    
    
    
    A Touch of the Sacred in "Art In The Streets" http://hub.am/iJVoXC    
    
    
    Residential Design:  Solar Shade Studies http://hub.am/kRrE6d    
    
    
    A Closed Street Can Have Surprising Benefits http://hub.am/kChlrG    
    
    
    DFW All Faiths Chapel - A Critique http://hub.am/kBySYJ    
    
    
    Residential Design:  Solar Shade Studies http://hub.am/jDUgzZ    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 1 http://hub.am/jRNULu    
    
    
    U of Arkansas Peace Tower - Fay Jones Looks East http://hub.am/mcZfIY    
    
    
    Using Alternative Transportation - Car2Go & MetroRail http://hub.am/iWUl0v    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 2 http://hub.am/meflqt    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 3 http://hub.am/nNuGOX    
    
    
    Residential Design - A Vision from the 1960's http://hub.am/qB0lJ8    
    
    
    Residential Tip -- Saving your Bacon with Video http://hub.am/rbuVbV    
    
    
    Residential Design Tip -- Hearth and TV http://hub.am/pliKva    
    
    
    Residential Design Tip -- Coaxing the Wind http://hub.am/nhgyqG    
    
    
    Little Cranberry Island - Two Very Basic Churches http://hub.am/rbfOYP     
    
    
    Residential Green Building Tip -- HVAC and Dehumidification http://hub.am/nk08vw     
    
    
    Residential Green Building Tip -- Hot Water http://hub.am/mXfECK     
    
    
    The Green School - What it Means and the Difference It Makes http://hub.am/pUwi4u     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Mr95Aa  This is something we've grappled with for quite a while.  I wrote a piece for EnvisionChurch cataloguing a number...    
    
    
    A City Chapel in the Historic Cemetery http://is.gd/rIwc1O     
    
    
    The Building Committee - a Great Group or a Big Mess? http://hub.am/rqXMsO     
    
    
    Austin Street Art - NBA meets Mary Poppins? http://hub.am/q1ddKz     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/GxXRES  Solomon's Porch sounds like it has a lot in common with a number of established ministries that have successfully...    
    
    
    Building a Church Family Life Center in Phases http://hub.am/oaRIgY     
    
    
    Austin Churches - Hidden All-Faith Jewels http://hub.am/uM6n4H     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part One http://hub.am/tSx81j     
    
    
    A Mobile Chapel - A Truck-Stop Church http://hub.am/umXLe0     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part Two http://hub.am/tu9S1E     
    
    
    Historic Preservation Myths - Part Three http://hub.am/sApjnj     
    
    
    Church Kitchen Ideas - Before and After Examples http://hub.am/uF1e5P     
    
    
    Building Preservation Myths - Part Four http://hub.am/uhsaRV     
    
    
    Historic Renovation of a Country Inn: 15 Tips - Part One http://hub.am/uHs1jX     
    
    
    Kevin Tuerff of Envromedia is an old friend, really excited to see he's blogging! http://lnkd.in/n4_TkP     
    
    
    Historic Inn Renovation - 15 Tips, Part Two http://hub.am/s4J6ta     
    
    
    LED Lighting Comparison -- Using It NOW!! http://hub.am/rBNhxl     
    
    
    Preserving A Country Inn - 15 Tips, Part Three http://hub.am/tNNF27     
    
    
    Historic Inn Preservation - 15 Tips, Part Four http://hub.am/uxrNPD     
    
    
    Austin to LA - Mid Century Modern Sources at the LACMA http://hub.am/uKLi6o     
    
    
    Church Architecture - What Makes It So Special? http://hub.am/eyLRA6    
    
    
    Church Kitchen Details - Don't Overlook These! http://hub.am/xXxGy7     
    
    
    Austin Churches Designed by Heimsath Architects http://hub.am/xTbkcU     
    
    
    Building Preservation Is Greenest! http://hub.am/wb3Xbq     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9tCKCc  Michael, Thanks for alerting us to this most interesting opinion.  I happen to agree - the impetus to make art,...    
    
    
    Architectural Watercolor Renderings Are Perfect For Master Plans http://hub.am/AdMqqG     
    
    
    Building Conservation - A Great Resource at the University of Texas http://hub.am/ysJ3LG     
    
    
    Adoration Chapel Stained Glass http://hub.am/zxdXnn     
    
    
    Church Design:  Top 10 Things to Know for Building Committees http://hub.am/hUxmFI    
    
    
    Demand Charge for Church Electricity:  Is This a Good Idea? http://hub.am/wm40ku     
    
    
    What is a Narthex? http://hub.am/yHhv4j     
    
    
    Liturgical Objects Get A New Life http://hub.am/GEz3Ws     
    
    
    Church Interior Design - Is Beige The Only Color? http://hub.am/GYljZI     
    
    
    Non Denominational Chapel of the Snows - World's Southernmost Church http://hub.am/HjStUL     
    
    
    Residential Solar Panels -- A First Report http://hub.am/Io1gpz     
    
    
    What Is A Church? An Outsider's Perspective http://hub.am/IAc9GH     
    
    
    Electric Car Implications - Saving Gas Is Just The Beginning http://hub.am/KwqUEB     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/r5EVRu  Wonderful spaces, but they really could be anywhere.  They have nothing to do with Corb's masterpiece, but perhaps...    
    
    
    The Church and Development - What's Missing Here? http://hub.am/K3EFtC     
    
    
    Building Restoration After Catastrophe http://blog.heimsath.com/blog-0/bid/84476/building-restoration-after-catastrophe …    
    
    
    Church Design -- Worship Space Lighting Control http://hub.am/MG4S36     
    
    
    Church Design - Then and Now http://hub.am/LBbdzd     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/rByUpf  Thanks for calling attention to this.  I'm not offended, but I do think it shows some insensitivity in an otherwise...    
    
    
    Master Planning for Congregations - 10 Essentials http://hub.am/PKO4i7     
    
    
    LEDs -- Energy Efficient Lighting for Residential and Church Design http://hub.am/e9Y5xK    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/7EG2Mj  We commissioned a wonderful liturgical artist, George Hoelzeman for a modern version of the "gates of paradise" --...    
    
    
    Sacred Place is Home For The Arts http://hub.am/TEZ9yD     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/aDMDE9  Betty Meyer, for me, was the publication Faith and Form.  I remember her image and byline in the publication for...    
    
    
    The Master Plan - What It Does and Doesn't Do http://hub.am/UhwLmD     
    
    
    Residential Sun Shades - They're Inexpensive and They Work! http://hub.am/UIAXPd     
    
    
    Very impressive interview with a remarkable graphic designer whose impish creations for the New Yorker caught my eye. …http://lnkd.in/EiBaFG     
    
    
    Residential Green Building - Frequently Asked Questions http://hub.am/Pfn1g6     
    
    
    Austin's Alternative - Giving MetroRail a Ride http://hub.am/S9oN0P     
    
    
    Sandy’s devastating blow - The Washington Post http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435723904644/ …    
    
    
    Sustainable Water Solutions - Green Building (Part 1) http://hub.am/RwqTbw     
    
    
    Sustainable Water Solutions - Green Outside Your Building (Part 2) http://hub.am/SkduQG     
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred - The Treaty Oak Vigil http://is.gd/DazCrd    
    
    
    Residential Green Architecture - Frequently Asked Questions Part 2 http://hub.am/W4XrYv     
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred Site - Update - Airport Blvd & MLK, Austin http://hub.am/hqK8id    
    
    
    About Sacred Space, Holy Place Blog & The Suddenly Sacred http://hub.am/fnibkE    
    
    
    Architectural 3D Design - My Personal Perspective http://hub.am/WK0xAV     
    
    
    Church Architecture Videos, Tips For A Successful Production http://hub.am/hUUrUo    
    
    
    The Church Design Process – Does It Look Like a Church? http://hub.am/WGDHyE     
    
    
    Church Steeple Restoration - Our Lady of Guadalupe in Austin http://hub.am/YtJXaE     
    
    
    Church Closure - No Easy Solution http://hub.am/YEEaza     
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 1 http://hub.am/dEifOb    
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 2 http://is.gd/EpiAUm    
    
    
    Designing Church Kitchens -- Part 3 http://hub.am/fELXLA    
    
    
    Disappearing Steeples?  Not These Churches! http://hub.am/11UPisa     
    
    
    Why Hire An Architect? http://is.gd/bbLHUr    
    
    
    A foggy day off the coast of Maine.  Ilseford Dock, Little Cranberry Island http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724952022/ …    
    
    
    The Islesford Hotel, Islesford, Maine.  One of many resort hotels along the Maine coast.  Influentia http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724958649/ …    
    
    
    AD Classics: USAFA Cadet Chapel / Skidmore, Owings & Merrill http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724958700/ …    
    
    
    A building in the shape of a giant traditional Chinese coin in northeastern China was chosen as one  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724992149/ …    
    
    
    The Beijing Tianzi Hotel was ranked China’s ugliest building for 2012. The three men depict Chinese  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435724992151/ …    
    
    
    Three Insulation Tips For Hot, Humid Climates http://hub.am/hXRAN2    
    
    
    Suddenly Sacred Memorial for T.D. Burnett http://hub.am/gpKAk5    
    
    
    Architectural Watercolor Prompts Questions During Tour of Spain http://hub.am/16JEH9F     
    
    
    Portland Hotel, downtown Portland Oregon, built in 1890. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187799/ …    
    
    
    Worcester Building, Portland Oregon, built in 1892. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187812/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | Century Building.  Architects: Reader, Coffin & Crocker.  Bui http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187843/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | Busch Stadium. Designed by Edward Durell Stone.  Built 1964-6 http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187929/ …    
    
    
    Built St. Louis | Vanished Buildings | A.S. Aloe Building.  International Style building constructed http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725187967/ …    
    
    
    Lost San Diego - Normal School - Built in 1897, Irving Gill, architect. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725188018/ …    
    
    
    Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252507/ …    
    
    
    A unique mid-century modern light fixture at the Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flick http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252513/ …    
    
    
    Dazzling stained glass - Chapel for the Children, Austin by _jjph, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725252521/ …    
    
    
    Scanning The Skyline: 10 Bizarre Barcode Buildings http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725269147/ …    
    
    
    Collaborative Building Design - Does It Really Work? http://is.gd/Lswf2n    
    
    
    20 Unusual Modern Table Designs | DeMilked http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725308007/ …    
    
    
    Memorial Tree for Arline S. Hall http://hub.am/fbyoDJ    
    
    
    Mahabodhi Temple in Bodh Gaya, India http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360849/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Cat Kindergarten http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360986/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Ladprao Tuk Chang - perhaps one of the world's ugliest buildings loca http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725360995/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Big Sheep Wool Gallery and Big Dog Information Center - New Zealand. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361001/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: The Giant Koala http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361007/ …    
    
    
    Buildings Shaped Like Animals: Gagudju Crocodile Holiday Inn, Australia. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361015/ …    
    
    
    Monster Fish in Canada by Kate and Neil, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361028/ …    
    
    
    Bulldozer building, California. http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725361040/ …    
    
    
    Architect as Shepherd -- Church Design http://hub.am/h8IQTK    
    
    
    Ben's article on the architecture, housing repair and giving spiritually just published in the Austi http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725504003/ …    
    
    
    TWA Terminal JFK) Airport by Eero Saarinen [Photograph: 1962  Gelatin Silver Print © Ezra Stoller -  http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725539424/ …    
    
    
    Celia Chapa House Memorial -  Robert T. Martinez, Near Willow Street http://hub.am/fkX85n    
    
    
    Building Permits and Development Codes:  "Why Do I Need A Permit?" http://hub.am/eDRcWR    
    
    
    Architectural Design Process Shared - Faith & Form Article http://hub.am/1fY69qf     
    
    
    Chapel of the Holy Cross Proves Architectural Ideas Take Time http://hub.am/18CzhP9     
    
    
    Design and 3D Imaging -- What it can mean for you! http://is.gd/OaVE6G    
    
    
    Pan Am Worldport Terminal at JFK Airport - Important Buildings We Lost in 2013 - Jenny Xie - The Atl http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972687/ …    
    
    
    Prentice Women's Hospital - Chicago - Important Buildings We Lost in 2013 - Jenny Xie - The Atlantic http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972697/ …    
    
    
    Cyclorama Building at Gettysburg, built in 1962,  designed by Richard Neutra - Important Buildings W http://pinterest.com/pin/549861435725972711/ …    
    
    
    The State of Historic Preservation in Texas http://is.gd/PJpTU4    
    
    
    How To Get A Permit - Explaining The Codes - Part 2 http://hub.am/fO4S7D    
    
    
    Not Just a Pretty Space:  How Architects Help You During Construction http://is.gd/Bfa8AJ    
    
    
    The IRS Plane Crash Building - Why Isn't This a Sacred Site? http://is.gd/dqKxVA    
    
    
    Salvage or Demolition?  One Creative Rehab = Two Garage Apartments. http://hub.am/fOxvRF    
    
    
    Architecture and Family http://is.gd/JrJjBZ    
    
    
    The Descansos Law - NM Adds Ghost Bike Protection http://hub.am/hjRYT7    
    
    
    RE: my blog on codes - another reason to respect them:  Engineer: Tough Japanese building codes worked : http://www.cbsnews.com/stories/2011/03/12/earlyshow/saturday/main20042459.shtml … via @cbsnews    
    
    
    A Free Landscaping Idea - Salvaged Plants http://hub.am/gaFkTs    
    
    
    Church Design:  Natural Light and Video Projection http://hub.am/i3xVPF    
    
    
    Building For Your Church or Non-Profit?  Avoid These Mistakes! http://hub.am/ggTysg    
    
    
    THE ROTHKO CHAPEL http://hub.am/fz3SB3    
    
    
    Green Building Doesn't Have to Look Like That.... http://hub.am/dZbYWP    
    
    
    Car2Go - Or Not Quite Ready 2Go? http://hub.am/f4Q0BX    
    
    
    Residential Construction --The Ties that Bind   http://hub.am/ew6fNF    
    
    
    Energy Security and Energy Efficient Buildings http://hub.am/eDGQ8O    
    
    
    Residential Design -- Trim Details http://hub.am/gKt6eZ    
    
    
    Car2Go - A Reliable Alternative? http://hub.am/euPjkg    
    
    
    The Stations of the Cross Project http://is.gd/Nm3ZD3    
    
    
    McMansion Critique http://hub.am/eIhiPZ    
    
    
    Designing Church Multipurpose Halls: 10 Things to Consider http://is.gd/qt1DiI    
    
    
    Designing Church Multipurpose Rooms: 10 Things to Consider http://is.gd/Yl7rve    
    
    
    New Suddenly Sacred Site at Airport Blvd. http://hub.am/l2P4QZ    
    
    
    Why Modern Architecture http://is.gd/SVnAfr    
    
    
    Residential Design -- The Difference a Truss Makes http://hub.am/lAFOdv    
    
    
    McMansion Critique http://is.gd/a2sMeg    
    
    
    Historic Preservation Tips - Care And Feeding Your Historic Building http://hub.am/iCpW5R    
    
    
    A Touch of the Sacred in "Art In The Streets" http://hub.am/iJVoXC    
    
    
    Residential Design:  Solar Shade Studies http://hub.am/kRrE6d    
    
    
    A Closed Street Can Have Surprising Benefits http://hub.am/kChlrG    
    
    
    DFW All Faiths Chapel - A Critique http://hub.am/kBySYJ    
    
    
    Residential Design:  Solar Shade Studies http://hub.am/jDUgzZ    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 1 http://hub.am/jRNULu    
    
    
    U of Arkansas Peace Tower - Fay Jones Looks East http://hub.am/mcZfIY    
    
    
    Using Alternative Transportation - Car2Go & MetroRail http://hub.am/iWUl0v    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 2 http://hub.am/meflqt    
    
    
    Baptismal Fonts -- How, What, Where? -- Part 3 http://hub.am/nNuGOX    
    
    
    Residential Design - A Vision from the 1960's http://hub.am/qB0lJ8    
    
    
    Residential Tip -- Saving your Bacon with Video http://hub.am/rbuVbV    
    
    
    Residential Design Tip -- Hearth and TV http://hub.am/pliKva    
    
    
    Residential Design Tip -- Coaxing the Wind http://hub.am/nhgyqG    
    
    
    