FBI seeking social media monitoring tool http://bit.ly/AguEVp  ... they're not alone!    
    
    
    66% of Americans buy their lunch every day, avg=$37/wk-> $2,000 /yr.  http://bit.ly/A7Ju5Z . think+measure=insight. insight+action=change    
    
    
    @metabrown312 Any action is change...I don't think I'd say that. Some actions repeat past behavior, but perhaps we quibble over language :)    
    
    
    @metabrown312 touché!    
    
    
    @jamet123 @merv @ajbowles true enough. But #predictive #analytics is most often like building furniture 100 yrs ago-1-at-a-time construction    
    
    
    @merv I wasn't with you, sorry to say    
    
    
    @merv would love to, maybe another time.    
    
    
    @JAdP @jamet123 @merv @ajbowles fine-crafted furniture is better than Ikea, but how many of us could afford it?    
    
    
    @JAdP @jamet123 @merv @ajbowles I agree that "cookbook" models don't typically work--I argue this frequently. One day this will change.    
    
    
    @JAdP @ajbowles @jamet123 @merv Some companies are making a stab at automation. #SAS RPM is an excellent first step-does 80% of what I do.    
    
    
    @JAdP @ajbowles @jamet123 @merv last 20% sometimes is very imp't, sometimes not. Sometimes an 80% solution is enough to improve decisions    
    
    
    I'm helping companies pick #datamining tools now. It's more about the pull and push of data & how models will be used than algorithms    
    
    
    @data_mining Top #datamining influencers on #Klout; I mentioned top 5 for me, but didn't mention @data_mining (Eric King) was ahead of me!    
    
    
    @data_mining clickthrough didn't work for me, but this does...http://www.facebook.com/pages/The-Modeling-Agency-TMA/189136044441536    
    
    
    @gilomarv contact me on linkedin and we can connect there. It will be fun to catch up.    
    
    
    The Potential of Predictive Analytics in Higher Ed - By Reihan Salam - The Agenda - National Review Online http://bit.ly/wYyreU     
    
    
    @B2Bspecialist I'd love to know more. Please send and email or call.    
    
    
    Using @KNIME for teaching text mining this month. I've been pleasantly surprised at its ease of use. Nice!    
    
    
    Oracle Debuts Analytical Software For 'Big Data' Tasks http://bit.ly/AdWXaL  - bundles its Oracle R Enterprise with ODM. Interesting...    
    
    
    (1/2) Data mining tool selection cannot be done with checklists. I'm on my 6th selection process for customers in the past year now.    
    
    
    (2/2) 4 selections have been completed, two in process. I've recommend 4 different tools. Why? Their needs were different.    
    
    
    (3/2) key factors: experience of users, cost, integration with databases for deployment, algorithms, and support.    
    
    
    Check out this article from FOX News. US government looks to mine social media to combat terrorist attacks, uprisings: http://fxn.ws/wr1A05     
    
    
    3 essential principles to consider prior pulling data for #predictive #analytics: 1) know your data; 2) know your data; 3) know your data.    
    
    
    know 1) level of aggregation applied to all derived fields; 2) what "NULL", 0, and "" mean; 3) time period data was collected    
    
    
    If you don't know these characteristics of your data (and many more!), you'll have no idea what the predictive models actually measure.    
    
    
    Unfortunately, I'm speaking from experience.    
    
    
    @metabrown312 Very interesting... IMHO any "data scientist" who knows  C++/C# should also learn SQL. SQL is a diff. animal, complements C++    
    
    
    @metabrown312 Once you know C++, you can pick up Java, R, Perl, etc. easily. SQL is critical in big data; how SQL code is written is diff.    
    
    
    @metabrown312 "pick-up" => "become proficient". My background is C; java is still not good, but I can read and edit java code.    
    
    
    KDD-2012: Industry/Gov Track Program Comm. http://bit.ly/wM5GCu  -- time to read papers (114)! Anyone going to Beijing? http://bit.ly/zyM1xi     
    
    
    Jeremy Lin and the Guy Who Saw Linsanity Coming - http://WSJ.com  http://on.wsj.com/yygedk  -- great example of measuring the right things    
    
    
    Giving text mining class final exam for UCSD Ext. program http://bit.ly/z3RRZB . #KNIME was great. can't wait for next time I teach it in May    
    
    
    My latest Data Mining and Predictive Analytics blog post: Target, Pregnancy, and Predictive Analytics, Part I http://bit.ly/y3NpoI     
    
    
    @kylemaxwell @data_nerd @smartdatacollective would be nice to think we were...I'd say the score for me was "nerdy": 1,214, "sexy":0    :)    
    
    
    What Is a Data Scientist (and What Isn't)? @neilraden http://soc.li/WfUgqwQ     
    
    
    Posted Saturday on my blog: Target, Pregnancy and #Predictive #Analytics, Part I http://bit.ly/oPLq4i     
    
    
    Data Mining andPredictive Analytics: Target, Pregnancy, and Predictive Analytics,Part II is up http://bit.ly/wtJqWl     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/q49N7C  I'm surprised at how many votes there are for "home made". That's great for what Neil Raden calls the Type I "Data...    
    
    
    Behind the Cover Story: How Much Does Target Know? - http://NYTimes.com  http://nyti.ms/Aestmw     
    
    
    NYTimes interview w/ Charles Duhigg--he talks to the "creepiness" factor in the interview. Duhigg gets it-it is about trends not individuals    
    
    
    But, ultimately, *individuals* are scored, so predictive models hit us at the individual level. At what point is it too personal? Good Quest    
    
    
    Key line from Duhigg interview on #predictive #analytics: "Pole told me that it [an 'off limits' topic] is more art than science."    
    
    
    @kdnuggets @metabrown312 agree in part-SQL not great for all algorithms, but is just fine for many (kNN, Decision Trees, even regression).    
    
    
    Looking forward to #eTail West next week with my colleagues and friends at Smarter Remarketer (@SmarterHQ) to tout behavioral analytics.    
    
    
    I don't care how big the data is as long as it is enough data.    
    
    
    cool service--Tweets about @deanabb have reached 20,953 people http://tweetreach.com/reach?q=%40deanabb&s=twitter … via @tweetreachapp    
    
    
    (1/2) The smaller the effect, the more data we need to measure it. More noise->need more data. High cardinality->more data.    
    
    
    (2/2) 
--Big data is often big because the target population is (relatively) small. 
--Big data also big bec. we have only indirect measures    
    
    
    (1/2) @data_nerd @mich8elwu the author states " the goal is to identify the relevant data from the irrelevant data (noise)"    
    
    
    (2/2) @data_nerd @mich8elwu conclusions don't address what information the "noise" contains (lots!) even if it isn't the "good stuff" :)    
    
    
    Behavioral Marketing Program Increases Conversion Rates for Footwear etc. http://multichannelmerchant.com/ecommerce/behavioral-marketing-conversions-footwear-etc-0223tpp9/ …    
    
    
    @data_nerd Thx!    
    
    
    Surrender to a Buyer Power - The Colbert Report - http://bit.ly/yfdzkp  - #predictive #analytics makes it to the mainstream. #funny!    
    
    
    (1/3) There is a fundamental misunderstanding of the power of the Target predictive models. Eric Siegel #pawcon tried to explain this on Fox    
    
    
    (2/3) the models weren't crystal balls predicting perfectly who was pregnant. Yes they were better than random->they could used for coupons    
    
    
    (3/3) Models didn't *know* anything. They separated pregnant- from non-pregnant-woman purchase patterns--any of us could probably do it too.    
    
    
    (4/3) Target & other retailers are wise not to push too hard. #uplift #modeling principles apply--some are turned off by the hard sell.    
    
    
    @mich8elwu @data_nerd @jasebell I'm sure the terminology is getting in the way! Without the "noise" we can't differentiate signal from noise    
    
    
    @mich8elwu @data_nerd @jasebell so I would never equate noise with "do not want". Even in signal processing, the noise much be characterized    
    
    
    @mich8elwu @data_nerd @jasebell in order to separate it from the signal. The more nonlinear the noise, the more "noise" data you need    
    
    
    @mich8elwu @data_nerd @jasebell that stated, I'm sure we're on the same side on this, but as I mentioned before, just are clashing on terms    
    
    
    @mich8elwu: [Lively debate w/ @deanabb & @data_nerd : What Data is Irrelevant http://ow.ly/9i9X3  -I'll comment (again!) later today! fun!    
    
    
    Read data mining / predictive analytics ▸ today's top stories via @nelsonforte @do6986 @welkaim ▸ http://paper.li/deanabb/1313761301 …    
    
    
    @FayeMerrideth Yes, I'll be busy at #PAWcon next week with 2 talks, a panel, moderating, and a workshop! See you there.    
    
    
    RT Planning call for "Liberating Big Data", webinar next Tues w @BrentLeary @deanabb & IBM's Richard Cloud http://bit.ly/whjz6Q  #SMTlive    
    
    
    @maggiefox thanks for moderating...looking forward to the webinar    
    
    
    light on tweeting this week and probably for March...tis the season to get work done and make customers happy!    
    
    
    Looking forward to #pawcon and #tawcon this coming week! Will tweet from there 4 sure.    
    
    
    Today's top stories in data mining / predictive analytics via @chicagokentlaw @salfordsystems ▸ http://paper.li/deanabb/1313761301?utm_source=subscription&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=paper_sub …    
    
    
    Heading from SAN to SFO to #PAWCon   If I can get thru screening--insane/slow line.  Why?    
    
    
    Gettin ready for webinar Liberating Big Data | Social Media Today http://bit.ly/w5j0Et  @ 12 EST with Richard Cloud @BrentLeary-come join us!    
    
    
    #smtlive @brentleary companies have challenge to be responsible with the data we use.    
    
    
    @ShimaMIACOTH @socialmedia2day The answer is "yes", but we have to be realistic about what things we can predict--can't predict 1-off events    
    
    
    @ShimaMIACOTH @socialmedia2day which analytic tool is too complex an answer for a tweet; depends on what question u need to answer re: data    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf Osama fayyd keynoting now. Big data--how does the data impact my business    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf hadoop / map-reduce not efficient or effective for statistical modeling (mostly preprocessing for #datamining)    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf 
30% of world is online. 60 hours of video uploaded to youtube every minute    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf big data...recency is critical. model: yahoo modeled "buy a car within 90days->display ads lift of 9X. email 3X    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf display ads use text analytics to place ads in the right place...don't put Greek Vacations in news about Greek riots    
    
    
    #TAWCon @osamaf hard to understand user intent: bass (music) vs. bass (fish). context matters (the semantic web!)    
    
    
    #TAWcon talk by Randy Saaf on sentiment in twitter for stock picking. Use stats+machine learning in ensembles    
    
    
    #TAWcon Andrew Fast describing the taxonomy of text mining methods (he created a tree segmentation of the text analytics talks at the conf!)    
    
    
    #TAWcon Andrew Fast 8 document classification, just a few on concept extraction and NLP.    
    
    
    @ShimaMIACOTH ?    
    
    
    #PAWcon getting ready to start the workshop Advanced Methods Hands-On with Statsoft.    
    
    
    Audio Archive: Liberating Big Data http://soc.li/UU3XGPd  with @BrentLeary, Richard Cloud and me. Discussed #bigdata, Target, and more    
    
    
    Defining "Big Data" - My interview with SAS at Predictive Analytics World http://bit.ly/ydmQnE     
    
    
    @metabrown312 one could argue one can never really use it all. another question is this: can we use enough to be useful?    
    
    
    CourtVision by Kirk Goldsberry http://bit.ly/GUJox0  -- intuitive, good visuals, and tries to find ways to explain the data    
    
    
    Joint Statistical Meeting 2012: Moderating a Statistical Learning & Data Mining Session-should be very interesting! http://bit.ly/H0fSGN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Nice to have wifi on #SWA flight from LGA to MDW, but it is sloooow!    
    
    
    (1/2) RT @data_nerd @nealschaffer Is #Mobile Driving Increase #SocialMedia? URL notes 30% mobile usrs r in China&India http://bit.ly/H4tQxe     
    
    
    (2/2) 30% mobile usrs r in China&India. But is this really interesting? 26+% of world pop is in China and India!    
    
    
    A taxonomy of tools that support the fluent and flexible use of visualizations http://lnkd.in/5aMUMw     
    
    
    Fraud Analysis in San Diego makes the Union Tribune: Worried about credit fraud? These companies are fighting for you  http://bit.ly/HPVEQc     
    
    
    @metabrown312 @kdnuggets appears to be an Aberdeen report that costs $399, but apparently it is free for now...I'll sign up and let you know    
    
    
    Will be on #dmradio today at 3pm EDT-Mining Enterprise Data with an Open Mind http://bit.ly/Hgb8Ns , with @kdnuggets, Eric Siegel & more    
    
    
    #dmradio beginning the show now...    
    
    
    #DMradio Bernie Spang (IBM)-challenge is understanding what is even possible to do with #bigdata. agreed. #bigdata can be a paradigm shift    
    
    
    #DMRadio Gregory Piatetsky #bigdata is a marketing term (what will we call big data in 3 years?), but it does capture the idea well    
    
    
    #DMRadio @kdnuggets referenced Aberdeen Group Analyst Insight: companies using #PredictiveAnalytics: 73% higher click-thru & 75% higher lift    
    
    
    #DMRadio Eric Siegel--#predictiveanalytics often valuable not be predicting very accurately, but by doing better than guessing    
    
    
    Latest Blog Post: Why Defining the Target Variable in Predictive Analytics is Critical http://bit.ly/HNVGtY     
    
    
    #DataMining and #PredictiveAnalytics: pick the target variable that models risk not your system http://bit.ly/oPLq4i     
    
    
    To Sample or Not to Sample...Does it Even Matter? - Bill Franks on @smartdataco http://bit.ly/HvxPzf . just commented: when to sample IMHO    
    
    
    Back on SWA flight using WiFi (SAN->MDW). As before, brutally slow. Not expecting T1, but how about 33.6 baud? And please no more Error 504!    
    
    
    quick blog post: the always funny Dilbert on Database marketing and spam http://bit.ly/HCx4oO     
    
    
    #predictive #analytics doesn't tell you the features to create. It tells you how predictive they are (or are not).    
    
    
    @metabrown312 my linkedin network is actually not big. My policy is to only connect to people I've met in person. Currently, 374 connects    
    
    
    @metabrown312 I've wondered too. Funny think is I'm ranked #1 in Predictive Analytics, Linear & Logistic Regr, Decision Trees, Cluster Anal.    
    
    
    @metabrown312 why indeed. Flattering...yes. accurate? ummm... no    
    
    
    @metabrown312 Of the data mining list, I'm connected to 6 (of the top 16 shown) and 2nd to 8 of them. So maybe these connections help.    
    
    
    RT  @kdnuggets alcohol may enhance problem solving skills http://bit.ly/IvgCFa  BAC 0.07=>illegal to drive, better Prob Solv. Really?    
    
    
    BAC 0.07: could it be reflexes are impaired, but using 'irrational' permutations to solve problems is a good thing? Should we all try it?    
    
    
    Isn't this what helps Random Forests succeed? (random variable subset selection)    
    
    
    hope to see u @ #pawcon Toronto April 25-26. Also teaching Hands-On #predictive #analytics using #statistica on Apr27 http://bit.ly/JfCUtw     
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis - call-out to #Predixion as easy-to-use UI for sentiment analysis.    
    
    
    #DMRadio: Sentiment Analysis - #IBM describing traditional BI tools, but 90% of data-the firehose-is not interesting. Must ID interstng data    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis -- what's next for #IBM? Twitter and qualifying comments (including segmenting into influencer, consumer, etc.)    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis: Stephanie McReynolds...social media is #1 consumer activity on the web (80%!)    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis: Stephanie McReynolds: social media is not just #big #data, but valuable data. SNA->influence->business strategy    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis: Stephanie McReynolds: not just loudest voice...it's about influence    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis: Stephanie McReynolds: who is being retweeted? distance retweets travel...-> reach of a tweet -> influence    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis w/ Stephanie McReynolds: what is the ROI of Social Media? Still early stages. EX: zynga.    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis w/ Stephanie McReynolds: Q: do you measure ROI? 75% of responders said no. Sign of where industry is    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis w/ Stephanie McReynolds: @jimericson do we have the KPIs to measure ROI? @deanabb: guess "yes", though imperfect    
    
    
    #DMRadio Sentiment Analysis show:  enjoyed it! Thanks for the topic and guests. Gotta go...    
    
    
    #SASGF12 live stream and taped sessions available at http://www.livestream.com/sasglobalforum2012 …    
    
    
    just touched down in Toronto for Predictive Analytics World. Looking forward to the new venue, though it's a bit chillier here than San Die…    
    
    
    @AnalyticsQueen great seeing you at #pawcon too. And the bonus is I *finally* get to hear your Five Myths of #Predictive #Analytics talk!    
    
    
    #PAWCon MTV social Analytics driven by VP of Analytics suspecting the influence but needing to quantify the effect>>measure first then model    
    
    
    #Pawcon ready for @AnalyticsQueen Piyanka Jain's talk: Five Myths of Predictive Analytics    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Myth #1: #predictive #analytics is something new. 
First application < 15th Century.    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen first credit score model 1930 (Fisher and Durand)    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen aside...Netflix winner from 2008 not being used because the ensembles are so difficult to run (complex).    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Myth #2: perfection in #predictive #analytics. Even "good" models make lots of errors    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Myth #3: we should always use #predictive #analytics (when we've got the data). No, it's expensive. Justify with ROI    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Consider using simpler methods first: profiling, correlation analysis, trend analysis, etc.    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Myth #4: good tool = good model. No "press the button" solution.    
    
    
    #pawcon We don't find any #predictive #analytics data cleansing tools. Why not? We have create a near endless list of ways to corrupt data!    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen Myth: good models->get used and generate $$$? Often missing link is buyin from decision makers    
    
    
    #PAWcon @AnalyticsQueen uses BADIR(tm) methodology, 5 steps in process: (similar to CRISP-DM).    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM - IBM goes after "grand challenges" Watson wasn't the goal in of itself. NLP was bec. 80% of data is unstructured    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM - Jeopardy--2500 types of questions, most freq type 3% of pop-> long tail, ambiguities. Not good for queries    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM Structured approach => build databases of all possible Qs and corresponding answers. NLP reduces combinatorics    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM - separate teams worked on different pieces: hypoth. generation, hypoth. scoring, final merge/rank, etc.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM - key: algorithms keep lots of candidate answers in the running for as long as possible.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM 16 TB memory, 20TB hard drive->almost all data held in memory. 20TB is small for all the data->a focused problem    
    
    
    #PAWcon Edward Nazarko IBM working with Wellpoint as first commercial application of Watson technology->medical diagnoses    
    
    
    #PAWcon Thanks for a great 2-day conference. See you in Chicago!    
    
    
    Latest blog post: another wisdom of crowds winner from the eMetrics / #PAWcon conference in Toronto: http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com     
    
    
    Leaving Toronto after a very nice #PAWcon inaugural event. Hanson workshop had fascinating group of attendees. See you in Chicago!    
    
    
    @MarnieLandon great meeting you at #PAWcon, but no tweets on the conference from such a prolific tweeter? :)    
    
    
    Want to go to #PAWcon Chicago? Click http://bit.ly/JZw9BG  and use the code DAB12 to get 15% off the price for 2 Day and Combo passes    
    
    
    @brunoaziza Strata? I wish! Next #datamining speaking gigs are @salfordsystems, a private Fortune 500 conf., #SAS connection, and #pawcon.    
    
    
    @brunoaziza would love to talk before #PAWcon, but at least wecan catch up there. Cheers!    
    
    
    Thanks to @Unilytics-http://unilytics.com-for providing data used in the wisdom of crowds experiment I blogged on here: http://bit.ly/K58b86     
    
    
    @revodavid: critique is not at you, of course, but with IHME.    
    
    
    @revodavid I got really confused when it appeared (from colors) that M life expectancy was higher than F in China, Saudi Arabia, and Mexico!    
    
    
    @revodavid scales are definitely a problem, but there are enough colors in the spectrum to accomodate. :)    
    
    
    @kdnuggets Data Visual: The Dwindling Arctic Ice Cap http://shar.es/2NOsw  -> not the 1st time->headline from 1/25/1950 http://bit.ly/Jk7xUv     
    
    
    Lies That ‘Leak’ Through Facial Expressions - Ideas Market - WSJ http://on.wsj.com/KIFHO6 ; Is 69% accuracy good?    
    
    
    Lies That ‘Leak’ Through Facial Expressions - Ideas Market - WSJ http://on.wsj.com/KIFHO6 ; Is 69% accuracy good on a 50/50 decision?    
    
    
    @kdnuggets data mining software poll still open: http://www.kdnuggets.com/2012/05/new-poll-analytics-data-mining-software-used.html …    
    
    
    At @salfordsystems Data Mining conference today and speaking on survey analysis.    
    
    
    Dan Steinberg kicking off the @salfordsystems #datamining conference. Ref to SanFran 2004 conf--only one with all 4 creators of CART there.    
    
    
    @salfordsystems #datamining 4 creators (Breiman, Friedman, Olshen, Stone) on panel: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XaeQo1KSmjA … -- can get full video from Salford    
    
    
    #salforddatamining kathleen kane (Fidelity) on True Lift modeling -- don't spend $$ on customers who will respond anyway!    
    
    
    #salforddatamining Kathleen Kane: Ex from attrition "look-alikes" model, contacted them, they attrite at higher rate then untreated. Yikes!    
    
    
    @SmarterHQ @kylelacey can you pick me up in San Diego?    
    
    
    Angoss Software and Lexalytics Form Partnership (via @kdnggets):  http://www.kdnuggets.com/2012/06/angoss-lexalytics-partnership.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+kdnuggets-data-mining-analytics+%28KDnuggets%3A+Data+Mining+and+Analytics%29 …. A natural fit    
    
    
    Are you a good story-teller? Successfuly explaning predictive models requires telling "data stories" (via TechTarget) http://bit.ly/JEIpb0     
    
    
    at @SASsoftware Customer Connection for Data Mining today. Speaking on 5 pet peeves in #predictive #analytics.    
    
    
    @SmarterHQ Hope the day goes well. Wish I could be there with you!    
    
    
    A big reason for #bigdata: enough data to segment and build custom for each segment. Context: "Segment" models in Enterprise Miner    
    
    
    Prepping for the 10am EDT JMP "analytically speaking" webinar. http://www.jmp.com/speaking     
    
    
    There's got to be a tie-in with #predictive #analytics somewhere; this post explains how to memorize a deck of cards http://artofmanliness.com/2012/06/01/how-to-memorize-a-deck-of-cards/?utm_source=Daily+Subscribers&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=53fff48dbb-RSS_EMAIL_CAMPAIGN/ …    
    
    
    Why math is still practical: Math professor's side mirror that eliminates 'blind spot' receives US patent  HT @Drudge_Report    
    
    
    #Pawcon Predictive Analytics World / Chicago coming in less than 2 weeks. 15% off registration using my code DAB12 at http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/chicago/register.php …    
    
    
    #Pawcon I'm also teaching an Advanced Methods Hands-on workshop 6/28 using @StatSoft Statistica. Can still to sign up! http://predictiveanalyticsworld.com/chicago/2012/handson_predictive_analytics.php …    
    
    
    (1/2) RT @minethatdata Executive tells me, "I just don't trust my analyst. No context around her work. All theory, no common sense to it."    
    
    
    (2/2) Analysts need "common sense" or else they generate great solutions to irrelevant "problems" or ones that can never be implement.    
    
    
    #JMP webcast Analytically Speaking hosted by @annemilley available On Demand at http://jmp.com/about/events/webcasts/ondemand_detail.shtml?reglink=70130000001rXs0 …. It was a fun interview / webcast!    
    
    
    I'll be moderating a JSM session on Wed Aug 1: "Predictive Analytics and Data Mining: The Software Makers" http://www.amstat.org/meetings/jsm/2012/onlineprogram/AbstractDetails.cfm?abstractid=303714 …    
    
    
    A blast from the past...John Elder and @deanabb at Barron Associates http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2012/06/where-it-began-john-elder-and-dean.html …    
    
    
    @Inga745 hi    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/skNdgp  Mark: I agree that's what a data scientist *should* be, but those with the title of data scientist that I see tend...    
    
    
    en route to #PAWcon / Chicago. In honor of being in Chicago, I'm taking the train in.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Eric Siegel keynote. Marketing is like dating. Ex: groundhog day. Bill Murray tests >1 hypotheses under the same conditions    
    
    
    #PAWCon predictive Analytics can predict the influence on behavior. Not just the behavior    
    
    
    #PAWCon Eric Siegel. #predictive #analytics helps us  decide not just *if we should treat but *which treatment (or none) gives best results    
    
    
    @jamet123 you were just referenced by Jason Verlen in the IBMTalk at #PAWCon    
    
    
    #PAWCon Antonia de Medinaceli speaking on fraud detection. Outlier detection: need to exine multi variate outliers    
    
    
    #PAWCon Jon Bates (Adobe) talk "be a social marketing hero". Chaos reigns in social media. We need intelligence to cut thru    
    
    
    #PAWCon Jon Bates. Forecasted sentiment of tweets before tweete published for MTV. Set record at time of >8k tweets/sec    
    
    
    #PAWCon expert panel on best practices. Jason Verlen: don't be scared just because data not fully "fixed". Make progress with what u have    
    
    
    #PAWCon expert panel on best practices: Antonia de Medinaceli tech success not nec. indicative of business success. Must b able 2 deploy!    
    
    
    #PAWCon expert panel on best practices: Kathy Lange ( #SAS) Analysts have to communicate with IT about data--often have different views    
    
    
    #PAWCon expert panel on best practices: gaining adoption: Antonia--start with smaller wins to reset expectations    
    
    
    @johnelder4 welcome aboard!    
    
    
    @JMP_software I just emailed her about it. U r absolutely right!    
    
    
    #PAWCon @johnelder4 lessons learned in data mining    
    
    
    #PAWCon @johnelder4: interplay between computer strengths and human analyst strength impt--they are more orthogonal than alike    
    
    
    #PAWCon @johnelder4: presenting intermediate #data #mining results to domain experts helps uncover hidden assumptions made by analysts    
    
    
    #PAWCon Jamie de Guerrero of Topsy. Use social web as the authority in recommendation. (search 3.0). Talk about big data!    
    
    
    #PAWcon my apologies to Jamie. Auto correct got the better of me with his last name: de Guerre    
    
    
    #PAWCon Randy Saaf of Alpha genius. Sentiment investing. Is the future of investing man or machine? Computers can solve but not ask right Qs    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: 1. Reporting 2. Building models. 3. Repeatable Processes for building models.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: 3. Either u have 1000s of modelers or a process to build the 1000s    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: 4.  Analytics is integrated across the organization (different kinds)    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: 60% of companies are still at Level 2    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: if models are viewed as code, org won't make it to Level 3.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman on What is Your Analytic Maturity Level: need a deployment strategy / environment to help Ops convert models    
    
    
    #PAWcon Bob Grossman: another way to say it- needs to be standard deployment software to plug models in    
    
    
    #PAWcon Day 2 kicking off with @brunoaziza in 2 minutes.    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza Is data a science or a service? References "Big Data" and Its Myths http://www.forbes.com/sites/ciocentral/2012/06/21/big-data-its-myths/ …    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: storing big data is a problem, but accessing the data is as/more challenging.    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: Milan lab predicts with 70% accuracy whether a (soccer) player is going to get hurt in 6 mo. (a chiropractor did it!)    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: for milan labs...not just about the data. Data was a service with a clear business objective    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: don't just get get if you think there is business value, get the data...period. Storage gets cheaper all the time.    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: storing data (me here): we have to organize the data or else it will look like my office!    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: costs dropping: food 10x; electricity 20x; transportation 100x, communications 1000x; data 500,000x    
    
    
    #PAWcon @brunoaziza: 52% of companies have no ADBMS (active database management system); we need to change to manage big data.    
    
    
    #PAWCon Roger Craig: jeopardy tournament of champions winner describes how he used text mining and #predictive #Analytics to prepare    
    
    
    #PAWcon Roger Craig:  built predictive modes (SVM) from bag of wordnet. Target: his actual responses from past games    
    
    
    #PAWcon Roger Craig. Models revealed what categories he would likely do poorly on that he had not yet seen    
    
    
    #PAWcon Roger Craig. Used #anki flash card software to practice: spaced repetition to reduce time-to-forget    
    
    
    #PAWcon Roger Craig: recommends augmenting human capital with #predictive #Analytics    
    
    
    #PAWcon Roger Craig. For education, moving to digital homework and tests=>can predict performance and develop individualized curricula    
    
    
    Quoted in "Putting predictive analytics to work" - Computerworld http://m.computerworld.com/s/article/9228230/Putting_predictive_analytics_to_work?taxonomyId=9 …    
    
    
    #PAWcon Thanks to @rogcraig for a great talk at PAW. If I had bothered to find your twitter username, I would have tweeted it!    
    
    
    #PAWcon postlude: runway lights out in Chicago...no flights coming or going now. guess I won't be leaving here anytime soon.    
    
    
    #PAWcon Hands-On Workshop: Thanks @StatSoft for all your support for and help with the workshop. Looking forward to Boston!    
    
    
    So how does the SWA app say that flight 2511 is "boarding" and "on-time" when I'm sitting inside at 10:15 at a closed airport?    
    
    
    Coming soon, at upcoming #JSM, "Predictive Analytics and Data Mining: The Software Makers" on Wednesday, Aug. 1, 2-4pm. http://www.marketwatch.com/story/software-makers-shed-light-on-big-data-issues-in-data-mining-and-predictive-analytics-2012-06-28 …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/icAZek  It gets peoples attention for the first hearing, after that, it doesn't matter. I can't remember the last time...    
    
    
    Very nice summary of the attitude that makes and employee/consultant successful from Inc. Mag: http://www.inc.com/jeff-haden/9-beliefs-of-remarkably-successful-people.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+inc%2Fheadlines+%28Inc.com+Headlines%29 …    
    
    
    World's Hardest Sudoku puzzle. I'm not sure if I want to know if I can solve it or not! http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/science-news/9359579/Worlds-hardest-sudoku-can-you-crack-it.html …    
    
    
    #predictive #analytics to the rescue! >90% of consumers unsubscribed from brand comms because message was irrelevant: http://www.sfgate.com/business/prweb/article/What-Does-1-800-Flowers-Capital-One-The-3672089.php …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/Ny692G  I agree with Bruce: try a different delimiter, or make sure the text fields are fully qualified with double-quotes....    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/cYVeWE  BA it seems to me is a relatively new incarnation. For example, INFORMS had their first conference with "Business...    
    
    
    what are college majors now? (hint: not STEM!) http://marginalrevolution.com/marginalrevolution/2011/11/college-has-been-oversold.html …. Why not? Maybe because it's too hard. http://www.nytimes.com/2011/11/06/education/edlife/why-science-majors-change-their-mind-its-just-so-darn-hard.html?pagewanted=all …    
    
    
    How do you know when the model is ready to deploy? 1) eval metric is good 2) eval metric is not too good 3) you have a 4 pm flight out    
    
    
    Models are never cookie-cutter. Even when I build the same model for the same customer, I've learned ++ on other gigs since the last time    
    
    
    Jul-12 Predictive Analytics Times: http://bit.ly/MB2ACT ; "What do data miners need to learn?" (me) & "Moneyball Marketing" @JohnBBates    
    
    
    predictive analytics can predict the college and career readiness of a student as early as fifth grade: http://www.marketwatch.com/story/dell-provides-schools-and-universities-with-predictive-analytics-based-decision-support-system-to-help-improve-student-outcomes-and-school-efficiency-2012-07-11 …    
    
    
    @tmpry_5150 Glad you like it. I laugh whenever I see the "stuck in LA traffic"    
    
    
    Indiana Economic Development Corp Names 8 'Companies to Watch' - @smarterhq one of them. Congrats! http://www.insideindianabusiness.com/newsitem.asp?id=54694 …    
    
    
    #dmradio without new automated ways to clean data for #predictive #analytics, new data size will outstrip our ability to analyze it    
    
    
    On the board and teaching in new UC/Irvine #predictive #analytics certificate prgm http://unex.uci.edu/certificates/it/predictive_analytics/courses.aspx … w/ @johnelder4 @jamet123 Eric Siegel    
    
    
    @johnelder4 Come on John...join the fun!    
    
    
    Rexer analytics data mining survey results are out: http://rexeranalytics.com/Data-Miner-Survey-Results-2011.html …; Interesting section on R (pros and cons): http://rexeranalytics.com/DMSurvey2011_R-Comments.html …    
    
    
    Rexer Analytics 2011 #DataMining Survey: (http://rexeranalytics.com/DMSurvey2011_R-Comments.html …) identify usual suspects: R is free, lots of algs but harder to spin up on it    
    
    
    Web analytics may be "behind", but they've had to deal with so many other issues: lots of data that is low info. content (log files, clicks)    
    
    
    (1/3) Never give up trying to understand what the client needs. I'm not referring to what the client says he/she needs.    
    
    
    (2/3) Most clients know what they want *and* what they need, but few know how to articulate that for #predictive #analytics    
    
    
    (3/3) My job is to not only deliver what I'm asked to, but to recommend a change in the project to meet the real unspoken need.    
    
    
    @revodavid I forgot my 4gLTE mifi. Sounds like it wouldn't have helped much!    
    
    
    Could predictive analytics have identified the Aurora shooter? http://blogs.computerworld.com/business-intelligenceanalytics/20749/could-data-mining-stop-mass-murderers …; IMHO: need more than just how much ammo he bought    
    
    
    @VZWSupport-didn't have my 4GLTE jetpack with me at the conference. Happy with it so far (2-3 weeks). One of best parts:digital info display    
    
    
    @VZWSupport location mentioned was San Diego convention center    
    
    
    @VZWSupport on the jetpack right now as a matter of fact from Redondo Beach    
    
    
    (1/4) classification is intuitive for most people: we want a to be able to identify fraudulent transactions, responders, etc.    
    
    
    (2/4) it seems that most people think of classification as a "look alike" association or "pattern matching": what do responders look like?    
    
    
    (3/4) but that's only 1 part of the problem. Classification *differentiates* 1s from 0s.    
    
    
    (4/4) Just fields are associated with 1s doesn't mean they are good for classification. 0s may also be strongly associated    
    
    
    (5/4) A difficult concept to convey to folks new to #predictive #analytics is that classification must differentiate, not just associate!    
    
    
    “@data_mining: Is it marketers vs. analytics? See study results: http://ow.ly/cQkg7  ” creative+ #Analytics (me!) describes @smarterhq    
    
    
    “@data_mining: Is it marketers vs. analytics? See study results: http://ow.ly/cQkg7  ” only quibble-storage is cheap; dont throw away #Data    
    
    
    Sometimes we collect data that doesn't drive today's decisions, but will drive tomorrow's once we have enough to build #predictive models    
    
    
        
    
    
    Springer Book "Journeys to Data Mining: Experiences from 15 Renowned Researchers" now out (my chapter is CH 1) http://www.amazon.com/Journeys-Data-Mining-Experiences-Researchers/dp/3642280463/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8&qid=1345094367&sr=8-3&keywords=journeys+to+data+mining ….    
    
    
    Springer Book  "Journeys to Data Mining ...": other chapters by @johnelder4 @kdnuggets, David Hand, Colleen McCue,…15 total    
    
    
    Springer Book "Journeys to Data Mining" -- Can read online at springer site http://www.springerlink.com/content/978-3-642-28047-4#section=1097954&page=1&locus=0 …    
    
    
    @metabrown312 @minethatdata Those aren't experts. LOL! I know many and they *are* experts in the analytics, just not in practical solutions!    
    
    
    Join me Thu, 2:30PM EDT for UC Irvine Extension Webinar: 7 Reasons You Need Predictive Analytics Today http://unex.uci.edu/services/events/#00865 …    
    
    
    Join me Thu, 2:30PM EDT for UCI Extension Webinar: 7 Reasons You Need Predictive Analytics Today http://unex.uci.edu/services/events/#00865 …    
    
    
    Almost ready for the 2:30PM EDT UCI Extension Webinar: 7 Reasons You Need Predictive Analytics... http://unex.uci.edu/services/events/#00865 …    
    
    
    Jumping on the 2:30PM EDT UCI Extension Webinar: 7 Reasons You Need Predictive Analytics now http://unex.uci.edu/services/events/#00865 … …    
    
    
    @B2Bspecialist where in Ontario? I can ask some friends in Ottawa with kids    
    
    
    to say #datamining is  "driven by the analytst" is just wrong. Data Mining algs are data-driven / inductive at the core (trees, NNets...)    
    
    
    A fairer way to critique the #datamining article: the author used the term data mining in a way data miners & industry themselves do not    
    
    
    The transition from #BI to #predictiveanalytics is on: @ComputerWorld best of BI for 2012 uses #PA http://www.computerworld.com/s/article/9230557/Best_of_BI_Booz_Allen_s_50_million_BI_investments_pays_rich_dividends …    
    
    
    News that romney campaign is using #datamining; seems they r slow 2 do what the obama campgn has been doing for months: http://www.kdnuggets.com/2011/07/obama-2012-data-analytics-team.html …    
    
    
    My  webinar "7 Reasons You Need Predictive Analytics" hosted by UC Irvine now available for playback (1hr 9min): https://uci.webex.com/ec0605ld/eventcenter/recording/recordAction.do?siteurl=uci&theAction=poprecord&ecFlag=true&recordID=61448317 …    
    
    
    Analytics in action! @smarterhq #web #analytics case study highlighted at @IR_Magazine in @Woodcraft case study: http://www.internetretailer.com/2012/08/28/showingand-acting-dollars-left-abandoned-carts?p=2 …    
    
    
    Analytics in action! @smarterhq web #analytics case study highlighted at @IR_Magazine in @Woodcraft case study: http://www.internetretailer.com/2012/08/28/showingand-acting-dollars-left-abandoned-carts?p=2 …    
    
    
    averages (and regression coefficients) are often good for reporting. They are awful for decisioning. they tell you nothing about tails.    
    
    
    #Analytics laugh of the day...and so true!  http://analystfirst.com/2012/07/30/1491/analyst-first-in-one-picture/406157_10150923302546401_2063510346_n/ …    
    
    
    Upcoming Workshop at Predictive Analytics World on how to build Ensembles in SPM on 10/3: thanks to @salfordsystems! http://www.marketwatch.com/story/advanced-predictive-modeling-workshop-offered-at-predictive-analytics-world-boston-2012-09-06 …    
    
    
    "Journeys to Data Mining: Experiences from 15 Renowned Researchers", Incl @deanabb @johnelder4 @kdnuggets David Hand http://www.amazon.com/Journeys-Data-Mining-Experiences-Researchers/dp/3642280463/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&ie=UTF8&qid=1347240589&sr=1-1&keywords=journeys+to+data+mining+in+books …    
    
    
    @johnelder4 hey! you tweeted!    
    
    
    New blog post at my blog: What do we call what we do? http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    New blog post at my blog: What do we call what we do? http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/  
(I still don't call myself a data scientist)    
    
    
    Will Dwinnell suggests (in the comments) eXtreme Analytics (XA). :)  http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2012/09/what-do-we-call-what-we-do.html …    
    
    
    LinkedIn Statistics & Analytics Consultants Group thread #datamining vs #statistics. I referd 2 great David Hand take: http://www.hstathome.com/xiazai/data%20mining%20statics.pdf ….    
    
    
    @SmarterHQ @shoporg sounds like it all went well!    
    
    
    @Hopley I don't think so...he didn't have a PhD in statistics!    
    
    
    #SWA inflight internet--unbelievably slow. Getting 14Kbps (<2KB/sec)...I think I had better speeds on my 33.6K modem... pic.twitter.com/FGFtJqUU    
    
    
    should have had 140Kbps    
    
    
    @mmmgaber didn't realize you were on twitter! Thanks for editing "Journeys to Data Mining: Experiences from 15 ..." http://www.amazon.com/Journeys-Data-Mining-Experiences-Researchers/dp/3642280463/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&ie=UTF8&qid=1347240589&sr=1-1&keywords=journeys+to+data+mining+in+books …    
    
    
    Predictive Analytics World / Boston regular price ends Friday http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/boston/register.php …. Register with code DAB12 to get 15% off. See you there!    
    
    
    Don't forget about "Advanced Methods Hands-On" workshop at #Pawcon / Boston, Thursday Oct 4th, sponsored by @Statsoft, using Statistica.    
    
    
    @StatSoft You send the trial discs (and USBs for those Macbook Air users!), I'll bring the data and drop it off at your booth Mon morning :)    
    
    
    JMP "Analytically Speaking" conversations w/ thought leaders on demand at http://www.jmp.com/images/email/temp/corporate/ETS31164.html?appid=31164&EMAIL=dean%40abbottanalytics.com …. Next 4 me 2 c: Bob Stine & Peter Bloomfield    
    
    
    New IRS Senior Operation Research Analyst GS-14 position, deadline of 10/04/12. This is a #predictive #analytics  job. https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/327572100 …    
    
    
    glad to be at another #PAWCON--first time in Boston. Eric Sigel opening up now    
    
    
    #PAWCON keynote by Scott Nicholson @scootrous -- Better Living Through Data Science. all about making better decisions    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: referenced good article on data science by @hmason at http://alexbraunstein.com/2011/08/09/hire-data-scientist-statistician/ …    
    
    
    #PAWCON @stootrous-data scientist: one who uses data to solve problems end-to-end from asking right questions to make insights actionable    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: definitions of data science can over-emphasize software part--you can do good analytics an not know Cassandra (LIKE ME!)    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: end to end data science...shows a 5-step process. Why not just use CRISP-DM? (http://www.linkedin.com/groups/CRISPDM-1950547/about …)    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: real-world...hadoop is great as a batch system, not good for iterative analytis (use the right tool for the right prob.)    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: data scientists he looks for are "data nerds"    
    
    
    #PAWCON @scootrous: will be huge talent migration to health care in next few years--that's where there is interesting data and lots of $$    
    
    
    @scootrous Ha! Good question! My guess, yes, but negatively correlated. It's the difference between "doers" and "watchers"    
    
    
    #PAWCON @nodexl showed near real-time map of twitter links. Very interesting! (open source excel addin at http://nodexl.codeplex.com/ )    
    
    
    #PAWCON @nodexl we have many weak ties through social media. What is the strength of weak ties? (refer'd Granovetter: http://sociology.stanford.edu/people/mgranovetter/documents/granstrengthweakties.pdf …)    
    
    
    #PAWCON @nodexl when do lots of connects not nec. mean influence. Ans: Bridges. Important network quality (Bonding being the other)    
    
    
    #PAWCON RT @kdnuggets Great presentation on Social Media analysis and NodeXL from @Marc_Smith - agreed. Thanks for referencing his name!    
    
    
    #pawcon @arobins defining analytics: @INFORMS definition -> about better decisions    
    
    
    @pawcon @arobins what we do: influence strategic, tactial and operational decisions from descriptive, predictive, and prescriptive analytics    
    
    
        
    
    
    #pawcon @arobins avoid 'black box' syndrome. critiques from decision makers helps to avoid gaining only 'science fair' status    
    
    
    #pawcon @kdnuggets where is #big #data in gartner hype cycle? social -> top of hype, #mapreduce -> disillusionment (http://www.forbes.com/sites/louiscolumbus/2012/08/04/hype-cycle-for-cloud-computing-shows-enterprises-finding-value-in-big-data-virtualization/ …)    
    
    
    @OperaSolutions to leverage Pervasive @DataRush in its technology stack http://www.dailyfinance.com/2012/10/02/opera-solutions-leverages-pervasive-software-platf/ …
Wow...very interesting!    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 moores law and progress: http://www.ebiztutors.com/images/paul/ml.jpg … Humans ability to build better machines a huge advantage for the species!    
    
    
    (1/2) #pawcon @johnelder4 easy for humans to "invent" explanations for data patterns (even random ones!)    
    
    
    (2/2) #pawcon @johnelder4 that is why analysts need to be the last line of defense for interpreting data rationally    
    
    
    @LouBajuk liked the photo from #TUCON2012--looking forward to the next time we can connect!    
    
    
    @metabrown312 figures that I'm doing my workshop on the day or your talk...missing hearing you *again*!    
    
    
    #PAWcon ready to start advanced methods hands on with #statistics. Looking forward to it!    
    
    
    From @Harvardbiz:  "The evidence is clear: Data-driven decisions tend to be better decisions." (http://hbr.org/2012/10/big-data-the-management-revolution/ar/1 …)    
    
    
    From @Harvardbiz: "The technical challenges of using #big #data are very real. But the managerial challenges are even greater". Yes!    
    
    
    reminder to media reporting on #big #data: big (or small) data doesn't predict anything. algorithms predict, people interpret & apply.    
    
    
    Great quote from @metabrown312: "We’re using way too much brute force in Big Data analysis today" - http://www.textanalyticsnews.com/west/content6.php?utm_source=LinkedIn&utm_medium=Social&utm_campaign=Article …    
    
    
    #big #data can overcome some problems because we can induce models from data, but it *never* is a substitute for thinking    
    
    
    Looking forward to @Data_Informed Live event in San Jose, Dec 10-11 I speak Dec 11th. @jamet123 Dec 10th. http://data-informedlive.cvent.com/events/data-informed-live-/event-summary-6b842d3e31ab4b77ba405f8be588f60d.aspx?utm_campaign=SocialFlow&utm_source=Twitter&utm_medium=Tweet …    
    
    
    Statistical analyst Nate Silver says humility is  [one] key to making accurate predictions (http://www.npr.org/books/titles/162589949/the-signal-and-the-noise-why-most-predictions-fail-but-some-dont …) -- agree!  HT @kdnuggets    
    
    
    Gearing up to teach another text mining course through UCSD extension: http://extension.ucsd.edu/studyarea/index.cfm?vAction=singleCourse&vStudyAreaID=14&vCourse=CSE-41151 …, Nov 2, 9, and 16, using @knime    
    
    
    Great time of year when #BlueAngels do their Miramar show. Can even catch the show from my house... pic.twitter.com/mz4dhqNh    
    
    
    @tdoyon on NYT graphic: it's interesting to me how the NYT graphic and your scatterplot highlight different jobs --both were insightful.    
    
    
    @tdoyon I'd love to unpack the numbers more -- one thing that I often like to see is lift--Dentist goes from 6% to 28% (huge!) but gets lost    
    
    
    @tdoyon Thanks for bringing this up--very interesting!    
    
    
    Here we go again with the conflation of #datamining and data collection http://www.information-management.com/news/data-mining-collection-back-in-federal-crosshairs-10023328-1.html?ET=informationmgmt:e5614:2130000a:&st=email&utm_source=editorial&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=IM_Daily_101512 …    
    
    
    What You Exhale — Carbon Dioxide — Impairs Decision-Making http://on.wsj.com/RcIV0M  via @WSJ -> get out of the board room to make key decisions!    
    
    
    @revodavid @readmatter I guess I'm officially a math nerd--I laughed soooo hard at the nonsense paper I created. It's The Onion for math!    
    
    
    StatSoft to Aid Struggling European Economies with Free Enterprise Analytics Software http://www.statsoft.com/support/blog/entryid/351/statsoft-to-aid-struggling-european-economies-with-free-enterprise-analytics-software/ … via @StatSoft    
    
    
    @brunoaziza I won't be at #strata this time. Rely want to get to one before too long!    
    
    
    Latest blog up up at Data Mining and Predictive Analytics: Data Preparation - Know Your Records at http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com     
    
    
    no surprise: @jamet123 post Big Data and Decision Mgmt http://bit.ly/mLca5c  is like "big data = lots of little data" http://www.sas.com/knowledge-exchange/business-analytics/innovation/big-data-defined/index.html … :)    
    
    
    @SalfordSystems upcoming webinar on Tree Ensembles, Friday, November 9, 10am-11am PST http://2.salford-systems.com/tree-ensembles-and-classification-and-regression-trees-webinar/ …    
    
    
    (1/3) new @PACESDSCEDU Predictive Analytics Center of Excellence (PACE) lecture series weekly Wed. 6pm.    
    
    
    (2/3) @PACESDSCEDU PACE is a San Diego Supercomputer Center (SDSC) initiative. I'll be speaking Nov 7th on Why Ensembles Win Competitions    
    
    
    (3/3) This tweet intentionally left blank    
    
    
    Great intro to #bigdata from @bobgrossman http://rgrossman.com/2012/06/06/an-introduction-to-big-data-for-general-reader/ … -- Bob is always an insightful read, but hasn't tweeted since 2009!    
    
    
    on political polling and a fair-minded critique of @fivethirtyeight: a model is only as good as the underlying data http://www.redstate.com/2012/10/31/on-polling-models-skewed-unskewed/ …    
    
    
    on political polling... insights come from interaction effects (i.e. subgroups): averages are helpful but can be deceptive #flawofaverages    
    
    
    Redskins predict Romney wins POTUS #overfit. if Redskins lose home game before election => challenger wins (17/18) http://www.usatoday.com/story/gameon/2012/11/04/nfl-redskins-rule-romney/1681023/ …    
    
    
    New blog post: Why Predictive Modelers Should be Suspicious of Statistical Tests (or why the Redskin Rule Fools Us) http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    @BrentLeary twitter breakdown would be fun to see!    
    
    
    @BrentLeary fascinating...good news for the country IMHO that there is such interest.    
    
    
    @BidwiserApp That's one thing I like about @SmartDataCo--I never explicitly mentioned 94%--they did the math!    
    
    
    @revodavid @fivethirtyeight how about 50 equal pop'd "states" with 26 D, 24 R (based loosely on 2012 POTUS results)! That'd b interesting!    
    
    
    @revodavid :) I fully agree with you! It would still look interesting though...    
    
    
    @dsdownunder I'll find out if the talk is being recorded (don't think so, but it doesn't hurt to ask!)    
    
    
    @PACESDSCEDU PACE Tech Talk @ San Diego Supercomputer Center tomorrow evening 6pm on Why Model Ensembles Win... http://pace.sdsc.edu/abbottanalytics     
    
    
    @smartdataco: easy to see every comment I've made to posts. @Linkedin: no way to see all my comments in their groups. Why not?    
    
    
    @Forbes Most valuable majors: #10 is applied math (glad I did something useful!), Love #11 (math)--pic is algebra! http://www.forbes.com/pictures/ffhk45ehm/no-11-mathematics/ …    
    
    
    @minethatdata I'm not a fan of hijacking brand loyalty, labeling it as engagement, then SM gets credit > completely agree!    
    
    
    @dsdownunder can you send me your email address?    
    
    
    @minethatdata @smarterhq - my comments on Kevin's loyalty vs. engagement tweet. Measuring engagement is key! http://www.smarterremarketer.com/how-do-you-define-engagement/ …    
    
    
    More good news for us: Math and Statistics at the top of the "best jobs" http://msnbc.msn.com-nbcnews9.net/jobs/     
    
    
    @revodavid even better!    
    
    
    @salfordsystems webinar on postprocessing of gradient boosting ensembles https://www.salford-systems.com/en/events/item/457-webinar-advances-in-gradient-boosting-the-power-of-post-processing … ; I'm looking forward to it!    
    
    
    (1/2) two reasons experience > certificates in #predictive #analytics: 1) it is both science *and* art; art is more experiential    
    
    
    (2/2) experience > certificates bec. there are so many ways #predictive #analytics can go wrong! > hard to describe it all in a course.    
    
    
    (3/2) purpose of certificate programs is to spin up analysts more quickly, giving them basic skills and a foundation to learn from.    
    
    
    Contributing to #oracle webinar "Marketing Strategies for Great Customer Experiences" Wed Nov 28, 11am-12 PST https://blogs.oracle.com/cx/entry/11_28_thought_leaders_webinar …    
    
    
    @OracleCX Gearing up for tomorrow's "Marketing Strategies for Great Customer Experiences" https://blogs.oracle.com/cx/entry/11_28_thought_leaders_webinar … with    
    
    
    Global Healthcare Analytics Market worth $10.8 Billion by 2017 - Sacramento Bee http://www.sacbee.com/2012/11/27/5012303/global-healthcare-analyticsmedical.html … - hope it will be well spent!    
    
    
    Digital statisticians and data analysts are the new studs on the block.
http://www.calgaryherald.com/technology/appeal+data+predictive+analytics/7584418/story.html#ixzz2DThpciGJ … - We still need a business objective 2 succeed!    
    
    
    (1/2) ... "using predictive analytics to gain valuable, yet potentially worrisome insights into people’s lives - http://www.walletblog.com/2012/11/predictive-analytics-consumer-scores/ …    
    
    
    @fasolamatt congratulations on studliness.    
    
    
    (2/2) Will #predictive #analytics suffer the same fate as #datamining? Will PA be tied to privacy abuses? (See http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2010/01/data-mining-and-privacyagain.html …)    
    
    
    New book (Feb2013) by Eric Siegel: Predictive Analytics: The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/WileyTitle/productCd-1118356853,descCd-buy.html …    
    
    
    @terrychristiani :) --> or he's already predicted he will *give* me a signed copy! :)    
    
    
    @OracleCX "Marketing Strategies for Great Customer Experiences" https://blogs.oracle.com/cx/entry/11_28_thought_leaders_webinar … starting in 25 minutes...    
    
    
    @jamet123 competing webinars! :)    
    
    
    I'm a Panelist on #DMRadio Rules, Rules, Rules: The Magic of Real-Time Decisioning http://lnkd.in/4hbsPi   today 3PM EST. Looking forward!    
    
    
    #dmradio Rules rules rules: Bruno Kurtic--real-time deployment of rules key to gain competitive advantages    
    
    
    @jimericson ha! the "competitive advantage" statement was a winner!    
    
    
    #dmradio Rules rules rules: Leo Sadovy @leosadovy -> #bigdata more attributes and transactions can now be run through business rule engines    
    
    
    #dmradio Rules rules rules: @leosadovy brings up text analytics as rules...yes! Big new use area for business rules    
    
    
    #dmradio Rules rules rules: Watson is a great example of rules in use--lots and lots and lots of rules key to its winning!    
    
    
    #dmradio Rules rules rules: @leosadovy ref. to book Normal Accidents http://www.amazon.com/Normal-Accidents-Living-High-Risk-Technologies/dp/0691004129 … and Kevin Slavin Ted Talk http://www.ted.com/talks/kevin_slavin_how_algorithms_shape_our_world.html …    
    
    
    #DMRadio Business Rules: Leo Sadovy @SASanalytics call center next-best-offer rules example: context determines messaging for cross/up sell    
    
    
    #DMRadio Business Rules: Patrick Surry @patricksurry they record interactions over a month, play back in a sandbox to test test test    
    
    
    Apple data mining scientist position wants either a PhD or MS with 5 years experience. Really? A dissertation is worth 5 yrs business exper?    
    
    
    @MatthiasBettag congrats!    
    
    
    just saw #IBM commercial during #MNF (Giants-Redskins) that actually said #predictive #analytics. I guess we really are mainstream!    
    
    
    Never build data without drawing pictures, especially with temporal information. Seeing what you know when decisions are made is critical!    
    
    
    @SmarterHQ wish I could be there!    
    
    
    Just saw it again today: averages are great for describing, awful for deciding #flawofaverages.    
    
    
    In two groups, selects and non-selects, the averages were about the same, but the selects had a much longer tail --good for predictions    
    
    
    5 Predictive Analytics use cases from real world--Insurance Networks News HT: @infomgmt. My #pawcon talk is #4. http://www.insurancenetworking.com/gallery/5-predictive-analytics-use-cases-31495-1.html …    
    
    
    #flawofaverages example: USDA guidelines for school lunches = 750-850 cals. for any students whether 5'2" 80 lbs or 6'2" 200.    
    
    
    @BrentLeary @bhalligan @mvolpe $20 on Pats....good bet!    
    
    
    @BrentLeary @bhalligan @mvolpe :)    
    
    
    December #PATimes out http://cts.vresp.com/c/?PredictionImpact/e1bdf793a6/9c0ecfa1a2/d1ed82cf33 … Includes my post Why Predictive Modelers Should be Suspicious of Statistical Tests    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PAWCON -- used the #PATimes hashtag for the latest Predictive Analytics Times http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/patimes/december12/ ….    
    
    
    great comment by Peter Bruce @statisticscom on inuition & statistical tests. http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2012/11/why-predictive-modelers-should-be.html … I added a link to a related NPR story    
    
    
    "No machine will pass a Turing Test", but it doesn't matter; let #AI do what it is good at: Robert French http://cacm.acm.org/magazines/2012/12/157871-moving-beyond-the-turing-test/fulltext …; EX: Watson    
    
    
    Sacbee - UC Irvine Extension Announces Winter Predictive Analytics Courses http://sacb.ee/TSbSSK  - 1) text analytics; 2) data preparation    
    
    
    Deep Learning: a big step forward or just another variant in #predictive #modeling? http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Deep_learning … & http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VdIURAu1-aU … - reading...    
    
    
    @minethatdata 9 of 10 models are garbage? Probably :)    
    
    
    (1/2) #DMRadio -- can analytics be put into part of the regular curriculum for verticals (business, health care, etc.)?    
    
    
    (2/3) #DMRadio - yes! This helps us understand *what* big data & analytics can do, not *how* to do it. Takes > a 2-week section to learn.    
    
    
    (3/3) #DMRadio -- that stated, Loretta's suggestion is essential for effective use of big data: few people will build, many must use.    
    
    
    @eric_kavanagh VLC works fine and is a good stopgap; and free. I think when I've listened before I've always booted up a PC to do it.    
    
    
    @RyanWithop Lost of youtube videos on R. http://Statistics.com  has intro courses on R. Use R to solve problems you know the answer to    
    
    
    (1/2) @RyanWithop If you solve problems you know the answer to in R, you validate you are using R correctly. Then move on to new probs :)    
    
    
    @RyanWithop What I did to learn R is start with the PVA data, watch some youtube on basic functions (import, data prep...), and build    
    
    
    @RyanWithop I don't remember which videos I liked best--if I have them written somewhere I'll send you those links    
    
    
    (1/2) RT @kdnuggets The 5 most influential data visualizations of all time: Choloera, March on Moscow, ore http://bit.ly/WejoGv  -@tableau    
    
    
    (2/2) quote, "The greatest value of a picture is when it forces us to notice what we never expected to see" John Tukey (HT @tableau)    
    
    
    (1/2) @insurance_news "Many CEOs hesitate to embrace predictive analytics out of concern over the time and expense" http://www.insurancenetworking.com/news/ceos-concerned-time-cost-implementing-predictive-analytics-31529-1.html …    
    
    
    (2/2) @insurance_news: Good list of suggestions. I'd add (1) start small; get a quick win, (2) get buy-in from IT/DBAs http://www.insurancenetworking.com/news/ceos-concerned-time-cost-implementing-predictive-analytics-31529-1.html …    
    
    
    (1/2) @WSJ Information analytics is emerging as one of the most powerful tools to help companies make better decisions http://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2012/12/16/nate-silver-fivethirtyeight-prove-predictive-analytics-getting-real/ …    
    
    
    (2/2) @WSJ key->"you keep evaluating and adjusting your models ... based on how well they perform in the real world" http://blogs.wsj.com/cio/2012/12/16/nate-silver-fivethirtyeight-prove-predictive-analytics-getting-real/ …    
    
    
    @jimsterne Ottawa is very nice in January--save some time to skate the canal and eat a beaver tail    
    
    
    @salfordsystems Thanks! Happy Holidays to all of you at Salford.    
    
    
    DL Flight 1722 landing in Detroit DTW slid off taxi-way. Snow is slippery!    
    
    
    Predictive Analytics: Dare To Try It At Home? http://po.st/pdPIGZ  via @B2Community - 1st time I've ever seen "pop culture" along with PA :)    
    
    
    Predictive Analytics: Dare To Try It At Home? http://po.st/pdPIGZ   via @B2Community. key: PA is intersection of data and human behavior    
    
    
    Top Posts from 2012 at Data Mining and Predictive Analytics blog: http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/ .    
    
    
    @minethatdata "best practices" are like averages. They get the gist, but are usually not actionable for specific customers #flawofaverages    
    
    
    @rogcraig Lead: doesn't it strike you that it may be a spurious correlation?    
    
    
    @minethatdata to assess ROI of campaigns, "Do the math" http://blog.minethatdata.com/2013/01/dear-catalog-ceos-full-price.html …    
    
    
    preface for Eric Siegel's new book "Predictive Analytics: The Power to Predict Who Will Click, Buy, Lie, or Die" @ http://www.pawcon.com/patimes/december12/#preface …    
    
    
    @smarterhq "5 Things Retailers Should Resolve Not to do in 2013" http://bit.ly/VGiZOz  - #6) predictive analytics + customer behavior = $$$!    
    
    
    HT @avinash married investment bankers realized they could save $27,000 if got divorced. So they did: http://goo.gl/mIhoI  #marriagepenalty    
    
    
    @avinash do you think the financial hit for high-income marrieds was an unintended consequence?    
    
    
    @avinash Tough indeed--I'm definitely not wired for that job!    
    
    
    @rogcraig it is interesting--for sure!    
    
    
    @revodavid I got a flu shot too--first time.    
    
    
    @hla3mi I'm not currently taking on any remote interns. Best of success to you in the search an in gaining data mining experience!    
    
    
    @pawcon PATimes now out http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/patimes/january13 … … - Eric Siegels new book; my article on getting models deployed    
    
    
    @pawcon Toronto Early Bird. 10 days left to register @ this rate! - use code on my blog for 15% discount http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com     
    
    
    data analysts/analytics listed as No. 4 tech job by recruiters (not even in top 10 last year)  http://data-informed.com/data-analytics-rising-as-top-priority-for-tech-hiring-pros-dice-reports/?utm_source=WIS&utm_medium=email&utm_campaign=Newsletter%2B-%2Bsubscribers …    
    
    
    @SiSense 2012 [Data] Professional Salary Survey (HT @kdnuggets http://www.kdnuggets.com/2013/01/big-data-impact-on-your-earnings-data-professional-salary-survey-results.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+kdnuggets-data-mining-analytics+%28KDnuggets%3A+Data+Mining+and+Analytics%29 …). 61% had higher $$ in 2012 vs 2011; men/women same $$    
    
    
    @SiSense 2012 [Data] Professional Salary Survey (HT @kdnuggets http://www.kdnuggets.com/2013/01/big-data-impact-on-your-earnings-data-professional-salary-survey-results.html?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Feed%3A+kdnuggets-data-mining-analytics+%28KDnuggets%3A+Data+Mining+and+Analytics%29 …) Skill to add most value: Project mgment, bus. skills.    
    
    
    @DavidPDinwiddie you play @StratOMatic? I haven't for years, but have play 1000s of games (baseball, football, basketball, hockey)    
    
    
    @DavidPDinwiddie no, never APBA. mostly baseball for me too. loved doing box scores and calculating batting averages. Had 100+ teams    
    
    
    @DavidPDinwiddie agree football #2 (better than college football). I had 27 yankees, 41 yankees, 46 red sox, 54 indians, etc. too    
    
    
        
    
    
    #FF thanks for your consistent support @kevinmacdonell @kdnuggets @salfordsystems @pawcon @terrychristiani @UCDDigital @brendantierney    
    
    
    "...all models are wrong, but some are useful." -  George E. P. Box. Corollary: All target variables are wrong, but some help decisions.    
    
    
    Why is it helpful to know the math behind algorithms? So we know how to and by how much we can break the rules on how they are built.    
    
    
    Understanding the math is helpful not so much to know how to comply, but why and when to comply: (see Will's post http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2009/04/taking-assumptions-with-grain-of-salt.html …)    
    
    
    Rexer Analytics 2013 Data Mining Survey http://www.rexeranalytics.com/Data-Miner-Survey-2013-Intro.html ….  use Access Code DA3T4. 15-20 min to complete. I'm doing it today.    
    
    
    predictive modelling is 3% better than guessing (and that's good!) via
@Computing_News http://www.computing.co.uk/ctg/news/2234753/predictive-analytics-helps-firms-to-get-about-three-per-cent-better-at-guessing-says-apt-chief …    
    
    
    Brain Scans Show No Difference Between Pie Chart and Bar Chart Perception http://soc.li/mlp84Ea  @SmartDataCo Personally, I prefer a table!    
    
    
    (1/3) The Q in the Tufts study was "est. the proportion percentage
of a smaller value in the graph to a larger value" http://www.eecs.tufts.edu/~epeck02/papers/CHI_fNIRS_2013.pdf …    
    
    
    (2/3) this is an interesting question, but if I was trying to communicate a ratio, I'd present a ratio! as a number or a bar chart    
    
    
    (3/3) the fact that bar charts are not great at showing ratios that aren't 1, 2, or 3 is not a surprise. 0.58 is hard to compute.    
    
    
    I gave @avinash +Kred in Marketing community influence on @Kred http://kred.com/avinash  http://bit.ly/pluskredvideo     
    
    
    (1/2) RT @kdnuggets Real scientists make their own data - but does it apply to data scientists? http://bit.ly/10XLX0j     
    
    
    (2/2) scientists don't "make" data, they create *experiments* that generate data. Data scientists should do the same.    
    
    
    Data Expert Siegel: Digital Analytics Helped Obama Get Re-Elected http://www.newsmax.com/Politics/siegel-obama-campaign-data/2013/01/24/id/472782 … - conservative site picks up on Eric's book chapter    
    
    
    Small Firms: LinkedIn Works (41%), Twitter Doesn't (3%) http://on.wsj.com/WyRfeX  via @WSJ. Youtube (16%), Facebook (14%). Yet I'm tweeting it    
    
    
    I need more RAM. And more disk space. Does this mean I need to move from my laptop to the cloud?    
    
    
    @ilblackdragon Maybe so. I'm on a macbook pro running MacOS and Windows (via Parallels). Having 16GB rather than 8GB RAM would be huge!    
    
    
    @John_A_Held I'm thinking more and more that this is the way to go, and I was slow to get there. Have to learn how to set it up.    
    
    
    @John_A_Held just signed up for Redshift. Thanks!    
    
    
    @kdnuggets @doug_laney The SGI angle is particularly interesting to me since it does *not* mention MineSet-maybe Ronni can chime in on this    
    
    
    @SmarterHQ Let's do it soon! Do you prefer before or after eTail west?    
    
    
    UC Irvine Extension Announces New Spring Predictive Analytics Courses http://newsle.com/article/0/59807135/ …; I'm teaching the Algorithms course Apr1-May19    
    
    
    New blog post: What to take home from your next #predictive #analytics conference: http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/2013/02/what-to-take-home-from-your-next.html ….    
    
    
    I gave @SmarterHQ +Kred in Marketing community influence on @Kred http://kred.com/SmarterHQ  http://bit.ly/pluskredvideo     
    
    
    I gave @decisionmgt +Kred in Bloggers community influence on @Kred http://kred.com/decisionmgt  http://bit.ly/pluskredvideo     
    
    
    I gave @avinash +Kred in Bloggers community influence on @Kred http://kred.com/avinash  http://bit.ly/pluskredvideo     
    
    
    I gave @MCanalytics +Kred in Marketing community influence on @Kred http://kred.com/MCanalytics  http://bit.ly/pluskredvideo     
    
    
    from @dmnews @Shoe_Carnival Cobbles Up a Retargeting Program using @smarterhq http://www.dmnews.com/shoe-carnival-cobbles-up-a-retargeting-program/article/280538/ … … -> analytics in action!    
    
    
    @dmnews on remarketing: http://www.dmnews.com/shoe-carnival-cobbles-up-a-retargeting-program/article/280538/# … effective #analytics needs rich data *and* expertise to know where & how to look. @smarterhq    
    
    
    @mmmgaber Thanks for the mention about the Journeys to Data Mining book! #datamining http://www.springer.com/computer/database+management+%26+information+retrieval/book/978-3-642-28046-7 …    
    
    
    #RT @knime #KNIME_UGM P.Winters and R:Silipo presenting a time series analysis using NN and AR made faster by #bigdata @DataRush    
    
    
    @pawcon Still time to register for the Advanced Methods Hands-on Workshop using #statistica Toronto, March 18 http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/toronto/2013/handson_predictive_analytics.php ….    
    
    
    Rexer Analytics 2013 Data Mining Survey http://www.rexeranalytics.com/Data-Miner-Survey-2013-Intro.html … extended until 4/22/13…. use Access Code DA3T4. 15-20 min to complete.    
    
    
    Stoked about our new models in @smarterhq SR2 Big Data platform, esp. #predictive #analytics days-to-purchase. http://www.smarterremarketer.com/news/smarter-remarketer-announces-new-sr2-big-data-platform-enabling-dynamic-onsite-messaging-in-real-time-for-retail-websites/ …    
    
    
    Apr 3 is #PredictiveAnalytics Day for Eric Siegel's book -> buy & get free on-demand training #buyliedie #bigdata http://bit.ly/Y788LI     
    
    
    Thanks for the recommendation! @RobertsPaige Let's hope sanity will ultimately win out in #bigdata. @data_nerd @dpatil @mthielbar    
    
    
    @mthielbar @RobertsPaige That's very kind of you!    
    
    
    20 minutes away from starting 2nd #Pawcon Toronto. I speak later this morning on 5 #Predictive #analytics pet peeves.    
    
    
    #pawcon Jane Griffin, Deloitte - #bigdata approaches enable data-driven decisions that are actionable in time to have an effect on behavior    
    
    
    #pawcon @JaneGriffin - #bigdata is not a substitute for good data.    
    
    
    #pawcon @rboire - "a fool with a tool is still a fool" - #bigdata technology works, but only in the hands of informed analysts    
    
    
    #pawcon @rboire - optimize (analyze) the data you already have (rather than dream about the data you don't yet have).    
    
    
    @TalentAnalytics @gretaroberts I'm looking forward to Greta's talk at #pawcon tomorrow morning.    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 - Becoming an ace with a robot as your wingman --> the interaction of humans and computers in #predictive #analytics    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 - we (analysts) are our organization's last best hope for rational interpretation of the data    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 moores law and progress: http://www.ebiztutors.com/images/paul/ml.jpg … Human ability to build better machines a huge advantage for the species!    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 projections of data-- like this set of butterflies forming airplane. Which view is interesting? pic.twitter.com/tkFIvEqMFd    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 - the figure of merit is key in any automatic (random) search. What is interesting? Hard for computers. Easy for Humans    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 computers can't create, contextualize, comprehend, care, or operate with common sense (which humans *can* do)    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 thinking fast and slow cognitive biases- frequency of exposure => like more. Should I tweet more?    
    
    
    1 #pawcon @johnelder4 good interpret ability of models is worse than useless. Huge bias if there is a coherent story u can  tell    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 even if data doesn't often support the story. Would your boss change mind if data went against his/her expectation?    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 if > 10000 hours experience, Blink (you've got good intuition now) otherwise ... Think    
    
    
    #pawcon Natalie kortum. How to measure brand. Net promoter score? Conjoined analysis? Surveys? Social? Social is informal conversations    
    
    
    NatalieKortum #pawcon brand measures are inconsistent. NPS favors to support. Others financial metrics. Dell combined them. An ensemble!    
    
    
        
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts @TalentAnalytics HR survey - can we quantify the typically qualitative measures in hiring/retaining analytics talent?    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts - ans: yes. Their questionnaire 20 minutes, 11 outputs. She says responses are stable over one's lifetime.    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts - analytics field is young and practitioners are young; but it's "the sexiest job of the 21st century" (#geeksaresexy)    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts have we put too many requirements into profiles to hire data scientists/analysts? their study results indicate "yes"    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts study results can be found here: http://www.talentanalytics.com/blog/2012-analytics-professionals-study-results-summary-and-qa/ …    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts of the 300+ data scientists surveyed, 16% PhD, 47% MA, 36% BA; dominated by math, stats, business.    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts functional clusters @talentanalytics found in analysis: data prep, programmer, managers, generalists. Which do u need?    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts analytics profess. fingerprint: highly curious, creative structured, detailed, structured. Low competitive, altruistic    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts the talent pool for data scientists is deeper than appears; req'ments are usually overspecified;    
    
    
    #FF thks for mentions @salfordsystems, ‏@TalentAnalytics, ‏@A_Crutch, @gretaroberts, ‏@philsimon, ‏@johnelder4, ‏@phernandomm, ‏@mthielbar    
    
    
        
    
    
    Last chance to participate in Rexer Analytics Data Miner / Data Mining survey http://www.rexeranalytics.com/Data-Miner-Survey-2013-Intro.html … Access Code: ER3X7    
    
    
    new blog post "Do Predictive Modelers Need to Know Math?" at http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    Begin teaching this week UCI Algorithms, Modeling Methods, Verification & Validation http://unex.uci.edu/courses/sectiondetail.aspx?year=2013&term=spring&sid=00054 …. Only one spot left...    
    
    
    @kevinmacdonell @Zite ugh!    
    
    
    @DamonRagusa @takabailando @SmartDataCo I get the "yes", but I'd reword it this way: to be innovative, "yes", to be good/profitable, "no"    
    
    
    @takabailando @DamonRagusa @SmartDataCo agreed. big hurdle to me: how quickly/effectively can we recover from being fooled by models    
    
    
    @DamonRagusa @takabailando @SmartDataCo will read when I get a chance--saw the provocative title--thanks for the HT    
    
    
    @metabrown312 Good point. Edison wasn't exactly a team player either though! :) But Edison certainly knew how to get "buy-in".    
    
    
        
    
    
    @WordsAbtNumbers Always a pleasure. I can't be too hard on the work-it's good as far as it goes. There are always xtra Qs we want answered!    
    
    
    #FF Thanks for the mentions this week @mjcavaretta @billfranksga @DamonRagusa @takabailando @SmartDataCo @JimOlick @TalentAnalytics    
    
    
    @NatalieKortum you're welcome. not that you needed a lot of help! :) See you in SF.    
    
    
    “@dirkvandenpoel: room is packed with 835 attendees for 1st keynote at @Informs #Analytics2013 conf @http://4sq.com/10HieVl” the head is me!    
    
    
    #analytics2013 keynote. Art and science of analytics. Both needed.    
    
    
    #analytics2013 keynote Jerry Allayne / Boeing. New vs 737 max? Decision based on multi variate cost function incl time to mkt > 737 max won    
    
    
    @deanabb: #analytics2013 keynote Jerry Allayne / Boeing. Airframe decisions based on analytics but there are ++ of emotions and soft reasons    
    
    
    #analytics2013 Edelman competition finalist talk on flood protection program in netherlands using analytics  reduced damage costs by 2/3    
    
    
        
    
    
    @agrobins @BellaRiverSA sounds great. will have to remember this one for next time!    
    
    
    @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/cs/2013/04/marketers_let_your_ego_go.html … 'data could usher in a world where advertising delivers on its original promise:more sales' HT @jimsterne    
    
    
    New post at Data Mining and #Predictive #Analytics blog http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/  - Math and Predictive Analytics - A Personal Account    
    
    
    My new blog post was prompted by a @salfordsystems marketer attending my @pawcon model #ensembles workshop (http://1.salford-systems.com/blog/bid/285726/Supercharging-Predictive-Modeling-A-Beginners-Perspective …)    
    
    
    #espndraftvote Teo    
    
    
    1. HT ‏@benhamner #Kaggle competition Whale Detection Competition: baseline 72%, winner 98% PCC; keys: feature extraction and ensembles    
    
    
    2. #Kaggle Whale detection competition: features were key. Needed to know something about signal processing (STFT, template matching, etc.)    
    
    
    3. #Kaggle whale detection competition: also needed to know how to build model #ensembles to win (Stochastic Gradient Boosting in this case)    
    
    
    4. as is typically the case with innovation, it is the cross-fertilization of disciplines that gives the dramatic improvement.    
    
    
    Speaking at the SoCal MRA Data Mining Event tonight in Anaheim.Not too late to sign up! http://socalmra.com/2013/04/02/save-the-date-data-mining-event/ …    
    
    
    Speaking at the @SoCalMRA Data Mining Event tonight in Anaheim.Not too late to sign up! http://socalmra.com/2013/04/02/save-the-date-data-mining-event/ …    
    
    
    Great time with @dennisyu yesterday after tag-teaming on text #analytics + social networking course; ideas, applications, insights    
    
    
    Happy to have made Dr. Jiang Zhou's list of the 10 most influential people in data analytics. http://www.deep-data-mining.com/2013/05/the-10-most-influential-people-in-data-analytics.html …    
    
    
    Just had a great time presenting at an Elder Research "Tech Talk" (thanks @johnelder4 for the invite!). I wonder how many companies do this?    
    
    
    Smarter Remarketer, LLC... - http://www.tie50.net/CompanyProfile/TiE50CompanyProfile_2013.asp?VwID=JNKSDPF8&amp;title=Smarter+Remarketer%2C+LLC …    
    
    
    Alteryx raises $12M to make predictive analytics user-friendly http://gigaom.com/2013/05/20/alteryx-raises-12m-to-make-predictive-analytics-user-friendly/ … via @gigaom -- user friendly R is a laudable goal!    
    
    
    stoked about @SmarterHQ being a TiE50 Startup winner http://www.tie50.net/TiE50Awards/TiE50_Winners_2013.asp … Judging criteria: Business Model, IP Value, & Leadership Team    
    
    
    @TDWI Executive Summit San Diego: Ten Best Practices in Operational Analytics #decisionmgt http://bit.ly/11ydLKo  - @decisionmgt & @deanabb    
    
    
    @Statsoft Newly released STATISTICA Ver. 12 has new workflow interface--can't wait to roll up my sleeves to use it. http://www.statsoft.com/products/statistica-12-new-features/ …    
    
    
    cast your vote! Predictive Analytics, Big Data, Data Mining, Data Science Software Used http://www.kdnuggets.com/2013/05/new-poll-analytics-big-data-data-mining-data-science-software-used.html … via @kdnuggets    
    
    
    0) We love to think that #bigdata will solve the black swan problem (in a tribute to C/Java programmers, I start counting at 0)    
    
    
    1) Reasons many black swan events cannot and will not be predicted by #predictive #analytics or #bigdata techniques    
    
    
    2) For first-time or extremely rare events (small N), there isn't history for the algorithms to create reliable models, or    
    
    
    3a) sometimes one could have predicted the event by looking at the right data.    
    
    
    3b)  If we don't or can't collect the necessary descriptor vars, or an uncomputed feature is essential, algorithms can't find the pattern    
    
    
    Remind myself again & again: averages are great for summaries but awful for decisions. Insights for decisions come from interactions    
    
    
    "Why the NSA Wants All That Verizon Metadata" from @PopMech http://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/military/news/why-the-nsa-wants-all-that-verizon-metadata-15562288?click=pm_news … -- my quotes from a #datamining perspective    
    
    
    RT Statistics: The language of science http://2.sas.com/6016kYGA  by @annemilley -Those who ignore statistics are condemned to reinvent it-Efron    
    
    
    Great visualization of U.S. regional speech (how people say 'crayfish'<<yes I'm from New England) http://www.businessinsider.com/22-maps-that-show-the-deepest-linguistic-conflicts-in-america-2013-6 …    
    
    
    Interesting ... #data #mining is used to describe the NSA / phone record analysis-- still taking the brunt of the privacy pushback, not PA    
    
    
    @metabrown312 I find the new LinkedIn layout worthless for me. The "influencers posts" tells me nothing--I'd rather see your posts!    
    
    
    @TraductorF1A3TV http://bit.ly/114APOE  #datamining -- Arturo, Thanks for alerting me--I had no idea! I think I'll let it play out awhile :)    
    
    
    on my way to #pawcon / Chicago; looking forward to day 2. Better late than never!    
    
    
    @cliqology cool    
    
    
    The Predictive Analytics Times Unveils Complete Online Portal to House and Expand its Popular Online Magazine Title http://www.prweb.com/releases/2013/6/prweb10818688.htm …    
    
    
    #pawcon Rayid Ghani keynote (Obama for America) - "I am a data scientist, I know nothing about politics" :)    
    
    
    #pawcon Rayid Ghani keynote: elections are an optimization process, need 270 Electoral votes (>> 270 make no difference). know your metric!    
    
    
    sorry Rahid #pawcon, forgot handle -- @rayidghani    
    
    
    @mabroukeh @pawcon coffee is a good thing...    
    
    
    @pawcon @rayidghani: key-->identifying persuadables (not the same as undecideds<<could be lazy). Had to *measure* reaction to policies.    
    
    
    What the NSA can't do with your data (probably) -- FCW http://fcw.com/Articles/2013/06/12/NSA-risk-assessment.aspx?sc_lang=en&Page=1 … via @FCWnow    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 beware of letting the future leak into your inputs for #predictive #modeling - if results are too good to be true...    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 lessons learned: data are going to be flawed, but don't let it stop you--could still improve your current decisions    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts -- analytics professional analysis showed analytics professionals are curious and creative.    
    
    
    #pawcon @gretaroberts @talentanalytics: key to hiring analytics professionals, diff reqs for programmers, data prep, managers & generalists    
    
    
    Webinar, what's new in #SAS Enterprise Miner 12.3 on June 20, led by @jaredldean http://go.sas.com/c8b07m  -- I hope to be there!    
    
    
    #smtnews #smtlive the NSA data doesn't convict, it can only create leads for investigators. It's like an automated tip line.    
    
    
    #SMTLive #SMTnews @metabrown312 Meta is exactly right. False positives are a huge problem which is why some*one* needs to investigate    
    
    
    @metabrown312 why would we know the successes of the NSA program any more than we know about #data #mining successes for companies? #SMTnews    
    
    
    I can almost never present company successes using #data #mining, at least not in any interesting way--they all keep a lid on it! #SMTnews    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day I have no doubt NSA can process phone meta data. If they are getting email/chat/text, harder 2 do in real time #SMTNews    
    
    
    @metabrown312 #SMTNews :)    
    
    
    @metabrown312 #SMTNews I've seen good successes in public sector from data like phone metadata--for investigative purposes--finding bad guys    
    
    
    @metabrown312 of course the failures aren't reported! LOL #SMTNews Point: we know so little about actual #data #mining success or failure    
    
    
    @PrivacyCamp thanks for the encryption link.    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews consumers do (or should) make the assumption that if they opt-in, they will be data mined.    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews but most consumers are apparently fine with it. It's only spam if you didn't want the solicitation, right? :)    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews yes, what should get people worried is exactly that--no opt out. Unless you move to Montana and live cash-only :)    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews this is a good policy issue weigh--what is the privacy/security tradeoff? Hard question. I don't have an answer.    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews (1/2) I think there will be a decrease as consumers feel more creeped out by data mining of email messages + more.    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews (2/2) There are already ads on conservative talk radio to dump gmail for other email services because of this.    
    
    
    @socialmedia2day #SMTNews +there's already significant drop in google searches anyway--other ways to get info (Siri, apps on smart phones..)    
    
    
    @mims the math is right for the Bayes Rule, the data they assume is not--there's much more to it than priors for good guy vs. bad guy.    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AFm6hs  The book you read depends a lot on your background and what you will be doing in the field. Any Berry and Linoff...    
    
    
    Do the Numbers Behind Prism Add Up? - The Numbers Guy - @WSJ http://on.wsj.com/11ff1jd  --thanks to @CarlBialik for bringing some sanity to this    
    
    
    PRISM Isn’t Data Mining and Other Falsehoods in the N.S.A. “Scandal” http://www.vanityfair.com/online/eichenwald/2013/06/prism-isnt-data-mining-NSA-scandalvia … @VanityFair - sanity! thanks to  @kurteichenwald    
    
    
    @cuneytgurcan @kdnuggets what prime causes are you referring to? Article mentions nothing of causes of reduced piracy. asking, not arguing.    
    
    
    @cuneytgurcan @kdnuggets glad many are optimistic about somalia (I've prayed for it for decades!). unpersuaded that data mining didn't help    
    
    
        
    
    
    will be speaking at ISACA San Diego Chapter Meeting Thursday, June 20 from noon-2PM on fraud analytics http://sdisaca0613-eorg.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    3 - RT @kdnuggets thats why 1) start small-get quick wins 2) have clear business objectives 3) get help-consultants >> knowledge transfer    
    
    
    1 - RT @kdnuggets http://www.informationweek.com/big-data/news/big-data-analytics/big-data-skills-scarce-among-marketing-pros/240156764 … "Big data projects are taking far too long, costing too much and not delivering on anticipated ROI"    
    
    
    2 - RT @kdnuggets  Why? "because it's...difficult to pinpoint and surgically extract critical insights without hiring expensive consultants"    
    
    
    New blog post: Big Data is Not Enough http://abbottanalytics.blogspot.com/  (first published at Predictive Analytics Times)    
    
    
    2 - non-statistician analysts are the new norm but (again) ... "Those who ignore Statistics are condemned to reinvent it." Brad Efron    
    
    
    1- I often read from critics of #data #mining that you can lie with #statistics. True. But you can also lie without statistics.    
    
    
    2- First let the data speak, understand why it "says" what it says, *then* form conclusions.    
    
    
    @legant66 - exactly :) I love Ottawa by the way. Hope it's nice there now.    
    
    
    @data_nerd I think I'm usually desperate!    
    
    
    Fascinating exclusive interview of Dan Steinberg of @salfordsystems by @kdnuggets http://www.kdnuggets.com/2013/06/exclusive-interview-dan-steinberg-salford-systems-data-mining-solutions-provider.html … incl. beginnings of salford sys.    
    
    
    advice from Dan Steinberg from @kdnuggets interview: "a budding ... data scientist needs considerable real world experience to learn"    
    
    
    @MGoldbergatDI :)    
    
    
    Ten Best Practices in Operational #Analytics @ TDWI #BI Executive Summit, Aug 20 / San Diego by @jamet123 & me http://events.tdwi.org/Events/San-Diego-BI-Executive-Summit-2013/Sessions/Tuesday/Ten-Best-Practices-in-Operational-Analytics.aspx …    
    
    
    @KMcCormickBlog @kevinmacdonell "Some statisticians are poor data miners" - agree! (and vice versa!) Stats literacy != stats course/textbook    
    
    
    Great time speaking at the #ISACA San Diego Chapter Meeting today on #fraud #analytics (http://www.isaca-sd.org/ ). Thanks for the invite!    
    
    
    @ISACANews I wish I did--I was speaking and didn't think of taking a photo before the talk. I don't recall anyone else taking one. Sorry!    
    
    
    Did I goof when I wrote "Big Data is not Enough"? Should I have written instead "Big Data are not enough"?    
    
    
    traffic to my blog: @kdnuggets referrals produce longest visit duration (by far) and lowest bounce rate. Worst? Bing, twitter and linkedin    
    
    
    @Kyle_Billings not ignoring your question; not a simple answer. Education and experience both important to learn the science *and* art    
    
    
    @Kyle_Billings  send me an email (dean@abbottanalytics.com) and I'll give you a more complete reply. I'll condense it for twitter too    
    
    
    #rpiran RPI Alumni networking webinar on Big Data--looking forward to it!    
    
    
    #rpiran Great to hear about several #RPI alums in San Diego    
    
    
    #rpiran Steve Mornelli -> formed a "data skeptics" group in New York. I love it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Having great success building logistic regression models by first id'ing interactions w/ association rules or decision trees. a win-win-win!    
    
    
    It's not that data is big that matters, it's that it is pervasive. Broader data means better decisions; more of the same data doesn't    
    
    
    teaching text mining overview at the "Data Intensive Summer School" today http://www.vscse.org/summerschool/2013/bigdata.html … incl. hands-on component using @knime    
    
    
    How do Analytics Competitors Recruit, Hire & Retain their #Analytics Dream Teams? Find out! Webinar w/ @GretaRoberts: http://bit.ly/11Jz37I     
    
    
        
    
    
    @LannyMorrow Thank you!    
    
    
    @JoelLesher @SmarterHQ LOL. Enjoyed the interactions: cross-fertilization of ideas => new innovation. Can't wait to see it all in action!    
    
    
    Saving Detroit From Itself http://on.wsj.com/17Jeh6F  @WSJ - shock stat:  About 70% of the city's financial journal entries are booked manually.    
    
    
    I think we've all experienced some of these!
http://bit.ly/18zoG6b     
    
    
    I often see Veracity included as a part of #BigData. The other 3 Vs define big data. Veracity is *always* important, big or small.    
    
    
    Fav Tukey quote from @kdnuggets ref.: "The best thing about being a statistician is that you get to play in everyone's backyard."    
    
    
        
    
    
    @burkepowers @data_nerd and "2) ???" can be the most important part! of becoming a good data scientist!    
    
    
    @burkepowers @data_nerd for me, the key ??? experiences were experiencing how #predictive #models fail, where theory doesn't cut it.    
    
    
    I'm in blackout mode with nose to the grindstone building risk models this week--unsupervised learning at that. Wish me luck!    
    
    
    “A leading ‘rock star’ consultant is... @deanabb." reveals his favorite marketing resource here - http://bit.ly/196cM3L-Thanks  @massrelevance!    
    
    
    Now that it's on the Wiley web site, I can announce my new book: Applied Predictive Analytics http://www.wiley.com/WileyCDA/WileyTitle/productCd-1118727967.html …    
    
    
    @aivoryuk I'm going to leave it at what the web site says for now. But it will be similar to the kind of material I teach regularly.    
    
    
    From Data Modeler to Data Scientist http://www.information-management.com/news/from-data-modeler-to-data-scientist-10024773-1.html … - interesting opinion on the differences. What do you think?    
    
    
    @minethatdata Zappos-interesting but key line is "None of these products is making Zappos any money yet." Can it work? Yes. Will it?   ???    
    
    
    Sinister Minds: Are Left-Handed People Smarter? http://www.newyorker.com/online/blogs/elements/2013/08/psychology-are-left-handed-people-smarter.html?mbid=social_retweet … via @NewYorker -- we're finally recognized! :)    
    
    
    HR Departments Invaded By Data Scientists http://shar.es/zl2jt  via @CIOonline -> don't think "invaded" is right word. Informed? Improved?    
    
    
    Data Mining Boot Camps http://lnkd.in/vq-TBg     
    
    
    I'm a Grade-A Damascus finder! 77 miles away, better than 85% of people. Can you get closer? http://toys.usvsth3m.com/damascus/     
    
    
    Modeling Analytics Dream Teams by @gretaroberts w/ @johnelder4 and @deanabb: how to develop & manage #datascientists http://www.talentanalytics.com/events/modeling-analytics-dream-teams-featuring-elder-research-inc/ …    
    
    
    was asked "how do I learn #big #data (management)?". I told him to read @billfranksga Taming The Big Data Tidal Wave http://www.amazon.com/Taming-Data-Tidal-Wave-Opportunities/dp/1118208781 …    
    
    
    Modeling Analytics Dream Teams, Wed Sep11 12pm EDT w/ @johnelder4, Dean Abbott, Sarah Will; moderated by @TalentAnalytics CEO @gretaroberts    
    
    
    What’s the NSA picking out of your phone calls? by @digitaltrends, quoting @predictanalytic @deanabb & @johnelder4 http://www.digitaltrends.com/mobile/whats-the-nsa-picking-out-of-your-phone-calls-just-unvolunteered-truths/#ixzz2drgqn0cq …    
    
    
    Upcoming speaking: @talentanlaytics webinar 9/11, @DMRadioOnline 9/19 & @pawcon / Boston. Looking forward to them!
http://abbottanalytics.com/data-mining-courses-and-seminars.php …    
    
    
    @Pawcon Boston and Berlin approaching. get 15% discount off registration for 2 Day and Combo passes with code DAB13 http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com     
    
    
    Modeling Analytics Dream Teams, Wed Sep11 12pm EDT w/ @johnelder4, Dean Abbott, Sarah Will; moderated by @TalentAnalytics CEO @gretaroberts    
    
    
    last call for tomorrow's Modeling Analytics Dream Teams hosted by @talentanalytics with @johnelder4, Sarah Will & me http://www.talentanalytics.com/events/modeling-analytics-dream-teams-featuring-elder-research-inc/ …    
    
    
    new how-to book "IBM SPSS Modeler Cookbook" by #Packt, http://www.packtpub.com/ibm-spss-modeler-cookbook/book … with @KMcCormickBlog @deanabb, @metabrown312    
    
    
        
    
    
    Build killer models @ #pawcon workshop Supercharging Prediction: Hands on Model Ensembles using @salfordsystems #SPM http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/boston/2013/ensembles_handson.php …    
    
    
    @tdoyon "Difference between FREQ and WEIGHTS". Thanks for the link--very clear explanation. Money idea: same coeffs, different stats :)    
    
    
    DMRadio Sep 19 3pm ET:  Best Practices for #Datamining w/ @deanabb @KDnuggets @KirkDBorne Jamie MacLennan (Predixion) http://www.information-management.com/dmradio/back-to-basics-best-practices-for-data-mining-10024869-1.html …    
    
    
    #DMradio leading off with @KirkDBorne -- Data mining *is* rocket science. :)    
    
    
    #DMradio @kdnuggets  beware of overfitting data--if you torture the data, it will confess. Have to apply statistical tests to avoid overfit    
    
    
        
    
    
    (2/2) @kiwidankun @kdnuggets the models of this type often ID individuals who are connected significantly to others. http://www.popularmechanics.com/technology/military/news/why-the-nsa-wants-all-that-verizon-metadata-15562288 …    
    
    
    Simpson's Paradox (HT @avinash http://vrl.ht/237B  ) -- good example of how single-variable/stepwise variable selection can fail    
    
    
    @revodavid @avinash Thanks for the reminder. And thanks for noting that this isn't really a paradox at all, just an apparent one!    
    
    
    Thanks for the mention! Also, Robert Mitchell did a fantastic job synthesizing the anecdotes into the article. http://lnkd.in/bj87Y4q     
    
    
    Counting down to Nov release of IBM SPSS Modeler Cookbook http://www.packtpub.com/ibm-spss-modeler-cookbook/book …. Thanks again @KMcCormickBlog @metabrown312 & @tomkhabaza    
    
    
    New issue of PA Times out http://www.predictiveanalyticsworld.com/patimes/the-role-of-analysts-after-model-deployment/ … incl. why analysts need to be involved *after* deployment @pawcon    
    
    
    MT @knime "Network Analysis meets Text Mining for Social Media Analysis  #KNIME Hands-On” 10/3 Boston http://www.meetup.com/Boston-Predictive-Analytics/events/139099822/ … see you there!    
    
    
    #pawcon Eric Siegel: response models predict the wrong thing. Really are propensity models but don't tell us who needs to be contacted    
    
    
    #pawcon need uplift modeling or persuasion modeling to predict affect of treatment on customer decisions    
    
    
    @kdnuggets glad we agree on what's important!!    
    
    
    #pawcon Eric Siegel how can we infer influence, a casual problem. A/B testing or treatment/control. Model over both sets.    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry #mapreduce is exactly what we did in the 80s (SIMD computers).    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry #bigdata isn't as big after selecting relevant pop'tions. Ex: @tripadvisor finding facebook friends who wrote reviews    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry: after awhile, more data doesn't change the stats or models. More data => more latency; sometimes less is better    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry: how much data is enough? Double size of data and examine your error metric. (1/2)    
    
    
    #pawcon doubling sample size is like the idea of Progressive Sampling David Jensen wrote about http://citeseerx.ist.psu.edu/viewdoc/summary?doi=10.1.1.44.6459 …    
    
    
    #pawcon Progressive Sampling--I should have referenced Foster Provost, David Jensen and Tim Oates    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry: better data beats bigger data every time!    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry: unbiased samples for Trip Advisor...listed hotels in some countries are only top end so bias toward high prices.    
    
    
    #pawcon Michael Berry: beware of making inferences from structurally biased data    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 plenary talk (too engrossed to remember to tweet).    
    
    
    #pawcon @johnelder4 subject matter experts are key to building good predictive models - pay a lot for hour(s) of their expertise.    
    
    
    MT @ilblackdragon # balls in bottle? #Ensemble 432 best person 420 actual 469; Ensemble wins! #pawcon #salfordsystems pic.twitter.com/snecw1gEKP    
    
    
        
    
    
    @KMcCormickBlog - good summary of our new book @IBMSPSS Modeler Cookbook (w/ @metabrown312 S. Mulcher & @tomkhabaza) http://keithmccormick.com/?p=156     
    
    
        
    
    
    @PACESDSCEDU #datamining bootcamp 2 - finished my #textmining talk, now scientific visualization by Amit Chourasia http://users.sdsc.edu/~amit/web/home     
    
    
    #RedSox robbed. #Letthemplay instead calling phantom tripping. Which ump actually made the call?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @doughelmreich agreed on Nava. Middlebrooks never touched Craig-feet irrelevant. So was the play done as soon as Craig tried to go home?    
    
    
    Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (CMS) requesting $803.5M, includes $$ for #fraudwasteandabuse #datamining. Send some my way!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @PredictDE #pawconDE Berlin -- morning plenary under way with Peter Gentsch    
    
    
    #emetrics @NatalieKortum owning the decision: big data started with web analytical.    
    
    
    @NatalieKortum #emetrics first link between data and business decisions is reporting.    
    
    
    @NatalieKortum #emetrics next steps in linking data to business decisions are KPIs and #business #intelligence #BI    
    
    
    @NatalieKortum #emetrics final links between data and decisions are #predictive #analytics and machine learning    
    
    
    .@NatalieKortum #emetrics politics of #bigdata -- for success, have to demonstate ROI on business problems *stakeholders* need solved    
    
    
    .@NatalieKortum #emetrics communicating analytics: the two minute rule. Make sure you can communicate ideas succinctly & with analogies    
    
    
    @apriljoycarter @TomWizki Sure enough, I'm here. Fun hearing from you! Congrats on the new house!    
    
    
    @KirkDBorne @CarpeDatumRx always fascinating what folks include and exclude from lists like this. I'm especially thinking Techniques & Tools    
    
    
    Got my print copy of IBM SPSS Modeler Cookbook today (thanks Jesus Salcedo!) http://www.packtpub.com/ibm-spss-modeler-cookbook/book … Nice seeing all the recipes!    
    
    
    @chriscrossross @KirkDBorne @CarpeDatumRx I was thinking Decision Trees. Random Forests. IBM Modeler. But I'm a #predictive kind of guy!    
    
    
    I love direct answers: "how many cups of coffee to drink, incl. all pro- & anti-coffee studies. The answer is: 3." http://althouse.blogspot.com/2013/11/exactly-how-many-cups-of-coffee-to.html …    
    
    
    @DataScienceCtrl with fascinating analysis of what constitutes a data scientist http://www.datasciencecentral.com/profiles/blogs/types-of-data-scientists?goback=.gde_5074372_member_5809380282171691011 …. Honored to be in top 10.    
    
    
    j.@DataScienceCtrl data science taxonomy http://www.datasciencecentral.com/profiles/blogs/types-of-data-scientists?goback=.gde_5074372_member_5809380282171691011 …, apparently I'm the most average #datascience professional. :)    
    
    
    .@minethatdata agree with the definition of analytics, though would not necessarily include phrase "convince somebody to". But yes, broad...    
    
    
    .@minethatdata reason I would omit "convince" (though it is often the case), my usual experience this: convince is done, just have to "do"    
    
    
    @minethatdata great question! Since I'm a consultant, often come in later (my data is biased). Usually C-suite or director decides; (1/2)    
    
    
    @minethatdata (2/3) very much mixed bag when analysts have to try to convince--these projects often die on the vine.    
    
    
    @minethatdata how did the C- / Director get convinced? When I can find out, usually peer-related from outside the organization (not inside)    
    
    
    @minethatdata "buy me some of that big data!" :)    
    
    
    @minethatdata you are right, but I think the first level should be with the project manager level, who can translate C-speak<->geek-speak    
    
    
    @minethatdata LOL  analysts are livid, and I see that too, usually smart people who don't get the business hurdles. (Betamax is better!!)    
    
    
    @sowmyanj send me an email. Dean@abbottanalytics.com    
    
    
    .@DataScienceCtrl with fascinating analysis of what constitutes a data scientist. Honored to be in top 10. http://ow.ly/r7ilh     
    
    
    Amazon just sent me an email indicating I might be interested in this book Applied Predictive Analytics by Dean Abbott. uh... ya! :)    
    
    
    "Far better an approximate answer to the right question...than the exact answer to the wrong question" John Tukey http://en.wikiquote.org/wiki/John_Tukey     
    
    
    I think about the idea in the Tukey quote often during #predictive modeling projects. I'm hired to increase ROI, not conduct basic R&D.    
    
    
    Always get a laugh from Mathgen random research papers (http://thatsmathematics.com/mathgen/ ). Should I submit this one? :)
http://thatsmathematics.com/mathgen/paper.php?nameType%5B1%5D=custom&customName%5B1%5D=Dean+Abbott&nameType%5B2%5D=generic&nameType%5B3%5D=generic&nameType%5B4%5D=custom&customName%5B4%5D=&seed=1543318700&format=pdf …    
    
    
    