@bassoforhire http://www.amato.org     
    
    
    @SteveUmstead @m_pallante "ho, ho, ho."    
    
    
    In other news, so bummed that @guarneschelli AND @chefanneburrell are gone from TNIC. I really need both of these chefs to feed me sometime.    
    
    
    @cmooresoprano Tony #Amato, and of course, Sally, too.  Both such sweet, wonderful souls.    
    
    
    @wilw My phone once autocorrected "Presbyterians" to "Lesbians." Still trying to figure that one out.    
    
    
    GET YOUR SCOTS ON!!  Check this video out -- The Rovin Dies Hard.wmv http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9qZZ01RFf_Q&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Looking for reading material?  Come see our Book Review Blog.  I contribute the 2nd Friday of every month. http://lnkd.in/HnTdUx     
    
    
    @JoeySalvia So say we all.    
    
    
    @dogjaunt My all time favorite salon name is one in Putnam Valley, NY, called, "Curl Up & Dye."    
    
    
    @michaelianblack About 10 minutes before your mind can form the question.    
    
    
    Got myself an early Christmas gift: A Princess of Mars by E R Burroughs. So excited. Haven't read it in @ 30 years. BMG (Big Manly Grunt)    
    
    
    @DonLagreca That's because those blue jerseys really were a jinx.  And hideous to boot.    
    
    
    @kellyoxford I just wish Kanye would shut up and use THAT passport.    
    
    
    Dates for the 2012 season of Air Pirates Radio Theater announced to cast today. Get ready! Gonna be a great season. Show details to follow.    
    
    
    Cowboys vs Giants: I think only their fans care who wins this wknd, because neither teams appears to want it.    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks Almost finished reading A Princess of Mars!  Thanks to Edgar Rice Burrougns, who got me hooked on reading.    
    
    
    The Air Pirates Radio Theater's 2012 season is set. We're bringing back some old faves and brand new shows, too! http://ning.it/mNX2NY     
    
    
    Checking out "Buy Local - Support the Arts" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/vbiDP6     
    
    
    @RealGregRay You're gonna need a bigger boat.    
    
    
    @RealGregRay I'll never put on another life jacket.    
    
    
    @shitgirlssay ...and then what?    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @johncleese Oh no!  I had not heard that.  This is tragic!  Did anyone clear this with Dame Judi Dench?    
    
    
    What are YOU reading on your next vacation?  @borderlessbooks has some suggestions.  http://www.booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake I think she's actually Bernard Lee re-incarnated.  So it's actually the same M for all the Bond films.    
    
    
    @maureenjohnson Morning Piggyback sounds perfect.    
    
    
    @theswizzle 2 completely different things, but NOT mutually exclusive.    
    
    
    Happy New Year!  Looking for something new to read in 2012?  Look at http://ning.it/uMthRY  for suggestions.    
    
    
    Booksellers without Borders lists their favorites of 2011 and most anticipated of 2012. http://lnkd.in/T5S6ww     
    
    
    More shameless self-promotion of my blog.  New posts coming soon!  Basso for Hire http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/?spref=tw     
    
    
    @WitchinWebs Thanks so much for the RT! :)    
    
    
    @kellyoxford I'd take that gig.    
    
    
    @MiniMenzel @kchenoweth It was SUCH a good show.  Shame the writers' strike came when it did.  Didn't help its chances at all.    
    
    
    BWB strikes again.  Shake your muggle-maker and see what Albert has to say. http://www.booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/2012/01/harry-potter-and-history.html …    
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders: New Girl by Paige Harbison http://booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/2012/01/new-girl-by-paige-harbison.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @AchingHope Ner!    
    
    
    @altonbrown Belated H.N.Y. to you, too, sir.    
    
    
    Such a shame. http://lnkd.in/uUAZBs     
    
    
    Checking out "Recordonline's "Best of 2011" Winners announced!" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/ws5maN     
    
    
    @ReneeHewitt They must have been driving when they tried to spell "loss." ;)    
    
    
    @JoeySalvia Sweeeeet!    
    
    
    Just added a new blog post on http://www.bassoforhire.blogspot.com  http://ning.it/zU5H9s     
    
    
    @borderlessbooks Thanks for the chirp!    
    
    
    @cherryduke Rock on!    
    
    
    @jamiegaul Just dabbling in it right now, but finding it kind of hard to work with.  Seems like limited options available.    
    
    
    @jamiegaul A month or so. To me it seems more geared toward film, and I'm doing pretty much all opera and stage, so that may be why.    
    
    
    @MiniChenoweth absolutely!    
    
    
    Just added a new blog post on http://hvBiz.com  http://ning.it/xkOtFl     
    
    
    Checking out "Attention Local Business Owners!" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/wU9FZw     
    
    
    I think my nose hairs froze this morning.    
    
    
    WOW! How frustrating can one week be?  May paint my face blue and start going "Braveheart" on a few people.    
    
    
    @JoeySalvia Bruce lost me at Jerry Maguire, if not earlier.    
    
    
    @Celeb_Marketing autotune is one of the worst calamities ever inflicted upon a fallen world.    
    
    
    Still, despite the overall frustrations of this week, there are a couple of opportunities peeking out at me.    
    
    
    Looking for IT Support Pros in the Orlando area.  Please email resumes directly to aandrews@designstrategy.com, or mes…http://lnkd.in/dPp6PK     
    
    
    @cherryduke That's a truly beautiful poem. Although, to be specific, "Amazing Grace" is not technically a Negro Spiritual.  Love it, though.    
    
    
    @PetraTolia :) Always.    
    
    
    @NathanFillion Polo    
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders: Harper Lee:  Fraud? http://booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/2012/01/harper-lee-fraud.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Reading "Raylan" by Elmore Leonard    
    
    
    One of my all time favorites!  Adopting a Rescue Panther - Easier Way to Save - New GEICO Commercial: http://youtu.be/8O1SX4x7uUE  via @youtube    
    
    
    Now hiring: PC Move/Deployment Technicians Needed (Monroe, LA) http://www.ziprecruiter.com/tjs/aea12b41     
    
    
    My latest blog post from Booksellers Without Borders...The China Gambit, by Allan Topol http://www.booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com     
    
    
    Basso for Hire: The China Gambit, by Allan Topol http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/02/china-gambit-by-allan-topol.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks Thanks for the tweet! I already had 1 reader say she was going to give it to her husband for Val. Day!    
    
    
    @billhommel does the president realize RG3 is a Christian?  Ah, let's let it be a surprise.    
    
    
    OboyoboyoBoito! Singing Mefistofele again this Fall!    
    
    
    @bluemtbistro One of my first loves hand fed me escargot by candlelight in a fine dining establishment in Graz, Austria.  Whew!    
    
    
    @kellyoxford That's a beautiful thing.    
    
    
    For those of you who read my more serious blogposts (both of you) I submit:  http://www.bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2011/11/desolate.html …    
    
    
    @SonshineMusic Do they have to be drafts?  Or can they be bottled beers?  ;)    
    
    
    @billhommel @AddThis You're on a roll today, my friend.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake If you can't see them, how do you know you're wearing them?  Did Dame Judi TELL you to wear them?    
    
    
    @SonshineMusic OOOOOOOOOOOHHHHHHHH!! Micro-brews.  Got it.    
    
    
    All we are saying is give bacon a chance.
Why Does Science Hate Bacon?: http://www.mrbaconpants.com/why-does-science-hate-bacon/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for posting this, Karen.  Good reading, and chortle-worthy. http://lnkd.in/99J-4t     
    
    
    This Valentine's Day, may your actions earn you the applause but not the clap.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake :/    
    
    
    @RobertKirkman Can't WAIT!    
    
    
    @simonpegg That's it? That's the question?    
    
    
    @altonbrown That's gonna encourage a lot of bad drivers.    
    
    
    @altonbrown If it got me a homemade cookie, I'd be driving blindfolded. Backwards. At night.    
    
    
    @simonpegg Ugh!  Sorry!  "answer?", not "question."  What a tool I am.    
    
    
    @speedkayser Thanks.

"Is it supposed to burn like this?"    
    
    
    @PetraTolia Perhaps their's is a love that dare not speak its name.    
    
    
    @PetraTolia Thanks so much.  Nothing significant on this end, but time will tell :)    
    
    
    @AudreyBentham Audrone!  Thanks for the follow back.  Hope you're well. :)    
    
    
    @CookingStyles Thanks very much for following me.    
    
    
    @ArtsWArtists Thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    @dw269 Congratulations on the 1st novel coming out, and thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    @Michael_Robb Thank you so much for following along.    
    
    
    Desperately seeking subject matter for my next blog.    
    
    
    @AJTopol We met briefly at B&N in NYC last week. Here's what I think so far of The China Gambit: http://www.bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/02/china-gambit-by-allan-topol.html …    
    
    
    Next Air Pirates show 3/17!  http://www.airpirateradio.com  for ticket info!    
    
    
    How does one get that little check mark by their twitter profile? I'm really me.  What else do I have to do?    
    
    
    @theswizzle Vegetarians are not only starving out all the animals, but they're hastening global warming.    
    
    
    Thus begins the long March.    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor "Underwear? I mean, under where?"    
    
    
    @Trudiuem I thought the ultimate answer was "42." (Hitch Hiker's Guide to the Galaxy."    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Thanks for the warning.  Although I have no intention of unfollowing you. LTIC (Laugh Til I Choke).    
    
    
    You too, can be Unpopular!!  Here's how. http://mail.google.com/mail/?ui=2&view=bsp&ver=ohhl4rw8mbn4 …    
    
    
    Good article by Jessica Liebman, and good advice for all you job seekers out there. http://lnkd.in/KfV3TS     
    
    
    Happy Independence Day to all my fellow Texicans!    
    
    
    @PatriciaHeaton Go soaring in a glider!    
    
    
    Blog Post - Basso for Hire: Keep the Change http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/03/keep-change.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Latest Book Review from Booksellers Without Borders: A Song of Ice and Fire - George R. R. Martin http://booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/2012/03/song-of-ice-and-fire-george-r-r-martin.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Baked, Fried, or Asploded?  Find out here http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/03/baked-fried-or-asploded.html …    
    
    
    @emmacaulfield By Grabthar's hammer.....what a savings... Quite possibly my favorite line from that movie.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Don't know who it was, but it wasn't me, Sugar.    
    
    
    Das fo shizzle to the mizzle, Shawty. @kellyoxford If there's one thing white people like, it's talking like black people on the internet.    
    
    
    Less than two weeks until the Air Pirates kick off a new season. Got tickets yet? http://lnkd.in/i8EF3H     
    
    
    Checking out "Who Are These People?" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/xfZrAw     
    
    
    @TheisenKathleen to prevent cross-fraternization, I suppose.    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor No, that's pretty much it.    
    
    
    @Stage32online One of my favorite quotes EVER.  Never knew it was Twain's.    
    
    
    Books, Dogs, China, Spies, and Quivering Loins?  It's all here in my last blogpost.  http://ning.it/wNWts4     
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor I shall.  Post haste.    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor Yay!    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor Loved it.  OK, you showed me yours, I'll show you mine http://www.bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2011/04/mostest-stoopitestest-ways-to-get-hurt.html …    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks 12 hits so far!  (quiver)    
    
    
    If you're really interested in why we eat bacon for breakfast check out http://bit.ly/hKevMj 
@altonbrown I will.  Right now.    
    
    
    @saramcclung Don't know if anyone's suggested it yet, but I much prefer almond milk to soy.    
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo That's why he's "the late" William Shakespeare.    
    
    
    @KariByron Likewise, I'm sure. :)    
    
    
    @TheisenKathleen Did you show them your picture? Maybe that would've turned the trick. ;)    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @SonshineMusic Oh, I hope so!    
    
    
    @TheisenKathleen ANIMALS!!!  Didn't they even listen to Jane Russell, when she said, "support can be beautiful"?    
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo How're you set for sonnets?    
    
    
    @pardeangel @lapetitecupcake @SonshineMusic "OCCUPY RETAIL WEDNESDAY!!"    
    
    
    @TheisenKathleen Brilliant! "We refuse to help you w/the software you bought from us.  Want to buy some more?" Lotta nerve.    
    
    
    @SteveMartinToGo Are you sure that's his Oscar he's wagging?  There's a reason they called him "Willie."    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks How many his do we have do far? I can't access it from my phone.    
    
    
    @jonrog1 I can't WAIT to see this!    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor Oh, thx. Glad u liked it. I'm so thrilled I may need to wear a helmet.    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor That's an amazingly great line.  I have to read this now, definitely.    
    
    
    Stayed up waaayyyy too late last night for The Walking Dead.  Feeling like a walker today.    
    
    
    As I was once told, "you can't expect to soar with the eagles in the morning if you're wallowing with the pigs all night."

Grunt    
    
    
    I'll be having a devilishly good time in October, singing the title role in Boito's "Mefistofele" with Taconic Opera.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @orthogirl09 You need David Arquette to arrange an introduction.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Depends on the timing.    
    
    
    Saturday night's almost here!  "Herb Marks: Every Price Has It's Man" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/wU9FZw     
    
    
    http://www.recruiter.com/articles/rise-of-the-new-metrics/ …    
    
    
    @cherryduke Unfortunately, I've never owned a really cool leather jacket. But I'll take their word for it.    
    
    
    @cherryduke (snort) Yes.  There it is, and there it is.    
    
    
    @cherryduke Love your website, especially the Nellie Forbush pics.    
    
    
    Finally watched Rise of The Planet of The Apes last night. Better than I'd hoped.    
    
    
    No surprise. They're very dense in carbs. @gretawire:“Eating white rice could increase the risk of developing Type 2 diabetes    
    
    
    Come see me tomorrow night at the Lycian Pavillion in Sugar Loaf with the Air Pirates Radio Theater http://ning.it/mNX2NY     
    
    
    #The Walking Dead  For those of you wondering when the Grimes Gang would leave Hershel's farm, well, okay then.    
    
    
    @WalkingDead_AMC Awesome!    
    
    
    These aren't the twerps you're looking for. @maureenjohnson Help me, Twitter. You're my only hope.    
    
    
    @JDFaverauthor "Do you validate?"    
    
    
    @WalkingDead_AMC Boy, when you guys leave a farm, you really leave a farm!    
    
    
    This week's Booksellers Without Borders: Laydown Lowdown http://booksellerswithoutborders.blogspot.com/2012/03/laydown-lowdown_20.html?spref=tw …
Thanks, Jenn!    
    
    
    @deankoontz Good luck with "House of Odd"!    
    
    
    @MaeValentino May I suggest "Out of the Corner of His Eye"?  That's my favorite of his.    
    
    
    Has anyone else had difficulty with BranchOut? I can't even get it to correct my profile information.    
    
    
    Fifty bucks will buy you more than you'd think...
http://ning.it/GNZcnw     
    
    
    For you book lovers, a little humor to start off the day...http://ning.it/GIiTxr    
    
    
    @PetraTolia Thanks for retweeting me, Petra! :)    
    
    
    @andrewcotto Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks 'tis true    
    
    
    @staceynilsson Put down the kitty, and step back with your hands where we can see them.    
    
    
    Spotlight on local author Michelle Zink at Booksellers Without Borders http://ning.it/GJtqZp     
    
    
    Game of Thrones fans!  Here's my review of Martin's books  http://ning.it/HaBfWI     
    
    
    I created group Booksellers Without Borders NY on Linkedin.: http://lnkd.in/xF-yiC     
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders NY now has a members only group on LinkedIn.    
    
    
    Say What???  My further adventures in miscommunication.  http://www.bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/04/say-what.html …    
    
    
    Featured Guest Blogger - Marlena of Mohegan http://ning.it/HdIU7W     
    
    
    I'm #reading Abraham Lincoln by Seth Grahame-Smith http://bit.ly/I0tEfD     
    
    
    Marked as to-read: Obama by Frank J. Fleming http://bit.ly/I0FRAQ     
    
    
    3 of 5 stars to Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury http://bit.ly/I1dbYo     
    
    
    5 of 5 stars to Tarzan of the Apes by Edgar Rice Burroughs http://bit.ly/I6YJyi     
    
    
    Marked as to-read: Frankenstein. L'immortale by Dean Koontz http://bit.ly/IcaMHH     
    
    
    5 of 5 stars to Timeline by Michael Crichton http://bit.ly/IcnMgk     
    
    
    Please, sir. I want some more...BW/OB writers discuss their "blue blanky" books. http://ning.it/HsWPKb     
    
    
    Reading A Song of Ice and Fire, by George R.R. Martin: Desperately awaiting book 6. http://bit.ly/IBgmq6     
    
    
    @borderlessbooks Yes, I did. Here's proof. pic.twitter.com/bxDrZscP    
    
    
    I dipped my toe in J. D. Robb's Pool.  Read my review of New York to Dallas.  http://ning.it/I8HImA     
    
    
    My latest blog.  Slight "Eeww" factor. http://lnkd.in/Bek-Hg     
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders: "There He Is...Miss America's Eye Candy..." http://www.booksellerswithoutbordersny.com/2012/04/there-he-ismiss-americas-eye-candy.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Basso for Hire: "There He Is...Miss America's Eye Candy..." http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/04/there-he-ismiss-americas-eye-candy.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    @petratolia Thanks for retweeting my blog!    
    
    
    She may be bald, but she's still a blonde.  Stop what you're doing and read her story.  Hug someone you love. http://ning.it/HWfjhX     
    
    
    5 of 5 stars to Watership Down by Richard Adams http://bit.ly/HVN3kg     
    
    
    3 of 5 stars to The Hunger Games by Suzanne Collins http://bit.ly/IOMaX0     
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders: Featured New Author: Glenn Pemberton http://www.booksellerswithoutbordersny.com/2012/04/featured-new-author-glenn-pemberton.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Allen West Confronted by Qu’ran-Wielding CAIR Director  http://conservativepapers.com/news/2012/04/20/allen-west-confronted-by-quran-wielding-cair-director/#.T6BAVQB4Cck.twitter …    
    
    
    Yesterday, dreamed I was riding the bus home @ the end of the day. Woke up & realized it was morning, and I hadn't even BEEN to work yet. :(    
    
    
    @joelivany Haven't done Nabucco yet, but Falstaff was my 1st opera. The whole thing is as joyous as popping open a bottle of champagne.    
    
    
    Goodbye to a dear friend http://ning.it/IQRM5S     
    
    
    Basso for Hire: Did Kipling have a crystal ball? http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2011/02/did-kipling-have-crystal-ball.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Bookstores, Bands, BlackJack, and Texas High School Football.    
    
    
    Bookstores, Bands, BlackJack, and Texas High School Football. http://lnkd.in/VQ_TDr     
    
    
    Adopting 2 kitties tonight. Decided to get the cute ones.    
    
    
    @kellyoxford He should've laid off the frozen burrito, I guess.    
    
    
    I've been on a roll this week.  Got at least 3 different people who won't speak to me now.    
    
    
    Apparently some people have different definitions of "candid."    
    
    
    @_CasualtyofLove I think I'm liking it so far.    
    
    
    @altonbrown That's profound.  Why indeed?  I want one now.    
    
    
    BTW, I'm all in for Team Alton on FNS @altonbrown    
    
    
    Maybe the grand finale will feature knife juggling between three finalists or somthing. @_CasualtyofLove    
    
    
    Got two new kitties!    
    
    
    Chloe pic.twitter.com/QuuCJrLo    
    
    
    Eboli pic.twitter.com/7BjlYYkI    
    
    
    They're seesters.  Eboli has what looks like an eyepatch on her right eye. @lapetitecupcake    
    
    
    She's named for a woman in an opera who also wears an eyepatch, Princess Eboli @lapetitecupcake    
    
    
    Dream yourself fit?
PUNY BASSO!!! http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/05/puny-basso.html …    
    
    
    Can you dream your way to fitness?  Er, maybe not...  http://ning.it/LkDdun     
    
    
    @altonbrown @FoodNetwork I was amazed all of you could keep eating all day while riding that bus.    
    
    
    @altonbrown @FoodNetwork Man, he just couldn't get past that pickle.  "Missed it by THAT much."    
    
    
    @altonbrown How can you tell which lawyers aren't the strange ones?    
    
    
    I'm not Chew material. @altonbrown @chrisc1221 Just one more reason you're the man, Alton.    
    
    
    @RevRioAgape @altonbrown @FoodNetwork I'm surprised more people didn't get queasy, sitting sideways or standing all that time.    
    
    
    @lastgeekgirl @GetGlue Well, bless your beautiful hide, wherever you may be.    
    
    
    @lastgeekgirl "I'm a lonesome polecat. Lonesome sad and blue. Cuz I ain't got no feminine polecat to tell my troubles to."    
    
    
    Thanks for retweeting my blog post!  @PetraTolia pic.twitter.com/rniB07Q2    
    
    
    - http://blog.heritage.org/2012/05/31/morning-bell-how-radical-were-wisconsins-reforms/ …    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks @lapetitecupcake I'm thinking of popping in tomorrow morning around 8 - 9. Will you be there?    
    
    
    @kellyoxford That's a good day.    
    
    
    You've never seen the two of them together, now, have you? @kellyoxford Steven Tyler could also be Jim Morrison's zombie corpse.    
    
    
    Thanks for the tip. @kellyoxford 100% of women with feather earrings are cool with one night stands.    
    
    
    Groan Worthy Free Associating http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/06/groan-worthy-free-associating.html …    
    
    
    My latest blog post:  Groanworthy Free Associating.
http://ning.it/La358N     
    
    
    Basso for Hire salutes a legend.  http://ning.it/MMGjbd     
    
    
    Come see me in "One On One" at the Lycian Centre!  http://ning.it/MMHAio     
    
    
    Ray Bradbury.  The man who messed with my mind.
http://ning.it/MMR2T3     
    
    
    @borderlessbooks Thanks for the promo.  Love that alliteration, by the way.    
    
    
    @borderlessbooks amen    
    
    
    "Man is a stream whose source is unknown."
 - Cemetery Man    
    
    
    bassoforhire has just signed up to Gothise - A place for alternative people http://tinyurl.com/7r6qlwn     
    
    
    Singing Boito's Mefistofele Oct 19, 21, 27 w/Taconic Opera. http://www.taconicopera.org     
    
    
    Finally saw "John Carter" on DVD last night.
Bitterly, bitterly disappointed. Were I not such a Burroughs fan, I MIGHT have liked it. Might.    
    
    
    Updated to include histrionics. A Princess of Mars - Edgar Rice Burroughs http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/01/princess-of-mars-edgar-rice-burrougs.html …    
    
    
    Congrats on the win for Team Alton last night! @altonbrown    
    
    
    @altonbrown all the way down to the 7th generation    
    
    
    @altonbrown @CreativeDrunk @SimonMajumdar Don't let that knowledge preclude fueling the jet.    
    
    
    Now I know why Disney marketed this film so poorly. @borderlessbooks http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/01/princess-of-mars-edgar-rice-burrougs.html#!/2012/01/princess-of-mars-edgar-rice-burrougs.html …    
    
    
    @bassoforhire Not even sure if I am an "alternative people," but we'll see.    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Interested in being womannapped?    
    
    
    @bassoforhire @altonbrown "...and He said unto them, 'oh, EWE're a stiff-necked generation.'"    
    
    
    @NadiaNarain It's to keep their pants up.    
    
    
    Umm.  Just realized my socks don't match.    
    
    
    poke @johncaramom    
    
    
    Scattershooting http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/06/when-i-lived-in-texas-there-was-iconic.html …    
    
    
    @altonbrown "Can you tell which thing is not like the others, by the time the others are gone?"    
    
    
    @altonbrown Sorry to see Emily go.  Congrats again to your Pad-Wan.    
    
    
    @green_drink @altonbrown Definitely.    
    
    
    It's Wrong.  So Wrong. http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/06/its-wrong-so-wrong.html …    
    
    
    @DavidCallinan Good morning (afternoon for you).  Thanks very much for following me.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake For me, if the bacon's real crispy, NO toast. If it's not crispy, toast (contrasting textures).    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Maybe she's trying to audition for a vampire flick.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake I'd almost rather have a zombie apocolypse than be overrun by hermaphroditic Belle sippy cup drones.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake I like a little chew to it.  BUT for the BLT, I go with crispy on white bread.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @WeAreEverAfter It's not a 2nd hand celebrity lingerie store, is it?    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @pardeangel It's got to be toast AND crispy bacon on a club, or you tug the sandwich apart.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Not to drag out this old debate, but: unicorns vs hermaphrotide Belle sibby cup drones? Who would win?    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Unless it's an S&M club. Wait.  That works on a couple of levels, doesn't it?    
    
    
    @bassoforhire @lapetitecupcake @WeAreEverAfter because 2nd hand celebrity lingerie raises some interesting possibilities.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake However, that in no way should disparage DJD.  It's merely a simile.    
    
    
    @bassoforhire @lapetitecupcake and an excellent one.    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow!  :) @Alan_Zhukovski    
    
    
    Did not know this.. pic.twitter.com/bel2weRD    
    
    
    Thanks for following me!  @TessVelazquez    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Sounds like a pinched sciatic nerve.  Hope it's not a disc thing.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake I may have some diagrams of stretches from a Phys Therapist. I'll see if I can find them and forward to you. Might help.    
    
    
    @billhommel That's some article.  How ignorant can one person be to think it's okay to think, let alone say something like that?    
    
    
    @billhommel (snort)    
    
    
    @billhommel Good one. Remember when Lockhart asked you "what's the quota" for coeds per BU law professors one night?  'Bout died.    
    
    
    @Argyle_Gargoyle @JohnPinette Nay Nay!    
    
    
    Now with a picture of the snake. http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2011/03/farewell-to-bangalore.html#!/2011/03/farewell-to-bangalore.html …    
    
    
    @billhommel Yeah, this was at dinner one night after one of them got fired or censored. To the statement that the prof "had" one too many...    
    
    
    @billhommel ...he responded, "what's the quota."  A great moment.    
    
    
    Hey, Hudson Valley!  6/29 and 6/30 Come see me in One on One. http://www.facebook.com/?ref=logo#!/events/462620610430922/ … pic.twitter.com/W4uNs2Hy    
    
    
        
    
    
    Just added a new event on http://hvBiz.com .  Support the Arts in Orange County! http://ning.it/OIDuZN     
    
    
    ONE ON ONE - Four Plays in One Night http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/06/one-on-one-four-plays-in-one-night.html …    
    
    
    Last night on FNS, "Good thing we already ate."  BEST LINE OF THE WEEKEND!!  Thanks for the belly laugh. @altonbrown    
    
    
    @GPTimes @AltonBrown That line almost as good as Hulk's beat down of Loki.    
    
    
    @TimothyMalcolm It's probably the potatoes.    
    
    
    Me, as John the gravedigger, in "Cemetery Man," by Ken Jenkins. pic.twitter.com/BybPh11i    
    
    
    @FallingSkiesTNT Well, I THINK so.  But I'm still not sure.  Trust, but verify.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake @rosannascotto @gregkellyfox5 Wait - there's strippers covering for someone? Isn't that an oxymoron?    
    
    
    @bassoforhire @lapetitecupcake @rosannascotto @gregkellyfox5 Oh, CONSOLING, not covering.  Okay, that makes more sense (I guess).  Carry on.    
    
    
    @bassoforhire @lapetitecupcake @rosannascotto @gregkellyfox5 "Fox5 - We console - You decide."    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake To quote your recent H & O reference, "it's a bitch, girl."    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake I knew a girl who had that once.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake She got it when she got caught in the rain without her falafel.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Oh, no!    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake See what happens when you go out in the rain without your falafel?    
    
    
    I'll bet all the sweet, green icing was flowing down, wasn't it? @lapetitecupcake    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake You must have left that cake out in the rain when the strippers on Fox5 disctracted you.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake ...or leap ONto it.  Now THAT'S quality daytime programming.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Loving this thread.  I may turn it into my next BFH blogpost.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Now I just have to relocate all of them.  Maybe DJD could throw the cake at the strippers.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Nor does DJD.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Kinda like 5;5, by the way.    
    
    
    @guarnaschelli That's a theory that I've long held, but have unfortunately never been able to successfully test.    
    
    
    Booksellers Without Borders: Laydown Lowdown http://www.booksellerswithoutbordersny.com/2012/07/laydown-lowdown.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    RIP Andy Griffith.  Have a Big Orange Drink on Me. http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/07/rip-andy-griffith-have-big-orange-drink.html …    
    
    
    Two twittering twerps   
Dont' Forget Your Falafel!!!! http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/07/dont-forget-your-falafel.html …    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow.  Here's a blog I wrote back in December about supporting local businesses. @occupySMALLst    
    
    
    @AbelUndercity @altonbrown I can't think of anyone more worthy of a defense squad.    
    
    
    @altonbrown You'd be angry too, if someone rubbed you and wrapped you in foil.    
    
    
    Bassoforhire gets philosophical.  The Mayan Higgs Boson God Particle Calendar Disruptor http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/07/mayan-higgs-boson-god-particle-calendar.html …    
    
    
    @altonbrown "Do you expect me to talk?"  "No, Mr. Brown, I expect you to cook."    
    
    
    Bazinga! @altonbrown I thought he did very well. & like you said, the same guy heckled him 4 times.    
    
    
    I didn't think they were obnoxious.  They were completely him and part of why I like him. @altonbrown    
    
    
    @altonbrown No. That's a cat IN a sombrero. I think the tweeter wants you to use a sombrero to draw a cat.    
    
    
    @ugottafriend @altonbrown Excellent point.    
    
    
    @JulieLeto @altonbrown Cheering throngs. Now you're talking.    
    
    
    @guarnaschelli It's true. Whenever I hear from friends coming home from abroad, they always say they can't wait to eat a burger.    
    
    
    Basso for Hire has Gone to the Dogs http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/07/basso-for-hire-has-gone-to-dogs.html …    
    
    
    I have, indeed.  @borderlessbooks    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Go for it.  You could probably find a league for that in Central Park.    
    
    
    @PetraTolia Thanks for the mention.    
    
    
    From Nutria, tis but a hop, skip and a jump to Capybara burgers. @altonbrown    
    
    
    Plus, it has that nice little human touch.  @altonbrown    
    
    
    "One day, lad, all this will be yours."  "What, the curtains?"  @altonbrown    
    
    
    Immense, cosmic power. @altonbrown    
    
    
    20 votes a day.  Didn't realize they were doing the tallying in Chicago. In that case, can I vote for Morimoto? @altonbrown    
    
    
    NOOOOOOOOO!!! @altonbrown    
    
    
    How about cheering THONGS? @bassoforhire @JulieLeto @altonbrown    
    
    
    @JulieLeto  Ya got me.  Guilty as charged.    
    
    
    @RandySpate @gretawire True. And that's why we have to pay attention and inform yourself as much as possible.    
    
    
    Impressive. However, his skills are not yet complete.  @EatFellowHumans needs more multi-taskers.  @altonbrown    
    
    
    @altonbrown and then it will taste like gussied up tofu.    
    
    
    Best response EVER. Thank you @altonbrown BTW, you've finally got me reading Good Eats: The Early Years. Love the interview at the beginning    
    
    
    @TheLemonBowl @GDeLaurentiis I thought Alton's hair was quite fetching, too.    
    
    
    @altonbrown @EatFellowHumans @FoodNetwork Outstanding!  Congrats on a well deserved win.  Enjoyed the format.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Really enjoyed watching u as a mentor, but I see why u wouldn't again. U were so personally invested in ur team. Well done. Thx.    
    
    
    Belated congratulations!  Really enjoyed watching this season.  Best of luck!  @EatFellowHumans    
    
    
    Hope all goes well, @KChenoweth, and here's hoping you catch a big doctor.    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine @lapetitecupcake Bartering for services, perhaps?    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine @lapetitecupcake Perhaps she gave them chickens, or something.    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine guess we're going with the "or something," then.    
    
    
    Press Release the Basso For Hire!!! http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/07/press-release-basso-for-hire.html …    
    
    
    The Walking Dead: - Special FX Makeup Artist and Co-Executive Producer Greg Nicotero http://blogs.amctv.com/the-walking-dead/2012/07/greg-nicotero-interview.php … via @AMC_TV    
    
    
    @loracainacts Good morning, Lora.  Thanks for the follow! :)    
    
    
    I read Unknown by Unknows http://bit.ly/Nevrhl     
    
    
    I read The Ant Men by Eric North http://bit.ly/OO8ODV     
    
    
    Good morning, @Cerullean.  Thanks very much for the follow.    
    
    
    Thanks @WilliamDeen  the follow!  @WilliamDeen    
    
    
    @loracainacts Boito's Mefistofele w/Taconic Opera, October 19, 21, & 27.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898672723/ …    
    
    
    It's so funny it burns! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898672726/ …    
    
    
    - http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898672756/ …    
    
    
    Defeat the Avengers... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898675365/ …    
    
    
    Lieutenant Dan! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898675366/ …    
    
    
    I said that so many times over the last year. Thanks goodness I'm on the way back. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898675715/ …    
    
    
    2" off my waist after 4 wraps w/Greens & Thermofit!  @itworksglobal    
    
    
    Where'd I go? http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/08/whered-i-go.html … I've been indundated in work and a too brief vacation.  Be back posting regularly again, soon.    
    
    
    Bacon, bacon, bacon!! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898678206/ …    
    
    
    @CherylBentley4 Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    Back in Bidness http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/08/back-in-bidness.html …    
    
    
    Well played, Mr. Stark. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898679194/ …    
    
    
    Dos Equus Man memes never fail. Also, he's freaking handsome. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898679196/ …    
    
    
    Love these pics http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898679216/ …    
    
    
    Seriously. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898679217/ …    
    
    
    I want a claymore http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898679224/ …    
    
    
    @castinstone Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @bassoforhire Equis.    
    
    
    True story http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898680522/ …    
    
    
    Just too stubborn. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898680541/ …    
    
    
    A happy tree painting Bob Ross http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898680546/ …    
    
    
    Eboli in repose http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898682854/ …    
    
    
    A most excellent cat nap. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898682855/ …    
    
    
    Body http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898682982/ …    
    
    
    Body Art. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898682989/ …    
    
    
    Walk on. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683257/ …    
    
    
    Darth Haul - awesome! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683637/ …    
    
    
    Charisma http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683639/ …    
    
    
    HA! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683733/ …    
    
    
    Well played, Ninja dog.  Very well played. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683744/ …    
    
    
    The dog speedometer. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683753/ …    
    
    
    Strangely hilarious. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898683765/ …    
    
    
    @TheisenKathleen @DLP_DSM Lake Compounce is in Bristol.  Pretty fun place, although it's been about 8 years since I was there.    
    
    
    too tired http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898685257/ …    
    
    
    Mom said it's time to come home! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898685266/ …    
    
    
    Anger Management. by waihey, via Flickr http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898685277/ …    
    
    
    Or a well played scene. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898685285/ …    
    
    
    Beatles + Yoda http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898685296/ …    
    
    
    . http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898686732/ …    
    
    
    Deja Vu http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898687889/ …    
    
    
    Wait, what? http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898687942/ …    
    
    
    Air Pirates Radio Theater « Sugar Loaf Performing Arts Center http://sugarloafpac.org/2012/09/air-pirates-radio-theater/ …    
    
    
    Media's One-Sided Coverage Is Clear Evidence Of Bias http://news.investors.com/ibd-editorials-viewpoint/082712-623715-one-sided-media-coverage-shows-bias.htm … via @IBDinvestors    
    
    
    Fact Checking Sally Kohn | MRCTV http://mrctv.org/blog/fact-checking-sally-kohn …    
    
    
    Well played, Mr. Eastwood.  Transcript of Clint Eastwood speech at RNC | Fox News http://fxn.ws/TBYA8J  via @foxnewspolitics    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine Thanks for pimping me out, Mel!    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine @bassoforhire @TeamEmThompson    
    
    
    Just in case. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898690486/ …    
    
    
    . http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898697418/ …    
    
    
    . http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898697421/ …    
    
    
    . http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898698453/ …    
    
    
    .... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898698457/ …    
    
    
    what's stopping you http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898698458/ …    
    
    
    Such a funny show http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898698459/ …    
    
    
    Arkham-Harley by *Chuckdee on deviantART http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898698462/ …    
    
    
    Get there fustest with the mostest. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898700824/ …    
    
    
    Taste my fury. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898700912/ …    
    
    
    I sawn what you did, there. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898700914/ …    
    
    
    It's a good thing. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898700916/ …    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine Yes.  Yes it are.    
    
    
    Aliens - Motion tracker http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898702158/ …    
    
    
    Singing at Taconic Opera's Gala. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898705941/ …    
    
    
    Thanks to Kat for posting. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898706186/ …    
    
    
    Via Rudy. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898706228/ …    
    
    
    Here's hoping your day goes as planned. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898708013/ …    
    
    
    Got this one from Analise http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898708029/ …    
    
    
    Cracks me up. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898708053/ …    
    
    
    Almost snorted. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898708859/ …    
    
    
    Lol. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898708892/ …    
    
    
    Ouch http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898709544/ …    
    
    
    ... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898709740/ …    
    
    
    From Giant George...  9/11 Rescue Dogs http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898710408/ …    
    
    
    Mr. Wonka has a message for you... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898710422/ …    
    
    
    Name puns http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898710425/ …    
    
    
    LTICAA (Laugh Til I Clog An Artery) http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898710429/ …    
    
    
    @PatriciaHeaton I'm just so sickened by this.  So awful.    
    
    
    Is it an EVIL basso confuso? http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898712216/ …    
    
    
    Book review: "What if...?"  1945, by Robert Conroy http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/09/what-if-1945-by-robert-conroy.html …    
    
    
    Hilarious, if icky.  Nursicle: Secret Nurse Glossary http://nursicle.blogspot.com/p/secret-nurse-glossery.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Basso Serioso http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898715542/ …    
    
    
    So cool http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898715553/ …    
    
    
    ...ice cube with strawberry frozen in middle - what a pretty drink this will make! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898715559/ …    
    
    
    We might have a problem http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898716022/ …    
    
    
    LOL. Hate when that happens. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898718611/ …    
    
    
    Ah, good times. Gooood  times. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898718971/ …    
    
    
    Yet another good one with which to beat myself over the head. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898719883/ …    
    
    
    @dreamsofwriting Thanks for the follow, Jenny!    
    
    
    Air Pirates Radio Theater « Sugar Loaf Performing Arts Center http://sugarloafpac.org/2012/11/air-pirates-radio-theater-3/ …    
    
    
    So say we all. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898720553/ …    
    
    
    4 of 5 stars to 1945 by Robert Conroy http://bit.ly/OFct9R     
    
    
    Competition in Music: Good or Bad? What's a good business http://ning.it/OFsHj9 ?    
    
    
    Book Review Blog: 1945, by Robert Conroy.  http://ning.it/OFsMDF     
    
    
    HP tells it like it is! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898724655/ …    
    
    
    Hmmm http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898724662/ …    
    
    
    Slice whole potatoes almost all the way through, s o that the slices are all still attached at the b http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898724673/ …    
    
    
    Molly Weasley is one bad mamma jamma! http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898726307/ …    
    
    
    All the single planets... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898726312/ …    
    
    
    Oh dear.  I need a moment alone.  Double Decker Taco Cupcakes | The Girl Who Ate Everything http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898726336/ …    
    
    
    Get your Wookie on. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898727313/ …    
    
    
    Is it time for the Gathering already? http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898727317/ …    
    
    
    Great Performances - Mefistofele http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/09/great-performances-mefistofele.html …    
    
    
    @gramilano Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @altonbrown Yes.  Yes they are.    
    
    
    4 of 5 stars to Piercing the Darkness by Frank Peretti http://bit.ly/QA8d7i     
    
    
    @kellyoxford I remember when that was all I WANTED.    
    
    
    Um...yeah. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898736254/ …    
    
    
    Churchill making his famous "V for victory" sign in 1943. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898736263/ …    
    
    
    -C.S Lewis.      So many people don't get this. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898736283/ …    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898740607/ …    
    
    
    True... so true... http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898740640/ …    
    
    
    Alack. Alas. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898740663/ …    
    
    
    .cone heads http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898742719/ …    
    
    
    Bassoforhire discusses evil, wicked books, in...You're Not Allowed http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/09/youre-not-allowed.html …    
    
    
    Thanks for following!  @sDaveda    
    
    
    Talkin bout pigs, taters, n such.  http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2012/10/come-back.html#!/2012/10/come-back.html …    
    
    
    Brain Memes http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898753170/ …    
    
    
    But it's not like anything could happen to him.  #walkingdead http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898753174/ …    
    
    
    Excellent opportunity to support the arts in the Hudson Valley http://ning.it/POCFtr     
    
    
    Excellent blog post by my nurse friend, Marlena of Mohegan, on how HIV changed everything http://ning.it/PjeZTz     
    
    
    Operation Basso Reducto Progress Report: July - September, 2012 http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862898763478/ …    
    
    
    Michelle Malkin » Who will vet the story-teller-in-chief’s latest Obamacare anecdote? http://michellemalkin.com/2012/10/08/who-will-vet-the-story-teller-in-chiefs-latest-obamacare-anecdote/ … via @michellemalkin    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Yep.  he's ready.    
    
    
    @NorthPoet Thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    Tech rehearsal tonight!  Mefistofele opens Friday, 10/19/12.  Son lo spirito che nega. pic.twitter.com/CFCL95Vh    
    
    
    Friday's Mefistofele (Alan Andrews) and Faust (John Roger) pic.twitter.com/tA0TvhWG    
    
    
    Apparently my twitter acct was hacked last wk, & everyone in the free world got a weird msg from me. s/b fixed now. Sorry.    
    
    
    @kseniaanske Thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @kellyoxford It should be encouraged and rewarded.    
    
    
    @TheFilmLobby Still more unanswered questions?    
    
    
    @ApiarySociety Thanks.  I had both Twitter and fb hacked in the same week.  Just now getting Twit active again.    
    
    
    Check out this #Movember effort to change the face of men's health http://us.movember.com/mospace/5503041  via @movember    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great Air Pirates show Saturday night at the SugarPAC.  Come see us Dec 15 in "Herb Marks, Freelance: It Ain't Such A Wonderful Life"    
    
    
    Thanksgiving ruminations from the Basso for Hire 
http://ning.it/TY5KWh     
    
    
    Blog Nog. Come see me perform in Sugar Loaf this month.  http://ning.it/TBvv1u     
    
    
    4 of 5 stars to One Shot by Lee Child http://bit.ly/RGYuSp     
    
    
    Any recommendations as to where I can go to eat haggis in Orange County?    
    
    
    Last Air Pirates show of 2012!  Hope you can come see us, or listen to the live broadcast.

http://lnkd.in/3urreq     
    
    
    Time to vote for the Hudson Valley's Best of 2012.  The link to the recordonline's site is in my blog post.  http://lnkd.in/MvPhAZ     
    
    
    @altonbrown Very cool.  Thanks, AB.  The loaves are actually a little bigger than I'd always imagined.    
    
    
    @altonbrown I've never had haggis before, and I'm on a mission to make it myself.  Any suggestions or advice?    
    
    
    My Part in LinkedIn's 200 Million Member Milestone http://lnkd.in/DD4uuH     
    
    
    White Calico Water Cats #3: Chloe gets an assist.
 http://youtu.be/yjBPtUvbj2k  via @youtube    
    
    
    White Calico Water Cats #4:  It's gone!: http://youtu.be/zBoJP4Prgqo  via @youtube    
    
    
    Maybe the hiatus built up my expectations too much, but I was only whelmed, not overwhelmed by #thewalkingdead Sunday night.    
    
    
    Michonne is really getting on my nerves.  Would it kill you to speak just every once in a while?  #thewalkingdead    
    
    
    Looking fwd to a great Sun-Mon getaway with Lenna for a belated Valentine's Day.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Looks like a mashup between Alien and Star Trek TNG.    
    
    
    @altonbrown That sounds fabulous.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Yeah, that's a safe bet.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Barney's Good Eats.    
    
    
    Seems legit...Rotting Smell In Congress Traced To Decaying Senator Who Died Inside Wall http://onion.com/12SRPZI  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    Well played, Chicks on the Right.  Very well played.  
So Easy Even A Kid Can Understand It - Chicks on the Right http://www.chicksontheright.com/categories/the-makeover-and-or-miscellaneous/item/22947-so-easy-even-a-kid-can-understand-it …    
    
    
    I so very much want this Bubble Wrap Calendar. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899212595/ …    
    
    
    Looking for IT Consultants for 3 month project in Delaware.    
    
    
    @altonbrown And this is why we love you.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Oh, no!  Apparently the Mayans were right, but just off by a few months.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Huzzah!    
    
    
    @altonbrown Nice.    
    
    
    My main reason for going on Twitter is to see what @altonbrown has been posting.    
    
    
    Multiple openings for solid Break/Fix techs in NYC.  Full and part time positions.    
    
    
    Looking for A/V support in Midtown Manhattan.  Fortune 500 clients.    
    
    
    Columbus, Ohio:  IMAC techs with imaging experience (Ghost).    
    
    
    @altonbrown Party on, Garth.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Extremely sweet!  That was always one of my favorites.    
    
    
    An over-produced resume just might be hurting your chances for a second look, let alone an interview. http://lnkd.in/h6BSjA     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: Level 2 Technical Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/9kog011n     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: Level 2 Technical Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/9kog011n     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: Level 2 Technical Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/9kog011n     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: Level 2 Technical Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/9kog011n     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support in Salt Lake City 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/zmuuyveq     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: Level 2 Technical Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/9kog011n     
    
    
    If soap bubbles rise out of the Vatican, does that mean we get pope-on-a-rope?    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Just tell everyone it's a tattoo of an amoeba.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Don't skimp on the pate.    
    
    
    @altonbrown Is it amphibious, as well?  That would curb the non Speedo-worthy Speedo wearing population.    
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support in Salt Lake City 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/zmuuyveq     
    
    
    Good interview prep tips from Arleen Bradley. http://lnkd.in/PfyemA     
    
    
    @altonbrown, here's a multi-purpose tool that's right up your alley. pic.twitter.com/SBiMriLlrO    
    
    
    @altonbrown Post-it Table.  The ultimate multi-purpose furniture. pic.twitter.com/0HqOO8lfi5    
    
    
    Distilled Zombies - Problem Solved! http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/03/distilled-zombies-problem-solved.html …    
    
    
    Great article. http://lnkd.in/X7RKMH     
    
    
    Good morning, @miragrant Loved the News Flesh trilogy.  I reviewed it on my blog.  Hope you enjoy. http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/01/how-scary-movies-and-george-romero.html#!/2013/01/how-scary-movies-and-george-romero.html …    
    
    
    @seananmcguire here's my review of News Flesh, in case @miragrant doesn't see it.  Enjoy. http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/01/how-scary-movies-and-george-romero.html#!/2013/01/how-scary-movies-and-george-romero.html …    
    
    
    @Bourdain It's @altonbrown, isn't it?    
    
    
    @seananmcguire I'm going to have to finally break down and get an eReader so I can read the prequel.    
    
    
    @Mark_MSCO Sort of like, "I'm exploring opportunities."    
    
    
    @simonpegg Atta boy.  That's how you do it.    
    
    
    Missing the point. @DaveKill @altonbrown    
    
    
    @Mark_MSCO  Ah.    
    
    
    @DaveKill @altonbrown LOL.    
    
    
    @mindofkevin @Grand_Illusions and then it eventually becomes, "do her grown kids still live in the house with her?"    
    
    
    @mindofkevin Crosswalk Nannystate.    
    
    
    @altonbrown the price you pay, I guess.  He's really gonna need a lot of those doggie biscuits now.    
    
    
    @kellyoxford Apparently writers do something, after all.    
    
    
    @secupp I guess they can take tolerance - they just can't dish it out.    
    
    
    @iamstevemartin I finally got around to seeing "The Big Year" yesterday. Better late than never. Fun stuff. Thanks as always for the laughs.    
    
    
    Denied: Gun Store Owner Refuses to Hand AR-15 over to Mark Kelly http://www.breitbart.com/Big-Government/2013/03/26/Denied-Gun-Store-Owner-Refuses-To-Hand-AR-15-Over-To-Mark-Kelly?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    Career Coaching - http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899375875/ … Here it is the next latest and greatest job search tool:  Pinterest    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RVEgRS  I'm looking forward to learning more, Arleen.  Thanks for the post.  I'm following your boards now, too.    
    
    
    Great article by Dave Kerpen! http://lnkd.in/fxumfV     
    
    
    What's Holding You Back? http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/03/whats-holding-you-back.html … - Great article by Dave Kerpen    
    
    
    @AuthorLMurphy  So far the only thing I've done like that is to share others' articles or posts.  I'd be interested in doing it, though.    
    
    
    Arleen Bradley's 2nd article on Pinterest tells me I have to tidy up my boards a bit.  Another good article. http://lnkd.in/iuqBKp     
    
    
    Geoffrey James has some good ideas on finding that happy place at work. http://lnkd.in/8qT-7N     
    
    
    @altonbrown Making my mouth water.    
    
    
    @RevDamon If you haven't seen "The Big Year" w/Steve Martin, Jack Black, & Owen Wilson, you need to do so.    
    
    
    @RevDamon  Especially if you're into "birding" at all.    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/GAgPQF  Excellent tips, Mark.  I'll certainly share this with my network.    
    
    
    @EatFellowHumans Enjoyed "Rebel Eats" last week.  Congrats again.    
    
    
    @RevDamon Necessitated by the desire to continue putting off the one remaining thing from the previous list.    
    
    
    Design Strategy is looking for A+ Certified Techs for Wilmington, Delaware.  Message me for details.    
    
    
    @altonbrown LAWSY!    
    
    
    @altonbrown Maybe the best tweet ever.    
    
    
    @Liberty92625 Thanks for following me!    
    
    
    Here comes the weekend, honey.  Let's hit it.  Delbert McClinton ~ I'm With You: http://youtu.be/Nzpb9WaIPKY  via @youtube    
    
    
    @IKnoNetwork - Thanks for the tweet!    
    
    
    Good insight from Robin Rayburn.  Know how to tell the story of your resume. http://lnkd.in/chAYCx     
    
    
    Thought provoking article by Jim Clifton http://lnkd.in/UhS33z     
    
    
    The Air Pirates take NYC April 13th: shttp://www.nypost.com/p/entertainment/theater/aargh_thar_be_pirates_7VsKq1ntU0xg4Z5DWolTBL    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/2Cp_kt  I also believe that "obligated" is the key word, here.  No, I don't think we're obligated to teach others about...    
    
    
    The one good thing about working multiple jobs 7 days a week: Monday's pretty much just another day.    
    
    
    The Air Pirates return to The Underground 4/20 with Herb Marks, Freelance: Make Me An Offer I Can Refuse. pic.twitter.com/ZNi5FusI32    
    
    
    Are you waiting to hear back from an interview? http://lnkd.in/vQCxiC     
    
    
    @AllenWest Fabulous book and wonderful movie.  Have to watch it again, now.    
    
    
    If I was on the road early on my way from home back to Baylor, I used to stop at this great little Czech bakery in West, TX. Prayers to all.    
    
    
    R.I.P. Pat Summerall.    
    
    
    @seananmcguire Sleep well.    
    
    
    @sDaveda My pleasure!  Great material is great material, right?    
    
    
    Shocking.  Are You Sitting Down? - Chicks on the Right http://chicksontheright.com/posts/item/24116-are-you-sitting-down …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/4AtmJf  Were they actually able to keep a straight face when they introduced that legislation?    
    
    
    Going to the Met to see Das Reingold tonight.    
    
    
    You had one job, Rhinemaidens.  ONE JOB!  Protect. The. Gold.
#dasrheingold #themet #metropolitanopera    
    
    
    @EricOwensSinger Great job last night, Alberich.  Plus, Harrison Moore says hello.    
    
    
    RIP, George.   George Jones - LIVE "He Stopped Loving Her Today": http://youtu.be/1R2F9f2Cl6Y  via @youtube    
    
    
    My blog about West, Texas and Westboro http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/04/west-westboro-wait-minute.html#!/2013/04/west-westboro-wait-minute.html …    
    
    
    @LordGrimdark @saladinahmed It is generally "God's wounds."  Just like "oddsblood" came from "God's blood."    
    
    
    Looking for A+ Certified Technical Support in San Antonio.    
    
    
    Part time IT Support needed in Greenwich, CT.  Email resume to me at aandrews@designstrategy.com    
    
    
    Arleen Bradley gives more advice for job searchers. http://lnkd.in/qy87_z     
    
    
    @altonbrown  "Nuts may contain nuts. No monkey nuts were harmed in the manufacturing, packaging, or shipping of these monkey nuts."    
    
    
    Checking out "My Review of Joe Abercrombie's "The First Law: The Blade Itself"" on http://hvBiz.com : http://ning.it/11YVTn2     
    
    
    @Breann_Johnson Good morning, and thanks for the follow.    
    
    
    Got Any Duck Food? http://wp.me/p3teKK-11     
    
    
    Got Any Duck Food? http://wp.me/p3teKK-11  via @bassoforhire    
    
    
    Got Any Duck Food? http://wp.me/p3teKK-15     
    
    
    If you've bounced about on your career path, read what Arleen Bradley has to say about tailoring your resume to highl…http://wp.me/p2JJFD-ix     
    
    
    Singing Verdi in church... 
<iframe src="http://www.facebook.com/video/embed?video_id=10151435406318443 …" width="720" height="1280" frameborder="0"></iframe>    
    
    
    Excellent "real world" advice from Daniel Shapero. http://lnkd.in/5HnhRH     
    
    
    @altonbrown The original Iron Chef: Miklos Molnar aka Ernie Kovacs en: http://youtu.be/zc7UdCrJRKI  via @youtube    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/a795Sx  Got to have a smokin' hot resume.    
    
    
    @altonbrown grammar matters, even when being insulted, apparently.    
    
    
    @altonbrown like Mike Tyson said, "how dare they challenge me with their thomewhat pwimitive skills."    
    
    
    @Wahlee_98 @altonbrown  That is an EXCELLENT, timey-wimey idea.    
    
    
    @bflay @MarchStephanie Don't know about NYC but http://www.briansbackyardbbq.com/  is about an hour away & they have GREAT nachos, bbq, and music.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Need quality IT Pros for projects this week in Newark, Delaware.  Email me at aandrews@designstrategy.com.    
    
    
    @ATHudd Agreed.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @seananmcguire @rachelcaine OH, PUPPIES!  I thought it was "poppies."  
Still, puppy hair up your nostrils - not good.    
    
    
    Good advice from Donna Fuscaldo. http://lnkd.in/Jfnssu     
    
    
    Of course they're available upon request.  Good resume writing advice from David Nicola. http://lnkd.in/gY2us2     
    
    
    Captivate Your Audience.   http://www.ulistic.com/msp-speaker/?sthash.GQfbqwbj.mjjo=%2Egde_150252_me … http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899760177/ …    
    
    
    How to get a #job in #Social Media #infographic http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899796608/ …    
    
    
    Don't let your resume get eaten by zombies. http://lnkd.in/HVXaFp     
    
    
    Pull This Thing Out of Me, or "Gigging for Grandaddy" http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/07/pull-this-thing-out-of-me-or-gigging.html …    
    
    
    @peterbromberg Thanks for the re-follow, Bro.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Don’t Fall For These Interview Tricks To Make You Say More Than You Should http://lnkd.in/G3ptv9     
    
    
        
    
    
    @whitehouse @intel http://michellemalkin.com/2013/07/16/big-surprise-white-house-immigration-fact-not-so-factual-after-all/ …    
    
    
    Looking for IT Pros for part time work in Salt Lake City.  Possible full time work as well.  Message me for details.    
    
    
    @altonbrown I admit I snorted when I saw this.    
    
    
    @jfox39 I'm a recruiter looking for IT pros in SLC.  Please accept my LinkedIn invitation to connect. - Alan Andrews    
    
    
    Winston Churchill http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899974476/ …    
    
    
    Oh, the agony.  When will it end? http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862899974880/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Started reading Twenty Thirty by @AlbertBrooks yesterday.  Just a few chapters in and he's got me already.    
    
    
    Looking for a Software Support Specialist in Louisville, Kentucky.    
    
    
    Looking for an Experienced HP Printer Technician in Overland Park, KS.  Contact me at aandrews@designstrategy.com    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/be3Ggb  More good information.  Thanks, Arleen!    
    
    
    My review of 2030, the new novel by @AlbertBrooks He promised me he'd be gentle.
http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/08/2030-by-albert-brooks-book-review_9.html#!/2013/08/2030-by-albert-brooks-book-review_9.html …    
    
    
    @AlbertBrooks Thanks!  I guess looks can be deceiving after all.    
    
    
    @guarnaschelli @altonbrown @FoodNetwork What a trifecta! Food Network Star, Cutthroat Kitchen, and Alex Guarnachelli on ICA.    
    
    
    @guerillaopera @bassoforhire    
    
    
    @guerillaopera My pleasure.    
    
    
    The woman took the daughter to the airport for her yearly visit to my parents' house in Texas.    
    
    
    Outstanding perspective on humans recruiting humans. http://lnkd.in/niD5by     
    
    
    More keen insight from Liz Ryan.  Be a human workplace. http://lnkd.in/-dDQ8k     
    
    
    Eboli in a thoughtful moment. http://pinterest.com/pin/448037862900126783/ …    
    
    
    @ConnectNY Glad to be here.    
    
    
    @krewemaynard @Talkmaster Just make it simple and change EVERY street name EVERYWHERE to BHO Blvd.    
    
    
    @peterbromberg More like "they were unable to discuss intelligently to the public."    
    
    
    I'm sure he has, @peterbromberg, & it probably gives him a warm, tingly feeling running down his leg.    
    
    
    @abbe_elliott Because he's @altonbrown and therefore brimming with coolness.    
    
    
    Factoid: You won't die if your recycling routine is to combine the last drops from different vodka bottles into a shot glass & drink them.    
    
    
    I walk past the new location for Butter on 45th Str every day.  Can't wait til it opens.  Drooling a bit right now.    
    
    
    @lapetitecupcake Don't know yet, but I'd love to hear @guarnaschelli describe them all. Nobody makes food sound better than she does.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @RBPundit Staggeringly stupid, isn't it?    
    
    
    Looking for a Level 1 IMAC tech for a full time position in Tampa.  Email me at aandrews@designstrategy.com with resume attached.    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 Thanks for following me in this parallel universe, Elle.    
    
    
    Need IT Support in Columbus, Ohio.  Send your resume to aandrews@designstrategy.com.    
    
    
    This drink:  I like it.  ANOTHER! pic.twitter.com/Y25v5KAMHA    
    
    
    Outstanding advice for "Millenials" trying to join the workforce.  http://blog.doostang.com/do-employers-want-to-hire-millennials/ …    
    
    
    @BarracudaMama @shawn_holster Big shocker there.    
    
    
    Yikes.  It was nice knowing you.  @ellethomas48    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 My favorite is still "infinity TIMES infinity."    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 Possibly the best tweet ever.    
    
    
    Garden has been an epic fail this year. But for 1 banana pepper plant and a valiant jalapeno plant, I am bereft of home grown veggies.    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 and of course, strapping a cheetah to your grandmother's back.    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 Seriously, that's like @kellyoxford funny.    
    
    
    @AlexScopino You're welcome, fellow cellar dweller.    
    
    
    What role are you playing today?  Liz Ryan of the Human Workplace compares business to theatre. http://lnkd.in/buBemac     
    
    
    What role are you playing today?  Liz Ryan compares business with theatre.  Business with a Human Voice | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130920002956-52594-business-with-a-human-voice …    
    
    
    Happy Unification Day to @NathanFillion and all the rest of you browncoats out there.  Stay shiny, you #bigdamnheroes    
    
    
    @KonniBurton @PollySpin @YoungCons For the Win!    
    
    
    @ellethomas48 Ghostbusters?    
    
    
    @humanworkplace I absolutely love your articles, Liz.  "A typical job ad is a key-encrusted spit in the wind."  Priceless.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ellethomas48 I always confuse those two.    
    
    
    If you want to work on IT Support projects in the New York Metro area, message me!  Flexible hours.    
    
    
    Fight the stuff.  Fear the thangs... pic.twitter.com/Z0faTLpyzW    
    
    
    The Great Gatsby: classic story of love, hope, excess, and despair, or just a bunch of petulant skunk cabbage?    
    
    
    Tip to job seekers:  Being persistant and being annoying are not the same thing. If you submit your resume 35 times in three days for the s…    
    
    
    @operabcast "Musik ist eine heilige Kunst."    
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    Networking: what's all the buzz about? - The Human Workplace http://blogs.denverpost.com/work/2013/09/11/networking-whats-all-the-buzz-about/1222/ … via @denverpost    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    Shocked!  Shocked am I!  Weird Man Begins Every Morning By Dousing His Naked Body In Water http://onion.com/1a4i9A6  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    From @humanworkplace: Job Search AFTER FIFTY, or Hope for the Bushwhacked Generation | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130804170446-52594-job-search-after-fifty …    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    @SonshineMusic @WalkingDead_AMC Oh, Carol.  What have you done, girl?    
    
    
    @guarnaschelli Come back to us, Carol.    
    
    
    @guarnaschelli Nice win on ICA for you and GZ yesterday.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/rjg10e5y     
    
    
    @SonshineMusic  Ack!!!!!    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    Are you right-brained or left-brained?  I'm ambi-branious. http://sommer-sommer.com/braintest?token=11c67f0df972e8fddfbe3a3467d9450981775203 …    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Customer Engineer II 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/2dgalq6p     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Build/service Request Specialist 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ped0t1re     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    @SonshineMusic  I know, right?    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Build/service Request Specialist 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ped0t1re     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
        
    
    
    1496 words so far for NaNoWriMo, so I'm way behind.  On the plus side, my main character almost got run over by a deer.    
    
    
    My #NaNoWriMo pacesetter animal. pic.twitter.com/ksChfZIUMV    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ExpSelf  Thanks!    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    I almost doubled my total from yesterday morning, so instead of two days off the pace, I'm now only...4? Math is fun! pic.twitter.com/Iz3Uwd7kqJ    
    
    
    @whedonesque  Everything will be fine now.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    My book review...Booksellers Without Borders: Tarbabies, by Allen R. Brady http://www.booksellerswithoutbordersny.com/2013/11/tarbabies-by-allen-r-brady.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support - Dallas 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lkdt2mnp     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    @SCrass7 @PatDollard What do they DO at these "churches?"  I mean seriously.    
    
    
    Let's hear it for Team Herschel! #TWD    
    
    
    Looking forward to Spaghetti Tuesday this Wednesday!
#teamherschel #TheWalkingDead    
    
    
    Don't hold your breath.   @JohnFromCranber    
    
    
    @JohnFromCranber Not even if Hilary Clinton tied them to a chair and Obama sawed their legs off.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
        
    
    
    @Redeemed1952  always.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    Good article by Krewe Maynard.  Obamacare != Healthcare | Liberty's Torch http://libertystorch.net/2013/11/obamacare-healthcare/ …    
    
    
    @lemaniesunshine @NaNoWriMo Well, even if you're not going to be able to do it this month, keep at it and finish it when you can.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ayvwk3av     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xk4xqw5f     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Desktop Support 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/syqctk4r     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    @PeterAlexander @gretawire Probably an Amazon drone.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
        
    
    
    @NaughtyBeyotch  because SO many Muslims watch Duck Dynasty. The network was grabbing at straws.    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: IT Support #002 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/crpue3hi     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Help Desk 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/xihdywaj     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Asset Coordinator 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ksscjxtz     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
        
    
    
    Design Strategy is hiring: IT Support Projects 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/e5ucgeik     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Asset Coordinator 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ksscjxtz     
    
    
    Probably not a strong OSHA presence in the factory... pic.twitter.com/kvYAGSUR5W    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Toner Technician - Chicago 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/1yhtjjge     
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Toner Technician - Chicago 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/1yhtjjge     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Toner Technician - Chicago 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/1yhtjjge     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Toner Technician - Chicago 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/1yhtjjge     
    
    
        
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Asset Coordinator 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ksscjxtz     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Toner Technician - Chicago 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/1yhtjjge     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: PC Hardware/software Support - Financial District 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/lveclbrr     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Tampa PC Moves 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/yzdgnk7n     
    
    
    Fun with dogs....
An Old Dog Can Teach You a Few New Tricks http://bassoforhire.blogspot.com/2013/12/an-old-dog-can-teach-you-few-new-tricks.html …    
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Tampa PC Moves 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/yzdgnk7n     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Tampa PC Moves 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/yzdgnk7n     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Tampa PC Moves 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/yzdgnk7n     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Asset Coordinator 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/ksscjxtz     
    
    
    DSC is hiring: Tampa PC Moves 
 http://talentdesk.com/s/yzdgnk7n     
    
    
    