Getting ready for #AOM2011 (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting) http://4sq.com/o5iht8    
    
    
    I love sessions with terms like MOO, MUD, MUSH and MUVE! Sitting in on #AOM2011 Second Life session at Grand Hyatt Bonham B    
    
    
    Loving #AOM2011 (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting w/ @aimeedars) http://4sq.com/oly6mz     
    
    
    I'm at Luke - A Chef John Besh Restaurant (125 E. Houston St., Soledad, San Antonio) http://4sq.com/pzfNSs     
    
    
    Thanks to everyone for a great #AOM2011 - looking forward to the closing reception 2nite (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting) http://4sq.com/nBNDdF     
    
    
    So long San Antonio and #AOM2011 (@ San Antonio International Airport (SAT) w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/rrFTDd     
    
    
    Half way home... (@ Charlotte Douglas International Airport (CLT) w/ 51 others) http://4sq.com/mZXRpT     
    
    
    Ahhhh VACATION (@ Albany International Airport (ALB) w/ 7 others) http://4sq.com/ncrakw     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/rdb5V6     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Newbie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/eSuKUq    
    
    
    Added AOM to the list (@ Academy of Management) http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    I'm at Stop and shop (Dobbs Ferry). http://4sq.com/f8A1bb    
    
    
    I just ousted Brett H. as the mayor of Town of Queensbury on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aULcTa     
    
    
    I just ousted Andrea L. as the mayor of Splashwater Kingdom on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/crqpOf     
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Academy of Management on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management (235 Elm Road, Briarcliff Manor). http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    Pls ignore any excessive tweets. Getting ready to improve my community knowledge at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Great topic! Sue from @AOMconnect. LinkedIn is one of our very active places. Looking forward to tips today at  #nptalk    
    
    
    We have a group and a company page started. The group rocks - very active. Find the co pg gets volunteers listing their roles as job #nptalk    
    
    
    @amy_stephan Academy of Management aom.org linkd.in/aomconnect - membership association, so our goal is engagement, not fundraising #nptalk    
    
    
    It's a closed group, but if you request to join, I'll let ya in :) #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope approved :) #nptalk    
    
    
    Oh - group tip - make use of the feature to send an auto message when requesting to join and getting approved.  #nptalk    
    
    
    Yes! top support RT @freefuturesorg: A2: Get as many staff, board members, etc to link their profile to official company page #nptalk    
    
    
    A2: At first, goal was # of members joining group, but now it's level of new posts/comments,etc. Still keep an eye on numbers too. #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope I seed discussions only when we have something to promote or got awesome press on a topic. Sometime facilitate others  #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope Mostly keep an eye on what discussions happen, remove inappropriate, connect people when appropriate #nptalk    
    
    
    @BANKONRAIN Hmmm, it kind of scares me that you think I'm an expert :) Will share what I can though! #nptalk    
    
    
    I needed to remind staff to connect their LI profile to the company pg - was tough and don't have full buy in. Focus on contribution #nptalk    
    
    
    BOG and notables aren't really in this space, so I try to foster the people who use the medium as a way to bring up new leaders #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 Goals on a personal LI pg are more difficult for SM folks. It becomes very intertwined with your company goals. #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 If you want to play a numbers game, I see lots of groups with posts about welcoming connection requests. I try to select value.  #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 - more a Q, but Google+ may quickly change the landscape for LI once they allow business pages. #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 Keyword optimization is, well, key. But review periodically as algorithms change often.  #nptalk    
    
    
    A4 Time spent will vary on time of yr and how much you need to nudge posts. I check in daily (5 min) and may comment weekly (1-2 hr) #nptalk    
    
    
    A4 All SM has such dangerous rabbitholes - you start reading too much and you just wasted half the day. I struggle to stay focused. #nptalk    
    
    
    A5 I have, but it's hard to make it relate. I've found a couple great folks in my world to connect with and ask questions personally #nptalk    
    
    
    @SocialNicole With the Answers, it seems more corporate level. idk maybe just me.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Gotta run, thanks for the tips...  #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone going to SMX NY next week? I'll be there Wed/Thurs if anyone is around :)    
    
    
    Looking for "green" tips in operations and management...how green are you?    
    
    
    Ghosts and goblins are already assembling for a #monsterhouseparty - glad those are my main peeps :)    
    
    
    Love the #smx feed - everything from tips and quotes to rivalry and throw downs :) Heading down tomorrow and Thursday.    
    
    
    Gotta remember to add #assnchat to my calendar. Keep forgetting,  then just stumbling upon it when there is a great topic - like volunteers    
    
    
    I'm at Dobbs ferry lutheran (43 ashford ave, Dobbs Ferry). http://4sq.com/fPpQMT    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Local" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/h3SwLW    
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management (235 Elm Road, Tuttle Road, Briarcliff Manor). http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    Ignore excessive tweets. But join the conversation about Building Influencer Programs at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Sue here, doing all things social/community for member academic non-profit. Been a while, so glad to be here!
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Rolling out a very light recognition system, just online notation based on usage. Would love insights on more and the results. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Moving on from a great topic at #cmgrchat and now checking in at   #nptalk    
    
    
    Yeah! RT @NPtalk: Todays topic is International Communications...we are lucky to have a special guest @AmyRSWard as a guest... #nptalk    
    
    
    A1: Hmm, kinda NEED to. We have an widely diverse membership and must be in touch everywhere. #nptalk    
    
    
    A true challenge. RT @thomscotch: A1 - Rather than international communication, wed better wonder about multilingual communications #nptalk    
    
    
    @freefuturesorg @NPtalk That one's been around a while. It has some great stuff though.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    I use translate.google all the time within the online spaces to keep pace. We need a language plan, though. #nptalk    
    
    
    :) RT @begerrit: wir koennen auch auf deutsch tweeten ;)! #nptalk    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1Ceid    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1Cet8    
    
    
    What is necessary for business success? http://ow.ly/1zhyD    
    
    
    Sorry, folks. Bear with me while I get some things sync-ed up.    
    
    
    I'm helping a fundraiser for my son's Sunday School. Shop great Avon products now through Oct 30 to help! Thanks!  http://soc.li/c8fG4xB     
    
    
    AMJ Award winning article. http://ht.ly/1ELBh    
    
    
    Award for AMJ LI http://ht.ly/1ELVs    
    
    
    AMR award winning article. FB http://ht.ly/1Fa35    
    
    
    AMR article http://ht.ly/1Fa44 LI    
    
    
    Picking up hubby - maybe he's fixed now. (@ Westchester Medical Center) http://4sq.com/7Njf6v    
    
    
    Sorry for an excessive posting, but joinin chat today about G+ at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Sue - social media peep for membership non-profit. Looking forward to this as I just set up our page yesterday :)  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @evanhamilton @sue_anne Ha! I'm flexible. I can go by "Ques" too. Us NP peeps roll with it like that.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A1. Already did. We've already seen our members here. My SM philosophy is to reach people where they want to exist #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Hmm.. strategy? Do you build these as community in and of themselves, or direct/support your own THROUGH them? Just askin' #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @sue_anne @evanhamilton Aha! I win :) lol #cmgrchat    
    
    
    YES! RT @20andengaged: @JPedde @E_Heilmeier I think Google is already prioritizing +1 in search. Another reason I made a page #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A2) Nope. One (wo)man show, more or less. But it will be nice to have the additional access once available as a backup. No worries #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Pushups done. Just starting at member np to get 1st mkt plan done. Staff is a big focus for me. Thx for the article #nptalk    
    
    
    Challenge for me is I have leader by-in, but they don't participate. Claim no-time, but feel it's great for those "below" then #nptalk    
    
    
    And how do you get results? I've started in the big 3, but results are single digit. What about for those looking at numbers? #nptalk    
    
    
    @WendyRae Great! I just posted a twitter word cloud to the office bulletin board with the question of What words do you want here? #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone in membership np? How do you engage a membership you may not be a part of? ie: mine is all PhD and outside my field #nptalk    
    
    
    Sometimes the plan gets to deep and you have to cut it off and focus on shorter term plans. Agree? #nptalk    
    
    
    @RachelJeanMpls Im in the same boat. I just did sessions with staff to invite their feedback. Went over great w/ solid ideas. #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone do staff SM guide? @Socialnicole @RachelJeanMpls Put logo, sm icons on all communications including email signatures #nptalk #nptalk    
    
    
    What's the metric for success? Limited results when numbers are expected is a tough sell. #nptalk    
    
    
    Ask permission - sometimes. Don't suck at copy. Build and brag the relationships.  #nptalk    
    
    
    @SocialNicole something must have gotten lost. I'm not even sure what big 3 means :)    
    
    
    Cast your AOM Vote. http://ow.ly/1JDNJ fb    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1JEuQ li    
    
    
    at ses - i need a lighter laptop    
    
    
    I just ousted Heather S. as the mayor of Doubletree Hotel on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/a1Fg3v     
    
    
    AOM Meeting Program posted. http://ow.ly/1KNz3    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Dobbs Ferry Lutheran Church on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/fPpQMT    
    
    
    I just ousted Tara S. as the mayor of Great Escape Lodge & Indoor Waterpark on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cCI6J3     
    
    
    slurping soup after getting braces on today. ouch.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Century Club" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/sYFW5N     
    
    
    lots of research to start my first forum and blog - wish me luck.    
    
    
    @graywolf all the time! but every now a then, a plan does come together.    
    
    
    how do the same specs get quotes from 10-200k? Geesh.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Campus Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/rtwntn     
    
    
    Checkin out foursquare. Is this stalkers for dummies? Hmm, not convinced, but will roll with it.    
    
    
    Member research http://ow.ly/1QdiV    
    
    
    Part of staffing for sm is training existing staff on its use. That's where I am now.  #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm 1st mktg/sm role here. Some staff think they're experts while others think it's hooey. Doing a staff guide and training. #nptalk    
    
    
    @JeromeHarrison can share offline. Found some great tools and guides. #nptalk    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Hot Tamale" badge on @foursquare! ¡Ay, caramba! http://4sq.com/t6zL5Z     
    
    
    Never feel truly home until I've had my Mighty :) (@ Mighty Taco) http://4sq.com/tt1Raf     
    
    
    how is it this late? too much more to do today...    
    
    
    Call for papers listing http://ow.ly/1VegN    
    
    
    Deabting going to #SESNY this year. Maybe I will skip a year. Any leads on what's in the works? Need to focus on more non profit stuff.    
    
    
    For mobile, would be interested in those w exp at conferences/seminars in particular. #nptalk    
    
    
    Permission is a good topic in and of itself. We've ignored permission for too long bc we have dif rights as np #nptalk    
    
    
    @cjmoeller have you looked at things like foursquare to get marked? #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm looking more on the knowledge side and engagement during events #nptalk    
    
    
    @andystitt829 agree - and I think that's one of Nicole's points on collect the data now while you decide. #nptalk    
    
    
    The key is mobile is a PIECE of the puzzle, not the full picture. You can't go solely mobile - or soley anything. Diversity of msg. #nptalk    
    
    
    I think you can collect the data at any time. Ppl are used to be asked for a mobile # and permission. They can choose not to supply. #nptalk    
    
    
    Often, the action we need is to do something elsewhere - online, in person. Struggle with the call to action and ability to act. #nptalk    
    
    
    Too many appts. today. Sorry to be missing  #nptalk    
    
    
    Check out this @Stonyfield video about organics, it had me singing along! http://moocrew.stonyfield.com/challenges/videos/garys-rap/ …    
    
    
    I'm at Grand Central Terminal (87 E 42nd St, Park Ave, New York) w/ 39 others. http://4sq.com/ebAV8D    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/hFwLx7    
    
    
    "To Automate or Not Automate... Your Community." that is the question at today's  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Automation ain't all bad. I have fond memories of Rosy the Robot :)  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @SueOnTheWeb Yes - there is so much automation that goes on. Sometimes we forget because it's, well, automatic!  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Has anyone gone to the B2B marketing programs? How are they? Considering one.    
    
    
    it's amazing how just a couple contacts post so much that it entirely fills my page view.    
    
    
    No conference call for once today! Get to lurk a bit in at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @Scottk1964 We love following you too :)    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock Makes ya miss the good ol' days when our parents just had us sit on each other's lap in the car, eh?    
    
    
    was wondering if there is a css zengarden contest for twitter?    
    
    
    Planning my day for #SESNY tomorrow. Looking for lots of great updates and new info from my tweeps.    
    
    
    I'm at SES New York Conference & Expo (New York, NY) w/ 31 others http://4sq.com/GD0brd     
    
    
    by the time I get this trending report done, the trend will change. Whew.    
    
    
    What did you do with your freebie day off from GLM? We went to Disneyland! OK, well, Six Flags - couldn't get the flight out :)    
    
    
    On my nightstand: baby monitor, rocket toy, ear thermometer that never works, tissues, wipes, cat brush, Parents mag, herbal eye pillow    
    
    
    wondering if the picnic benches outside the office are too far from the wireless :)    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Adventurer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gMNVI7    
    
    
    Great day at #AOM2012 (@ AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA) http://4sq.com/Ox89af     
    
    
    Learning lots at #AOM2012 (@ AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/RxI2Oj     
    
    
    I'm at AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA (Boston, MA) http://4sq.com/NhJJ2u     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Trainspotter" badge on @foursquare for checking in at trains and subway stations! http://4sq.com/ONtsC3     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Flame Broiled” badge on @foursquare for checking in to burger joints! Cheeseburgers all around! http://4sq.com/Nq0Fbg     
    
    
    Actually had a week to join in #cmgrchat and it's off. But will try to make next week to hang with the SoMe folks at NASA. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Getting ready for #InformzUC (@ Westchester County Airport (HPN) w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/NXVaRo     
    
    
    Send Time Optimization hits the user at a time they are best able to respond = better CTR  #InformzUC    
    
    
    How is your member getting the information they need about you? Written word? Events? Know the vehicle to tailor the message.  #InformzUC    
    
    
    I'll be there with all my tech-guy's Qs :) @stkulp Come to my session on iMIS at 10:15. All the cool kids will be there #InformzUC    
    
    
    Blogging is a key source for outreach and giving members an outlet to share your message. Need to pull that out of my dream file. #InformzUC    
    
    
    Luv these. RT @Informz: Which #emailmarketing personality are you? #InformzUC #Iheartemailmarketing pic.twitter.com/BLPKYl8l #InformzUC    
    
    
    It’s ok to include notes on what type of content you would want to include when you get stuck and move on-keep the article moving #InformzUC    
    
    
    Do your members know how to use your social media accounts? Tell them! Learn what they want from you. Ask them!  #InformzUC    
    
    
    Thanks for a great #InformzUC (@ Chicago O'Hare International Airport (ORD) w/ 194 others) http://4sq.com/UTk3ga     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super User" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/fKD2GR    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Back to School badge on @foursquare for checking in back on campus! Time to party! Er, study. http://4sq.com/NGWQgI     
    
    
    Getting ready for a day at #SMX (@ Metro North - Hastings on Hudson Train Station) http://4sq.com/POQZ6z     
    
    
    Talking, Not Stalking! Tips for Effective Retargeting sans the Creep-Factor – #SMX http://bit.ly/PvDIP1  Always makes me pause. #smx    
    
    
    Love when technology is a barrier at a conference about technology :) #stuckbyaconcretewall #smx    
    
    
    Really must get back into my Google+ Too  much potential not to  #smx    
    
    
    Gifting... and retweeting as gifting. Interesting... #smx    
    
    
    I just ousted @eddiewilders as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    I just ousted @seanacrimmins as the mayor of Doubleday's Restaurant & Sports Bar on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cDE3Vv    
    
    
    Is "it just happens" really an answer? I need to remember that next time I find myself using that.    
    
    
    @jaymohr37 Great show tonite! Good 2 know you've been thru Dobbs b4. Will never have Greek the same.    
    
    
    Hi all! Sue w/ Academy of Management. Mktg/SM for member-based scholarly org. #nptalk    
    
    
    There's 2 things here: building a network and learning the industry from links posted. I need to lrn about the industry Im in #nptalk    
    
    
    My main role is online community mngr. As such, the relationship is key and learning to build engagement and engage conversation. #nptalk    
    
    
    I use linkedin groups more for professional development. I can find those w more knowledge to bounce ideas around.  #nptalk    
    
    
    @Socialnicole disagree that LI is static. The groups have tons of activity. And they're building their platform to include more #nptalk    
    
    
    those "looking" should get linkedin recommendations too. I quoted some in cover sheets on in my reference list 4 pre-screen approach #nptalk    
    
    
    Associations have their own communities and programs. I know ASAE has their own and a mentoring program #nptalk    
    
    
    When I was looking, I also started a blog on what I knew best to get more search ranking is employers did google me.  #nptalk    
    
    
    Think it's flavors.me #nptalk    
    
    
    meetup, tweetup, local business groups - find events and just go and speak - but do speak. #nptalk    
    
    
    Just checking out klout -used twittercounter and tweetstats mainly- is clout supposed to be individual or business w/ FB and LI? #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Big numbers are great, but how do you use them to direct your community? I only use when doing board presentations. #CmgrChat    
    
    
    And some of it has to do w your community - mine is a very focused population, so THEIR influence doesn't play as much as the 1:1 #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Rather focus on the community, but for jobs - no. I rarely use my personal (just for these chats), but active 4 my community face #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Very interested in mobile, but going to bail on ya this week - we're membership driven, so mobile giving doesn't hit the mark. #nptalk    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Manor on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/i48Lvl    
    
    
    Hootsuite v. Tweetdeck? Anyone? Been revisiting Hootsuite and kind of liking it. May switch back.    
    
    
    I'm the first in this role, so there were no expectations, but high hopes. But my role is widely mixed across many avenues #cmgrchat    
    
    
    As part of a membership nonprofit, getting members to talk to each other is highly important - ROI will grow for org to grow #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @JPedde I do try to set my own goals - and share any results with the staff as a baseline for ROI.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Is the majority of the $ from advertising in the cmty or from member growth/dues? #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Our cmty is service based, so more convo = success. Other areas, member sign up is metric, but many factors can lay claim #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Even nonprofits have goals (sometimes hidden) to see $ from sm. The measure for us is engaging membership=renew + attend mtgs #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Reports to the board are crucial. With NP board which changes each year, new goals may be expected. I have to set the bar. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I think the cmgr role is still emerging. We'll see more roles created. My boss is awesome and sees me directing a dept in 2 yrs. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Offline events will be key! I'm looking for a sponsor for tweetups or they don't happen. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Closed early for snow, but one more tweetchat to go! OK, so I get an hour off when it's all said and done. I'll take it. :)    
    
    
    Sue from @AOMConnect in the social media/marketing/cmty areas. Will listen in as long as I can today. #nptalk    
    
    
    Yes! Seen a lot recently. Haven't tried. RT @coien: #nptalk familiar with paper.li? Seen those "The _____ Daily" tweets? #nptalk    
    
    
    Been using Hootsuite, but am weighing it after their change to paid. Don't know if benefits are there for the cost for us. 
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Lurking a bit, but it's been a long time since I sat in on  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/idVi6c    
    
    
    Lurking today and checking out  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    What's cool? The topic of the day I'm joining in today at  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Ha! You can't be cool to 100% of the people 100% of the time  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Does every audience have a "cool" or to some groups is their "cool" in rejecting the concept? #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Bacon is cool. Hmm.. Kevin Bacon?  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    "Using Content to Build Community" (http://bit.ly/17SCxBT ) topic today at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Strategy. These guys crack me up at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I fall in the two week out strategy crew. Strategy becomes pie in the sky. Much needed.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Biggest challenge - good one. Managing a diverse global community within a narrow focus area of academia.  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    :) Sorry no speakers or video -- extremely low tech equip for high tech gig - following for a bit though!  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Are there any of nonprofit community folks? I find my (membership) nonprofit crew is much more difficult to engage.  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    The Anatomy of a Private Online Member Community [Infographic] http://info.socious.com/bid/65372/The-Anatomy-of-a-Private-Online-Member-Community-Infographic … via @SociousSoftware    
    
    
    Joining @HubSpot "Science of Email Marketing" #EmailSci Webinar #emailsci    
    
    
    Do you have best practices for the nonprofit world? Biggest struggle is complaint of too much em balanced w/ em as best method #emailsci    
    
    
    Love this guy's title as Social Media Scientist! #emailsci    
    
    
    Can't wait for the recording of the @hubspot webinar - too much to digest & completely against everything I thought about email #emailsci    
    
    
    Packed and ready for #AOM2013. App downloaded, schedule overbooked, slideshow in need of edits, ready to give Mickey a high five.    
    
    
    Must cool off here after sessions at #AOM2013 pic.twitter.com/hmgEKUBzes    
    
    
    Just became the mayor of #AOM2013 on @foursquare! Crown me! http://4sq.com/15QI4um  pic.twitter.com/vc6DkBCd6E    
    
    
    Must haves for #AOM2013 - blinged out badge, snorkel, umbrella, water. pic.twitter.com/MbIrTNU3fY    
    
    
    In Florida and just put on a fleece. Gotta love convention centers. Need to take a stroll outside to warm up.    
    
    
    We need to do a photo slideshow of #AOM2013 attendees with Mickey ears. #awesome Next year, photo booth!    
    
    
    We've been Goofy bombed. pic.twitter.com/ZIu66b7tX8    
    
    
    #AOM2013Farewell Gathering (@ Ariel's) http://4sq.com/18sOjVu     
    
    
    #AOM2013 Farewell Gathering (@ Ariel's) http://4sq.com/14uZysu     
    
    
    Sea world is still my favorite. pic.twitter.com/OMocBYaoZL    
    
    
    I'm at Orlando International Airport (MCO) - @mco (Orlando, FL) w/ 63 others http://4sq.com/1cSSJtO     
    
    
    I'm at Westchester County Airport (HPN) (White Plains, NY) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/14lDlOj     
    
    
    hmmm...realizing I haven't tweeted directly in 3 months. Wow. But I check FB daily. Guess you see where my loyalties lie.    
    
    
    I'm at Chuck E. Cheese's - @chuckecheese (Nanuet, NY) http://4sq.com/19YsnmG     
    
    
    I'm at Skateland Family Fun Center (Lockport, NY) http://4sq.com/17YMJ0P     
    
    
    I'm at @Arbys (Cortland, NY) http://4sq.com/16czE1q     
    
    
    Back to school, reading, writing, rithmatic. (@ Springhurst Elementary School) http://4sq.com/198lsWb     
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management - @aomconnect (Briarcliff Manor, NY) http://4sq.com/18sG8bx     
    
    
    Following along #cmgrhangout today, so excuse excessive social media geekdom. Even better - follow too and become one of us! :)    
    
    
    The power of hangouts is being quickly adopted regardless of skill or industry. It's easy to use and engaging. #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Whenever God closes a door, He opens a window. Boy, doesn't He know the cost of heating these days? Brrr...    
    
    
    Practical Tips for Managing Linkedin and Facebook (on Top of Everything Else) - Newsletters - Publ.. http://bit.ly/enbevf    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Barista" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gSVeVO    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Groupie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gYP77W    
    
    
    SEO is like fitness - a balanced approached with constant review and development #seosm    
    
    
    Are you "doing" social or "being" social - ppl will see the difference in the fake smile. #seosm    
    
    
    Social competition includes comparison before the decision and rating afterwards for more WOM #seosm    
    
    
    Do social ranking by socials rate in the ROI? to the C-Suite? tweetlevel, klout, etc? Or is it hooey?  #seosm    
    
    
    Do you think twice on the "Ides of March"?    
    
    
    I truly believe keep your friends close, enemies closer - but you can make use of them if you know their network, use strengths #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I find 1:1 doesn't work as ppl want a soapbox to stand on. Sometimes embrace them enough to let their trueness show #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Like the guest blog! RT @JPedde: Ah yes, but if you 1:1 give them soapbox options. Blog post perhaps? Work to create a survey?  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    went a lil bonkers, but I think its back tweetchat isok.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Yup, I do hope more get through ok. I'm pretty boring on this topic. Looking for good tips :)  #nptalk    
    
    
    Hi! Joining as best I can today. Sue w/ a scholarly member nonprofit. #nptalk    
    
    
    We will be beginning the process of a website design. What are good things to look for in an agency/artist? #nptalk    
    
    
    And there is a lot design research that can be considered as well. Eye patterns, use of stock v. own images, white space, copy etc #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm on the np side starting to look for a designer to add our membership personality. That's the key for us - reflect our members. #nptalk    
    
    
    And also to be clear to separate the function from the design and approach each independently as well as how they integrate
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Becoming an expert in global websites at  #sesny    
    
    
    Second session talking about eHow and Demand Media. For a "second-rate" content, getting a lot of SEO play.  #sesny    
    
    
    Inspired, confused, educated at #sesny    
    
    
    What the key at #sesny - video, engagement, relationships.    
    
    
    @storyspinner great tips - solos are tough #sesny    
    
    
    Great smile at #blekko booth :)    
    
    
    Likes are the new links :) #sesny    
    
    
    After #sesny see an ad for local organic (farmers market) - entirely new context    
    
    
    SES New York 2011 - Day 2 Coverage #SESNY http://blog.searchenginewatch.com/110323-165142     
    
    
    @jasonyormark Great job today at the FB presentation! Thanks for the insights    
    
    
    Love starting the day at#sesny with freebies! Thanks David!    
    
    
    Content turns browsers into buyers - #sesny    
    
    
    Hubby is being scheduled for his 3rd surgery for rotator cuff - losing hope for him to ever work in his field again. :(    
    
    
    TV - lean back experience; Computer - lean forward; mobile - stand up - more likely to action #sesny    
    
    
    So the "master tools" session should now be renamed "My baby is ugly" #sesny @tim_ash    
    
    
    Key takeaway - avoid slice and dice optimization - its putting lipstick on a pig #sesny    
    
    
    @thegrok great presentation - thanks for goodies!    
    
    
    Serve your customer as a raving fan to promote a favorable review #sesny    
    
    
    Last session at #sesny decided to try out site clinic - maybe some final inspiration    
    
    
    Revisiting my library. Is it geeky or cool that half of the SEO, analytics and branding books I own are autographed?    
    
    
    @SESConf Thanks for listing me in the NY list of attendeees, but more useful to use @susieques than @AOMConnect    
    
    
    According to @Klout, @susieques's Klout score is 28 and climbing.  How influential are you?  http://bit.ly/hhvZym    
    
    
    Analytics. I don't focus enough time on learning the tools to truly make analytics for the community stronger. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @tmonhollon Ah yes, I printed your daily dozen. Weeks ago. It's on my to-do list too :) #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Everyone is talking +1 so Twitters getting tied up... maybe slow go today
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Off topic, anyone here attend #sesny as well? #nptalk    
    
    
    OK, never official said hello to my np tweet. So, hi! Sue from @aomconnect
#nptalk    
    
    
    Generational communications talk on  #nptalk    
    
    
    I think I will passively listen, as we have a limited span. Main group is 40-65; dif purposed to dif generations #nptalk    
    
    
    done @storyspinner if you haven't already would you mind answering @LiBeckIM's question on FB? http://on.fb.me/h1CrVc    
    
    
    my fav so far... @graywolf I'll gladly pay you tuesday for +1 today    
    
    
    I entered the @RoadID Giveaway to win a @TrekTravel trip to the Tour de France and more. http://bit.ly/h0c5IK    
    
    
    cleaning up the ol' resume. time to plunge fully in the world of SEO! Who's hiring?    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    Great meeting people around Westchester as interested in SEO as I am. Keep sending recommendations! This is great stuff!    
    
    
    I just ousted Ed T. as the mayor of Gould Park on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/9I8alp    
    
    
    1 person team - though all staff has taken some part of the role to heart - sometimes it's rolling that back in that's the key
 #nptalk    
    
    
    @aokolue Hmm... and I find the eNew/blasts is what ppl all have a hand in - even when they shouldn't
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Agreed - deadlines - even/especially self imposed. I let too much slack bcuz it isn't priority, then the "to-do" just grows #nptalk    
    
    
    Preparing my schedule for #MMCCon tomorrow. Looking forward to some great discussions!    
    
    
    Bear with messages the next couple of days. In DC talking marketing, membership and communication at   #mmccon    
    
    
    Accidental view - great image!  Good reinforcement that things are not as they seem #mmccon    
    
    
    We have it on record where men look at a cocktail party - make them wear eye trackers - lmao!  #mmccon    
    
    
    Did u see the gorilla in the room? Love this one...  #mmccon    
    
    
    OK, ok you got me on the other changes... we truly don't notice the obvious when we are too occupied with the challenge at hand.  #mmccon    
    
    
    "We can't multitask" as I listen, watch, tweet, notetake, etc...  #mmccon    
    
    
    We make assumptions about our world. Don’t take in what is really happening. Scary we make choices on assumptions, not reality.  #mmccon    
    
    
    The curse of knowledge – we think others see what we see. We think others know what we know.  #mmccon    
    
    
    AWESOME opening session. Thank you!   #mmccon    
    
    
    Sacred zombie cows are sacred vows that have lost their worshipers.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Prerequisite for change is to edit out the crap. Then you can move on and innovate.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombie spotting: low or decreasing profit, declining participation, no one admits to owning it, no excitement, no one hates it lg1 #mmccon    
    
    
    @theharringtonco Would be facinated to hear your plans on QR. Sooo love the concept, but haven't implemented.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Best practice for Boards is to have a conversation about what we should STOP doing and not just what to do more of. lg 1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Love it! RT @ridnow: "I havent Failed. Ive Just found 10k ways that wont work." Thanks, Edison... #mmccon    
    
    
    Much of what we call management consists of making it difficult for people to get their work done. – Peter Drucker #mmccon    
    
    
    Is the zombie cow just a big scarey cardboard sheet that can be blown over, but needs someone to step up to puff… lg1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombies are creepy. Glad to know I have the magic slaying tools to stop them :)  #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombie killing: just stop it; make the case; merge with something else; give it away; use a good crisis lg 1 #mmccon    
    
    
    What happens when you get bit by a zombie? You become one! Don’t let your sacred zombie cows bite you! #rabbithole #mmccon    
    
    
    Have to admit - a lot more tweeps here than I thought! Thanks to all for updates on sessions I'm not in - awesome!  #mmccon    
    
    
    Woot! Truffles as prizes for participation in lc3. Any switchers?  #mmccon    
    
    
    Breadth of media channels gives opportunities for message distribution and outreach to new audiences.  lc3
 #mmccon    
    
    
    @ElizabethB Haven't used DM in a while - but reconsidering postcard reminders. Just need ammo/stats to get budget. #mmccon    
    
    
    Email and direct mail are like peanut butter and jelly lc3 #mmccon    
    
    
    @Heleeene mmcc #mmccon    
    
    
    Ahhh! Need a power cord. May have to run back to hotel to grab it. Anyone have one to share in Comm Strat next? #mmccon    
    
    
    Photos on websites need to demonstrate interaction, not talking heads. Need to tell a story relevant to the content on the page lc3 #mmccon    
    
    
    @ChatterBachs Thanks - standard dell laptop #mmccon    
    
    
    @ChatterBachs thanks anyway. Its a quick walk. Back for tweetup    
    
    
    Hmm, interesting mobile stats on expedential growth, but is there a cross ref to age/interest groups? ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Wow idea - major mtg dues incr, but got an itouch which was sponsored, and included assn app. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    These aren’t “online cities” or “megaolopises” – “community” needs to keep the closeness and connection of every voice matters. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Don’t open the community floodgates all at once. Prospective community participants won’t be able to follow along successfully. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    When launching a social network, don’t tell them it’s a social network – use the tools and terminology that will engage your members #mmccon    
    
    
    Who here manages online communities for their assn? Would love to connect and share war stories.  #mmccon    
    
    
    A brand is a promise you make and keep every day #MMCCon    
    
    
    @BillWalker7 the pen makes my hand hurts :)    
    
    
    Should have worn Groundswell green today to show support :)  #mmccon    
    
    
    HERO – Highly empowered and resourceful operative #mmccon    
    
    
    Four technologies empower customers: smart mobile devices; social technology; cloud computing; pervasive video  #mmccon    
    
    
    IDEA; identify mass influencers; deliver groundswell customer service; empower with mobile information; amplify your fan activity. #mmccon    
    
    
    Treat your volunteers like royalty to encourage further loyalty #mmccon    
    
    
    In our membership of 19,000, I track 200 active twitter and 30 active linkedin users. #mmccon    
    
    
    @johnYSchen I made a list in twitter of members. Check followers against db. Also collected profile to incl twitter Monthly db check #mmccon    
    
    
    Oh really, you just quoted star trek. I just lost a little respect :) #mmccon    
    
    
    Me too! We need a tweep table for discussion group :) RT @maddiegrant: In session about multi-modal campaigns. #mmccon    
    
    
    a while at first, but not long for maintenance. @johnYSchen I tried doing that...was taking me forever. How long did that take you? #mmccon    
    
    
    Then look to the left to find it... RT @lmasri: I get the desire to gather mkting intel, but why 4 step login 2get @jbernoff slides #mmccon    
    
    
    The most retweetable time for @aomconnect is 10AM on Monday (EST).  #mmccon    
    
    
    love it! RT @G_J_W: Ask members or conf attendees to create "unofficial" insider tips re: travel, wifi hotspots lj1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Hi Phil! Nice to meet ya :) lf4 #mmccon    
    
    
    I love ppl that refer to it as "The Twitter" #MMCCon    
    
    
    @laurenhefner Laptop until battery died :) sb cool picm #MMCCon lf4    
    
    
    Yes there is a chocolate council #MMCCon lf4    
    
    
    I'm at Stuck on the runway at DCA (Arlington) http://4sq.com/kfNMQT    
    
    
    Had to turn on Pandora. Too quiet in the office today without the chatter from tweeps at  #mmccon    
    
    
    Oh what a sad day. #LI put Sarah Palin in my "recommended connections" - oh LinkedIn, I thought we understood each other! Alas!    
    
    
    Very cool! Going to be doing a Fresh Wave house party! Awesome goodies coming! Who's coming? @HousePartyFun @fresh_wave    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    Great topic! Sue from @aomconnect Lots of possiblities, but it is defining the WHY! #nptalk    
    
    
    Looks like I missed something good at #cmmeetup - count me in next time.    
    
    
    @ritasofelmsford Thanks for the follow! You guys are THE best! Planning on seeing you tomorrow! Yippee!    
    
    
    I just ousted @michaelblatter as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Photogenic" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/msDSY8    
    
    
    Hmmm, 2 interviews this week and my best suits are at the cleaners. At least I have back ups.    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    A day of "rest" while daycare is closed after a week at Search Engine Strategies.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock You actually look at calories there? I did once. Ruined the experience. I feel obligated to order kids meals now.    
    
    
    only 143 new projects in my inbox. 102 of them from my "brilliant idea" to include logos in listings. Note to self: no more brilliant ideas.    
    
    
    one conference call to go and I'm done for the day! Hoorray! And then to buy a bday gift for family party tonight.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock mine throws a tantrum when it breaks off and won't stay on again. gotta make banana glue.the peel makes a great hat    
    
    
    setting tons of google gagets. going a little nuts now that I got approval    
    
    
    lovin chai    
    
    
    cold medicine wearing off. fading fast. thank God MIL is taking the boy tonight!    
    
    
    why are people facinated with the back button. u don't need it. Geesh.    
    
    
    My so has decided I am "da" - which has been the case for a while, but now that my hubby is "ma." Now I know he's screwing with us.    
    
    
    Totally addicted to Tagalongs.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: sure beats my pasta with meat sauce and tagalongs    
    
    
    @sitelogic: with the wind in nyc today, I have a nice fro to join in!    
    
    
    getting old - had to switch to big fonts setting today. ugh    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: but the rain is clearing, so hopefully on your way soon.    
    
    
    It took me 2 weeks to catch up from 4 days out of the office. Can't go anywhere.    
    
    
    realizing I only like cold green tea. My hot tea is gross. Have to go get my chai    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: yes,  but acknowledging addiction is the first step to recovery.    
    
    
    ok, I think WW is out the window today. 3 thin mints and 2 tags along after Taco Bell. Blah.    
    
    
    Planning for SES. What's new this year?    
    
    
    Why do people feel they must email projects 3 times and call me twice within an hour. Ugh.    
    
    
    My cat is 17lbs. Vet now has her on the Atkins plan. My cat. On Atkins. Doh.    
    
    
    Reading: "How to Develop a Content Strategy Process"( http://twitthis.com/7tbki9 )    
    
    
    Hubby's waiting at airport for cousin to arrive and has Tracy Morgan sit down next to him. All hubby says is "when you going back on Howard"    
    
    
    about 20 police cars just decended on the street just below my office. gotta see what happened.    
    
    
    @cordialcricket Nice meeting you at the Retailer Forum booth at #NYIGF. Thanks for stopping by!    
    
    
    Excuse the next hour of tweets. But feel free to join the party! Logging in to  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Comm mgt has evolved from a tech role and spewing msgs to a mktg role of listening and engaging #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Many roles touch cmm mgt. For years, I had a title of Web Mngr which mean from domain, srvr to copywriting, design. More roles now #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Excuse the flurry of msgs. Following along today on  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    How many host their own community? What benefits/push back do you get?
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Kickin' job search for SEO, community building and e-marketing into high gear. Visit http://www.susanfernandez.info for overview.    
    
    
    I'm trying @RowFeeder to track tweets and facebook posts. Sign up and we both get 250 bonus posts: http://s.rowfeeder.com/a89bd0e4camjm-t     
    
    
    What are great tools to show reach and connections in graphs, charts, etc - something cool for the board? rowfeeder/trendistic/tweetreach ??    
    
    
    Great! Planning my first now! @KellyLux Join #CMGRchat today for *IRL Meetups of Online Communities* 2pm EST. See you there!    
    
    
    @deirdrereid You're the best!    
    
    
    Excuse excessive tweeting. Joining #CMGRchat today for *IRL Meetups of Online Communities*    
    
    
    We have one Annual Meeting each yr - last yr some tweeps asked to do one and sent out an informal date/time but bombed. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Next month we're doing our first official event - praying it goes well. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A2: I'm going to try social-ite awards and hand out $5 giftcards by recognizing those I see active in each space
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    love it RT @savvysarahjane: @cmgrchat A2) I like when meetups are like an oreo: mingle time | presentation/activity | mingle time #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Hmm, need more info on this Twizzo thing - nothing worthwhile came up googling it #cmgrchat    
    
    
    We have pushback on our own community because it's one more thing to do/remember. LinkedIn is best with our membership assn
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Checking in today at  #nptalk    
    
    
    Many co hire someone not knowing what to expect. How should we (the ones filling the roles) set the co expectations? #nptalk    
    
    
    I just ousted @michaelblatter as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    What tools are used for this? I'm doing my first multiple person blog as a live blog for a conference. Using WordPress. #nptalk    
    
    
    @wildwomanfund Thanks. Nice - you'll have to stop in and say hi when you visit :) #nptalk    
    
    
    #FF @wildwomanfund @DigitalKaitlyn @smallchangefund @SocialNicole via http://followfriday.com    
    
    
    @DigitalKaitlyn Thanks for the input on Tweetdeck. Did my first experiments. Great w/ Twitter; Failed on FB & LI    
    
    
    Getting ready for #AOM2011 (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting) http://4sq.com/o5iht8    
    
    
    I love sessions with terms like MOO, MUD, MUSH and MUVE! Sitting in on #AOM2011 Second Life session at Grand Hyatt Bonham B    
    
    
    Loving #AOM2011 (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting w/ @aimeedars) http://4sq.com/oly6mz     
    
    
    I'm at Luke - A Chef John Besh Restaurant (125 E. Houston St., Soledad, San Antonio) http://4sq.com/pzfNSs     
    
    
    Thanks to everyone for a great #AOM2011 - looking forward to the closing reception 2nite (@ AOM 2011 Annual Meeting) http://4sq.com/nBNDdF     
    
    
    So long San Antonio and #AOM2011 (@ San Antonio International Airport (SAT) w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/rrFTDd     
    
    
    Half way home... (@ Charlotte Douglas International Airport (CLT) w/ 51 others) http://4sq.com/mZXRpT     
    
    
    Ahhhh VACATION (@ Albany International Airport (ALB) w/ 7 others) http://4sq.com/ncrakw     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "JetSetter" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/rdb5V6     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Newbie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/eSuKUq    
    
    
    Added AOM to the list (@ Academy of Management) http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    I'm at Stop and shop (Dobbs Ferry). http://4sq.com/f8A1bb    
    
    
    I just ousted Brett H. as the mayor of Town of Queensbury on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/aULcTa     
    
    
    I just ousted Andrea L. as the mayor of Splashwater Kingdom on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/crqpOf     
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Academy of Management on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management (235 Elm Road, Briarcliff Manor). http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    Pls ignore any excessive tweets. Getting ready to improve my community knowledge at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Great topic! Sue from @AOMconnect. LinkedIn is one of our very active places. Looking forward to tips today at  #nptalk    
    
    
    We have a group and a company page started. The group rocks - very active. Find the co pg gets volunteers listing their roles as job #nptalk    
    
    
    @amy_stephan Academy of Management aom.org linkd.in/aomconnect - membership association, so our goal is engagement, not fundraising #nptalk    
    
    
    It's a closed group, but if you request to join, I'll let ya in :) #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope approved :) #nptalk    
    
    
    Oh - group tip - make use of the feature to send an auto message when requesting to join and getting approved.  #nptalk    
    
    
    Yes! top support RT @freefuturesorg: A2: Get as many staff, board members, etc to link their profile to official company page #nptalk    
    
    
    A2: At first, goal was # of members joining group, but now it's level of new posts/comments,etc. Still keep an eye on numbers too. #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope I seed discussions only when we have something to promote or got awesome press on a topic. Sometime facilitate others  #nptalk    
    
    
    @digitalhope Mostly keep an eye on what discussions happen, remove inappropriate, connect people when appropriate #nptalk    
    
    
    @BANKONRAIN Hmmm, it kind of scares me that you think I'm an expert :) Will share what I can though! #nptalk    
    
    
    I needed to remind staff to connect their LI profile to the company pg - was tough and don't have full buy in. Focus on contribution #nptalk    
    
    
    BOG and notables aren't really in this space, so I try to foster the people who use the medium as a way to bring up new leaders #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 Goals on a personal LI pg are more difficult for SM folks. It becomes very intertwined with your company goals. #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 If you want to play a numbers game, I see lots of groups with posts about welcoming connection requests. I try to select value.  #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 - more a Q, but Google+ may quickly change the landscape for LI once they allow business pages. #nptalk    
    
    
    A3 Keyword optimization is, well, key. But review periodically as algorithms change often.  #nptalk    
    
    
    A4 Time spent will vary on time of yr and how much you need to nudge posts. I check in daily (5 min) and may comment weekly (1-2 hr) #nptalk    
    
    
    A4 All SM has such dangerous rabbitholes - you start reading too much and you just wasted half the day. I struggle to stay focused. #nptalk    
    
    
    A5 I have, but it's hard to make it relate. I've found a couple great folks in my world to connect with and ask questions personally #nptalk    
    
    
    @SocialNicole With the Answers, it seems more corporate level. idk maybe just me.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Gotta run, thanks for the tips...  #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone going to SMX NY next week? I'll be there Wed/Thurs if anyone is around :)    
    
    
    Looking for "green" tips in operations and management...how green are you?    
    
    
    Ghosts and goblins are already assembling for a #monsterhouseparty - glad those are my main peeps :)    
    
    
    Love the #smx feed - everything from tips and quotes to rivalry and throw downs :) Heading down tomorrow and Thursday.    
    
    
    Gotta remember to add #assnchat to my calendar. Keep forgetting,  then just stumbling upon it when there is a great topic - like volunteers    
    
    
    I'm at Dobbs ferry lutheran (43 ashford ave, Dobbs Ferry). http://4sq.com/fPpQMT    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Local" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/h3SwLW    
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management (235 Elm Road, Tuttle Road, Briarcliff Manor). http://4sq.com/ek0TxL    
    
    
    Ignore excessive tweets. But join the conversation about Building Influencer Programs at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Sue here, doing all things social/community for member academic non-profit. Been a while, so glad to be here!
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Rolling out a very light recognition system, just online notation based on usage. Would love insights on more and the results. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Moving on from a great topic at #cmgrchat and now checking in at   #nptalk    
    
    
    Yeah! RT @NPtalk: Todays topic is International Communications...we are lucky to have a special guest @AmyRSWard as a guest... #nptalk    
    
    
    A1: Hmm, kinda NEED to. We have an widely diverse membership and must be in touch everywhere. #nptalk    
    
    
    A true challenge. RT @thomscotch: A1 - Rather than international communication, wed better wonder about multilingual communications #nptalk    
    
    
    @freefuturesorg @NPtalk That one's been around a while. It has some great stuff though.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    I use translate.google all the time within the online spaces to keep pace. We need a language plan, though. #nptalk    
    
    
    :) RT @begerrit: wir koennen auch auf deutsch tweeten ;)! #nptalk    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1Ceid    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1Cet8    
    
    
    What is necessary for business success? http://ow.ly/1zhyD    
    
    
    Sorry, folks. Bear with me while I get some things sync-ed up.    
    
    
    I'm helping a fundraiser for my son's Sunday School. Shop great Avon products now through Oct 30 to help! Thanks!  http://soc.li/c8fG4xB     
    
    
    AMJ Award winning article. http://ht.ly/1ELBh    
    
    
    Award for AMJ LI http://ht.ly/1ELVs    
    
    
    AMR award winning article. FB http://ht.ly/1Fa35    
    
    
    AMR article http://ht.ly/1Fa44 LI    
    
    
    Picking up hubby - maybe he's fixed now. (@ Westchester Medical Center) http://4sq.com/7Njf6v    
    
    
    Sorry for an excessive posting, but joinin chat today about G+ at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Sue - social media peep for membership non-profit. Looking forward to this as I just set up our page yesterday :)  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @evanhamilton @sue_anne Ha! I'm flexible. I can go by "Ques" too. Us NP peeps roll with it like that.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A1. Already did. We've already seen our members here. My SM philosophy is to reach people where they want to exist #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Hmm.. strategy? Do you build these as community in and of themselves, or direct/support your own THROUGH them? Just askin' #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @sue_anne @evanhamilton Aha! I win :) lol #cmgrchat    
    
    
    YES! RT @20andengaged: @JPedde @E_Heilmeier I think Google is already prioritizing +1 in search. Another reason I made a page #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A2) Nope. One (wo)man show, more or less. But it will be nice to have the additional access once available as a backup. No worries #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Pushups done. Just starting at member np to get 1st mkt plan done. Staff is a big focus for me. Thx for the article #nptalk    
    
    
    Challenge for me is I have leader by-in, but they don't participate. Claim no-time, but feel it's great for those "below" then #nptalk    
    
    
    And how do you get results? I've started in the big 3, but results are single digit. What about for those looking at numbers? #nptalk    
    
    
    @WendyRae Great! I just posted a twitter word cloud to the office bulletin board with the question of What words do you want here? #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone in membership np? How do you engage a membership you may not be a part of? ie: mine is all PhD and outside my field #nptalk    
    
    
    Sometimes the plan gets to deep and you have to cut it off and focus on shorter term plans. Agree? #nptalk    
    
    
    @RachelJeanMpls Im in the same boat. I just did sessions with staff to invite their feedback. Went over great w/ solid ideas. #nptalk    
    
    
    Anyone do staff SM guide? @Socialnicole @RachelJeanMpls Put logo, sm icons on all communications including email signatures #nptalk #nptalk    
    
    
    What's the metric for success? Limited results when numbers are expected is a tough sell. #nptalk    
    
    
    Ask permission - sometimes. Don't suck at copy. Build and brag the relationships.  #nptalk    
    
    
    @SocialNicole something must have gotten lost. I'm not even sure what big 3 means :)    
    
    
    Cast your AOM Vote. http://ow.ly/1JDNJ fb    
    
    
    http://ow.ly/1JEuQ li    
    
    
    at ses - i need a lighter laptop    
    
    
    I just ousted Heather S. as the mayor of Doubletree Hotel on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/a1Fg3v     
    
    
    AOM Meeting Program posted. http://ow.ly/1KNz3    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Dobbs Ferry Lutheran Church on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/fPpQMT    
    
    
    I just ousted Tara S. as the mayor of Great Escape Lodge & Indoor Waterpark on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cCI6J3     
    
    
    slurping soup after getting braces on today. ouch.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Century Club" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/sYFW5N     
    
    
    lots of research to start my first forum and blog - wish me luck.    
    
    
    @graywolf all the time! but every now a then, a plan does come together.    
    
    
    how do the same specs get quotes from 10-200k? Geesh.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Campus Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/rtwntn     
    
    
    Checkin out foursquare. Is this stalkers for dummies? Hmm, not convinced, but will roll with it.    
    
    
    Member research http://ow.ly/1QdiV    
    
    
    Part of staffing for sm is training existing staff on its use. That's where I am now.  #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm 1st mktg/sm role here. Some staff think they're experts while others think it's hooey. Doing a staff guide and training. #nptalk    
    
    
    @JeromeHarrison can share offline. Found some great tools and guides. #nptalk    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Hot Tamale" badge on @foursquare! ¡Ay, caramba! http://4sq.com/t6zL5Z     
    
    
    Never feel truly home until I've had my Mighty :) (@ Mighty Taco) http://4sq.com/tt1Raf     
    
    
    how is it this late? too much more to do today...    
    
    
    Call for papers listing http://ow.ly/1VegN    
    
    
    Deabting going to #SESNY this year. Maybe I will skip a year. Any leads on what's in the works? Need to focus on more non profit stuff.    
    
    
    For mobile, would be interested in those w exp at conferences/seminars in particular. #nptalk    
    
    
    Permission is a good topic in and of itself. We've ignored permission for too long bc we have dif rights as np #nptalk    
    
    
    @cjmoeller have you looked at things like foursquare to get marked? #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm looking more on the knowledge side and engagement during events #nptalk    
    
    
    @andystitt829 agree - and I think that's one of Nicole's points on collect the data now while you decide. #nptalk    
    
    
    The key is mobile is a PIECE of the puzzle, not the full picture. You can't go solely mobile - or soley anything. Diversity of msg. #nptalk    
    
    
    I think you can collect the data at any time. Ppl are used to be asked for a mobile # and permission. They can choose not to supply. #nptalk    
    
    
    Often, the action we need is to do something elsewhere - online, in person. Struggle with the call to action and ability to act. #nptalk    
    
    
    Too many appts. today. Sorry to be missing  #nptalk    
    
    
    Check out this @Stonyfield video about organics, it had me singing along! http://moocrew.stonyfield.com/challenges/videos/garys-rap/ …    
    
    
    I'm at Grand Central Terminal (87 E 42nd St, Park Ave, New York) w/ 39 others. http://4sq.com/ebAV8D    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Swarm" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/hFwLx7    
    
    
    "To Automate or Not Automate... Your Community." that is the question at today's  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Automation ain't all bad. I have fond memories of Rosy the Robot :)  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @SueOnTheWeb Yes - there is so much automation that goes on. Sometimes we forget because it's, well, automatic!  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Has anyone gone to the B2B marketing programs? How are they? Considering one.    
    
    
    it's amazing how just a couple contacts post so much that it entirely fills my page view.    
    
    
    No conference call for once today! Get to lurk a bit in at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @Scottk1964 We love following you too :)    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock Makes ya miss the good ol' days when our parents just had us sit on each other's lap in the car, eh?    
    
    
    was wondering if there is a css zengarden contest for twitter?    
    
    
    Planning my day for #SESNY tomorrow. Looking for lots of great updates and new info from my tweeps.    
    
    
    I'm at SES New York Conference & Expo (New York, NY) w/ 31 others http://4sq.com/GD0brd     
    
    
    by the time I get this trending report done, the trend will change. Whew.    
    
    
    What did you do with your freebie day off from GLM? We went to Disneyland! OK, well, Six Flags - couldn't get the flight out :)    
    
    
    On my nightstand: baby monitor, rocket toy, ear thermometer that never works, tissues, wipes, cat brush, Parents mag, herbal eye pillow    
    
    
    wondering if the picnic benches outside the office are too far from the wireless :)    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Adventurer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gMNVI7    
    
    
    Great day at #AOM2012 (@ AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA) http://4sq.com/Ox89af     
    
    
    Learning lots at #AOM2012 (@ AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA w/ 2 others) http://4sq.com/RxI2Oj     
    
    
    I'm at AOM 2012 Annual Meeting - Boston, MA (Boston, MA) http://4sq.com/NhJJ2u     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Trainspotter" badge on @foursquare for checking in at trains and subway stations! http://4sq.com/ONtsC3     
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Flame Broiled” badge on @foursquare for checking in to burger joints! Cheeseburgers all around! http://4sq.com/Nq0Fbg     
    
    
    Actually had a week to join in #cmgrchat and it's off. But will try to make next week to hang with the SoMe folks at NASA. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Getting ready for #InformzUC (@ Westchester County Airport (HPN) w/ 6 others) http://4sq.com/NXVaRo     
    
    
    Send Time Optimization hits the user at a time they are best able to respond = better CTR  #InformzUC    
    
    
    How is your member getting the information they need about you? Written word? Events? Know the vehicle to tailor the message.  #InformzUC    
    
    
    I'll be there with all my tech-guy's Qs :) @stkulp Come to my session on iMIS at 10:15. All the cool kids will be there #InformzUC    
    
    
    Blogging is a key source for outreach and giving members an outlet to share your message. Need to pull that out of my dream file. #InformzUC    
    
    
    Luv these. RT @Informz: Which #emailmarketing personality are you? #InformzUC #Iheartemailmarketing pic.twitter.com/BLPKYl8l #InformzUC    
    
    
    It’s ok to include notes on what type of content you would want to include when you get stuck and move on-keep the article moving #InformzUC    
    
    
    Do your members know how to use your social media accounts? Tell them! Learn what they want from you. Ask them!  #InformzUC    
    
    
    Thanks for a great #InformzUC (@ Chicago O'Hare International Airport (ORD) w/ 194 others) http://4sq.com/UTk3ga     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Super User" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/fKD2GR    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Back to School badge on @foursquare for checking in back on campus! Time to party! Er, study. http://4sq.com/NGWQgI     
    
    
    Getting ready for a day at #SMX (@ Metro North - Hastings on Hudson Train Station) http://4sq.com/POQZ6z     
    
    
    Talking, Not Stalking! Tips for Effective Retargeting sans the Creep-Factor – #SMX http://bit.ly/PvDIP1  Always makes me pause. #smx    
    
    
    Love when technology is a barrier at a conference about technology :) #stuckbyaconcretewall #smx    
    
    
    Really must get back into my Google+ Too  much potential not to  #smx    
    
    
    Gifting... and retweeting as gifting. Interesting... #smx    
    
    
    I just ousted @eddiewilders as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    I just ousted @seanacrimmins as the mayor of Doubleday's Restaurant & Sports Bar on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/cDE3Vv    
    
    
    Is "it just happens" really an answer? I need to remember that next time I find myself using that.    
    
    
    @jaymohr37 Great show tonite! Good 2 know you've been thru Dobbs b4. Will never have Greek the same.    
    
    
    Hi all! Sue w/ Academy of Management. Mktg/SM for member-based scholarly org. #nptalk    
    
    
    There's 2 things here: building a network and learning the industry from links posted. I need to lrn about the industry Im in #nptalk    
    
    
    My main role is online community mngr. As such, the relationship is key and learning to build engagement and engage conversation. #nptalk    
    
    
    I use linkedin groups more for professional development. I can find those w more knowledge to bounce ideas around.  #nptalk    
    
    
    @Socialnicole disagree that LI is static. The groups have tons of activity. And they're building their platform to include more #nptalk    
    
    
    those "looking" should get linkedin recommendations too. I quoted some in cover sheets on in my reference list 4 pre-screen approach #nptalk    
    
    
    Associations have their own communities and programs. I know ASAE has their own and a mentoring program #nptalk    
    
    
    When I was looking, I also started a blog on what I knew best to get more search ranking is employers did google me.  #nptalk    
    
    
    Think it's flavors.me #nptalk    
    
    
    meetup, tweetup, local business groups - find events and just go and speak - but do speak. #nptalk    
    
    
    Just checking out klout -used twittercounter and tweetstats mainly- is clout supposed to be individual or business w/ FB and LI? #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Big numbers are great, but how do you use them to direct your community? I only use when doing board presentations. #CmgrChat    
    
    
    And some of it has to do w your community - mine is a very focused population, so THEIR influence doesn't play as much as the 1:1 #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Rather focus on the community, but for jobs - no. I rarely use my personal (just for these chats), but active 4 my community face #CmgrChat    
    
    
    Very interested in mobile, but going to bail on ya this week - we're membership driven, so mobile giving doesn't hit the mark. #nptalk    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Manor on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/i48Lvl    
    
    
    Hootsuite v. Tweetdeck? Anyone? Been revisiting Hootsuite and kind of liking it. May switch back.    
    
    
    I'm the first in this role, so there were no expectations, but high hopes. But my role is widely mixed across many avenues #cmgrchat    
    
    
    As part of a membership nonprofit, getting members to talk to each other is highly important - ROI will grow for org to grow #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @JPedde I do try to set my own goals - and share any results with the staff as a baseline for ROI.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Is the majority of the $ from advertising in the cmty or from member growth/dues? #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Our cmty is service based, so more convo = success. Other areas, member sign up is metric, but many factors can lay claim #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Even nonprofits have goals (sometimes hidden) to see $ from sm. The measure for us is engaging membership=renew + attend mtgs #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Reports to the board are crucial. With NP board which changes each year, new goals may be expected. I have to set the bar. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I think the cmgr role is still emerging. We'll see more roles created. My boss is awesome and sees me directing a dept in 2 yrs. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Offline events will be key! I'm looking for a sponsor for tweetups or they don't happen. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Closed early for snow, but one more tweetchat to go! OK, so I get an hour off when it's all said and done. I'll take it. :)    
    
    
    Sue from @AOMConnect in the social media/marketing/cmty areas. Will listen in as long as I can today. #nptalk    
    
    
    Yes! Seen a lot recently. Haven't tried. RT @coien: #nptalk familiar with paper.li? Seen those "The _____ Daily" tweets? #nptalk    
    
    
    Been using Hootsuite, but am weighing it after their change to paid. Don't know if benefits are there for the cost for us. 
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Lurking a bit, but it's been a long time since I sat in on  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Explorer" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/idVi6c    
    
    
    Lurking today and checking out  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    What's cool? The topic of the day I'm joining in today at  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Ha! You can't be cool to 100% of the people 100% of the time  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Does every audience have a "cool" or to some groups is their "cool" in rejecting the concept? #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Bacon is cool. Hmm.. Kevin Bacon?  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    "Using Content to Build Community" (http://bit.ly/17SCxBT ) topic today at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Strategy. These guys crack me up at  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I fall in the two week out strategy crew. Strategy becomes pie in the sky. Much needed.  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Biggest challenge - good one. Managing a diverse global community within a narrow focus area of academia.  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    :) Sorry no speakers or video -- extremely low tech equip for high tech gig - following for a bit though!  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Are there any of nonprofit community folks? I find my (membership) nonprofit crew is much more difficult to engage.  #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    The Anatomy of a Private Online Member Community [Infographic] http://info.socious.com/bid/65372/The-Anatomy-of-a-Private-Online-Member-Community-Infographic … via @SociousSoftware    
    
    
    Joining @HubSpot "Science of Email Marketing" #EmailSci Webinar #emailsci    
    
    
    Do you have best practices for the nonprofit world? Biggest struggle is complaint of too much em balanced w/ em as best method #emailsci    
    
    
    Love this guy's title as Social Media Scientist! #emailsci    
    
    
    Can't wait for the recording of the @hubspot webinar - too much to digest & completely against everything I thought about email #emailsci    
    
    
    Packed and ready for #AOM2013. App downloaded, schedule overbooked, slideshow in need of edits, ready to give Mickey a high five.    
    
    
    Must cool off here after sessions at #AOM2013 pic.twitter.com/hmgEKUBzes    
    
    
    Just became the mayor of #AOM2013 on @foursquare! Crown me! http://4sq.com/15QI4um  pic.twitter.com/vc6DkBCd6E    
    
    
    Must haves for #AOM2013 - blinged out badge, snorkel, umbrella, water. pic.twitter.com/MbIrTNU3fY    
    
    
    In Florida and just put on a fleece. Gotta love convention centers. Need to take a stroll outside to warm up.    
    
    
    We need to do a photo slideshow of #AOM2013 attendees with Mickey ears. #awesome Next year, photo booth!    
    
    
    We've been Goofy bombed. pic.twitter.com/ZIu66b7tX8    
    
    
    #AOM2013Farewell Gathering (@ Ariel's) http://4sq.com/18sOjVu     
    
    
    #AOM2013 Farewell Gathering (@ Ariel's) http://4sq.com/14uZysu     
    
    
    Sea world is still my favorite. pic.twitter.com/OMocBYaoZL    
    
    
    I'm at Orlando International Airport (MCO) - @mco (Orlando, FL) w/ 63 others http://4sq.com/1cSSJtO     
    
    
    I'm at Westchester County Airport (HPN) (White Plains, NY) w/ 5 others http://4sq.com/14lDlOj     
    
    
    hmmm...realizing I haven't tweeted directly in 3 months. Wow. But I check FB daily. Guess you see where my loyalties lie.    
    
    
    I'm at Chuck E. Cheese's - @chuckecheese (Nanuet, NY) http://4sq.com/19YsnmG     
    
    
    I'm at Skateland Family Fun Center (Lockport, NY) http://4sq.com/17YMJ0P     
    
    
    I'm at @Arbys (Cortland, NY) http://4sq.com/16czE1q     
    
    
    Back to school, reading, writing, rithmatic. (@ Springhurst Elementary School) http://4sq.com/198lsWb     
    
    
    I'm at Academy of Management - @aomconnect (Briarcliff Manor, NY) http://4sq.com/18sG8bx     
    
    
    Following along #cmgrhangout today, so excuse excessive social media geekdom. Even better - follow too and become one of us! :)    
    
    
    The power of hangouts is being quickly adopted regardless of skill or industry. It's easy to use and engaging. #cmgrhangout    
    
    
    Whenever God closes a door, He opens a window. Boy, doesn't He know the cost of heating these days? Brrr...    
    
    
    Practical Tips for Managing Linkedin and Facebook (on Top of Everything Else) - Newsletters - Publ.. http://bit.ly/enbevf    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Barista" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gSVeVO    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Groupie" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/gYP77W    
    
    
    SEO is like fitness - a balanced approached with constant review and development #seosm    
    
    
    Are you "doing" social or "being" social - ppl will see the difference in the fake smile. #seosm    
    
    
    Social competition includes comparison before the decision and rating afterwards for more WOM #seosm    
    
    
    Do social ranking by socials rate in the ROI? to the C-Suite? tweetlevel, klout, etc? Or is it hooey?  #seosm    
    
    
    Do you think twice on the "Ides of March"?    
    
    
    I truly believe keep your friends close, enemies closer - but you can make use of them if you know their network, use strengths #cmgrchat    
    
    
    I find 1:1 doesn't work as ppl want a soapbox to stand on. Sometimes embrace them enough to let their trueness show #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Like the guest blog! RT @JPedde: Ah yes, but if you 1:1 give them soapbox options. Blog post perhaps? Work to create a survey?  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    went a lil bonkers, but I think its back tweetchat isok.
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Yup, I do hope more get through ok. I'm pretty boring on this topic. Looking for good tips :)  #nptalk    
    
    
    Hi! Joining as best I can today. Sue w/ a scholarly member nonprofit. #nptalk    
    
    
    We will be beginning the process of a website design. What are good things to look for in an agency/artist? #nptalk    
    
    
    And there is a lot design research that can be considered as well. Eye patterns, use of stock v. own images, white space, copy etc #nptalk    
    
    
    I'm on the np side starting to look for a designer to add our membership personality. That's the key for us - reflect our members. #nptalk    
    
    
    And also to be clear to separate the function from the design and approach each independently as well as how they integrate
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Becoming an expert in global websites at  #sesny    
    
    
    Second session talking about eHow and Demand Media. For a "second-rate" content, getting a lot of SEO play.  #sesny    
    
    
    Inspired, confused, educated at #sesny    
    
    
    What the key at #sesny - video, engagement, relationships.    
    
    
    @storyspinner great tips - solos are tough #sesny    
    
    
    Great smile at #blekko booth :)    
    
    
    Likes are the new links :) #sesny    
    
    
    After #sesny see an ad for local organic (farmers market) - entirely new context    
    
    
    SES New York 2011 - Day 2 Coverage #SESNY http://blog.searchenginewatch.com/110323-165142     
    
    
    @jasonyormark Great job today at the FB presentation! Thanks for the insights    
    
    
    Love starting the day at#sesny with freebies! Thanks David!    
    
    
    Content turns browsers into buyers - #sesny    
    
    
    Hubby is being scheduled for his 3rd surgery for rotator cuff - losing hope for him to ever work in his field again. :(    
    
    
    TV - lean back experience; Computer - lean forward; mobile - stand up - more likely to action #sesny    
    
    
    So the "master tools" session should now be renamed "My baby is ugly" #sesny @tim_ash    
    
    
    Key takeaway - avoid slice and dice optimization - its putting lipstick on a pig #sesny    
    
    
    @thegrok great presentation - thanks for goodies!    
    
    
    Serve your customer as a raving fan to promote a favorable review #sesny    
    
    
    Last session at #sesny decided to try out site clinic - maybe some final inspiration    
    
    
    Revisiting my library. Is it geeky or cool that half of the SEO, analytics and branding books I own are autographed?    
    
    
    @SESConf Thanks for listing me in the NY list of attendeees, but more useful to use @susieques than @AOMConnect    
    
    
    According to @Klout, @susieques's Klout score is 28 and climbing.  How influential are you?  http://bit.ly/hhvZym    
    
    
    Analytics. I don't focus enough time on learning the tools to truly make analytics for the community stronger. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    @tmonhollon Ah yes, I printed your daily dozen. Weeks ago. It's on my to-do list too :) #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Everyone is talking +1 so Twitters getting tied up... maybe slow go today
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Off topic, anyone here attend #sesny as well? #nptalk    
    
    
    OK, never official said hello to my np tweet. So, hi! Sue from @aomconnect
#nptalk    
    
    
    Generational communications talk on  #nptalk    
    
    
    I think I will passively listen, as we have a limited span. Main group is 40-65; dif purposed to dif generations #nptalk    
    
    
    done @storyspinner if you haven't already would you mind answering @LiBeckIM's question on FB? http://on.fb.me/h1CrVc    
    
    
    my fav so far... @graywolf I'll gladly pay you tuesday for +1 today    
    
    
    I entered the @RoadID Giveaway to win a @TrekTravel trip to the Tour de France and more. http://bit.ly/h0c5IK    
    
    
    cleaning up the ol' resume. time to plunge fully in the world of SEO! Who's hiring?    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    Great meeting people around Westchester as interested in SEO as I am. Keep sending recommendations! This is great stuff!    
    
    
    I just ousted Ed T. as the mayor of Gould Park on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/9I8alp    
    
    
    1 person team - though all staff has taken some part of the role to heart - sometimes it's rolling that back in that's the key
 #nptalk    
    
    
    @aokolue Hmm... and I find the eNew/blasts is what ppl all have a hand in - even when they shouldn't
 #nptalk    
    
    
    Agreed - deadlines - even/especially self imposed. I let too much slack bcuz it isn't priority, then the "to-do" just grows #nptalk    
    
    
    Preparing my schedule for #MMCCon tomorrow. Looking forward to some great discussions!    
    
    
    Bear with messages the next couple of days. In DC talking marketing, membership and communication at   #mmccon    
    
    
    Accidental view - great image!  Good reinforcement that things are not as they seem #mmccon    
    
    
    We have it on record where men look at a cocktail party - make them wear eye trackers - lmao!  #mmccon    
    
    
    Did u see the gorilla in the room? Love this one...  #mmccon    
    
    
    OK, ok you got me on the other changes... we truly don't notice the obvious when we are too occupied with the challenge at hand.  #mmccon    
    
    
    "We can't multitask" as I listen, watch, tweet, notetake, etc...  #mmccon    
    
    
    We make assumptions about our world. Don’t take in what is really happening. Scary we make choices on assumptions, not reality.  #mmccon    
    
    
    The curse of knowledge – we think others see what we see. We think others know what we know.  #mmccon    
    
    
    AWESOME opening session. Thank you!   #mmccon    
    
    
    Sacred zombie cows are sacred vows that have lost their worshipers.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Prerequisite for change is to edit out the crap. Then you can move on and innovate.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombie spotting: low or decreasing profit, declining participation, no one admits to owning it, no excitement, no one hates it lg1 #mmccon    
    
    
    @theharringtonco Would be facinated to hear your plans on QR. Sooo love the concept, but haven't implemented.  #mmccon    
    
    
    Best practice for Boards is to have a conversation about what we should STOP doing and not just what to do more of. lg 1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Love it! RT @ridnow: "I havent Failed. Ive Just found 10k ways that wont work." Thanks, Edison... #mmccon    
    
    
    Much of what we call management consists of making it difficult for people to get their work done. – Peter Drucker #mmccon    
    
    
    Is the zombie cow just a big scarey cardboard sheet that can be blown over, but needs someone to step up to puff… lg1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombies are creepy. Glad to know I have the magic slaying tools to stop them :)  #mmccon    
    
    
    Zombie killing: just stop it; make the case; merge with something else; give it away; use a good crisis lg 1 #mmccon    
    
    
    What happens when you get bit by a zombie? You become one! Don’t let your sacred zombie cows bite you! #rabbithole #mmccon    
    
    
    Have to admit - a lot more tweeps here than I thought! Thanks to all for updates on sessions I'm not in - awesome!  #mmccon    
    
    
    Woot! Truffles as prizes for participation in lc3. Any switchers?  #mmccon    
    
    
    Breadth of media channels gives opportunities for message distribution and outreach to new audiences.  lc3
 #mmccon    
    
    
    @ElizabethB Haven't used DM in a while - but reconsidering postcard reminders. Just need ammo/stats to get budget. #mmccon    
    
    
    Email and direct mail are like peanut butter and jelly lc3 #mmccon    
    
    
    @Heleeene mmcc #mmccon    
    
    
    Ahhh! Need a power cord. May have to run back to hotel to grab it. Anyone have one to share in Comm Strat next? #mmccon    
    
    
    Photos on websites need to demonstrate interaction, not talking heads. Need to tell a story relevant to the content on the page lc3 #mmccon    
    
    
    @ChatterBachs Thanks - standard dell laptop #mmccon    
    
    
    @ChatterBachs thanks anyway. Its a quick walk. Back for tweetup    
    
    
    Hmm, interesting mobile stats on expedential growth, but is there a cross ref to age/interest groups? ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Wow idea - major mtg dues incr, but got an itouch which was sponsored, and included assn app. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    These aren’t “online cities” or “megaolopises” – “community” needs to keep the closeness and connection of every voice matters. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Don’t open the community floodgates all at once. Prospective community participants won’t be able to follow along successfully. ld1 #mmccon    
    
    
    When launching a social network, don’t tell them it’s a social network – use the tools and terminology that will engage your members #mmccon    
    
    
    Who here manages online communities for their assn? Would love to connect and share war stories.  #mmccon    
    
    
    A brand is a promise you make and keep every day #MMCCon    
    
    
    @BillWalker7 the pen makes my hand hurts :)    
    
    
    Should have worn Groundswell green today to show support :)  #mmccon    
    
    
    HERO – Highly empowered and resourceful operative #mmccon    
    
    
    Four technologies empower customers: smart mobile devices; social technology; cloud computing; pervasive video  #mmccon    
    
    
    IDEA; identify mass influencers; deliver groundswell customer service; empower with mobile information; amplify your fan activity. #mmccon    
    
    
    Treat your volunteers like royalty to encourage further loyalty #mmccon    
    
    
    In our membership of 19,000, I track 200 active twitter and 30 active linkedin users. #mmccon    
    
    
    @johnYSchen I made a list in twitter of members. Check followers against db. Also collected profile to incl twitter Monthly db check #mmccon    
    
    
    Oh really, you just quoted star trek. I just lost a little respect :) #mmccon    
    
    
    Me too! We need a tweep table for discussion group :) RT @maddiegrant: In session about multi-modal campaigns. #mmccon    
    
    
    a while at first, but not long for maintenance. @johnYSchen I tried doing that...was taking me forever. How long did that take you? #mmccon    
    
    
    Then look to the left to find it... RT @lmasri: I get the desire to gather mkting intel, but why 4 step login 2get @jbernoff slides #mmccon    
    
    
    The most retweetable time for @aomconnect is 10AM on Monday (EST).  #mmccon    
    
    
    love it! RT @G_J_W: Ask members or conf attendees to create "unofficial" insider tips re: travel, wifi hotspots lj1 #mmccon    
    
    
    Hi Phil! Nice to meet ya :) lf4 #mmccon    
    
    
    I love ppl that refer to it as "The Twitter" #MMCCon    
    
    
    @laurenhefner Laptop until battery died :) sb cool picm #MMCCon lf4    
    
    
    Yes there is a chocolate council #MMCCon lf4    
    
    
    I'm at Stuck on the runway at DCA (Arlington) http://4sq.com/kfNMQT    
    
    
    Had to turn on Pandora. Too quiet in the office today without the chatter from tweeps at  #mmccon    
    
    
    Oh what a sad day. #LI put Sarah Palin in my "recommended connections" - oh LinkedIn, I thought we understood each other! Alas!    
    
    
    Very cool! Going to be doing a Fresh Wave house party! Awesome goodies coming! Who's coming? @HousePartyFun @fresh_wave    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    Great topic! Sue from @aomconnect Lots of possiblities, but it is defining the WHY! #nptalk    
    
    
    Looks like I missed something good at #cmmeetup - count me in next time.    
    
    
    @ritasofelmsford Thanks for the follow! You guys are THE best! Planning on seeing you tomorrow! Yippee!    
    
    
    I just ousted @michaelblatter as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Photogenic" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/msDSY8    
    
    
    Hmmm, 2 interviews this week and my best suits are at the cleaners. At least I have back ups.    
    
    
    I just ousted @chrisgaur as the mayor of Pace University on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/bYpesu    
    
    
    A day of "rest" while daycare is closed after a week at Search Engine Strategies.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock You actually look at calories there? I did once. Ruined the experience. I feel obligated to order kids meals now.    
    
    
    only 143 new projects in my inbox. 102 of them from my "brilliant idea" to include logos in listings. Note to self: no more brilliant ideas.    
    
    
    one conference call to go and I'm done for the day! Hoorray! And then to buy a bday gift for family party tonight.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock mine throws a tantrum when it breaks off and won't stay on again. gotta make banana glue.the peel makes a great hat    
    
    
    setting tons of google gagets. going a little nuts now that I got approval    
    
    
    lovin chai    
    
    
    cold medicine wearing off. fading fast. thank God MIL is taking the boy tonight!    
    
    
    why are people facinated with the back button. u don't need it. Geesh.    
    
    
    My so has decided I am "da" - which has been the case for a while, but now that my hubby is "ma." Now I know he's screwing with us.    
    
    
    Totally addicted to Tagalongs.    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: sure beats my pasta with meat sauce and tagalongs    
    
    
    @sitelogic: with the wind in nyc today, I have a nice fro to join in!    
    
    
    getting old - had to switch to big fonts setting today. ugh    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: but the rain is clearing, so hopefully on your way soon.    
    
    
    It took me 2 weeks to catch up from 4 days out of the office. Can't go anywhere.    
    
    
    realizing I only like cold green tea. My hot tea is gross. Have to go get my chai    
    
    
    @JenniferLaycock: yes,  but acknowledging addiction is the first step to recovery.    
    
    
    ok, I think WW is out the window today. 3 thin mints and 2 tags along after Taco Bell. Blah.    
    
    
    Planning for SES. What's new this year?    
    
    
    Why do people feel they must email projects 3 times and call me twice within an hour. Ugh.    
    
    
    My cat is 17lbs. Vet now has her on the Atkins plan. My cat. On Atkins. Doh.    
    
    
    Reading: "How to Develop a Content Strategy Process"( http://twitthis.com/7tbki9 )    
    
    
    Hubby's waiting at airport for cousin to arrive and has Tracy Morgan sit down next to him. All hubby says is "when you going back on Howard"    
    
    
    about 20 police cars just decended on the street just below my office. gotta see what happened.    
    
    
    @cordialcricket Nice meeting you at the Retailer Forum booth at #NYIGF. Thanks for stopping by!    
    
    
    Excuse the next hour of tweets. But feel free to join the party! Logging in to  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Comm mgt has evolved from a tech role and spewing msgs to a mktg role of listening and engaging #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Many roles touch cmm mgt. For years, I had a title of Web Mngr which mean from domain, srvr to copywriting, design. More roles now #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Excuse the flurry of msgs. Following along today on  #cmgrchat    
    
    
    How many host their own community? What benefits/push back do you get?
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Kickin' job search for SEO, community building and e-marketing into high gear. Visit http://www.susanfernandez.info for overview.    
    
    
    I'm trying @RowFeeder to track tweets and facebook posts. Sign up and we both get 250 bonus posts: http://s.rowfeeder.com/a89bd0e4camjm-t     
    
    
    What are great tools to show reach and connections in graphs, charts, etc - something cool for the board? rowfeeder/trendistic/tweetreach ??    
    
    
    Great! Planning my first now! @KellyLux Join #CMGRchat today for *IRL Meetups of Online Communities* 2pm EST. See you there!    
    
    
    @deirdrereid You're the best!    
    
    
    Excuse excessive tweeting. Joining #CMGRchat today for *IRL Meetups of Online Communities*    
    
    
    We have one Annual Meeting each yr - last yr some tweeps asked to do one and sent out an informal date/time but bombed. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Next month we're doing our first official event - praying it goes well. #cmgrchat    
    
    
    A2: I'm going to try social-ite awards and hand out $5 giftcards by recognizing those I see active in each space
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    love it RT @savvysarahjane: @cmgrchat A2) I like when meetups are like an oreo: mingle time | presentation/activity | mingle time #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Hmm, need more info on this Twizzo thing - nothing worthwhile came up googling it #cmgrchat    
    
    
    We have pushback on our own community because it's one more thing to do/remember. LinkedIn is best with our membership assn
 #cmgrchat    
    
    
    Checking in today at  #nptalk    
    
    
    Many co hire someone not knowing what to expect. How should we (the ones filling the roles) set the co expectations? #nptalk    
    
    
    I just ousted @michaelblatter as the mayor of Brick Oven Pizza on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/asLuvv    
    
    
    What tools are used for this? I'm doing my first multiple person blog as a live blog for a conference. Using WordPress. #nptalk    
    
    
    @wildwomanfund Thanks. Nice - you'll have to stop in and say hi when you visit :) #nptalk    
    
    
    #FF @wildwomanfund @DigitalKaitlyn @smallchangefund @SocialNicole via http://followfriday.com    
    
    
    @DigitalKaitlyn Thanks for the input on Tweetdeck. Did my first experiments. Great w/ Twitter; Failed on FB & LI    
    
    
    