Hey folks! If you already downloaded my free Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook, I've updated a few pages with some... http://fb.me/2Im84sTo4     
    
    
    I'll be resending the link to the free Balanced Bites Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook tomorrow morning, so make... http://fb.me/2wBQZgYQW     
    
    
    Holiday Recipe Round-Up - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bjny3bn  #paleo    
    
    
    Working on a tree nut-free apple crisp/crumble idea. Will post a recipe when something turns out well. About to... http://fb.me/1XsRBkQGe     
    
    
    Monday Motivation: If you don't like it, change it. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/pod42dv  #paleo    
    
    
    Reminder! I'll be sending out an updated version of the FREE Balanced Bites Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook... http://fb.me/2478Zs2ul     
    
    
    @AdvDressmaking :)    
    
    
    5 Questions with Paleo Parents, authors of Eat Like a Dinosaur - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6tw99vu  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Sweet & Sour Gummy Gelatin Snacks - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/q7hv3nt  #paleo    
    
    
    FAQs: How can I eat Paleo without a gallbladder? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/av363ou  #paleo    
    
    
    My friends have an annual party the day after Thanksgiving, and it alternates between being an apps party or a... http://fb.me/3mpVXLfmU     
    
    
    Looking for healthy holiday recipes that are gluten-free, grain-free, and Paleo-friendly? 

Grab my FREE... http://fb.me/2DuOUI1pb     
    
    
    Okay, folks - if you're on my emailing list already, the updated Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook will start... http://fb.me/6zUdqZOwp     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #101: Cholesterol Clarity with Jimmy Moore - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ngqxsrw  #paleo    
    
    
    If you haven't yet shared the link for my FREE, 60-page Healthy Holiday eBook with your friends, what are you... http://fb.me/27wckfAuR     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Grain-Free Salmon Cakes  Great recipe that everyone will love!  #balancedbites #salmonc http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880855840/ …    
    
    
    Lemon Rosemary Broiled Salmon     People are often timid when it comes to cooking fish, but it’s one http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880855842/ …    
    
    
    Simple Shrimp Ceviche  This recipe was fantastic, so I had to share it with you all immediately. Ple http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880855845/ …    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode 14 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/875wd7x  #paleo    
    
    
    I love this!!! RT @IntDesWellness: @21daysugardetox @againstallgrain DOUBLE score at Costco tonight! #21DSD #paleo pic.twitter.com/shzUg9F7Nf    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Thanksgiving Stuffing Meatballs - from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d7wjmlr  #paleo    
    
    
    5:58pm brazenathletics - class cheers on limitless_bigj while he crushes his back squat set.… http://instagram.com/p/hKrJ1iBr2r/     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #84: Guest Kendall Kendrick of http://Primal-Balance.com  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d6pmnw6  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #54: Top 10 Questions we get - "protein overload," gall bladder removal, agave, Cod... http://tinyurl.com/bnpe2yp  #paleo    
    
    
    5 Questions with Marin Sun Farms - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/4bbyu8r  #paleo    
    
    
    @hellywhiting my book has a meal plan you can use. Also follow @ThePaleoMom and Mickey trescott (idk her handle)    
    
    
    If you are using sugar in recipes for the holidays, there's no need to worry about how to "get rid" of the extra... http://fb.me/2PnqmPoA9     
    
    
    It looks like December 2010 is when searches for "paleo diet" surpassed those for "gluten free diet" in Google.... http://fb.me/29ASR44fB     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #11 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bwr95qz  #paleo    
    
    
    @imperfectWell @JHunFun @21daysugardetox @againstallgrain I updated this post to list the stores carrying it now. http://balbit.es/1eobnaV     
    
    
    In case you missed this news, "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" is now in Costco stores across the US. Here is a list of... http://fb.me/30MeNEnPF     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Early Girl Tomato & Avocado Salad   Great salad to complete a meal!  #balancedbites #to http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880860742/ …    
    
    
    Kale Salad with Tahini Dressing  This recipe is a great one to try with ingredients you have on-hand http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880860757/ …    
    
    
    Enjoy this FREE GIFT gift from me!

My Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook is the perfect companion for your... http://fb.me/14TLcJ6xQ     
    
    
    @GGGW30 @HealthyLiving HAHAHAH!!!    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: What Should You Be Doing With Your Life? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/42pfc9r  #paleo    
    
    
    @thekat0711 yum! me too ;)    
    
    
    Grab my Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook, FREE! A full-color, 60-page guide to delicious holidays! #paleo #glutenfree http://balbit.es/healthyholidayebook …    
    
    
    Want to win one of THREE copies of my new book?! Go like Elevate Your Energy for a chance to win! http://fb.me/1MxmRmrei     
    
    
    @MrVilleneuve She has to want change for herself, you can't want it for her. I hope she is in a "ready" place!    
    
    
    @100daysrealfood thanks for the RT :)    
    
    
    @EricJacksons hey now!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #73: Blood type diet, candida, CrossFit, light therapy - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/aguebxa  #paleo    
    
    
    I've decided that it's definitely not too soon to start my holiday season Elf-a-thon! :) 

This movie is chock... http://fb.me/2RtDfxj9H     
    
    
    @rwp0921 Glad you enjoyed it!    
    
    
    @MrVilleneuve So would I! I don't get a say in that, however. It has to come from a French publisher!    
    
    
    @CertifiedFitGk YUM! One of my faves!    
    
    
    @MrVilleneuve Great to hear her motivation. Also great that others were spreading the word. :) My best to you both.    
    
    
    A super classy dinner I made up: deli-turkey "carpaccio" hahah! Topped with @kasandrinos EVOO and… http://instagram.com/p/hNK2JQhr5o/     
    
    
    A recent review of "The 21-Day Sugar Detox":

"Yes, I lost weight. More than 7 pounds over 3 weeks. That’s the... http://fb.me/3646yj6hj     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #39: Adrenal Fatigue Part 2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c2qsorn  #paleo    
    
    
    Practical Paleo is now available for pre-order! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6utbsaw  #paleo    
    
    
    [POST] 4 Super-foods the media tells you are unhealthy.

If you’re looking for a post about acai, gogi berries,... http://fb.me/17Y2pNQv5     
    
    
    @robthedogquinn @againstallgrain YES!!!    
    
    
    4 Super-foods the media tells you are unhealthy. --> http://bit.ly/4superfoods     
    
    
    Quick breakfast of three scrambled eggs with pickled herring (Blue Hill Bay brand wild) and some… http://instagram.com/p/hOQPQIhryM/     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Apple Streusel Egg Muffins - from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/aesu3cq  #paleo    
    
    
    @goodcleanchow Focus on a combination of what you know you need to teach people and what they want to learn. It's for them, not you :)    
    
    
    I LOVE THIS SO MUCH. Go Like Thrive as the Fittest for more like this. Liz and I will be talking to Jen Sinkler... http://fb.me/2yB8ouTS8     
    
    
    You guys are absolutely going to LOVE this book from @nomnompaleo . It's an experience and a joy to read - even... http://fb.me/2x4sCX94P     
    
    
    Is "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" or "Practical Paleo" on your holiday gift list this year? To give or to receive?! Tell me!! #giftofhealth    
    
    
    @damonridesbikes @RELEVANTpodcast YES!! That's awesome. I have a free support email series too at http://balbit.es/1a54tmE  (top left link)    
    
    
    @damonridesbikes @RELEVANTpodcast I'll be signing copies on Jan 14th up in your area as well -details on my website sidebar    
    
    
    Practical Paleo Review Round-Up #2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9svz9e4  #paleo    
    
    
    @sardo02 it's fine but I just purée the pan roasted veggies in mine - grab my free eBook    
    
    
    FAQs: Is protein powder okay on a Paleo diet? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ps5zw3y  #paleo    
    
    
    @EPICbar ha nice!    
    
    
    @sardo02 yes I did    
    
    
    Chronic Lyme Disease: Kevin's Inspiring Practical Paleo Testimonial - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bvuu6g3  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #66: The 21-Day Sugar Detox - FAQs and questions answered! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/arxuthq  #paleo    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: 8 ways to show love that don't involve food. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ae6hjwp  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Tomato & Olive Salad - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7qsvnew  #paleo    
    
    
    A busy morning of prep. Apple crumble is done, turkey is in the oven, Brussels are prepped, and the broth,... http://fb.me/2xTQsnRbw     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving everyone! This year, among countless other little things, I am so very thankful for the... http://fb.me/6BnUMgKtW     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast Episode #115 [encore]: Surviving the holidays – indulging, family & cocktails! http://nblo.gs/Rwusl     
    
    
    Surviving the holiday season - enjoy! http://balbit.es/BBpodcast115  http://fb.me/6ylEnsR7x     
    
    
    Episode #115  Surviving the holidays -indulging, family & cocktails!  #balancedbites #podcast #holid http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880869076/ …    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #110: The 21-Day Sugar Detox book, FAQs Part 1 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/o4ww5x3  #paleo    
    
    
    Thanksgiving dinner made entirely by @scottamillsdc & I! So good! http://fb.me/21gHQihMQ     
    
    
    Apple crisp with whipped vanilla bean grass-fed heavy cream on top! #delish http://fb.me/118Gcw1mS     
    
    
    My Thanksgiving table included recipes from my free Healthy Holiday eBook - http://balbit.es/healthyholidayebook …... http://fb.me/6MdcCpMy4     
    
    
    2012 Healthy Holiday Gift Guide - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/dx9qlpv  #paleo    
    
    
    @robbwolf @z_dustin hahahahahah    
    
    
    @CaveGirlEats I'm going to go out on a limb here and say about 3# of that is just on your face, the rest went into the meal...    
    
    
    The 21-Day Sugar Detox - Official Book Trailer! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/py7wkye  #paleo    
    
    
    5 Questions with "Paleo Pals" author, Sarah Fragoso - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c8l7esw  #paleo    
    
    
    Dinner Into Breakfast: Skirt Steak Tacos, Steak & Eggs - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3edzgru  #paleo    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman :-)    
    
    
    @sardo02 um... No    
    
    
    @RosemarySewart @squattypotty :-)    
    
    
    Did you cook up something for your loved ones from my free Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook? What did you make? 

If... http://fb.me/Sgz0Wr79     
    
    
    The 21-Day Sugar Detox Review Round-up #1 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qddn93d  #paleo    
    
    
    If you're looking for some motivation and tips for fitness around the holiday season, check out this "4-Week... http://fb.me/1Z75JSgxN     
    
    
        
    
    
    @AnthonyMichaeI @robbwolf I have a whole list of tips in my free Healthy Holiday Recipes ebook --> http://balbit.es/healthyholidayebook …    
    
    
    @robbwolf @brownheart My best advice on top of Robb's (which I have never been good at, but agree with)-write a book for them, not for you.    
    
    
    @brownheart @robbwolf hence my advice - write it for them, and what they need. Not a self-fulfilling project.    
    
    
    Is my website loading for you? I can't tell if it's my internet or what :/ http://www.balancedbites.com     
    
    
    Looking for an awesome holiday gift that won't clutter the life of your loved one with more stuff? 

Offer them... http://fb.me/2CaEG7DCd     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Turkey & Bacon Club Salad     I love making salads out of whatever random ingredients I http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880872891/ …    
    
    
    Butternut Squash Soup  This time, I had the idea of throwing in a couple of possibly non-traditional http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880872895/ …    
    
    
    If you've been planning on giving one of my books to your loved ones for the holidays this year, Amazon is... http://fb.me/1aIC3zCjN     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #107: Special Guest Michelle from Nom Nom Paleo  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/kw6oy7a  #paleo    
    
    
    @CertifiedFitGk they're always a favorite!    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Pumpkin Cranberry Muffins from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9t6zcrx  #paleo    
    
    
    Did you hear about the 30% OFF Black Friday book sale on Amazon??

Amazon's offering my new 21DSD cookbook for... http://fb.me/Rn2Krrfn     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #108: Paleo Jerks, Thinning hair, Adrenal Fatigue and Aging Skin - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/mnd75s2  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #63: Dizziness, adrenal fatigue, Tourette Syndrome, HCG Diet  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d2s8caz  #paleo    
    
    
    4 Super-foods the media tells you are unhealthy - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d7a94dv  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #16 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7arynlf  #paleo    
    
    
    We love hosting friends for brunch! @petespaleo and Sarah came by today all the way from San Diego! :-)... http://fb.me/1x4Rud8mI     
    
    
    FAQs: All about The 21-Day Sugar Detox book - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lquf8xw  #paleo    
    
    
    Buttery Turnip Puree  This buttery puree was the result of this kitchen play-time. The texture was v http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880877734/ …    
    
    
    Garlic & Dill Vegetables   Cooking carrots in a pan with sufficient fat and seasonings will allow th http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880877743/ …    
    
    
    Where in Upper West Side (NYC) can we get a bite to eat? Near Beacon Theater would be a plus...    
    
    
    Book Review: Sweet Potato Power by Ashley Tudor - and a giveaway! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/78puyno  #paleo    
    
    
    @aharrin awesome!    
    
    
    We are definitely super-fans. guster tonight and again tomorrow in NYC :-) can't wait to hear this… http://instagram.com/p/hW_sEhhr_O/     
    
    
    We are definitely super-fans. @guster tonight and again tomorrow in NYC :-) can't wait to hear this… http://instagram.com/p/hW_sEhhr_O/     
    
    
    Real Life Changes - Emily's Story: "Every choice matters." - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3c2wmbr  #paleo    
    
    
    Robb Wolf on The Balanced Bites Podcast: Paleo media myths & sustainability. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6whn567  #paleo    
    
    
    Practical Paleo 30-Day Meal Plan Testimonial: Janelle & Athletic Performance - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9fkrdpx  #paleo    
    
    
    I'm always honored when fellow practitioners speak so highly of my work. A recent Amazon review from Tuit... http://fb.me/6A0GlD4On     
    
    
    @SportiShorti Preparation is key- it's just 3 weeks :)    
    
    
    The Real Deal on Adrenal Fatigue - Guest post on http://RobbWolf.com  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/84sr5c6  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #52: Microwaves, personal lubricant, weight gain help, sun protection and more. - Bites... http://tinyurl.com/9o3t5cj  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #106: Special Guest Katy Bowman of Aligned and Well - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ke2fqxn  #paleo    
    
    
    Saw @Guster two days in a row with @scottamillsdc - both shows were awesome - as always. Today took me back to my 'Cuse days w/ Parachute!    
    
    
    Hey folks! A friendly reminder here that if your local Costco is on the list of stores that received "The 21-Day... http://fb.me/36RHbnI2C     
    
    
    Don't miss out on this awesome deal from Amazon: Save 30% off any of my books! Use code BOOKDEAL to get the... http://fb.me/1vjkHEML4     
    
    
    Monday Motivation: Be Open to Opportunity - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3p7pe6u  #paleo    
    
    
    5 Questions with "Make it Paleo" authors Bill Staley & Hayley Mason - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3p9bhjf  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #92: Nutrition Coaching Business Talk with Jessica Mishra - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qakf27x  #paleo    
    
    
    Today is the start of the final #21DSD for 2013 - and a big group is starting, while an even bigger group will... http://fb.me/29vcepkTP     
    
    
    Okay, folks - here's your CYBER MONDAY offer from me... since I have nothing to sell you and therefore can't... http://fb.me/10NP8THrH     
    
    
    I have a CYBER MONDAY giveaway going on over on FB - hop onto my page if you're on it to join in. Nothing to sell you, just enter to win!    
    
    
    Grain-Free Coconut Flour Muffins  This recipe is SO EASY that it’s one that I can follow; and after  http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880886943/ …    
    
    
    Grain-Free Sausage & Apple Stuffing  I can enjoy all of the same flavors and stuffing awesomeness wi http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880886947/ …    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Crockpot Braised Beef Shanks - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/43h7r2n  #paleo    
    
    
    Curious about what the recipes are in "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" book versus "The 21-Day Sugar Detox Cookbook" ?... http://fb.me/1LmeSIoLX     
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman Um………….    
    
    
    NEW JERSEY! Don't miss out on the Balanced Bites Seminar on January 4th at a very special price (home court... http://fb.me/2w1X5Izot     
    
    
    FAQs: All about fermented cod liver oil (and why I don't take fish oil) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cq6rzao  #paleo    
    
    
    CYBER MONDAY DEAL! AMAZON is still offering this awesome deal - use it on any one of my books if you haven't used... http://fb.me/267WdDiv3     
    
    
    @goodcleanchow it's an acquired taste. I do like it in certain ways.    
    
    
    @Cdparker1122 It's best to take it when you'll remember to take it ;)    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman People truly confuse the cellular need for glucose with a dietary need for sugar. It's very sad.    
    
    
    Super Simple Sugar Scrub - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d65r37b  #paleo    
    
    
    Warning: this post is a rant...

I'm just going to say this ONE TIME for anyone who sees these "FREE KINDLE... http://fb.me/3464ArZhJ     
    
    
    @Cdparker1122 If I had to vote, I would vote am.    
    
    
    @dannycotton Nope.    
    
    
    @goodcleanchow I have a great recipe in my book, mostly butter ;)    
    
    
    If you've wondered how to make zucchini or carrot noodles, this is the tool I use --> http://amzn.to/Uegl1J ... http://fb.me/27ssiDDuA     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #113: Listener Q&A - Body Image Perspective & Body Composition - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/pavuwz2  #paleo    
    
    
    Did you know that I have a YouTube channel? I sometimes make videos in spurts, but I'll be committed to more... http://fb.me/2cTYUtBSc     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #104: Special Guest Trina Felber of Primal Life Organics - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qaxqzmz  #paleo    
    
    
    Practical Paleo Review Round-Up #4 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d2pywyv  #paleo    
    
    
    I am obsessed with the fact that @garyvee consistently goes off-the-script while narrating his own book because he can't help himself :-)    
    
    
    @rachmole Why no animals? You could do a grain-free granola with coconut milk & fruit…    
    
    
    I spy... :-) Kitchen Before & After: A 1970s Kitchen Gets a Jaw Dropping Overhaul — Reader Kitchen R http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880891677/ …    
    
    
    Today's breakfast is brought to you by Thanksgiving leftovers (turkey) and @petespaleo bacon. Salad for breakfast... http://fb.me/1VA8RCxuX     
    
    
    @rachmole Grain-free granola -- no grains… google for a recipe, tons of #paleo websites have them!    
    
    
    .@garyvee - listening to TYE & realizing how I got to where I am with what I'm doing. I adopted Twitter early, helped folks, no right hooks.    
    
    
    .@garyvee and I did so gladly, as I still do. I respond to every SM request/question that comes in - whether immediately or not. Every one.    
    
    
    .@garyvee (except from trolls)    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #93: Pete & Sarah Servold - paleo chef tips & real skincare - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/kh4vayt  #paleo    
    
    
    @garyvee It makes me feel like I'm getting the real-deal/something special by listening vs reading. Hooray for audio learners! #bonus    
    
    
    @melicious11 @CaveGirlEats I'm ready for ya here but I think our Cave Girl friend was perhaps trampled by goats #homesteadingproblems    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: People first. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7y35qyl  #paleo    
    
    
    Dinner tonight is soup and sweet potato fries with healthy homemade ketchup (recipe in the #21dsd books) - no... http://fb.me/PwQPfMth     
    
    
    Roasted Winter Squash with Coconut Butter  My favorite way to cook winter squash is to roast it. I f http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880893672/ …    
    
    
    The WINNERS of my Cyber Monday 3-book package giveaway are: 
Rochelle Berryman
Wil Jeudy
Samantha Kastelz

I hope... http://fb.me/1QL56hzei     
    
    
    Sautéed Red Cabbage with Onions & Apples from Practical Paleo   This is a recipe I created after see http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880893683/ …    
    
    
    Paleo Magazine (September / October) - Feeding Kids: What the USDA Recommends vs The Paleo Diet - Bites... http://tinyurl.com/3lrrzgb  #paleo    
    
    
    As of two weeks from today, I will have THREE published books. Learn more here -->… http://instagram.com/p/henvlNhr38/     
    
    
    @theoptimalk @melicious11 The best gifts!    
    
    
    Seattle area folks! I'll be back at Third Place Books (where I signed books in the dark last year when the power... http://fb.me/1k4pviXb5     
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman I think @primalpalate published 3 in even less time!! ;0)    
    
    
    @ChrisMasterjohn hahahah #safeflight    
    
    
    DON'T MISS OUT on upcoming events! RSVP via the sidebar link on my website or… http://instagram.com/p/het3xLhrxy/     
    
    
    DON'T MISS OUT on upcoming events! RSVP via the sidebar link on my website or http://balbit.es/2014eventbrite  http://fb.me/1UBOrW4f2     
    
    
    FYI: All events I post about are open to the public, not just members of the hosting... http://fb.me/2IHTqzDCs     
    
    
    @paleolyssa All events will have all the books, yes :)    
    
    
    @Cazzowary @Bella_Marchesa HA! Well, they seem like cookies, but sort of just look like them #notsweet ;)    
    
    
    A hot new release and a book that released over a year ago that STILL tops the most wished for and recommended... http://fb.me/WmGsD39z     
    
    
    Homemade Ketchup Recipe - *21DSD, no sweetener-added - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/npycmra  #paleo    
    
    
    If anyone is a @garyvee fan, I highly recommend his books on @audible_com versus in-print. His off-script bits are the bomb.    
    
    
    @MissSkinnyGenes @garyvee @audible_com it's too bad my books don't lend themselves 2 audio, bc I'd love to narrate them. #specialprojectsoon    
    
    
    5 Questions (and a Giveaway!) with "The Million Year Meal" author, Ian Lucas - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6luhttm  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #85: Dating, wine, pre-colonoscopy food, being too clean? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/acej6w2  #paleo    
    
    
    @FeedingFWCF lol!    
    
    
    UPCOMING EVENTS INFO - DON'T MISS OUT!!! Please tag or share with friends who may also be interested so they don't... http://fb.me/KRdElUHL     
    
    
    OMG IT'S HERE!!!! #21dsdcookbook http://amzn.to/WmUpjb  http://instagram.com/p/hgVdk2hr8N/     
    
    
    YES, THERE ARE TWO NEW #21DSD BOOKS! The main guide book is the "blue" one and the additional cookbook… http://instagram.com/p/hgW4DMBr9t/     
    
    
    YES, THERE ARE TWO NEW #21DSD BOOKS! The main guide book is the "blue" one and the additional cookbook (with meal... http://fb.me/3epACU1zh     
    
    
    Whenever possible, take your shoes off! :-) Another great post from Dr. Scott A. Mills with some simple, helpful... http://fb.me/2VaUCzT5d     
    
    
    @PrimalToad Yeah, it was hilarious to me. Esp b/c the reason for writing these books isn't to make money- that's easier done other ways.    
    
    
    @PrimalToad I think you meant to say "quit," not "quite."    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #70: Practical Paleo meal plans, exercise, diet for kids - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ba3ljqh  #paleo    
    
    
    @cookinuplife @CaveGirlEats @Paleokits NICE!    
    
    
    5 Questions with Caitlin Weeks Author of Mediterranean Paleo Cooking and Giveaway! http://fb.me/VWj9gZFH     
    
    
    5 Questions with Caitlin Weeks Author of Mediterranean Paleo Cooking and Giveaway! http://nblo.gs/RI56T     
    
    
    Check out this interview with my good friend Caitlin Weeks - Grass Fed Girl - about her awesome new eBook,... http://fb.me/6v6nz9Npe     
    
    
    Check out my previous post to learn how to grab a copy of the Mediterranean Paleo Cooking eBook/PDF - and get a... http://fb.me/13tGjoD2K     
    
    
    @StevenHarlow1 YAY!    
    
    
    5 Questions with Joe Salama author of "The Paleo Miracle"  I am very pleased to share with all of yo http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880898912/ …    
    
    
    5 Questions with Mira & Jayson Calton authors of Rich Food Poor Food.  Simply stated the Rich Food,  http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880898918/ …    
    
    
    Q: "But, Diane... how do you DO IT ALL yourself?!"
A: "I don't."

My team ROCKS. I <3 them. 

MEET THEM HERE -->... http://fb.me/6jlepYWPI     
    
    
    @NursePaleo YUM!!    
    
    
    "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" is back under $21 on Amazon right now! WOOT! Less than the old PDF price-you'll love it!--> http://amzn.to/Wcpmqr     
    
    
    It's almost surreal to have my third baby here today! You are going to LOVE these recipes!!! #21dsd… http://instagram.com/p/hhBkQoBr43/     
    
    
    Keep "Practical Paleo" in Costco stores - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/au3jar8  #paleo    
    
    
    @candy67cane woot!    
    
    
    One of my favorite recipes & photos in the book! Ahi Tuna Poke Bowl - it's on the cover, too!… http://instagram.com/p/hhRVTnhrxW/     
    
    
    Are you watching this debate about eating meat (or not)? I am! 

Dr. Chris Masterjohn and Joel Salatin are there... http://fb.me/6AJcvjGiU     
    
    
    Are you watching the #vegdebate ?? http://balbit.es/191TzlP     
    
    
    This guy calling a chicken "somebody" needs to read @johndurant 's book- he is humanizing a chicken quite nicely. #vegdebate    
    
    
    Sorry to call him "this guy" but I didn't catch his name - tuned in later b/c of frozen streams. #vegdebate    
    
    
    Joel has it right about our responsibility as humans to "massage" pasture-based ecology in raising animals/food #vegdebate    
    
    
    @wendytaylor Seriously, it's such a weak point, they need to stop using it in their arguments. #vegdebate    
    
    
    I don't know why I find these arguments about growing chickens in order to kill/eat them vs growing tomatoes hilarious, but I do. #vegdebate    
    
    
    AMEN Joel! We don't need corn and soybeans! #vegdebate #growgrass    
    
    
    @staubio @Pamela_Lund that makes zero sense. increased demand will drive supply up and price down. #economics    
    
    
    @ancestrally @DoctorKateND @IQ2US seriously frustrating    
    
    
    @DCHealthyBites HAHAHAHA    
    
    
    @staubio @Pamela_Lund We aren't disagreeing on the CAFO issue. None of us sees them as efficient. Growing grass is fairly cheap.    
    
    
    UGH buffering again! #vegdebate    
    
    
    @hossfirooznia @staubio @Pamela_Lund There is plenty of land that could be used but is not.    
    
    
    @staubio @Pamela_Lund I'm sorry you are confused about the cost of raising grass-fed cows.    
    
    
    @staubio @hossfirooznia @Pamela_Lund We do need a different way of helping grass-fed cows become distributed within semi-local areas.    
    
    
    @olaforsstrom Hope so!    
    
    
    Calling Joel Salatin an alternative farmer is quite oxymoronic. #vegdebate    
    
    
    Joel farms as farming should be. Being contrary to the status-quo doesn't make him alternative. It makes him legit. #vegdebate    
    
    
    @staubio @hossfirooznia @Pamela_Lund Many do. If I had a yard, perhaps I would.    
    
    
    @hossfirooznia @Pamela_Lund @staubio if you say so.    
    
    
    @staubio @hossfirooznia @Pamela_Lund So, something being "a lot of work" means we shouldn't do it? Raising food used to be our only work.    
    
    
    @staubio @hossfirooznia @Pamela_Lund I don't think the low cost is a real cost analysis.Cost to whom?And to what?Taxpayers pay,the land pays    
    
    
    EAT ALL THE THINGS WITH FACES #vegdebate #myvote #eatmeat #pastureraised    
    
    
    @melissamcewen I'm one of those zombies :)    
    
    
    @peakscale True, true. ;)    
    
    
    @tomnikkola @ChrisMasterjohn @JoelSalatin grass-fed lamb steak for me.    
    
    
    @AncestralizeMe agreed. Was that moderator biased? or is it me?    
    
    
    @jenn_labrie @AncestralizeMe Maybe all the meat-eaters were out on farms killing their food? ;)    
    
    
    @hollywoodhomest I think @PaleoParents hashtag that one all the time #morevegetablesthanavegetarian    
    
    
    Restocked my shelves :-) #practicalpaleo #21dsd #paleobooks http://fb.me/1Jyb3SfAS     
    
    
    @skyrudich SO yummy!    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #24, Listener Questions - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7km6zqp  #paleo    
    
    
    @skyrudich AWESOME    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Chocolate Almond Butter Cups - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/chwy3vx  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Tart & Creamy Applesauce  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9wz99p5  #paleo    
    
    
    @sairez lol    
    
    
    Hey everyone! 

We've got just TWO upcoming Balanced Bites Seminars - one in NJ and one in Philly - if you've... http://fb.me/6uWaN3WFo     
    
    
    A little motivation and some thoughts from me on this Thursday morning...

Three and a half years ago, I quit a... http://fb.me/2KQ1bQI5S     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #116: Special Guest Melissa Joulwan, Author of Well Fed 2 http://fb.me/2wzH6oagI     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #116: Special Guest Melissa Joulwan, Author of Well Fed 2 http://nblo.gs/RJcg3     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #22 Liz talks about her mystery trip - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7khfj7n  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast Episode 116 | Special Guest Melissa Joulwan, Author of Well Fed 2   #balanced http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880902915/ …    
    
    
    5 Questions with Jaclyn, Author of "Bone Broth A Recipe for Health."  I had the pleasure of interven http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880902926/ …    
    
    
    Heads up folks! 

I've changed the way my emailing list/emails are working recently. 

They'll no longer send you... http://fb.me/Qo8T6eo0     
    
    
    @jensinkler YESSS!    
    
    
    COSTCO UPDATE! 

Okay, folks... whether or not the 21DSD books hit ALL Coscto stores in the US & Canada is really... http://fb.me/18kWKDQUM     
    
    
    COSTCO UPDATE! 

Okay, folks... whether or not the 21DSD books hit ALL Coscto stores in the US & Canada is really... http://fb.me/17g6QnOkG     
    
    
    Paleo Meal Delivery  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/khbjus7  #paleo    
    
    
    A great review of The 21 Day Sugar Detox by Paleo in Melbourne.

"Why I love it: This book is the ultimate guide... http://fb.me/Pps2e2P1     
    
    
    @davidmholmes TRUE!    
    
    
    @Paleoga @cbcbooks :-)    
    
    
    @CollectivEvolve @KippinItPaleo NICE!    
    
    
    @AmyMyersMD Hey Doc! What's the best way to reach you directly regarding a private question? (not health related)    
    
    
    Oooh... I'm going to have some exciting news for you about my upcoming California & Northwest tour dates... stay... http://fb.me/QBIrLm5S     
    
    
    @jcpage22 You could… but less of it - 1/2 of what is called for would probably work. :)    
    
    
    Chris Kresser on The Balanced Bites Podcast talking about all things digestion - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3mcocmx  #paleo    
    
    
    @CollectivEvolve Thanks :)    
    
    
    If you've been looking for a way to make your transition to Paleo easier, this guide from Primal Palate may be... http://fb.me/3aZnLxdsY     
    
    
    @NaturopathicHnF Thank you so much for the offer! The stop is one of many and I don't even know if I'll be in town for lunch!    
    
    
    @NaturopathicHnF Get back in touch when we're closer to it if you can -- I'll check my itinerary/schedule.    
    
    
    @Kim_TX @nomnompaleo :-) Keep us posted!    
    
    
    "Everyone can rise above their circumstances and achieve success if they are dedicated to and passionate about... http://fb.me/3cFosvmn9     
    
    
    @glutenfreegirl hahahahahaha    
    
    
    Because I know that sometimes I introduce ingredients in recipes that are unfamiliar to you... This is a helpful... http://fb.me/6qyiC0bJU     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #6 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3wcw8a6  #paleo    
    
    
    So, I have been working on a big skin-progress/skincare post for many months (meaning I start it and then somehow... http://fb.me/1YNvISYLz     
    
    
    I AM FLOORED RIGHT NOW. I just found out that "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" made The New York Times bestseller list!... http://fb.me/3cWucEpLU     
    
    
    @glutenfreegirl I didn't really think it would happen going into the holidays - but I am honestly so, so grateful and just amazed.    
    
    
    @jordanleigh_91 They are all being worked through little by little!    
    
    
    Thanks everyone :-) It all began here on Twitter!!! #longhaul #thankyou    
    
    
    Announcing new coaching services from the Balanced Bites team - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/nv7d6mz  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #80: The Hormone Cure with Dr. Sara Gottfried, pt 2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ch7fayp  #paleo    
    
    
    I worked so insanely hard to make this book something you all would love and feel was truly helpful to… http://instagram.com/p/hlRTlwBrzz/     
    
    
    I worked so insanely hard to make this book something you all would love and feel was truly helpful to you - THIS... http://fb.me/2VLIqIjBn     
    
    
    @ZeekySquirrel @65Rika sorry you feel that way but please don't troll my feed with anti-omnivore comments. Thanks. #iblocktrolls    
    
    
    Guys - when making these Buffalo Chicken Egg Muffins - or ANY muffin recipes I give you for that matter - you... http://fb.me/2MgfsJWtV     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #12 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bnbat6m  #paleo    
    
    
    I'm cooking from grassfedgirl 's "Mediterranean Paleo Cooking" eBook this morning and my house smells… http://instagram.com/p/hldfAdhr0B/     
    
    
    @FMFBlogger Yes, and yes. It depends. I am aware that there are sometimes duplicates. It'll pass your feed momentarily. Relax :)    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger And, when I can, I actually delete the duplicates.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @FMFBlogger I tell it to send to FB, it goes to twitter, too. But it gives a FB link on twitter, which some can't see-So, if I want everyone    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger 2 see something easily,I post to IG and tell it to send 2 both FB & Twitter, then I usually delete the auto tweet from FB - whew    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger exactly. and I know some twitter peeps aren't active on fb and those links are annoying to them, so I often delete them.    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger It's not a lot of work, it's a click if I'm at my desk. Doesn't stress me- sometimes I just leave it.    
    
    
    This is freaking delicious!!! From grassfedgirl 's eBook Mediterranean Paleo Cooking - Fig & Ginger… http://instagram.com/p/hluBrjBr_G/     
    
    
    @melaniealissa NICE! Those are a favorite for sure!    
    
    
    @melaniealissa :) I'm pretty good at meatballs! HA!    
    
    
    Congrats 2 my fellow @nytimes bestseller @garyvee w/his new one @jjjrhbook & my new #21daysugardetox book (Dining) http://balbit.es/1gKzjXw     
    
    
    The Balanced Bites Podcast is moving to Thursday! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d6mg3xu  #paleo    
    
    
    Do you (or someone you know) have a small business? One that could perhaps use some help in the branding... http://fb.me/18yLf6TuC     
    
    
    Paleo Magazine: Modern Day Primal Living - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3bzs96e  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #48: Diane talks Practical Paleo on Underground Wellness Radio - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/chmosx2  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #56: Gall Bladder, tongue toxicity, gastric bypass, hula hoops & hormones - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cnytuca  #paleo    
    
    
    5 Questions with Kelly Milton author of Paleo Happy Hour and Giveaway!  - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lvhst42  #paleo    
    
    
    Halloween Recipe Round-up (and a spook-tacular 21DSD-friendly treat recipe!) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/pxktwz8  #paleo    
    
    
    @65Rika I was replying to the other person :-)    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Spaghetti Sauce - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lz3c8nr  #paleo    
    
    
    I need to share this with all of you, but I had to wait until she saw this in-print first. Now she has, so now I... http://fb.me/3wP7yM5Os     
    
    
    Catch me LIVE tomorrow on the Primal Diet Modern Health show hosted by Beverly Meyer! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cxt568l  #paleo    
    
    
    @dittobritto @againstallgrain yesssss!!!    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain what recipe?    
    
    
    @jonathanbailor lol!    
    
    
    @alexisjbell @againstallgrain @PrimalPalate some of my favorite people!!!    
    
    
    @JoyfulAbode @DrGhaheri @PaleoParents wasn't me tho I looked for one today    
    
    
    Harper & our tree! We trimmed it tonight.This is our first tree together but it's the start of an annual event,... http://fb.me/UCWiMX27     
    
    
    The Dish on Sugar &amp; Sweeteners - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3npjwkw  #paleo    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain hard to know without seeing the recipe but my flourless one in PP is great.    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain were you trying to make it without much sweetener? That may be the problem if so- the sweetener helps bind    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #47: Weston A. Price, Organ meats, Kombucha, and Sourdough - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cww5qmg  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #31 - Women's Wellness (Part 1) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bsu8kbe  #paleo    
    
    
    Breakfast - leftover cauli-mash mixed into scrambled eggs with @petespaleo bacon and a peppermint mocha... http://fb.me/14TrFyyA2     
    
    
    @MrVilleneuve it may be an old printing but I'll check...    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain I doubt they will bind in a very moist way without the sweetener in bulk other than stevia. You could...    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain try some gelatin mixed in. Cocoa powder dries the mix up as much as the flours do. The batter...    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @againstallgrain should be very wet/not runny but very soft to pour into the pan    
    
    
    2011 Healthy Holiday Gift Guide: Paleo Edition - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7mlg4ld  #paleo    
    
    
    Question: Have you picked up a copy of my new book, "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" yet? If so... print or ePub... http://fb.me/6q8ganJFT     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #20 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7r2xv89  #paleo    
    
    
    @ENERGYbits Sounds fun, but I'm not a fitness expert. Have you asked @jensinkler ?    
    
    
    @_ms_golightly YUM!    
    
    
    Meet the team: Anthony DiSarro - coach, athlete, and family man. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/layqzdb  #paleo    
    
    
    Dinner is chicken thighs with @tessemaes wing sauce, steamed broccoli and spiced Granny Smith applesauce from the... http://fb.me/2H2MGTtRd     
    
    
    The largest group EVER to take on The 21-Day Sugar Detox will kick off on Monday, January 6th! You can do... http://fb.me/6CrEkrGiJ     
    
    
    @JensGonePaleo totally    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #75: Mira & Jayson Calton talk "Rich Food Poor Food" - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/boalefs  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #29 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6p456m6  #paleo    
    
    
    @CaveGirlEats link didn't work for me :(    
    
    
    @Kevin_byDesign @ConnerHabib  Carrots are AOK :)    
    
    
    HEY NORTHERN NJ & PHILLY AREA PEEPS! 
(Or if you have friends/loved ones who live nearby...) 

A ticket to the... http://fb.me/6o28UcM0Z     
    
    
    @EPICbar @CaveGirlEats I wouldn't be, except @Scottamillsdc had to hit the road early today #sad - at least he'll be back on Friday!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #96: Cortisone injections, legumes, adrenal imbalance & weight re-gain fears - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/m23xdgg  #paleo    
    
    
    @DeeFitty You can email brooke@balancedbites.com for info on review copies!    
    
    
    @ajlukban @ConnerHabib http://amzn.to/Wcpmqr     
    
    
    NJ/Philly peeps, don't miss out! Balanced Bites Nutrition seminars in your areas! #paleo #crossfit Register here --> http://balbit.es/2014eventbrite     
    
    
    Getting an enter case of your new book is such a happy day!!! The #21dsdcookbook - I call it "the purple one."... http://fb.me/17InbW06k     
    
    
    @JessicaDDickson Probably not. Maybe report it to the company who hosts it? You can find that info via a whois search on the domain.    
    
    
    @JessicaDDickson More work than is probably necessary. There will always be copycats - whatever ;)    
    
    
    @katieekitchen @21daysugardetox YUM!    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Pumpkin Soufflé - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cljsur4  #paleo    
    
    
    Upcoming events! RSVP & register here --> http://balbit.es/2014eventbrite  http://instagram.com/p/htRi1IBr7f/     
    
    
    @RachaelPeirce GOOD LUCK!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #34: Fish Oil, Cod Liver Oil, FSVs & Cravings - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6oelpa2  #paleo    
    
    
    @AnthonyMichaeI TOMORROW?! Only at my gym for a WOD. On 1/4/14 I'll be teaching a seminar @BrazenAthletics deets --> http://balbit.es/brazen2014     
    
    
    @AnthonyMichaeI Wondering where you got that idea…?    
    
    
    In case you missed it... 

FAQ: How do I treat (or prevent) a cold or flu naturally? [with video]... http://fb.me/2y9ldf5Lk     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #71: Mark Sisson talks The Primal Connection! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/b6ylo3p  #paleo    
    
    
    @JeffSandquistDC @21daysugardetox Hoping so! It depends on sales of the first book - buy one (or 10) there to help ;) @victorybelt @costco    
    
    
        
    
    
    @JeffSandquistDC @21daysugardetox @VictoryBelt @Costco If your store wasn't on the list then it wasn't there to begin with though ;)    
    
    
    Why you want more stomach acid, not less. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/84now9x  #paleo    
    
    
    Is "Practical Paleo" or "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" (and/or 21DSD cookbook) on your Christmas list this year? To give or receive?!    
    
    
    @JeffSandquistDC @21daysugardetox @VictoryBelt @Costco Wow, so it sold out in the store? Did you see it there before? Some were 'hiding'…    
    
    
    @CoffeeBaconBks @JeffSandquistDC @VictoryBelt @Costco Thanks! That means your location is already SOLD OUT of the @21daysugardetox book!    
    
    
    @BarbarianOgre I'm glad you like it!    
    
    
    @RianVDM YES!!!!!! #amen #spoton    
    
    
    @BarbarianOgre I figured levity was important when helping folks get away from sugar and junky foods :-)    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #21 with Karen Pendergrass of Paleo Approved - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/89h7ugl  #paleo    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: Does your desire for security keep you from your calling? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cypfhej  #paleo    
    
    
    BIG NEWS!!! 

Liz and I will be launching an ONLINE VERSION of our seminar event - complete with a live Q&A... http://fb.me/37PZy3ST9     
    
    
    @WholeNewMom @FrugalPaleo My book, "Practical Paleo," will be really helpful to you. AI meal plan with notes on recipes for modifications    
    
    
    @FrugalPaleo No plans for it, sorry. Blame Liz's goats!!    
    
    
    @WholeNewMom What's up?    
    
    
    @WholeNewMom Contact brooke@balancedbites.com for review copy info.    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #76: JJ Virgin talks about "The Virgin Diet" - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/b6e286o  #paleo    
    
    
    Hi everyone! On this week's podcast Diane and Liz will be talking about staying on track during the holidays.... http://fb.me/RkhMC0IJ     
    
    
    Paleo Pitfall: "The Accidental Low-Carber."  (ALCer)

I see this often when folks just don't realize that they... http://fb.me/2a4TBuTJr     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #40: SPECIAL EPISODE! Athlete recovery & Steve's Club - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/76vr896  #paleo    
    
    
    I want to say thank you again to everyone who has supported my work in "The 21-Day Sugar Detox." 

Seeing the... http://fb.me/6qo8ip6dw     
    
    
    @essayareayaitch @Fitflix @ENERGYbits @maryeatsgreen @jmusso28 The pumpkin pancakes are a crowd-favorite! :-/ hmm...    
    
    
    @maryeatsgreen @jmusso28 THANKS! :)    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: The Secret Powers of Time, and are you past, present, or future oriented? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8ege54c  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #30 with Jimmy Moore - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d9ocadp  #paleo    
    
    
    FAQs: What are dense carb sources on a Paleo diet? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3bchn2p  #paleo    
    
    
    I tasted Jackson's Honest Chips last year at the Weston A. Price Foundation Conference and was IN LOVE with them.... http://fb.me/2G5AKmbMs     
    
    
    I just backed World's First Organic Coconut Oil Potato Chip on @Kickstarter http://kck.st/18w4B20  #realfood #jerf #delicious    
    
    
    @HonestChips @kickstarter backed- and shared :)    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Hot & Sweet Ginger-Garlic Chicken - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lp7jkpb  #paleo    
    
    
    BIG NEWS!!! 
(In case you missed this yesterday.) http://fb.me/2XSHP9KGT     
    
    
    @grokgrub @kickstarter I have, but I haven't tried the product yet - this one I have tried and it's insanely good!    
    
    
    5 Questions with Kelly Milton author of Paleo Happy Hour.  This week I am thrilled to share an inter http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880934457/ …    
    
    
    5 Questions with Caitlin Weeks Author of Mediterranean Paleo Cooking.  This week I am excited to sha http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880934460/ …    
    
    
    @HonestChips @kickstarter Awesome. I know @PrimalPalate shared it too :) We loved the chips when we tried them!    
    
    
    Nutrition in the NBA; Part I: Lessons learned in L.A. help Howard's career http://cbsprt.co/1bxJA7u  via @cbssports --> http://amzn.to/Wcpmqr     
    
    
    Nutrition in the NBA; Part I: Dwight Howard Q&A http://cbsprt.co/1hMStz0  via @cbssports #21DSD #nobread --> http://amzn.to/Wcpmqr     
    
    
    BIG NEWS GUYS. 
(In case you missed it yesterday).

Liz and I will be launching an ONLINE VERSION of our seminar... http://fb.me/2nyshGmcp     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #99: Non-Paleo Loved Ones, HIV, Footwear, and Blog Etiquette - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/mlxq6uv  #paleo    
    
    
    @JLeonard1622 :)    
    
    
    THANK YOU! ;) RT @FindUrBalance: .@balancedbites Got you listed in my healthy gift roundup! Thanks for being awesome. http://ow.ly/rGf8t     
    
    
    @FindUrBalance also- LOVE the new site design… mine's in progress so this is good inspiration!    
    
    
    @FindUrBalance @pjrvs Thanks for the tip - love his work :)    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger Ooh, lucky you!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #42: Fibromyalgia, Dexilant, Seasonal Allergies, Essential oils, Paleo on a cruise -... http://tinyurl.com/79enjh5  #paleo    
    
    
    @PaulArcu @hollyhoneyburke They are- as in the book! #practicalpaleo    
    
    
    How to: Find a good chiropractor. 

More practical advice from Dr. Scott A. Mills.... http://fb.me/6Cdv0WSEI     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #46: Adrenal Fatigue Part 3, with special guest Dr. Dan Kalish - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c9449nk  #paleo    
    
    
    Do you visit my website/blog? If so, is it usually after I've posted a link to it from here/you receive an email... http://fb.me/3vyTAFCZZ     
    
    
    @juliainor thanks!    
    
    
    @johndurant sounds so strangely familiar...    
    
    
    15 Delicious Lettuce-Wrap Ideas - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/busjq5g  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #25, Listener Questions, with guest Diana Rodgers - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7jre9d9  #paleo    
    
    
    FLORIDA FOLKS! This is the only event I'll have in your area - come meet me and ask your questions! 

I tried... http://fb.me/1dSFAlKt2     
    
    
    FLORIDA! This is your book signing event (my only event in your area!) - join me! --> http://balbit.es/19jUNZR  #naples #21DSD #practicalpaleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Spinach Salad with Fresh Mint & Orange Vinaigrette  #balancedbites #paleo #salads http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880939154/ …    
    
    
    Easy Baked Kale Chips  Here’s my recipe, but feel free to tinker with spices and toppings. Baked kal http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880939158/ …    
    
    
    *BIG UPCOMING EVENTS ANNOUNCEMENT*

I've got amazing friends joining me for the west coast tour! If you're coming... http://fb.me/16yyUAVnr     
    
    
    UPCOMING EVENTS! I'll be joined by @primalpalate for a bunch of dates and @nomnompaleo for one as well… http://instagram.com/p/h04gdEBr9_/     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #15 - Adrenal Fatigue, Part 1 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/75zur2f  #paleo    
    
    
    Wild cod was on sale at my WF this week. Topped it with some ghee, s&p, and homemade pesto and broiled 10 mins-... http://fb.me/1XFBFhAwA     
    
    
    How I'm eating it- over salad. [see precious pic for info on the fish] http://fb.me/10ppE9Su0     
    
    
    How I'm eating it, over salad [see previous pic for info on the fish] @kasandrinos EVOO on the salad with lemon... http://fb.me/33jCQsSTC     
    
    
    5 Questions with "Paleo Comfort Foods" Authors Julie & Charles Mayfield - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3dsf6td  #paleo    
    
    
    If there's one thing I sort of can't let go of as a graphic designer, it's the desire to constantly redesign my... http://fb.me/2qXHnzOmP     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #117: Handling haters, MSG in bone broth, bras & emotional recovery http://fb.me/1YNHJLPkb     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #117: Handling haters, MSG in bone broth, bras & emotional recovery http://nblo.gs/RWTyk     
    
    
    How to Find a “Good” Chiropractor | Dr. Scott A. Mills  #balancedbites #chiropractor #scottmills http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880940264/ …    
    
    
    @KBergCBS @drcateshanahan @robbwolf @Mark_Sisson @cookingcaveman @livinlowcarbman thanks!!    
    
    
    TONIGHT! See you at the Montclair NJ Public Library! 7pm - I'll have a copy of the #21dsdcookbook with… http://instagram.com/p/h1pMohhr1C/     
    
    
    Announcing: The Balanced Bites Podcast - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3hxbd4d  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast Episode 117 | Listener Q&A   Handling haters, MSG in bone broth, bras & emoti http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880940940/ …    
    
    
    OMG!!! Best package ever!!! eatingevolved chocolates http://instagram.com/p/h2C1c4hr60/     
    
    
    OMG!!! Best package ever!!! @eatingevolved chocolates http://fb.me/11760R4KR     
    
    
    What a fun night at the Montclair Public Library tonight! I had a great crowd and even a family from Australia... http://fb.me/1unj3JJhg     
    
    
    @juliainor @CaveGirlEats Classic. #iramble #shedoesnotlisten    
    
    
    @thecourtneykerr ha! good to know. #watching    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #64: Surviving the holidays - indulging, family & cocktails! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/co8hu6q  #paleo    
    
    
    Tomorrow begins 12 Days of Giveaways on the blog! My team has been working on this for weeks! They have such... http://fb.me/6mu3gZejM     
    
    
    @snooki check out primal life Organics all natural stuff    
    
    
    @snooki sometimes realizing what goes on kids' skin makes you realize what's on ours too ;-) #nojunk    
    
    
    FAQ: All about the book, Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8gaol2w  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 1 – Splits 59 & Rickaroons http://fb.me/1WpSGgGbR     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 1 – Splits 59 & Rickaroons http://nblo.gs/RXF3n     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #102: Candida, Paleo bread, nightly pee breaks and FODMAPs - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/kutvxuc  #paleo    
    
    
    [12 DAYS OF GIVEAWAYS] Starts today! Day #1 is BIG!! Enter over on the blog for a chance to win $250 from... http://fb.me/6tZ0GrJ5O     
    
    
    @juliacavagnaro NICE!    
    
    
    @sardo02 probably not if it's intended to thicken things as well as coat- maybe try a mix of coconut flour & arrowroot starch    
    
    
    "It's never a bad time to start a business unless you're starting a mediocre business." - @garyvee #crushit --> http://amzn.to/18Go9Om     
    
    
    @robbwolf @ChrisMasterjohn I think it's going to continue growing. The potential for helping to heal autoimmunity is the big pusher IMO    
    
    
    @robbwolf @ChrisMasterjohn vs "just a diet," looking better naked, or doing it bc crossfit (ahem, robb wolf) made it "cool"    
    
    
        
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast Episode #115 [encore]: Surviving the holidays - indulging, family & cocktails! -... http://tinyurl.com/m6jacjs  #paleo    
    
    
    Breakfast today: eggs, wild pickled herring (Blue Hill Bay brand) and Wellshire liverwurst - both from my Whole... http://fb.me/6y7GpzsNP     
    
    
    @Nutri2Fruition no corn- I listed the brand in the pic caption    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman @CaveGirlEats thanks!!!    
    
    
    @lftfitness @robbwolf @ChrisMasterjohn Well, realistically, many books out teach Paleo w/o naming it that #virgindiet #bloodsugarsolution    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #59: BIG news, weight loss time, non-paleo family, cold care & more! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bmyt2wc  #paleo    
    
    
    Day 1 of my 12 Days of Giveaways is live on the blog today! Don't miss the amazing gift from Splits 59 and Rickaroons! :) Happy Holidays!!    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! Thanks paleokits for this lovely gift! http://instagram.com/p/h3_n6mBr8T/     
    
    
    Balanced Bites- 12 Days of Giveaways!  In honor of all of you that have supported my work, I’ve team http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880944984/ …    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: "Freshness in a Glass" Green Juice  #greenjuice #balancedbites #juice http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880944989/ …    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #3 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/5rryqrq  #paleo    
    
    
    I truly appreciate every review left on Amazon of my books. I read them all, and this is the most recent one... http://fb.me/6xWTmnThz     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Mineral-Rich Bone Broth - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3lnnu5y  #paleo    
    
    
    @tallgirlswims @BrazenAthletics haha awesome!! :-)    
    
    
    Bacon: Health Food or Devil in Delicious Disguise? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3mclayh  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #72: Sarah of http://ThePaleoMom.com  talks Autoimmune & Paleo! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/b4kn8cd  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 2 – Real Skincare & The Skintervention Guide! http://fb.me/3x9vTQlpM     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 2 – Real Skincare & The Skintervention Guide! http://nblo.gs/S0Ipd     
    
    
    I received this email yesterday from Jennifer:

"Hey! 
I just wanted to write to you and tell you about my... http://fb.me/1FDc20Rfw     
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 2 - REAL skincare & the Skintervention Guide http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880948176/ …    
    
    
    Fresh Mango Salsa  - Salsa is a fantastic addition to loads of dishes including grilled meats, seafo http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880948182/ …    
    
    
    [12 DAYS OF GIVEAWAYS] Day 2 is all about SKINCARE from Real. and The Skintervention Guide!!!

Hop on over to the... http://fb.me/2rd5HncTv     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #61: Tattoos, "chicken skin," raw foods & blood sugar - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cp28fvx  #paleo    
    
    
    Come out to meet me and @primalpalate in January on the west coast! (Or hit up an east coast seminar… http://instagram.com/p/h6DouiBrz-/     
    
    
    It's time to announce our WINNER for Day 1 of the 12 Days of giveaways!

And the Lucky Fan is..... Alexandria... http://fb.me/1SJH7taTd     
    
    
    @gooberguz @PrimalPalate not in the plans    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #97: A rebuttal to Sally Fallon's Take on Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lxq8a25  #paleo    
    
    
    @gooberguz @PrimalPalate yeah, just not in the cards this trip    
    
    
    @thecourtneykerr @bluehost @shoegirlinNola I had to leave blue long ago for that reason. media temple has never crashed on me    
    
    
    @coachrut maybe you'll find one with my new book in it! #21daysugardetox #paleo    
    
    
    @MyIgnition @moonfitness :-)    
    
    
    @MyIgnition @tycolby @moonfitness that's my fave too!    
    
    
    Meet the team: Charissa Talbot - Communications Coordinator & The 21-Day Sugar Detox Lead Moderator -... http://tinyurl.com/aqno86a  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3rwl6hy  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #8 with guest Chris Kresser on digestion - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3pthwba  #paleo    
    
    
    Bites I Love: Steve's Original Paleo Kits, Grass-Fed Jerky and more! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6orqdqm  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 3 – Epic Bars, Omghee & Tropical Traditions! http://fb.me/2zfwq43kN     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 3 – Epic Bars, Omghee & Tropical Traditions! http://nblo.gs/S1QCE     
    
    
    @DocCarnahan @joeyandrory yay!    
    
    
    Book Review: "Wheat Belly" by William Davis, MD - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3hakq5m  #paleo    
    
    
    Day 2's winner is......

JESSICA PEREZ!

Jessica has won a sample pack from Real.l. and a free copy of Liz... http://fb.me/6BH23O5vf     
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 3 - Epic Bars, OMGHEE and tropical tradition http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880952861/ …    
    
    
    I know most of us here follow a grain-free way of eating (perhaps you call it Paleo, perhaps not), but I'm... http://fb.me/2LfswgIsB     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #19 - Paleo 101, part 2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7muqxbc  #paleo    
    
    
    A cold, grey Sunday on the couch with HGTV, football, and some homemade carrot soup. Recipe in the… http://instagram.com/p/h9GXkJBr2K/     
    
    
    @Running_Tall @DareYouToBlog awesome! If you didn't get a chance to review the book/program yet on amazon please take a moment to do so!    
    
    
    @goodcleanchow oooh!    
    
    
    @bckoskela it's my new fave way to make them!    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: One step at a time. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d2ce9kv  #paleo    
    
    
    With all the fun going on around here with my 12 Days of Giveaways, I almost forgot to remind you guys that my... http://fb.me/19ON13bpb     
    
    
    Do you have a humidifier that you love? If so, which one?! #winter    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #77: No thyroid, eyesight, female face hair & gym challenges - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/clfom4l  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Sautéed Red Cabbage with Onions & Apples - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/n3kbopa  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #17 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8yd9l5v  #paleo    
    
    
    Super exciting news... my podcasting and seminar-teaching partner-in-crime, Liz Wolfe (no relation to Robb Wolf,... http://fb.me/3zO2L8J8C     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 4 – All 3 Books from The Food Lovers Primal Palate & goodies from Cappell http://fb.me/1a9W9Bz7X     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 4 – All 3 Books from The Food Lovers Primal Palate & goodies from Cappellos! http://nblo.gs/S2Out     
    
    
    What's your biggest "In the kitchen" question these days? I've answered tons of questions on my blog in my FAQs... http://fb.me/3b9thmnJK     
    
    
    Rule #1 when it comes to eating REAL FOOD… #EatTheYolks --> http://balbit.es/Amazon_EatTheYolks …    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 4 - Make it paleo, 30 day guide to paleo, ga http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880957497/ …    
    
    
    Eat The Yolks by Liz Wolfe, NTP   Super exciting news... my podcasting and seminar-teaching partner- http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880957502/ …    
    
    
    NEW JERSEY! (And anyone within about two hours...) this is your event! Saturday, January 4th is… http://instagram.com/p/h_Df-Lhr9w/     
    
    
    "Gather: The Art of Paleo Entertaining" - Share the Paleo lifestyle with family & friends (and a... http://tinyurl.com/bu6rejk  #paleo    
    
    
    The Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways DAY 3 Winner is....

Memrie Rounsaville

Congratulations! Memrie has won... http://fb.me/1SbC0aRoN     
    
    
    PHILLY! This is your event - don't miss out... And maybe even save $20 by signing up early.… http://instagram.com/p/h_Wp6vhrzY/     
    
    
    As evidenced clearly each day @brazenathletics (where I WOD) RT @robbwolf: A different look at the #crossfit "cult" http://www.sweatandbutterjournal.com/2013/12/in-defense-of-your-crossfit-cult.html …    
    
    
    Lunch today is leftover Balsamic Braised Beef (recipe from Practical Paleo) over a boat-ton of steamed broccoli... http://fb.me/QZg3zNmk     
    
    
    FAQs: What is Paleo? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c5tcbku  #paleo    
    
    
    . @chriskresser @glutenfreegirl do you know of any hotels downtown with kitchens in the rooms? Efficiencies? Suites?    
    
    
    Ermagherd did you hear?! @cavegirleats has a real book releasing at the end of February! Go pre-order… http://instagram.com/p/h_t1T9BrwH/     
    
    
    @jensinkler you just made me think extra hard about your abbreviation. I had to google MT last week, this time, I got it w/o a google! ;)    
    
    
    If you pre-ordered "The 21-Day Sugar Detox Cookbook," it looks like it started shipping from Amazon today! Woot!    
    
    
    Satsuma + epicbar = delicious! Find where to get them or order online at http://epicbar.com  http://instagram.com/p/iACsJAhr6n/     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Spinach Salad with Fresh Mint & Orange Vinaigrette - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3kwl9d3  #paleo    
    
    
    I'm sitting here (impatiently) waiting for a batch of my Sweet & Sour Gummy Gelatin Snacks to set in the fridge.... http://fb.me/16Jq9SEUB     
    
    
    Practical Paleo Testimonial: Former vegan finds health - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ncl46ux  #paleo    
    
    
    5 Questions with "Well Fed" author Melissa Joulwan & a giveaway of her book! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6q9m5ss  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 5 – Books from Paleo Parents, Paleo Mom & 3 lbs of bacon! http://fb.me/2vKoombYA     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 5 – Books from Paleo Parents, Paleo Mom & 3 lbs of bacon! http://nblo.gs/S44op     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #68: Back to Basics - gut healing, leanness, calcium & Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ajun4lw  #paleo    
    
    
    My nutrition challenge is over... now what? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/882z6zg  #paleo    
    
    
    The Day 4 Winner of The 12 Days of Giveaways is...

Lori Carroll!

Lori has won Make it Paleo, The 30 Day Guide... http://fb.me/1eUg7MsFG     
    
    
    I've been busy in my kitchen lately (what else is new?!). Beef & garlic broth (recipe on my blog and in... http://fb.me/2HBOA4UK6     
    
    
    CrossFit-curious? Check out this new post from Dr. Scott A. Mills about his first year.... http://fb.me/2Q6QaaUhE     
    
    
    This is a snack to remind everyone to go pre-order @cavegirleats book, #EatTheYolks… http://instagram.com/p/iCBLGxBr0X/     
    
    
    A lot of what we teach in the seminar about fat and cholesterol (and your health) comes from what I've learned... http://fb.me/2xy5znrfc     
    
    
    Troubleshooting Your Digestive Issues: Tips for Common Digestive Issues in Pregnancy (part 4) - Bites... http://tinyurl.com/k6dm4zl  #paleo    
    
    
    @HeatherJ0611 nice!    
    
    
    So, I posted something pretty important for you all to read here just about an hour ago, but since it included a... http://fb.me/LIV9WH56     
    
    
    I'm making the caldo verde (green soup) recipe from the #21dsdcookbook today but I'm subbing in beef… http://instagram.com/p/iCSRIfBr4G/     
    
    
    I'm skipping the purée step since I have carrots in here and don't want an orange soup :-) about to… http://instagram.com/p/iCTJ6Dhr5N/     
    
    
    This is hilarious! Hash-tagging your spices and sauces may be one of the most brilliant #21DSD ideas… http://instagram.com/p/iCUJ7WBr60/     
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 5 - Eat Like a Dinosaur, Beyond Bacon, The P http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880964170/ …    
    
    
    So, "The 21-Day Sugar Detox Cookbook" officially released today... did you order one or grab a copy at a store... http://fb.me/15r2WB1kF     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #1 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3fnwtlo  #paleo    
    
    
    I absolutely LOVE reading your reviews and experiences with the 21DSD program in reviews on Amazon. 

Tag friends... http://fb.me/6xrnsvg3K     
    
    
    .@phineasflapdood a follow is yours!    
    
    
    @AmandaLaura626 Thank you! I shared it I think on the FB page!! ;)    
    
    
    @phineasflapdood Ha! Awesome! Thanks!    
    
    
    Preview of some of the recipe photos from the #21DSDcookbook #21DSD - it released today! --> http://amzn.to/WmUpjb  pic.twitter.com/tzwReb6ugU    
    
    
    Looking for 100+ tasty and sweetener-free Paleo, gluten-free, grain-free recipes? 

Guess what? 

That's EXACTLY... http://fb.me/2IKhQe3kR     
    
    
    Fresh Blueberry Crumble  When you’re looking for a quick and easy dessert, baking fruit with a nutty http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880965275/ …    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #62: Vampire hands, thyroid, binge eating recovery, ex vegan, not menstruating? -... http://tinyurl.com/a7l9hm7  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #38: All About Poop - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6wt7r45  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 6 – Primal Life Organics & OraWellness! http://fb.me/6kSmEhD9M     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 6 – Primal Life Organics & OraWellness! http://nblo.gs/S7jU9     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Pumpkin Pancakes from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/979a6ok  #paleo    
    
    
    Hey folks! If you have completed a #21DSD before and have the new book, would you take just a moment… http://instagram.com/p/iEMA7PBr8y/     
    
    
    Just 5 days left to save $20 on our NJ Seminar! 

The event is all day on Saturday, January 4th at Brazen... http://fb.me/19pVlngfn     
    
    
    @dietitiancassie @maximumPR @KellyOC @livinlowcarbman @tomnikkola Don't know of any.    
    
    
    @dietitiancassie @CaveGirlEats Right?! #worst    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Garlic & Dill Vegetables - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6lwacvh  #paleo    
    
    
    It's time to announce our 12 Days of Giveaways DAY 5 WINNER!!! 

Congratulations, Brooke Silberhorn!!

Brooke has... http://fb.me/2AgmSG8It     
    
    
    It's time to announce our 12 Days of Giveaways DAY 5 WINNER!!!

Congratulations, Brooke Silberhorn!!

Brooke has... http://fb.me/3v69tBiVG     
    
    
    It's time to announce our 12 Days of Giveaways DAY 5 WINNER!!!

Congratulations, Brooke Silberhorn!!

Brooke has... http://fb.me/6FfRKuXz3     
    
    
    @CaveGirlEats @dittobritto Lots of great comments on the podcast blog post, too.    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 6 - Primal Life Organics & Orawellness  #bal http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880967792/ …    
    
    
    Did you get my FREE 60-page Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook? It'll help make your Christmas dinner complete!

Yes?... http://fb.me/TjT2DiOW     
    
    
    @PaleoNut88 @CaveGirlEats Last week, #117  - just one question.    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #50: Canola, Paleo Newbie, Sensitivities, Adrenal Support - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cdkfoyg  #paleo    
    
    
    @ruthwalters @BangsandaBun start here --> http://amzn.to/practicalpaleo     
    
    
    Amazon's top new nutrition books - good company. #21dsdcookbook #eattheyolks http://instagram.com/p/iFGPfHBr17/     
    
    
    Jumpstart your #PRIMAL lifestyle w/ @JennaPhillips on her retreat in Fiji, February 7th-15th. Check this out! http://balbit.es/1dPke4O     
    
    
    @sub3mike81 AWESOME! :) happy holidays!    
    
    
    I'm finalizing my FAQs about The 21-Day Sugar Detox Cookbook blog post now... what questions do you have about... http://fb.me/2UHAXxeVI     
    
    
    @PaulArcu @JennaPhillips Pretty certain it isn't an $11k trip    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #5 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3aspyvl  #paleo    
    
    
    @PaulArcu @JennaPhillips Why would your first reaction to my sharing that information be to assume it was insanely expensive? #strange    
    
    
    @PaulArcu @JennaPhillips why would I share a seemingly impossible-to-take trip with my followers? I'm not elitist.    
    
    
    Meet the team: Liz Wolfe - Balanced Bites Partner & Nutritionist - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cq7spbt  #paleo    
    
    
    .@sjp on #WWHL - her hair is AMAZING as always. <3    
    
    
    @geraldineaugust AWESOME!    
    
    
    @iuhill @sjp I can see how a very young viewer might not!    
    
    
    Don't forget to visit the blog today (and for the next 5 days!) to enter to win my 12 Days of Giveaways! 

Today... http://fb.me/6z6N2IFMP     
    
    
    @geraldineaugust Awesome! I enjoyed those even (maybe better?!) the next day - I made them with the cook-out coleslaw, yum!    
    
    
    My take on: Flax, chia, juice cleanses, green smoothies & juicing - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/n6oy5dw  #paleo    
    
    
    Welcome Mark's Daily Apple 21-Day Primal Blueprint Challenge Participants! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9dx3jpx  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 7 – The 21 Day Sugar Detox books & one-on-one support for your 21 days! http://fb.me/2huv0td3E     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 7 – The 21 Day Sugar Detox books & one-on-one support for your 21 days! http://nblo.gs/S924r     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 7 – The 21 Day Sugar Detox books & one-on-one support for your 21 days! http://fb.me/39YQeE6Dh     
    
    
    Hey Canada, heads up! Repost: from @aglaeepaleord "Not too long ago, Health Canada decided that the term coconut... http://fb.me/2VQ7MKRJU     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #9 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6kz9gm4  #paleo    
    
    
    The 12 Days of Giveaways, Day 6 winner is...

Tina Bean!!!

Tina has won prizes from OraWellness and Primal Life... http://fb.me/2MCQ3MbSG     
    
    
    This travel humidifier worked (at home) beautifully last night - I didn't wake up coughing once! #winning #minithings http://amzn.to/J7NKsF     
    
    
    @grokgrub Top right corner of the website -blue box! :)    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 7 | 21 day sugar detox book and cookbook, pl http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880971364/ …    
    
    
    @CheriStammen Thanks! :)    
    
    
    @CheriStammen We have @graphicdsigns to thank for that design!    
    
    
    My piping hot bowl of Portuguese Caldo Verde (with carrots b/c I didn't have parsnips) - recipe from the... http://fb.me/374FQ9x1f     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #118: All about Liz Wolf’s new book “Eat the Yolks” http://fb.me/13bdjxWcb     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #118: All about Liz Wolf’s new book “Eat the Yolks” http://nblo.gs/S9ue5     
    
    
    I went to record a podcast and came back to find you all freaking out about my soup picture...    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Italian Sausage Spice Blend - from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d2hasyu  #paleo    
    
    
    Today's lunch is Creamy Mushroom Soup from the #21dsdcookbook with sardines topped with @kasandrinos EVOO & hot... http://fb.me/1egq6jCRc     
    
    
    @thecourtneykerr site is down again while the show is airing… seriously look into @mediatemple    
    
    
    @mediatemple consider that my referral if you host her site :) That darned site is always down when they air her show! :(    
    
    
    @mediatemple Oooh! :) Awesome!    
    
    
    Hey folks! Y'all are clear that I have TWO new books out right now, right? 

The 21-Day Sugar Detox (guide book)... http://fb.me/15IhQxJk4     
    
    
    FAQs: How will I get calcium on a Paleo diet? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/4xmlzl9  #paleo    
    
    
    A text message I just got from cousin who I gifted Practical Paleo "Starts reading Practical Paleo, eats spaghetti... http://fb.me/XjpXxhEB     
    
    
    The Balanced Bites Podast Episode 118 | All about Liz's NEW boook - Eat the Yolks  #balancedbites #c http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880973092/ …    
    
    
    @mediatemple I don't have an aff link    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Greek-Style Lamb Meatballs - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d72sx78  #paleo    
    
    
    Hey folks, hopefully this helps! Click on it to see it closer/read the details. I'll be adding it to my post... http://fb.me/6jBdIDnmD     
    
    
    Hey folks, hopefully this helps! Click on it to see it closer/read the details. I'll be adding it to my post... http://fb.me/2snKQtBYK     
    
    
    The 21-Day Sugar Detox Review Round-up #2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/mcevncz  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #116: Special Guest Melissa Joulwan, Author of Well Fed 2 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/q3aqr4k  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 8 – Steve’s Paleo Goods, Red Boats Fish Sauce & a copy of Rich Food Poor http://fb.me/2ad1bug4t     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 8 – Steve’s Paleo Goods, Red Boats Fish Sauce & a copy of Rich Food Poor F... http://nblo.gs/SavPk     
    
    
    @cookinuplife yum!    
    
    
    @skyrudich love lamb!    
    
    
    @caralills @paleOMG nice!    
    
    
    @brianmovement thanks! Are you planning on starting in jan?    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #88: Guest Danielle Walker of "Against All Grain" - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/nr633gz  #paleo    
    
    
    The 12 Days of giveaways Day 7 winner is....

Alicia Sonde!!!

Alicia has won a copy of The 21 Day Sugar Detox... http://fb.me/QZdLUldL     
    
    
    In case you missed the post I made last night... this should help to clarify what's in each of my new books. I'll... http://fb.me/2Evvz8UJX     
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 8 - Steve's Paleo Goods, Rich Food, Poor Foo http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880976539/ …    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #112: Listener Q&A - Laser Hair Removal, Monthly Sugar Cravings & Brain Fog - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/km42osx  #paleo    
    
    
    Pork chops from my 1/2 hog (seasoned with salt, pepper, and garlic) are getting seared for 2 mins per side over... http://fb.me/2SI8uYKTI     
    
    
    Real Life Changes - Lori's Story "Small Tweaks Matter... Go Paleo" - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3vlyxp2  #paleo    
    
    
    Monday Motivation: Setbacks & Failures - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/m2ag297  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Lemon Rosemary Broiled Salmon - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/73p9dqv  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 9 – Cholesterol Clarity, Paleo Treats & Justin’s Nut Butters http://fb.me/2Y69O9uDt     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 9 – Cholesterol Clarity, Paleo Treats & Justin’s Nut Butters http://nblo.gs/SbUsu     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Smoky Mexican Tortilla-less Soup - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bzbf82q  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 9 - Cholesterol Clarity, Justin's Nut Butter http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880979780/ …    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Grain-Free Magic Cookie Bars           SUGAR ALERT!!! I’m taking this opportunity to ma http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880979791/ …    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Not-So-Sweet Chocolate Walnut Truffles     I love chocolate. There is no way around it. http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880979795/ …    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Spaghetti Squash Bolognese from Practical Paleo (And more ideas for replacing pasta!) -... http://tinyurl.com/c2nons7  #paleo    
    
    
    The 12 Days of Giveaways Day 8 Winner is....

Kelly King!!! 

Kelly has won prizes from @PaleoKits PaleoKits by... http://fb.me/6q5rBdON9     
    
    
    @starlight36 hmm... What kind of biz?    
    
    
    @starlight36 Too much to tweet…    
    
    
    @PaleoProfessor Fantastic, glad you love it - and thank YOU.    
    
    
    The fabulous Melissa Joulwan (of WellFed and WellFed 2 fame and The Clothes Make The Girl) has a new post about... http://fb.me/3cS1CJZ5e     
    
    
    Practical Paleo is now a New York Times Bestseller! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cxpadls  #paleo    
    
    
    FLORIDA PEEPS! Don't miss your only event coming up - a book signing at CrossFit Redline in Naples on 12/27.... http://fb.me/6CqsRbP4a     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #117: Handling haters, MSG in bone broth, bras & emotional recovery - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/p8swnww  #paleo    
    
    
    Hoboken! If you've been waiting for an amazing CrossFit gym in your area - brazenathletics will be IT!!! http://instagram.com/p/iM8IYUBr4t/     
    
    
    Real Life Changes - Emma's Story: A yoga teacher gone Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bw6bp33  #paleo    
    
    
    @cookinuplife Those are a fan-favorite and there's a 21DSD version, too!    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways (update) -- don't forget to enter the giveaway today on the blog and for the next three... http://fb.me/2w7eU6xDN     
    
    
        
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 10 – Tessemae’s & a copy of Against All Grain: Delectable Paleo Recipes t http://fb.me/Saia7SpP     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 10 – Tessemae’s & a copy of Against All Grain: Delectable Paleo Recipes to... http://nblo.gs/Sev8X     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Buffalo Chicken Egg Muffins - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d3lpvyp  #paleo    
    
    
    @BrainboxCoach yum!    
    
    
    UPCOMING EVENTS:

12/27/13: Naples, FL (book signing w/ Q&A)
1/4/14: Fairfield, NJ (Balanced Bites Seminar)... http://fb.me/1eJuR8mD1     
    
    
    Day 9 winner is.......

 Renee Howe!!!!

Renee has won prizes from Paleo Treats: Rations for the Driven, Justin's... http://fb.me/1dkhBQifx     
    
    
    Our Top Five Chocolate Obsessions - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6rljbbn  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 10 - Against All Grain & Tessamaes dressing  http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880984977/ …    
    
    
    Ice pops are a fantastic, nostalgic treat, but clearly what’s available in stores is an array of ove http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880984993/ …    
    
    
    Yes! brazenathletics / CrossFit Willlow is taking over this globo!!! #bebrazenordontbother http://instagram.com/p/iPAOQnhr4q/     
    
    
    Monday Motivation: I used to hate my thighs. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7medq8m  #paleo    
    
    
    @BrainboxCoach awesome!    
    
    
    @prettynpaleo I honestly have no idea - that was a post from MANY years ago… :-/    
    
    
    @lucyindasky Awesome! Hope to see you there!    
    
    
    Did you grab a copy of "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" at a local bookstore or Costco? 

If so, where? Tell me what... http://fb.me/2r3NQzq94     
    
    
    [NEW POST] FAQs: All about The 21-Day Sugar Detox Cookbook -->... http://fb.me/6AXUDTAmT     
    
    
    FAQs: All about The 21-Day Sugar Detox COOKBOOK http://fb.me/3ryqcnrRB     
    
    
    FAQs: All about The 21-Day Sugar Detox COOKBOOK http://nblo.gs/Sf98x     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #60: Omega 6 fats, quitting caffeine, hypoglycemia, sardines & more - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d5yvozh  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Crockpot braised lamb shanks (Osso Buco) with tomato sauce - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/d8ruzr5  #paleo    
    
    
    Who is giving/asking for/maybe already GOT one of my books as a holiday gift this year? Which book? And why are... http://fb.me/2aJQTruSm     
    
    
    SO many of you had amazing responses to the question I posted about an hour ago - I decided to pick TWO winners... http://fb.me/3scp8wU1L     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #98: Fermented with Jill Ciciarelli - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/mxbot99  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #13 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/6nwfgvl  #paleo    
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 11 – A copy of Practical Paleo and one-on-one nutrition coaching! http://fb.me/2LjOd9ewQ     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 11 – A copy of Practical Paleo and one-on-one nutrition coaching! http://nblo.gs/SfAxP     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #53: Shift work, coffee, skin care secrets & more! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9cayrvb  #paleo    
    
    
    Happy Monday! The new year is upon us, and I want to PUSH you to ask yourself the HARD QUESTIONS. Life and HEALTH... http://fb.me/2WRluRtXV     
    
    
    The Balanced Bites 12 Days of giveaways day 10 Winner is... 

Jessica Braley!!!

Jessica has won prizes from... http://fb.me/UzfJVXyR     
    
    
    We've got TONS of folks starting a 21-Day Sugar Detox in January! If you're one of them, please comment below and... http://fb.me/2TrbBlwGg     
    
    
    If you're cooking a holiday meal in the next few days, be sure to grab my FREE Healthy Holiday Recipes eBook if... http://fb.me/2DRUBPnCU     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #27 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/76hden2  #paleo    
    
    
    @Fitnationmag Awesome! :)    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #4 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3poygo2  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 11 - Practical Paleo and Wellness Coaching   http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880991617/ …    
    
    
    @erinash612 @21daysugardetox I think talking to your doctor about it is a good idea. I might say Energy mods though as a starting point.    
    
    
    @EveHandmade ;-)    
    
    
    Healthy cooking fats: it's not JUST about smoke point, it's also important to consider how STABLE the fat is (how... http://fb.me/1b8xDXRTk     
    
    
    @KelseyAlbers @CaveGirlEats YESSSS!!!    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Pumpkin Custard (or Crustless Pumpkin Pie)  #balancedbites #pumpkin #pumpkincustard http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880991976/ …    
    
    
    If you missed my previous post on choosing healthy cooking fats, click on over to the page to check it out!    
    
    
    Tonight I made my Lemon & Artichoke chicken and added capers and cauliflower! #winning #delish… http://instagram.com/p/iSdV36Br49/     
    
    
    FAQs: How can I eat Paleo on a budget? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8nfyeqe  #paleo    
    
    
    Featured Chef for July at US Wellness Meats - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3v4r39w  #paleo    
    
    
    One signed copy of "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" at Newark Airport, Terminal C across from gate 103 - have at it! http://fb.me/2n1GNRj1M     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 12 – Paleo Happy Hour & Eating Evolved! http://fb.me/R3VOMKu8     
    
    
    12 Days of Giveaways – Day 12 – Paleo Happy Hour & Eating Evolved! http://nblo.gs/SgOZW     
    
    
    Balanced Bites 12 Days of Giveaways | ENTER TO WIN! Day 12 - Paleo Happy Hour & Eating Evolved  #bal http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604880994049/ …    
    
    
    Practical Paleo release: My thoughts and thanks. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8advrks  #paleo    
    
    
    The Day 11 Winner for the 12 Days of Giveaways is....

Agata! 

Congratulations! You have won a copy of Practical... http://fb.me/6yyz8DrbB     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #69: Talking nutrient synergy with Dr. Chris Masterjohn! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ahk93fh  #paleo    
    
    
    @goodcleanchow yummy!    
    
    
    @AmyMyersMD they are so good!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Merry Christmas from Naples, FL! http://fb.me/3eY2Wxbs3     
    
    
    Practical Paleo Book Extras: 30-Day Meal Plan Shopping Lists - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cnesmao  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #45: Women, Body Image, Emotional Eating, and Real Health - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bqhhxyp  #paleo    
    
    
    @TheYoungRetiree :-) yay!    
    
    
    @AmyMyersMD :-)    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #81: Salt, Shakeology, yeast infections, & calorie counting - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bs5mqrw  #paleo    
    
    
    What research says (and does not say) about the flu shot - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/at9euay  #paleo    
    
    
    @PencilsPancakes @againstallgrain awesome! Do you also have the #21dsdbook ?    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Monday Motivation: The World is Your Oyster - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3ob7rbm  #paleo    
    
    
    @pacho_mama HA- yes!    
    
    
    Okay, I know @GaryVee is just following me now - NJ, now Naples, FL! :-) #jabjab #jerseypeoplerock    
    
    
    Merry Christmas @hgtv #loveholiday from Naples, FL pic.twitter.com/c5arJ3wQfh    
    
    
    @k_m_owens @againstallgrain @PrimalPalate nice!!!    
    
    
    @jstoneaccessory @nomnompaleo woot!!!    
    
    
    @xeoth not sure but probably lard.    
    
    
    @xeoth use my cooking fats guide    
    
    
    I'm nervous that Mariah's earrings are going to rip right off of her ears! #heavybling #bublespecial    
    
    
    @hafilipowicz @Scottamillsdc thought the same thing, but I am willing to bet not #queenofchristmas #wwhl    
    
    
    @ttsocb5 WOOT!!!    
    
    
    If you're anywhere near Naples, FL on Friday (Dec 27), I'd love to see you at my book signing at CrossFit... http://fb.me/3ejnDcYz0     
    
    
    FAQ: How do I treat (or prevent) a cold or flu naturally? [with video] - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/q3c2x72  #paleo    
    
    
    How to: Make Clarified Butter or Ghee - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c3oqlte  #paleo    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #10 with guest Robb Wolf - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7fpwlaz  #paleo    
    
    
    @Lerryn_G awesome! We also have a huge group kicking off on Monday 1/6!    
    
    
    At Food & Thought Organic Market in Naples, FL - I could definitely live here! (I make my own but the fact that... http://fb.me/RBWYRVAg     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Vanilla Bean Coconut Ice Pops - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/b4pa85w  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #119: White potatoes, natural sweeteners and calcium supplements http://fb.me/2kxHqsWaN     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #119: White potatoes, natural sweeteners and calcium supplements http://nblo.gs/SkI1R     
    
    
    Holiday Treats Recipe Round-Up, and a Grain-Free Chocolate Eclair Recipe from The Paleo Mom - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bgwhee3  #paleo    
    
    
    Awesome lunch with @redlinealid13 @redlinecoach and @scottamillsdc at @thecounter here in Naples, FL :-)... http://fb.me/RORWFHmM     
    
    
    Heads up folks! The official start date for the first 21-Day Sugar Detox / #21DSD of 2014 will be Monday, January... http://fb.me/39ketgCSd     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #23: Micronutrients & Disease: "Naked Calories" authors Jayson & Mira... http://tinyurl.com/7cp8hqt  #paleo    
    
    
    @Craig_Albert @Scottamillsdc @CounterBurger as always! Hope to see you in the north east sooner than later!    
    
    
    @brothafree so awesome!    
    
    
    FLORIDA! Don't miss out on this free event tomorrow evening - my only one in the state. Starts at 6pm - hope to... http://fb.me/6CjclOUuD     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #37: Low-Carb Cruise, Nutrition Ed., FODMAPs, Carbs & Satiety? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bw2mvh2  #paleo    
    
    
    Healthy Holiday Recipes E-Book: 24 Paleo Recipes for Any Occasion [FREE!] - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/pevyvsz  #paleo    
    
    
    Points of Performance: Speed &amp; Strength (Part 1) - How do your lifts stack up? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/8avadwd  #paleo    
    
    
    Did you get one of my books for Christmas this week? If so, which one?

Are you joining us for The 21-Day Sugar... http://fb.me/2CNR7Fny6     
    
    
    Happy Birthday to the one and only @livinlowcarbman !!!    
    
    
    NEW JERSEY (and NY/CT area folks, too!) this is your event! Come spend a day with us @brazenathletics and learn... http://fb.me/6jQTcKgHf     
    
    
    @stephanodda not sure what you mean. My site is http://balancedbites.com     
    
    
    5 Questions with "30-Day Intro to Paleo" eBook authors Bill Staley & Hayley Mason - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/k3spzg6  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    @sarahvrose woot!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @TheCavemomma great to see you again!!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #86: Talking Paleo pregnancy, baby & books with Arsy! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/be2m5ho  #paleo    
    
    
    My thanks to @redlinecoach and everyone at CrossFit Redline for the hospitality today - my phone isn't letting me... http://fb.me/RjaEHNKj     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #44: Michelle of Nom Nom Paleo talks about feeding a busy Paleo family - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/84s4rh9  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    Heads up to my Kindle users who own "Practical Paleo" - I believe an update is available for you now via Amazon.... http://fb.me/1Tgvisb1o     
    
    
    Three of the top 9 nutrition books on Amazon right now (kindle version in there too) - pretty amazing!... http://fb.me/6pvRz8IGt     
    
    
    @slbrewer10 @againstallgrain woot!    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #18 - Paleo 101, part 1 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7u4em74  #paleo    
    
    
    A cute little health food shop on Marco Island, FL - found a new brand of coconut aminos, too but this one has... http://fb.me/2xfCJ05MA     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #67: The Beauty-cast! Acne, dark circles, & Paleo skincare - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bx6mjhg  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    Had a really fantastic meal at @thelocalnaples tonight! Grass-fed rib eye and a pork shoulder - gluten-free... http://fb.me/6jx59dEE7     
    
    
        
    
    
    @pacho_mama @CaveGirlEats :)    
    
    
    @punzel @21daysugardetox woot!    
    
    
    @OliviaOfLovely @continuants yep, no sweeteners on the #21dsd http://www.21dsd.com     
    
    
    @punzel @21daysugardetox yay!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #91: All things digestion - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/lbb8nrf  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #118: All about Liz Wolfe's new book "Eat the Yolks" - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/ppqemgk  #paleo    
    
    
    My Advice on Turning Nutrition Education Into a Career - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3kmhcey  #paleo    
    
    
    Thanks to @livesolafide from @flametofork for this pic! Both #21dsd books at her local @wholefoods… http://instagram.com/p/igSf9iBrzv/     
    
    
    @bflay do you weight train too?    
    
    
    Leftover grass-fed rib eye from @thelocalnaples last night is turned into a breakfast salad today! Noms. #paleo http://fb.me/Yw3EP6lM     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #119: White potatoes, natural sweeteners & calcium supplements  #balancedbites #podc http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604881018929/ …    
    
    
    [NEW POST] How to get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox --> http://balbit.es/21dsdgetstarted     
    
    
    How to get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox http://fb.me/22yuhmcOw     
    
    
    How to get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox http://nblo.gs/SpdEO     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #57: Hormones, multivitamins, post-op & special diets (oh my!) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9yyjmv2  #paleo    
    
    
    How do I get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox?” This post is here to help you get started, and for  http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604881019260/ …    
    
    
    [NEW POST!] How to get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox! Please share it and tag friends so they can… http://instagram.com/p/igsXUnhrwT/     
    
    
    "How to get started on The 21-Day Sugar Detox" -- new post up on the blog today -- linked also from the page here,... http://fb.me/N1cKfx0n     
    
    
    If you don't already have a spiralizer (used for making zucchini or other veggie "noodles" as shown in several of... http://fb.me/2T1YblrP5     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #35: Mineral deficiency, Hormonal Issues & Skin Help - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7qjwkq4  #paleo    
    
    
    @DeeFitty Brooke doesn't run the twitter account :-)    
    
    
    Hey folks - a heads up... 

If you feel like you are doing well with your eating habits, that you don't need to... http://fb.me/T6oJIqih     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #100: Ask us (almost) anything! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qh9g4fy  #paleo    
    
    
    SAN DIEGO FOLKS! 

I'm heading your way with my friends Hayley & Bill of Primal Palate fame on Sunday, 1/12 for a... http://fb.me/6xcmaFjrj     
    
    
    @Mock1 I have several blog posts up on these topics- check the site balanced http://balbit.es/1hOWQai     
    
    
    @Mock1 the short answer: most of it is entirely new content- the core of the program is the same, but the actual book content is new    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Bacon-Wrapped Smoky Chicken Thighs from Practical Paleo - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/84cs9xf  #paleo    
    
    
    Veria Voices: Health & wellness experts - video introductions and giveaways! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/blz8kpe  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #94: The Food Lovers dish & talk 30 days of Paleo cooking - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/n45zed3  #paleo    
    
    
    @Mock1 cool. I recommend the books in print but whatever suits your needs!    
    
    
    @jensinkler @werkingrl lol! I used to be a gummy candy fiend. Back in the day...    
    
    
    @ang_84 way way back I was on blogger free- but everyone uses wordpress now. Paid. I'd recommend you just go for it. t isn't pricey-worth it    
    
    
    @alainapettus yes!!    
    
    
    @CookingCaveman @ang_84 oh I see we basically said the same thing! So yeah, that :-)    
    
    
    Why do we want to make changes in the New Year? Are we more successful if we do so? Check out this video. 

I... http://fb.me/1eUDqSYtT     
    
    
    @BryanBallart @PrimalPalate We both live on the east coast and have events locally and semi-locally regularly, so no specific tour.    
    
    
    @BryanBallart I'm teaching in NJ (1/4) and Philly (1/25) in the coming weeks and have a signing in CT as well (1/5).    
    
    
        
    
    
    @BryanBallart @PaleoBakehouse wasn't in miami- no plans tho.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @BryanBallart baked goodies? I am allergic to tree nuts and am also starting a #21DSD soon so probably not the best time ;)    
    
    
    NEW JERSEY! 

Kick off 2014 with so much information about nutrition & health that your head might explode ;)... http://fb.me/15EZABqGp     
    
    
        
    
    
    Podcast Episode #109: Special Guest John Durant of The Paleo Manifesto - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/mtvuz6s  #paleo    
    
    
    @tysummerlin @nomnompaleo @Mark_Sisson considering they sold out of all of their copies of "Practical Paleo," I'd say they see reason to ;)    
    
    
    @savannahxolynn I would follow what she says that feels right for you. White rice is fairly innocuous if you feel good eating it.    
    
    
    A recent review of "Practical Paleo" on Amazon from AVinje:

"My husband and I have been on again off again... http://fb.me/2dsUuWHuV     
    
    
    Anyone know if it's possible to use an iPhone 4 as a wireless "mic pack" and play the sound via wireless bluetooth speaker like a jam box?    
    
    
    @BadAssPaleo @primalpower WOOT!!! :) Which store??    
    
    
    @savannahxolynn You can get more carbs and less protein other ways as well- I have a whole chart of carb sources on my blog.    
    
    
    @savannahxolynn and in my book.    
    
    
    @BadAssPaleo @primalpower sweet!    
    
    
    @mandy1965 thanks - will look into it.    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #82: Carb confusion, gout, thyroid & plateaus, baby food - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/c8tjs9m  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mandiclossey YESSSS!    
    
    
    @Chelsea_Maier @mikaCORR ha! Glad you enjoy!    
    
    
    @ttsocb5 awesome! Glad to hear it!    
    
    
    One of the best 100% dark chocolate to eat. Very smooth and tasty. The other brand I find edible at 100% is... http://fb.me/2pfj7isn7     
    
    
    Merry Christmas to us! New Instagram wall art in our home :-) starring@guster http://instagram.com/p/ikabJSBrzp/     
    
    
    If you're joining us for the HUGE kick-off of the #21DSD on Monday, January 6th, make sure you sign up for our... http://fb.me/1fgNZp0th     
    
    
    Joining us for the HUGE #21DSD on 1/6? Sign up for FREE Daily Detox Emails, delivered to your inbox --> http://bit.ly/21DSDemails     
    
    
    @mandiclossey @DrKarenOsburn ditto!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #33, Special Edition: The Surprising Truth about Olive Oil! - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cvoco9a  #paleo    
    
    
    @anille67 @jbrookshire01 @coconut this is covered in the book    
    
    
    @ADashofMeg woot!    
    
    
    @DrKarenOsburn yes.    
    
    
    FAQs: All about The 21-Day Sugar Detox COOKBOOK - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qzw87m3  #paleo    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #114: Hair loss, acne, cooking fats, Rejuvelac, zero impact living & dairy - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/p3r2ndn  #paleo    
    
    
    @anille67 @jbrookshire01 @COCONUT in every yes/no list    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #51: Eczema, psoriasis, fuel for running & more. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/98ft6ld  #paleo    
    
    
    @mmlivingstonexo chocolate usually is, coconut is usually not- you can also ask @ThePaleoMom for more details    
    
    
    @FMFBlogger awesome! Tons are in!    
    
    
    Who here is taking on The 21-Day Sugar Detox in January?!

If you want to start your 21DSD tomorrow, go right... http://fb.me/6rsny6TRo     
    
    
    @SerenaMarieRD :)    
    
    
    @shellabarger313 my fave!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Who here has decided to go Paleo in 2014? The Squeaky Clean 30-Day Meal Plan in "Practical Paleo" can be your... http://fb.me/1fvVFOWi2     
    
    
    Sign up for FREE Daily Detox Emails now to get ready for Monday, 1/6 --> http://bit.ly/21DSDemails  http://instagram.com/p/imitSwhr2O/     
    
    
    Sign up for FREE Daily Detox Emails now to get ready for Monday, 1/6 --> http://bit.ly/21DSDemails  http://fb.me/2zqtO8KrM     
    
    
    Ready to kick sugar & carb cravings to the curb?! A HUGE group kicks off on Monday, January 6th! 

How to get... http://fb.me/1T5QiWmMI     
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #26 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7xyztgr  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Spaghetti Sauce  #balancedbites #21dsd #spaghettisauce http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604881033915/ …    
    
    
    Moo-Less Chocolate Mousse Whoa, it’s been AGES since I even thought about making pudding. Not only h http://pinterest.com/pin/242842604881033927/ …    
    
    
    Introducing The Healthy Baby Code by Chris Kresser, L.Ac. - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/432kp2m  #paleo    
    
    
    @livinlowcarbman Thank you!!!    
    
    
    @SummersDaze YES!    
    
    
    @Grain_is_bad have you been to my blog? One of my most popular posts is on fclo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Raw Sauerkraut - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7u56exe  #paleo    
    
    
    Autoimmune Protocol for Paleo - we need your feedback - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/afcv7oa  #paleo    
    
    
    Happy New Year!!!

The 21-Day Sugar Detox kicks off in five days on Monday, January 6th! 

There's still time to... http://fb.me/1aDsI7Qzs     
    
    
    Are you paralyzing others with Paleo Perfectionism? - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/crxzmfw  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    Question for those of you who had "The 21-Day Sugar Detox" PDF eBooks and who NOW have the printed book as... http://fb.me/3DyOT0If3     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #111:Self love, body image & shifting perception - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/m5bz6xm  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    @bckoskela YUM!    
    
    
    @triNGathlete where are you reading that? page #?    
    
    
    @triNGathlete Just was intended to mean that I don't recommend eating lots of those items listed even if you want to eat g-free...    
    
    
    @triNGathlete but they don't contain gluten- which was the main point of the chart - to explain where it is/isn't. that said, I think that    
    
    
    @triNGathlete in an update at some point I will probably move arrowroot elsewhere.I think it's okay in small amounts here & there for starch    
    
    
    @triNGathlete It's an okay source of starch, though I prefer folks to use whole-food forms versus flours most often.    
    
    
    @triNGathlete and… thanks ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Tomorrow's podcast episode features guest Chris Kresser L.Ac talking with me all about his new book, "Your... http://fb.me/12eaE1KD7     
    
    
    Halloween Recipe Round-up (and a spook-tacular 21DSD-friendly treat recipe!) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/pxktwz8  #paleo    
    
    
    Chronic Lyme Disease: Kevin's Inspiring Practical Paleo Testimonial - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/bvuu6g3  #paleo    
    
    
    @ThePBQ I have literally heard it ALL.    
    
    
    What healthy habits are you excited to put into place (or to keep!) in 2014? 

I'll start - I'm going to try a... http://fb.me/6Eg60ecac     
    
    
        
    
    
    WEST COAST! We are coming for ya! Come out to meet me and @primalpalate (and @NomNompaleo in PDX) next… http://instagram.com/p/iq7T4ZBr6h/     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #57: Hormones, multivitamins, post-op & special diets (oh my!) - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/9yyjmv2  #paleo    
    
    
    HEADS UP! If you are planning to be at an upcoming book signing event, arrive AT OR BEFORE the start time! 

We... http://fb.me/2QmR0HsmY     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #120: Special Guest Chris Kresser, author of “Your Personal Paleo Code” http://fb.me/1LaSCjgrH     
    
    
        
    
    
    @koshergut Um… I was there already when the #21DSD released! No planned events right now. I live in NJ though.    
    
    
    Balanced Bites Podcast: Episode #26 - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7xyztgr  #paleo    
    
    
    @DannyRayGrayson @chriskresser thanks!    
    
    
    @SeanParnellUSA That is BIG.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Maybe this tweak to the #21dsdcookbook cover will help folks tell it apart from the #21dsdbook ...? We… http://instagram.com/p/irkq2nBr3n/     
    
    
    @SeanParnellUSA That is the best motivation you can have. #liveabetterlife #giftofhealth    
    
    
    @SeanParnellUSA Your kids will follow your example as well- this is a good lesson for you all!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @smartsexypaleo awww- thanks!!! Glad you like. Happy happy to you and yours!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Post your photos while on The 21-Day Sugar Detox and tag them with #21DSD !!! Get the shareable and… http://instagram.com/p/isEJq0Br59/     
    
    
    If you're on the #21DSD or starting on Monday... here's your shareable! http://instagram.com/p/isEVlwhr6L/     
    
    
    Book Review: "Wheat Belly" by William Davis, MD - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/3hakq5m  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    This is fun! Get your own personal stylist @stitchfix #style #fashion #notfood https://stitchfix.com/referral/3317966 …    
    
    
    @EllenSeeley @WholeFoods @Tessemaes YAY! #21DSD    
    
    
    Why did Hulu show me #mystrangeaddiction clips?! Sooooo crazy! And definitely steeeee-range!    
    
    
    Podcast Episode #104: Special Guest Trina Felber of Primal Life Organics - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/qaxqzmz  #paleo    
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Mini Mexi-Meatloaves - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/cjompho  #paleo    
    
    
        
    
    
    Are you starting The 21-Day Sugar Detox on Monday? On a clean-eating or Paleo challenge? Worried you'll miss your... http://fb.me/2jm4xt8f6     
    
    
    MY VERY OWN NOM NOM PALEO MINI-MICHELLE ACTION FIGURE!!! #food4humans http://instagram.com/p/itcqB2hryP/     
    
    
    Pittsburgh! Go learn how to make #kombucha with #fermented author Jill of @1stcomeshealth on Jan 22, 6:30pm  --> http://balbit.es/1a69j7X     
    
    
    Hey folks! If you want to keep seeing what I post, find out about upcoming live events, get recipes, etcetera, be... http://fb.me/T5yeXIAk     
    
    
    Podcast Episode #117: Handling haters, MSG in bone broth, bras & emotional recovery - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/p8swnww  #paleo    
    
    
    Hey folks! If you're on Google+, I'll be joining Chris Kresser L.Ac for his Virtual Launch Party of "Your... http://fb.me/1fXDN3LOf     
    
    
    The LIVE Google hangout with Chris Kresser, Michelle Tam (of Nom Nom Paleo), Robb Wolf, and myself begins in just... http://fb.me/6zuw0mrLU     
    
    
    Easy Recipe: Raw Sauerkraut - Bites Archive http://tinyurl.com/7u56exe  #paleo    
    
    
    @SeanParnellUSA @LaurieSnell NICE!!!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I liked a @YouTube video from @marieforleo http://youtu.be/FOMFgxigSys?a  How To Start Turning Your BIG Idea into Reality    
    
    
    