Floor lamp recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Big Lots is recalling more than 43,000 Classic Quarters ... http://bit.ly/yVhjpW     
    
    
    Save time on your taxes by filing a 1040EZ: When doing your taxes this year, you can save time and maybe some mo... http://bit.ly/An6pio     
    
    
    U.S. Postal Service price changes: It's soon going to cost you more to mail a first class letter. Beginning Janu... http://bit.ly/Ap3d1U     
    
    
    BMW recall: From Contact 13, we have a consumer alert. BMW is recalling nearly 89,000 mini coopers. http://bit.ly/zsgu05     
    
    
    Used Car prices expected to climb: Kelley Blue Book says now is the time to buy a used or pre-owned vehicle. Use... http://bit.ly/ABRDKq     
    
    
    Burger King delivery: Burger King is testing delivery service. Bloomberg says there are four locations in Virgin... http://bit.ly/zFB0Aq     
    
    
    World's Best and Worst Airport Terminals: Frommers has released its new list of the World's 10 Best and Worst Ai... http://bit.ly/zREBLo     
    
    
    Visa launches digital credit card: Visa's digital wallet is now available on some smartphones. http://bit.ly/Awc6uE     
    
    
    Desk chair recall: Steelcase is recalling about 11,000 Amia desk chairs sold nationwide. The problem is the pivo... http://bit.ly/x7vzvy     
    
    
    Giant Bicycle recall: We have a consumer alert involving a bike recall. Giant Bicycle is recalling its 2012 Gian... http://bit.ly/xMbPxa     
    
    
    Know when to book your flight and hotel: Did you know when you look into booking a flight or hotel has a lot to ... http://bit.ly/weGEaL     
    
    
    IRS help for Filing taxes: The IRS says it's free online file service is now available for the 2011 tax filing year. http://bit.ly/wWijiS     
    
    
    Lunch box recall: A consumer alert about a lunch box recall. California Innovations is recalling 248,000 Expanda... http://bit.ly/yFkpze     
    
    
    Family Dollar stores expanding: In this tough economy, dollar stores are doing really well. http://bit.ly/yMEKVy     
    
    
    Facebook users make change to TImeline: A major change for Facebook. USA Today reports the social network is mak... http://bit.ly/A0zKdB     
    
    
    Jones’ Mock Salt recall: Jones’ Seasoning Blends LLC announced a recall of Jones’ Mock Salt Original as well as ... http://bit.ly/xKhSj5     
    
    
    Worst places in the country to look for work: If you're in the market for a job, we have a list of where you don... http://bit.ly/z0g2lF     
    
    
    Bicycle handlebars recalled: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of some bicycle handlebars. http://bit.ly/yEbpAl     
    
    
    Warning about phony Super Bowl tickets: The countdown to the Super Bowl is underway. http://bit.ly/zvL0LE     
    
    
    Tire recall: A consumer alert involving a tire recall. Toyo is recalling about 69,000 Extensa A/S tires. http://bit.ly/y00wYp     
    
    
    Phishing scheme targets banking info: The FBI is issuing a warning about a new scam out there to steal your money. http://bit.ly/A0DmUq     
    
    
    JC Penny permanent mark down: JC Penney shoppers will no longer have to wait for a sale to get a deal. http://bit.ly/wMUprf     
    
    
    Spirit Airlines fined: The U.S. Department of Transportation has fined Spirit Airlines $100,000. ConsumerAffairs... http://bit.ly/xUGKYZ     
    
    
    BBB warns public of phishing scam: Better Business Bureau is warning consumers about a new twist in the ongoing ... http://bit.ly/xpxjPZ     
    
    
    It is an amazing day here in Las Vegas... too bad I have been dealing with that nasty bug that's been going around for nearly two weeks!!!    
    
    
    Mazda recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Mazda is recalling more than 52,000 Tribute SUV's. http://bit.ly/w4afYw     
    
    
    Collection agency reaches out to movie renters: Some former Hollywood Video customers say they're receiving coll... http://bit.ly/yuxkaR     
    
    
    Infant car seat recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Britax is recalling about 14,000 Chaperone infant c... http://bit.ly/xaZX6H     
    
    
    Automotive suppliers fined: Two Japanese automotive suppliers have been fined. Consumer Affairs says the Yazaki ... http://bit.ly/yL2wBv     
    
    
    Walgreens recall: We have a consumer alert involving a recall. Walgreens is voluntarily recalling certain lots o... http://bit.ly/zHFzfk     
    
    
    New System for stopping email scams: Several tech giants are taking a stand against online scams. Google, Facebo... http://bit.ly/zFuG6C     
    
    
    Investigation into airbag deployment: The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration says it is upgrading it... http://bit.ly/AFoDAu     
    
    
    Major fine against debt buyer: The Federal Trade Commission announced a $2.5 million fine against one of the lar... http://bit.ly/xMwLNN     
    
    
    Necessary paperwork for filing your taxes: So you're all ready to file your taxes. You head out to H&R Block, or... http://bit.ly/wwQsiL     
    
    
    Settlement in pre-paid calling card case: Several marketers of pre-paid calling cards have agreed to a multi-mil... http://bit.ly/wZ4Pgw     
    
    
    Aunt Jemima Pancake Recall: Pinnacle Foods is recalling some of its Aunt Jemima Frozen Pancakes. The product may... http://bit.ly/x5giG0     
    
    
    Getting Ready for Our Caucus Special on Channel 13 with my co anchor Steve Wolford
C u at 7 PM tonight for the latest results at KTNV!    
    
    
    Vermillion speaks out as charity faces loss of funding: County commissioners plan to discuss how many of your ta... http://bit.ly/wOt49p     
    
    
    Law enforcement sites hacked: It seems like your information isn't safe on any site these days. http://bit.ly/yboefi     
    
    
    Valentine's Day spending: Spending on our loved ones is expected to jump this Valentine's Day. The National Reta... http://bit.ly/zGj9tt     
    
    
    Toyota and Honda recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert about a vehicle recall from two automakers. http://bit.ly/xXMQ0W     
    
    
    Some background screening apps may violate law: The Federal Trade Commission has warned marketers of six mobile ... http://bit.ly/x79k4a     
    
    
    Redbox and Verizon joining forces: Netflix has a new competitor. Redbox and Verizon are joining forces to provid... http://bit.ly/yWysPn     
    
    
    Children's wear recall: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of some children's wear. Weeplay kids is r... http://bit.ly/AePOvS     
    
    
    Seafood company fined for false labeling of fish: Seafood Solutions Inc. is sentenced in federal court to pay $1... http://bit.ly/zidWw6     
    
    
    Possible Amazon store: Amazon may be considering opening a small boutique store. According to Daily Finance, the... http://bit.ly/x3BoAy     
    
    
    Cactus Boot allows customers to reclaim belongings: Cactus Boot and Shoe Repair was back open on Thursday, but n... http://bit.ly/xwcIdz     
    
    
    Valentine's Day scams to watch out for: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Did you know Valentine's Day is a m... http://bit.ly/zYFji1     
    
    
    Chevy Trailblazer investigation: Federal regulators are investigating complaints involving the Chevy Trailblazer... http://bit.ly/xxMeGq     
    
    
    Agents seize thousands of unsafe hair dryers: U.S. Customs and Border Protection agents have seized thousands of... http://bit.ly/yRIcRc     
    
    
    Counterfeit cancer drug warning: A warning tonight about a counterfeit cancer drug. Drug maker Roche says counte... http://bit.ly/xduAHg     
    
    
    Lipstick warning: Attention ladies. We have a warning about some popular lipstick brands. The Food and Drug Admi... http://bit.ly/zjfzzh     
    
    
    Airlines complaints on the rise: If you've flown lately, think back, did you have a good or bad experience? Comp... http://bit.ly/yNE9TX     
    
    
    Koff & Kold and Kold Sore recall: A Contact 13 consumer alert involving two different medicines. Wholistic Herbs... http://bit.ly/wlY5Gk     
    
    
    Avoiding identity-theft: Almost 50 million people subscribed to some form of identity-theft protection in 2010. ... http://bit.ly/zqBLg0     
    
    
    Credit climate of the average Las Vegas consumer: A new report gives some insight into just how much debt many L... http://bit.ly/zoWGFs     
    
    
    Synthetic bath salt drug illegal in Nevada: Synthetic drugs known as bath salts are now illegal in Nevada. The b... http://bit.ly/xnd3Np     
    
    
    Allegiant Air fined for violating rules protecting travelers: The U.S. Department of Transportation has fined Al... http://bit.ly/AdnPex     
    
    
    New FCC rule on robo-calls: It looks like we're finally going to see the end of robo-calls. The FCC has adopted ... http://bit.ly/yif8J6     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and we answer them. http://bit.ly/zezBjs     
    
    
    Teapot recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Ganz USA is recalling it's Dancing Teapot. The ceramic teapo... http://bit.ly/zKPNnG     
    
    
    Beware of freebies that may not be free: Lots of restaurants these days offer special deals like free dessert on... http://bit.ly/wThBgl     
    
    
    FDA to investigate AeroShot: The Food and Drug Administration is launching an investigation into AeroShot Pure E... http://bit.ly/wZapq1     
    
    
    Cutting down your cell phone bill: Many of us are trying to cut back on that rising cell phone bill. And more th... http://bit.ly/x5xYhg     
    
    
    Overdraft fees investigation: A new government agency is looking at overdraft fees. http://bit.ly/x43h5b     
    
    
    Bicycle recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. It involves the recall of more than 10,000 Fuji Women's Cru... http://bit.ly/w5LMcQ     
    
    
    Smartphones and ID theft: Your smartphone may be putting you at a greater risk of identity theft. That's accordi... http://bit.ly/yT3U6i     
    
    
    Honda recall: Honda is recalling about 45,000 Odyssey vans. The recall effects vans from the 2008-2009 model years. http://bit.ly/wf7DyW     
    
    
    What not to do when interviewing for a job: A lot of people are looking for jobs around the country and the tric... http://bit.ly/AqhLyX     
    
    
    Problem with Cox voicemail: Attention Cox home phone customers, if you're having trouble with your voicemail ser... http://bit.ly/yYW13Z     
    
    
    Nissan recall: Nissan is recalling more than 79,000 vehicles because of possible gasoline leaks. The automaker i... http://bit.ly/xniugF     
    
    
    Apple announces event, iPad 3 launch expected: (AP) -- Apple is inviting reporters to an event next Wednesday in... http://bit.ly/wtcmyB     
    
    
    Gas cylinders recalled: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. More than 29 million units of gas cylinders from Wo... http://bit.ly/xrxmyJ     
    
    
    FTC: identity theft tops consumer complaints: Consumers filed more than 1.8 million complaints with the Federal ... http://bit.ly/y3sqwr     
    
    
    Using credit cards to save on gas: Using the right credit card can save you money when filling up your gas tank.... http://bit.ly/wr6ZhS     
    
    
    All meat products now require nutritional labels: You might notice a change the next time you visit a meat count... http://bit.ly/A2OYU6     
    
    
    New Google privacy policy takes effect today: Google has sixty of so different privacy policies across their dif... http://bit.ly/wqgT0c     
    
    
    Children's pajamas recall: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of children's pajamas. Papa Bear Lounge... http://bit.ly/AhrMak     
    
    
    Dog treat warning: Vets across the country are raising concern about a popular dog treat they say is injuring an... http://bit.ly/wOHUqJ     
    
    
    No more unlimited data at AT&T: AT&T is ending its unlimited data plan. That's according to Consumer Affairs. Th... http://bit.ly/wYFCO6     
    
    
    Hammock recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Twin Oaks is recalling some hammocks. http://bit.ly/wg332P     
    
    
    Rearview cameras in all cars: Work is being done to improve vehicle safety when drivers are backing their cars u... http://bit.ly/xKnSCk     
    
    
    File a complaint with your bank: Do you have an issue with your bank? The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau i... http://bit.ly/zCf2pt     
    
    
    Filing a complaint against your bank: Do you have an issue with your bank? The Consumer Financial Protection Bur... http://bit.ly/xStiSc     
    
    
    Night light recall: American Tack & Hardware is recalling about 227,000 LED night lights. An electrical short ci... http://bit.ly/x3UlHr     
    
    
    Mortgage fraud warning: Nevada's Attorney General is warning you of foreclosure settlement scams and loan modifi... http://bit.ly/Aq9R9u     
    
    
    Frequent flier auctions: If you're part of a frequent flier program, you've probably received emails trying to g... http://bit.ly/z7dwHy     
    
    
    Worst passwords of 2011: People are making things easy for hackers these days. That's because most people pick p... http://bit.ly/wxB2a0     
    
    
    Recalled products still on store shelves: The Consumer Product Safety Commission says some recalled products are... http://bit.ly/wRUEKA     
    
    
    Avoid ads for free credit checks: Nevada's Attorney General is warning you about ads promising free annual credi... http://bit.ly/zvnnvO     
    
    
    Paying for college: College grads are struggling with student loan payments. According to the New York Federal R... http://bit.ly/y4cBIh     
    
    
    AMEX using social media: American Express is using social media in an all new way. The credit card company has a... http://bit.ly/zkvBg8     
    
    
    Boys' jacket recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. It's involving the recall of some boys' jackets sold a... http://bit.ly/yWVnGT     
    
    
    Ford sends out do-it-yourself repair: If you own a Ford, we have a do-it-yourself repair to tell you about. The ... http://bit.ly/AwPI0j     
    
    
    Ford Taurus investigation: Safety regulators are investigating claims of sticky throttles in Ford Tauruses. The ... http://bit.ly/wYhoW6     
    
    
    TrueCar releases automakers with the top marks: If you're in the market for a new car, a newly released list may... http://bit.ly/AC4IFj     
    
    
    Removing an error from your credit report: Are you looking to remove inaccurate information from your credit rep... http://bit.ly/y0Gmsg     
    
    
    Feds investigating Chase: The federal government is investigating JP Morgan Chase. The bank is accused of engagi... http://bit.ly/xbSBcc     
    
    
    BBB reveals most complaints: The Better Business Bureau has revealed a list of "America's Most Complained About ... http://bit.ly/wU3XHc     
    
    
    Trading in your old electronics: Are you looking to get rid of some old electronics? You can make some money sel... http://bit.ly/zaqOLg     
    
    
    Professor proposes flat-weight pricing for airlines: A Princeton University professor is proposing that airfares... http://bit.ly/zIjPKO     
    
    
    Fake Caller ID: Cyberthieves are stepping up phone call scams. USA Today reports more and more fraudsters are us... http://bit.ly/y8io9n     
    
    
    Beware of spot delivery: Consumer Affairs is warning car-buyers about what's known as spot delivery. That's when... http://bit.ly/Alzb0g     
    
    
    Kawasaki Recall: Kawasaki Motors is recalling some its 2012 four-wheeled utility vehicles. The fuel tube can scr... http://bit.ly/FSt4yD     
    
    
    FAA reconsidering rules for electronic devices: The FAA is reconsidering its stance on electronic devices. http://bit.ly/GCO1fb     
    
    
    Scammers using Microsoft name to gain your trust: An old scam is popping up again. Scammers are using Microsoft’... http://bit.ly/GDwDva     
    
    
    Effort to inform prepaid debit card users of fees: Testing is being done to help consumers avoid unexpected fees... http://bit.ly/GDlkhB     
    
    
    AAA says don't believe everything you hear about gas: Have you heard the rumor about gas hitting the $5 per gall... http://bit.ly/GNq875     
    
    
    Mobile wallets a growing trend: Are you tired of carrying a wallet? You may not need to anymore. Pretty soon, al... http://bit.ly/GQIZjJ     
    
    
    Some employers asking job applicants for Facebook passwords: What would you do for a job? Would you give up your... http://bit.ly/GSKqMh     
    
    
    Charger chords replaced for most Chevy Volts: General Motors says it's replacing the charger chords for most of ... http://bit.ly/GSB7PT     
    
    
    Data breach investigation: Verizon reports that 95 percent of the data stolen in 2011 was personal information. ... http://bit.ly/GTgyBH     
    
    
    Honda recall: A consumer alert from Contact 13. Honda is recalling some of its 2006 CR-V Crossover SUVs. The pro... http://bit.ly/GTgwd1     
    
    
    Adjustable mattress base recalled: A consumer alert from Contact 13 this afternoon. About 25,000 adjustable matt... http://bit.ly/GTKFnL     
    
    
    Most fuel-efficient vehicle: Are you looking for a car that's going to save you a little more cash at the gas pu... http://bit.ly/H9SF6Z     
    
    
    Hidden cell phone charges: Most of us feel our cell phone bills are too high. But how carefully have you gone ov... http://bit.ly/H5Lxfg     
    
    
    BMW recall: BMW is recalling more than a million 5 and 6 Series vehicles. The recall involves vehicles built bet... http://bit.ly/H5Lv6Z     
    
    
    Call for better consumer privacy: The Federal Trade Commission is calling on Congress to pass legislation protec... http://bit.ly/H9SGrC     
    
    
    Pranksters causing havoc at hotels: A group of pranksters is causing havoc at hotels across the country. http://bit.ly/Hc2F1T     
    
    
    New app claims to protect smart phone users: A new app is promising to help you protect your smart phone from ha... http://bit.ly/HbyYxF     
    
    
    Airline rate hikes: Airfare prices are soaring along with gas prices. Southwest says it is raising fares by $4 t... http://bit.ly/HbGF7a     
    
    
    Automated calls about lowering your credit rate: Many of us are getting automated calls these days about lowerin... http://bit.ly/HeirXI     
    
    
    DVD vs. streaming video: More and more Americans are downloading movies. In fact, streaming video will overtake ... http://bit.ly/HfWF3K     
    
    
    Dirty Dining: Jugoo Chinese Restaurant: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - A valley restaurant is shut down by health inspec... http://bit.ly/HgHF4S     
    
    
    Mailbag: water fee question: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and we answe... http://bit.ly/Hk5lW5     
    
    
    Mailbag: Relative needs help scam: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and we... http://bit.ly/Hk5kBz     
    
    
    Tax preparation firm accused of fraud: The Justice Department is suing a national tax preparation firm for alleg... http://bit.ly/HjcA6Z     
    
    
    Tax deductions: Money is tight these days and that has a lot of tax payers looking for every tax deduction and w... http://bit.ly/HjcCeY     
    
    
    Grocery stores taking stand against coupons: The next time you head to the grocery store, it may not be quite as... http://bit.ly/HNUIOV     
    
    
    Cream puff recall: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of some creams puffs. Creme Curls Bakery is rec... http://bit.ly/HHQpX5     
    
    
    Burger King making changes: Burger King is making some changes. The fast-food restaurant slipped to third place ... http://bit.ly/HPsPCL     
    
    
    Thieves are stealing tax refunds: You can't be too careful when doing your taxes these days. More than 460,000 t... http://bit.ly/HPsSON     
    
    
    Fish food recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving the recall of some fish food. It's involving War... http://bit.ly/HHQqdq     
    
    
    Chinese hedge and grass trimmers recalled: Thousands of Chinese-made grass and hedge trimmers are being recalled... http://bit.ly/HWceCx     
    
    
    Chrysler recalls small Jeeps to fix gas valves: Chrysler is recalling about 1,700 small Jeeps because faulty gas... http://bit.ly/I8opMB     
    
    
    New database aimed to disable stolen smart phones: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) -- They're convenient, they're fast, and... http://bit.ly/ID6lbS     
    
    
    Planters Peanut recall: A consumer alert involving the recall of some peanuts. Kraft foods is recalling some Pla... http://bit.ly/IoT2dg     
    
    
    Beware of survey taking: Who doesn't love to get something for free. But if you're asked to fill out a survey in... http://bit.ly/Iw8Izg     
    
    
    FHA adjusting loan program guidelines: While it's harder than in the past to get a home mortgage, FHA loans are ... http://bit.ly/IoT0lv     
    
    
    New wireless in-car recharging technology: Chrysler has announced some cool new technology. It's wireless in-car... http://bit.ly/IQOYkz     
    
    
    Bicycle carrier seat recall: We have a consumer alert involving a recall parents should know about. It's called ... http://bit.ly/IlCNkH     
    
    
    Gas prices in the $4 range for the summer: Think gas prices are high now? The government says they're going high... http://bit.ly/IlCNAZ     
    
    
    Crib recall: Nearly 17,000 drop-side Rockland Furniture cribs sold at JC Penney stores are being recalled. http://bit.ly/IGcG8j     
    
    
    Do bug bite remedies work?: As we head into summer and prepare for the bugs that come with the season, you may w... http://bit.ly/IzVBt0     
    
    
    Fix for unintended acceleration incidents: Federal safety regulators are proposing a fix for unintended accelera... http://bit.ly/IzVBt2     
    
    
    Carmakers ignoring standards for car seat installation: A new study has found out that it is not always car seat... http://bit.ly/J6yRj8     
    
    
    Airline performance has improved: Airline Performance Improved in February. The Department of Transportation rep... http://bit.ly/IEaFZe     
    
    
    New car price at record high: Bad news if you're in the market for a new vehicle. New cars are selling for a rec... http://bit.ly/J7lCyt     
    
    
    Tax deadline looming: With the Tax Deadline looming, taxpayers are being reminded about the free tax filing avai... http://bit.ly/ILxSde     
    
    
    Warning about senior scams: The Nevada State Contactors Board is warning the public about scams targeting senior... http://bit.ly/IF6zNR     
    
    
    Best Buy announces locations for store closings: Best Buy has announced the locations of 50 stores that it is cl... http://bit.ly/IUhDWH     
    
    
    Tuna linked to salmonella outbreak in 20 states: The government says a yellowfin tuna product sold at restaurant... http://bit.ly/IUhG4G     
    
    
    BMW recalling 2,800 cars for fire risk: BMW is recalling about 2,800 cars because a circuit board can overheat a... http://bit.ly/IXO5u4     
    
    
    Experts: Caffeine can decrease blood flow to the brain: In the right amounts, caffeine can help us stay awake, f... http://bit.ly/J1rQmV     
    
    
    Analysts believe gas prices are starting to drop: Analysts say gas prices are starting to fall, getting further ... http://bit.ly/IVljw2     
    
    
    Beware of scam emails promising easy money: Every week, we hear from viewers asking to check out emails they've ... http://bit.ly/IINwWn     
    
    
    Health District's new report highlights old problems: When Contact 13 first investigated a Health District emplo... http://bit.ly/JBIbeR     
    
    
    Cost of prom on the rise: There is the dress, shoes, jewelry, flowers and photos. It is no surprise that the cos... http://bit.ly/IYX5BO     
    
    
    Bank of America warning customers website not theirs: A news release went out this morning and a new website tha... http://bit.ly/JbrqMJ     
    
    
    Thousands of grills being recalled: More than 87,000 gas grills, sold at Home Depot stores nationwide, are being... http://bit.ly/JeOeXb     
    
    
    BMW Recall: We have a consumer alert. BMW is recalling some turbocharged cars and SUVs. 6 models from 2011 and 2... http://bit.ly/JcyCbD     
    
    
    Mobile payments: Do you use your smartphone to pay your bills and make purchases? Experts say most of us will by 2020. http://bit.ly/JcyBnU     
    
    
    Be careful what you put on social media sites: Be careful what you Facebook or Tweet. Employers are continuing t... http://bit.ly/JcyCs3     
    
    
    Grill recall: This time of year, many of us are starting to use the grill. We have a consumer alert involving a ... http://bit.ly/JcyBo6     
    
    
    LVMPD investigating theft of safe-deposit boxes: Police say three masked men entered the private vault business ... http://bit.ly/JcyCIp     
    
    
    13 contractors disciplined: At its April 2012 meetings, the Nevada State Contractors Board adjudicated cases inv... http://bit.ly/I92ZOC     
    
    
        
    
    
    FBI wants computer owners to check for malware: Thousands of computer-users could be unable to get online this summer. http://bit.ly/IgozPn     
    
    
    Company launches pizza product recall over listeria concerns: A Michigan company says it's recalling pizza calzo... http://bit.ly/IgHbif     
    
    
    Airline merger could mean even higher airline fees: The cost of air travel has been steadily increasing over the... http://bit.ly/JmW2uv     
    
    
    Protecting your computer and finding free WiFi: We all know it's important to protect your computer from viruses... http://bit.ly/Jy4sze     
    
    
    American Community Survey: Have you received something in the mail called the American Community Survey? Some va... http://bit.ly/JPCL0y     
    
    
    Watchdog group looks at arbitration clauses: The government is looking into the use of arbitration clauses. The ... http://bit.ly/JYq9o7     
    
    
    Airfare deals not expected this summer: Don't expect to find cheap airfare during the summer months. A combinati... http://bit.ly/JYqbw1     
    
    
    Small portable pools can pose overlooked dangers: They are an inexpensive way to add some fun to the backyard, b... http://bit.ly/JSscOI     
    
    
    Water customers with big bills caused by leaks: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - You must have a leak. It's the answer a l... http://bit.ly/J3N7vg     
    
    
    How many berries does it take to boost brain power?: For a while now, berries have been called "superfruit," abl... http://bit.ly/IIzgfG     
    
    
    Samsung holds title of world's top cell phone company: As South Korea-based Samsung has risen to the top, Finnis... http://bit.ly/Kn3YMS     
    
    
    Report: Apple legally sidesteps billions in taxes: A new report says Apple Inc. uses subsidiaries in Ireland, th... http://bit.ly/Jjm8Mw     
    
    
    Social Networking Online Protection Act: A bill has been introduced that would ban employers from asking for the... http://bit.ly/KvOshQ     
    
    
    Computer recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. A couple Lenovo ThinkCentre computers are being recalled. http://bit.ly/IKCUT7     
    
    
    Avoid credit killers: We all know that a good credit score is essential to getting a home or car loan. So it's i... http://bit.ly/KvOsye     
    
    
    Hidden airline fee complaint site: A new website wants to hear your complaints about hidden airline fees. The si... http://bit.ly/KvOsyk     
    
    
    Common credit score killers: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) -- We all know that a good credit score is essential to gettin... http://bit.ly/KzfXqC     
    
    
    Switching car insurance: It appears many drivers aren't too happy with their auto insurance. Of those consumers ... http://bit.ly/IU0QGV     
    
    
    Fake Verizon email: The Better Business Bureau has a warning tonight about a phishing scam targeting Verizon customers. http://bit.ly/JHB4nQ     
    
    
    How much are mothers worth?: Just in time for Mother's Day, we're finding just how hard mom is working. Salary.c... http://bit.ly/KQf8dl     
    
    
    What to shop for in May: If you love big sales, you're going to have to wait a few weeks. That's because the big... http://bit.ly/KQf8dp     
    
    
    New Text scam: You've Won a Walmart Gift Card! That's the subject line of a text message grabbing a lot of atten... http://bit.ly/JUyon1     
    
    
    Target phasing out  Amazon's Kindle: Target Corp. says it's phasing out http://Amazon.com  Inc.'s e-reader Kind... http://bit.ly/JWyNW6     
    
    
    Beware of Memorial Day scams: Memorial Day is a time to honor those who serve, and remember those who have died.... http://bit.ly/KgKUkv     
    
    
    Airfare continues to soar: It continues to cost more to fly. According to the U.S. Department of Transportation,... http://bit.ly/J3wbHo     
    
    
    Mailbag: Secret Shopper: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 Mailbag. You email us questions and we answer th... http://bit.ly/J3CD0P     
    
    
    Mortgage loan rates fall: Mortgage loan rates are hitting a new 60 year low. Freddie Mac says a fixed 30 year mo... http://bit.ly/KkgLgv     
    
    
    Spirit hiking fees: It's getting more and more expensive to fly these days. Now we're learning more about the ne... http://bit.ly/J8x5SU     
    
    
    Scammers sending out phony emails: The Better Business Bureau is warning that internet thieves are finding more ... http://bit.ly/J8x8hp     
    
    
    Facebook privacy: Facebook users are being reminded to protect themselves. A new Consumer Reports study finds th... http://bit.ly/J8x8hr     
    
    
    Salmonella in dog food sickens 14 people across US: Federal health officials say at least 14 people in nine stat... http://bit.ly/JyOXC1     
    
    
    Scientists: Chemical in red wine could help prevent cell aging: There's more potentially good news for those who... http://bit.ly/JHxgAf     
    
    
    National gas prices down 7 cents in past 2 weeks: The average price of a gallon of gasoline nationwide has dropp... http://bit.ly/KHc4NT     
    
    
    Dog food recall: There's a nationwide dog food recall after 14 people got sick with salmonella. The Centers for ... http://bit.ly/KUXKS6     
    
    
    Chrysler recall: Chrysler is recalling more than 127,000 Dodge Charger and Chrysler 300 vehicles. There's a pote... http://bit.ly/KUXNgW     
    
    
    Toothbrush recall: We have a Consumer Alert: The Spinbrush Rechargeable SONIC toothbrush is being recalled. That... http://bit.ly/L1dzGX     
    
    
    Expect fewer incentives when car shopping: Car dealers and manufacturers usually try to draw you into their show... http://bit.ly/LG2azl     
    
    
    Visa making card swiping even easier: The company provides what is known as the Easy Payment service. That's the... http://bit.ly/LG2aPB     
    
    
    Internet scam targets travelers: The FBI is warning the public about a new scam targeting international traveler... http://bit.ly/LPSWjV     
    
    
    Ford adds Virginia to Windstar minivan recall: Ford has added 27,000 Windstar minivans from Virginia to a larger... http://bit.ly/LeOxUM     
    
    
    Waters closed, oysters recalled after 14 illnesses: Louisiana health officials say they closed a harvesting area... http://bit.ly/LeOwjG     
    
    
    Bassinet recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. Kolcraft is recalling about its Tender Vibes & Light Vibes... http://bit.ly/LfYn8V     
    
    
    Unredeemed rewards miles: Are you sitting on a bunch of frequent flyer miles? You're not alone. http://bit.ly/Joq8LS     
    
    
    Ford recall: We have a consumer alert involving a recall from a major automaker. Ford is recalling about more th... http://bit.ly/Joq8LW     
    
    
    Child product recalls: A new report says almost half of all recalls last year were for kids products. Consumer R... http://bit.ly/KOWhAu     
    
    
    Facebook stock scam: Social media giant Facebook is set to go public and start selling stock. It's not only gain... http://bit.ly/KnxL75     
    
    
    Step stool recall: One million folding step stools are being recalled. They were made by Kennedy International Inc. http://bit.ly/JYYjcA     
    
    
    Fake Amazon email scam: The Better Business Bureau is awarning the public about a new email phishing scam. It lo... http://bit.ly/KnxIIC     
    
    
    Cell phone use in flight: Are you tired of having to shut off your cell phone when you board a flight? Things ar... http://bit.ly/JN58iG     
    
    
    Study on child injuries: Most of us don't think of a baby bottles, pacifier or sippy cup as dangerous. But a new... http://bit.ly/JKbi2L     
    
    
    When to buy an extended warranty: We've all purchased a product at some point where we were offered an extended ... http://bit.ly/JeCRE8     
    
    
    What you should know before signing a lease: Since the housing market collapsed 4 years ago many people have bee... http://bit.ly/LctAxD     
    
    
    Dirty Dining: China Olive: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - A valley restaurant is shut down for a long list of problems l... http://bit.ly/KcLsD9     
    
    
    Crib tent recall: Attention parents. We have a consumer alert involving the recall of a children's product. http://bit.ly/KjXE52     
    
    
    Consumers are getting their bills paid: Americans are doign a better job of making their mortgage payments and o... http://bit.ly/KjXFGe     
    
    
    Fighting back against telemarketers: We all hate getting a call from someone trying to sell us something or take... http://bit.ly/LXg4e3     
    
    
    Cookware recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. About 4,600 Circulon Cookware Sets are being recalled. http://bit.ly/KUgP85     
    
    
    Modern Medical owner charged with malpractice: A Contact 13 investigation is getting results at the state level.... http://bit.ly/LYrCxF     
    
    
    Henna tattoo ink could cause scarring and blisters: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) -- If you consider getting a Henna tatt... http://bit.ly/LhUUug     
    
    
    BBB warning about mailings to valley residents: A warning today from the Southern Nevada Better Business Bureau.... http://bit.ly/KJy4tk     
    
    
    Toilet and cabinet lock recall: And we have a consumer alert involving the recall of some Toilet and Cabinet Loc... http://bit.ly/KJy4Jy     
    
    
    Airlines making billions from baggage fees: None of us like paying those baggage fees at the airport. But it app... http://bit.ly/KJy4JA     
    
    
    Turkey burger recall: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of some turkey burgers. Foster Farms is reca... http://bit.ly/KYVQkz     
    
    
    Reno's Silver Legacy Resort files for bankruptcy: The Silver Legacy Resort Casino in Reno has filed for Chapter ... http://bit.ly/K1SaOK     
    
    
    Fire risk brings recall of nearly 87,000 Jeeps: Chrysler is recalling nearly 87,000 Jeep Wranglers in the U.S., ... http://bit.ly/M5y1Ha     
    
    
    California school kids urge Crayola to rethink recycling: A group of California grade school students wants Cray... http://bit.ly/KoUP3k     
    
    
    Jeep Wrangler recall: Chrysler is recalling nearly 87,000 Jeep Wranglers. The problem is debris can get caught b... http://bit.ly/K4PMG3     
    
    
    No more unlimited data plan for Verizon customers: Verizon is phasing out its unlimited data plan for all custom... http://bit.ly/K4PMWl     
    
    
    Bagged salad recall: It involves the expanded recall of some bagged salad. The voluntary recall involves salad u... http://bit.ly/K4PMG6     
    
    
    Cable providers combine wi-fi networks: Some cable TV giants are linking their wireless networks together. Cox C... http://bit.ly/Lv73w1     
    
    
    California lettuce grower expands recall across nation: SALINAS, Calif. (AP) -- A California lettuce grower has ... http://bit.ly/K9HxIY     
    
    
    Car sales and prices both on the rise: It's getting more expensive to buy a car, but auto sales continue to clim... http://bit.ly/Mjj3O5     
    
    
    Trampoline recall: And we have a consumer alert involving the recall of about 40,000 First Fitness Trampolines w... http://bit.ly/Mjj44l     
    
    
    Proposal for new prepaid card rules: The feds are proposing new rules for prepaid card. Prepaid card users curre... http://bit.ly/Kpr9VF     
    
    
    United: No more early boarding for families: Attention families flying out of town for their summer vacation. Un... http://bit.ly/Kpr9VH     
    
    
    Family Dollar to sell tobacco products: Family Dollar stores are under fire for their plan to start selling toba... http://bit.ly/KgG2c8     
    
    
    Consumers handling debt better: A new report shows consumers are getting a better handle on their debt. Credit r... http://bit.ly/LuoNF9     
    
    
    Higher gas mileage standards: Consumer advocates are endorsing higher gas mileage standards. The Obama Administr... http://bit.ly/Kj0RmQ     
    
    
    16 million homeowners under water: 16 million homeowners are still under water. The website, Zillow, reports tha... http://bit.ly/LINrop     
    
    
    Scam looks like Facebook notice: Scammers are sending out a fake Facebook notice. The suspicious email informs F... http://bit.ly/KpnvKQ     
    
    
    Busy Memorial Day weekend: Thanks to the three-day weekend, Memorial Day is also a great time for road trips. An... http://bit.ly/KpnyGg     
    
    
    Blender recall: Kitchen Selectives is recalling its 6-Speed Blender. While in use, the pitcher can separate from... http://bit.ly/Kz2rCe     
    
    
    Chevy Malibu recall: A Contact 13 consumer alert, Chevrolet is recalling its 2012 Malibu. It turns out the roof ... http://bit.ly/KpnyGm     
    
    
    Best sunscreen: As the heat rises, it's important to put on your sunscreen. Consumer Reports tested multiple bra... http://bit.ly/Kz2ttG     
    
    
    Local contractors disciplined: The Nevada State Contractors Board has disciplined several local contractors. http://bit.ly/MCEARO     
    
    
    Safety officials warn of portable pool hazards: The Consumer Product Safety Commission is warning that portable ... http://bit.ly/KDcSVw     
    
    
    Study: Calcium supplements may be bad for the heart: Taking calcium supplements to build stronger bones may be b... http://bit.ly/LrlBYa     
    
    
    Prices at the pump continue to ease slightly: The pain at the pump continues to ease slightly as we head towards... http://bit.ly/KxDhmL     
    
    
    Imaginarium Activity Centers recalled: A consumer alert from Toys "R" Us. The toy store giant is recalling its I... http://bit.ly/LGWLU8     
    
    
    Used car prices falling: Good news for anyone in the market for a used car. A big drop is expected in used car prices. http://bit.ly/LUFuK8     
    
    
    Cheapest Cars to Maintain: Looking for a car that won't cost you a fortune in repair bills? According to the res... http://bit.ly/LUFuKe     
    
    
    FDA warns about counterfeit Adderall tablets: The Food and Drug Administration is warning consumers that a count... http://bit.ly/LGWJvy     
    
    
    Hundreds of salmonella cases tied to chicks: Federal health officials say more than 300 cases of salmonella have... http://bit.ly/KVhExx     
    
    
    Better financing rates for car buyers: Now's the time to shop for a new car. According to a report from Experian... http://bit.ly/KhqEz5     
    
    
    Cricket to sell the iPhone: It feels like it's only a matter of time until everyone owns an iPhone. Cricket Wire... http://bit.ly/NjRgxp     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: money wiring scam: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions an... http://bit.ly/LKBNDO     
    
    
    Contact 13 mailbag: Do Not Call: Here's another letter from our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and w... http://bit.ly/LKBKYQ     
    
    
    Pastor astounded by Summerlin church's water charges: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - Money going down the drain. That's ... http://bit.ly/KSCQUd     
    
    
    Pastor astounded by Summerlin church's water charges: Business owners, non-profit organizations and homeowners a... http://bit.ly/KSCQUd     
    
    
    Prices at the pump still falling: Gas prices have fallen another nickel over the past week to a national average... http://bit.ly/KVrYoK     
    
    
    Fisker expands recall of plug-in hybrid Karma: Fisker Automotive is expanding a recall of its 2012 plug-in hybri... http://bit.ly/JIZZdG     
    
    
    Small business owners afraid new water surcharge could force them to close: Frustrations are mounting from small... http://bit.ly/Mu8awI     
    
    
    Coffeemaker recall: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of a coffeemaker. It's the Black & Decker Spac... http://bit.ly/MGvGXc     
    
    
    Highest fuel-efficiency vehicle: If you're in the market for a new car and you're looking for fuel-efficiency th... http://bit.ly/LbaeG7     
    
    
    Debt collection settlement: West Virginia's Attorney General says five companies have settled complaints of ille... http://bit.ly/LbaeWp     
    
    
    Fake text messages about gift cards: How would you like a free gift card to your favorite store? Scammers are us... http://bit.ly/M98omY     
    
    
    Lasagna products recalled in Nevada: A lasagna product has been recalled in several states including Nevada. http://bit.ly/Lv55p0     
    
    
    Lasagna recall: We have a consumer alert involving a recall from the Windsor Quality Food Company. http://bit.ly/MdzNnU     
    
    
    BBB warning of summer scams: As summer approaches the Better Business Bureau is warning the public of common sum... http://bit.ly/MdzLwr     
    
    
    Kia recall: We have a consumer alert involving a car recall. Kia is recalling about 22,000 Kia Borregos from the... http://bit.ly/MdzLML     
    
    
    Facebook app store: Apple, Google and Amazon have some new competition. Facebook is rolling out an app center. http://bit.ly/Mp1xJO     
    
    
    Phishing scam targeting military: We have a Contatct 13 consumer alert. A new phishing scam is targeting the mil... http://bit.ly/LK3Wwf     
    
    
    Bowflex dumbbell recall: Nautilus is recalling the Bowflex SelectTech 1090 Dumbbells. The weight selector dial o... http://bit.ly/Mp8xWX     
    
    
    Father's Day gift giving: The Better Business Bureau wants to help families avoid issues with gifts they buy for... http://bit.ly/LREdjl     
    
    
    Password safety: In the wake of the LinkedIn password hack, Microsoft is offering advise on changing your passwo... http://bit.ly/LREdzz     
    
    
    Fake Aflac checks: Aflac has issued a scam alert. The insurance company says consumers are receiving phone calls... http://bit.ly/N9rWh8     
    
    
    Consumers frustrated with utility surcharges: Consumers are frustrated with utility surcharges and fees. A new s... http://bit.ly/N9CqgJ     
    
    
    Store brands vs name brands: Store brands can knock a big chunk off your grocery bill. That's according to a new... http://bit.ly/L3JutH     
    
    
    Less credit card offers: You may have noticed your mailbox isn't as crowded as it used to be with credit card of... http://bit.ly/LDClOm     
    
    
    New Verizon plan: Verizon Wireless has formally unveiled a new pricing plan. Calls and texts are unlimited, but ... http://bit.ly/LDClOo     
    
    
    Finance education: A new survey says students can benefit from personal finance education. USA Funds, a non-prof... http://bit.ly/OBB2Al     
    
    
    Stroller recall: We have a consumer alert for perents. Kolcraft is recalling about 36,000 Contours Options three... http://bit.ly/LcY5Do     
    
    
    Jeep investigation expanding: Safety regulators are expanded their investigation into older model Jeeps. They ma... http://bit.ly/M8URuF     
    
    
    Call for tighter credit card control: There's a new effort for tighter control on subprime credit cards.A curren... http://bit.ly/NHj96q     
    
    
    Stroller dangers: We have a Contact 13 consumer Alert. The Consumer Product Safety Commission is reminding paren... http://bit.ly/NHjaXZ     
    
    
    Scam claims to pay utility bills: President Obama is not offering to pay your utility bills. A new scam claims t... http://bit.ly/NHBaS6     
    
    
    Bank phishing scam, credit report questions: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) -- Some Valley residents are getting an email ... http://bit.ly/N7phio     
    
    
    Water Authority surcharge outrages homeowners, businesses: Many are outraged with a new surcharge and plan to co... http://bit.ly/NauyWv     
    
    
    Credit card complaints: Do you have a complaint about your credit card company? Now there's a website dedicated ... http://bit.ly/LIlPPY     
    
    
    Consumers complaining about their bank: Banks appear to be what most consumers are complaining about. That's acc... http://bit.ly/LIlPQ2     
    
    
    Sunscreen changes: The FDA is cracking down on sunscreen come December when labels on sunscreens will be changin... http://bit.ly/PBTh9o     
    
    
    Sears Vacations: Sears is moving into the travel business. The retailer is attempting to re-invent itself and wa... http://bit.ly/LIlQ6k     
    
    
    Unlicensed contractor crackdown: The Nevada State Contractors Board is cracking down on unlicensed contractors. ... http://bit.ly/PBTidq     
    
    
    Contractors disciplined: Several contractors have been disciplined by the Nevada State Contractors Board. http://bit.ly/NZJnBb     
    
    
    Online college warning: Getting a college degree can be very expensive, especially these days. http://bit.ly/LJ1gTx     
    
    
    Banks responding to consumer complaints: Consumers are filing complaints against their banks. But are the banks ... http://bit.ly/O5lBUA     
    
    
    Health insurance rebates: You could be getting a check in the mail from your health insurance company. According... http://bit.ly/MCjJgT     
    
    
    Auto Industry complaints: Automakers are getting better at fixing average problems with vehicles. J. D. Power & ... http://bit.ly/MCjJgV     
    
    
    GM to recall Cruze cars over risk of engine fire: The risk of engine fires is forcing General Motors to recall i... http://bit.ly/MEBxdc     
    
    
    Tesla holds celebration for new electric car debut: There's a new electric car on the market, and this weekend t... http://bit.ly/MHl9IW     
    
    
    Airline prices rising: Bad news for anyone flying out of town on vacation this summer. Airfare is up and planes ... http://bit.ly/OlcNtJ     
    
    
    App helps military families make money decisions: Service men and women face unique finance issues like frequent... http://bit.ly/NsXaKN     
    
    
    Protect yourself from vacation ID theft: Vacations are a time to relax. But remember, going on vacation can also... http://bit.ly/MLOtxT     
    
    
    Twitter scams: It's also important to beware of scams on Twitter. Many of those scams start with a link. http://bit.ly/OlMALQ     
    
    
    GM Recall: General Motors is recalling 413,418 Chevrolet Cruzes. The recall involves the 2011 and 2012 model years. http://bit.ly/MrsMmb     
    
    
    Monitoring children online: Are you monitoring your child's online activity? More than ever, there are a wide va... http://bit.ly/MrsMCr     
    
    
    Car insurance monitoring: Do you tend to drive a little too fast? If you have bad driving habits, you may not li... http://bit.ly/Qd47Tw     
    
    
    Booking a trip with Orbitz?: Online travel agency Orbitz could cost you more depending on what kind of computer ... http://bit.ly/M16o5E     
    
    
    FBI Sting nets 24 hackers: A couple dozen hackers are off the streets today. The FBI arrested 24 people after a ... http://bit.ly/OxFTX3     
    
    
    Facebook drops Friends Nearby app: Facebook has dropped its 'Friends Nearby' app. The social network launched th... http://bit.ly/MBwCsT     
    
    
    Children's sleepwear recall: We have a consumer alert for parents involving a recall of children's sleepwear. Th... http://bit.ly/MYRCJ6     
    
    
    Warning about reverse mortgages: The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is raising concerns about reverse mort... http://bit.ly/N85xKI     
    
    
    Teens accused of drowning kittens: What were they thinking?: The two teenage boys accused of killing newborn kit... http://bit.ly/OLf5mf     
    
    
    Understanding sale ads: Everybody likes a good sale. But sometimes you may not be getting the deal you expected. http://bit.ly/NYbV8I     
    
    
    Contractor scams: The summer is a popular time for home improvement projects. That's why the Better Business Bur... http://bit.ly/NYbX0f     
    
    
    New Verizon plan: Verizon's new service plan is now in effect. The carrier's "Share Everything" plan replaces a ... http://bit.ly/NYbV8M     
    
    
    Magazine subscription warning: The Better Business Bureau is issuing a warning about magazine subscriptions. It'... http://bit.ly/NixB02     
    
    
    Top used car picks: Are you in the market for a new car. Consumer Affairs has made its top picks based on consum... http://bit.ly/OjxmVm     
    
    
    Kids' lamp recalled: Discovery Kids is recalling its Animated Marine and Safari Lamps. The problem is some inter... http://bit.ly/R4M3v6     
    
    
    Beware of travel scams: Don't spoil your vacation this summer by being a victim of travel fraud. The Better Busi... http://bit.ly/OvE3Uk     
    
    
    CONSUMER ALERT: Grocery bills going up: Mother Nature is beating parts of the country with sweltering heat and p... http://bit.ly/OztIGX     
    
    
    Olympic scam warning: We have a consumer alert about a scam involving the Olympics. An email is circulating, cla... http://bit.ly/NtyzH0     
    
    
    New research into different factors surrounding weight loss: British researchers are looking at different factor... http://bit.ly/PwV1nT     
    
    
    Dog food recall: We have a consumer alert for pet owners. Mars Petcare announces the recall of some of its Pedig... http://bit.ly/MSpbjZ     
    
    
    Tire recall: We have a consumer alert involving a tire recall. The TBC Corporation is recalling a couple models ... http://bit.ly/NDua4h     
    
    
    Isuzu recall: More than 11,000 Isuzu SUVs are being recalled. The problem is parts in the rear suspension can ru... http://bit.ly/MWqRsO     
    
    
    GM 60-day money-back guarantee: General Motors is offering a 60-day money-back guarantee. The deal is for all 20... http://bit.ly/MWqQF9     
    
    
    CONSUMER ALERT: Pop-up Ads: Those annoying little things aren't just confined to your computer anymore. http://bit.ly/S6cAZD     
    
    
    How to handle a robocall: Everyone hates robocalls. But what should you do when you get one? http://bit.ly/NlLn3U     
    
    
    Social Security services online: A lot of people are going online to check out their social security statements. http://bit.ly/NlLpc9     
    
    
    Saw recall: Before you start that summer project at home, we have a consumer alert. The Bosch Tool Corporation i... http://bit.ly/N3U1We     
    
    
    Can your landscape impact your power bill?: The heat radiated by desert landscaping may be upping your power bill. http://bit.ly/NMGAHf     
    
    
    Student loan online tool: How much will your degree cost? There’s a new way to get a good idea. http://bit.ly/NavChU     
    
    
    High chair recall: We have a consumer alert for parents. It's involving the recall of nearly half-a-million Chic... http://bit.ly/OdVZyh     
    
    
    Food-related diseases database: The Food and Drug Administration is working to speed up the government's respons... http://bit.ly/NPPvrl     
    
    
    Contact 13 mailbag: Microsoft scam: Also from our Contact 13 mailbag. Don writes: I have been getting phone call... http://bit.ly/Nus5cK     
    
    
    Contact 13 mailbag: grandparent scam: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and... http://bit.ly/Nus5cM     
    
    
    Yahoo email accounts hacked: You have one more reason to worry about viral emails this summer. USA Today reports... http://bit.ly/OjMSwb     
    
    
    Swing set recall: We have a consumer alert for those of you with little ones at home. Troxel is recalling more t... http://bit.ly/OjMU7b     
    
    
    Toyota investigation: There are new questions arising about whether the Toyota Acceleration Problem is really solved. http://bit.ly/Nh0lKh     
    
    
    Credit card use surges: Consumers are swiping their credit cards. The latest report by the Federal Reserve says ... http://bit.ly/MqkoBl     
    
    
    Ford recalls Escape crossover vehicles: Ford Motor Co. is recalling 8,266 redesigned 2013 Escape SUVs in the U.S... http://bit.ly/NWfO0B     
    
    
    Price hike when you charge: You could see a price hike for some goods and services if you like to shop with your... http://bit.ly/NNQ6f1     
    
    
    New Venetian & Palazzo mobile app: The Venetian and Palazzo have launched a new mobile app. It's called the VP P... http://bit.ly/OBf0uN     
    
    
    Fake IRS email: A New IRS scam is making the rounds. It's a spam email with the heading “Report of Foreign Bank ... http://bit.ly/Nz5woU     
    
    
    Bad date app: A new mobile app promises to save you from a bad date. The free iPhone app was launched by matchma... http://bit.ly/Nz5woW     
    
    
    Ford recall: Ford is recalling some 2013 Escapes. The positioning of carpet padding could lead to the risk of a crash. http://bit.ly/O32XtG     
    
    
    Close look at consumer debt: We're getting a better idea of where many Las Vegans stand financially. http://bit.ly/O32YO4     
    
    
    Pet treat lawsuit: Complaints are mounting over pet treats made in China. http://bit.ly/OPFMQY     
    
    
    IRS scams: Another warning today about circulating scams claiming to be from the IRS. We told you yesterday abou... http://bit.ly/Oa9mTQ     
    
    
    New supervision over credit bureaus: A consumer watchdog is set to oversee credit bureaus. http://bit.ly/M7pMtY     
    
    
    New AT&T plan: AT&T today announced plans to start offering customers shared mobile data plans. http://bit.ly/PiX0tU     
    
    
    Parents spending big bucks for back-to-school: Parents say they'll shell out the bucks for school supplies this ... http://bit.ly/NPg6CY     
    
    
    Capital One to pay $210 million: Some Capital One customers will be getting a check in the mail. The Financial C... http://bit.ly/On8lIl     
    
    
    Used-car prices to rise: If you're shopping around for a car, you better be prepared to pay a little more for so... http://bit.ly/NPy9cq     
    
    
    Meeting on water surcharge: Changes may be coming for water customers frustrated about some new fees that are ad... http://bit.ly/P24eyS     
    
    
    Viacom channels back on DirecTV: Good news for DirecTV customers. You'll be getting back more than a dozen chann... http://bit.ly/Pr5b7w     
    
    
    Students with major debt: A lot of kids these days are graduating from college with some major debt. A new gover... http://bit.ly/PkNcvZ     
    
    
    Power strip recall: Burlington Coat Factory is recalling some power strips. http://bit.ly/QhljK9     
    
    
    Latest unemployment numbers rose in 27 states: Nevada remains at the top of the list for unemployment, but the j... http://bit.ly/O7w0J2     
    
    
    United Airlines raises fares by up to $10 per round trip: United Airlines is raising fares within the U.S. by up... http://bit.ly/PuI4J5     
    
    
    Manufacturing problem caused Ford Escape recall: A manufacturing problem at a company that makes fuel lines is t... http://bit.ly/NK6nzA     
    
    
    JCPenney getting rid of traditional check out lines: Stores are still up and running, but big changes are coming... http://bit.ly/NKmQUj     
    
    
    FDA approves new prescription diet drug: The Food and Drug Administration has approved a new prescription diet d... http://bit.ly/OW5rKF     
    
    
    Gas prices heading back up: Gas prices are headed back up after weeks of slowly going down. http://bit.ly/Pc4fDh     
    
    
    Drivers holding on to their cars: Consumers are going longer between auto purchases. The days of trading a car e... http://bit.ly/OuNY8v     
    
    
    Employers looking at Facebook: Researchers say they've confirmed what many suspected. Facebook could cost you yo... http://bit.ly/PUk9Q4     
    
    
    Baby boomers beware: Scammers are targeting baby boomers. The American Association of Retired Persons is beginni... http://bit.ly/Ovh9s9     
    
    
    Stroller recall: We have a consumer alert for parents. Peg Perego is recalling more than 200,000 strollers becau... http://bit.ly/PdyyJM     
    
    
    Walmart fighting possible fee to shop: Walmart is fighting a decision that could result in a fee to pay when you shop. http://bit.ly/Q1A92U     
    
    
    Nevada attorney general warns of immigration services scams: Nevadans are being advised in English and Spanish t... http://bit.ly/OC1BTz     
    
    
    US Airways profit triples; fares up, fuel down: US Airways says its second-quarter profit tripled to $306 millio... http://bit.ly/NXdynS     
    
    
    Apple to release new Mac operating system: Apple will release its new operating system for Mac computers on Wednesday. http://bit.ly/NXdvIK     
    
    
    Retailers against credit card deal: The battle is heating up over a proposed $6 billion settlement between credi... http://bit.ly/OEH68A     
    
    
    Drivers buying smaller cars: More and more drivers are stepping into smaller vehicles. http://bit.ly/Pny4AL     
    
    
    Airlines must include taxes in ads: Have you ever been slapped with unexpected fees when buying a plan ticket? A... http://bit.ly/PnLCfz     
    
    
    Auto insurance premiums on the rise: Many drivers are watching their auto insurance premiums go up this year. http://bit.ly/PnLCfD     
    
    
    Accused drug-dealing doctor stripped of license: A former hospital chief has been stripped of his license to pra... http://bit.ly/PKey2a     
    
    
    Burlington slapped with fine: Burlington Coat Factory has been slapped with a $1.5 million fine. The U.S. Consum... http://bit.ly/PwXD2p     
    
    
    New Carfax app: Carfax has released a mobile app for Droid smartphones. The app makes it easier to view Carfax V... http://bit.ly/PNrKmZ     
    
    
    Super market prices continue to climb: It looks like prices at the super market are just going to get worse. The... http://bit.ly/PNrKn6     
    
    
    Stroller recall: We have another stroller recall to report. It's the second one this week. http://bit.ly/O2126D     
    
    
    Ford to recall 485,000 small SUVs to fix throttles: Ford is recalling nearly 485,000 Escapes and Mavericks to fi... http://bit.ly/PNQdss     
    
    
    Capital One lawsuit settlement: Capital One is paying $12 million to settle a lawsuit. The payment covers a rang... http://bit.ly/O5WtIC     
    
    
    More malware & spam in 2012: Are you seeing more junk mail in your inbox? A new study says malware and spam are ... http://bit.ly/O5WtIJ     
    
    
    Tire recall: Michelin is recalling BF Goodrich and Uniroyal Tires. The problem involves tread separation in the ... http://bit.ly/PS1k3o     
    
    
    Trader Joe's product recalled in Southern Nevada: A California firm is recalling a Trader Joe's product sold in ... http://bit.ly/OUXulx     
    
    
    Hyundai recalls some Santa Fe, Sonata for air bags: Hyundai Motor Co. is recalling some Santa Fe SUVs and Sonata... http://bit.ly/PWJiwZ     
    
    
    Beware of Olympic email scams: The Better Business Bureau is warning the public about Olympic-themed email scams. http://bit.ly/Q6BV5D     
    
    
    Banking apps: Many banks offer smartphone apps for convenient access to your account. But experts say be careful. http://bit.ly/OgvKZW     
    
    
    Nevada car insurance rates are high: Nevada is home to some of the highest car insurance rates in the country. T... http://bit.ly/Q6I5Dv     
    
    
    BBB email warning: The Better Business Bureau is warning the public about a gift card scam. People nationwide ar... http://bit.ly/QXfoWr     
    
    
    Consumer Financial Protection Bureau report: The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau is calling its first six m... http://bit.ly/R4uk9E     
    
    
    Understanding your credit report: Consumers need to understand the importance of their credit report. That's the... http://bit.ly/OkcLxC     
    
    
    Child carrier recall: Liberty Mountain is recalling its Kenta and Kenta Plus child carriers. The side strap's se... http://bit.ly/OkcOcI     
    
    
    Food items recalled due to onions: We have a consumer alert involving the recall of several food products. http://bit.ly/Qryerm     
    
    
    Hotmail being phased out: Attention Hotmail users. Microsoft is phasing out Hotmail and replacing it with a new ... http://bit.ly/PtM0WB     
    
    
    Toy car recall: Green Toys Inc. is recalling its mini vehicles. Detachable wheels and hubcaps on the cars pose a... http://bit.ly/OEjTZH     
    
    
    USPS bracing for default on $5 billion: The U.S. Postal Service is asking Congress for a lifeline. http://bit.ly/QfAS47     
    
    
    Toyota recalling SUVs, sedans: Toyota is recalling 778,000 RAV4 SUVs and Lexus HS 250h sedans to fix a suspensio... http://bit.ly/QfYi9v     
    
    
    Better Business Bureau has new president and CEO: Some major changes are coming to the Better Business Bureau of... http://bit.ly/PJcK5D     
    
    
    US Bank ATMs back online after 2-hour power outage: U.S. Bancorp says service has been restored at its 8,000 aut... http://bit.ly/QW0xP4     
    
    
    Late season travelers can still get a bargain: With just a few weeks before summer is over and school starts, th... http://bit.ly/R48QYW     
    
    
    Fake Facebook profiles: Facebook says it's looking to disable more than 83 million fake accounts. The social med... http://bit.ly/RQhlo9     
    
    
    Survey finds what hotel customers want: Are you looking for a good hotel rate during your next trip? The most po... http://bit.ly/RQvHEV     
    
    
    BBB warning on door-to-door sales: he Better Business Bureau is warning the public about door-to-door salesmen. ... http://bit.ly/OZlPfx     
    
    
    Citigroup tries another housing tack: Own to rent: Citigroup is trying something new to keep struggling homeowne... http://bit.ly/Mygo1v     
    
    
    $43,000 returned to victims in loan scam: Seven people scammed by a business called Save Your House got restitut... http://bit.ly/Mygo1B     
    
    
    Loan modification scam victims receive refunds: A dozen valley residents received some big checks today. It was ... http://bit.ly/MRPIdi     
    
    
    Childrens PJs recalled: Some children's pajamas by My Clothes Inc is being recalled. It turns out the pajamas fa... http://bit.ly/O5GpuL     
    
    
    Sweepstakes scam: Some folks who lost money in a bogus sweepstakes are getting their money back. http://bit.ly/O5GnTR     
    
    
    Fast food is getting better: A new study says fast food is getting better. The report comes from research firm T... http://bit.ly/MRPIdm     
    
    
    New Starbucks pay plan: Paying for your latte is about to get a whole lot easier. Starbucks will soon be accepti... http://bit.ly/O5GpuN     
    
    
    Fraudulent credit card charges: Are you keeping a close eye on your credit card bill? Unauthorized credit card c... http://bit.ly/O7LPW8     
    
    
    Election scam warning: Don't let scammers get their hands on your money this election year. The Better Business ... http://bit.ly/O7LNOb     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: sweepstakes warning: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions ... http://bit.ly/MDbPZI     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: sewer charges: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and we... http://bit.ly/MDbNAX     
    
    
    FTC fines background check company: Many employers these days do background checks for job candidates. Well, ima... http://bit.ly/QK2Nta     
    
    
    GE dishwasher recall: General Electric is recalling more than a million dishwashers because of a fire hazard. It... http://bit.ly/MDCDcj     
    
    
    GM recalls more than 38,000 Impala police cars: General Motors is recalling more than 38,000 Chevrolet Impala po... http://bit.ly/PauDMh     
    
    
    Independent foreclosure review: Did you go through a foreclosure in 2009 or 2010? There's some good news if you'... http://bit.ly/SoSiZu     
    
    
    Child bracelets recalled: We have a Consumer Alert for parents. Some Animal Snap Bracelets are being recalled. http://bit.ly/Ppr88b     
    
    
    Cell Phone Right to Know Act: How dangerous is your cell phone? Congressman Dennis Kucinich has introduced the C... http://bit.ly/SoSgB1     
    
    
    Home values: We can all agree, home buyers should be sure they know how much a home is really worth. A new rule ... http://bit.ly/SoSgB3     
    
    
    Sausage recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. Johnsonville Sausage is recalling approximately 48,000 poun... http://bit.ly/SoSiZy     
    
    
    Pay with your phone app: Another system is in the works that would allow you to pay for things with your smartphone. http://bit.ly/NFK8f9     
    
    
    New Apple TV venture: Apple is working on a new way to break into TV. The Wall Street Journal says Apple is talk... http://bit.ly/RWZuib     
    
    
    Hotel fees: Do you feel like your being nickle and dimed by airline fees? Well guess what, hotels are also hitti... http://bit.ly/OlM1eO     
    
    
    Gerber recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. Gerber Gear is recalling nearly 120,000 Machetes. The proble... http://bit.ly/OBmLHd     
    
    
    Bunk bed recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. PBteen, a division of Williams-Sonoma, is recalling about ... http://bit.ly/Q8cg8S     
    
    
    Give your input on gift cards: Have you ever had an issue when trying to use a gift card. We've heard a lot of y... http://bit.ly/PzEHCa     
    
    
    Ceiling fan recall: We have a Consumer Alert. It involves the recall of this Emerson Corsair Ceiling Fans. http://bit.ly/PzNiER     
    
    
    Denied a bank account: Forget trying to get a credit card, some people can’t even open bank accounts. Many peopl... http://bit.ly/OFYO1I     
    
    
    List compiled of nation's worst airports for layovers: To help keep your vacation plans on track, U.S. News and ... http://bit.ly/NRkUJj     
    
    
    GM, Isuzu recall 249,000 SUVs to fix power windows: General Motors and Isuzu are recalling more than 249,000 SUV... http://bit.ly/OyvvIy     
    
    
    Indiana melons linked to U.S. salmonella outbreak: Health officials in Indiana and Kentucky say they are investi... http://bit.ly/S6SNds     
    
    
    GM vehicles recalled: General Motors is recalling a long list of different vehicles. http://bit.ly/SjCY3e     
    
    
    Suzuki recall: Suzuki has issued a recall for 2004-2006 Forenza models, along with 2005-2006 Renos. http://bit.ly/NZvkID     
    
    
    Labor Day travel: If you're planning to travel this coming Labor Day, you won't be alone. 33 million Americans p... http://bit.ly/Qo3Avp     
    
    
    Travel sites sued: A major lawsuit is accusing some travel websites of cheating customers. The companies named i... http://bit.ly/Qo3ynh     
    
    
    Airline leg space: If it feels like you are running out of leg space every time you fly, it's because you are. http://bit.ly/PUTfwd     
    
    
    WalMart layaway: It's only August but WalMart is already bringing back its popular holiday layaway program. http://bit.ly/PUThUS     
    
    
    New T-Mobile data plan: T-Mobile is making a big move to attract more customers. The cell phone provider says it... http://bit.ly/STDSkn     
    
    
    Financial rating system proposed: There's a call for better monitoring of financial service companies. The Consu... http://bit.ly/STDSkr     
    
    
    Indictment handed down in mortgage loan fraud case: 2 Las Vegas men have been indicted for their involvement in ... http://bit.ly/SoB4Qq     
    
    
    LG and Kenmore dryer recall: LG Electronics and Sears are recalling about 21,000 LG and Kenmore Elite gas dryers. http://bit.ly/QrlKwj     
    
    
    Scam offers Valley woman free $7,000 federal grant: With high unemployment and foreclosure rates Nevada is at th... http://bit.ly/Sy4g6f     
    
    
    Record $478 million judgment against marketers: A record $478 million judgment has been handed down against the ... http://bit.ly/OaDy0p     
    
    
    Contractors disciplined by Nevada State Contractors Board: Six contractors have been disciplined by the Nevada S... http://bit.ly/OaDA8P     
    
    
    FTC suing DISH Network: The Federal Trade Commission is suing DISH Network, claiming it illegally called million... http://bit.ly/OaDy0t     
    
    
    New homeowner assistance hotline coming: Some help is coming for those hit hardest by the foreclosure crisis. A ... http://bit.ly/Sy5KPm     
    
    
    Jury orders Samsung to pay $1.05 billion: Samsung is expected to appeal today's ruling from a jury in California... http://bit.ly/OdM3YI     
    
    
    Charges filed against founder of Baby Can Read: The man behind the "Your Baby Can Read" program is in trouble wi... http://bit.ly/TBpgGE     
    
    
    Sherwin-Williams recall: Sherwin-Williams is recalling some paint. http://bit.ly/TBpgGI     
    
    
    Fuel economy standards: New fuel economy standards are expected to help consumers save at the pump. http://bit.ly/QFRS55     
    
    
    Some transparency improving: Some banks are working to be a little more transparent. That's according to the non... http://bit.ly/TBpi1i     
    
    
    Dangerous back-to-school supplies: A new report says high levels of toxic chemicals are in some children's back-... http://bit.ly/TBpi1m     
    
    
    Investing in gold: Exercise caution when buying gold. That's the message from the Federal Trade Commission. http://bit.ly/SXeSgE     
    
    
    Warning about calls from charities: Beware of scams following natural disaster, Isaac. http://bit.ly/R2P10z     
    
    
    Exploding battery recall: A recall is being expanded involving some exploding batteries. Batteries Plus is recal... http://bit.ly/QK7moB     
    
    
    Amazon tablet sales on fire: Amazon's Kindle Fire evidently was a big hit. The internet retailer says it's sold ... http://bit.ly/R3fCKO     
    
    
    Mr. Coffee recall: A Mr. Coffee Single Cup Brewer is being recalled. It turns out a build-up of steam in the wat... http://bit.ly/QKDCYL     
    
    
    CONSUMER ALERT: Organic fruit and vegetables: If you buy organic fruits and vegetables, you know they often cost... http://bit.ly/Q0aM6J     
    
    
    What to know when making an auto insurance claim: AAA estimates thousands of drivers were involved in auto accid... http://bit.ly/R5fwIk     
    
    
    New Walmart app could make shopping experience faster: Walmart is testing a new app that it hopes will make your... http://bit.ly/NPq20o     
    
    
    Victims of robocall scam refunded: Refunds are being mailed out to victims of a robocall scam. http://bit.ly/R5fxfh     
    
    
    Increase in malware: Experts are seeing a surge in malware. McAfee says computer viruses were up in the the seco... http://bit.ly/NPpZSg     
    
    
    Baby bather recall: We have a consumer alert for parents. About 2 million Mother's Touch Deluxe Baby Bathers are... http://bit.ly/R9c3bG     
    
    
    Apple information allegedly stolen: Has your Apple device been compromised? A hacker group claims they’ve been s... http://bit.ly/TiWT4w     
    
    
    More people were buying new cars in August: August was a good month for many car dealers. When all the sales wer... http://bit.ly/TnzayB     
    
    
    Best things to buy in September: Now's the best time to buy an iPhone, a new pair of jeans or a bed. Savings web... http://bit.ly/RfNuKn     
    
    
    Prepaid debit card fees: Some people are getting into a lot of financial trouble with prepaid debit cards. That'... http://bit.ly/NWoCkE     
    
    
    Ford recall: Ford is recalling certain 2013 Escape vehicles. The recalled SUVs were equipped with 1.6L engines. http://bit.ly/NWoCkG     
    
    
    Valley woman warns others of bogus lottery winning call: It's hard to win the lottery if you never play but scam... http://bit.ly/OXlibu     
    
    
    Power strips being recalled: Legrand Wiremold is recalling about 14,000 power strips. These under the cabinet po... http://bit.ly/OZCkFO     
    
    
    Amazon introduces new Kindle tablets: Amazon has introduced three new Kindle tablets. The company promised they'... http://bit.ly/P5Z9WQ     
    
    
    Nevada AG warns of misleading advertisments: A Contact 13 Consumer Alert to warn you about concerning an ad in t... http://bit.ly/QDQgUa     
    
    
    New online game offers sports betting: A new game claims to let you place bets on sporting events from the comfo... http://bit.ly/TD4wmv     
    
    
    New tablet for kids: Toys R Us is introducing its own Android WiFi tablet. It's called the Tabeo. http://bit.ly/TD4yLa     
    
    
    FTC sends out refunds for work-at-home scam victims: The Federal Trade Commission is mailing out some refund checks. http://bit.ly/RFabHR     
    
    
    Chevy Volt hurting GM: General Motors is battling back reports about its cash flow. http://bit.ly/RFabHV     
    
    
    Airport security gets poor marks: A new survey is giving airport security poor marks. http://bit.ly/RJLaG7     
    
    
    Cantaloupes being recalled: Smith's stores across the valley are warning their customers that their cantaloupes ... http://bit.ly/R8RCw9     
    
    
    Retail sales up: It's a sign that the economy may be getting better. Retail sales are climbing and are expected ... http://bit.ly/PtEsWK     
    
    
    Tarmac delays: If you felt like you sat on the runway for too long during your last flight, you're not alone. A ... http://bit.ly/PtEtd0     
    
    
    Installing a car seat: Many parents have no idea how to properly install a car seat. That's according to new res... http://bit.ly/PtEqy0     
    
    
    Safest way for babies to sleep: The Consumer Product Safety Commssion is launching a new campaign aimed at keepi... http://bit.ly/UgWkXI     
    
    
    Couple accused of stealing money from desperate homeowners: A local man and woman accused of taking thousands of... http://bit.ly/OCJA8s     
    
    
    Chrome do not track option: Google is adding a do not track option to its Chrome browser by the end of the year.... http://bit.ly/PRgTWs     
    
    
    Reverse mortgage oversight: Officials are looking into whether stronger oversight is needed to protect seniors w... http://bit.ly/UnfNHT     
    
    
    H&M children's bottle recalled: Attention parents. H&M is recalling some children's water bottles. The bottle's ... http://bit.ly/PRgW4x     
    
    
    Contractors Board participates in national sting: Some locals are in trouble after being cited in a national sti... http://bit.ly/PRmrQN     
    
    
    Internet access while you fly: JetBlue has announced it plans to provide internet access to its passengers. The ... http://bit.ly/PRmufm     
    
    
    having a retirement plan: Times have changed and so has the way people are thinking about retirement. These days... http://bit.ly/PRmufs     
    
    
    Groupon Payments: Groupon is branching out from daily deals to online payment processing. The company has launch... http://bit.ly/RH4SZj     
    
    
    Store brands vs. name brands: Buying store brands instead of name brands can lead to big savings. http://bit.ly/RLC9No     
    
    
    New iPad Mini: The new iPhone 5 isn't the only new gadget folks are going to want from Apple this year. A lot of... http://bit.ly/RH4Tfz     
    
    
    GM recall: General Motors is recalling nearly 500,000 Chevrolet, Pontiac and Saturn cars. http://bit.ly/RLCb7K     
    
    
    Contractors disciplined by Contractors Board: Several valley contractors are in trouble with the Nevada State Co... http://bit.ly/RH4UQL     
    
    
    Trader Joe's recalls peanut butter: Trader Joe's is recalling its house brand of peanut butter over fears of pos... http://bit.ly/UH7jKg     
    
    
    Gas prices down just slightly over 2 weeks: The average U.S. price of a gallon of gasoline dipped by less than o... http://bit.ly/PYuBGS     
    
    
    Qualifying for credit: Help could soon be on the way for some people being denied a credit card because they don... http://bit.ly/Ssqati     
    
    
    ATM fees up: ATM fees are rising to new levels. Financial research firm BankRate found that ATM surcharges have ... http://bit.ly/OYrZrZ     
    
    
    Discover to pay fine: Discover is giving refunds to some of it's cardholders. The company has agreed to pay back... http://bit.ly/OYrZIe     
    
    
    Borrower vs. lender credit scores: It turns out your credit score may not be as good as you think it is. A new s... http://bit.ly/Twz22A     
    
    
    Price of old Kindle marked down: Are you in the market for a new tablet? Amazon recently introduced a new genera... http://bit.ly/Twz4HM     
    
    
    General Motors recall: General Motors is recalling some 2013 Chevrolet Sonic vehicles. http://bit.ly/VDEWMA     
    
    
    More fuel-efficient vehicles coming: More drivers could soon be switching to hybrid vehicles. A new report by Ed... http://bit.ly/VDEVIs     
    
    
    New line of tablets: There's some new competition for Apple's iPad and Amazon's Kindle Fire. Barnes & Noble has ... http://bit.ly/VPpltv     
    
    
    New Myspace: You may not remember the social website that came before Facebook. But a music star is trying to gi... http://bit.ly/VPpjSp     
    
    
    10 used vehicles to avoid: The used car market is hot right now. But Forbes Magazine says some models aren't a g... http://bit.ly/UOQ6Ag     
    
    
    College debt on the rise: A new report shows college debt continues to grow. http://bit.ly/QgdP6r     
    
    
    Fresh & Easy recall: Fresh & Easy is recalling some popular nut butters. The recall is tied to the possibility o... http://bit.ly/UOQ6Ai     
    
    
    General Mills recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. General Mills is Recalling its Almond Nature Valley S... http://bit.ly/VVtQTr     
    
    
    Drowning danger report: Drowning is the leading cause of unintentional death among young children in the home. http://bit.ly/TNzYja     
    
    
    T-Mobile merging with Metro PCS: Cell phone provider T-Mobile is merging with Metro PCS. The deal still needs th... http://bit.ly/Wqz3mv     
    
    
    Top Safety Picks: The Insurance Institute for Highway Safety just released some of its Top Safety Picks for 2013. http://bit.ly/Uj93fj     
    
    
    More electronics for kids this holiday: More and more companies are using gadgets and entertainment to attract y... http://bit.ly/Wqz5KY     
    
    
    Americans paying off some debt: Americans are doing a much better job managing their credit card debt. http://bit.ly/Uj93fq     
    
    
    Air travel expected to be rough this holiday: Higher fares and longer lines are predicted for air travelers this... http://bit.ly/Uj93fu     
    
    
    Kitten drowning witness accuses neighbor of intimidation: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - You heard it first on Action Ne... http://bit.ly/UjZPiQ     
    
    
    Some Starbucks stores low on Pumpkin Spice syrup: Fans of Starbucks' Pumpkin Spice Lattes are in a bit of a pani... http://bit.ly/QSYF7p     
    
    
    Chrysler recall: Chrysler is recalling some of its Dodge Ram 1500 and Dodge Dakota trucks. The recall involves m... http://bit.ly/QSINTW     
    
    
    Walmart debit card: American Express and Walmart are teaming up. The companies have come up with a new low-fee p... http://bit.ly/QSIM2u     
    
    
    Honda recall: Honda is recalling some CR-V's. The recall involves 2002 to 2006 model years. http://bit.ly/QSINU2     
    
    
    Mortgage fraud: Hundreds have been charged in connection with a mortgage fraud scheme that targeted distressed h... http://bit.ly/QSINU6     
    
    
    Graco highchair recall: Parents listen up. The Consumer Product Safety Commission is voluntarily recalling the G... http://bit.ly/QSIMiQ     
    
    
    Report on expensive toys this holiday: It's going to be an expensive holiday season if you have young kids. http://bit.ly/VMLFGI     
    
    
    Toyota recalling millions of vehicles worldwide: Toyota is recalling more than seven-million vehicles. The recal... http://bit.ly/R9sVeq     
    
    
    Using a coupon on a date: Are you a coupon user? Many of us are willing to use a coupon to save a few bucks. But... http://bit.ly/WTveq9     
    
    
    Halloween goes to the dogs: It looks like Americans won't be forgetting their fur kids this Halloween. They're g... http://bit.ly/WTveqb     
    
    
    Cooking causes most home fires: A new report finds most home fires start in the kitchen. http://bit.ly/UJIoIN     
    
    
    Wire scam warning: Many of the stories we bring you for Contact 13 involve watching out for requests to wire money. http://bit.ly/UJIoIP     
    
    
    Counterfeit air bags: There's been an increase in the sale of counterfeit air bags. That's according to the Nati... http://bit.ly/WTvdCp     
    
    
    Study: Medications potent 40 years after expiration date: Are you spending too much money on medication? If you ... http://bit.ly/UV0rvJ     
    
    
    October may be good month to purchase vehicles: October may be a good time to shop for a new 2012 vehicle. Kelle... http://bit.ly/X6a6ge     
    
    
    Possible steering problem with Hyundai Santa Fe vehicles: Federal regulators are looking into a steering problem... http://bit.ly/QxWcQG     
    
    
    Company linked to illness expands peanut recall: A New Mexico food company that produced the peanut butter linke... http://bit.ly/XbkcfR     
    
    
    Hyundai recall: Federal regulators are looking into a steering problem involving the Hyundai Santa Fe. http://bit.ly/V30HZQ     
    
    
    Best Buy online price match: Just in time for your holiday shopping, Best Buy says it plans to match the online ... http://bit.ly/XfIyFj     
    
    
    September car deals: This month may be a good time to shop for a new car. http://bit.ly/V30Iga     
    
    
    Las Vegas housing market: Good news for anyone looking to buy a home. Banks are increasing home loans to consumers. http://bit.ly/XfIyFl     
    
    
    Feds warn of Android phone malware: The FBI is warning the public about a couple of malware attacks involving An... http://bit.ly/XfIB47     
    
    
    Highchair recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. Graco is recalling 86,000 of it's Classic Woo... http://bit.ly/WBuPte     
    
    
    Best and worst states for credit: A new list is out of the best and worst states for credit. http://bit.ly/WBuPJw     
    
    
    Most iPhone accidents happen in the kitchen: Have you ever broken your iPhone? http://bit.ly/WBuNBD     
    
    
    Target recalling dog treats: Attention dog owners: There's a recall of dog treats you should know about. http://bit.ly/XqnZpI     
    
    
    Average shopper expected to spend nearly $750 on holiday goodies: Americans are expected to spend more money thi... http://bit.ly/WNhpKI     
    
    
    Laundry detergent packets being mistaken by children as candy: More cases are being reported of children eating ... http://bit.ly/VluexN     
    
    
    Banana Boat recalls spray sunscreen products: Energizer Holdings is asking customers not to use 23 of its Banana... http://bit.ly/Rh4lJp     
    
    
    Some Banana Boat products pulled from stores: Several Banana Boat sun care products are being pulled off store shelves. http://bit.ly/VAs51l     
    
    
    Nissan recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving a major recall from Nissan. http://bit.ly/VAMTG8     
    
    
    Bassinet recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving the recall of 97,000 Eddie Bauer Rocking Wood Bassinets. http://bit.ly/XQpq0Y     
    
    
    Stopping robocalls: This year, the Federal Trade Commission took action to stop billions of robocalls. But many ... http://bit.ly/XQpq12     
    
    
    U.S. sues Bank of America for $1B for mortgage fraud: The top federal prosecutor in Manhattan says he's suing Ba... http://bit.ly/StOKGT     
    
    
    Barnes & Noble PIN pad tampering was "sophisticated" crime: Barnes & Noble  Inc. says the tampering of devices u... http://bit.ly/QYjyxB     
    
    
    Contractors Board warns of scams targeting seniors: The Nevada State Contractors Board is working to raise aware... http://bit.ly/VFsHTD     
    
    
    Barnes & Noble hacked: Barnes & Noble has been hit by hackers. The bookseller says the crooks broke into payment... http://bit.ly/REgdpf     
    
    
    Paint companies settle FTC charges: Two of the nation's leading paint companies have agreed to settle charges. http://bit.ly/SVUDwx     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ford sticking throttles: A Contact 13 consumer alert for Ford owners. Some Taurus and Mercury Sable models are b... http://bit.ly/XNgkD2     
    
    
    Hot toys disappearing: It's not even Halloween, but some popular holiday toys are already in short supply becaus... http://bit.ly/SVUDwJ     
    
    
    You Paid for It: Viewers sound off about trashed CCSD furniture: Tonight, our viewers are sounding off about whe... http://bit.ly/Ygjxu5     
    
    
    Gas prices drop 21 cents over past 2 weeks: The average price of a gallon of gasoline has dropped 21 cents over ... http://bit.ly/WomAmU     
    
    
    Some items found for cheaper after the holiday: It's hard to avoid holiday deals, but you should also remember t... http://bit.ly/Zj0lNL     
    
    
    Busy postal season: If you're mailing a holiday gift somewhere, don't procrastinate. The busiest mailing day for... http://bit.ly/Zj0lgM     
    
    
    Target joins in early opening for Black Friday shoppers: A couple more retailers are joining the movement to sta... http://bit.ly/ZyLka1     
    
    
    Moneygram to forfeit millions: Moneygram is forking over $100 million. The payment transfer company admits it ai... http://bit.ly/Zj0lNN     
    
    
    Look out for a spike in spam this holiday: Beware of a possible increase in spam emails. The holidays mean peopl... http://bit.ly/ZyLiyX     
    
    
    Create a spending strategy this holiday: The holidays are just about here. And according to the National Retail ... http://bit.ly/ZDROEw     
    
    
    Best days to do your holiday shopping: Do you know the best days to actually spend your money this holiday shopp... http://bit.ly/Zo7uws     
    
    
    Space heater safety: With the arrival of the recent cold snap, it's important to be safe when trying to keep war... http://bit.ly/ZDROED     
    
    
    Top 12 scams of Christmas: It's important to be safe online. To help, security technology firm McAfee has releas... http://bit.ly/ZDROUV     
    
    
    US Public Yellowpages bill hitting mailboxes confusing businesses: It's standard practice for businesses to adve... http://bit.ly/TCAcFK     
    
    
    Hearing delayed for two boys accused of killing kittens: Tuesday's plea hearing for the two boys accused of kill... http://bit.ly/ZpOWMg     
    
    
    Toyota recalls vehicles for steering, pump defects: Toyota Motor Corp. says it's recalling 2.77 million vehicles... http://bit.ly/SoTaxE     
    
    
    Some experts say carrying cellphone close to chest bad idea: It is something that lots of women admit to doing -... http://bit.ly/WiN7RG     
    
    
    Cellphone apps help with holiday shopping: It seems like there is an cellphone application for just about everyt... http://bit.ly/10epIQn     
    
    
    GM recall: General Motors is recalling some Cadillac XTS Vehicles. The vehicles fail to comply with federal head... http://bit.ly/Wqk0vP     
    
    
    Child's travel bed recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. Especially if you're going some wher... http://bit.ly/Wqk26Y     
    
    
    Preview: Tonight on Action News Live @ 11: Teachers quitting, angry parents demanding answers and students caugh... http://bit.ly/UbAJyx     
    
    
    Home sales up: U.S. sales of previously occupied homes rose solidly in October. Sales were helped by improvement... http://bit.ly/106YE6C     
    
    
    Tuna recall: We have a contact 13 consumer alert involving tuna. Chicken of the Sea Solid White Albacore Tuna in... http://bit.ly/106YE6E     
    
    
    Facebook spam warning: Clicking 'like' may be causing you to help spread the latest spam on Facebook. The Better... http://bit.ly/10nUgza     
    
    
    Toxic toys still on store shelves: We have a consumer alert about a new survey that found dangerous and toxic to... http://bit.ly/10nUgzc     
    
    
    Car seat recall: We have a consumer alert for parents with little ones in car seats. Britax is recalling its con... http://bit.ly/WyjLij     
    
    
    Facebook security improvements: More security is being put in place for Facebook users. Facebook is providing an... http://bit.ly/WyjJqA     
    
    
    Black Friday deals: Black Friday is more like Black Thursday this year, with many retailers opening their doors ... http://bit.ly/XCedog     
    
    
    Survey: Almost half of kids hoping Santa brings them an iPad: Here's something to keep in mind if you plan on bu... http://bit.ly/10eF0ph     
    
    
    Toyota recalls pickups, spare tires can come loose: Toyota is recalling about 150,000 Tacoma midsize pickups bec... http://bit.ly/XDsxNw     
    
    
        
    
    
    Cyber Monday: Black Friday wasn't the only thing starting early this year. You can already find Cyber Monday dea... http://bit.ly/10IpKAj     
    
    
    Same-day Postal Service delivery: The U.S. Postal Service wants to offer you same-day delivery for online orders... http://bit.ly/10IpKAl     
    
    
    Be prepared when shopping on Black Friday: Are you heading out tonight to take advantage of the Black Friday sal... http://bit.ly/XLbn0p     
    
    
    Salad dressing recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Newman's Own is recalling its Lite Honey Mustard Dressing. http://bit.ly/10JPWeW     
    
    
    Sara Lee recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Sara Lee is recalling its Butter Streusel Coffee Cake. http://bit.ly/1109haO     
    
    
    Cyber Monday safety: It's Cyber Monday. If you're shopping online, remember to beware of internet scams. http://bit.ly/1109haU     
    
    
    Cyber attack to watch out for: Here's an important reminder on this Cyber Monday. Cyber threats are getting more... http://bit.ly/10JPWf0     
    
    
    CONSUMER ALERT: Grapefruit interaction: The following is a consumer alert involving the potential for a dangerou... http://bit.ly/114bJx2     
    
    
    Seniors warned about possible scams: The Nevada State Contractors Board, in collaboration with with the Nevada H... http://bit.ly/Vc5hAY     
    
    
    Drugmaker Ranbaxy halts generic Lipitor production: Ranbaxy Pharmaceuticals Inc. has halted production of generi... http://bit.ly/11s0sa1     
    
    
    Ford recalls Escapes, Fusions for engine fire risk: Ford is recalling more than 89,000 new Escape SUVs and Fusio... http://bit.ly/11x3GsJ     
    
    
    Starbucks to open another 1,500 cafes in the U.S.: Another Starbucks may soon pop up around the corner, with the... http://bit.ly/TRxE5B     
    
    
    H&M starting clothing recycling program: They always say fashions recycle, but now H&M is taking that literally. http://bit.ly/VOLHe9     
    
    
    Popular child bath seat recalled for drowning hazard: The Consumer Product Safety Commission said the "Dream On ... http://bit.ly/U3UoPE     
    
    
    Protect yourself when shopping: The Federal Trade Commission is reminding you to protect yourself when shopping ... http://bit.ly/U0eUS7     
    
    
    T-Mobile making some changes: T-Mobile is finally getting the iPhone. And the carrier is making a move that's sh... http://bit.ly/XLqnKU     
    
    
    Ford repair work: Ford is updating software on its 2013 escape SUV's and fusion cars. The automakers is looking ... http://bit.ly/XLqpSR     
    
    
    USDA testing: A new round of testing is being put in place to help cut down on recalls involving meat. http://bit.ly/XLqpST     
    
    
    Stroller recall: We have a consumer alert for mom and dad. It's involving the recall of the City Versa stroller. http://bit.ly/XTY9O8     
    
    
    Beware of predatory lending: There are still major issues involving predatory lending, despite recent legislatio... http://bit.ly/U8IxjY     
    
    
    New cell phone provider: DISH Network is getting into the cell phone market. http://bit.ly/XTY7Wm     
    
    
    Bank rankings: Bank of America is the least popular bank in the country. That's according to a report by the Ame... http://bit.ly/U8IzII     
    
    
    Strong November retail numbers: November was a good month for retailers. Sales last month rebounded in the after... http://bit.ly/UHI6M5     
    
    
    No more loud commercials: Say goodbye to those loud TV commercials. Starting today, blaring commercials that are... http://bit.ly/UHI72p     
    
    
    GM changes pickups: General Motors has unveiled redesigned GMC Sierra and Silverado pickups. http://bit.ly/W1AJpN     
    
    
    Price changes at American Airlines: Things are changing at American Airlines. They're now offering up a new fare... http://bit.ly/W1AMld     
    
    
    CPSC: Nearly 40 children killed from TV tipovers last year: Flatscreen TV's are dropping in price, which means m... http://bit.ly/UojIQM     
    
    
    Protect your identity: This time of year, many shoppers are signing up for new credit cards and layaway programs. http://bit.ly/V0e6en     
    
    
    Best of the best for 2013: http://Cars.com  releases the finalists for the "Best of 2013." http://bit.ly/WkZpte     
    
    
    Smart TV danger: Do you have one of those state-of-the-art smart TVs that connects to the internet? http://bit.ly/WkZnlb     
    
    
    Feds watching student lenders: The government is taking a closer look at student lenders. http://bit.ly/WkZptg     
    
    
    Governor warns public of unlicensed contractors: Nevada Governor Brian Sandoval has teamed up with the Nevada St... http://bit.ly/WkZnlf     
    
    
    Toyota to pay fine: Toyota has agreed to pay a multi-million dollar fine. http://bit.ly/V3azfx     
    
    
    LG washing machine recall: LG Electronics is recalling nearly half-a-million top-loading washing machines. http://bit.ly/XFSEh0     
    
    
    Some credit card customers refunded: Some folks will be getting a nice holiday gift from their credit card compa... http://bit.ly/SNHFpf     
    
    
    Caribou Coffee bought for $340 million: An affiliate of Joh. A. Benskiser is paying $340 million for Caribou Cof... http://bit.ly/UMMNp3     
    
    
    Hyundai recalls Velosters over shattering sunroofs: Hyundai is recalling about 13,500 Veloster hatchbacks in the... http://bit.ly/ZPkzAC     
    
    
    Facebook ads: Facebook plans to add video advertisements in its news feeds. That's expected to begin in the firs... http://bit.ly/ZRKUOx     
    
    
    Child online privacy: There's growing concern about the privacy of children who use mobile and desktop apps. http://bit.ly/ZRKUOz     
    
    
    What to know before buying toys this holiday season: The Better Business Bureau is providing some help for paren... http://bit.ly/ZRKSpU     
    
    
    Making air travel easier: From lost luggage to delayed flights, you can expect a few bumps in the road when trav... http://bit.ly/ZRKSpW     
    
    
    Suzuki recall: We have a consumer alert involving a recall from Suzuki. The automaker is recalling some 2007 XL-... http://bit.ly/VcekRB     
    
    
    Buying a car in 2013: Next year may be a good time to buy a car. As many as 500,000 more drivers are coming off ... http://bit.ly/VcekRF     
    
    
    Online customer satisfaction survey: More and more people are apparently shopping online, and are happy with the... http://bit.ly/YUK3N1     
    
    
    Direct TV price hike: Direct TV is hiking prices. The satellite provider is rising prices an average 4.5 percent. http://bit.ly/TKcqMw     
    
    
    Baby recliner recalled after reported deaths: Major U.S. stores are recalling a popular baby recliner, after rep... http://bit.ly/10BxpD8     
    
    
    Vega recalls 30,000-plus motorcycle helmets: Vega Helmet Corp. is recalling more than 30,000 XTS motorcycle helm... http://bit.ly/TUxX5e     
    
    
    Sam's Club recalling smoked salmon: Sam's Club is recalling some smoked salmon, because it might be contaminated... http://bit.ly/VrBl2F     
    
    
    New Year resolution apps: These days there are apps for everything. That includes ones to help with your New Yea... http://bit.ly/YHHEQV     
    
    
    Top scams of 2012: Americans had to be on guard again this year. There were plenty of scammers trying to cheat t... http://bit.ly/U1ddsr     
    
    
    Safest cars for 2013: Are you in the market for a new car in 2013? The Insurance Institute for Highway Safety ha... http://bit.ly/XjyC19     
    
    
    Travel trends this year: Are you making any plans to travel in 2013? USA Today is reporting on the top trends to... http://bit.ly/XjyC1c     
    
    
    Toyata Scion changes: The Toyota Scion is growing up. After years of trying to attract younger buyers, the Scion... http://bit.ly/W2WQFV     
    
    
    75-watt incandescent bulbs retired: The New Year means lights out for 75-watt light bulbs.  Under federal law, 7... http://bit.ly/W2WRJT     
    
    
    Intelligent plastic food labels: Do you know how fresh the food is when you go grocery shopping? Labels on some ... http://bit.ly/ZgZiQs     
    
    
    Airline violations: 2012 was a record year for airline violations. The U.S. Department of Transportation issued ... http://bit.ly/ZgZiQu     
    
    
    New home sales up: Americans bought new homes in November, at the fastest pace in more than two and a half years. http://bit.ly/VznojC     
    
    
    After-Christmas sales: Good news for anyone looking for a good sales. After sluggish holiday sales, many retaile... http://bit.ly/XsoZ0d     
    
    
    Strong luxury car sales: The luxury car industry had a good 2012. Mercedes-Benz sold more cars than ever last year. http://bit.ly/Xsp1VP     
    
    
    Wendy's menu changes: Call it a sign of the times, Wendy's is expanding its value menu. http://bit.ly/Ws81Zz     
    
    
    GM recall: It's a bad start to the new year for General Motors. GM is recalling various 2013 Chevrolet, Cadillac... http://bit.ly/Ws83R7     
    
    
    What to keep in mind when signing up for gym memberships: One of the most common New Year's resolutions is to lo... http://bit.ly/ZxscvJ     
    
    
    Foreclosed homeowners could get money back: Nevada homeowners if your home was foreclosed on in 2009 or 2010 you... http://bit.ly/WFIDQe     
    
    
    Home Again program: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - Contact 13 has heard from countless struggling homeowners throughout ... http://bit.ly/WFIDQk     
    
    
    Computer virus scam: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert about a new computer virus. The Better Business Bureau ... http://bit.ly/Vbqayw     
    
    
    2012 consumer satisfaction: The list is out for the U.S. companies with the worst customer service. It's all par... http://bit.ly/VbqayC     
    
    
    Target online price-match: Target is looking to earn some points when it comes to customer satisfaction. http://bit.ly/Vbq9uB     
    
    
    Fisher-Price recall: Fisher-Price is recalling 800,000 Newborn Rock 'n Play Sleepers. http://bit.ly/VDrB6t     
    
    
    New online Social Security services: It's getting easier to find information about Social Security when you go online. http://bit.ly/XO1D5m     
    
    
    BBB warning of top scams: The Better Business Bureau has come up with a list of the top scams of 2012. http://bit.ly/XO1C12     
    
    
    PC sales down: Holiday-season sales of personal computers fell for the first time in more than five years. http://bit.ly/XXrB6q     
    
    
    Possible post office changes: You may start to see some changes at your local post office. http://bit.ly/WYNpZe     
    
    
    Portable heater recall: It's getting cold outside. We want to make sure you're not using a recalled portable hea... http://bit.ly/XXrDLE     
    
    
    What to know about e-receipts: Many retailers these days offer e-receipts. An electronic receipt sent to your em... http://bit.ly/XXrBmR     
    
    
    Gas on the rise: Bad news at the gas pump, prices are heading back up. http://bit.ly/13wnmy3     
    
    
    Tax changes when filing next year: Taxpayers will see several changes when they file next year. http://bit.ly/13wnmOr     
    
    
    Avoid fake coupon websites: Many people these days go online for coupons. It's an easy way to save money. http://bit.ly/VWZ1z3     
    
    
    New Corvette unveiled at Detroit Auto Show: General Motors rolled out what it hopes will be a modern classic at ... http://bit.ly/VWZ3qW     
    
    
    Improving auto sales: 2012 was a good year for auto makers. U.S. retail sales were better than expected last mon... http://bit.ly/X8M8OI     
    
    
    Super Bowl scams: The Super Bowl is right around the corner. The Better Business Bureau is warning consumers to ... http://bit.ly/10d2b5j     
    
    
    Pajama recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. Target is recalling some children's pajamas. The... http://bit.ly/13EGvhd     
    
    
    Fake FTC email: Scammers are pretending to be the Federal Trade Commission. The FTC says small businesses have b... http://bit.ly/S4At6W     
    
    
    Daily flights to begin from Los Angeles to Las Vegas: Virgin America is making it easier to get to and from Sout... http://bit.ly/ZZvh3k     
    
    
    Yelp health reviews: Yelp will soon be including health department ratings for restaurants. Right now it's only ... http://bit.ly/Uxv6fj     
    
    
    New homeowner protection: The feds are providing more protections for homeowners struggling to stay in their hom... http://bit.ly/Uxv6fq     
    
    
    Honda issues recall because of airbag problem: Honda says it's recalling 748,000 Pilot and Odyssey vehicles beca... http://bit.ly/13RJXp2     
    
    
    Delta frequent flier changes: Delta announced it's changing its frequent flier rules. The airline is now adding ... http://bit.ly/URXmtk     
    
    
    How to avoid being a catfish victim: News of Notre Dame linebacker Manti Te'o becoming the possible victim of an... http://bit.ly/VSPuZM     
    
    
    Southwest boarding changes: Do you want to be the first to board on a Southwest Airlines flight? Now you can pay... http://bit.ly/VSPvg5     
    
    
    FTC cramming case: A group of companies is accussed of placing $70 million in bogus charges on consumer phone bills. http://bit.ly/VSPvgb     
    
    
    Home sales up: U.S. home sales rose to 5-year high in 2012. It's all thanks to record-low mortgage rates and ste... http://bit.ly/URXoBi     
    
    
    New credit card fees start today: You might want to check those credit card receipts carefully today. New rules ... http://bit.ly/VKNxgN     
    
    
    Cell phones on planes: Airlines are getting tougher with passengers over cell phone use. http://bit.ly/VT1PMp     
    
    
    Consumer confidence down: Consumer confidence has taken a major hit in January. Experts blame it on the public's... http://bit.ly/11eyg8B     
    
    
    Home prices on the rise: The value of your home is continuing to rise. Average home prices across the United Sta... http://bit.ly/TWMaio     
    
    
    New IRS social media platform: The Internal Revenue Service is extending its services when it comes to social media. http://bit.ly/11eygFH     
    
    
    Why plastic is better than cash: Plenty of people don't carry cash these days. Most retailers make it easy enoug... http://bit.ly/11eygW3     
    
    
    Contact 13 helps locals get their heat back on: This winter has been a cold one, and many of us are turning up t... http://bit.ly/TWMayI     
    
    
    Toyota recalls vehicles for air bags, wipers: Toyota is recalling 907,000 vehicles, mostly Corolla models, aroun... http://bit.ly/Wymzul     
    
    
    Bunk bed recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. World Imports is recalling some bunk beds. http://bit.ly/ToqDgY     
    
    
    iPhones tend to come with hefty bill: There's no argument iPhones are hugely popular. But customers who use them... http://bit.ly/WaCJJ7     
    
    
    BBB reports surge in phone scam: The Better Business Bueau says they're seeing a surge in an old scam. It's the ... http://bit.ly/WaCLRc     
    
    
    Want to make money with your phone?: Do you have a smartphone? There are no apps available that could help you m... http://bit.ly/TFbury     
    
    
    Keep your info safe when using wi-fi: People do it everyday, browsing the internet at your local coffee shop. Bu... http://bit.ly/129KJuE     
    
    
    Paying less for a smartphone: If you own a smartphone, you know the bill can easily top more than $100 a month. ... http://bit.ly/11WlXD3     
    
    
    Comments wanted on credit card reform: The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau wants to hear from you. It's ask... http://bit.ly/11WlXTj     
    
    
    Lean Cuisine recall: Lean Cuisine is recalling its Culinary Collection Mushroom Mezzaluna Ravioli. http://bit.ly/U75WXc     
    
    
    New Apple gadget: Are you ready for the latest gadget from Apple? http://bit.ly/WV9MkG     
    
    
    Credit reporting errors: Do you have good credit? http://bit.ly/WV9NFn     
    
    
    Do Not Call email: Is your telephone number on the National Do Not Call Registry? http://bit.ly/U75YhI     
    
    
    United Airlines fined: United has been fined for violating tarmac delay rules. The Airline has been fined $130,000. http://bit.ly/XBmw17     
    
    
    Most respected company: Amazon is the most respected company in America. Amazon has edged out Apple in this year... http://bit.ly/WmXfGV     
    
    
    Americans unhappy with their bank: Most people would like to switch banks. That's according to a new survey by M... http://bit.ly/XBmw1d     
    
    
    Details regarding new mortgage rules: We're learning details about new mortgage rules meant to protect you. The ... http://bit.ly/XBmw1f     
    
    
    Organic baby spinach being recalled nationwide: A California company is recalling some baby spinach because it c... http://bit.ly/Wqa8Qw     
    
    
    Valentine's Day spending: How much are you spending on your Valentine this year? According to CNN the average pe... http://bit.ly/UkHPo7     
    
    
    Food recalls reach a high: Food recalls hit a two-year high in the fourth quarter of 2012. http://bit.ly/12MtjEO     
    
    
    Internet providers meeting expected speeds: Are you happy with your broadband speed? A study by the Federal Comm... http://bit.ly/12MtjVa     
    
    
    Toyota paying $29 million: Toyota is paying again to settle unintended acceleration complaints. http://bit.ly/12qe1dv     
    
    
    No answers in dog illnesses: Dog treat-related illnesses continue to puzzle the Food and Drug Administration. http://bit.ly/12Mthg7     
    
    
    Costco accused of selling fake Tiffany rings: The jewelry company said its rings have never been sold at the who... http://bit.ly/XPuDHK     
    
    
    Average Nevadan's debt: Nevadans have a lower credit score than the average American. That's according to Credit... http://bit.ly/XocZcK     
    
    
    What affects your insurance rates: Looking to pay less for insurance? It turns out there's a lot more that influ... http://bit.ly/UzK72M     
    
    
    Best Buy price-matching: Best Buy is launching a new price-matching guarantee. http://bit.ly/UzK7jb     
    
    
    Consumer spending down: Americans are spending less these days on everything. The Deloitte Consumer Spending Ind... http://bit.ly/12JG4Vc     
    
    
    Old vs. new designed washing machine: When shopping for a washing machine, cheaper may be better. http://bit.ly/12JG7Ap     
    
    
    Protect your info during tax season: Tax season is in full swing. But if you're not careful, your refund could b... http://bit.ly/12JG4Vp     
    
    
    Credit transfers: Credit card balance transfers can save you money. But Card Hub, a credit card comparison sit... http://bit.ly/WVOiVh     
    
    
    What to know about foreclosures: Make sure you know the facts, before you ever walk away from a foreclosed home. http://bit.ly/YdWDVs     
    
    
    Increase in debt for older Americans: A new study find older Americans are deeper in debt than previous generations. http://bit.ly/YdWAJr     
    
    
    Fish mislabeling study: You may not be getting what you paid for when it comes to buying fish. http://bit.ly/WVOlAv     
    
    
    FBI computer scam: We have a warning about a scam we've warned you about before, and it's making the rounds again. http://bit.ly/13ugsaz     
    
    
    Safer drivers may pay more for insurance: Contrary to popular believe, safe drivers may pay more for auto insurance. http://bit.ly/VUA3Ds     
    
    
    Great mortgage rates: Now is the best time to go shopping for a mortgage loan. http://bit.ly/13ugsr9     
    
    
    Difficult time paying off payday loans: Most people who take out payday loans find themselves having to pay th... http://bit.ly/13ugtvk     
    
    
    Microsoft hit by hackers: Microsoft is the latest technology company targeted by hackers. http://bit.ly/13EP21T     
    
    
    Barnes & Noble sale?: There may be some changes at the top for Barnes & Noble. http://bit.ly/W9sM2B     
    
    
    Gas prices surge: Lately, we've seen a big spike in gas prices and now your wallet could take a big hit at the... http://bit.ly/13LogVC     
    
    
    Ford engine trouble: Government officials are looking into an engine problem in some ford vehicles. http://bit.ly/W9sMj3     
    
    
    Purina defends Beneful: The Purina dog food company says Beneful is safe for dogs. http://bit.ly/ZK2Asp     
    
    
    Strong auto sales: Automakers say February was a very good month. http://bit.ly/ZK2D7C     
    
    
    Biggest traveler complaints: What do you hate most about flying? If you said cramped seats, you're not alone. http://bit.ly/ZXOLXv     
    
    
    Top signs of identity theft: The U.S. Federal Trade Commission says identity theft continues to be the top con... http://bit.ly/ZXOLXF     
    
    
    Top 5 mortgage fraud consumer complaints: Las Vegas, NV - In conjunction with National Consumer Protection Wee... http://bit.ly/105Ihtz     
    
    
    Solar panel complaint update: We have an update to a story we brought you last month. That's when we introduce... http://bit.ly/ZXOMdW     
    
    
    More employers checking credit: A new study shows employer credit checks are preventing the nation's hardest-h... http://bit.ly/XLErlr     
    
    
    Obama backs idea of unlocking cell phones: Do you love your smartphone, but hate your service provider? Unfort... http://bit.ly/Z7V1gx     
    
    
    Mortgage refinancing now tougher: Plenty of Nevada homeowners can tell you refinancing your mortgage isn't eas... http://bit.ly/Z7V1gB     
    
    
    Car title loan dangers: A warning for anyone considering a car title loan. http://bit.ly/Z7UZVQ     
    
    
    High fees for tax refund loans: There's a warning out about a new and expensive tax refund loan. http://bit.ly/VGgU6I     
    
    
    Fake FTC email warning: The Federal Trade Commission has a warning for small businesses. http://bit.ly/VGgTzE     
    
    
    Top consumer complaints of 2012: The Federal Trade Commission is releasing new details about consumer complain... http://bit.ly/Yz8z3A     
    
    
    How to handle telemarketers: Most people don't know their rights when it comes to telemarketers. That's accord... http://bit.ly/WYabXL     
    
    
    Best mattresses: We all love a good night's sleep. To help, Consumer Reports tested the latest mattresses on t... http://bit.ly/Zk1Mfi     
    
    
    Keep a record of prized possessions: Are you covered if thieves break into your home? Unless you have records ... http://bit.ly/XXTUyF     
    
    
    Facebook changes: Facebook is unveiling a redesign of its news feed. The social media site's CEO Mark Zuckerbe... http://bit.ly/XXTUyP     
    
    
    Crack down on spam text messages: The Federal Trade Commission is cracking down on spam text messages. http://bit.ly/X3UI8D     
    
    
    Tuna recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. Bumble Bee Foods has issued a voluntary recall. http://bit.ly/X3UKNO     
    
    
    Subaru recalls 50,000 "zombie" cars: Japanese carmaker Subaru is recalling nearly 50,000 vehicles because they... http://bit.ly/10jmZVH     
    
    
    Smartphone wallets: Experts still say, your smartphone could soon become your wallet. http://bit.ly/ZBzA7L     
    
    
    FTC accuses company of deceptive practices: A New York-based Operation has temporarily been shut down for alle... http://bit.ly/ZBzA7N     
    
    
    Understanding your credit: Experts say too many people don't understand their own credit. http://bit.ly/YeBbPN     
    
    
    Baby product manufacturer faces penalty: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. A baby product manufacturer is p... http://bit.ly/YeBc63     
    
    
    Crimes of the cubicle: Are you looking to get a raise or promotion at work this year? http://Salary.com  ha... http://bit.ly/YZWrbS     
    
    
    Many renters aren't insured: Plenty of people rent in this economy. But a new survey says many of those people... http://bit.ly/YZWrbW     
    
    
    Top reward cards for 2013: Today's reward cards can be a great way to stretch your dollars. But it's important... http://bit.ly/YZWrbY     
    
    
    Metro PCS and T-Mobile merger: Changes are happening in the wireless arena. Federal regulators have given the ... http://bit.ly/ZLuwhb     
    
    
    Netflix gets social: Your Facebook friends can now see what you're watching on Netflix. http://bit.ly/ZLuwhh     
    
    
    Dog food accused of making pets sick: Pet owners are pointing to another dog food for making their pets sick. http://bit.ly/YoxRS4     
    
    
    Top cars with best mileage: Looking to buy a more fuel-efficient car? http://bit.ly/ZLuxBR     
    
    
    Nissan recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert involving a vehicle recall. http://bit.ly/YthDag     
    
    
    Online ad rules: The government says online ads can be deceptive and unfair, so they've made some changes. http://bit.ly/YthDr0     
    
    
    H&R Block tax issue: A tax return alert for anyone who filed their taxes with H&R Block. There's a hang-up wit... http://bit.ly/XzRmue     
    
    
    Honda recall: Honda is recalling 180,000 vehicles in the U-S because of a break problem. http://bit.ly/156CcKr     
    
    
    Educate yourself before buying a home: During the last housing boom, a lot of Americans learned they had signe... http://bit.ly/156CfpN     
    
    
    Worst customer service: Walmart tops the list of retailers with the worst customer service. http://bit.ly/XWHwmi     
    
    
    Home sales are hot: Homes are selling at a record pace. Industry figures show homes sold faster last month tha... http://bit.ly/15jHwdM     
    
    
    Ford recall: Ford is recalling some 2013 Focus and Escape vehicles. http://bit.ly/XWHvPl     
    
    
        
    
    
    Help for homeowners event: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) Nevada still tops the nation when it comes to foreclosures. An... http://bit.ly/15o5jcw     
    
    
    Credit Unions vs. Banks: In the battle between credit unions and banks, it appears to be no contest. http://bit.ly/WF7okK     
    
    
    Hostess deal: There's something to look forward to from the snack world. http://bit.ly/ZtG3Rp     
    
    
    FTC warning about new phone scam: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert about a new phone scam. The caller claim... http://bit.ly/ZtG47H     
    
    
    GM recalls 27,000 vehicles to fix transmissions: General Motors is recalling nearly 27,000 Buicks and Cadillac... http://bit.ly/Y7rUwv     
    
    
    Americans are shopping: Americans are still doing plenty of shopping. New figures show consumer spending level... http://bit.ly/10ofnD1     
    
    
    Complaints about Ford mileage: Ford is facing some criticism from some unhappy drivers. http://bit.ly/Z3vBjE     
    
    
    Picking the right auto insurance: It's important for drivers to protect themselves with auto insurance. But ho... http://bit.ly/Z3vCUu     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: Time to reach into our Contact 13 mailbag. You email us questions and we answer them on the air. http://bit.ly/11rFYxY     
    
    
    Netflix suit: Netflix has agreed to settle a privacy suit for $9 million. http://bit.ly/11u6AlI     
    
    
    Rising prices at the gas pump: Attention drivers, we've got some bad news. http://bit.ly/11rFYOe     
    
    
    Easter spending: Retailers are hoping for some sweet results when it comes to consumer spending this Easter. http://bit.ly/11Ew0Jr     
    
    
    Beware of tax scams: As we approach the home stretch of tax filing season, it's important to remember to avoid... http://bit.ly/ZRzbgL     
    
    
    New home sales down: The price of a new home was up as new home sales fell slightly in February. http://bit.ly/YEb9cz     
    
    
    Crib recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving the recall of a crib. http://bit.ly/Xfpc6q     
    
    
    Tax refund delay: Good news for anyone waiting for their check from the government. http://bit.ly/ZZFIpK     
    
    
    Facebook competitors: A number of Facebook competitors are springing up, as some Facebook users continue compl... http://bit.ly/ZZFIpN     
    
    
    A number of programs help prevent foreclosure: Some federal programs have improved their efforts to help homeo... http://bit.ly/XfpaLX     
    
    
    T-Mobile to offer iPhone: The iPhone is coming to T-Mobile. The wireless provider says it will start offering ... http://bit.ly/ZZFIpP     
    
    
    Contact 13 Mailbag: It's time to reach into our Contact 13 Mailbag. You email us questions and we answer them ... http://bit.ly/11Xhssn     
    
    
    Stroller recalls: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert for parents. We have two stroller recalls to tell you about. http://bit.ly/11Xhsst     
    
    
    24 E. coli illnesses linked to frozen foods: Health officials say at least 24 people have become sick from an ... http://bit.ly/122jtjj     
    
    
    Local firefighters claim fire station infested with bed bugs: Local firefighters say that their fire station i... http://bit.ly/10ukDEd     
    
    
    Airline passenger complaints soaring: A new study shows passengers are more fed up than ever with airlines. http://bit.ly/12BsnEH     
    
    
    Gas prices falling: Good news for drivers, you may see lower gas prices this summer. http://bit.ly/10MmKDq     
    
    
    Housing crisis continues: Most people feel the housing crisis isn't over just yet. http://bit.ly/Ybe6Qn     
    
    
    DPL Enterprises fined: A local business is in hot water for selling thousands of gallons of mis-branded and di... http://bit.ly/12EDYD0     
    
    
    Portrait studio at 2 retailers now closed: Things are changing at two major retailers. http://bit.ly/16NfCaM     
    
    
    Some things last longer than others: These days it seems like we're always trading things in for the latest an... http://bit.ly/16NfCr2     
    
    
    New airline rankings: A new list is out, showing just how well airlines are performing. It's all part of the l... http://bit.ly/ZBaMjj     
    
    
    Be smart when banking online: With wi-fi, you can access your bank account from anywhere in the world these da... http://bit.ly/ZBaLfe     
    
    
    Former charter school administrator arrested: A man at the center of a Contact 13 investigation is facing char... http://bit.ly/12H6X9o     
    
    
    Virtual bank teller: Bank of America is introducing new ATM machines with virtual tellers. http://bit.ly/12027oG     
    
    
    Japanese automakers recall vehicles: Japanese automakers are recalling millions of vehicles. http://bit.ly/12027oK     
    
    
    Hiring pest control help: April is National Pest Management Month. If you're looking to hire some help, make s... http://bit.ly/110defW     
    
    
    More teens logging off Facebook: It's not cool to be on Facebook anymore. http://bit.ly/YwuhYN     
    
    
    February tarmac delays: There were a lot of tarmac delays during the month of February. http://bit.ly/Ywuif5     
    
    
    Cramming charges: How closely do you look at your cell phone bill? The Federal Trade Commission has taken lega... http://bit.ly/17oOi2H     
    
    
    Cost of owning a car is up: If it feels to you like it's more expensive to own a car these days, you're right.... http://bit.ly/17oOgbe     
    
    
    Credit card report: When you've got a credit card, there's nothing better than 0% interest. And it appears, a ... http://bit.ly/17oWgsP     
    
    
    Protect yourself the next time you move: The government wants to help you, the next time you move. The U.S. De... http://bit.ly/17oWgJ6     
    
    
    Tricycle recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert for parents. Huffy is recalling its Slider Tricycles. http://bit.ly/11mBeaJ     
    
    
    Protect your identity: Are you doing enough to protect your identity? The Better Business Bureau is reminding ... http://bit.ly/13pYonh     
    
    
    Student debt hurting economy: If your a college graduate under 30, chances are you may be under a mountain of debt. http://bit.ly/13qx4VX     
    
    
    Nissan recalls SUVs to fix brake problem: Nissan is recalling more than 19,000 Nissan and Infiniti SUVs becaus... http://bit.ly/15sS9zh     
    
    
    Home repair scams: Attention homeowners, beware if you're doing any major home renovations or repairs this Spring. http://bit.ly/126jpj8     
    
    
    Email scam warning: There's a new email scam to watch out for. The Better Business Bureau says the email mainl... http://bit.ly/ZiOUb9     
    
    
    Consumer info for sale: Mastercard and American Express are stepping up the sale of their customer information. http://bit.ly/ZiOSjG     
    
    
    Las Vegas is bad for your wallet: Las Vegas is one of the worst cities for your wallet. http://bit.ly/ZiOSzW     
    
    
    Texas explosion scam: Scammers are using the Texas fertilizer plant explosion to target their latest victims. http://bit.ly/11RFRKh     
    
    
    Distracted driving guidelines: Federal safety regulators have issued new rules they hope will limit distracted... http://bit.ly/148shch     
    
    
    Spending your tax refund: Tax season is finally over. So do you know what you're doing with your refund? http://bit.ly/148shsB     
    
    
    Americans getting scammed: Have you been scammed? If so, you're not alone. http://bit.ly/11RFUWs     
    
    
    Snapchat smartphone app raising concerns: A smartphone app that's gaining in popularity, offers a quick way to... http://bit.ly/14tBWdu     
    
    
    Credit cards that help you save money on travel: CardHub has released a list of credit cards that can help you... http://bit.ly/152TRIc     
    
    
    FTC looking to stop cramming scam: The Federal Trade Commission is looking for ways to protect you from gettin... http://bit.ly/152TRIk     
    
    
    Mortgage info to be released: Fannie Mae is preparing to share some of its data with private investors. http://bit.ly/12sWFHW     
    
    
    Baby stuff you don't need: A new report by the Mother Nature Network says some popular baby products are a was... http://bit.ly/12sWFYe     
    
    
    Southwest fined: Southwest Airlines isn't doing such a good job of handling your complaints. http://bit.ly/12sWD2O     
    
    
    Prepaid calling card company in trouble: A company selling prepaid calling cards is in trouble with the government. http://bit.ly/18OcUCF     
    
    
    Memorial Day holiday scams: The Better Business Bureau has a new warning as Memorial Day approaches. http://bit.ly/18OcX1x     
    
    
    Mother's Day email scams: The Better Business Bureau wants to warn you about email scams to watch for. http://bit.ly/18OcUCJ     
    
    
    Buying jewelry for mom: Buying jewelry for your mom or other special woman in your life this Mother's Day? http://bit.ly/18OcUCP     
    
    
    BMW recalls model 3 Series cars due to airbag problem: BMW has issued a recall involving its 2002 and 2003 BMW... http://bit.ly/13AFuXK     
    
    
    Barbecue brush bristles could get stuck in your intestines: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) -- Your barbecue brush could ... http://bit.ly/13RCqH4     
    
    
    Smartphone costs could be going up: If you think the price of your $200 smartphone is pricey, think again. http://bit.ly/10GkDUn     
    
    
    DEBT COLLECTORS!!!  HOW TO PUT AN END TO THOSE CALLS... ON ACTION NEWS LIVE AT 11!!!
MY STORY FOLLOWS BODY OF PROOF ON CHANNEL 13!!!    
    
    
    IT'S A BIG WEEK FOR ABC... JOIN US FOR THE NEWS AT 5, 6, AND 11 PM FOR SOME GREAT STORIES FOLLOWING SOME BIG ABC SHOWS ON CHANNEL 13!!!    
    
    
    Only 2 of 13 small SUVs do well in crash tests: Only two of 13 small SUVs are getting passing grades in front-... http://bit.ly/13qfSKF     
    
    
    OMG!  Big Night on ABC! Watch Grey's Anatomy and Scandal!  Then at 11: 
Contact 13:: How credit cards and smartphones together = Easy Scam!!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Bank alternatives: Americans are finding more and more alternatives to banks. Many people are looking to take ... http://bit.ly/13txmpx     
    
    
    Possible changes to cosmetics: A Congressional bill is looking to make cosmetics safer for you. http://bit.ly/16rCL7I     
    
    
    Stroller safety: The government has signed off on a new stroller safety rule. http://bit.ly/16rCMIE     
    
    
    Summer airfare to soar: If you plan to fly this summer, be prepared to pay a hefty price. http://bit.ly/16rCLo4     
    
    
    Retailers avoiding price-matching: Retailers are finding ways to get out of price-matching guarantees. http://bit.ly/16rCLob     
    
    
    Computer repair scam: No one likes computer problems. http://bit.ly/16FYk4r     
    
    
    Best family cars: Kelley Blue Book has released it's annual list of the best family cars. http://bit.ly/16FYk4x     
    
    
    Sunscreen labels may be misleading: Some sunscreen labels may be misleading. That's according to the consumer ... http://bit.ly/14popAB     
    
    
    Homeowners deed scam: Don't be scammed into paying for a copy of your property deed. http://bit.ly/16FYk4B     
    
    
    Bed recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for mom and dad. http://bit.ly/1a2C8Oz     
    
    
    Air travel survey: Wi-fi is the most sought after amenity in the air. http://bit.ly/180s387     
    
    
    Summer travel and your pet: Are you traveling this summer, and not sure what to do with your four-legged famil... http://bit.ly/1a2C9lx     
    
    
    Oklahoma donation scam: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Scammers are already trying to take advantage of ... http://bit.ly/1a2Cbd5     
    
    
    Roller shades recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Insolroll is recalling some of its roller shades wi... http://bit.ly/14yIlRI     
    
    
    Rug Recall: A Contact 13 consumer alert for Home Depot shoppers. Some rugs by Nourison are being recalled. http://bit.ly/13NFDEY     
    
    
    Memorial Day safety: Make sure to play it safe during your Memorial Day cookout. http://bit.ly/16Xtgxi     
    
    
    Virgin America #1: Virgin America topped the latest airline satisfaction rankings from Consumer Reports. http://bit.ly/16XteFE     
    
    
    Phone scam warning: The Better Business Bureau is reporting the resurgence of a classic phone scam. http://bit.ly/16XteFH     
    
    
    Consumer Reports ranks best and worst sunscreens: As pool season kicks into high gear, you and your family wil... http://bit.ly/177aljM     
    
    
    Homeowners having trouble paying mortgage: Despite improvements in the housing market, many homeowners are sti... http://bit.ly/143jPFF     
    
    
    Retailer swipe fees: The fight continues over swipe fees charged to merchants who accept your Visa and MasterCard. http://bit.ly/143jSB7     
    
    
    Contact 13 helps mother after birthday party food fiasco: It's important that every detail is just right when ... http://bit.ly/17pxo9w     
    
    
    Decline in mortgage or refinancing applications: Less people are applying for a mortgage or refinancing. http://bit.ly/11zBgBu     
    
    
    H&M recalls water bottles because of choking hazard: H&M is recalling some children's water bottles because of... http://bit.ly/11A6AAi     
    
    
    Pottery Barn Kids issues safety recall for crib bumpers: Pottery Barn Kids is recalling Sweet Lambie Crib Bumpers. http://bit.ly/148hPfb     
    
    
    Price comparison for your flight getting tougher: Trying to find the best deal for a flight is getting tougher... http://bit.ly/15knVfr     
    
    
    Hepatitis A outbreak linked to Oregon berry farm: The Food and Drug Administration is investigating an outbrea... http://bit.ly/11IGdbx     
    
    
    Travel scam season: The summer travel season is here, that also means the official start of the travel scam season. http://bit.ly/17Tq9ah     
    
    
    homeowners' insurance spike: The cost of homeowners' insurance is heading up. http://bit.ly/17Tq6ew     
    
    
    U.S. auto sales up: U.S. auto sales rebounded in May. http://bit.ly/15zpir0     
    
    
    Ford recall: Ford motor is recalling 465,000 2013 vehicles because a fuel leak could lead to a fire. http://bit.ly/15zpiHk     
    
    
    Americans are wasting too much food: The government is working to help you waste less food. A new report says ... http://bit.ly/135vp3y     
    
    
    What to buy in June: A lot of shoppers head to the mall this time of year, looking to beat the heat. http://bit.ly/18RZlGW     
    
    
    Prepaid airline fees: United Airlines is offering extra leg room and no luggage fees. But if you want the perk... http://bit.ly/135vm81     
    
    
    Money for victims of foreclosure: If you faced a foreclosure, some money could be coming your way. The Nevada ... http://bit.ly/135vp3I     
    
    
    Chrysler refuses U.S. request to recall vehicles: Chrysler is refusing a request by U.S. safety regulators to ... http://bit.ly/14xb6eZ     
    
    
    Chrysler to recall 630,000 Jeeps: Chrysler is recalling nearly 630,000 Jeep SUVs to fix air bag and transmissi... http://bit.ly/15TTeOw     
    
    
    Target rolling out organic, natural grocery brand: Target Corp. is planning a new organic and natural store br... http://bit.ly/18grub6     
    
    
    Toyota unveils redesigned version of the Corolla: Toyota has unveiled the first completely redesigned version ... http://bit.ly/19au5TF     
    
    
    My little guy isn't so little anymore! Move over #McEnroe... here comes Matthew!!! #happymom pic.twitter.com/x3r1lzMLc3    
    
    
    Good news for housing market across Las Vegas: It's going to cost consumers more to buy a home in the Valley, ... http://bit.ly/14RGDZ9     
    
    
    @DonGuevara1 Like the picture Don!!!    
    
    
    Don g and I are getting ready to turn it out on the news!!! C u soon pic.twitter.com/JqgE4qhuIz    
    
    
    @mlopardi @TriciaKean awww!!! THAT IS WHY I LOVE HAVING MICHAEL AS MY NEWSROOM NEIGHBOR!!!    
    
    
    Company recalls 165,000 baby recliners: A children's product maker is recalling about 165,000 baby recliners l... http://bit.ly/16s1fux     
    
    
    Happy Fathers Day!  We celebrated ours in the OC!#HappyFathersDay pic.twitter.com/cSNBpl26HA    
    
    
    Stride Rite girls sandals being recalled: An important recall notice for parents. http://bit.ly/13VOhm7     
    
    
    Baby bath seat recalled: We have a Contact 13, Consumer Alert. Thousands of baby bath seats are being recalled. http://bit.ly/143fdR1     
    
    
    Beef recall: There's a major ground beef recall to tell you about. http://bit.ly/19SgS2b     
    
    
    Pet food recall: Natura Pet is recalling some of its dry pet foods. There's a chance the food may be contamina... http://bit.ly/143fe7r     
    
    
    Stroller recall: We have a Contact 13 Consumer Alert. A Stroller is being recalled by Kolcraft. http://bit.ly/1965Bfe     
    
    
    Seniors target of online social security scam: New numbers show just how much scam artisits are targeting seni... http://bit.ly/196h8ev     
    
    
    New scam involves Affordable Care Act: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert about a new scam targeting seniors. http://bit.ly/15qUypl     
    
    
    States where your ID is most likely to be stolen: A new list names the top 10 states where your identity is mo... http://bit.ly/19bnGsi     
    
    
    Ross to pay civil penalty: Ross stores are paying a major penalty for failing to report an issue with some chi... http://bit.ly/19mFLUr     
    
    
    Exploding cell phone warning: There's a new warning about exploding cell phones. http://bit.ly/15An9ZE     
    
    
    Starbucks raising prices on many coffee drinks: Your Starbucks latte is going to cost you a little bit more. http://bit.ly/17d23DV     
    
    
    Chandeliers being recalled nationwide: Action News has a Consumer Alert involving a couple chandeliers sold na... http://bit.ly/15Hbp7D     
    
    
    Consumer Reports provides list of best laundrydetergents: Consumer Reports has released its list of the best l... http://bit.ly/19vy7XY     
    
    
    2 viewers receive letters about education grants and unexpected money: Two Action News viewers receive letters... http://bit.ly/13f0rdA     
    
    
    Tonight at 11... If you have a computer you want to check out my story...what happened to a Valley man who tried to get his computer fixed!    
    
    
    Contact 13 helps local couple solve dispute with funeral home: A local couple reached out to Contact 13 after ... http://bit.ly/1a7C99f     
    
    
    What to know if you're contacted by a collection agency: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - It's time to reach into our Co... http://bit.ly/17SSk63     
    
    
    New Chrysler recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for Chrysler owners. The automaker is recalling nearl... http://bit.ly/17T0yv1     
    
    
        
    
    
    Home buyers considering ARM loans: Mortgage rates are on the rise again, and that's got some potential homeown... http://bit.ly/16k0Es9     
    
    
    @ProducerSU call me I don't have your current number!! I miss u girl!    
    
    
    Ford recall: Ford is recalling nearly 13,000 vehicles. http://bit.ly/13KG8Ff     
    
    
    Prepaid Card Report: Credit card comparison website CardHub has released its 2013 Prepaid Card Report. http://bit.ly/12XuDnp     
    
    
    Mortgage relief business shut down: The government has shut down a mortgage relief business. http://bit.ly/12XuFvr     
    
    
    Foreclosure report: The number of foreclosed homes on the market is down sharply. http://bit.ly/13KG8Vx     
    
    
    Hyundai investigation: Federal officials are investigating complaints involving a loss of steering in Hyundai'... http://bit.ly/1apZNOr     
    
    
    America's favorite brands: A new survey reveals some of America's favorite brands. http://bit.ly/16rgYYc     
    
    
    Shop around for best prescription drug prices: Are you paying too much for your prescriptions filled? Consumer... http://bit.ly/15fJ1KX     
    
    
    Mystery shoppers and lottery scams: Today's Contact 13 Mailbag contains information about a scam revolving aro... http://bit.ly/13aHjaM     
    
    
    Homeowners insurance protection when on vacation: Are you renting a condo during your summer vacation this sum... http://bit.ly/1aJsbLk     
    
    
    Should you get an extended car warranty: If you're in the market for a new car, you may be wondering if you ne... http://bit.ly/1aJsdTv     
    
    
    Foreclosure numbers down: Foreclosures numbers are continuing to fall. http://bit.ly/13ncShx     
    
    
    Cell phone hacking: A new report shows just how easy it is to hack into your cellphone. http://bit.ly/1aJsdTB     
    
    
    Military Consumer Protection Day: Tomorrow marks the first Military Consumer Protection Day. http://bit.ly/1bljPJf     
    
    
    Dealing with debt collectors: Many of us have received a call at some point from debt collectors. And it's imp... http://bit.ly/15DiSWm     
    
    
    AT&T upgrade: Tired of your old phone? You can fix that if you're an AT&T customer. http://bit.ly/1blzYOS     
    
    
    Reports of Jeeps stalling: Jeep owners are continuing to complain about problems with stalling. http://bit.ly/1aQovHY     
    
    
    Cost of college: The fall semester is just around the corner and it's costing more and more to go to college t... http://bit.ly/14ezLdx     
    
    
    Mitsubishi recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving the Mitsubishi Outlander. http://bit.ly/13V6luT     
    
    
    Best appliance brands: J.D. Power & Associates has released its list of the best brands for appliances. http://bit.ly/1ba3xUp     
    
    
    Bath seat recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving a infant bath seat. http://bit.ly/1ba3Ajg     
    
    
    Online travel scam: Looking for a good travel deal this summer? http://bit.ly/1ba3xUB     
    
    
    Children's clothing recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. http://bit.ly/13YISc7     
    
    
    Crib recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert for parents. http://bit.ly/13YIQ3W     
    
    
    Infant jumper recall: We want to tell you about the recall of the Kids II Baby Einstein Activity Jumper. http://bit.ly/13YUITD     
    
    
    Link promising video of royal baby delivers virus: The royal birth in Britain has triggered a new social media scam. http://bit.ly/14Ocgs2     
    
    
    Back to school spending: Expect to spend more during your back-to-school shopping trip this fall. http://bit.ly/14gGkX9     
    
    
    Charges in massive hacking: 5 people are charged in connection with a major hacking operation. http://bit.ly/14gGldv     
    
    
    Royal birth Facebook scam: The royal birth in Britain has triggered a new social media scam. http://bit.ly/1brTeuY     
    
    
        
    
    
    FDA warns of steroids in vitamin B supplement: The Food and Drug Administration is warning consumers to avoid ... http://bit.ly/1bvrjud     
    
    
        
    
    
    No cap for bank fees: A federal judge strikes down a rule that sets a cap on the fees that banks charge mercha... http://bit.ly/1bKY32O     
    
    
    Possible refund for some payday loan customers: Some payday loan customers could be getting a refund. http://bit.ly/1bKY32U     
    
    
    Southwest fined: Southwest Airlines is fined for violating price advertising rules. http://bit.ly/1bKY5b4     
    
    
    Faster internet coming to a Starbucks near you: Starbucks is partnering up with Google. http://bit.ly/14DVlCj     
    
    
    Child furniture recalled: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert involving the national recall of some children's... http://bit.ly/16JnLhf     
    
    
    Think before you post: Are you sharing too much info online? http://bit.ly/17mz0LE     
    
    
    Top consumer complaints: An annual list of the country's top consumer complaints finds many of the usual suspects. http://bit.ly/1ct9gTr     
    
    
    Think before you download: Be careful what you download on your computer. http://bit.ly/17mz120     
    
    
    E. coli concerns prompt nationwide beef recall: More ground beef is being recalled across the country for fear... http://bit.ly/1c0fVa8     
    
    
    Save money when doing your back to school shopping: It's time again for back to school shopping. http://bit.ly/157Vuy9     
    
    
    Chevy Volt price cut: If you're in the market for a new car, General Motors has an offer for you. http://bit.ly/1c9ZXdr     
    
    
    Kitty litter lawsuit: Some cat lovers are suing Clorox, the maker of Fresh Step cat litter. http://bit.ly/157Vuyh     
    
    
    August is a good time to buy a new car: August just might be the best month to visit a new car showroom. http://bit.ly/14oG90k     
    
    
    Security freeze on your credit: Identity theft cases are on the rise and that means your risk of being a victi... http://bit.ly/14oQoSd     
    
    
    Water rate hike likely: Las Vegas, NV (KTNV) - You're probably going to be paying more for your water soon. Th... http://bit.ly/13VpOwC     
    
    
    Grant Scam: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert about an ongoing phone scam involving fake grant money. http://bit.ly/15zOvON     
    
    
    Americans doing better with credit: Americans are doing much better at handling their credit. http://bit.ly/1cxQvAN     
    
    
    Local tech expert discusses baby monitor hacking: It's a horrifying idea for parents: Strangers getting to you... http://bit.ly/15FuiY3     
    
    
        
    
    
    Black & Decker coffeemakers recalled due to injury hazard: More Black & Decker Spacemaker Coffeemakers are bei... http://bit.ly/14VIy2L     
    
    
    @ProducingVegas @victoria_spilab @KTNV @LasVegasRikkiC @mtelles    
    
    
        
    
    
    Cookie dough being recalled by ConAgra because of peanuts: Cookie dough, sold at some Nevada grocery stores, i... http://bit.ly/151ltbT     
    
    
    Call for Action helps valley woman get new wheelchair: Imagine the feeling of being trapped in your own home. ... http://bit.ly/1chle1E     
    
    
    Facebook shares some user data: Facebook is sharing a lot of information about its users. http://bit.ly/12Qn8DA     
    
    
    Southwest drink vouchers: Do you have a few drink tickets saved for your next Southwest flight? http://bit.ly/1cl8XJu     
    
    
    Fake Netflix email: Did you get an email from Netflix recently? http://bit.ly/12Qn5Ym     
    
    
    Android targeted by malware: How safe is the personal information on your smartphone? http://bit.ly/1cl8XJA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Research a company you plan to do business with: Many of us book our vacations online these days. http://bit.ly/1dzDtmQ     
    
    
    iPad rentals on Hawaiian Airlines: Hawaiian Airlines passengers are getting a new on-board distraction the iPad Mini. http://bit.ly/176ScMH     
    
    
    J&J recalls Infant Motrin due to plastic specks: Johnson & Johnson is recalling 200,000 bottles of Motrin Infa... http://bit.ly/19uEp6a     
    
    
    Affordable Care Act scam: With one month until health care enrollment beings under the Affordable Care Act, th... http://bit.ly/13BDJew     
    
    
    Scam artists claim to be Southwest Gas employees: Beware of any calls you get allegedly from Southwest Gas. Th... http://bit.ly/1ekgUmH     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ready-to-eat chicken, ham products being recalled: Garden Fresh Foods, a Milwaukee establishment, is recalling... http://bit.ly/1fJVjSL     
    
    
    Nissan recalling 900,000 vehicles worldwide: Nissan is recalling more than 900,000 vehicles worldwide. http://bit.ly/1fKBFGf     
    
    
    New details regarding remaining animals at Las Vegas Zoo: Action News has heard from many viewers over the pas... http://bit.ly/17lFttT     
    
    
    Terry the Chimp leaves Las Vegas, heads for Florida: Terry the Chimpanzee has left the building. He has left t... http://bit.ly/17uv6UW     
    
    
    Merry Xmas to all!!!! Tune into action news at 6 and 11 pm!!! @SpencerLubitz joins me at 6 now pic.twitter.com/IvRjGEienu    
    
    
    Getting ready to ring in the new year on channel 13 at 11 pm Vegas Style!!! pic.twitter.com/c212rgJicO    
    
    
    @TriciaKean    
    
    
    @gschiller13 @corbydavidson    
    
    
    I had fun with the Fabulous Ladies of Las Vegas!!!  HOT LADIES @StefanieJay @mariemortera @paulafrancis8 @LisaRemillard    
    
    
    I am riding solo on the 11 pm news tonight!  Join me for Action News Live at 11    
    
    
    @AnissaChristal @ProWerksMedia @RickMoonen @TriciaKean @sararoseryan    
    
    
    @AnissaChristal @ProWerksMedia @RickMoonen @sararoseryan I can't wait to see it!!!    
    
    
    Floor lamp recall: We have a Contact 13 consumer alert. Big Lots is recalling more than 43,000 Classic Quarters ... http://bit.ly/yVhjpW     
    
    
    Save time on your taxes by filing a 1040EZ: When doing your taxes this year, you can save time and maybe some mo... http://bit.ly/An6pio     
    
    
    U.S. Postal Service price changes: It's soon going to cost you more to mail a first class letter. Beginning Janu... http://bit.ly/Ap3d1U     
    
    
    BMW recall: From Contact 13, we have a consumer alert. BMW is recalling nearly 89,000 mini coopers. http://bit.ly/zsgu05     
    
    
    Used Car prices expected to climb: Kelley Blue Book says now is the time to buy a used or pre-owned vehicle. Use... http://bit.ly/ABRDKq     
    
    
    Burger King delivery: Burger King is testing delivery service. Bloomberg says there are four locations in Virgin... http://bit.ly/zFB0Aq     
    
    
    World's Best and Worst Airport Terminals: Frommers has released its new list of the World's 10 Best and Worst Ai... http://bit.ly/zREBLo     
    
    
    