Listening to @clsaarinen's wonderful preso on meaningful discussions. Amazing how she creates an environment of safety online. #instcon12    
    
    
    @busynessgirl Maybe outcomes as "tags" to assignments and content, which would exist outside the rubric? Someday…..    
    
    
    Shout out from Lisa Frazier to the awesome Instructure implementation managers #instcon12    
    
    
    Heading home now after a fabulous #instcon12 Thanks to everyone, especially @sunnywash and her team for hosting an amazing conference.    
    
    
    Tears of Joy: Canvas Analytics is ON http://j.mp/NGDyXW  Great screenshots from @busynessgirl    
    
    
    Connected Learning Infographic | Connected Learning http://awe.sm/5nD14     
    
    
    @scottwdennis thanks for notes. Those were some of the sessions I wanted to attend and couldn't. Look
forward to video uploads! #instcon12    
    
    
    Mozilla Open Badges ships Beta release | The Mozilla Blog http://awe.sm/5nD1P     
    
    
    Awesome faculty group here at Pasadena City College. Fastest transition to Canvas EVER (Summer classes starting in only 7 days!)    
    
    
    What are badges? / Courses, Study Groups, and Challenges / Knowledge Base - P2PU Support http://awe.sm/5nD1n     
    
    
    @chris3edwards sleep tight then! I'm off to bed as well. Flight from Pasadena to HOME tomorrow. Yay home.    
    
    
    Rubric for Language Skills « http://awe.sm/5nD2A     
    
    
    Scale-Free Schools / An Introduction on Vimeo http://awe.sm/5nD84     
    
    
    Scale-Free Schools / A Day In The Life on Vimeo http://awe.sm/5nD9J     
    
    
    thanks @busyinessgirl for some great tips! --> Online Office Hours in Canvas http://j.mp/Kze3lN  @instructure @learncanvas    
    
    
    Badges, Portfolios, and Blending Formal and Informal Learning | FunnyMonkey http://awe.sm/5nD9o     
    
    
    @clsaarinen Absolutely. Still loving your preso from #instcon12 - could we feature a discussion in the Designer Guide? http://guides.instructure.com/s/2204/m/5834/l/55357-posting-and-responding-to-discussion-topics …    
    
    
    @clsaarinen great! just sent you the info    
    
    
    Tin Can API Viewer http://awe.sm/5nDAV     
    
    
    Badges – Less Yack, More Hack « Lonely Lion http://awe.sm/5nDBv     
    
    
    Check it. @devlindaley announcing Analytics in Canvas http://vimeo.com/44878523     
    
    
    Working through the hard stuff of #badges: Developing a Conceptual Framework while Unearthing Underlying Tensions http://awe.sm/5nDCV     
    
    
    What is good design? http://awe.sm/i0VM5  (nice list)    
    
    
    Yes. Yes. Let’s make badges not stink : Sharing Nicely http://awe.sm/5nDCj     
    
    
    @scottwdennis SO cute! We've got lots of them around here that's fo' sure..    
    
    
    Can Badging Be the Zipcar of Testing and Assessment? | DMLcentral http://awe.sm/5nDDE     
    
    
    Man, I wish you guys all the luck in the world! Peer 2 Peer University (P2PU) | HASTAC http://awe.sm/5nDFX     
    
    
    Nothing like the looping sound of a record player when you least expect it. Ah, nostalgia. Thank you Jon Barrios http://awe.sm/5nDFr     
    
    
    @busynessgirl Safe travels!    
    
    
    Very cool. Badges Go To Graduate School | iterating toward openness http://awe.sm/5nD4F     
    
    
    @busynessgirl speaking of math and Angry Birds, why… there's a course for that. =) http://www.udemy.com/math-is-everywhere-applications-of-finite-math/ …    
    
    
    @iampaulanthony hadn't checked in for a while.. love the "moooodmap" http://friendlymusic.com/#mood  - keep rockin'!    
    
    
    U.S. Student-Loan Debt Swells http://www.businessweek.com/video#video=xtZG1sNDqC4FIl8aXdFDRyBIdGSXeluR …    
    
    
    The Six Enemies of Greatness (and Happiness) - Forbes http://awe.sm/5oIb0     
    
    
    Bake House Piano Drop 2012 - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLaK     
    
    
    Wheat and chessboard - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLeB     
    
    
    @deekgeek @jordandayton Sweet!    
    
    
    @deekgeek @jordandayton "InstructureMan" - isn't he adorable? =)    
    
    
    Circular Automower (video) - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLhs     
    
    
    For all you northeasterners…. Canvas User Group - a NERCOMP event http://linkd.in/NmvxpB  organized by @clsaarinen    
    
    
    Washington State Higher Ed Shifting to Instructure Canvas -- Campus Technology http://awe.sm/5tVue     
    
    
    Seth Godin Blog: Monetizing digital attention http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2012/07/monetizing-digital-attention.html … via @ThisIsSethsBlog    
    
    
    The Google+ Hangout that changed the way I will view communication forever http://tnw.to/k1FK  via @TNWinsider    
    
    
    Examples « Designing Better Learning Experiences http://awe.sm/5ugpw     
    
    
    Online Teaching Tips - YouTube http://awe.sm/5uhcP     
    
    
    great idea for using comments in the SpeedGrader @busynessgirl Video Code Easter Eggs http://j.mp/SFlYDP  @learncanvas    
    
    
    e-Learning Project Management - YouTube http://awe.sm/5uhrR     
    
    
    @deekgeek hi! Still working on that! I'll let you know when it goes live (probably not 'til September)    
    
    
    Adding Captions to Tegrity Recordings http://awe.sm/5vckN  - nice vid @scottwdennis (p.s. does anybody in WA want to caption all our vids?)    
    
    
    @scottwdennis Thank you! That's a great start.    
    
    
    The Center for Generational Studies - Cost-Saving Webinars to Resolve Your Generational Challenges http://awe.sm/5xHQh     
    
    
    5/23/00 Short Summary of Learning Style Inventories http://awe.sm/5xHRJ     
    
    
    oldie but goodie: Are College Students Techno Idiots? | Inside Higher Ed http://awe.sm/5xHja     
    
    
    The Millennial Muddle: How Stereotyping Students Became an Industry - Students - The Chronicle of Higher Education http://awe.sm/5xImS     
    
    
    Thank you @allibrown27 and @mallgood01 for updated docs on Mobile Apps! !!! http://awe.sm/d1uJu  @learncanvas    
    
    
    Taking forward change in technology-enhanced education http://awe.sm/5xItr     
    
    
    Twitter Symbols might come in handy at some point! http://awe.sm/b1yv0     
    
    
    Charles Dziuban on The Net Generation, Learning Styles and Technology-Enhanced Education Start at 12:00 http://awe.sm/5xHSY     
    
    
    Michelle Pacansky-Brock and Chuck Dziuban - "Ask the Experts" panel - Sloan-C ALN conference 2008 - YouTube http://awe.sm/5xJ5l     
    
    
    Narrating • Curating • Sharing: "No digital facelifts" http://ustre.am/:8iLi  - thanks for lead @jstein    
    
    
    Oh my goodness, a tripod site! Asynchronous Learning Network ความหมาย http://awe.sm/5xJ9c     
    
    
    NCAT: Learning MarketSpace, October 2001 http://awe.sm/5xJEt     
    
    
    Bayston - Key to Long-Dziuban http://awe.sm/5xJGb     
    
    
    @brocansky Thanks for your well-produced VISUAL slides. =) http://awe.sm/5xJLI     
    
    
    Technology - Alan Jacobs - The Great Unbundling of the University - The Atlantic http://awe.sm/5xJUF     
    
    
    Macrowikinomics http://awe.sm/5xJVD     
    
    
    Many Eyes : Probability to use web based educational service http://awe.sm/5xJcc     
    
    
    Many Eyes : Education spending and unemployment http://awe.sm/5xJeR     
    
    
    Check out recently updated Admin Guide http://guides.instructure.com/m/4214  via @allibrown27 (Post suggestions below the lesson) @learncanvas @instructure    
    
    
    Many Eyes : Education vs Hours Per Week http://awe.sm/5xJfo     
    
    
    @JordanDayton You ran up there??? Crazy cat    
    
    
    Getting ready for on-site training with Vancouver SD tomorrow. S'gonna be good! #instructure #learncanvas    
    
    
    Many Eyes : Gender wage gap by educational attainment http://awe.sm/5xJgV     
    
    
    Looking forward to: Best Practices for Teaching with Emerging Technologies Michelle Pacansky-Brock: Books http://awe.sm/5xKcs     
    
    
    @injenuity @jjjohnson01 @mattmcghie @jordandayton Hail Captain JJ, Rogue of Rogues! ps I love Washington. Was just in Vancouver today..    
    
    
    Sloan-C’s Definition of ‘Online Course’ May Be Out of Sync with Reality « Educational Technology and Change Journal http://awe.sm/5xN3E     
    
    
    Rogue Med Student Tackles the Web's Ultimate Irony http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2012/08/researchgate/ …    
    
    
    Have you read Groundswell? Charlene Li, Josh Bernoff: Books http://awe.sm/5xPLm     
    
    
    What your designs say about you (moral component of design)| Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xm3L     
    
    
    http://vimeo.com/47732039  Bill Gates: Employers decide whether a new credentialing system will take hold or not.    
    
    
    Lisa Harouni: A primer on 3D printing | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xmZu     
    
    
    Dan Meyer: Math class needs a makeover | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnPG  (Math reasoning example at 5:00)    
    
    
    PPT causing the illusion of understanding. Dance vs. powerpoint, a modest proposal | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnjK     
    
    
    @holden @instructure Try one of the suggestions under the "How do I include extra credit..." section here: http://guides.instructure.com/s/2204/m/4152/l/46543-what-is-the-difference-between-a-canvas-assignment-and-a-canvas-activity …    
    
    
    @holden @chris3edwards @instructure @iYantho oh good, you found it already!    
    
    
    @chris3edwards thanks! :)    
    
    
    Joe Sabia: The technology of storytelling | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnoG     
    
    
    Beauty is in the limbic system of the beholder - Richard Seymour | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnw4     
    
    
    Steve Jobs building NeXT 20 min (Learning Simulations & Apple II's in the Classroom) http://awe.sm/5ySTn     
    
    
    Thanks @clonghb for your intro to the #CATprogram. Excited to have you in the course!    
    
    
    What is ZebraZapps? on Vimeo http://awe.sm/605iD     
    
    
    PRO ZebraZapps - LMS preview on Vimeo http://awe.sm/605rn     
    
    
    ImTranslator - Plug-in for FireFox. Version 4.16 http://awe.sm/hHfM     
    
    
    The CAT Preparation Course is now live. Take a look around. Tell your friends. https://training.instructure.com/courses/360911  #CATProgram    
    
    
    @snappity you can definitely count that toward CAT Hours @chris3edwards more info on the #CATprogram here http://bit.ly/CATprogram     
    
    
    Great post! Hacking the Screwdriver: Instructure’s Canvas and the Future of the LMS http://awe.sm/f08Rw     
    
    
    I want to go to near space! Take me! Lucky Edgar. - HD balloon flight to 95,000ft - YouTube http://awe.sm/a0YR2     
    
    
    Free, open-enrollment PBL (Project Based Learning) course in Canvas @biepbl #instructure http://awe.sm/f0ia9     
    
    
    The Canvas Video Contest has begun! Submissions due by Sept 30th. http://www.instructure.com/video-contest  #Instructure    
    
    
    The New Credentialing Stack http://awe.sm/j4ba9     
    
    
    a @whitmer lead... Nice K12 resource! | MIT + K12 http://awe.sm/c1BUr     
    
    
    Great book. The Extraordinary Leader : Turning Good Managers into Great Leaders http://awe.sm/a2bdK     
    
    
    Latest @instructure blog post: http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/215810/Listening-to-Our-Customers … - newly organized feature request forum will make you smile thx 2 @busynessgirl    
    
    
    @injenuity NicE!    
    
    
    Lovely advice. http://www.marcandangel.com/2012/01/29/20-things-to-start-doing-in-your-relationships/ …    
    
    
    @spolsky on User Interface and FEELINGS...nothing more than FEELINGS... http://www.joelonsoftware.com/uibook/chapters/fog0000000057.html …    
    
    
    Excellent video channel with lots of great @instructure Canvas tutorials by Brown University http://awe.sm/b3v5b     
    
    
    Just noticed this LTI integration - YouTube For Schools http://awe.sm/m3RTq  - sweet!    
    
    
    New lesson on Canvas Guides thx to @allibrown27 How do I give my students extra credit?: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78195-how-do-i-give-my-students-extra-credit …    
    
    
    We Have a Plan: Canvas Status Communication Plan via @memacfar http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/219651/We-Have-a-Plan-Canvas-Status-Communication-Plan …    
    
    
    Mozilla and P2PU badge pilot program - http://awe.sm/i4axm  built off of OSQA, cool!    
    
    
    Canvas Guides | How do I link course content to a Quiz question?: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78275-how-do-i-link-course-content-to-a-quiz-question … @learncanvas    
    
    
    w00t! @brackenm @allibrown27 for LTI documentation & moodle course import http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/220762/LTI-Common-Cartridge-and-Moodle …    
    
    
    @devlindaley tells the Instructure story, shares startup approach http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XD6eOd6K8Qw … just another fun and busy day @instructure    
    
    
    Props to @clsaarinen for organizing first #CanvasSIG Enjoy @testorip @chris3edwards @whitmer !    
    
    
    The Most Important Challenge For Colleges Isn't Price-It's Attention - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/06/the-most-important-challenge-for-colleges-isnt-price-its-attention/258471 …    
    
    
    Checking out Purdue University's digital badge app tonight http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/passport-profile/id552400654?mt=8 … #openbadges    
    
    
    Chris McAvoy's overview of Mozilla's Open Badges project - YouTube http://awe.sm/f4atB     
    
    
    Astra Taylor on the Unschooled Life - YouTube http://awe.sm/k45cq     
    
    
    MebiPenny 2012 aka nerds nerding out about nerdy nerd things (love it) http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/220126/MebiPenny-2012-Results-and-Wrapup …    
    
    
    @parkerwightman Good for you!! #beatsthechest #tribalpride    
    
    
    @prawsthorne Thank you for the "fall cleaning" - very helpful for newcomers. #openbadges    
    
    
    @clonghb =) something about donkeys and goats…there are rules but they obviously get broken.. to each their own!    
    
    
    Just in case you hadn't heard: http://awe.sm/g5B7V  #openbadges    
    
    
    @holden just in case you didn't see it, we now have a separate guide on extra credit: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78195-how-do-i-give-my-students-extra-credit …    
    
    
    http://Amazon.com : Rework (9780307463746): Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson: Books http://awe.sm/e57WK     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland You and your team were awesome this morning! I see only training awesomeness coming from Rider. =)    
    
    
    Read all about it! The CAT's out of the bag http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/222533/The-CAT-s-out-of-the-bag … #CATprogram    
    
    
    @tinsleykim that's correct - Level 1 of the #CATprogram is free - more benefits if you advance to Level 2, which does have a fee.    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland you bet!    
    
    
    the importance of designing and implementing a communication architecture via @bhorowitz http://awe.sm/d5CAM     
    
    
    Vision versus Hallucination – Founders and Pivots « Steve Blank http://awe.sm/i5MGs     
    
    
    Don't delay! You still have 20 minutes to register for LearnCanvas LIVE! https://learncanvas.webex.com/mw0307l/mywebex/default.do?siteurl=learncanvas … @instructure @learncanvas    
    
    
    @clsaarinen u rocked the first LearnCanvas LIVE! webinar - way to go!!    
    
    
    @coursera launches The Lean LaunchPad Online « Steve Blank http://awe.sm/d5CDg     
    
    
    Algorithm predicts tweet-worthy articles --> http://phys.org/news/2012-08-news-article-tweetworthy-algorithm.html …    
    
    
    Badges in the real world | o p e n m a t t http://awe.sm/f5LOF  #openbadges    
    
    
    Online Sign Up Sheet -- Jooners http://awe.sm/a5Czj  (great idea for quick sign-up and collaboration, hope it takes off)    
    
    
    Having a blast working with @PHMschools this week. Especially after Notre Dame beat Michigan last wknd. :) Irish spirits are high.    
    
    
    Nice blog of tech tools powered by Randy Hogue and friends @PHMschools http://dmstechplace.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    4 good posts on Standards-Based Grading: 1) http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=391 … 2) http://mctownsley.blogspot.com/2012/09/standards-based-grading-explainers.html …  3) http://fnoschese.wordpress.com/2012/08/23/keep-it-simple-standards-based-grading/ … 4) http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=2859 …    
    
    
    More ideas for implementing SBG Grading: 1) http://alwaysformative.blogspot.com/p/standards-based-grading-implementation.html … 2) http://standardsbasedgrading.wordpress.com/2012/09/23/student-tracking-sheet-for-sbg-learning-targets/ … 3) http://blog.mrmeyer.com/?p=5597     
    
    
    Standards-Based Grading: FAQ http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=673 …    
    
    
    Foundation: HTML Templates http://awe.sm/i5N9l     
    
    
    Another Java vulnerability puts *1 billion* users at risk http://blogs.computerworld.com/malware-and-vulnerabilities/21056/another-critical-java-vulnerability-puts-1-billion-users-risk …    
    
    
    Take time to contemplate says Susan Cain: The power of introverts | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/c5PAQ     
    
    
    @busynessgirl You've probably already seen this: beautiful online graphing calculator https://www.desmos.com/calculator     
    
    
    @sjciske thanks!  I take it you are a fellow intro. =)    
    
    
    http://degreed.com/  is now in BETA - talks to #openbadges - congrats @davidblake @ericgsharp @mgadams3 @opencontent    
    
    
    Open UI Designer position http://awe.sm/m5Zjy  #instructure @pzich wish you were out of school - spread the word pls    
    
    
    Via @nprnews and @rodandon: In Japan, Mobile Startups Take Gaming To Next Level http://n.pr/NEU2gx     
    
    
    Add a touch of humor to your K12 course with daily cartoon widget in Canvas - embed code here: http://www.andertoons.com/free-cartoons/  thx @rodandon    
    
    
    @rodanadon I mis-tweeted your handle earlier. Can't wait till you push your CS course into Canvas. It's gonna be awesome! #makeitpublic    
    
    
    Ask a Neuroscientist: Thinking and physical activity | Minnesota Public Radio News http://awe.sm/k5Glv     
    
    
    v00t! @jstein has just launched our new learning blog: Share Like a Pollinator, Blog Like a Bee (speak like a German) http://awe.sm/g689F     
    
    
    me gusta… here's to our many lives of reinvention! http://www.smbc-comics.com/index.php?db=comics&id=2722 …    
    
    
    This is SUCH good news for the 21st century. Cute Images Make Us 44% Sharper [STUDY] http://awe.sm/g68Lt     
    
    
    Leaving ADDIE for SAM #leavingaddieforsam http://www.astd.org/Publications/Books/Leaving-ADDIE-for-SAM … by Michael Allen with @rhillsites    
    
    
    love this article: The Trouble With Online Education - http://NYTimes.com  http://awe.sm/e5bPU     
    
    
    Open Architecture: Our Course Could be Your Life http://learning.instructure.com/2012/10/open-architecture-our-course-could-be-your-life/ … via @jimgroom    
    
    
    Teachers, Designers: BUY THIS. Joseph Bergin et al have done us a great service by collecting, refining #pedpatterns http://awe.sm/b5cUr     
    
    
    @jodiemoule where do I download @thecookapp ? Thx 4 a good read    
    
    
    Distilling the patterns of group dynamics - some interesting ideas here - Pattern Language of Group Process http://awe.sm/l5Hc9     
    
    
    Nice tips on using the Media Comment Tool to "coach" your students in Canvas http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/220095/Coaching-with-Canvas-Media … #Instructure    
    
    
    QR Code generator - create QR Codes for free via @clonghb - goQR.me http://awe.sm/j5p07     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland Good Luck!!    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland Oh, that's awesome. I want to hear more!    
    
    
    Many thanks to @clonghb for sharing a showcase course in #Canvas with activities from his Physics A class. Super cool. https://canvas.instructure.com/courses/769163/     
    
    
    Browse PhET contributions http://awe.sm/c5kHJ  These Math and Science Simulations embed very nicely in #Canvas    
    
    
    Check out @ryankshaw's work on html5 video captioning solution. Happiness for mobile and accessibility! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cBkgxtlMdTU …    
    
    
    New single by good friend! Into The Blue | Naomi LaViolette http://awe.sm/n5Uc5     
    
    
    Nice intro to #openbadges rocket fuel for the accreditation of skills thanks to @dajbelshaw http://awe.sm/g67ZY     
    
    
    all I have to say today is: @scottwdennis is in the house and we are *so* glad to have him at @instructure (sad for Wash, happy for Utah)    
    
    
    Educause resource (from May 2012) Easy-to-read description of #openbadges http://awe.sm/f67n6     
    
    
    CODING TOGETHER | Piazza Report for Summer 2012 class on iPhone iPad development http://awe.sm/f69y9     
    
    
    Users Bring Real Value to Big Data, Machine Translation | Cloudline | http://Wired.com  http://awe.sm/k5ltM     
    
    
    DIARY OF A PUBLIC SCHOOL TEACHER!: Morning Meeting Moments Create Critical Thinkers! http://awe.sm/l6IHk     
    
    
    Happyness! New @instructure video you can use to introduce your faculty to #canvas + groovy new look and feel http://www.instructure.com/try-canvas     
    
    
    @bignato @instructure Obrigada. ;) Kudos to @mattmcghie for awesome new promo video!    
    
    
    2nd of 5 days here in Mishawaka, IN. Penn Harris Madison SD is leaving textbooks behind and building their digital curriculum in Canvas.    
    
    
    Hunting for new course design ideas? See updated list of public Canvas courses here: http://guides.instructure.com/s/2204/m/5834/l/55579-staff-picks … #instructure #CATProgram    
    
    
    Headed home after long but fun week in Mishawaka, IN. Penn Harris Madison SD is off to a great start with Canvas!    
    
    
    @chris3edwards lame-o. too much eating out this week for me too…    
    
    
    Hi @foresmac Sitting in MDW. Not raining here… =)    
    
    
    @clonghb Happy Birthday! =)    
    
    
    Great post by @clonghb re: Flipped Classrooms: ASQ Before You Teach -  http://learning.instructure.com/2012/10/flipped-asq/ …    
    
    
    @clonghb Absolutely! =)    
    
    
    I know I'm last to the party, but Notability app for iPad is sort of awesome https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/notability-take-notes-annotate/id360593530?mt=8 …    
    
    
    How to learn more about #openbadges | Bananigans! http://awe.sm/d7vB7     
    
    
    This looks kind of cool. Wonder how good it is. How To Develop & Document Personas & Scenarios by Susan Weinschenk http://awe.sm/c7vlv     
    
    
    @parkerwightman thanks!    
    
    
    Course-Management Companies Challenge MOOC Providers The Chronicle of Higher Education http://awe.sm/n7x3s  #instructure    
    
    
    #instructure Takes On The Courseras & Udacities Of The World With Its Own Open Course Network | TechCrunch http://awe.sm/i8QNt     
    
    
    Wish I could see Elbow in London before the end of the year… Garvey's gonna write music for King Kong musical. http://www.nme.com/news/elbow/66861 …    
    
    
    lol Jimmy Kimmel iPad Mini Commercial http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RyWSEwKPo8s&sns=fb …    
    
    
    Nice  summary of Mayer's Ten Principles of Multimedia Learning via Regina DeLong at the Univ of Utah http://ericsnewblog.blogspot.com/  #CATProgram    
    
    
    Just in case you didn't see the announcement, Open online courses for *everyone* http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/239786/Four-score-and-yesterday … #CanvasNet &then http://www.instructure.com/try-canvas     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland Glad to hear it. Now go cut some trees!    
    
    
    w00t! Give it up for @busynessgirl's new math games - http://bit.ly/algeboats  http://bit.ly/algeburstlite     
    
    
    Apache OpenOffice, LibreOffice aim for Office 2013, cloud support in '13, '14 | ZDNet http://awe.sm/g9J4g     
    
    
    Incorporating Differentiation - Gooru http://awe.sm/m8tD3     
    
    
    kinda like a diigo/endnote for students http://www.citelighter.com/tutorial  - looks promising!    
    
    
    Game of Thrones Violin Cover - be the 3,947,730th viewer http://youtu.be/1yydcG9woWA     
    
    
    Community "club" first, space, tools second. Post on Coworking http://dangerouslyawesome.com/2011/08/coworking-core-values-4-of-5-community/ …    
    
    
    7min interview with @davidblake re: http://Degreed.com  http://soundcloud.com/instructional_design/david-blake-degreed-com …    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland yeah, I definitely dig diigo.. here's a group you might like needs updating http://groups.diigo.com/group/best-edu_blogs …    
    
    
    interesting idea. How do we leave "rough edges" in our online or offline environments that invite participation? http://dangerouslyawesome.com/2012/10/offline-user-experience-design-lessons/ …    
    
    
    @codecademy I would like to second this suggestion http://help.codecademy.com/customer/portal/questions/394020-suggestion-keyboard-shortcut-for-starting-next-exercise-and-next-session- …    
    
    
    Here I go! :) @parkerwightman http://www.codecademy.com/courses/ruby-beginner-en-d1Ylq/2 …    
    
    
    my_name="!nozilla".upcase.reverse rar rar rar http://www.codecademy.com/users/designsolver62663 …    
    
    
    I didn't know... We could be hauling around "BicycleBook Pros" http://Folklore.org : Macintosh Stories: Bicycle http://awe.sm/k8v9r     
    
    
    If you ever need an OER intro video, there are lots here to choose from >> Why Open Education Matters http://awe.sm/m8t0T     
    
    
    @Codecademy thank you! (I noticed it minutes after I tweeted…) I have the observation skills of a tiger. =)    
    
    
    http://www.insidehighered.com/news/2012/10/01/competency-based-education-may-get-boost … - 20 institutions have joined WGU with competency-based offerings    
    
    
    Thx Debbie Pearson @usufact for sharing her training experiences http://trackcanvastraining.blogspot.com/  #Instructure #CATProgram    
    
    
    Tips on managing online discussions - ie. post to first reply and latest reply, assign discussion roles and moderators http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uTpEVLxbcvQ …    
    
    
    @debbiepearson68 great Turnitin resource https://usu.instructure.com/courses/58886/wiki/turnitin … Share here: http://help.instructure.com/forums/20351027-community-created-resources … #CATProgram #Instructure    
    
    
    Incorporating Differentiation - Gooru http://awe.sm/m8tD3     
    
    
    Nice @tceb62 lecture (start about min 10) http://youtu.be/lGOTwFvkfhU  &then read the book: http://www.ideo.com/by-ideo/change-by-design?cbd …    
    
    
    Phenom post about learning programming, which can be applied to many other kinds of learning/being/thinking. thank you @worrydream    
    
    
    @dadweiss See link to @worrydream's post: http://worrydream.com/LearnableProgramming/ …    
    
    
    @JordanDayton Have you seen/used this journal app? https://itunes.apple.com/app/day-one-journal-diary/id421706526 …    
    
    
    @web20classroom how about a thinking and doing workforce for a dynamic global economy? I don't see those as mutually exclusive. #WISE2012    
    
    
    @jordandayton @scottwdennis @allibrown27 Spread out your Tweets over the day with @bufferapp: http://buff.ly/Tx4xFF     
    
    
    Just finished delivering training at Kenan-Flagler. Wish I had time for at drive to the beach or mountains. <3 the beautiful fall colors..    
    
    
    Solar eclipse timelapse video in Australia http://www.guardian.co.uk/science/video/2012/nov/14/solar-eclipse-australia-timelapse-video …    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/Tx8Dh9  Assessing Online Facilitation (AOF) Instrument (en español también)    
    
    
    @busynessgirl I'm reading A Theory of Fun on the way back to SLC -- it's great! http://www.amazon.com/Theory-Fun-Game-Design/dp/1932111972 …    
    
    
    @iDevKaren Awesome job!    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/Tx8Lx3  Effective online facilitator is equal parts Instructor, Social Director, Program Manager, Technical Assistant    
    
    
    NEW: Crocodoc and Grading in Canvas by @busynessgirl http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/243761/Crocodoc-and-Grading-in-Canvas … Check out screenshots of SpeedGrader in action #CATprogram    
    
    
    Yay for unwarranted optimism! http://bit.ly/VZ2VJe     
    
    
    The anti-MOOC? Small costly online courses http://bit.ly/Wfv9zu  via @instructure    
    
    
    An Idea Too Sensible to Try, Until Now - Commentary - The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/UeHjnW     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving Canvas Friends http://bit.ly/UgxtSH     
    
    
    List of Assessment Tools http://bit.ly/UgYqFY     
    
    
    Strategic Innovation and Ideas | Canvas Network http://bit.ly/Wtg3qe     
    
    
    thx @dadweiss for link to situated cognition article (1989) by @jseelybrown http://www.exploratorium.edu/ifi/resources/museumeducation/situated.html …    
    
    
    Today’s Campus Innovation Interview #4 – @whitmer of Instructure Canvas http://bit.ly/UemPMk     
    
    
    thx to @BarryBerkus Designing from Nature and using onion skin overlays to track how ideas evolve (power to the pencil) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X95etnApDS8&feature=share&list=ULX95etnApDS8 …    
    
    
    Disasters as an opportunity for design http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i6RM2qM9zDU&feature=share&list=ULi6RM2qM9zDU …    
    
    
    How architects get ideas and the iterative  on them http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fwJB7KzDEbQ&feature=share&list=ULfwJB7KzDEbQ …    
    
    
    Great insight into the mind of a designer http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vmHoGicPQQQ&feature=share&list=ULvmHoGicPQQQ …    
    
    
    Constraints, opportunities, problems in the mind of a designer http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KtbtzcSkc5o&feature=share&list=ULKtbtzcSkc5o …    
    
    
    Canvas Network: Instructure takes on Coursera, et al, with a unique approach to MOOCs | ZDNet http://zd.net/Wth15K     
    
    
    Thank you Charlie, I mean, @alliBrown27 for the new quickstart guides>> Student: http://guides.instructure.com/m/8470  Instructor: http://guides.instructure.com/m/8472     
    
    
    Show Me Your Badge http://nyti.ms/UepzJn  #openbadges    
    
    
    I just donated to #Wikipedia. Help keep it free! #keepitfree http://bit.ly/tDmpbI     
    
    
    A Future Full of Badges The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/UepDJg  #openbadges    
    
    
    #openbadges | Computer Science Student Network http://bit.ly/UeA2oh     
    
    
    Get your Canvas on >>> InstructureCon 2013 http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/247069/Announcing-InstructureCon-2013 …    
    
    
    Academic Partnerships, Instructure Partner for Online Learning Initiative http://bit.ly/Yu04sy     
    
    
    Examples of Alpine skiing badges - Ecole de ski http://bit.ly/WtrbU4  - notice the student-centric "I Can" statements #openbadges    
    
    
    Boy Scouts of America - Entrepreneurship Badge http://bit.ly/UeBkj9  #openbadges    
    
    
    Cars 2: The Video Game Achievements http://bit.ly/UeBMhb  - We need a name for achievement-like badges - microbadges? #openbadges    
    
    
    Annotated Documents within Canvas.mp4 (from the Student's perspective) - YouTube http://bit.ly/VgWETU  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Crocodoc demonstration - YouTube http://bit.ly/VgWKuE  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Great tips for Smart Student Presentations -  http://learning.instructure.com/2012/12/smart-student-presentations/ …    
    
    
    To Learn, Learn to Ask (good eLearning pic) http://bit.ly/Vh5IrG     
    
    
    Five-Minute Film Festival: The Future of Education | Edutopia http://bit.ly/YIW1Zx     
    
    
    @dadweiss you'll like this https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fiGabUBQEnM …    
    
    
    Creativity is the Future of Education - YouTube vid http://bit.ly/YJ448J     
    
    
    Digital Aristotle: Thoughts on the Future of Education (Digital Aristotle) http://bit.ly/VhnOtP     
    
    
    Is YouTube Making Us Smarter?  YouTube http://bit.ly/VhorDy     
    
    
    Sugata Mitra, "Hole in the wall" guy, tells his story https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hqsTD4CzRYM …    
    
    
    PHD Comics: Beware the Profzi Scheme http://bit.ly/Wv6yXm     
    
    
    Numberphile - YouTube http://bit.ly/YOuFkI  - Awesome way of introducing graphs using Choose Your Own Adventure books.    
    
    
    Teaching Online course developed by the team @USFlearning >> http://bit.ly/YjzvGm  #CATProgram    
    
    
    How Chocolate Can Help Repair Spinal Damage in Rats: http://bit.ly/Vk9vEA     
    
    
    Top 100 Tools for Learning 2012 « Centre for Learning & Performance Technologies http://bit.ly/YPxBO7     
    
    
    The Hobbit: An Unexpected Journey, Video #9: http://youtu.be/4vqyzHwnEiY     
    
    
    Learning objects repositories - EduTech Wiki http://bit.ly/Vb6C9j     
    
    
    Something like http://www.oswd.org/  or http://ui-patterns.com/  but for online course design… takers, anyone?    
    
    
    thanks @clonghb for sharing this tidbit about submitting Google Spreadsheets in Canvas (they ARE Crocodoc-able) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZlSAq1DzfPk&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Fostering Critical Thinking Using Asynchronous Discussions - Center for Innovation in Research and Teaching http://bit.ly/YyPl01  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Download link to Using the Four-Questions Technique to Enhance Critical Thinking in Online Discussions http://bit.ly/YyPxwc  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Writing Effective Learning Objectives from Queen's University (2008) http://bit.ly/Vba7MU  #CATProgram    
    
    
    Enjoying working with the @PLTWorg folks in Indianapolis today. Awesome curricula meets awesome #Canvas learning platform    
    
    
    How to Design Effective Online Group Work Activities - Faculty Focus | Faculty Focus http://bit.ly/YyR3OX  #CATprogram    
    
    
    @snappity irony, indeed. I bet there are a lot of folks in a similar situation..    
    
    
    @snappity absolutely! next deadline is 6/30    
    
    
    12 Screencasting Tools For Creating Video Tutorials (seeking updated list - do you have one?) http://on.mash.to/YySyNa     
    
    
    Melanie's Canvas Training Hours Blog: Training Hours Part III: Digital Tools http://bit.ly/YIz0pI  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Developing a 21st Century Entrepreneurship Curriculum: http://wp.me/prGQZ-3nK  via @sgblank    
    
    
    ► Love HYPEM http://bit.ly/Zr2Lf8     
    
    
    A to Z: Web 2.0 http://bit.ly/YIz3St  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Cool. @rmurchshafer embeds this single-page intro for students into several of his courses https://bluecast.creighton.edu/blueline/orientation/StudentOrientation.html … #CATProgram #Instructure    
    
    
    @snappity yes, of course! that's the nice thing about rolling deadlines. You can jump on the #CATprogram bandwagon every 6 mo    
    
    
    @busynessgirl you'll like this =) Vi Hart - Doodling in Math Class - YouTube http://bit.ly/YOtMbS     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland way to go, awesomner!    
    
    
    Peaceful music for Christmastime ♫ Colour Bird – Hymns from Nineveh http://spoti.fi/UPpkVh  #Spotify    
    
    
    Fernando Rubio on Why I Use @canvasnet http://vimeo.com/55814680  -- check out his course here: https://www.canvas.net/courses/improving-your-spanish-pronunciation …    
    
    
    Hit of Dewey: "the art of thus giving shape to human powers and adapting them to social service, is the supreme art" http://bit.ly/VkH5KF     
    
    
    hey, good news... I've been using http://allmytweets.com  in the meantime. http://blog.twitter.com/2012/12/your-twitter-archive.html … via @twitter    
    
    
    When do I *stop* doing customer interviews and start writing code? http://bit.ly/12pIKo1     
    
    
    Zeitgeist 2012: The Most Blogged Artists and Tracks of the Year • The Hype Machine Blog http://bit.ly/12q0uQj     
    
    
    The Best Education Tools For Teachers - Edudemic http://bit.ly/T7Qqr1  via @edudemic    
    
    
    Nice job! Enjoying reading Helice Agria's #CATprogram training blog.    
    
    
    Loving new icon set in #canvas. So clean! #watchout2013    
    
    
    Great op for #CATprogram @HybridPed Online Journal to host MOOC focused on MOOC on #canvasnet http://bit.ly/UhCv0f  via @jessifer @slamteach…    
    
    
    @rmurchshafer Congratulations!    
    
    
    @ThomasTurano … and Bob couldn't be happier. ;) Happy New Year!    
    
    
    Reuse, not production, is key to positive MOOC impact - http://learning.instructure.com?p=53learning.instructure.com/?p=53     
    
    
    5 Tips to Optimize Canvas for the New Year http://bit.ly/TtDddF     
    
    
    Writing goals for 2013 today. Inviting more forgiveness, compassion, peace, and joy into my life. http://bit.ly/UiPOxA  (thx @iPEC_Coaching)    
    
    
    happy new year @scottwdennis @clsaarinen @allibrown27 @JordanDayton @busynessgirl @chris3edwards @jstein @mattmcghie @mallgood01 we miss u    
    
    
    @busynessgirl oh, that was for @mallgood01 ! =)    
    
    
    Needless competition is what is killing higher education, Followers of the Apocalyspe edition | Hapgood http://bit.ly/UneeYk     
    
    
    link to @heliceagria's sweet training blog http://bit.ly/TuDAVa  #CATprogram    
    
    
    Canvas for F2F Instruction Quick Reference Guide.docx http://bit.ly/UgG60b  via #CATprogram participants @mesacc - great job!    
    
    
    hey hey hey - it's a voicethread LTI app for Canvas! http://bit.ly/UiMuSX     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/Uj07mQ  Vanilla Forums now has auto-login for Canvas http://bit.ly/UiMthV     
    
    
    Another great preso by Helice Agria @mesacc re: "Canvalytics" - http://bit.ly/UgGZFW  and http://bit.ly/TtfGcM  #CATprogram    
    
    
    What kind of learning do you value the most? - YouTube http://bit.ly/UI5Nux  #moocmooc    
    
    
    DON’T treat others the way YOU want to be treated. | Zen Workplace http://bit.ly/UnfvyC     
    
    
    Most blogged-about music in 2012 - new playlist in Spotify. ♫ Hype Machine Zeitgeist 2012 http://spoti.fi/VTg2XV  #Spotify    
    
    
    2012 Instructure Year in Review http://bit.ly/X6DK4Q     
    
    
    In the End, Monoliths Crack « Piazza Blog http://bit.ly/ULAdvT     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland Congratulations on your 40 hrs! Especially with everything you've got going on! #CATProgram    
    
    
    Facebook Charging $100 to Message Mark Zuckerberg http://on.mash.to/VUT2IF     
    
    
    Declines in Tuition Revenue Leave Many Colleges Financially Squeezed - Bottom Line-The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/UWyTX9     
    
    
    Believe you can change (in honor of @aaronsw) http://bit.ly/UZSHsH     
    
    
    OLPC XO-4 convertible laptop is faster than ever and coming soon (hands-on) | The Verge http://bit.ly/UWzzM5     
    
    
    The 31 most influential classic books in education – a crowd-sourced list « Granted, but… http://bit.ly/VUST80     
    
    
    "Colleges are about branding and validation, period. That’s why they can afford to post their lectures ... for free." http://bit.ly/UWGl4A     
    
    
    Mix videos, GIFs & sounds! http://bit.ly/VWQxWi  - high production value? no. easy way to get organized before a lecture? yes.    
    
    
    My favorite LTI Tool right now: Redirect Tool http://bit.ly/V01VW0  works for course, user, and account navs in #Canvas    
    
    
    @clonghb :-) glad you enjoyed it!    
    
    
    How California’s Online Education Pilot Will End College As We Know It | TechCrunch http://tcrn.ch/W42tWz     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland looks gooood    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland nice! and why am I not surprised? ;)    
    
    
    Some Nice Resources for Implementation & Training | Closing the Gap http://bit.ly/WdLh0N  #CATProgram    
    
    
    Interactive Statistics and Connected Learning http://bit.ly/VS4Le7  - I'd kinda like to see a lesson plan before I donate..    
    
    
    Conscious Parenting at TEDxSF (7 Billion Well) - YouTube http://bit.ly/WhYu96     
    
    
    Form Follows Function http://bit.ly/Wi6tmC  that's two Warhol hits in one night    
    
    
    What if Khan Academy was made in Japan? - YouTube http://bit.ly/VSi0vk     
    
    
    What is the best iPad stylus? - YouTube http://bit.ly/VTDgB4  (I like the jot pro)    
    
    
    TinEye Labs - Multicolr Search Lab http://bit.ly/Wybas6     
    
    
    Canvas Peer Review Assignments - Teacher and Student Perspective-YouTube http://bit.ly/VOM4rC  thx @jstein    
    
    
    New tutorial video on Groups - Creation and Management (for Instructors) on Vimeo http://bit.ly/VOOsyO  thx to @JordanDayton #CATprogram    
    
    
    "Learning Analytics and Knowledge" - facilitated by @gsiemens | Canvas Network http://bit.ly/WApsbC     
    
    
    @clsaarinen Trying to restrain myself from signing up for too many but enrolled here and so far, it's great! https://www.edx.org/courses/BerkeleyX/CS169.1x/2013_Spring/about …    
    
    
    Holiday Gift Ideas for Young Makers & Tinkerers http://bit.ly/Whq1aA  great for #homeschoolers    
    
    
    I want to try this. Suitable Technologies Beam Remote Presence System http://bit.ly/WhJojZ     
    
    
    Noam Chomsky on Post-Modernism (wonder if he's changed his mind at all since then) http://bit.ly/WhSPQd     
    
    
    We should be living in the future already | tomasz by Tomasz Tunguz http://bit.ly/VS1zPR     
    
    
    How to nail your product market fit and sales pitch with a value proposition diagram | tomasz by Tomasz Tunguz http://bit.ly/VS1pIb     
    
    
    Haven't tried it yet, but looks cool: Free Technology for Teachers: How To Use Google Docs **Offline** http://bit.ly/WRbhz8  via @clsaarinen    
    
    
    does anybody else like freshbooks theme song as much as I do? #jinglesstillwork - YouTube http://bit.ly/WhUhlQ     
    
    
    Is there a tool out there like this for ux design? Ability to fork is cool. Overview Video - Upverter http://bit.ly/WhVnOn     
    
    
    Did anyone get to play with this at #CES2013 What did you think? PaperTab: http://bit.ly/YkQGIN     
    
    
    @rishtal hmm. looks interesting. I'll take a look. thanks!    
    
    
    @hong_chau @nercomp @canvassupport @instructure we prefer that whenever possible folks link to Guides, since it is constantly being updated.    
    
    
    ACE to assess Udacity courses for credit | Inside Higher Ed http://bit.ly/VS3KCQ     
    
    
    Canvas Instruction Guide in ASL - YouTube http://bit.ly/WMYspv  (I want a transcript) #CATprogram via @scott    
    
    
    @clsaarinen come back soon!! Have a safe trip home.    
    
    
    I like this man's "messy wiki mind" - fun to read through http://learningevolves.wikispaces.com/pyramid     
    
    
    and yes! another follower of pedagogical patterns http://learningevolves.wikispaces.com/design+patterns     
    
    
    The Centipede was happy quite / Until the toad in fun / Said, Pray which leg comes after which?    
    
    
    This wrought her mind to such a pitch She lay distracted in a ditch Considering how to run —Anonymous    
    
    
    Holiday Gift Ideas for Young Makers & Tinkerers http://bit.ly/YoqIEa  - good list for homeschoolers and others with the gift of time    
    
    
    Nice resource page on basic HTML & CSS http://www.dontfeartheinternet.com/resources     
    
    
    Removing a group or individual from a Collaboration will remove permissions from the Google Doc as well! Lovely. http://vimeo.com/58256742     
    
    
    via @ddmeyer What if Khan Academy was made in Japan? - YouTube http://bit.ly/WNE8V1     
    
    
    3-Act Math Tasks http://bit.ly/WGgfPk  @ddmeyer knows how to create great activities,problems - thinking of Allen's CCAF http://bit.ly/WGghXg     
    
    
    Trenet, trenet, you are my muse. The most complete collection of Trenet I've ever found. Thanks to @spotify http://spoti.fi/VsThPU  #Spotify    
    
    
    The 4 Learning Styles: What defines your learning and training style? - YouTube http://bit.ly/11gvfVf     
    
    
    @hong_chau @clsaarinen I don't know of anyway to turn off home link in course nav, if that's what you mean..    
    
    
    What I'll Miss Most About the MiniDisc http://mashable.com/2013/02/01/minidisc-discontinued/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    @instructure is looking for Software Engineers in Chicagoland
http://jobvite.com/m?3llfHfwm  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Software Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3WqfHfw2  #job    
    
    
    Gonna check out Learning Creative Learning http://bit.ly/WKMUWt  #medialabcourse    
    
    
    TEDxCreativeCoast - McGrath Davies-The Future Will Not Be Multiple Choice-YouTube http://bit.ly/WKJeDZ     
    
    
    Ambient music/sounds to change it up. // Thunderstorm http://bit.ly/VNbRyX     
    
    
    E-Book Reader Accessibility and Comparison Matrix - Accessible Classroom Technologies-Carmen Wiki http://bit.ly/WL5bTp     
    
    
    A Tale of Two MOOCs | http://bit.ly/WMDhGK     
    
    
    A Dangerous but Powerful Idea - Counter Acceleration and Speed with Slowness and Wholeness : The Knowledge Tree http://bit.ly/WRtH5i  (2007)    
    
    
    It’s the Feedback, Silly! P2PU’s Plan for Badges | Peer to Peer University http://bit.ly/W00ynk  #obenbadges    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Employee Referral!
http://jobvite.com/m?3hjNHfwO  #job    
    
    
    Force Flash Update in Google Chrome (when you don't want to wait) - YouTube http://bit.ly/X0glUv     
    
    
    Grand Canyon – Street View! –Google Maps http://bit.ly/YmHUEv     
    
    
    Learning Creative Learning - Session 1- #medialabcourse http://bit.ly/X0BsWP     
    
    
    Touché: Enhancing Touch Interaction on Humans, Screens, Liquids, and Everyday Objects - YouTube http://bit.ly/157vUNq     
    
    
    Tom Wujec: Build a tower, build a team - YouTube http://bit.ly/Xbglhk  #lcl367 #medialabcourse    
    
    
    Classic How It Works Video: A Differential Gear | Popular Science http://bit.ly/15fL2se  #lcl367    
    
    
    Blending High- and Low-Tech Worlds with a Maker-Driven Agenda | DML Hub http://bit.ly/XbAgN7  #lcl367 #medialabcourse    
    
    
    @Sassmo if you need a small group home, feel free to join us in #lcl367 https://plus.google.com/communities/114116863745397967050 …    
    
    
    Video http://bit.ly/Xd0P4u  the danger of decontextualized content #lcl367 #medialabcourse    
    
    
    @worrydream shares a powerful lesson on abstraction http://worrydream.com/#!/LadderOfAbstraction … #lcl367 #medialabcourse    
    
    
    great re-make ♫ Maneater – the bird and the bee http://spoti.fi/JyIGY3  #Spotify    
    
    
    http://allisonweiss.wordpress.com/2013/02/16/finger-patterns-gears-from-my-childhood/ … "Gears from my childhood" Week 2 activity #medialabcourse #lcl367    
    
    
    Resource being pulled together by K12 teachers in #medialabcourse https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/lv?key=0Am2cxA0SJglEdGhpRVk4NnVLUnRodzU3YzRzQW4zZmc&usp=sharing …    
    
    
    MOOCs and Pedagogy: Part 2 | Larry Cuban on School Reform and Classroom Practice http://bit.ly/15kMaL9     
    
    
    @worrydream had you seen this video? http://youtu.be/XaA9UwHE0yg  related to your abstraction examples    
    
    
    #ds106 community activity (blog posts, comments and tweets) - gource-YouTube http://bit.ly/Xcogy8  - way cool.    
    
    
    thinking: where does conversation come from? maybe we need an auto group-merger when activity is low http://cogdogblog.com/2013/02/15/ds106-comment-groups/ … #ds106    
    
    
    If you ever need a kick in the pants to come up with a fun assignment: Hello. #ds106 http://assignments.ds106.us/     
    
    
    Russian meteor exploded with force of **30** Hiroshima bombs - Telegraph http://bit.ly/Yyl8cR     
    
    
    Historia de la música occidental en siete minutos | History of Western Music in seven minutes. http://youtu.be/If_T1Q9u6FM     
    
    
    RSS workaround for twitter that works for most widgets: http://davidwarlick.com/2cents/?p=3981  << @jstein    
    
    
    6312 online courses currently listed at http://myeducationpath.com/courses/     
    
    
    @clonghb me too! love that you designate data repository or keep in form    
    
    
    Let Children’s Play (with Technology) Be Their Work in Education  http://bit.ly/YyEgYi  nice infographic on Mindstorms #medialabcourse    
    
    
    a shout out to all the beautiful people who encourage me to keep groovin'. thanks #KidPresident http://youtu.be/l-gQLqv9f4o     
    
    
    History of the Internet:1969-2012 | Daily Infographic http://bit.ly/Xd0Mc8     
    
    
    Awesome strikes again. How to create captions for the videos uploaded in Canvas http://ow.ly/hOWuk  #accessibility #universaldesign    
    
    
    Really Useful Development Resources - http://bit.ly/YC8ABg  #linkfest    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Software Engineers Chicagoland
http://jobvite.com/m?3uGoIfw0  #job    
    
    
    @hackpad (based on etherpad) looks cool Q: What is the limit of simultaneous users per page? http://ow.ly/hPd8w  http://ow.ly/hPvpx     
    
    
    If you aren't totally sick on infographics yet, I give you an infographic on infographics http://bit.ly/Xd0QbP     
    
    
    @ricetopher are you referring to those specific visualizations or to http://qz.com  ?    
    
    
    Prettiest interactive timeline I've ever seen.. The Evolution of the Web http://bit.ly/YyFnqH     
    
    
    Catch a glimpse of new #instructure HQ under construction... http://www.instructure.com/about-us     
    
    
    Why Gloomy Pundits and Politicians Are Wrong About America's Education System - Derek Thompson-The Atlantic http://bit.ly/YBOOG2     
    
    
    @hackpad that's great! I believe http://titanpad.com/  has a practical limit of 16 concurrent users - at least that has been my experience    
    
    
    important to expect failure (we need another word IMO) http://precisiondiving.com/2013/02/07/redefining-failure/ … #medialabcourse    
    
    
    @cstarrett How about "cogniventure" or "metaventure" as potential replacement? "I cognivized"? I'll keep cogniventuring. =) #medialabcourse    
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K_M1Ii92OY8#t=2m25s … use Adobe Reader to build a syllabus (complete with objectives based on Bloom's taxonomy) thx 2 @idbygeorge    
    
    
    @clsaarinen woot! u rock    
    
    
    @cstarrett it's a #failprize I have #failprizes all the time, all day long, everyday. Now we're getting somewhere... =)    
    
    
    @cstarrett sí sí, it's an original. Instead of #fail all over the place, we should start #failprize whenever we observe a learning event    
    
    
    @cstarrett #failprize as in "Your prize for failing" and "Surprise! You just learned something!"    
    
    
    @JordanDayton explains how to add captions to your uploaded videos in Canvas http://vimeo.com/59855852#  More here >> http://ow.ly/hTYJK     
    
    
    this looks good http://www.amazon.es/How-Learning-Works-Research-Based-Jossey-Bass/dp/0470484101 … thx for lead @dadweiss    
    
    
    @rubenrp shares his preso on SAMR in high school http://www.hippasus.com/rrpweblog/archives/2012/12/12/SAMRUpperSecondary.pdf … - Substitution, Augmentation, Modification, Redefinition #CATProgram    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Release Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?31pZIfwR  #job    
    
    
    another great project to do with my nieces and nephews from #medialabcourse http://hlt.media.mit.edu/?p=2505     
    
    
    LiveCode, modern-day HyperCard http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/1755283828/open-source-edition-of-livecode … Does anybody have a spare £55,000 ? #medialabcourse    
    
    
    @clonghb I can second that @busynessgirl has put together a great course!    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland not right now, but I'll be sure to tweet next time we are. :)    
    
    
    Steve Blank's honest account of Failure and Redemption http://bit.ly/XDEaib     
    
    
    List of different ways you can use the iPad plus some of the tried and true apps http://bit.ly/XDN0ML  #edtech    
    
    
    Stop Requiring College Degrees - Andrew McAfee-Harvard Business Review http://bit.ly/15Nql7q  #openbadges via @degreed    
    
    
    @busynessgirl I think it was http://rubriq.com     
    
    
    #LAK13: Recipes in capturing and analyzing data: Canvas Network Discussion Activity Data http://mashe.hawksey.info/2013/02/lak13-recipes-in-capturing-and-analyzing-data-canvas-network-discussion-activity-data/ … via @mhawksey < very cool!    
    
    
    The Case Against Gold Stars http://bit.ly/15NKudw  good for #openbadges conversation    
    
    
    Passion, Curiosity, Strategy, Idea-Refinement, Interest-Driven, Self-Assessment in WOW http://youtu.be/BhuOzBS_O-M  #gamemooc #medialabcourse    
    
    
    Most Thorough Summary (to date) of MOOC Completion Rates |e-Literate http://bit.ly/13kfbaG  - average completion rate 7.6% via @PhilOnEdTech    
    
    
    Real-life skills found in game play (final 10 min from #gamesmooc webinar) http://youtu.be/Aby1mzt2mjo?t=1h17m24s … #medialabcourse @cstarrett re: #failprize    
    
    
    @haskell's preso on Gaming in Education and the Game of Education http://bit.ly/WkXG8t     
    
    
    Don't miss live Google spreadsheet with data from Canvas Network course Discussion activity: http://bit.ly/13kqHmw  via @mhawksey    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland busy, busy!    
    
    
    @kurtbeer I've been to @ice_il before - fun conference, enjoy!    
    
    
    another coding school - thinkful - http://bit.ly/15SelSa  Self-Guided Curriculum + Relevant Skills + Live Mentor + Employer Network (Jobs)    
    
    
    @davidweiss here's that 3doodler I was telling you about  http://www.the3doodler.com/gallery/     
    
    
    Alan Kay: Powerful Ideas Need Love Too! #medialabcourse (Loved the "1 piano per child" analogy!) http://www.campbells.org/Rant+Rave/r+r_PowerfulIdeas.html …    
    
    
    Session 4: Powerful Ideas - Exploring learning as a form of translation http://bit.ly/147dmd2  #medialabcourse    
    
    
    Badges Lend Gravitas To Free Education Revolution - Forbes http://onforb.es/XBo2xz  #openbadges    
    
    
    @cstarrett +1 repeat signs! :)    
    
    
    Digital Badges: An Annotated Research Bibliography v1 | HASTAC http://bit.ly/14abuA6  #openbadges    
    
    
    Exploring CUNY Games Network | Category Archive|Education Games http://bit.ly/13uir3B  #gamesmooc    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Financial Analyst
http://jobvite.com/m?3v7CJfwH  #job    
    
    
    @JordanDayton - awesome intro to March 9th release >> VARIED DUE DATES - hurray!! :) http://help.instructure.com/entries/21637300-03-09-13-Canvas-Production-Release-Notes-Featuring-Varied-Due-Dates …    
    
    
    Critical Technology: Personal Curriculum Mapping (PCM) http://bit.ly/13DrgIc     
    
    
    @JohnLacey's http://www.dystopiadaily.com/  < fun idea for a  final project http://www.johnlacey.com/edcmooc/dystopia-daily/#more-3449 …    
    
    
    Kitchen Hacks | Food & Drinks|Learnist http://bit.ly/14tmlFs     
    
    
    @grantwiggins looks way cool @clonghb have you tried the Video Physics app?    
    
    
    Emerging Student Patterns in MOOCs: A Graphical View http://bit.ly/13HnltS   < Hmm, what about the Networkers, Doers, and Talkers?    
    
    
    Ten Tips for Designing Mobile Learning Content by Gerry Griffin : Learning Solutions Magazine http://bit.ly/13Hw6El     
    
    
    Organizing my browser tabs now more than I'm organizing my desktop files. Need better tab organization - tips? http://bit.ly/13Hwfrn     
    
    
    5 examples of how the languages we speak can affect the way we think http://bit.ly/YgQMuX     
    
    
    @Spanish_110 es http://wisr.co/ZnsVL1     
    
    
    @501SpanishVerbs to grieve, to groan, to moan http://wisr.co/Znt1Cb     
    
    
    @501SpanishVerbs probarse http://wisr.co/Znt5C7     
    
    
    Reuben Margolin: On Kinetic Art - YouTube http://bit.ly/14GhiSp     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: QA Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3hCfKfwC  #job    
    
    
    @kurtbeer Training in Noblesville, IN today - in your neck of the woods!    
    
    
    Short personality test based on C. Jung and I. Briggs Myers type theory http://bit.ly/Yk7qL2     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Liferay Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3HzQKfwA  #job    
    
    
    Jesse Robinson » Making an image transparent in Pixlr http://bit.ly/103rFAs     
    
    
    SVPG: The Inconvenient Truth About Product http://bit.ly/YkBO85     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/Ylce2O  A conceptual model of cMOOCs by @fredbartels    
    
    
    Airplay Mirroring Alternative for OLDER iOS devices: iPhone 4 / 3GS and iPad 1 - YouTube http://bit.ly/ZEeZOh     
    
    
    via @fredbartels Social Networks Reveal Structure (And Weaknesses) of Businesses http://bit.ly/YpQjaM  @busynessgirl #CNSoME    
    
    
    Breaking Down: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=g2vGlSNbPYQ … Building Up: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4BtKAkP5xOk …    
    
    
    The Sight Reading Project - great for a Canvas recording assignment: Exercise Viewer http://bit.ly/Zj0PzY     
    
    
    Adult education is "a co-operative venture in non-authoritarian, informal learning": Eduard C. Lindeman http://bit.ly/ZlI276     
    
    
    The Importance of Community to Learning http://bit.ly/ZlIsdD     
    
    
    Great tips for delivering online course - instructor's presence is key http://bit.ly/Y8R5N9     
    
    
    Different than you might be used to: Creating Engaging Presentations http://bit.ly/ZlIEJV     
    
    
    Using Visuals and Visual Learning | Tennessee Teaching and Learning Center http://bit.ly/ZlIRwy     
    
    
    Using Andragogy to Meet the Needs of Adult Learners | The Sloan Consortium http://bit.ly/ZlJt5x     
    
    
    Principles of Online [Course] Design: Analysis-Objectives-Activities-Evaluation-Strategies http://bit.ly/ZlJLck     
    
    
    Community-Based Learning and Research http://bit.ly/ZlK7js     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: QA Engineer Intern
http://jobvite.com/m?3xQuLfwm  #job    
    
    
    =) nice find. Le papier ne sera jamais mort / Paper is not dead on http://bit.ly/Zm9DoE  ! on Vimeo http://bit.ly/Y9nHGt     
    
    
    My favorite list on this site; by NETS standards http://bit.ly/YaHFk7     
    
    
    "Hi, my name is Joe. And I work in Da Button Factory" - Create pretty buttons online, quickly! http://bit.ly/YaMbyV     
    
    
    Learners Should Be Developing Their Own Essential Questions | User Generated Education http://bit.ly/11E3Yhn     
    
    
    Design Is Hacking How We Learn http://slidesha.re/11E4xYt  (Slides 24 & 25)    
    
    
    Experience Trumps Theory: Reviving the Apprenticeship Model - 99U http://bit.ly/11LDbQ7     
    
    
    Manifesto for Teaching Online (UK) http://bit.ly/11LFbrI     
    
    
    5 Reasons to Use Group Chat - TalkerApp Blog http://bit.ly/168aJso     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Marketing Intern
http://jobvite.com/m?3op7Lfwp  #job    
    
    
    It's coming.... WebRTC... Interop Notes say Firefox and Chrome can now talk to each other - WebRTC http://bit.ly/YrI41H     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Market Development Representative
http://jobvite.com/m?3biMMfwL  #job    
    
    
    See-through brain - YouTube http://bit.ly/ZhJskj     
    
    
    Announcing the Canvas App Center http://bit.ly/114HoyR     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Software Engineer - SIS Integration
http://jobvite.com/m?3OO3Nfwc  #job    
    
    
    CAT Corner Hours in t minus 12 https://training.instructure.com/courses/360912/conferences/21103 … #CATProgram  Learning today about BigBlueButton Conferences    
    
    
    Great webinar @instructure @mhawksey: turning Canvas Discussion Data into this http://hawksey.info/nodegl/#0AqGkLMU9sHmLdEo1SWk5RTZRcE5CNmFTXzZhaUpmUmc … See: http://mashe.hawksey.info/2013/02/lak13-recipes-in-capturing-and-analyzing-data-using-sna-on-canvas-discussions-with-nodexl-for-when-its-not-a-snapp/ … Übercool    
    
    
    @chris3edwards @sexysaxman oh my goodness oh my goodness...    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Client Services Coordinator
http://jobvite.com/m?3LSRPfw3  #job    
    
    
    The Lean Startup - iterate, iterate, iterate http://bit.ly/11cdVHn     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Director, Business Intelligence
http://jobvite.com/m?3O1xQfwW  #job    
    
    
    @emwitty Why yes, I have. :) I work for Instructure, maker of Canvas. What's up?    
    
    
    @emwitty Ha ha - it's all good! If you ever need a demo of Canvas, let me know. Documentation here: http://guides.instructure.com/     
    
    
    @emwitty Oh, and spread the word out there in Chicago: http://instructure.github.io/lti_bounty     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Product Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3YeiRfw5  #job    
    
    
    Middle School and High School Collaboration Rubric http://bit.ly/10wdXlY     
    
    
    Workshops — Hackidemia http://bit.ly/15PI4hg     
    
    
    "you cannot simply transport what you do in the classroom online." http://bit.ly/15PLaC1     
    
    
    Spotify launches in Hong Kong http://bit.ly/12hBOsf  | First Komeda http://bit.ly/12hBOsh , then Spotify. The Swedes are killing it.    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Director, K12 Sales
http://jobvite.com/m?3h83Rfw3  #job    
    
    
    Viewpoint: MOOCs can strengthen academia « Armando Fox http://bit.ly/10KMNIm     
    
    
    What Online Learners Want Article - Magna Publications http://bit.ly/184GgRr     
    
    
    Characteristics of Successful Online Teachers and Learners http://bit.ly/184Gjg0     
    
    
    ZAPT Document Converter (WORD DOC > ACCESSIBLE HTML) http://bit.ly/13LwQqF     
    
    
    Designing for Social Media - Goodreads in Social Media 2013 - Serendipity35 http://bit.ly/184M8de     
    
    
    Thanks to @ShaunJHolland for sharing this: http://bit.ly/10MQjSB  http://bit.ly/10MQjSD  #catprogram    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Software Engineer Intern
http://jobvite.com/m?3sUISfwG  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Director, Talent Acquisition
http://jobvite.com/m?3TSrTfwP  #job    
    
    
    Roominate: A Building Toy for Girls – How-To http://bit.ly/17oEiLB     
    
    
    Instructure Raises $30-Million in Funds - Wired Campus-The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/1b6dIEk     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Director, Services
http://jobvite.com/m?3PWdUfwC  #job    
    
    
    Mozilla Open Badges Blog — Former President Bill Clinton Supports Open Badges at Clinton Global Initiative America http://bit.ly/11NccWn     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Social Media Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3iFVUfww  #job    
    
    
    @melrizzuto @ThomasTurano is the totally tubular -- I'll see you there!    
    
    
    @ThomasTurano perhaps, perhaps.. :)    
    
    
    gearing up for my third #instcon - sgonna be goooood.    
    
    
    @snappity @thomasturano @heliceagria is here already??! oh, yeah    
    
    
    @snappity great job! Can't wait to watch the rerun.    
    
    
    Ready to learn from @clonghb alls about the Canvas Challenge at Huntington Beach Union High School District    
    
    
    @emily_wood awesome! I'll see you in SpeedGrader :)    
    
    
    @clonghb souped up his Canvas Challenge with a @Prulu forum and @google docs FAQ pic.twitter.com/zhkwIWxV53    
    
    
    @allibrown27 rockin her preso on documentation >> appreciate the docs team hard work! http://guides.instructure.com  #instcon    
    
    
    @clonghb you were pretty über yourself, Mister Long! Thx for introducing me to the new food source http://www.larabar.com/products/uber     
    
    
    Now begins the two months it will take to digest all of the cool presos and connect w/ all the cool people I met at #instcon #awesome    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland Safe travels! So great seeing you.    
    
    
    "Learning occurs best in a playful state, and anxiety inhibits playfulness." http://bit.ly/1c8Nguh  school as prison pic.twitter.com/7kXB1qssSa    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Mobile Engineer - Android
http://jobvite.com/m?36eFVgwF  #job    
    
    
    @budtheteacher nice what we don't know that we don't know is what hurts us the most. That's why we need each other. And twitter. Ya know? :)    
    
    
    Nice blog for language faculty from UMD team: http://bit.ly/12AOxZL     
    
    
    "Focus on giving your readers a reason to interact, not just leave a comment." http://bit.ly/12DReJY  (good advice for online discussions)    
    
    
    Linear Gradients http://bit.ly/12go3Za  #cooltool    
    
    
    Devoth's HEX 2 RGBA Color Calculator http://bit.ly/12go4MJ  #cooltool    
    
    
    HSLa Grid http://bit.ly/15jlISs  #cooltool    
    
    
    Dribbble - Browse by color http://bit.ly/15jlKtK  #cooltool    
    
    
    Dan Higbie | Design, Development, and Photography http://bit.ly/15jlVFm  makes me miss the west coast    
    
    
    Fonts tagged 'handwritten' | Font Squirrel http://bit.ly/12golz7  #cooltool #nomorecomicsans    
    
    
    Just learned about Discourse last week - love the idea of this as an LTI tool in Canvas http://bit.ly/12gouTo     
    
    
    Idea Selection: Rationality is not enough >> "Collect and share all available information" http://bit.ly/15pfpNj     
    
    
    @busynessgirl back to the future http://bit.ly/1aQ4lg9     
    
    
    PerfectReader 2 Lite - Fast, Beautiful PDF Reader & Annotator for ALL the devices and works great with Canvas #cooltool    
    
    
    I spy @davidweiss http://cl.ly/image/2P1i3Q3w0X21 … #wwdc :)    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: GL Accountant
http://jobvite.com/m?3SFGXgwV  #job    
    
    
    Protip for watching #instcon presentations, fast: http://bit.ly/15sc7Xy  Visit YTchannel here: http://bit.ly/15sc5iq     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/12MzFYL  when unscalable is good    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Facilities Coordinator
http://jobvite.com/m?3QCnYgwy  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Art Director
http://jobvite.com/m?3sM5Ygw2  #job    
    
    
    FEAR OF FLYING on Vimeo http://bit.ly/18JpPeM     
    
    
    This I Believe http://bit.ly/13DnZ6D     
    
    
    @wardjhs & friends shares great resources for flipped classroom >> http://www.flipinutah.org/     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Recruiter
http://jobvite.com/m?3mtNZgwm  #job    
    
    
    @IantheMorris @scottwdennis I think u guys set the new #canvas training world record!    
    
    
    Of Romans and Milestones http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/307721/ … #canvas by #instructure hits 7 million users    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Mid-Size Regional Director, K12
http://jobvite.com/m?353v0gwo  #job    
    
    
    Qualtrics and Instructure Partner to Reveal Top Motivations for MOOC Students | Canvas by Instructure http://bit.ly/1d8dZdN     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Inside Sales Rep
http://jobvite.com/m?3eBb1gwM  #job    
    
    
    @snappity cool! First Five: 5 Steps to a Canvas Course:Public - Google Drive http://bit.ly/13JQlCD     
    
    
    Come 'n get it.. 2.0 >> Canvas for Android http://bit.ly/16Be7Pp  and Canvas for iPhone, iPod touch, and iPad http://bit.ly/16Be6uw     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Canvas Network Business Development Representative
http://jobvite.com/m?35GT1gwq  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Part-Time Office Coordinator
http://jobvite.com/m?36Dy2gw4  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Senior Business Development Manager (Position Based in the United Kin...
http://jobvite.com/m?3YGg3gwI  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Director of DevOps
http://jobvite.com/m?3AO23gwe  #job    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Database Admininstrator (DBA)
http://jobvite.com/m?38DL4gwl  #job    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland oh yeah! I'm gonna add that last one to the fall cohort class.    
    
    
    Finally back in the office and enjoying my new view of Death Star and the Wasatch Front pic.twitter.com/LbPOuBeXgn    
    
    
    @hahntro Dantooine ... I mean ... noooooo!    
    
    
    Strong start @StefanieSand! Looking forward to the next eight weeks as well! #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: QA Automation Engineer
http://jobvite.com/m?3n7x5gwR  #job    
    
    
    Thx @mkaulbach @robinwb for pointing to this resource on connecting with online learners http://bit.ly/16a72q7  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Just wrapped up our first #CATProgram Corner Hour with about 10 folks in #BigBlueButton. Moving to Chat now http://bit.ly/19kiBrp     
    
    
    **45** Canvas Training Videos now avail http://bit.ly/1bYCBqD  w abt 20 more on the way - Great work by @scottwdennis @jordandayton @sspend    
    
    
    Thx to @suesstudio for link to article "How to Build an Ethical Online Course" @HybridPed http://bit.ly/17srzGD  #catprogram #canvaslms    
    
    
    Technology at it's finest. http://www.ipadgameforcats.com/  #catprogram #canvaslms    
    
    
    @pintar you go girl! :)    
    
    
    @anna_kraftson Wonderful to see you approaching beginning Canvas instructors from the standpoint of mobile devices.    
    
    
    @canvasnet with all the cousins http://bit.ly/GCWdTU  (interactive map)    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Software Engineer - Partnerships
http://jobvite.com/m?3Ceg6gwX  #job    
    
    
    @KathyRuby1 I just posted the peer assignments in the Week 2 Backchannel. I will update when more submissions come in.    
    
    
    yep | Maslow's Hierarchy of Needs, updated http://bit.ly/18CwUuG     
    
    
    16 of us in the #CATProgram Corner Hours this morning using Padlet and LinoIt #CanvasLMS Moving to course chat now... http://bit.ly/19kiBrp     
    
    
    @carsonau cool! good news is it's archived for 14 days in the course so you can watch the whole thing when you have the time.    
    
    
    EdTechTrek | Makers are Timeless… http://bit.ly/GCXdYa  what are you making this weekend?    
    
    
    The Passion-driven classroom by @AngelaMaiers - Know and show your passion, the students’ passion, the world passion http://amzn.to/GCY6jo     
    
    
    @wardjhs - another list ThingLink http://bit.ly/15N5B2I     
    
    
    @StefanieSand Way to go! Enjoy your weekend!    
    
    
    Student Video: Common Craft - "It's Funner!" | Common Craft http://bit.ly/19vQFVR     
    
    
    pretty, module-esque | Curiosity http://bit.ly/18CApB3  - also Blendspaces, which you can embed in Canvas pages http://bit.ly/GCYVbZ     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Marketing Campaign Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3X9J6gwG  #job    
    
    
    Ender's Game - Movie Trailers - iTunes http://bit.ly/GCZCCi     
    
    
    Enjoying the CanvasLIVE Q&A with @Befitt Great questions from the Canvas Community https://learncanvas.webex.com/  < Join us next time #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    @KathyRuby1 http://www.spreadshirt.com/design-your-own-t-shirt-C59 … send me your ideas!    
    
    
    amazing ▶ Brandon Wynn - Still Rings - 2013 World Championships - Event Finals - YouTube http://bit.ly/17p8rGj     
    
    
    http://usergeneratededucation.wordpress.com/2013/05/07/its-all-about-connection/ … - Education. It's all about relationships. via @jackiegerstein    
    
    
    @ryflinn great ideas here for K12 writing rubrics pic.twitter.com/ocubjCYCIi    
    
    
    @iDevKaren Agreed! We have an awesome cohort this fall. #CATprogram #canvaslms    
    
    
    Really do not tire of @jmessersmith's sound http://spoti.fi/18YAJer     
    
    
    90% of happiness comes from the way you process the world http://bit.ly/1ac07KV  thx @tinsleykim    
    
    
    "Active Student: The deep consequences of a theory are unlikely to be obvious to one who reads about, or..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qx-LRgF     
    
    
    "Adopt An Artifact: Because students are human, they try to solve all problems in a similar way, using..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qx-Ln18     
    
    
    "Anonymous Feedback: Often your students know things about your course that you do not. If you don’t..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qx-LwaC     
    
    
    "Build and Maintain Confidence: Students expect the one and only right solution to a problem from the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qy3ZmBK     
    
    
    Such a great series. "Meet me here" by @todayislucid http://bit.ly/16Y1kYR  | Congrats on Oil Man    
    
    
    Love the fall. Cue: One day like this http://open.spotify.com/track/7oTYgZAZhTlZnZEH45mfpo …    
    
    
    Via @bigpiclearning: how a teacher in Mexico teaches by curating challenges for his kids http://www.wired.com/business/2013/10/free-thinkers/ …”    
    
    
    "Built-In Failure: Learning comes from experience, and much useful experience comes from failure. But a..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qy9aSIA     
    
    
    @StefanieSand Oh they will...don't you worry @sunnywash and team will make sure of that.    
    
    
    Getting started with Week 4 in the #CATprogram. This week's assignment: create a captioned video tutorial for faculty. #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    A Manifesto for Active Learning - The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/19dzkij     
    
    
    "Challenge Understanding: Students may think they understand a topic when in fact they do not. Give them..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyFdRGz     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Manager, Technical Support
http://jobvite.com/m?3bXb7gwb  #job    
    
    
     via @robinwb http://bit.ly/18UY1kN  and http://bit.ly/GPir5l  < good stuff!    
    
    
    "Consistent Metaphor (AKA Analogy): When students need a way to think of a [technical] topic outside of..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyLCn06     
    
    
    We are brainstorming survey questions to ask our faculty in #CATprogram Corner Hours http://titanpad.com/i-HwikaxST459O7WuhuiUIy7i42nfoQ6aTTCCvD9Ar … #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Critique: If students aren’t proficient enough to do modeling themselves, provide them with a model..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyQgDwl     
    
    
    A Pecha Kucha rubric via @suesstudio http://bit.ly/1h9ATTW     
    
    
    @suesstudio and I like how you adapted it https://www.dropbox.com/s/ccuj84k9c1chkja/Screenshot%202013-10-23%2015.37.14.png …    
    
    
    Online Course Lady: Writing with Aesop: 50+ Storytelling Ideas http://bit.ly/1adqAeq  via @suesstudio #CATprogram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Different Approaches: Every person obtains information differently, using different sensory modalities...." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyW1yRA     
    
    
    Super excited to see new additions to the Rubric Gallery from this fall's #CATProgram cohort: https://canvas.instructure.com/courses/784436/modules … #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Different Exercise Levels: Exercises must be located at the upper limit of the student’s current skill..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qybLb96     
    
    
    "Differentiated Feedback: One piece of feedback will be more or less appropriate for any one student,..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qygpBhv     
    
    
    "Early Bird: Students often remember best what they learn first. Teach the most important material, the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qymelJz     
    
    
    "Early Warning: If students fall behind or miss early material, it will be difficult for them to catch..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyslx06     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Sr. UX Designer
http://jobvite.com/m?3tfC7gwc  #job    
    
    
    @KathyRuby1's video tutorial on creating Rubrics https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MJbb4x7_rzo#t=283 … #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Smartphones make a difference... http://bit.ly/1aEpHM6  pic.twitter.com/Um0hn9VtgB    
    
    
    #CATProgram Corner Hours starting in t minus 3 minutes.. all about @Prulu Course Q&A Tool | Taking notes here: http://bit.ly/1hqhm1K     
    
    
    "Embrace Correction: Students rarely get it right the first time. A lot can be learned from revising..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qyyT3ZM     
    
    
    @digilang shares how to use automatic captions in @YouTube to speed up the captioning process http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NyO7ZRZg6aE&feature=youtu.be … #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    How to Create a Group Discussion in the Canvas LMS - YouTube http://bit.ly/1cerDu7  via @StefanieSand #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Two days til opening! Ender's Game (2013) - IMDb http://imdb.to/1clyAJQ     
    
    
    "Expand the Known World: A student’s learning will be deeper if they associate a new concept to their..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qz1tRW5     
    
    
    Lunchtime inspiration. Quotes on Design http://bit.ly/1cmiaAV     
    
    
    Education Outrage: Faculty putting their existing courses on line is ... kind of like filming a play to make a movie http://bit.ly/1cdVCCo     
    
    
    "Explore For Yourself: Students are often afraid of taking responsibility for their own learning. Assign..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qz7DBYl     
    
    
    @suesstudio's video tutorial on Importing Content http://bit.ly/1cervuF  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Expose the Process: Examples are an important part of any teaching effort, but examples often only show..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzB_a4v     
    
    
    Infographic: How to Implement Blended Learning 2.0 | Getting Smart http://bit.ly/1cvlmdq     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Fair Grading: You want to be fair in your grading. You want your students to be satisfied that you are..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzHfuNq     
    
    
    @devinknighton that's awesome. I'll have to check it out! I'm rebooting this wknd with http://amzn.com/B008L03XOQ     
    
    
    Rethinking Online Community in MOOCs Used for Blended Learning (EDUCAUSE Review) http://bit.ly/HyLmv3     
    
    
    "Fair Project Grading: If your grading scheme is too monolithic, some student or team may suffer because..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzNsoqR     
    
    
    Personalize Your Canvas Experience - YouTube http://bit.ly/1cerIhe  via @anna_kraftson #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Fair Team Grading: You need to make grading fair to the whole team and to each individual. Base part of..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzUEiAN     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Writing Manager
http://jobvite.com/m?3G967gwN  #job    
    
    
    It doesn't really matter where they are, real troublemakers never stop tinkering with the status quo. http://bit.ly/1cdSCGd     
    
    
    Interactive eBook about Gravity built with @ZebraZapps http://bit.ly/1cBPqZ5     
    
    
    "Feedback: Unless the work is assessed and feedback is given, you won’t be able to correct any..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzZydik     
    
    
    Feedback Loops and Audio - YouTube http://bit.ly/1cerMh9  via @robinwb #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Feedback Sandwich: You need to point out where the student’s understanding is faulty and correct any..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzfXpAV     
    
    
    @anna_kraftson Why Schools Are 'Blending' Learning | EdSurge News http://bit.ly/1cTSNXB     
    
    
    Moderating and Regrading Quizzes in Canvas - YouTube http://bit.ly/1cesqv5  via Jeff Brandt @SaltLakeCC #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Fixer Upper: Too often students work only on “toy” problems because they don’t have the experience or..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzl2aL7     
    
    
    @PatriciaCaicedo congrats!!    
    
    
    For more EdTech goodness check out the Google Authorized Education Trainer Program http://bit.ly/1gv2kJf  pic.twitter.com/vIQ9gVvcoC    
    
    
    The App Generation: How Today's Youth Navigate Identity, Intimacy, and Imagination in a Digital World Howard Gardner http://amzn.to/1beCp17     
    
    
    Ex. of the Hippocratic typology http://amzn.com/0736927018  to follow http://amzn.com/0984402136  and http://amzn.com/1412925304  pic.twitter.com/5nBZrmhjqS    
    
    
    going to check out... Canva: Beautifully Simple Page Layouts, Online http://bit.ly/1huRxgU     
    
    
    Captioning Tips for Faculty by @tinsleykim - YouTube http://bit.ly/1hqwkY5  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Gold Star: Normally the reward structure is private. In grading, you give the student praise, but this..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzqa8OZ     
    
    
    "Grade It Again, Sam: An education or training situation should provide a safe environment in which..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28qzwMkiw     
    
    
    Goodbye Nerf. Hello AirForce Blow Guns http://m.heraldextra.com/news/local/south/woodland-hills/family-works-together-to-create-fun-foam-gun-for-all/article_0880306b-afeb-506e-99ac-9477a4da5eb9.html?mobile_touch=true …    
    
    
    "Groups Work: You are only one resource for the students. Given the number and difficulty of student..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_6rqkq     
    
    
    http://blogs.edweek.org/edweek/teacherbeat/2013/11/group_recommends_score_on_mult.html … < New test for wannabe teachers    
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Data Scientist
http://jobvite.com/m?306z8gwy  #job    
    
    
    Ideas are a Dime a Dozen. People Who Implement Them are Priceless - Forbes http://onforb.es/1hugDzd     
    
    
    "Honor Questions: Some students are afraid of asking questions in front of the whole group, because the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_CrQm8     
    
    
    Lots of great tips for the #K12 DI Classroom http://bit.ly/1cBToAT     
    
    
    "Industry Partner: Industry reality is quite different from the academic one. By the time students..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_IUf2E     
    
    
    Top 10 eLearning Industry Trends For 2013 | The Upside Learning Blog http://bit.ly/1aSLW0U     
    
    
    "Invisible Teacher: Often the students only trust the teacher and (maybe) themselves, therefore, when..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_O0nOk     
    
    
    "The best technology is the one you already have, know how to use, and can afford" http://bit.ly/1aSM7t8     
    
    
    "Key Ideas Dominate Grading: If your grading scheme weights material according to its difficulty, or..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_TX2BS     
    
    
    "Kinds of Exam: You have to examine the knowledge of your students, but not all topics can be examined..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_ZH7fi     
    
    
    @anna_kraftson @mural Super cool! Spread the word. It's a great tool.    
    
    
    @emwitty great to hear! :) hi Michael Berger, hi #MWALLT friends!    
    
    
    "perception grounded in our prior experience" "play as a way of being" "design for an experience instead of outcomes" http://bit.ly/1axMad3     
    
    
    Meet Bo & Yana, delightful robots that fuse play with programming. http://www.play-i.com?src=tw&utm_source=fb&utm_medium=ads&utm_campaign=acquisitionplay-i.com/?src=tw&utm_so … via @playi    
    
    
    "Larger Than Life: When faced with a new concept, students often focus on low level details, ignoring..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_fbYoc     
    
    
    Mobile Submissions from the Student Point of View http://bit.ly/1axYQ3G  - also see @wardjhs's site: http://bit.ly/1axZ3nv  #CanvasLIVE    
    
    
    "Linking Old To New: Learning too many new things often leads to a sense of rejection and then to..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_lxsPy     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Solutions Engineer – International  (Position Based in the United Kin...
http://jobvite.com/m?3BK78gwl  #job    
    
    
    Student on the Common Core http://bit.ly/I7Wpea  "As a craft, teaching is an interaction. We teach to free minds...to inspire...to equip"    
    
    
    @wardjhs you're welcome! Here are the results from survey https://docs.google.com/a/instructure.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AsZU1aOHX2kSdHBWNHo1RWRIZzNhNktnSjJWOW5yRnc#gid=0 … Feel free to add others https://docs.google.com/a/instructure.com/forms/d/1Qk9Jy9L1NU5TajCilQUKuOJDguPr5axAk9OGHvg3dI4/viewform …    
    
    
    Excited for this week's CAT Corner Hour starting in 30 min... Taking a look at the @ViaResponse LTI integration #CanvasLMS #CATProgram    
    
    
    "Mission Impossible: Any sufficiently complex topic can be understood at many levels of abstraction. But..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_rr8Bb     
    
    
    @anna_kraftson fun project (and way to use EtherPad!)    
    
    
    The Trouble With Rubrics http://bit.ly/1hqriL9  via @umwctln #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Mock Exams: In order to have a meaningful examination you can’t tell students about every detail in an..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q_xaVFz     
    
    
    Something Very Big Is Coming: Our Most Important Technology Project Yet—Stephen Wolfram Blog http://bit.ly/1ay19nh     
    
    
    "Multi Pronged Attack: Sometimes eliminating stuff for making room for new topics is the best choice,..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-1Ldbc     
    
    
    13 things mentally strong people don't do http://www.lifehack.org/articles/communication/13-things-mentally-strong-people-dont.html …    
    
    
    History from modern DNA analysis http://blogs.smithsonianmag.com/science/2013/11/a-history-of-slavery-and-genocide-is-hidden-in-modern-dna/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Alternative Learning Place http://bit.ly/1axQ9Gu  - DESIGN, BUILD, TEST, REVISE (curriculum for 5 & 6 yr olds)    
    
    
    LOL @StefanieSand - YouTube http://bit.ly/18dxRgl     
    
    
    "Nobody is Perfect: Students expect the one and only right solution to a problem from the instructor...." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-6x3N8     
    
    
    2012 TED Talk http://bit.ly/1gUU6dB  "true education is about giving people a voice and enabling them to express their voice."    
    
    
    11 Brilliant Ways To Frame Critical Content: A Complexities Chart http://bit.ly/18HCYQj     
    
    
    Adaptive learning: The best approaches we've seen so far | Education Dive http://bit.ly/1hQU5ss     
    
    
    "One Concept - Several Implementations: An abstract concept is hard to understand without a concrete..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-CkoEi     
    
    
    "Say What? 5 Ways to Get Students to Listen" http://bit.ly/18HHjCY     
    
    
    @anna_kraftson great intro to External Apps for K12 Teachers!    
    
    
    Bitcoin: When Money is Not an Investment http://linkd.in/1i4OMWs     
    
    
    Thx to @robinwb for adding to the Assignment Gallery http://bit.ly/18chReA  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "One Grade For All: You want all team members to benefit equally from the teamwork experience, in terms..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-J9AKI     
    
    
    Napoleon CATS Week 6 Assignment (awesome) http://bit.ly/HXTg0u  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Own Words: Students may be able to repeat definitions and other material verbatim but they may not have..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-PS7_j     
    
    
    Thx to @umwctln for summarizing activities from the Fall 2013 cohort http://bit.ly/18ocqXS  #CanvasLMS #CATProgram    
    
    
    If we value student learning styles, why not allow teachers play to their own strengths as well? http://bit.ly/1aTUHY2  via @suesstudio    
    
    
    @StefanieSand My pleasure! I know I learned every bit as much as the #CATProgram participants. Thanks for giving so much to this cohort.    
    
    
    Web-based drawing tools via @k12techtrainer http://bit.ly/1c5xXp8  http://bit.ly/1aTVAzV  http://bit.ly/1c5xYJQ  http://bit.ly/1c5y1Fj     
    
    
    Instructure is looking for: Solutions Engineer – International  (Position Based in Australia)
http://jobvite.com/m?3QHE9gw5  #job    
    
    
    Thx to @digilang for curating and tagging links from the CAT Curriculum Course http://bit.ly/18od5Zj  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Designing Effective Online Assignments - Do Your Job Better - The Chronicle of Higher Education http://bit.ly/18v4moo     
    
    
    "Peer Feedback: Students are knowledgable and are able to give helpful feedback, but often they are not..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-VPrXs     
    
    
    I can totally do this. The Epic Split feat. Van Damme (Live Test 6) - YouTube http://bit.ly/18ZCTYs     
    
    
    Should You Let Students Lead Discussion Boards? - Faculty Focus | Faculty Focus http://bit.ly/18ZCZiP     
    
    
    thank you @robinwb for both of these: http://bit.ly/18ZCZPR  http://bit.ly/18xpuu6  #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    "Peer Grading: You want to teach your students how to evaluate quality and how to negotiate for it. You..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-bP7Ga     
    
    
    Congrats to all the cool CATs who completed Level 2 this fall! Certificates here: https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=0B8ZU1aOHX2kSbFB5TnByb0hVTkU&usp=sharing … #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    Thx to @KathyRuby1 for adding examples to External App Gallery https://canvas.instructure.com/courses/812387/wiki/cat2-external-app-5?module_item_id=5256712 … #CATProgram #CanvasLMS    
    
    
    And a huge thank you to @heliceagria for being an awesome guide and TA #CATProgram #CanvasLMS She also helped build http://bit.ly/18of9k0     
    
    
    This should be fun dinner conversation... Thanksgiving Day 5:38pm SpaceX | Launch Central http://bit.ly/1icZdat     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Unexamined Life: Lecture Capture and Data Capture http://bit.ly/1aTV3xZ     
    
    
    "Physical Analogy: While it is rather easy for learners to comprehend concepts that are concrete because..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-hSdhZ     
    
    
    Learning from my sis about Horsenalities! Hippocratic/Brain Based ideas http://bit.ly/IuOUy4  http://bit.ly/IuPJXJ  pic.twitter.com/tOxBxES9Fr    
    
    
    @JimRoepcke old tweet.. was just looking for HyperCard equiv on iPad. What did you think of NovoCard?    
    
    
    "Prefer Writing: Students need to practice writing, both because it is a useful skill and because it..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-nA-Yi     
    
    
    Checking out Zahmoo for collecting stories in any organization or family. http://bit.ly/1fNiVrF     
    
    
    "Real World Experience: Some concepts are too abstract for students to conceive their value. Students..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-tLGRL     
    
    
    "Rearrangement: You consider teaching these new ideas at the end of the course, because in order to..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q-zn180     
    
    
    "Reflection: Students often anticipate that an instructor will solve each and every problem for them...." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q104AXfX     
    
    
    "Role Play: Most teaching styles respect the auditories, a few the visuals, and even fewer the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10A5fnY     
    
    
    "Round and Deep: Experienced students will relate a new concept to their own real-world experiences,..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10FySWV     
    
    
    @katejbrod glad you like these and kudos to @Befitt for organizing the #CanvasLIVE series. She does an awesome job!    
    
    
    "Round Robin: However, you want to get everyone’s participation and input and you especially want to..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10Lm_Hz     
    
    
    Join us 1PM Mountain for #CanvasLIVE session re: SpeedGrader for iPad: https://learncanvas.webex.com/mw0307l/mywebex/default.do?siteurl=learncanvas … #CanvasK12 Handout: https://docs.google.com/a/instructure.com/document/d/1ccvQXi53IIgawGxgPGX8SpJao9_A7aFxNWSBZC28tGo/edit …    
    
    
    @StefanieSand Congrats!    
    
    
    "See Before Hear: Learners often find it difficult to convert what they’ve heard in the classroom into..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10RT3UC     
    
    
    Course Home Pages with Purpose http://bit.ly/18q5RRe  - Great reminders!    
    
    
    #hourofcode starts this Monday... http://bit.ly/196jDML     
    
    
    Amazing Kids of Character Series: Portraits of Courage - YouTube http://bit.ly/1eXFhDf  -- Living in the moment. So cool.    
    
    
    "Self Test: If your students don’t understand what you have presented, they have a poor basis for..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10XPHbL     
    
    
    Oooh, new find. Nice sound for snowy day. #spotifydelivers ♫ Reach – Broken Fences http://spoti.fi/1cswCZM  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    Checking out Ghost Blogging Platform http://bit.ly/1gfpFPf  "just a blogging platform"  more simpler than WordPress, open source    
    
    
    "Shot Gun Seminar: A typical technique to broaden a group of learners’ understanding of a field or..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10dnY9M     
    
    
    Córdoba looks in the mirror of chaos http://bit.ly/1gifU2M  - Civilians face lootings during recent police force strike #fabricofsociety    
    
    
    "Education is the most powerful weapon which you can use to change the world" http://www.forbes.com/sites/mfonobong … http://spoti.fi/18hxam4     
    
    
    Remembering Nelson Mandela: "I am an ordinary man." http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LnGeMBNS9ZA …    
    
    
    Early notification systems "have to be tuned to ... maximize their positive impact on diverse student populations." http://bit.ly/ILYAEu     
    
    
    "Solution Before Abstraction: An abstract concept can become the basis for a large number of..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10kFlXA     
    
    
    Trying out simple storytelling with @Narrable http://bit.ly/1gk46Nm     
    
    
    @narrable cool thanks! :)    
    
    
    922 - CanvasLIVE 2013 - Item Analysis in Quizzes http://bit.ly/19dkzyJ  - thanks to @befitt @jstein @HilaryScharton    
    
    
    VideoNot.es: The easiest way to take notes synchronized with videos! http://bit.ly/18xlEh0     
    
    
    Rapt Media - http://bit.ly/18xoNgZ  | "Choose your own adventure" interactive videos.. lots of uses    
    
    
    "Spiral: Topics in a course are often interrelated. Too often, many different topics are required for..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q10qQw5E     
    
    
    Photograph Puzzle Maker http://bit.ly/18xparL  » need to make quick holiday gift for the kids? try this - paste on wood or cardboard    
    
    
    What's Your Learning Style? http://bit.ly/1f2wv6X  (old, but embeds nicely on any page)    
    
    
    923 - CanvasLIVE 2013 - Mobile Series: Grading On-the-Go with Wi-Fi On-the-Side http://bit.ly/18xEnsQ  - Focus on SpeedGrader    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Six Attributes of Courage | Psychology Today http://bit.ly/1gmxlz2     
    
    
    ▶ How To Paint Pine Needles - Mural Joe - YouTube http://bit.ly/1h1aVBd  essential knowledge    
    
    
    Official Blog: New Google Sheets: faster, more powerful, and works offline http://bit.ly/1h1bXNn     
    
    
    MUST EAT ZEEERO 7 ♫ All Of Us – Zero 7 http://spoti.fi/YH9aRS  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    @allibrown27 LOL. :) http://xkcd.com/1285/     
    
    
    "Student Online Portfolios: Students need feedback from others as well as yourself. They can get..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q110ByIr     
    
    
    How the Power of Interest Drives Learning | MindShift http://bit.ly/Jaz0td     
    
    
    "Students Decide: Sometimes it is impossible to make decisions concerning course material and approach..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q115odOT     
    
    
    Beautiful game art goes public ... http://boingboing.net/2013/12/11/glitch.html …    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland and there we are, in living color! :) thanks for sharing and happy holidays    
    
    
    "Study Groups: Your best students may often by bored, because they have finished a task quickly while..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11BXxMe     
    
    
    @mostardiving listens like a good bedtime story. #acoustic #quirky #London more if you like: http://themostardiving… http://spoti.fi/18vnl0M     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Team Teaching: Some topics are very broad and complex. These topics provide a real challenge if you..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11OH48E     
    
    
    "Test Tube: When students encounter holes in their knowledge, we would like for them to seek out an..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11UFsSW     
    
    
    "Three Bears: Many problems challenge the learner to find a solution positioned along some continuum...." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11aBv5R     
    
    
    Defining the problem you are solving is as interesting and difficult as solving it. | An interview with Tom Geismar http://bit.ly/1fkWMNX     
    
    
    Tile http://bit.ly/1c3o3EW  the world's largest lost and found    
    
    
    "Tool Box: Knowledge is not the only result of the learning effort. Group work and real world..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11g2aIS     
    
    
    Coughs, colds, and flu. http://bit.ly/IZwdDz  What's the best treatment? Pray tell.    
    
    
    "Try It Yourself: Students usually believe they have understood the topic, but this is often only true..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11lu5A_     
    
    
    50+ Inexpensive (and useful) DIY Gift Ideas http://bit.ly/1fLLvXH  (including coffee filter wreath!)    
    
    
    "War Game: There is no substitute for learning-by-doing. But the traditional classroom or..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11rmnat     
    
    
    Miniatur Wunderland  largest model railway / railroad of the world - YouTube http://bit.ly/1cd0ycC     
    
    
    "Wider Perspective: Even though such realities as economic conditions, human behavior, and..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q11xuswF     
    
    
    "Digestible Packets: People can only concentrate for a limited period of time. If a topic takes longer..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q122V-Gg     
    
    
    status: safely nested. Happy Holidays! ♫ holiday cheer by Allison Weiss http://spoti.fi/1kASkhQ  #NowPlaying    
    
    
    New Feature Screencast http://bit.ly/JlNYMH  by @JordanDayton includes ability to set dates for showing correct answers in quizzes    
    
    
    Read Professor Josh's Jumble ▸ http://paper.li/professorjosh/1326485652 …    
    
    
    "Fill In The Blanks: Beginning students need to work on larger projects than has been typical in the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q1296WrK     
    
    
    "Human Professor: At some point in your teaching, students will make serious transgressions of the code..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12EpHhr     
    
    
    The Christmas Story - YouTube http://bit.ly/19M6Gbc  (so cute!)    
    
    
    "Lay Of The Land: Learning a topic incrementally may not be the best way to learn for all students...." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12KciN2     
    
    
    "Mistake: Debugging is an essential skill, whether done with a sophisticated debugger, or just by..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12Qwwvw     
    
    
    @zebrazapps how to build a branching role play from start to finish http://vimeo.com/82127410  Practice w/ Santa: http://zebr.as/18ZSCtR     
    
    
    "New Pedagogy for New Paradigms: The thing you need to teach has characteristics different from what..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12XDYGI     
    
    
    2014: Also the Year of the Green Smoothie. Got my Vitamix, greens, mason jars. #rawsome Favorite recipes anyone?    
    
    
    "Reduce Risk: While you must evaluate your students, the exam process often gets in the way of..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12datJB     
    
    
    "Repeat Yourself: Things heard only once are more likely to be forgotten. Therefore, repeat important..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12kUT3l     
    
    
    Just because. Yellow. http://bit.ly/19XxcOJ   http://bit.ly/Ki77Qz   http://bit.ly/19XxcOK     
    
    
    We need to talk about TED | Benjamin Bratton | Comment is free http://bit.ly/1hSpaZm     
    
    
    "Set The Stage: At the beginning of the course and when introducing new topics, you need to get the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12rJ6qs     
    
    
    "Shout It From The Rooftops: Many of your students consider themselves shy. You will recognize them in..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q12x0XSH     
    
    
    "Student Driven Lecture: If many students have the same questions you may need to spend more time on a..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q13286fR     
    
    
    Design to the nines and the rule of thirds | Webdesigner Depot http://bit.ly/1cL0kcN     
    
    
    Attempt to mix storytelling, decision making. Game mechanics reveal their bones. Reminds me a little of Myst.  http://www.wired.com/gamelife/2013/12/the-novelist/ …    
    
    
    When you're bored w/ Lorem Ipsum... try Anguish Languish! http://bit.ly/1g3LCNU     
    
    
    "truly innovative ideas often look like bad ideas at the time." http://bit.ly/1g3zZq8     
    
    
    Understand These 10 Principles of Good Design http://bit.ly/1cLce6B     
    
    
    Publons: academic peer review + social networking http://bit.ly/1kcZhIr     
    
    
    Not All Private Universities Jumping Into Online Courses http://bit.ly/1i1X3qS     
    
    
    "Student Selected Activities: Rigid grading schemes increase risk and usually do not increase student..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q139Mfk9     
    
    
    Can Home Visits By Teachers Improve Education? http://bit.ly/19SyxGe     
    
    
    All great people to learn from: http://www.trainingpressreleases.com/news/bob-little-press-pr/2014/the-fifth-annual-top-ten-e-learning-movers-and-shakers …    
    
    
    Seasons: Flash Animation - YouTube http://bit.ly/1ct2Foe     
    
    
    A Vibrating Watch That Messes With Your Perception of Time | Wired Design http://wrd.cm/19SzdLP     
    
    
    "Take A Risk: Your job is to educate students. You don’t have the option of not doing anything. Take a..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q13GO8SB     
    
    
    Glitchy Aerial Photos Turn Real Buildings Into Artist Renderings | Raw File http://wrd.cm/1i1Xt0k     
    
    
    ▶ Robin Williams narrates Pecos Bill Part I: http://bit.ly/1li0eNq  Part II: http://bit.ly/1li0eNr  | quotables galore :-)    
    
    
    "Teacher’s Language: Once of the most important aspects of good teaching is the medium with which the..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q13NOWkQ     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Toy Box: Students often have no real concept of the breadth of application of computer science or of..." http://tmblr.co/Zex28q13UTpNP     
    
    
    Listening to @clsaarinen's wonderful preso on meaningful discussions. Amazing how she creates an environment of safety online. #instcon12    
    
    
    @busynessgirl Maybe outcomes as "tags" to assignments and content, which would exist outside the rubric? Someday…..    
    
    
    Shout out from Lisa Frazier to the awesome Instructure implementation managers #instcon12    
    
    
    Heading home now after a fabulous #instcon12 Thanks to everyone, especially @sunnywash and her team for hosting an amazing conference.    
    
    
    Tears of Joy: Canvas Analytics is ON http://j.mp/NGDyXW  Great screenshots from @busynessgirl    
    
    
    Connected Learning Infographic | Connected Learning http://awe.sm/5nD14     
    
    
    @scottwdennis thanks for notes. Those were some of the sessions I wanted to attend and couldn't. Look
forward to video uploads! #instcon12    
    
    
    Mozilla Open Badges ships Beta release | The Mozilla Blog http://awe.sm/5nD1P     
    
    
    Awesome faculty group here at Pasadena City College. Fastest transition to Canvas EVER (Summer classes starting in only 7 days!)    
    
    
    What are badges? / Courses, Study Groups, and Challenges / Knowledge Base - P2PU Support http://awe.sm/5nD1n     
    
    
    @chris3edwards sleep tight then! I'm off to bed as well. Flight from Pasadena to HOME tomorrow. Yay home.    
    
    
    Rubric for Language Skills « http://awe.sm/5nD2A     
    
    
    Scale-Free Schools / An Introduction on Vimeo http://awe.sm/5nD84     
    
    
    Scale-Free Schools / A Day In The Life on Vimeo http://awe.sm/5nD9J     
    
    
    thanks @busyinessgirl for some great tips! --> Online Office Hours in Canvas http://j.mp/Kze3lN  @instructure @learncanvas    
    
    
    Badges, Portfolios, and Blending Formal and Informal Learning | FunnyMonkey http://awe.sm/5nD9o     
    
    
    @clsaarinen Absolutely. Still loving your preso from #instcon12 - could we feature a discussion in the Designer Guide? http://guides.instructure.com/s/2204/m/5834/l/55357-posting-and-responding-to-discussion-topics …    
    
    
    @clsaarinen great! just sent you the info    
    
    
    Tin Can API Viewer http://awe.sm/5nDAV     
    
    
    Badges – Less Yack, More Hack « Lonely Lion http://awe.sm/5nDBv     
    
    
    Check it. @devlindaley announcing Analytics in Canvas http://vimeo.com/44878523     
    
    
    Working through the hard stuff of #badges: Developing a Conceptual Framework while Unearthing Underlying Tensions http://awe.sm/5nDCV     
    
    
    What is good design? http://awe.sm/i0VM5  (nice list)    
    
    
    Yes. Yes. Let’s make badges not stink : Sharing Nicely http://awe.sm/5nDCj     
    
    
    @scottwdennis SO cute! We've got lots of them around here that's fo' sure..    
    
    
    Can Badging Be the Zipcar of Testing and Assessment? | DMLcentral http://awe.sm/5nDDE     
    
    
    Man, I wish you guys all the luck in the world! Peer 2 Peer University (P2PU) | HASTAC http://awe.sm/5nDFX     
    
    
    Nothing like the looping sound of a record player when you least expect it. Ah, nostalgia. Thank you Jon Barrios http://awe.sm/5nDFr     
    
    
    @busynessgirl Safe travels!    
    
    
    Very cool. Badges Go To Graduate School | iterating toward openness http://awe.sm/5nD4F     
    
    
    @busynessgirl speaking of math and Angry Birds, why… there's a course for that. =) http://www.udemy.com/math-is-everywhere-applications-of-finite-math/ …    
    
    
    @iampaulanthony hadn't checked in for a while.. love the "moooodmap" http://friendlymusic.com/#mood  - keep rockin'!    
    
    
    U.S. Student-Loan Debt Swells http://www.businessweek.com/video#video=xtZG1sNDqC4FIl8aXdFDRyBIdGSXeluR …    
    
    
    The Six Enemies of Greatness (and Happiness) - Forbes http://awe.sm/5oIb0     
    
    
    Bake House Piano Drop 2012 - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLaK     
    
    
    Wheat and chessboard - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLeB     
    
    
    @deekgeek @jordandayton Sweet!    
    
    
    @deekgeek @jordandayton "InstructureMan" - isn't he adorable? =)    
    
    
    Circular Automower (video) - 101qs http://awe.sm/5tLhs     
    
    
    For all you northeasterners…. Canvas User Group - a NERCOMP event http://linkd.in/NmvxpB  organized by @clsaarinen    
    
    
    Washington State Higher Ed Shifting to Instructure Canvas -- Campus Technology http://awe.sm/5tVue     
    
    
    Seth Godin Blog: Monetizing digital attention http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2012/07/monetizing-digital-attention.html … via @ThisIsSethsBlog    
    
    
    The Google+ Hangout that changed the way I will view communication forever http://tnw.to/k1FK  via @TNWinsider    
    
    
    Examples « Designing Better Learning Experiences http://awe.sm/5ugpw     
    
    
    Online Teaching Tips - YouTube http://awe.sm/5uhcP     
    
    
    great idea for using comments in the SpeedGrader @busynessgirl Video Code Easter Eggs http://j.mp/SFlYDP  @learncanvas    
    
    
    e-Learning Project Management - YouTube http://awe.sm/5uhrR     
    
    
    @deekgeek hi! Still working on that! I'll let you know when it goes live (probably not 'til September)    
    
    
    Adding Captions to Tegrity Recordings http://awe.sm/5vckN  - nice vid @scottwdennis (p.s. does anybody in WA want to caption all our vids?)    
    
    
    @scottwdennis Thank you! That's a great start.    
    
    
    The Center for Generational Studies - Cost-Saving Webinars to Resolve Your Generational Challenges http://awe.sm/5xHQh     
    
    
    5/23/00 Short Summary of Learning Style Inventories http://awe.sm/5xHRJ     
    
    
    oldie but goodie: Are College Students Techno Idiots? | Inside Higher Ed http://awe.sm/5xHja     
    
    
    The Millennial Muddle: How Stereotyping Students Became an Industry - Students - The Chronicle of Higher Education http://awe.sm/5xImS     
    
    
    Thank you @allibrown27 and @mallgood01 for updated docs on Mobile Apps! !!! http://awe.sm/d1uJu  @learncanvas    
    
    
    Taking forward change in technology-enhanced education http://awe.sm/5xItr     
    
    
    Twitter Symbols might come in handy at some point! http://awe.sm/b1yv0     
    
    
    Charles Dziuban on The Net Generation, Learning Styles and Technology-Enhanced Education Start at 12:00 http://awe.sm/5xHSY     
    
    
    Michelle Pacansky-Brock and Chuck Dziuban - "Ask the Experts" panel - Sloan-C ALN conference 2008 - YouTube http://awe.sm/5xJ5l     
    
    
    Narrating • Curating • Sharing: "No digital facelifts" http://ustre.am/:8iLi  - thanks for lead @jstein    
    
    
    Oh my goodness, a tripod site! Asynchronous Learning Network ความหมาย http://awe.sm/5xJ9c     
    
    
    NCAT: Learning MarketSpace, October 2001 http://awe.sm/5xJEt     
    
    
    Bayston - Key to Long-Dziuban http://awe.sm/5xJGb     
    
    
    @brocansky Thanks for your well-produced VISUAL slides. =) http://awe.sm/5xJLI     
    
    
    Technology - Alan Jacobs - The Great Unbundling of the University - The Atlantic http://awe.sm/5xJUF     
    
    
    Macrowikinomics http://awe.sm/5xJVD     
    
    
    Many Eyes : Probability to use web based educational service http://awe.sm/5xJcc     
    
    
    Many Eyes : Education spending and unemployment http://awe.sm/5xJeR     
    
    
    Check out recently updated Admin Guide http://guides.instructure.com/m/4214  via @allibrown27 (Post suggestions below the lesson) @learncanvas @instructure    
    
    
    Many Eyes : Education vs Hours Per Week http://awe.sm/5xJfo     
    
    
    @JordanDayton You ran up there??? Crazy cat    
    
    
    Getting ready for on-site training with Vancouver SD tomorrow. S'gonna be good! #instructure #learncanvas    
    
    
    Many Eyes : Gender wage gap by educational attainment http://awe.sm/5xJgV     
    
    
    Looking forward to: Best Practices for Teaching with Emerging Technologies Michelle Pacansky-Brock: Books http://awe.sm/5xKcs     
    
    
    @injenuity @jjjohnson01 @mattmcghie @jordandayton Hail Captain JJ, Rogue of Rogues! ps I love Washington. Was just in Vancouver today..    
    
    
    Sloan-C’s Definition of ‘Online Course’ May Be Out of Sync with Reality « Educational Technology and Change Journal http://awe.sm/5xN3E     
    
    
    Rogue Med Student Tackles the Web's Ultimate Irony http://www.wired.com/wiredenterprise/2012/08/researchgate/ …    
    
    
    Have you read Groundswell? Charlene Li, Josh Bernoff: Books http://awe.sm/5xPLm     
    
    
    What your designs say about you (moral component of design)| Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xm3L     
    
    
    http://vimeo.com/47732039  Bill Gates: Employers decide whether a new credentialing system will take hold or not.    
    
    
    Lisa Harouni: A primer on 3D printing | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xmZu     
    
    
    Dan Meyer: Math class needs a makeover | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnPG  (Math reasoning example at 5:00)    
    
    
    PPT causing the illusion of understanding. Dance vs. powerpoint, a modest proposal | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnjK     
    
    
    @holden @instructure Try one of the suggestions under the "How do I include extra credit..." section here: http://guides.instructure.com/s/2204/m/4152/l/46543-what-is-the-difference-between-a-canvas-assignment-and-a-canvas-activity …    
    
    
    @holden @chris3edwards @instructure @iYantho oh good, you found it already!    
    
    
    @chris3edwards thanks! :)    
    
    
    Joe Sabia: The technology of storytelling | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnoG     
    
    
    Beauty is in the limbic system of the beholder - Richard Seymour | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/5xnw4     
    
    
    Steve Jobs building NeXT 20 min (Learning Simulations & Apple II's in the Classroom) http://awe.sm/5ySTn     
    
    
    Thanks @clonghb for your intro to the #CATprogram. Excited to have you in the course!    
    
    
    What is ZebraZapps? on Vimeo http://awe.sm/605iD     
    
    
    PRO ZebraZapps - LMS preview on Vimeo http://awe.sm/605rn     
    
    
    ImTranslator - Plug-in for FireFox. Version 4.16 http://awe.sm/hHfM     
    
    
    The CAT Preparation Course is now live. Take a look around. Tell your friends. https://training.instructure.com/courses/360911  #CATProgram    
    
    
    @snappity you can definitely count that toward CAT Hours @chris3edwards more info on the #CATprogram here http://bit.ly/CATprogram     
    
    
    Great post! Hacking the Screwdriver: Instructure’s Canvas and the Future of the LMS http://awe.sm/f08Rw     
    
    
    I want to go to near space! Take me! Lucky Edgar. - HD balloon flight to 95,000ft - YouTube http://awe.sm/a0YR2     
    
    
    Free, open-enrollment PBL (Project Based Learning) course in Canvas @biepbl #instructure http://awe.sm/f0ia9     
    
    
    The Canvas Video Contest has begun! Submissions due by Sept 30th. http://www.instructure.com/video-contest  #Instructure    
    
    
    The New Credentialing Stack http://awe.sm/j4ba9     
    
    
    a @whitmer lead... Nice K12 resource! | MIT + K12 http://awe.sm/c1BUr     
    
    
    Great book. The Extraordinary Leader : Turning Good Managers into Great Leaders http://awe.sm/a2bdK     
    
    
    Latest @instructure blog post: http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/215810/Listening-to-Our-Customers … - newly organized feature request forum will make you smile thx 2 @busynessgirl    
    
    
    @injenuity NicE!    
    
    
    Lovely advice. http://www.marcandangel.com/2012/01/29/20-things-to-start-doing-in-your-relationships/ …    
    
    
    @spolsky on User Interface and FEELINGS...nothing more than FEELINGS... http://www.joelonsoftware.com/uibook/chapters/fog0000000057.html …    
    
    
    Excellent video channel with lots of great @instructure Canvas tutorials by Brown University http://awe.sm/b3v5b     
    
    
    Just noticed this LTI integration - YouTube For Schools http://awe.sm/m3RTq  - sweet!    
    
    
    New lesson on Canvas Guides thx to @allibrown27 How do I give my students extra credit?: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78195-how-do-i-give-my-students-extra-credit …    
    
    
    We Have a Plan: Canvas Status Communication Plan via @memacfar http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/219651/We-Have-a-Plan-Canvas-Status-Communication-Plan …    
    
    
    Mozilla and P2PU badge pilot program - http://awe.sm/i4axm  built off of OSQA, cool!    
    
    
    Canvas Guides | How do I link course content to a Quiz question?: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78275-how-do-i-link-course-content-to-a-quiz-question … @learncanvas    
    
    
    w00t! @brackenm @allibrown27 for LTI documentation & moodle course import http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/220762/LTI-Common-Cartridge-and-Moodle …    
    
    
    @devlindaley tells the Instructure story, shares startup approach http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XD6eOd6K8Qw … just another fun and busy day @instructure    
    
    
    Props to @clsaarinen for organizing first #CanvasSIG Enjoy @testorip @chris3edwards @whitmer !    
    
    
    The Most Important Challenge For Colleges Isn't Price-It's Attention - The Atlantic http://www.theatlantic.com/business/archive/2012/06/the-most-important-challenge-for-colleges-isnt-price-its-attention/258471 …    
    
    
    Checking out Purdue University's digital badge app tonight http://itunes.apple.com/us/app/passport-profile/id552400654?mt=8 … #openbadges    
    
    
    Chris McAvoy's overview of Mozilla's Open Badges project - YouTube http://awe.sm/f4atB     
    
    
    Astra Taylor on the Unschooled Life - YouTube http://awe.sm/k45cq     
    
    
    MebiPenny 2012 aka nerds nerding out about nerdy nerd things (love it) http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/220126/MebiPenny-2012-Results-and-Wrapup …    
    
    
    @parkerwightman Good for you!! #beatsthechest #tribalpride    
    
    
    @prawsthorne Thank you for the "fall cleaning" - very helpful for newcomers. #openbadges    
    
    
    @clonghb =) something about donkeys and goats…there are rules but they obviously get broken.. to each their own!    
    
    
    Just in case you hadn't heard: http://awe.sm/g5B7V  #openbadges    
    
    
    @holden just in case you didn't see it, we now have a separate guide on extra credit: http://guides.instructure.com/m/4152/l/78195-how-do-i-give-my-students-extra-credit …    
    
    
    http://Amazon.com : Rework (9780307463746): Jason Fried, David Heinemeier Hansson: Books http://awe.sm/e57WK     
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland You and your team were awesome this morning! I see only training awesomeness coming from Rider. =)    
    
    
    Read all about it! The CAT's out of the bag http://voice.instructure.com/blog/bid/222533/The-CAT-s-out-of-the-bag … #CATprogram    
    
    
    @tinsleykim that's correct - Level 1 of the #CATprogram is free - more benefits if you advance to Level 2, which does have a fee.    
    
    
    @ShaunJHolland you bet!    
    
    
    the importance of designing and implementing a communication architecture via @bhorowitz http://awe.sm/d5CAM     
    
    
    Vision versus Hallucination – Founders and Pivots « Steve Blank http://awe.sm/i5MGs     
    
    
    Don't delay! You still have 20 minutes to register for LearnCanvas LIVE! https://learncanvas.webex.com/mw0307l/mywebex/default.do?siteurl=learncanvas … @instructure @learncanvas    
    
    
    @clsaarinen u rocked the first LearnCanvas LIVE! webinar - way to go!!    
    
    
    @coursera launches The Lean LaunchPad Online « Steve Blank http://awe.sm/d5CDg     
    
    
    Algorithm predicts tweet-worthy articles --> http://phys.org/news/2012-08-news-article-tweetworthy-algorithm.html …    
    
    
    Badges in the real world | o p e n m a t t http://awe.sm/f5LOF  #openbadges    
    
    
    Online Sign Up Sheet -- Jooners http://awe.sm/a5Czj  (great idea for quick sign-up and collaboration, hope it takes off)    
    
    
    Having a blast working with @PHMschools this week. Especially after Notre Dame beat Michigan last wknd. :) Irish spirits are high.    
    
    
    Nice blog of tech tools powered by Randy Hogue and friends @PHMschools http://dmstechplace.blogspot.com/     
    
    
    4 good posts on Standards-Based Grading: 1) http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=391 … 2) http://mctownsley.blogspot.com/2012/09/standards-based-grading-explainers.html …  3) http://fnoschese.wordpress.com/2012/08/23/keep-it-simple-standards-based-grading/ … 4) http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=2859 …    
    
    
    More ideas for implementing SBG Grading: 1) http://alwaysformative.blogspot.com/p/standards-based-grading-implementation.html … 2) http://standardsbasedgrading.wordpress.com/2012/09/23/student-tracking-sheet-for-sbg-learning-targets/ … 3) http://blog.mrmeyer.com/?p=5597     
    
    
    Standards-Based Grading: FAQ http://shawncornally.com/wordpress/?p=673 …    
    
    
    Foundation: HTML Templates http://awe.sm/i5N9l     
    
    
    Another Java vulnerability puts *1 billion* users at risk http://blogs.computerworld.com/malware-and-vulnerabilities/21056/another-critical-java-vulnerability-puts-1-billion-users-risk …    
    
    
    Take time to contemplate says Susan Cain: The power of introverts | Video on http://TED.com  http://awe.sm/c5PAQ     
    
    
    @busynessgirl You've probably already seen this: beautiful online graphing calculator https://www.desmos.com/calculator     
    
    
    @sjciske thanks!  I take it you are a fellow intro. =)    
    
    
    http://degreed.com/  is now in BETA - talks to #openbadges - congrats @davidblake @ericgsharp @mgadams3 @opencontent    
    
    
    Open UI Designer position http://awe.sm/m5Zjy  #instructure @pzich wish you were out of school - spread the word pls    
    
    
    Via @nprnews and @rodandon: In Japan, Mobile Startups Take Gaming To Next Level http://n.pr/NEU2gx     
    
    
    Add a touch of humor to your K12 course with daily cartoon widget in Canvas - embed code here: http://www.andertoons.com/free-cartoons/  thx @rodandon    
    
    
    @rodanadon I mis-tweeted your handle earlier. Can't wait till you push your CS course into Canvas. It's gonna be awesome! #makeitpublic    
    
    
    Ask a Neuroscientist: Thinking and physical activity | Minnesota Public Radio News http://awe.sm/k5Glv     
    
    
    v00t! @jstein has just launched our new learning blog: Share Like a Pollinator, Blog Like a Bee (speak like a German) http://awe.sm/g689F     
    
    
    me gusta… here's to our many lives of reinvention! http://www.smbc-comics.com/index.php?db=comics&id=2722 …    
    
    
    This is SUCH good news for the 21st century. Cute Images Make Us 44% Sharper [STUDY] http://awe.sm/g68Lt     
    
    
    Leaving ADDIE for SAM #leavingaddieforsam http://www.astd.org/Publications/Books/Leaving-ADDIE-for-SAM … by Michael Allen with @rhillsites    
    
    
    love this article: The Trouble With Online Education - http://NYTimes.com  http://awe.sm/e5bPU     
    
    
    Open Architecture: Our Course Could be Your Life http://learning.instructure.com/2012/10/open-architecture-our-course-could-be-your-life/ … via @jimgroom    
    
    
    Teachers, Designers: BUY THIS. Joseph Bergin et al have done us a great service by collecting, refining #pedpatterns http://awe.sm/b5cUr     
    
    
    