Nice preview of what's to come for nonprofits at LinkedIn by Bryan Breckenridge http://sliwww.slideshare.net/SM4nonprofits/bryan-breckenridge …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    At #cofsf community foundations conferences.  What's the most innovative success by a community foundation?    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Craig Newmark's great idea - your board members should retweet/share your messages in social media http://bit.ly/nMcOt9  via @AddThis    
    
    
    @CPFSOfficial Thanks so much for getting the word out!  Help ppl find great nonprofits helping soldiers, vets and their families!    
    
    
    Awesome product managers are like gold.  Thanks Drew @road3llc for signing on to be an advisor to our nonprofit!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm speaking at the Stanford Graduate School of Business on Innovations in Philanthropy. http://alumni.gsb.stanford.edu/events/chapters/BayArea/speaker11162011.html …    
    
    
    awesome vivanista fundraising summit!  speakers from many creative sectors about make donating fun! @vivanista @laynegray @briteSF    
    
    
    great to see you on Twitter!   @emmettcarson    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Today is the last day of the Green Choice Awards http://www.greatnonprofits.org/green. Tell us which are the best environmental nonprofits!    
    
    
    @pndblog hey Mitch, today's the last day of  Green Choice Awards. Vote for your favorite environmental groups.  http://bit.ly/greenchoice    
    
    
    @ssstrom hey stephanie, today's the last day of Green Choice Awards. I'll send you the list of best environmental nonprofits after the votes    
    
    
        
    
    
    @chrisabraham Today's the last day of Green Choice Awards. Vote for your favorite environmental groups http://bit.ly/greenchoice (pls RT!)    
    
    
    @socialentrprnr Nathaniel, today's the last day of Green Choice Awards. Vote for ur favorite environmental groups http://bit.ly/greenchoice    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Hewlett_Found Foundation names new president, Stanford law school dean Larry Kramer.   http://bit.ly/GXM2Tl   Congrats!    
    
    
    In Vancouver enjoying the skiing and Shanghaiese food. At AFP conference speaking tomorrow about Telling Your Story.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Congrats to Hacienda de los Milagros for also being voted the Top Local Animal Nonprofit on HuffPost! http://bit.ly/IxbYsf     
    
    
    Top Local 'Green' Nonprofit Of The Month (VOTE!) http://huff.to/I4SawY  via @HuffingtonPost    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great article on how families are overcoming poverty - Investing in Homegrown Solutions http://huff.to/LMU6ru  via @HuffPostImpact    
    
    
    I created group Listening to Your Stakeholders on Linkedin.: http://lnkd.in/M8eyPT     
    
    
    Top 5 List: We Pick 5 Service Projects for Lindsay Lohan via @GreatNonprofits http://greatnonprofits.org/nonprofitnews/lindsay-lohan-car-crash/ … via @GreatNonprofits    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great stories of volunteers who read to kids.  This inspires me to want to read!  http://bit.ly/dnqC80    
    
    
    I'm hiring! Internship: Online Marketing and Social  at GreatNonprofits - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/Jrx7Sh     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/dsDetn    
    
    
    I'm hiring! Online Marketing Associate - Contract Po at GreatNonprofits - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/qMXNgu     
    
    
        
    
    
    Top-Rated National Charities — @GreatNonprofits http://greatnonprofits.org/nonprofitnews/top-national-nonprofits/ … via @GreatNonprofits    
    
    
    @vicvrana @CDEgger @GreatNonprofits Thanks for spreading the word, Victoria!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-mDpxW  Thanks for asking!  1. Would love to see a nonprofit rate for the conference 2. Ditto Rhonda's suggestion 3. A...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @maxmind we are having website slowness.  Can you let me know if your network issue has been resolved?    
    
    
    I'm hiring! VP of Product at GreatNonprofits - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/8JwyTz     
    
    
    If you want to donate, check out the highly-rated @FeedTheChildren in #Oklahomacity.  Great reviews: http://bit.ly/19Z3gOr     
    
    
    Abercrombie and Fitch are out of sync with the socially-conscious generation. http://ow.ly/l4IIc     
    
    
    I'm hiring! VP of Product at GreatNonprofits - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/8UNyGB     
    
    
    Sobratos step down from running daily operations at the family's Silicon Valley real estate company http://lnkd.in/epZqWK     
    
    
        
    
    
    Susan G. Komen sues smaller charities that use pink and the phrase "for the cure" http://huff.to/fGHigV    
    
    
        
    
    
    Thanks @vicvrana for the shout out to share knowledge about nonprofits @GreatNonprofits at #socap13    
    
    
    My latest post: Keep It Simple - Lessons On Feedback Tools for Nonprofits | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131009130111-489685-keep-it-simple-lessons-on-feedback-tools-for-nonprofits …    
    
    
    I'm hiring! VP Business Development at GreatNonprofits - San Francisco Bay Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/bihdynC     
    
    
        
    
    
    Great presentation by @StacyDon on gov procurement reform #CfASummit. Results in more competition, access for small biz and transparency    
    
    
    @Aaron_Hurst says people are looking for purpose and self-expression.  At the Social Venture Partners summit #svp13.    
    
    
        
    
    
    My post on "How to help the Phillippines" on LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131114182408-489685-how-to-help-phillipines …    
    
    
        
    
    
    What awesome karma in the air today with so many of you supporting nonprofits! Love and gratitude all around! pic.twitter.com/qoC6PCJ0Fp    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Know of a great nonprofit improving social justice?  Nominate them for  the GreatNonprofit's Social Justice Campaign. http://bit.ly/nosix0     
    
    
    Check this video out -- How to find great local nonprofits to get involved in! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=afS0MzYLe6g&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    