Viendo... RT @Alltop What makes an employee happy [infographic] http://goo.gl/UiLrr     
    
    
    +1000 RT @gapingvoid Work is the new rock and roll.    
    
    
    Already feel confuse about the version numbers :) RT @Chris_Skinner #Mckinsey: Industry 4.0 =the internet of things http://www.mckinsey.com/Insights/Business_Technology/The_Internet_of_Things_and_the_future_of_manufacturing?cid=other-eml-alt-mip-mck-oth-1306 … …    
    
    
    Verano #tech con #humor RT @HuffPostTech 
Computers are like air conditioners: 
They stop working properly when you open Windows    
    
    
    Agree! RT @ericries "Anyone who says failure is not an option has also ruled out innovation." http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/06/the-lab-or-the-factory.html …    
    
    
    TNW Poll | The most awesome web browser right now is ______ ? (@TheNextWeb) http://wedgi.es/15blY5Z  via @wedgies    
    
    
        
    
    
    Burnout? "Overnight success is fictional. Overnight success comes after years of hard, sustainable work" http://andrewdumont.me/avoiding-burnout … Great advise    
    
    
    @AchimMuellers A nice pitch to overcome the fear of networking too!    
    
    
    @robinwauters What would be (hypothetically) the new valuation the investors would give to that ;))?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Do you use your phone in the bathroom? 
 No, I #WaitToTweet http://wedgi.es/19YjbhA 
 or
 Yes. Yes I do. http://wedgi.es/1aIFx9M  via @wedgies    
    
    
    +1000: "In silence, one learns to discern what truly merits attention." comment on Tech Addiction @nytimes http://nyti.ms/1ddtKgv     
    
    
    Melody Meckfessel, responsible of everything tech in Google http://www.businessinsider.com/the-woman-quietly-responsible-for-google-2013-7 …    
    
    
    Interesting read: Doug Engelbart and the vision thing: Is Silicon Valley lacking imagination? http://gigaom.com/2013/07/05/doug-engelbart-and-the-vision-thing-is-silicon-valley-suffering-from-a-failure-of-imagination/ … @gigaom    
    
    
    Many businesses make money with it... RT @hnshah The Network Effect is Dead, Long Live the Network Effect http://kiss.ly/181ZVme     
    
    
    How to wisely use every penny: 10 Extreme Bootstrapping Ideas http://www.inc.com/christina-desmarais/10-extreme-bootstrapping-ideas.html … via @Inc    
    
    
    #Summer #techthings :) RT @CharlieBeckett Why does my Kindle Touch freeze in the sun? (it's not even getting hot, just running v slow)    
    
    
        
    
    
    A concrete example of why you must not confuse value for free: Why conference tickets cost money… http://tnw.to/q2L6  via @thenextweb    
    
    
        
    
    
    Interesting RT @eesley: Check out "she  : The Documentary" http://buff.ly/1c5rzQ6  #Vimeo #womenintechnology #stanford #goodgirlsgonegee    
    
    
    Albert Einstein said: "If A is to succeed in life, then A = x + y + z. Work is x, y is play and z is to listen." #Quote    
    
    
        
    
    
    I've just downloaded the new published (free) Visual Innovation Accelerator ebook incl. 40+Tools. Get it here: http://bit.ly/YjFw38     
    
    
    Cute! RT @xavierverdaguer: apple's worst days…:( RT @elies: Ha! RT @nokia_uk: Thanks, #Apple ;) pic.twitter.com/WcIFAJIQbm    
    
    
    @Premios_Ondas: "Sin mis fracasos no hubiera aprendido todo lo que sé" @juanralucas Ondas 2010.  http://buff.ly/16qcXXz  #Ondas2013    
    
    
    @AchimMuellers Spammers are the plague of our days :-\    
    
    
        
    
    
    There is fear without innovation. But there is no innovation without fear ;) RT @gapingvoid Innovation vs Fear  http://buff.ly/14f3xNT     
    
    
    This is a nice case of an enterprise 2.0 realization #goodread Is There Life After Email? Yes, & It's Amazing @berkun http://buff.ly/1890BBY     
    
    
    The evolution of the cloud as pictured by @gapingvoid Brilliant! http://us1.campaign-archive2.com/?u=028de8672d5f9a229f15e9edf&id=d99bd781af … #cartoon #cloud    
    
    
    Ya tengo mi ticket para Spain Startup & Investor Summit. http://www.ticketea.com/spain-startup  #socialticketing Mad, 9-10-11 OCT    
    
    
    Tech blogs & women editors: A nice surprise & a top bar for @TheNextWeb y The Verge MT @kelly_heather: Gender counts pic.twitter.com/1HfD45rhFK    
    
    
        
    
    
    Golden rule of content: You have to love them every day, even if they don´t buy from you every day; 
 http://shar.es/KbDxX  by @gapingvoid    
    
    
    When your gadgets get too smart (part 2)...  http://geek-and-poke.com/geekandpoke/2013/9/8/when-your-gadgets-get-too-smart-part-2 … #geekhumour    
    
    
    I had missed this: Great food for thought by @cuchullainn on a topic question! Can we teach entrepreneurs? http://conorneill.com/2013/07/30/can-we-teach-entrepreneurs/#comments …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    A course on creating value form innovation, IE Business School. Yes, innovator can be taught! http://the-i-thread.tumblr.com/post/62147504922/a-course-on-creating-value-from-innovation-ie-business …    
    
    
    Why Dwolla Charges 25 Cents to Send $11 or $11 million | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130919181742-24171-why-dwolla-charges-25-cents-to-send-11-or-11-million …    
    
    
    El hilo de innovación - English version: A course on creating value from innovation, IE Business School (yes,… http://tmblr.co/Z4G4Msw2hW6s     
    
    
    Saved on @Delicious: http://disciplinedentrepreneurship.com/blog/first-business-news-bill-discusses-crisis-entrepreneurship-education?goback=%2Egde_4631029_member_273414557#%21 … First Business News: Bill Discusses the Crisis in Entrepreneurship Education | Disciplined...    
    
    
    Good read RT @deesley Great insights, Sonar's lesson's learned: false positives, branding, being sold vs being bought http://buff.ly/19InsDy     
    
    
    En un ratito al @CIBBVA con @mitefspain "success stories on internet trends", @BernieHernie y otros...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    1 of many articles about the fall of BB: @JaumeTeixi: Fall of BlackBerry, The smartphone inventor failed to adapt http://ow.ly/pkFel     
    
    
    What you call 'disruptive' is just... `Obsoletive' by @stratechery http://stratechery.com/2013/obsoletive/ …    
    
    
    Won't tell which 1 I take :) RT @jmejias RT @FastCompany This is your brain on coffee (& beer):  pic.twitter.com/1yo5kka1hX    
    
    
    Qué horror RT @enekoknorr Candy Crush is the new FarmVille: it's played by people who had never played games before.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Dejà vu? RT @fodor "Greece is collapsing, the Iranians are getting aggressive, & Rome is in disarray. Welcome back to 430 BC." (John Clees)    
    
    
    This is how my brain works ;) https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=620771587975147&set=a.134304433288534.37873.132853273433650&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    Ha! RT @joehas Stream for @Spain_StartUp conf http://goo.gl/tQYVNL  Entrepreneurs will speak in English, politicians in Spanish. worldwide    
    
    
    We still excell at explaining a solution rather than pitching why there is a market. No opportunity in solutions without pains #spainstartup    
    
    
    Great words from @zaryn: "It's not going to be easy!" #entrepreneur #journey #Spainstartup    
    
    
    Says Nelly Kroes: "startups in Europe grow slower than elsewhere... Besides, they soon leave Europe" #EUstartup #challenge at #Spainstartup    
    
    
    Lack of product development capability and go to market capability are mentioned recurrelly at #Spainstartup. Glad my work is in need :)    
    
    
    Listening to @apartovi talk on the concept of failure on the stage of #Spainstartup...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Compite con el IE, donde doy clase. Mi enhorabuena RT @fodor IESE Ranks 1st in Europe - The Economist’s 2013 Ranking http://shar.es/Evngm     
    
    
    Quality, time and cost. You can't have the three at a time!! RT @gapingvoid "Anti-Art" http://instagram.com/p/fVU0WHoap-/     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Want 2 fix advertising, this is 4 you: MT @tefdigital @Wayra is inviting innovation to help accelerate #advertising http://buff.ly/15EGblG     
    
    
    via @GuyKawasaki: “The scariest moment is always just before you start.” ― Stephen King, On Writing. I used to read him a lot when I was 15.    
    
    
    MT @schwentker @LDFleming " w/ the blurring of online & offline shopping we dropped the 'e' from ecommerce"    
    
    
    Although this is also for beginners I'm taking the Hour of Code. Are you? @codeorg http://csedweek.org/  #hourofcode    
    
    
    A special warning against all the buzz RT @berkun "Big data" is sometimes bad data and "little data" is sometimes the best data.    
    
    
    @phodgson That too!! :)    
    
    
    Think, decide and be! RT @85Broads "It is our choices, that show what we truly are, far more than our abilities.” @jk_rowling #quote    
    
    
    @pkedrosky What´s interesting is that all social networks dropped in semester count. Only Instagram went up.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ya en @opinno...    
    
    
        
    
    
    I agree w/ Bob Dorf @opinno, who says his book is more a post than a letter by letter manual. Passion a must to have it right #leanstartup    
    
    
    Je, je RT @enekoknorr Bill Gates Is Trying To Convince Real Madrid To Rename Its Stadium 'Microsoft Bernabéu' http://ow.ly/261shJ     
    
    
    I tell my clients "Innovation should help you solve problems". Now a great post @Chris_Skinner diggs ... http://tmi.me/1bl773     
    
    
    El mejor producto no siempre gana RT @rodriguezhernan Comparativa #BlackberryMessenger #BBM versus #WhatsApp http://evpo.st/H9dzrs     
    
    
    La recepcionista digital!: MyTime’s Amazing App Lets You Book Haircuts, Massages…Any Appointment http://tcrn.ch/16D0iBc     
    
    
        
    
    
    Ireland´s Startup Ecosystem tomorrow. At Area31 of @IEbusiness 19.00 h via @joehas    
    
    
    Arguments against seed startups staying in Silicon Valley. I agree on the distractions bit: http://bit.ly/19WLtdU     
    
    
    Now with a big group that has gathered at area31 of @iebusiness to hear about the Irish Startup ecosystem.    
    
    
    @Gary_Leyden says launchpad (Ireland's # 1 tech accelerator) is open for Spanish entrepreneurs http://lnkd.in/3cUUgx  150 startups last year    
    
    
    #recomendar via @MoisesNaim Read this NYTimes report by the great @LizAlderman on youth joblessness in Europe. http://nyti.ms/1bAXiqO     
    
    
        
    
    
    @ibanborras ¡Qué bueno!    
    
    
    My congrats to @robinwauters & team on the day of release of their new digital edition venture @tech_eu Let's make Internet in Europe glow!    
    
    
    cc @foodinthebox RT @Innovaspain: @NaturalMachines crea impresora 3D de comida variada del mundo http://goo.gl/mghQnm  @FoodiniMeals    
    
    
    ... "manager" (no es directivo), "curator" (¿comisario de contenidos?),...    
    
    
    About @marta_dominguez: 1.1K followers from 21 countries, mostly Spain and United States. Check yours at http://twtrland.com  @twtrland    
    
    
    About @marta_dominguez: 1,113 followers, 64% Men, 79% from Spain, 33% power users. See all http://twtrland.com/profile/marta_dominguez/followers … via @twtrland    
    
    
        
    
    
    +1 RT @Ematnadze Keep Wonder Alive | Sign the #idontknow manifesto http://cono.rs/idontknow/     
    
    
    I'll be judging the final exam of students in the International MBA of @IEbusiness this Thursday.    
    
    
    Set for the final IMBA exam ready. Not intended to intemidate anyone :)  My juzging will start now  #IEbusinessIMBA pic.twitter.com/7OtMnde8zS    
    
    
    True! RT @mathewi not true RT @Pogue: Dear blogs: Any headline that ends in a question mark can be answered by the word “no.”    
    
    
        
    
    
    ¡¡¡SI!!! @isabel_avila @hernandezeat @felixlopez @ginestal @alefeldman @Pacomoraleschef    
    
    
    @rodrigoconz Una impresora 3D @Ultra_lab    
    
    
    Curl up with a cup of cocoa and the best long reads of the year, courtesy of @Pocket http://buff.ly/1jl125G     
    
    
    My take for  January´s HBR cartoon caption contest": Pals, we outnumber our enemy!!!" — Marta Domínguez  http://disq.us/8goymw     
    
    
    On the day of Mao´s 120 anniversary ;)... RT @500startups 2013, a year of epic proportions for e-commerce in China http://buff.ly/1ij5twA     
    
    
    I'm with Oprah #2014 RT @MeredithMBell "To do less than your best is a sin." - Oprah Winfrey    
    
    
    #2014propositions RT @aginnt "the more ideas you implement, the more ideas you'll have." http://bit.ly/1fTOME1     
    
    
    #2014propositions RT @ilikevests Making blogging work 4 you = investing in long form content& publication ... http://tmi.me/1dfcFw     
    
    
    From a bestseller in my childhood RT @tseelig Isaac Asimov Predicts in 1964 What the World Will Look Like ... http://tmi.me/1dfd6v     
    
    
        
    
    
    +1 RT @pazgarde RT @ajmasia: Todos necesitamos sentir que progresamos | José A. Marina #UNEDAlgeciras    
    
    
    Primer "exit" RT @AntonioDomingo Comenta.tv startup surgida en Wayra comprada por empresa norteamericana http://bit.ly/KDYno8     
    
    
    Si todavía no te agobia "beber" tuits a destajo, no leas esto: Twitter I love the stream, but I need more filters  http://gigaom.com/2014/01/09/drinking-from-the-twitter-firehose-i-love-the-stream-but-i-need-more-filters-and-bridges/ …    
    
    
    @cuchullainn some TEDx should simply dissapear. They´re many and mediocre. Original TED is still inspiring.    
    
    
        
    
    
    "a successful business is a never-ending process of adapting & improving", startup execution transcends idea from D 1 http://gust.com/angel-investing/startup-blogs/2012/10/21/startup-execution-transcends-the-idea-from-day-one/ …    
    
    
    #interesting rear view RT @juliomayol Dear all: the internet on the news in 1981 http://wimp.com/theinternet/     
    
    
    Great facts sheet by @tech_eu RT @chrija Almost 100 accelerators in Europe! #hydemo pic.twitter.com/ve03d04t8i    
    
    
    #comparisons RT @Bill_Gross "The entire country of Nigeria had 72 mbs connection. I had 150 mbs to my home in ... http://tmi.me/1dtG2x     
    
    
    #comparissons RT @arusbridger 85 richest people have the same wealth as 50% of world's population  http://theguardian.com/business/2014/ …    
    
    
    And she was my professor of creativity ;) RT @tseelig I will be tweeting from @davos with wef    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    ¿Globalización v 3.0? RT @Bill_Gross: "Competition is not going to be between countries - it will be between cities" - CEO Cisco #wef14    
    
    
    