Jumbo Sweet...yup!  http://yfrog.com/kjujwltj    
    
    
    My year with the Telegraph and its Ghouls in this here New Statesman  
http://www.newstatesman.com/comedy/2011/08/column-telegraph-writing-knew …    
    
    
    Its a Goats day satursay at Goat's Pride Dairy. Liittle kids are ever so cute!!  http://yfrog.com/h4ut1lkj     
    
    
    I think I'm sitting behind Rupert Murdoch at a Michael Franti convcert. Am I Right?  http://yfrog.com/kh4kpjjj     
    
    
    Did anybody else feel a bit queezzy ....earthquake?    
    
    
    Suddenly, the bright star at the center of Silicon Valley's universe has gone out. Indeed. Thank you Steve Jobs for making Silicon Valley.    
    
    
    Dog #1842, my hero! Strays in Athens tagged, collared & vaccinated, not destroyed, so they may demonstrate 4 freedom!  http://shar.es/bb2ar     
    
    
    Vancouver is the kind of place, on a rainy morning, there's someone handing out free umbrellas!!    
    
    
    And in the afternoon the sun shines!!    
    
    
    Staring out the window    
    
    
    Interesting interview with MOA Archivist telling the story of a project I got to work on  CBC.ca North by Northwest: http://bit.ly/uQMvRh     
    
    
    Bravo Marty, saw #Hugo the first good 3D movie. Loved the Little Tramp ref. Perfect casting of a  #Doberman!  And it's a  #Digitizers movie!    
    
    
    This is definitely going to be me this afternoon. A new Christmas eve eve tradition. Now, where's the snow? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Bcq7CC7R74&sns=tw …    
    
    
    Happy New Year, happy new gadget! Oooh got a spiraling grater, it makes beets fun. pic.twitter.com/Uimsk5ti    
    
    
    We know how to roll on NYE. Veggie rice bowls all around. pic.twitter.com/rRIrcV3G    
    
    
    Some bodys birthday today xx  Happy day @PaulBAdams    
    
    
    http://tgam.ca/DQ7d  /via @globeandmail US rejects Keystone Pipeline.  Yay!!!    
    
    
    @DamonLindelof Betty White is a Canadian National Treasure.    
    
    
    Just passed @thekilling_amc filming on Abbott and Pender Sts. Looks cool! pic.twitter.com/Qwx2vHn8    
    
    
    The fact that I am aware I can't pull off wearing one of those cool people beanie/stocking hats makes the world a far better place.    
    
    
    Chinese parade going past my window!! Hung hay fat choy! pic.twitter.com/0OdscHUw    
    
    
    Paradise is not wallpapered with idiots. In fact there is no wallpaper.    
    
    
    Oh Google, you are the Skynet come to life...so post-human. Google's Driverless Autonomous Vehicles  at Symposium: http://nyti.ms/Aljh0V     
    
    
    RIBA the robot bear nurse  lifts one human at a time in Japan http://shar.es/gbcpm   But really, why do I love these robot stories so much!?    
    
    
    Wow. Lee Brain gives powerful testimony at pipeline joint review panel http://thetyee.ca/Video/2012/02/23/Oil-Man-Son/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    so cool! “@MOA_UBC: Our newest blog post is written by Dustin Rivers, an intern working at MOA. Read his story about.. http://fb.me/1qnVpCyvP ”    
    
    
    Wow. The overwhelming presence of Tokyo Sky Tree. Paul Virilio would have much to say on this http://mdn.mainichi.jp/features/news/20120303p2a00m0na002000c.html … @eurogradschool    
    
    
    This is so me....Richmond Review - Wanted: Food blogger to eat at a restaurant a day: http://bit.ly/A5pgtk  via @AddThis    
    
    
    MadMen...Season 4 starts in 22 days...'its time to start a new tab.'    
    
    
    MOOCs, Large Courses Open to All, Topple Campus Walls: http://nyti.ms/AxlsUq  90,000 students    
    
    
    Sharing the Video Metadata Love: http://blogs.archives.gov/online-public-access/?p=7458#.T1jNtBgX9RM.twitter …    
    
    
    Sustainable Japanese Hand-Crank Vending Machine  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kDaQR4NudKw&sns=tw … via @youtube If only the drinks were free after all that cranking!    
    
    
    Read read so hard, yeah! *Viewer discretion advised* B*tches in Bookshops. Read so hard librarians tryin’ ta... http://fb.me/1CkGSWdI5 ”    
    
    
    Going to see Jiro Deams of Sushi, then going to Shuraku Sushi Bar for my own sushi dreaming. #Vancouver #sushi    
    
    
    Words.  Sticky words in my head. 'Cool. Cool cool. Cool, cool, cool.'    
    
    
    #Community @nbccommunity is a bad influence....  on my internal humour sensor.    
    
    
    Yay!! “@Rove: Rove LA coming to U.S. screens from July!  http://latimesblogs.latimes.com/showtracker/2012/03/tv-guide-network-rove-la-standup-stiletto.html …”    
    
    
    You're sad “@Dave_T_Dickson: #EarthHour tonight? C'mon. The #FinalFour is on & #Canucks vs. And next you'll want us to turn off...#nochance”    
    
    
    Inebriates tipping news stands till 4am! Big sports nite? How's that progress since last year? let's give em a downtown party @MayorGregor    
    
    
    Oh you British Library, you are Hilarrrious! “@britishlibrary: Unicorn Cookbook found at #BritishLibrary http://bit.ly/HA2YCP ”    
    
    
    Yay. @Rove: Made by a mate and his mates RT @SuperDingoHero He's a battler. He's a hero. He's bionic. He's SUPER DINGO! http://youtu.be/rAlugcmkx-U     
    
    
    Indian Man Single-Handedly Plants a 1,360 Acre Forest http://www.treehugger.com/natural-sciences/man-single-handedly-plants-entire-forest.html … via @TreeHugger    
    
    
    My kind a place 😊“@chillwinston: If you are looking to escape the rain and the game..”    
    
    
    “@michaelidov: When in Rome, right? pic.twitter.com/6St69U0u”. Too right!    
    
    
    Visual effects artists complain they're often employed in electronic sweatshops http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-ct-visual-effects-workers-20120420,0,563491.story …    
    
    
    NYTimes Lense:  Conjoined 11 yrd old Twins by Annabel Clark: http://nyti.ms/I922lo     
    
    
    Oh how I miss Australia. “@COFAartdesmedia: "i'm so drunk" "me too" *pause* "so what class do we have now?" #cofashuttlebusoverheard”    
    
    
    “@ShannonLaBelle: Congrats! @CloudscapeComic: Whoo! We made it to our goal of $3000 and still going!  http://www.indiegogo.com/Giants-of-Main-Street?c=home …” Well done!    
    
    
    To all those people who faced this wet Monday start of @bikingToWork Week ... I salute you!    
    
    
    Oh, Ouch. “@DamonLindelof: So it begins! 
"Reading the reviews. Seems like you screwed up Prometheus with your crappy writing. Good job.”    
    
    
    This is a bit subversive, but I like it!!  http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/arts/celebrity-photos/celebrity-photos-of-the-week-may-30/article2446691/ …    
    
    
    @CBCVancouver what is all that stuff floating around in the air downtown?    
    
    
    Intentionally using extra dishes just so I can turn on the mostly empty dish washer this week. Missing @PaulBAdams    
    
    
    “Perfect companion, we are having, soup poured, new friends welcomed, exper  @ Chill Winston http://instagr.am/p/LgVMtnPs-x/ ” #stillwinterweather    
    
    
    Working towards getting a twitter certificate    
    
    
    It's the perfect weekend of you're shooting @TheKillingAMC in #Vancouver pic.twitter.com/WoW2kqgp    
    
    
    It's Mai Tai time @disney #aulani resort @gohawaii  @ Aulani Beach Cove http://instagr.am/p/MKLeAeKnKL/     
    
    
    Nice night for a stroll, despite the chill.  http://instagr.am/p/MK9Q2XjDjA/     
    
    
    Keeping it reul #5pinbowling yo pic.twitter.com/M4vclUDZ    
    
    
    “@ShannonLaBelle: BLOG: Cycling on Sea Island and Iona Island: http://carfreevancouver.com/2012/06/22/cycling-on-sea-island-and-iona-island/ … #RichmondBC #bikeyvr” Very cool!    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle can your studies explain this? RT “@GreatDismal: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2kCqkVOkDbE …
「こびと劇場」予告編 !!!”    
    
    
    Saw #MoonriseKingdom yesterday. Loved it. Thank you rainy day Vancouver, oh ... and Wes Anderson.    
    
    
    At the Art? Gallery at Canada Place #CanadaDay pic.twitter.com/VKckD0LL    
    
    
    @TheatreTerrific yay! Water is fantastic. Thanks for making my neighborhood inspiring. pic.twitter.com/9CTn9WGK    
    
    
    Also nice to have the park free of drug dealers for the afternoon,    
    
    
    Getting ready for a weekend BBQ, this time with no rain contingency plan! #Vancouver    
    
    
    @MargaretAtwood at ComicCon...too much. Remember when it was just sweaty storm troopers: Hangin' out with the Klingons http://twitpic.com/a7bs81 ”    
    
    
    Word! “@MelissaStetten: The only person who enjoys the sound of a motorcycle is the asshole riding it.”    
    
    
    So are we. 10th anniv. It gets better “@chris_e_simpson: Watching Firefly. Not terribly impressed... Bit like red dwarf without the humour”    
    
    
    Archives catalogue state of Canadiana as collection set to move into new home http://thetyee.ca/CanadianPress/2012/07/28/Library-Moves-19554017/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    F$&:k no! “@GammaCounter: “David Beckham underwear ad projected onto the White Cliffs of Dover,” is just mental. http://bit.ly/OBFot7 ”    
    
    
    Tonight a very special dinner at @MikuRestaurant. So looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Tonight a very special dinner at @MikuRestaurant. So looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Congrats! So exciting!! “@PaulBAdams: #Writing milestone: completed first draft treatment of new screenplay @ParkRoad. Celebrating ...    
    
    
    Oh Snap! “@BreakingBad_AMC: "To my other favorite W.W. It’s an honour working with you. Fondly, G.B"    
    
    
    “@IanMartin: On a train. Just bought a fizzy drink and giant Mars bar off the trolley. I am fifty fucking nine years old. #selfloathetweet”    
    
    
    Designated Community needs definition. Preserving for who? OAIS    
    
    
    Thrilled 2b@ #mwda2012 Memory of the World in Digital Age @UNESCO http://www.unesco.org/new/en/communication-and-information/events/calendar-of-events/events-websites/the-memory-of-the-world-in-the-digital-age-digitization-and-preservation/ … #digitalpreservation #archives #libraries” Vancouver    
    
    
    Loved #mwda2012 #MotW2012 Thank you UNESCO & Luciana Duranti UBC for bringing together such a experience & knowledge. Amazing conference!    
    
    
    Visited @ShawnHunt opening Archetypes. Magnificent, confronting, opulent, & even tender. Macaulay gallery, Vancouver http://dlvr.it/2DX8NJ     
    
    
    Where? Where is this? I want to go! “@JaneEspenson: Omg!  Making my own s'mores at the table! pic.twitter.com/foAmKztO”    
    
    
    Also saw @Loopermovie, finally an excellent, original film! “@LillyLyle: @greatdismal Just got back from LOOPER, definitely the REAL DEAL.”    
    
    
    World Information Architecture Day 2013 Seeks Local Coordinators. World IA Day is February, 2013 http://iainstitute.org/news/001381.php     
    
    
    “@GreatDismal: Saw Looper matinee. Digestion in progress.” Always the sign of a good movie. Lingers.    
    
    
    If the calculations of Paglen’s team are correct, his little archive will survive longer than people http://www.artnews.com/2012/09/27/engravings-for-the-e-t-in-all-of-us/ …    
    
    
    Yay #VIFF #Hipstamatic #JohnS #Pistil pic.twitter.com/W0iqKIGk    
    
    
    @Slate: The past is not dead. In fact, it's suing: http://slate.me/Sei0ny  #ClassicSlateHeadlines  Misquoting authors, how important are words?    
    
    
    Disappointed the tweet from my new iPhone4 didn't work on Friday...when got to shake Vince Gilligan's hand. Albuquerque survivors!    
    
    
    Counting the days now...until a Niçoise Bouillabaisse with the accompanying croutons and rouille!    
    
    
    This job ad is whack! Where's the kool-aide? - @lululemon is hiring a Social Media Educator: http://ow.ly/f8w3d ”    
    
    
    Amazon knows @lizpadilla: "box set of 'The Wire', bottle of Veuve Clicquot, and wool socks." Looks like I'll be seeing you in the spring!    
    
    
    Stories we tell ourselves. Story telling in the Digital Age http://matadornetwork.com/life/the-importance-of-storytelling-in-the-digital-age/ …    
    
    
    About collusion. @theCurrentCBC Radio interview w Jacques Duchesneau on  Corruption in Government vs Democracy http://www.cbc.ca/thecurrent/episode/2012/11/14/jacques-duchesneau-on-ending-quebec-corruption/ …    
    
    
    Yup! “@News1130radio: RT @Jesse_Johnston: Teachers & staff picketing @ the BCIT campus in #Burnaby. Ugly weather! pic.twitter.com/pIhFZhNW”    
    
    
    Downtown too! “@News1130radio: No school today at @BCIT  due to job action. @Jesse_Johnston reports from the #Burnaby BCIT campus this AM.”    
    
    
    Just how long did you have to wait for this one? #punchlinewaitingtimes “@DamonLindelof: Been there.  Done that.   http://bbc.in/RWaPPm ”    
    
    
    Long sleep-deprived shadows in Regents Park.  http://yfrog.com/f7j00jj    
    
    
    Tibetan monks shopping in Harrods, why not?  http://yfrog.com/459i4qj    
    
    
    Get me out of London! 1 hour of traffic, oh why? http://yfrog.com/2szj2uj    
    
    
    So many tunnels, how do we know we're actually not going in underground circles? http://yfrog.com/0ylnsbj    
    
    
    Yet another tunnel out of London. The Thames is a windy lady,  http://yfrog.com/2o709iuj    
    
    
    At last, on the M25. Muscles relaxing, jaw unclenching, knuckles releasing their white grip. Till Monday, London. http://yfrog.com/myfk6ej    
    
    
    Capturing traces of time. Photographic Paper, Decades Past Its Expiration Date | American Photo http://www.americanphotomag.com/photo-gallery/2012/11/photographic-paper-decades-past-its-expiration-date … via @AmericanPhoto    
    
    
    Very yummy pub lunch in Winchelsea,  lovely spot! But no wireless, can't have everything. http://yfrog.com/4wtgsj    
    
    
    Next life, I want to come back as a little dog, with an owner who takes me along to the cafe for a bacon sandwich. http://yfrog.com/e6z71nj    
    
    
    Oh Hastings, who says you're a bit rough? Yes those are al fresco mens urinals. Not for the shy ... http://yfrog.com/756mnoj    
    
    
    So long London town, till we stress again.  http://yfrog.com/j6453yj  enough said.    
    
    
    Bien arrive! Our first night in Nice. Ou, tres jolie!  http://yfrog.com/j542ecj    
    
    
    Rioting on the streets of Nice. Ok, a small group of students, followed by 6 police cars. Nice is for of oldies.  http://yfrog.com/muy5ctj    
    
    
    Le Cote D'Azur.  Wow!  The colour of the water is indescribably beautiful.  http://yfrog.com/7e69pbj    
    
    
    Paul fait cuire notre dîner ce soir du potage de poulet en notre appartement.  http://yfrog.com/77sr3hj    
    
    
    The trains only ran to Monte Carlo today. So we must slum it - it's a dogs life.  http://yfrog.com/nejypkj    
    
    
    It's good to be 50! Breakfast at the Carlton  http://yfrog.com/ncmn8lj    
    
    
    Après petit dejeuner and due coupe de Champsies  http://yfrog.com/4chzhpj wow!    
    
    
    @lizpadilla Happy 50th birthday mon cherie!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @PaulBAdams - Hope all your wishes come true! pic.twitter.com/yf31FufF    
    
    
    Mmmm, what a special day, how lucky I am. And how grateful for each new day  http://yfrog.com/55draocj    
    
    
    Morning in Menton. Not breakfast at the Carlton, it's better!  http://yfrog.com/3v7hsvj  and Italy just steps away.    
    
    
    Menton, welcome to the land of Limoncello, de Citron, Vert et Mandarin! Mmmm  http://yfrog.com/07qgkdj    
    
    
    Last day in the Sud. Its gorgeous sun. Lovely, but also looking forward to being home in Vancity.  http://yfrog.com/6z3zhhj    
    
    
    Its all rainbows and sunburst at london heathrow now its time to go.  http://yfrog.com/j4vmzhj    
    
    
    Im back baby!  Sunday morning coffee on Granvillle Island, its good to be home!  http://yfrog.com/j4g7qoj    
    
    
    Todays Perugina Bacio wisdom : a true friend knows all there is to know about you yet still likes you.  :)    
    
    
    Are you ever too old for cold pizza for breakfast?  Not if I splash a bit of white truffle oil on. Maintenant, où sont les  pomme frites?    
    
    
    Happy new Rabbit year!!!  Fangs and claws are put away for another 11 years, yeah! Bye bye puss.    
    
    
    Godard's 'Every Man for Himself', wow, thumbs up, right up, way the heck up there, "ah eh hey!"    
    
    
    Reading 'The Slap' by Christos Tsiolkas. I am transported to a breathless Melbourne summer, gasping for a breeze on the tram to St. Kilda.    
    
    
    spending sunday morning creating an MadMen avatar, and I like it.    
    
    
    @TransLink huge line at metro town for BCIT 130. Already more than 1 bus worth.  4 SFU/UBC buses already passed! Why not serve this line!    
    
    
    Styled my profile with a sweet theme using Themeleon by @COLOURlovers http://clrlv.rs/newthemeleon Love it?    
    
    
    In Albuquerque, going to the set of Breaking Bad in a few minutes. Fanboyishly excited.    
    
    
    Today I am itemizing my expenses for taxes...or......there must be some socks that need folding!?!    
    
    
    Learning French, and trying to understand Cricket....why do I do these things?!?    
    
    
    Team le Canada a bien bowled jusqu'à ce que les 25ème over, mais effondré à des 210-run humiliants.    
    
    
    Easy to recognize love at first sight...lucky oranghutan!  Love means sharing your monkey biscuits!  http://shar.es/3dZuF     
    
    
    Woke to a winter wonderland pt2 this morning.  To all of the humble oscar noms...winnings not everything, its an honour to be nominated.    
    
    
    Word of the day, asinine (with descriptive photo) http://yfrog.com/h278655382j    
    
    
    Not too many people made it to the Winteruption Fest at Granville Island. Winter interupted... http://yfrog.com/h49b7uoj    
    
    
    I wanna be an Astrophotographer...but I don't have a back yard. Maybe I can mock it up in my condo?
http://legault.perso.sfr.fr/STS-133.html    
    
    
    IGN's Top Sci-Fi TV shows of all time.  Agree...but #Lost?... Good TV, but sci-fi? http://tv.ign.com/articles/114/1143800p5.html … (Jonesing for some real sci-fi on tv)    
    
    
    Oh Cricket: Why does this seem so sad...
"Can you help us reach 500 followers by the end of the World Cup? Please RT #cricket #cwc2011"    
    
    
    Bring it on!  Making College Free, Online http://thetyee.ca/Mediacheck/2011/03/01/MakingCollegeFreeOnline/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    Went to Granville Islamd to get some artichokes from the artichoke lady. No lady today, just Tom Cruise and the Mission Implausable 3.    
    
    
    Oohh, love a good dystopic reading. YA but story sounds good. Matched by Ally Condle http://myfavouritebooks.blogspot.com/2010/12/matched-by-ally-condle.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The book is dead, long live the book. Authors are writing their own stories in the brave new e-world http://tinyurl.com/49u9h78    
    
    
    Charlie fired from 2 1/2 Men.  Producers are gonna have a hard time finding a drug addled, porn-friendly, narcissistic replacement in LA.    
    
    
    Utility Construction - Shaughnessy http://ow.ly/1bFD6g    
    
    
    I could bid £146.00 to have Jon Snow follow me on Twitter...would I have to wear clown socks?  http://bit.ly/Twitrelief    
    
    
    Here is a link.  http://goo.gl/F798w A BBC lawyer says I cannot tell you what the link is about. I have stepped through the looking glass    
    
    
    Guess I picked the wrong week to watch That Mitchell and Webb Look S3!  Remain Indoors Quiz Broadcast  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ga_rCnueID8 … via @youtube    
    
    
    $200,000 for an android replica? That seems a bargain.  The Geminoid DK  http://tinyurl.com/4q2lf26    
    
    
    This concludes Autumn Watch for today. As the days grow shorter, I hope you'll join us for more indoor skive watching.    
    
    
    Having a Kingyo lunch moment. Basking in the specialness. i even get a whole pot of tea!  http://yfrog.com/h8s16btj    
    
    
    Yup, this is too good!  http://yfrog.com/hs5ocmgj    
    
    
    I am the modern BoardBisMan tucking into my slimy okra and toro rice bowl at the lunch counter at Kingyo.  http://yfrog.com/h0vk1ywj    
    
    
    The only thing better than Sunday lunch, is Sunday lunch plus lemon merangue pie!!! http://yfrog.com/gzuabij    
    
    
    "Freedom of the press is guaranteed only to those who own one."
GE pays zero tax on 2010 profits of $14.2 billion  http://yhoo.it/gqFJx4    
    
    
    They predicted rain all weekend, and it didn't. yeah!    
    
    
    Sipping my JJ Beans, and remembering why I love Granville Island    
    
    
    Right on Sydney Girls High School Astronomy Club for finding the most aesthetically pleasing astronomical target!!  http://shar.es/3SaMH     
    
    
    @zizekspeaks  and this is why I love Twitter, its like having visible thought bubbles... too bad dogs can't twitter.    
    
    
    I love going to lunch, but now I need a nap. Doesn't help that its dark outside at 3:47pm    
    
    
    Pane au Chocolat and a good coffee make everything right.    
    
    
    Drying out after a stroll in pouring rain...still, makes a change from staying indoors watching the pouring rain.    
    
    
    I like it... might counteract the Microsoft shouting pwd reminder...or could be amusing with sys ads if I forget my pwd http://weyume.com/2011/04/05/passfirmations/ …    
    
    
    Dont watch unless you want to break out into a spontaneous "There beneath the blue suburban skies...' all day.... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7sCeyqDPViE&feature=share …    
    
    
    Space 1st : Australians (duh!) perfect beer in space  http://media.smh.com.au/technology/tech-talk/an-aussie-space-first-beer-2293426.html    
    
    
    I feel very sanctimoneous tuning up my bike and riding in the sunny fresh air to the Granville Island market! Harumph!    
    
    
    Er, sanctimonious.  http://yfrog.com/h4tdrfuj    
    
    
    @Rove1974 We are all happy you're here to remind us and you are happy too!! Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    knee deep in flash, why does vacuuming the house sound like more fun?    
    
    
    Who wants to play Mad Men season 4 -  I'll start.  SCDP gets a new client...IBM ?!    
    
    
    Saw #Limitless yesterday. Loved the cinematography, liked the story and ideas.   Made me think, after.  Sign of a good film!!    
    
    
    FBI memo alleges aliens did in fact land in New Mexico http://yhoo.it/dPsVHR    New Mexico, been there... some of us managed to escape.    
    
    
    This is Monday on the northwest coast ... http://pic.gd/a5ed0d    
    
    
    Brilliant...except for the decapitated zombie bodies. Yikes! @simonblackwell Extraordinarily detailed .. of St Paul's.: http://bit.ly/dZwsbW    
    
    
    Getting very loud outside Rogers Arena! Peut-être la discussion political en français est terminée ?    
    
    
    Vancouverites must've been moved by French language Canadian Federal #elxn41 Debate last night!  They were shouting & cheering all night!    
    
    
    Vancouver fashion: rubber pancho, leggings, booties, dinosaur tuque, hoop earrings, plunger coffee mug. http://pic.gd/31ce85    
    
    
    Watching the snow fall, from bed, with a nice hot coffee!! Its good to be home! http://yfrog.com/75uyywj    
    
    
    "We all travel the Milky Way together, trees and men." 
— John Muir (The Mountains of California)    
    
    
    What a beautiful day. It's as iif someone cut a hole in the clouds over False Creeck to let the sun in. Thank you.    
    
    
    Oh Vancouver! I picker the wrong day for a quick errand to Granville St....it was BLAZZIN! Contact high!    
    
    
    Property rights for Animals:  http://www.smh.com.au/environment/animals/give-animals-property-rights-uni-lecturer-20110422-1dr79.html#poll … "Why would somebody give animals more rights than humans?" Yet we do to corporations!    
    
    
    Another winner, thanks to @tripadvisor. Burger 55, Penticton. Yum!  http://yfrog.com/h3cu6swj   http://yfrog.com/h31egxyj    
    
    
    Chaser's Letter To The Queen http://www.smh.com.au/lifestyle/royal-wedding/abc-not-amused-as-royals-ban-chaser-threaten-coverage-20110427-1dwyd.html …  Royals demand ABC cancel the Chaser, as #royalwedding commentators, or lose video feeds..    
    
    
    Nice window display at BlackberryBooks Granville Island. www poetryIsDead.ca  http://yfrog.com/hsushdvj    
    
    
    10 years later, two wars ongoing, $900US billion spent, 6000 soldiers died, 42,000 soldiers injured. Iraqi Refugees + 2.1 mil. @BarackObama    
    
    
    digitally freshen up : A term used to excuse oneself from face-time company for reasons of a burning desire to check email & social media.    
    
    
    digitally freshen up : or...update one's avatar because #MadMen season 5 is not available till early 2012!    
    
    
    Paul is reading my copy of Superman #900...I'm trying to hold back the spoilers. What a couple of nerds.    
    
    
    Good weeks work...its Finally Friday! yeah!  If only the weather would cooperate and supply some Sun day.    
    
    
    Neurowear: "Just imagine if we have organs that doesn’t exist, moreover we can control that new body?" http://neurowear.net/?p=81  #ThankYou Japan!    
    
    
    Okay, torrential rain and hail now in #Vancouver. When the going gets tough, we go 10-pin #bowling !! http://yfrog.com/gzoq4dkj    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle you are so on! Hope you enjoyed your first #DOXA2011 
Might go on Thursday.    
    
    
    @CWWRyan @photoclassic Pair of Golden Eagles are resident at the Museum of Anthropology at the University of BC in Vancouver. Just saw one.    
    
    
    @DamonLindelof Right on Vancouver!    
    
    
    A bit wet at Granville Island. Not fit for man or gull. Still #oyamasausage still a draw, worth the soggy visit. http://yfrog.com/gytzpyej    
    
    
    Signs of spring  ... False Creek Canada Geese (Branta canadensis) and goslings Too Cute! http://hpstm.tc/p/gg2d #hipstamatic    
    
    
    Did you guys see the new Torchwood trailer? Hooray!  http://bit.ly/lJpz3g    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle take/post pictures if you can. Would love to see them. I bet you even got sun in #halifax , lucky you.    
    
    
    I'll be on the Tonight Show with @jayleno tonight, along with @ParisHilton and INXS.  http://yfrog.com/h65vzfcj    
    
    
    I sound like those people who move near an airport...I know it's the Stanley Cup and all, but will the masses outside Roger's Arena...sshhh.    
    
    
    Consider honey http://gu.com/p/2pe6x/tw  Nice article in the @guardian The simplest resources are the best. Clean air, water, and bees.    
    
    
    Yeah! The Official STAR TREK Convention: 45th Anniversary in VANCOUVER, BC. June 10-12  http://www.creationent.com/cal/stvan.htm#events … Don't miss the Klingon Breakfast    
    
    
    Saw a group of women wearing hockey jerseys, with baby strollers outside Rogers Arena. You know what they were don't you? Mother Canuckers    
    
    
    Finally watched #Firefly sci-fi series from Joss Whedon via #Netfix.  Enjoyed the originality of the story  and the world.  Joss rocks!!    
    
    
    I think I saw Liza Minelli on the 44 Express bus this morning. Yes?    
    
    
    Information / Futurist consorts, watch & enjoy #Mailer & #McLuhan Debate the Electronic Age 1968 http://shar.es/HYPJr  #Digital @thomgillespie    
    
    
    Lots of people are asking whether Peep Show is coming back. It is! Series 7 will be filmed later this year & transmitted, well, even later.    
    
    
    Can photo albums survive the digital age? http://gu.com/p/2qp55/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    And so it begins #Vancouver. Good luck to all #stanleycup #Canucks  Just hope everyone gets home healthy, esp the players!,    
    
    
    Yeah Hockey is over. now everyone please go home, quietly and quickly. See you in a few weeks when the hockey starts up again.    
    
    
    It's getting dark in the car park. Might go to the room. Oh God. http://yfrog.com/kit9ldqj     
    
    
    Indeed. #Vancouver  http://hpstm.tc/p/kwss #hipstamatic    
    
    
    Walked across our beautiful downtown #vancouver today. Not a single #Canucks jersey in sight. They cant use them to hide behind anymore.    
    
    
    There is nothing but the journey. #VadeMecum    
    
    
    Interesting. Carrying written tweets by train from San Fran to D.C., route of the 1st transcontinental telegram (1861) http://creativetime.org/programs/archive/2011/tweets/?p=118 …    
    
    
    British Library & Google 'There is no doubt that #digitization will greatly benefit the research process.'  http://gu.com/p/3v2j7/tw . 150m works    
    
    
    Sense-Roid jacket lets you cuddle yourself (Wired UK) http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2011-06/22/sense-roid-self-hugging-jacket …. the ideal haptic communication partner..Domo arigato Japan!    
    
    
    Have you seen a foreign film with an American villain (pref. played by Yank actor) in the last 10 years? Drop me a line, I'm making a list.    
    
    
    Is it fair to make an interview candidate wait 15 minutes?    
    
    
    Wishing everyone a happy and fun Canada Day!!  http://yfrog.com/hs6jqdkej from Steveston.    
    
    
    Had A Glorious Morning Hike In Whistler. So Green And Quiet, With The Sweet Smells Of Earth.  http://hpstm.tc/p/pj2x    
    
    
    Re: Cemetery Discovery Day @ShannonLaBelle "Why not bring a picnic." Really?! That's a find.    
    
    
    If only my iphone could take a picture of itself, watching Mad Max on the iphone. Does it get any better?...sweet!!!!    
    
    
    Don't write off the Goose till you see the box going into the hole.    
    
    
    Excellent talk by MIT's Sherry Turkle who spent 15 years exploring our lives on the #digitalterrain. Alone Together: http://bit.ly/ngw84H     
    
    
    Awesome iPhoto pic of last Space Shuttle Launch Captured from an Airplane Window Seat by 18 yr old http://www.petapixel.com/2011/07/08/last-space-shuttle-launch-captured-from-an-airplane-window-seat/ … via @petapixel #NASA    
    
    
    Nous finissons par faire de la vitesse elle-même le symbole de l'innovation?  Paul #Virilio vitesse ARTE: http://www.arte.tv/fr/2151166,CmC=2395272.html#.Th3G0ihu9ik.tweet … #Digitization    
    
    
    Speaking of digitization, new from Digitalism - Forrest Gump http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JT5gotTnoDg&feature=share … via @youtube  schön schön wunderbar! @digitalismMusic    
    
    
    slideshow Community Supported Fishery (CSF ) trip Nass River BC,  canneries & Alert Bay http://flic.kr/s/aHsjvjLSry  http://www.wildbcsalmon.org  @ocean_wise    
    
    
    Enjoying the rain at #Vancouver West End Farmers Market.  #bummersummer cant keep this beautiful produce away  http://yfrog.com/khcn6yjj    
    
    
    IN SHOCK: just got off phone call with my technophobe 86 year old mother who informs me she is about to buy an #iPad    
    
    
    "And so the beauty of lilies falls on angels and men, bears and squirrels, wolves and sheep, birds and bees.." John Muir    
    
    
    Sipping a Granville Island IPA, after the 1.5 hr long customs inspection. I bet Donald Sutherland didnt have to wait. He's very tall!    
    
    
    Just installed the new #apple #OSX. I'm really not sure why they thought reversing my mouse wheel direction would be a good idea.    
    
    
    It's pouring rain, and sunny with patches of blue sky in #Vancouver. Some more words for 'rain' are needed. Its prainshining   #bummersummer    
    
    
    What's your fave LIVING female SF writer (besides Le Guin)? Somebody's looking for them... help...    
    
    
    So long #AmyWinehouse  Such an amazing voice, a true jazz - worthy style. But such a mess. Drugs suck.    
    
    
    Clean fresh air. I love Vancouver!    
    
    
    Orions Reflection, where new stars are forming inside the dense nebula.  So beautiful  http://on.natgeo.com/nd1AGy  via @NatGeo    
    
    
    Jumbo Sweet...yup!  http://yfrog.com/kjujwltj    
    
    
    My year with the Telegraph and its Ghouls in this here New Statesman  
http://www.newstatesman.com/comedy/2011/08/column-telegraph-writing-knew …    
    
    
    Its a Goats day satursay at Goat's Pride Dairy. Liittle kids are ever so cute!!  http://yfrog.com/h4ut1lkj     
    
    
    I think I'm sitting behind Rupert Murdoch at a Michael Franti convcert. Am I Right?  http://yfrog.com/kh4kpjjj     
    
    
    Did anybody else feel a bit queezzy ....earthquake?    
    
    
    Suddenly, the bright star at the center of Silicon Valley's universe has gone out. Indeed. Thank you Steve Jobs for making Silicon Valley.    
    
    
    Dog #1842, my hero! Strays in Athens tagged, collared & vaccinated, not destroyed, so they may demonstrate 4 freedom!  http://shar.es/bb2ar     
    
    
    Vancouver is the kind of place, on a rainy morning, there's someone handing out free umbrellas!!    
    
    
    And in the afternoon the sun shines!!    
    
    
    Staring out the window    
    
    
    Interesting interview with MOA Archivist telling the story of a project I got to work on  CBC.ca North by Northwest: http://bit.ly/uQMvRh     
    
    
    Bravo Marty, saw #Hugo the first good 3D movie. Loved the Little Tramp ref. Perfect casting of a  #Doberman!  And it's a  #Digitizers movie!    
    
    
    This is definitely going to be me this afternoon. A new Christmas eve eve tradition. Now, where's the snow? http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Bcq7CC7R74&sns=tw …    
    
    
    Happy New Year, happy new gadget! Oooh got a spiraling grater, it makes beets fun. pic.twitter.com/Uimsk5ti    
    
    
    We know how to roll on NYE. Veggie rice bowls all around. pic.twitter.com/rRIrcV3G    
    
    
    Some bodys birthday today xx  Happy day @PaulBAdams    
    
    
    http://tgam.ca/DQ7d  /via @globeandmail US rejects Keystone Pipeline.  Yay!!!    
    
    
    @DamonLindelof Betty White is a Canadian National Treasure.    
    
    
    Just passed @thekilling_amc filming on Abbott and Pender Sts. Looks cool! pic.twitter.com/Qwx2vHn8    
    
    
    The fact that I am aware I can't pull off wearing one of those cool people beanie/stocking hats makes the world a far better place.    
    
    
    Chinese parade going past my window!! Hung hay fat choy! pic.twitter.com/0OdscHUw    
    
    
    Paradise is not wallpapered with idiots. In fact there is no wallpaper.    
    
    
    Oh Google, you are the Skynet come to life...so post-human. Google's Driverless Autonomous Vehicles  at Symposium: http://nyti.ms/Aljh0V     
    
    
    RIBA the robot bear nurse  lifts one human at a time in Japan http://shar.es/gbcpm   But really, why do I love these robot stories so much!?    
    
    
    Wow. Lee Brain gives powerful testimony at pipeline joint review panel http://thetyee.ca/Video/2012/02/23/Oil-Man-Son/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    so cool! “@MOA_UBC: Our newest blog post is written by Dustin Rivers, an intern working at MOA. Read his story about.. http://fb.me/1qnVpCyvP ”    
    
    
    Wow. The overwhelming presence of Tokyo Sky Tree. Paul Virilio would have much to say on this http://mdn.mainichi.jp/features/news/20120303p2a00m0na002000c.html … @eurogradschool    
    
    
    This is so me....Richmond Review - Wanted: Food blogger to eat at a restaurant a day: http://bit.ly/A5pgtk  via @AddThis    
    
    
    MadMen...Season 4 starts in 22 days...'its time to start a new tab.'    
    
    
    MOOCs, Large Courses Open to All, Topple Campus Walls: http://nyti.ms/AxlsUq  90,000 students    
    
    
    Sharing the Video Metadata Love: http://blogs.archives.gov/online-public-access/?p=7458#.T1jNtBgX9RM.twitter …    
    
    
    Sustainable Japanese Hand-Crank Vending Machine  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kDaQR4NudKw&sns=tw … via @youtube If only the drinks were free after all that cranking!    
    
    
    Read read so hard, yeah! *Viewer discretion advised* B*tches in Bookshops. Read so hard librarians tryin’ ta... http://fb.me/1CkGSWdI5 ”    
    
    
    Going to see Jiro Deams of Sushi, then going to Shuraku Sushi Bar for my own sushi dreaming. #Vancouver #sushi    
    
    
    Words.  Sticky words in my head. 'Cool. Cool cool. Cool, cool, cool.'    
    
    
    #Community @nbccommunity is a bad influence....  on my internal humour sensor.    
    
    
    Yay!! “@Rove: Rove LA coming to U.S. screens from July!  http://latimesblogs.latimes.com/showtracker/2012/03/tv-guide-network-rove-la-standup-stiletto.html …”    
    
    
    You're sad “@Dave_T_Dickson: #EarthHour tonight? C'mon. The #FinalFour is on & #Canucks vs. And next you'll want us to turn off...#nochance”    
    
    
    Inebriates tipping news stands till 4am! Big sports nite? How's that progress since last year? let's give em a downtown party @MayorGregor    
    
    
    Oh you British Library, you are Hilarrrious! “@britishlibrary: Unicorn Cookbook found at #BritishLibrary http://bit.ly/HA2YCP ”    
    
    
    Yay. @Rove: Made by a mate and his mates RT @SuperDingoHero He's a battler. He's a hero. He's bionic. He's SUPER DINGO! http://youtu.be/rAlugcmkx-U     
    
    
    Indian Man Single-Handedly Plants a 1,360 Acre Forest http://www.treehugger.com/natural-sciences/man-single-handedly-plants-entire-forest.html … via @TreeHugger    
    
    
    My kind a place 😊“@chillwinston: If you are looking to escape the rain and the game..”    
    
    
    “@michaelidov: When in Rome, right? pic.twitter.com/6St69U0u”. Too right!    
    
    
    Visual effects artists complain they're often employed in electronic sweatshops http://www.latimes.com/business/la-fi-ct-visual-effects-workers-20120420,0,563491.story …    
    
    
    NYTimes Lense:  Conjoined 11 yrd old Twins by Annabel Clark: http://nyti.ms/I922lo     
    
    
    Oh how I miss Australia. “@COFAartdesmedia: "i'm so drunk" "me too" *pause* "so what class do we have now?" #cofashuttlebusoverheard”    
    
    
    “@ShannonLaBelle: Congrats! @CloudscapeComic: Whoo! We made it to our goal of $3000 and still going!  http://www.indiegogo.com/Giants-of-Main-Street?c=home …” Well done!    
    
    
    To all those people who faced this wet Monday start of @bikingToWork Week ... I salute you!    
    
    
    Oh, Ouch. “@DamonLindelof: So it begins! 
"Reading the reviews. Seems like you screwed up Prometheus with your crappy writing. Good job.”    
    
    
    This is a bit subversive, but I like it!!  http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/arts/celebrity-photos/celebrity-photos-of-the-week-may-30/article2446691/ …    
    
    
    @CBCVancouver what is all that stuff floating around in the air downtown?    
    
    
    Intentionally using extra dishes just so I can turn on the mostly empty dish washer this week. Missing @PaulBAdams    
    
    
    “Perfect companion, we are having, soup poured, new friends welcomed, exper  @ Chill Winston http://instagr.am/p/LgVMtnPs-x/ ” #stillwinterweather    
    
    
    Working towards getting a twitter certificate    
    
    
    It's the perfect weekend of you're shooting @TheKillingAMC in #Vancouver pic.twitter.com/WoW2kqgp    
    
    
    It's Mai Tai time @disney #aulani resort @gohawaii  @ Aulani Beach Cove http://instagr.am/p/MKLeAeKnKL/     
    
    
    Nice night for a stroll, despite the chill.  http://instagr.am/p/MK9Q2XjDjA/     
    
    
    Keeping it reul #5pinbowling yo pic.twitter.com/M4vclUDZ    
    
    
    “@ShannonLaBelle: BLOG: Cycling on Sea Island and Iona Island: http://carfreevancouver.com/2012/06/22/cycling-on-sea-island-and-iona-island/ … #RichmondBC #bikeyvr” Very cool!    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle can your studies explain this? RT “@GreatDismal: http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=2kCqkVOkDbE …
「こびと劇場」予告編 !!!”    
    
    
    Saw #MoonriseKingdom yesterday. Loved it. Thank you rainy day Vancouver, oh ... and Wes Anderson.    
    
    
    At the Art? Gallery at Canada Place #CanadaDay pic.twitter.com/VKckD0LL    
    
    
    @TheatreTerrific yay! Water is fantastic. Thanks for making my neighborhood inspiring. pic.twitter.com/9CTn9WGK    
    
    
    Also nice to have the park free of drug dealers for the afternoon,    
    
    
    Getting ready for a weekend BBQ, this time with no rain contingency plan! #Vancouver    
    
    
    @MargaretAtwood at ComicCon...too much. Remember when it was just sweaty storm troopers: Hangin' out with the Klingons http://twitpic.com/a7bs81 ”    
    
    
    Word! “@MelissaStetten: The only person who enjoys the sound of a motorcycle is the asshole riding it.”    
    
    
    So are we. 10th anniv. It gets better “@chris_e_simpson: Watching Firefly. Not terribly impressed... Bit like red dwarf without the humour”    
    
    
    Archives catalogue state of Canadiana as collection set to move into new home http://thetyee.ca/CanadianPress/2012/07/28/Library-Moves-19554017/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    F$&:k no! “@GammaCounter: “David Beckham underwear ad projected onto the White Cliffs of Dover,” is just mental. http://bit.ly/OBFot7 ”    
    
    
    Tonight a very special dinner at @MikuRestaurant. So looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Tonight a very special dinner at @MikuRestaurant. So looking forward to it!    
    
    
    Congrats! So exciting!! “@PaulBAdams: #Writing milestone: completed first draft treatment of new screenplay @ParkRoad. Celebrating ...    
    
    
    Oh Snap! “@BreakingBad_AMC: "To my other favorite W.W. It’s an honour working with you. Fondly, G.B"    
    
    
    “@IanMartin: On a train. Just bought a fizzy drink and giant Mars bar off the trolley. I am fifty fucking nine years old. #selfloathetweet”    
    
    
    Designated Community needs definition. Preserving for who? OAIS    
    
    
    Thrilled 2b@ #mwda2012 Memory of the World in Digital Age @UNESCO http://www.unesco.org/new/en/communication-and-information/events/calendar-of-events/events-websites/the-memory-of-the-world-in-the-digital-age-digitization-and-preservation/ … #digitalpreservation #archives #libraries” Vancouver    
    
    
    Loved #mwda2012 #MotW2012 Thank you UNESCO & Luciana Duranti UBC for bringing together such a experience & knowledge. Amazing conference!    
    
    
    Visited @ShawnHunt opening Archetypes. Magnificent, confronting, opulent, & even tender. Macaulay gallery, Vancouver http://dlvr.it/2DX8NJ     
    
    
    Where? Where is this? I want to go! “@JaneEspenson: Omg!  Making my own s'mores at the table! pic.twitter.com/foAmKztO”    
    
    
    Also saw @Loopermovie, finally an excellent, original film! “@LillyLyle: @greatdismal Just got back from LOOPER, definitely the REAL DEAL.”    
    
    
    World Information Architecture Day 2013 Seeks Local Coordinators. World IA Day is February, 2013 http://iainstitute.org/news/001381.php     
    
    
    “@GreatDismal: Saw Looper matinee. Digestion in progress.” Always the sign of a good movie. Lingers.    
    
    
    If the calculations of Paglen’s team are correct, his little archive will survive longer than people http://www.artnews.com/2012/09/27/engravings-for-the-e-t-in-all-of-us/ …    
    
    
    Yay #VIFF #Hipstamatic #JohnS #Pistil pic.twitter.com/W0iqKIGk    
    
    
    @Slate: The past is not dead. In fact, it's suing: http://slate.me/Sei0ny  #ClassicSlateHeadlines  Misquoting authors, how important are words?    
    
    
    Disappointed the tweet from my new iPhone4 didn't work on Friday...when got to shake Vince Gilligan's hand. Albuquerque survivors!    
    
    
    Counting the days now...until a Niçoise Bouillabaisse with the accompanying croutons and rouille!    
    
    
    This job ad is whack! Where's the kool-aide? - @lululemon is hiring a Social Media Educator: http://ow.ly/f8w3d ”    
    
    
    Amazon knows @lizpadilla: "box set of 'The Wire', bottle of Veuve Clicquot, and wool socks." Looks like I'll be seeing you in the spring!    
    
    
    Stories we tell ourselves. Story telling in the Digital Age http://matadornetwork.com/life/the-importance-of-storytelling-in-the-digital-age/ …    
    
    
    About collusion. @theCurrentCBC Radio interview w Jacques Duchesneau on  Corruption in Government vs Democracy http://www.cbc.ca/thecurrent/episode/2012/11/14/jacques-duchesneau-on-ending-quebec-corruption/ …    
    
    
    Yup! “@News1130radio: RT @Jesse_Johnston: Teachers & staff picketing @ the BCIT campus in #Burnaby. Ugly weather! pic.twitter.com/pIhFZhNW”    
    
    
    Downtown too! “@News1130radio: No school today at @BCIT  due to job action. @Jesse_Johnston reports from the #Burnaby BCIT campus this AM.”    
    
    
    Just how long did you have to wait for this one? #punchlinewaitingtimes “@DamonLindelof: Been there.  Done that.   http://bbc.in/RWaPPm ”    
    
    
    Long sleep-deprived shadows in Regents Park.  http://yfrog.com/f7j00jj    
    
    
    Tibetan monks shopping in Harrods, why not?  http://yfrog.com/459i4qj    
    
    
    Get me out of London! 1 hour of traffic, oh why? http://yfrog.com/2szj2uj    
    
    
    So many tunnels, how do we know we're actually not going in underground circles? http://yfrog.com/0ylnsbj    
    
    
    Yet another tunnel out of London. The Thames is a windy lady,  http://yfrog.com/2o709iuj    
    
    
    At last, on the M25. Muscles relaxing, jaw unclenching, knuckles releasing their white grip. Till Monday, London. http://yfrog.com/myfk6ej    
    
    
    Capturing traces of time. Photographic Paper, Decades Past Its Expiration Date | American Photo http://www.americanphotomag.com/photo-gallery/2012/11/photographic-paper-decades-past-its-expiration-date … via @AmericanPhoto    
    
    
    Very yummy pub lunch in Winchelsea,  lovely spot! But no wireless, can't have everything. http://yfrog.com/4wtgsj    
    
    
    Next life, I want to come back as a little dog, with an owner who takes me along to the cafe for a bacon sandwich. http://yfrog.com/e6z71nj    
    
    
    Oh Hastings, who says you're a bit rough? Yes those are al fresco mens urinals. Not for the shy ... http://yfrog.com/756mnoj    
    
    
    So long London town, till we stress again.  http://yfrog.com/j6453yj  enough said.    
    
    
    Bien arrive! Our first night in Nice. Ou, tres jolie!  http://yfrog.com/j542ecj    
    
    
    Rioting on the streets of Nice. Ok, a small group of students, followed by 6 police cars. Nice is for of oldies.  http://yfrog.com/muy5ctj    
    
    
    Le Cote D'Azur.  Wow!  The colour of the water is indescribably beautiful.  http://yfrog.com/7e69pbj    
    
    
    Paul fait cuire notre dîner ce soir du potage de poulet en notre appartement.  http://yfrog.com/77sr3hj    
    
    
    The trains only ran to Monte Carlo today. So we must slum it - it's a dogs life.  http://yfrog.com/nejypkj    
    
    
    It's good to be 50! Breakfast at the Carlton  http://yfrog.com/ncmn8lj    
    
    
    Après petit dejeuner and due coupe de Champsies  http://yfrog.com/4chzhpj wow!    
    
    
    @lizpadilla Happy 50th birthday mon cherie!    
    
    
    Happy Birthday @PaulBAdams - Hope all your wishes come true! pic.twitter.com/yf31FufF    
    
    
    Mmmm, what a special day, how lucky I am. And how grateful for each new day  http://yfrog.com/55draocj    
    
    
    Morning in Menton. Not breakfast at the Carlton, it's better!  http://yfrog.com/3v7hsvj  and Italy just steps away.    
    
    
    Menton, welcome to the land of Limoncello, de Citron, Vert et Mandarin! Mmmm  http://yfrog.com/07qgkdj    
    
    
    Last day in the Sud. Its gorgeous sun. Lovely, but also looking forward to being home in Vancity.  http://yfrog.com/6z3zhhj    
    
    
    Its all rainbows and sunburst at london heathrow now its time to go.  http://yfrog.com/j4vmzhj    
    
    
    Im back baby!  Sunday morning coffee on Granvillle Island, its good to be home!  http://yfrog.com/j4g7qoj    
    
    
    Todays Perugina Bacio wisdom : a true friend knows all there is to know about you yet still likes you.  :)    
    
    
    Are you ever too old for cold pizza for breakfast?  Not if I splash a bit of white truffle oil on. Maintenant, où sont les  pomme frites?    
    
    
    Happy new Rabbit year!!!  Fangs and claws are put away for another 11 years, yeah! Bye bye puss.    
    
    
    Godard's 'Every Man for Himself', wow, thumbs up, right up, way the heck up there, "ah eh hey!"    
    
    
    Reading 'The Slap' by Christos Tsiolkas. I am transported to a breathless Melbourne summer, gasping for a breeze on the tram to St. Kilda.    
    
    
    spending sunday morning creating an MadMen avatar, and I like it.    
    
    
    @TransLink huge line at metro town for BCIT 130. Already more than 1 bus worth.  4 SFU/UBC buses already passed! Why not serve this line!    
    
    
    Styled my profile with a sweet theme using Themeleon by @COLOURlovers http://clrlv.rs/newthemeleon Love it?    
    
    
    In Albuquerque, going to the set of Breaking Bad in a few minutes. Fanboyishly excited.    
    
    
    Today I am itemizing my expenses for taxes...or......there must be some socks that need folding!?!    
    
    
    Learning French, and trying to understand Cricket....why do I do these things?!?    
    
    
    Team le Canada a bien bowled jusqu'à ce que les 25ème over, mais effondré à des 210-run humiliants.    
    
    
    Easy to recognize love at first sight...lucky oranghutan!  Love means sharing your monkey biscuits!  http://shar.es/3dZuF     
    
    
    Woke to a winter wonderland pt2 this morning.  To all of the humble oscar noms...winnings not everything, its an honour to be nominated.    
    
    
    Word of the day, asinine (with descriptive photo) http://yfrog.com/h278655382j    
    
    
    Not too many people made it to the Winteruption Fest at Granville Island. Winter interupted... http://yfrog.com/h49b7uoj    
    
    
    I wanna be an Astrophotographer...but I don't have a back yard. Maybe I can mock it up in my condo?
http://legault.perso.sfr.fr/STS-133.html    
    
    
    IGN's Top Sci-Fi TV shows of all time.  Agree...but #Lost?... Good TV, but sci-fi? http://tv.ign.com/articles/114/1143800p5.html … (Jonesing for some real sci-fi on tv)    
    
    
    Oh Cricket: Why does this seem so sad...
"Can you help us reach 500 followers by the end of the World Cup? Please RT #cricket #cwc2011"    
    
    
    Bring it on!  Making College Free, Online http://thetyee.ca/Mediacheck/2011/03/01/MakingCollegeFreeOnline/ … via @thetyee    
    
    
    Went to Granville Islamd to get some artichokes from the artichoke lady. No lady today, just Tom Cruise and the Mission Implausable 3.    
    
    
    Oohh, love a good dystopic reading. YA but story sounds good. Matched by Ally Condle http://myfavouritebooks.blogspot.com/2010/12/matched-by-ally-condle.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    The book is dead, long live the book. Authors are writing their own stories in the brave new e-world http://tinyurl.com/49u9h78    
    
    
    Charlie fired from 2 1/2 Men.  Producers are gonna have a hard time finding a drug addled, porn-friendly, narcissistic replacement in LA.    
    
    
    Utility Construction - Shaughnessy http://ow.ly/1bFD6g    
    
    
    I could bid £146.00 to have Jon Snow follow me on Twitter...would I have to wear clown socks?  http://bit.ly/Twitrelief    
    
    
    Here is a link.  http://goo.gl/F798w A BBC lawyer says I cannot tell you what the link is about. I have stepped through the looking glass    
    
    
    Guess I picked the wrong week to watch That Mitchell and Webb Look S3!  Remain Indoors Quiz Broadcast  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ga_rCnueID8 … via @youtube    
    
    
    $200,000 for an android replica? That seems a bargain.  The Geminoid DK  http://tinyurl.com/4q2lf26    
    
    
    This concludes Autumn Watch for today. As the days grow shorter, I hope you'll join us for more indoor skive watching.    
    
    
    Having a Kingyo lunch moment. Basking in the specialness. i even get a whole pot of tea!  http://yfrog.com/h8s16btj    
    
    
    Yup, this is too good!  http://yfrog.com/hs5ocmgj    
    
    
    I am the modern BoardBisMan tucking into my slimy okra and toro rice bowl at the lunch counter at Kingyo.  http://yfrog.com/h0vk1ywj    
    
    
    The only thing better than Sunday lunch, is Sunday lunch plus lemon merangue pie!!! http://yfrog.com/gzuabij    
    
    
    "Freedom of the press is guaranteed only to those who own one."
GE pays zero tax on 2010 profits of $14.2 billion  http://yhoo.it/gqFJx4    
    
    
    They predicted rain all weekend, and it didn't. yeah!    
    
    
    Sipping my JJ Beans, and remembering why I love Granville Island    
    
    
    Right on Sydney Girls High School Astronomy Club for finding the most aesthetically pleasing astronomical target!!  http://shar.es/3SaMH     
    
    
    @zizekspeaks  and this is why I love Twitter, its like having visible thought bubbles... too bad dogs can't twitter.    
    
    
    I love going to lunch, but now I need a nap. Doesn't help that its dark outside at 3:47pm    
    
    
    Pane au Chocolat and a good coffee make everything right.    
    
    
    Drying out after a stroll in pouring rain...still, makes a change from staying indoors watching the pouring rain.    
    
    
    I like it... might counteract the Microsoft shouting pwd reminder...or could be amusing with sys ads if I forget my pwd http://weyume.com/2011/04/05/passfirmations/ …    
    
    
    Dont watch unless you want to break out into a spontaneous "There beneath the blue suburban skies...' all day.... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7sCeyqDPViE&feature=share …    
    
    
    Space 1st : Australians (duh!) perfect beer in space  http://media.smh.com.au/technology/tech-talk/an-aussie-space-first-beer-2293426.html    
    
    
    I feel very sanctimoneous tuning up my bike and riding in the sunny fresh air to the Granville Island market! Harumph!    
    
    
    Er, sanctimonious.  http://yfrog.com/h4tdrfuj    
    
    
    @Rove1974 We are all happy you're here to remind us and you are happy too!! Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    knee deep in flash, why does vacuuming the house sound like more fun?    
    
    
    Who wants to play Mad Men season 4 -  I'll start.  SCDP gets a new client...IBM ?!    
    
    
    Saw #Limitless yesterday. Loved the cinematography, liked the story and ideas.   Made me think, after.  Sign of a good film!!    
    
    
    FBI memo alleges aliens did in fact land in New Mexico http://yhoo.it/dPsVHR    New Mexico, been there... some of us managed to escape.    
    
    
    This is Monday on the northwest coast ... http://pic.gd/a5ed0d    
    
    
    Brilliant...except for the decapitated zombie bodies. Yikes! @simonblackwell Extraordinarily detailed .. of St Paul's.: http://bit.ly/dZwsbW    
    
    
    Getting very loud outside Rogers Arena! Peut-être la discussion political en français est terminée ?    
    
    
    Vancouverites must've been moved by French language Canadian Federal #elxn41 Debate last night!  They were shouting & cheering all night!    
    
    
    Vancouver fashion: rubber pancho, leggings, booties, dinosaur tuque, hoop earrings, plunger coffee mug. http://pic.gd/31ce85    
    
    
    Watching the snow fall, from bed, with a nice hot coffee!! Its good to be home! http://yfrog.com/75uyywj    
    
    
    "We all travel the Milky Way together, trees and men." 
— John Muir (The Mountains of California)    
    
    
    What a beautiful day. It's as iif someone cut a hole in the clouds over False Creeck to let the sun in. Thank you.    
    
    
    Oh Vancouver! I picker the wrong day for a quick errand to Granville St....it was BLAZZIN! Contact high!    
    
    
    Property rights for Animals:  http://www.smh.com.au/environment/animals/give-animals-property-rights-uni-lecturer-20110422-1dr79.html#poll … "Why would somebody give animals more rights than humans?" Yet we do to corporations!    
    
    
    Another winner, thanks to @tripadvisor. Burger 55, Penticton. Yum!  http://yfrog.com/h3cu6swj   http://yfrog.com/h31egxyj    
    
    
    Chaser's Letter To The Queen http://www.smh.com.au/lifestyle/royal-wedding/abc-not-amused-as-royals-ban-chaser-threaten-coverage-20110427-1dwyd.html …  Royals demand ABC cancel the Chaser, as #royalwedding commentators, or lose video feeds..    
    
    
    Nice window display at BlackberryBooks Granville Island. www poetryIsDead.ca  http://yfrog.com/hsushdvj    
    
    
    10 years later, two wars ongoing, $900US billion spent, 6000 soldiers died, 42,000 soldiers injured. Iraqi Refugees + 2.1 mil. @BarackObama    
    
    
    digitally freshen up : A term used to excuse oneself from face-time company for reasons of a burning desire to check email & social media.    
    
    
    digitally freshen up : or...update one's avatar because #MadMen season 5 is not available till early 2012!    
    
    
    Paul is reading my copy of Superman #900...I'm trying to hold back the spoilers. What a couple of nerds.    
    
    
    Good weeks work...its Finally Friday! yeah!  If only the weather would cooperate and supply some Sun day.    
    
    
    Neurowear: "Just imagine if we have organs that doesn’t exist, moreover we can control that new body?" http://neurowear.net/?p=81  #ThankYou Japan!    
    
    
    Okay, torrential rain and hail now in #Vancouver. When the going gets tough, we go 10-pin #bowling !! http://yfrog.com/gzoq4dkj    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle you are so on! Hope you enjoyed your first #DOXA2011 
Might go on Thursday.    
    
    
    @CWWRyan @photoclassic Pair of Golden Eagles are resident at the Museum of Anthropology at the University of BC in Vancouver. Just saw one.    
    
    
    @DamonLindelof Right on Vancouver!    
    
    
    A bit wet at Granville Island. Not fit for man or gull. Still #oyamasausage still a draw, worth the soggy visit. http://yfrog.com/gytzpyej    
    
    
    Signs of spring  ... False Creek Canada Geese (Branta canadensis) and goslings Too Cute! http://hpstm.tc/p/gg2d #hipstamatic    
    
    
    Did you guys see the new Torchwood trailer? Hooray!  http://bit.ly/lJpz3g    
    
    
    @ShannonLaBelle take/post pictures if you can. Would love to see them. I bet you even got sun in #halifax , lucky you.    
    
    
    I'll be on the Tonight Show with @jayleno tonight, along with @ParisHilton and INXS.  http://yfrog.com/h65vzfcj    
    
    
    I sound like those people who move near an airport...I know it's the Stanley Cup and all, but will the masses outside Roger's Arena...sshhh.    
    
    
    Consider honey http://gu.com/p/2pe6x/tw  Nice article in the @guardian The simplest resources are the best. Clean air, water, and bees.    
    
    
    Yeah! The Official STAR TREK Convention: 45th Anniversary in VANCOUVER, BC. June 10-12  http://www.creationent.com/cal/stvan.htm#events … Don't miss the Klingon Breakfast    
    
    
    Saw a group of women wearing hockey jerseys, with baby strollers outside Rogers Arena. You know what they were don't you? Mother Canuckers    
    
    
    Finally watched #Firefly sci-fi series from Joss Whedon via #Netfix.  Enjoyed the originality of the story  and the world.  Joss rocks!!    
    
    
    I think I saw Liza Minelli on the 44 Express bus this morning. Yes?    
    
    
    Information / Futurist consorts, watch & enjoy #Mailer & #McLuhan Debate the Electronic Age 1968 http://shar.es/HYPJr  #Digital @thomgillespie    
    
    
    Lots of people are asking whether Peep Show is coming back. It is! Series 7 will be filmed later this year & transmitted, well, even later.    
    
    
    Can photo albums survive the digital age? http://gu.com/p/2qp55/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    And so it begins #Vancouver. Good luck to all #stanleycup #Canucks  Just hope everyone gets home healthy, esp the players!,    
    
    
    Yeah Hockey is over. now everyone please go home, quietly and quickly. See you in a few weeks when the hockey starts up again.    
    
    
    It's getting dark in the car park. Might go to the room. Oh God. http://yfrog.com/kit9ldqj     
    
    
    Indeed. #Vancouver  http://hpstm.tc/p/kwss #hipstamatic    
    
    
    Walked across our beautiful downtown #vancouver today. Not a single #Canucks jersey in sight. They cant use them to hide behind anymore.    
    
    
    There is nothing but the journey. #VadeMecum    
    
    
    Interesting. Carrying written tweets by train from San Fran to D.C., route of the 1st transcontinental telegram (1861) http://creativetime.org/programs/archive/2011/tweets/?p=118 …    
    
    
    British Library & Google 'There is no doubt that #digitization will greatly benefit the research process.'  http://gu.com/p/3v2j7/tw . 150m works    
    
    
    Sense-Roid jacket lets you cuddle yourself (Wired UK) http://www.wired.co.uk/news/archive/2011-06/22/sense-roid-self-hugging-jacket …. the ideal haptic communication partner..Domo arigato Japan!    
    
    
    Have you seen a foreign film with an American villain (pref. played by Yank actor) in the last 10 years? Drop me a line, I'm making a list.    
    
    
    Is it fair to make an interview candidate wait 15 minutes?    
    
    
    Wishing everyone a happy and fun Canada Day!!  http://yfrog.com/hs6jqdkej from Steveston.    
    
    
    Had A Glorious Morning Hike In Whistler. So Green And Quiet, With The Sweet Smells Of Earth.  http://hpstm.tc/p/pj2x    
    
    
    Re: Cemetery Discovery Day @ShannonLaBelle "Why not bring a picnic." Really?! That's a find.    
    
    
    If only my iphone could take a picture of itself, watching Mad Max on the iphone. Does it get any better?...sweet!!!!    
    
    
    Don't write off the Goose till you see the box going into the hole.    
    
    
    Excellent talk by MIT's Sherry Turkle who spent 15 years exploring our lives on the #digitalterrain. Alone Together: http://bit.ly/ngw84H     
    
    
    Awesome iPhoto pic of last Space Shuttle Launch Captured from an Airplane Window Seat by 18 yr old http://www.petapixel.com/2011/07/08/last-space-shuttle-launch-captured-from-an-airplane-window-seat/ … via @petapixel #NASA    
    
    
    Nous finissons par faire de la vitesse elle-même le symbole de l'innovation?  Paul #Virilio vitesse ARTE: http://www.arte.tv/fr/2151166,CmC=2395272.html#.Th3G0ihu9ik.tweet … #Digitization    
    
    
    Speaking of digitization, new from Digitalism - Forrest Gump http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JT5gotTnoDg&feature=share … via @youtube  schön schön wunderbar! @digitalismMusic    
    
    
    slideshow Community Supported Fishery (CSF ) trip Nass River BC,  canneries & Alert Bay http://flic.kr/s/aHsjvjLSry  http://www.wildbcsalmon.org  @ocean_wise    
    
    
    Enjoying the rain at #Vancouver West End Farmers Market.  #bummersummer cant keep this beautiful produce away  http://yfrog.com/khcn6yjj    
    
    
    IN SHOCK: just got off phone call with my technophobe 86 year old mother who informs me she is about to buy an #iPad    
    
    
    "And so the beauty of lilies falls on angels and men, bears and squirrels, wolves and sheep, birds and bees.." John Muir    
    
    
    Sipping a Granville Island IPA, after the 1.5 hr long customs inspection. I bet Donald Sutherland didnt have to wait. He's very tall!    
    
    
    Just installed the new #apple #OSX. I'm really not sure why they thought reversing my mouse wheel direction would be a good idea.    
    
    
    It's pouring rain, and sunny with patches of blue sky in #Vancouver. Some more words for 'rain' are needed. Its prainshining   #bummersummer    
    
    
    What's your fave LIVING female SF writer (besides Le Guin)? Somebody's looking for them... help...    
    
    
    So long #AmyWinehouse  Such an amazing voice, a true jazz - worthy style. But such a mess. Drugs suck.    
    
    
    Clean fresh air. I love Vancouver!    
    
    
    Orions Reflection, where new stars are forming inside the dense nebula.  So beautiful  http://on.natgeo.com/nd1AGy  via @NatGeo    
    
    
    