Alzheimer's Resource Center and Lifestyle Trends for Seniors http://ow.ly/7BSmo     
    
    
    How to deal with the challenges of vision loss among elders: http://ow.ly/7BSQ6     
    
    
    Is Hospice Only for the Dying? Find out here: http://ow.ly/7BRQt     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: Dealing with an Uncooperative Doctor http://ow.ly/7HrNh     
    
    
    Live radio show at 2 PM EST today - "What Caregivers Can and Can't ask their Physicians" http://ow.ly/7Ir9T     
    
    
    Driving Safety Tips and Car Modifications for Seniors and Caregivers http://nblo.gs/qKVwH     
    
    
    Live radio show in 15 minutes - "What Caregivers Can and Can't ask their Physicians" http://ow.ly/7IrfG  #caregiving #eldercare    
    
    
    LIVE NOW - radio show - "What Caregivers Can and Can't Ask Their Physicians"- http://ow.ly/7IrkV     
    
    
    Did you miss yesterday's radio show, "What Physicians Can and Can't Ask their Physicians"? Catch it here: http://ow.ly/7JXiv     
    
    
    Be prepared for emergencies by collecting and organizing vital documentation now, to avoid scrambling around later. http://ow.ly/7KiR1     
    
    
    New video show available on-demand now - Dealing with Caregiver Denial about a Senior's Condition: http://ow.ly/7LDoU     
    
    
    Are you stalled from caregiver burnout? You're not alone...http://ow.ly/7KjOG    
    
    
    Breast cancer drug no longer approved by Food and Drug Administration http://nblo.gs/qVf5I     
    
    
    Steps for Getting Hospice Care for Your Loved One http://ow.ly/7Kk7J     
    
    
    How to Find QUALITY Respite Care for Caregivers http://ow.ly/7KiVO     
    
    
    Fitness Programs and Exercises to Improve Physical Performance of Seniors - and help their caregivers! http://ow.ly/7Kj66     
    
    
    Webinar's are always available on-demand from eCareDiary. Check them out here: http://ow.ly/7Kkgy     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: Oral Care for Seniors with Arthritis Check it out! http://ow.ly/7OXtX     
    
    
    Home for the Holidays: A Status Check for Elderly Relatives http://nblo.gs/r5kvj     
    
    
    Join eCareDiary today at 2 PM EST for our live radio show! "Spirituality in Caregiving" http://ow.ly/7Qfpb     
    
    
    Live now! - Radio Show: "Spirituality in Caregiving" http://ow.ly/7Qftk  Check it out!    
    
    
    What does Healthcare Reform mean for you? Find out here: http://ow.ly/7RNEa  #caregiving #healthcare    
    
    
    Nutrition for Long Term Care and Wellness:http://ow.ly/7ROEX     
    
    
    juicy couture outlet store online http://nblo.gs/reX8r     
    
    
    juicy couture outlet store online http://nblo.gs/reX8t     
    
    
    juicy couture outlet store online http://nblo.gs/reX8s     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: Protecting Your Parents' Assets - http://ow.ly/7TgsK     
    
    
    Dementia is NOT a lighter version of Alzheimer's. Learn more here...http://ow.ly/7RPzt    
    
    
    Many services required to support aging in place are NOT covered by Medicare. Learn how to make home care more affordable here:...    
    
    
        
    
    
    Learn about traditional healing exercises that raise awareness of energetic anatomy and maximize its power for health and vitality......    
    
    
    Key Skills Every Caregiver Needs: Tips from Top Doctors! http://nblo.gs/rqr97     
    
    
    Live at 2 PM EST - Radio Show - "Massage Therapy for the Geriatric Population" http://ow.ly/7Xlyk     
    
    
    Live in 15 mins! - Radio Show - "Massage Therapy for the Geriatric Population" http://ow.ly/7XlAe     
    
    
    Live NOW! - Radio Show - "Massage Therapy for the Geriatric Population" http://ow.ly/7XlBJ     
    
    
    Did you miss yesterday's radio show, "Massage Therapy for the Geriatric Population"? Catch it here: http://ow.ly/7YyGl     
    
    
    Aging is a scary thing for many people, but it doesn't need to be faced alone. Learn how to ease the fear of growing older here:...    
    
    
    Your caregiving support group should consist of many different people you can trust and depend on....learn more...http://ow.ly/7YyQw    
    
    
    Facilitating a Meaningful End-of-Life Experience for a Senior: http://ow.ly/7YySI     
    
    
    Is Hospice Care Possible Without Medicare Coverage? http://ow.ly/82G6N     
    
    
    Don't forget to like eCareDiary on Facebook for daily tips, tricks and eldercare advice! http://ow.ly/7RPK2     
    
    
    Choosing the Right Caregiver for Your Elderly Loved One http://nblo.gs/rKV4C     
    
    
    New video now available on demand: When Your Parent Moves In: Tips for Caregivershttp://ow.ly/84C1M    
    
    
    Live radio show at 2 PM EST - "Being an African-American Caregiver" http://ow.ly/84C9l     
    
    
    Live in 15 minutes! - Radio Show - "Being an African-American Caregiver" http://ow.ly/84CbZ     
    
    
    Live NOW! - Radio Show - "Being an African-American Caregiver" http://ow.ly/84Cel     
    
    
    Did you miss yesterday's radio show, "Being an African-American Caregiver"? Catch it here: http://ow.ly/87c79     
    
    
    Get information about Alzheimer's and take action to boost the quality of your loved one's life here: here: http://ow.ly/87d5w     
    
    
    Learn why an online support group is an important tool for seniors living with Alzheimer's: http://ow.ly/87d9w     
    
    
    'Tis the Season for Safety Gifts for Seniors! http://nblo.gs/s5BSI     
    
    
    Radio show live now! - "The Village Movement: A Unique Concept for Senior Living" http://ow.ly/8aHhZ  Please join us!    
    
    
    Live radio show at 2 pm EST today - "The Village Movement: A Unique Concept for Senior Living" http://ow.ly/8aHhq  Please join us!    
    
    
    Did you miss yesterday's radio show, "The Village Movement: An Innovative Concept for Senior Living"? Catch it here: http://ow.ly/8bFG8     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: "Unhappy with Nursing Home Care?:Steps Caregivers Can Take" http://ow.ly/8dwxx     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: "Are there any Non-Traditional Treatments for Depression?" http://ow.ly/8dwAn     
    
    
    Delaying the Onset of Disability in Older Adults: http://ow.ly/8g5jY     
    
    
    You Can Stay Home! : Modifications for Seniors to Age in Place http://nblo.gs/siOcx     
    
    
    When Your Parent Moves In: Tips for Caregivers http://ow.ly/8g5pE     
    
    
    Home Remodeling Strategies for Aging in Place http://ow.ly/8g5mu     
    
    
        
    
    
    Getting the most from your doctors visit...http://ow.ly/8g5vn    
    
    
    Friday, 1/13 - 11:30 am - Radio Show featuring Polly Whitehorn of eCareDiary. For more information please visit: http://WCWP.org .    
    
    
    Caring Too Much? : Watch Out for Compassion Fatigue! http://nblo.gs/svXrm     
    
    
    Private Home Care Assisted Living http://nblo.gs/swmVC     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: Are visual cues recommended as Dementia memory aides?http://ow.ly/8nGiO     
    
    
    New Expert Q & A: Are Flu Shots Linked with Alzheimer's Disease?http://ow.ly/8uima     
    
    
    Stay Hazard Free this Winter! : Safety Checklist for Seniors http://nblo.gs/sKCzs     
    
    
    Radio Show - 2 PM EST - "Life Care Planning for Family Caregivers" http://ow.ly/8vKRb     
    
    
    Live now! Radio Show - 2 PM EST - "Life Care Planning for Family Caregivers" http://ow.ly/8vKU6     
    
    
    Do You Have a Life Care Plan? http://nblo.gs/sRuJC     
    
    
    New Expert Q&A: Making Caregiving a Family Affairhttp://ow.ly/8Cexf    
    
    
    Accepting the Truth About Our Parents http://nblo.gs/t4wlg     
    
    
    Register for eCareDiary's FREE Webinar: Managing Care Before, During and After a Hospitilizaiton. http://ow.ly/8Cezk     
    
    
        
    
    
    WHAT ARE YOU AFRAID OF? : Making Caregiving Changes in the New Year http://nblo.gs/tlw1I     
    
    
    I'm broadcasting live at 2pm! Why does mom or dad need physical therapy? http://tobtr.com/s/2746651 . #BlogTalkRadio    
    
    
    Thank you VibrantNation for listing eCareDiary in your tools for long distance caregivers! http://bit.ly/w6bTkN     
    
    
    Bridge the Communication Gap with an Elder with Alzheimer's! http://nblo.gs/tD39n     
    
    
    The New York Times calls The Green House Project “the most comprehensive effort to reinvent the nursing home” http://nyti.ms/vbqYL4     
    
    
    What if we could create nursing homes that feel like home?  Tune in now!  http://bit.ly/xFsY1Q     
    
    
    If you missed it, don't worry, we recorded it. Learn about The Green House Project movement. http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    The ways in which popular culture portrays aging seem worth paying attention to. Have you seen The Iron Lady? http://ow.ly/8ZXGn     
    
    
    Thank you Retirement Education Plus for writing about eCareDiary as a way for families to stay connected and organized!...    
    
    
    Planning Your Caregiving Needs: Get Started Soon! http://nblo.gs/tURGq     
    
    
    Dementia Care - Bathing Without A Battle - Tune In Now!  http://bit.ly/AxRh9e     
    
    
    If you missed it on Tuesday, listen to the recording! Dementia Care - Bathing Without a Battle. http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    Five Musts When Your Elderly Loved One Leaves The Hospital http://nblo.gs/ubQ1l     
    
    
    Is It Possible to Be a Long Distance Caregiver? http://bit.ly/z2QjtH     
    
    
    Is It Possible to Be a Long Distance Caregiver?  Tune in NOW!  http://bit.ly/z2QjtH     
    
    
        
    
    
    Take Control of Caregiving: The Care Diary Tool is Here to Help!   http://bit.ly/wJBxC5     
    
    
    If you are a long distance caregiver or know someone who is... http://bit.ly/xoANol     
    
    
    eCareDiary - The Future of Caregiving for Seniors - http://bit.ly/wJBxC5     
    
    
    Are Falls One of the Main Causes of Hip Fractures Among Seniors? http://nblo.gs/utPFT     
    
    
    A Physician Training Program That Focuses on Empowering Caregivers?  Join the discussion - http://bit.ly/AgXECa     
    
    
    Are Falls One of the Main Causes of Hip Fractures Among Seniors? http://nblo.gs/utToG     
    
    
    If you had the opportunity to train a medical student on how to be a better physician, what would you tell them? #docTraining    
    
    
    What questions do you have about how today's physicians are being prepared to interact with patients and caregivers? #docTraining    
    
    
    Training Physicians for the 21st Century and What That Means for Caregivers and Their
Families. Tune In Now! http://bit.ly/AgXECa     
    
    
    How UCF's physician training program will empower caregivers.  http://bit.ly/zIE5S9     
    
    
    Why Person-Centered Care Matters http://nblo.gs/uM7Yx     
    
    
    Journeying from Heartbreak to Hope: Guidelines for Caregivers  http://bit.ly/xUIrso     
    
    
    Journeying from Heartbreak to Hope: Guidelines for Caregivers.  Tune in Now! http://bit.ly/xUIrso     
    
    
    Journeying from Heartbreak to Hope: Guidelines for Caregivers, with Dietrich Stroeh was very powerful. http://bit.ly/zbllGz     
    
    
    @kimlinder Thank you!    
    
    
    @AgingAbundantly Thank you for the RT!    
    
    
    Exercise inspiration for caregivers http://bit.ly/zoaaA7  #caregivers #caregiving    
    
    
    Reconnecting with Siblings to Create a Care Team for Aging Parents http://bit.ly/AejQuw     
    
    
    Help Your Elderly Parent Retire from Driving http://bit.ly/wMU2k5     
    
    
    Are Your Parents Hiding Their Health Problems From You? http://nblo.gs/v4vvF     
    
    
    Reconnecting with Siblings to Create a Care Team for Aging Parents.  Join us on Tuesday - http://bit.ly/AejQuw     
    
    
    Reconnecting with Siblings to Create a Care Team for Aging Parents - Tune In Now! http://bit.ly/AejQuw     
    
    
    Reconnecting with Siblings to Create a Care Team for Aging Parents was excellent! You can listen at http://bit.ly/zbllGz     
    
    
    Are there More People with Alzheimer's Now than Ever Before? Thursday, March 15th at 1:00PM EST -  http://bit.ly/AlfagA     
    
    
    Medication List now online http://nblo.gs/vcXCB     
    
    
    Are there More People with Alzheimer's Now than Ever Before? Tune in Now! - http://bit.ly/AlfagA     
    
    
    Author Cathie Borrie on Dealing with the Reality of Alzheimer's - http://bit.ly/zaG820     
    
    
    Are Nursing Homes Really the Best Option for Our Loved Ones? - Perception & Reality http://bit.ly/zfjU4W     
    
    
    Applying the "Just Do It" Philosophy to Caregiving http://nblo.gs/vlNYM     
    
    
    This is my first post http://nblo.gs/vn0XE     
    
    
    Are Nursing Homes Really the Best Option for Our Loved Ones? Tune In Now - http://bit.ly/zfjU4W     
    
    
    Seeing Alzheimer's Differently: A New Approach to Care. Join us on Thursday, March 22nd at 1:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/gKKAke     
    
    
    Are Nursing Homes Really the Best Option for Our Loved Ones? - Perception & Reality
http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    The imagery of illness and dying through the power of photography - http://bit.ly/GRnOgB     
    
    
    Five Keys to Preventing Osteopathic Fractures http://nblo.gs/vD7yb     
    
    
    When a Loved One is Diagnosed with Cancer:  Tips for Caregivers. Join us on Tuesday, March 27th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/GSoz4A     
    
    
    eCareDiary to Present at 2012 Aging in America Conference http://nblo.gs/vDFQy     
    
    
    eCareDiary to Present at 2012 Aging in America Conference in Washington, DC on Saturday, March 31st - http://bit.ly/GSVrvx     
    
    
    When a Loved One is Diagnosed with Cancer:  Tips for Caregivers - Tune In Now http://bit.ly/GSoz4A     
    
    
    eCareDiary to Lead Workshop on Tools and Technology for Caregivers at the 2012 Aging in America Conference http://bit.ly/GXm0VK     
    
    
    How Caregivers Can Prevent Burnout and Build Resilience. Join us on Tuesday, April 3rd at 2:00PM EST - http://bit.ly/HeVPmJ     
    
    
    Caring for Your Aging Parents Causing Family Disputes? http://nblo.gs/vViAq     
    
    
    How Caregivers Can Prevent Burnout and Build Resilience - Tune In Now!  http://bit.ly/HeVPmJ     
    
    
    How Caregivers Can Prevent Burnout and Build Resilience - Check out Tuesday's show!
http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    Why is Mom's Dementia Worse in the Evenings? http://nblo.gs/wcaxm     
    
    
    What Families Can Do to Prepare for Their Elder Years - Join us on Tuesday, April 10th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/HSw8IX     
    
    
    What Families Can Do to Prepare for Their Elder Years - Tune in Now! http://bit.ly/HSw8IX     
    
    
    Faye Levow will help you and your family get out denial and start preparing for your elder years in advance. http://bit.ly/IuFsse     
    
    
    Why is My Balance Worsening? http://nblo.gs/wtH66     
    
    
    Senior Living Interior Designs for Health Care and Assisted Living Facilities- Tuesday, April 17th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/Ir3iC8     
    
    
    Senior Living Interior Designs for Health Care and Assisted Living Facilities, is now available on-demand.
http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    Making Your Parent's Move to a Care Community Guilt-Free http://nblo.gs/wM87S     
    
    
    Isn't it Time Hospitals Manage Patient Care Coordination? Join us on Tuesday, April 24th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/aihP6W     
    
    
    Strategies for Uniting Families: Tools and Technology to Help Family Caregivers - Join us 4/26 at 1:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/I59qPl     
    
    
    Montessori Learning Programs for Seniors with Dementia - Join us on Tuesday, May 1st at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/JlA99G     
    
    
    Don't Fall into the Guilt Trap! - 3 Tips for Caregivers http://nblo.gs/x41UG     
    
    
    Montessori Learning Programs for Seniors with Dementia - Click this link to tune in now - http://bit.ly/JlA99G     
    
    
    Yesterday's radio show featuring Dr. John Zeisel was excellent! It's available on demand now - http://bit.ly/ImHV56     
    
    
    eCareDiary to Broadcast First Live Online Support Group for Family Caregivers, "Caregivers Speak!" http://nblo.gs/x9An8     
    
    
    CAREGIVERS SPEAK! http://eCareDiary.com  introduces the first LIVE online support group created by and for caregivers. http://bit.ly/K5nBGA     
    
    
    eCareDiary is now available through Robert Lee Care Center. http://www.robertleecarecenter.com/     
    
    
    Aging at Home? Tips for Preventing Injuries and Isolation http://nblo.gs/xl9fw     
    
    
    http://eCareDiary.com  introduces the first LIVE online support group created by and for caregivers Caregivers Speak! http://bit.ly/K5nBGA     
    
    
    CAREGIVERS SPEAK! - the first LIVE online support group created by and for caregivers, will air today at 2:00PM EST - http://bit.ly/K5nBGA     
    
    
    Tune in Now for Caregivers Speak! - http://bit.ly/K5nBGA     
    
    
    CAREGIVERS SPEAK! was a great success.  It's now available on demand. Check it out! http://bit.ly/LcL1u9     
    
    
    Dance and Meditate Your Way to Better Balance! http://nblo.gs/xCSyH     
    
    
    The ABCs of Recovery from Mental Illness - Join us on Tuesday, May 15th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/LJNhJK     
    
    
    Creative Arts Programs for Older Adults-Join us on Tuesday, May 22nd at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/KdTIFe     
    
    
    Why Do I Feel This Way? Caregiver Tips for Handling Irrational Feelings http://nblo.gs/xUKVJ     
    
    
    Today's Empowering Caregivers Radio Show is all about creative arts programs for older adults.  Join as at 2:00 EST- http://bit.ly/KdTIFe     
    
    
    Taking Medications Safely http://nblo.gs/xXdkg     
    
    
    Yesterday's radio show, Creative Arts Programs for Older Adults is now on demand. Click the link to listen- http://bit.ly/KfLyMa     
    
    
    How Does a Caregiver's Role Change when Dealing with Addictions? Join us on Tuesday, May 29th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/KLabCF     
    
    
    Being an Advocate, NOT an Annoyance for Your Loved One! http://nblo.gs/y8vrI     
    
    
    Cinderella Shoes just by Christian Louboutin Can change Mothers and dads Inside Princesses. http://nblo.gs/ybT3y     
    
    
    Real estate Web site Red Bottoms Boots or shoes. http://nblo.gs/ybT3x     
    
    
    FREE Webinar- Can't You Make it Stop? A Positive Approach to Dementia Communication and Behaviors. Today at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/KNL1iV     
    
    
    Can't You Make it Stop? A Positive Approach to Dementia Communication and Behaviors - available now on-demand  http://bit.ly/M7GISc     
    
    
    CAREGIVERS SPEAK! Join us on Tuesday, June 5th at 2:00PM EST.  Click here to listen live - http://bit.ly/KlMRss     
    
    
    The Aging Eye: Preventative Strategies to Combat Visual Loss http://nblo.gs/ym0Gj     
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! How Caregivers Can Break Through Negativity. Join us at 2:00 PM EST. Click here to listen live - http://bit.ly/KlMRss     
    
    
    Why Does Grandma Wander? - Understanding Coping Mechanisms of Seniors with Dementia http://nblo.gs/yCOam     
    
    
    Communicating with Your Healthcare Team: Tips for High Impact Interactions!  Join us Today, June 12th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/L2L4MG     
    
    
    Read Aloud Books for Memory Challenged Adults - Check out the video interview here - http://bit.ly/K7HD1x     
    
    
    Learning to Speak the Language of Dementia. Join us on Tuesday, June 19th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/LrxylW     
    
    
    Know Your Rights! - The Low-Down on Medicare's Coverage of Hospital Stays http://nblo.gs/yU5BP     
    
    
    Learning to Speak the Language of Dementia is now available on-demand on eCareDiary. Click the link to check it out- http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    Nation-Wide Adult and Senior Services Offered by Easter Seals.  Join us on Tuesday, June 26th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/Kz8mJh     
    
    
    FREE Webinar - Healing in Place: How Technology Can Come to the Rescue of Caregivers! Thursday, June 28th at 2:00PM.  http://bit.ly/MraOAN     
    
    
    Oprah's OWN network is looking for Caregivers to be part of a show on caring for elderly parents - http://bit.ly/Kxt9NP     
    
    
    FREE Webinar - Healing in Place: How Technology Can Come to the Rescue of Caregivers! Thursday, 6/28 at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/MraOAN     
    
    
    Nation-Wide Adult and Senior Services Offered by Easter Seals- Join us on Tuesday, June 26th at 2:00PM EST.
http://bit.ly/Kz8mJh     
    
    
    Maintaining the Dignity of Your Care Partner - Even in the Worst Circumstances http://nblo.gs/zblVs     
    
    
    Nation-Wide Adult and Senior Services Offered by Easter Seals is now available on-demand - http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    FREE Webinar - Healing in Place: How Technology Can Come to the Rescue of Caregivers! Thursday, 6/28 at 2:00PM EST http://bit.ly/MraOAN     
    
    
    Healthcare Reform is Constitutional: What's it Mean for You! http://nblo.gs/zsasP     
    
    
    Smart Cooking Strategies to Improve Senior Well-Being - Join us on Tuesday, July 3rd at 2:00PM EST - http://bit.ly/N44PSo     
    
    
    Smart Cooking Strategies to Improve Senior Well-Being - Log in now to listen live! http://bit.ly/N44PSo  #CookingSeniors    
    
    
    FREE Webinar - Healing in Place: How Technology Can Come to the Rescue of Caregivers! Now available on-demand http://bit.ly/LTjRLj     
    
    
    Find great advice and support for caregivers at http://eCareDiary.com  #caregiving http://bit.ly/NcO9rT     
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! The first http://bit.ly/PqD9uU  LIVE online support group created by and for #caregivers http://bit.ly/PqD9uU     
    
    
    Stay Active, Stay Mobile: The Secret to Senior Independence http://nblo.gs/zHb35     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! online support group meets today at 2:00 PM EST. #caregiver http://bit.ly/PqD9uU     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Maintaining the Dignity of Your Care Partners- now available on-demand http://bit.ly/L8DLho     
    
    
    Protect Your Loved Ones from Online Counterfeit Drugs! http://nblo.gs/zVwrl     
    
    
    #Caregiving in Hispanic Families: A Cultural Perspective.  Join us on Tuesday, July 17th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/M2N5rl     
    
    
    #Caregiving in Hispanic Families: A Cultural Perspective. Join us today at 2:00 PM! http://bit.ly/M2N5rl     
    
    
    #Caregiving in Hispanic Families: A Cultural Perspective is now available on-demand. http://bit.ly/pDW6SI     
    
    
    eCareDiary is now on google+.  Check out our page and follow us! http://bit.ly/MMnwHU     
    
    
    How Walkers Can Empower Seniors http://nblo.gs/AcbtA     
    
    
    Lifelines to Win Against Caner. Join us on Tuesday, July 24th at 2:00PM EST.  http://bit.ly/Pqqwhs     
    
    
    Lifelines to Win Against Cancer.  Join us on Today, July 24th at 2:00PM EST.  http://bit.ly/Pqqwhs     
    
    
    Lifelines to Win Against Cancer with Joni Aldrich now available on demand - http://bit.ly/OpMC0H     
    
    
    Building a Network of Professional and Volunteers Serving Older Adults. Join us 7/31 at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/PQR8rZ  #caregiving    
    
    
    Status of Adelma http://nblo.gs/Alv08     
    
    
    Are Your Pills Causing Spills? : Managing Senior Medication http://nblo.gs/Aqn7j     
    
    
    Building a Network of Professional and Volunteers Serving Older Adults.  Join us on Tuesday, July 31st at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/PQR8rZ     
    
    
    Building a Network of Professional and Volunteers Serving Older Adults- Listen Live Now http://tobtr.com/s/3421599 . #Caregiving    
    
    
        
    
    
    Put a smile on your face :-) Learn about the "Health Benefits of Laughter" #caregivers http://bit.ly/OJsicT     
    
    
    How Holistic Medicine Can Help in Better Health Management. Join us on Tuesday, August 7th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/Ne164h  #caregivers    
    
    
    Maintaing Your Personal Dignity in the Face of Adversity http://nblo.gs/AGNay     
    
    
    How Holistic Medicine Can Help in Better Health Management. Now available on-demand http://bit.ly/O6xTJ4  #caregiving    
    
    
    5 Tips for Managing Your Prescription Drugs from http://grandparents.com  http://bit.ly/ONz1QK     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Maintaining Your Personal Dignity While Caregiving 7/14/12 at 2:00PM EST http://bit.ly/MkLEWl     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Maintaining Your Personal Dignity While #Caregiving. Join us today at 2:00PM EST http://bit.ly/MkLEWl     
    
    
    Maintaining Your Personal Dignity While Caregiving-  Listen in now at http://tobtr.com/s/3522885  #Caregivers Speak!    
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Maintaining Your Personal Dignity While Caregiving. Listen in now at http://tobtr.com/s/3522885     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Maintaining Your Personal Dignity While Caregiving.  Now available on-demand http://bit.ly/Mxkmfs  #caregiving    
    
    
    Movie ideas for the weekend from http://grandparents.com  http://bit.ly/NiL9Kq     
    
    
    Check out the New York Times' New Old Age blog http://bit.ly/N5wntX  - Jane Gross will be on our show Tuesday! http://bit.ly/N5wntX     
    
    
    Lessons in Caring for Your Aging Parent and Yourself. Join us on Tuesday, August 21st at 2:00PM EST http://bit.ly/N5wntX  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Lessons in Caring for Your Aging Parent and Yourself with Jane Gross -  tune in now! http://bit.ly/N5wntX  #caregiving    
    
    
    Lessons in Caring for Your Aging Parent and Yourself with jane Gross is now available on-demand. Listen Now! http://bit.ly/OWfWjP     
    
    
    How to be Present with Patients and Loved Ones. Join us on Tuesday, August 28th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/RN8s4i  #Caregiving    
    
    
    How to be Present with Patients and Loved Ones is now available on-demand: http://bit.ly/OKwKHt  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Rewards and Pitfalls of Family #Caregiving.  Join us on Tuesday, September 4th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/NGME2S  #Caregivers    
    
    
    Rewards and Pitfalls of Family #Caregiving with author, Harriet Tramer. Join us on Today at 2:00PM EST.  http://bit.ly/NGME2S     
    
    
    Rewards and Pitfalls of Family #Caregiving with author, Harriet Tramer, is now available on-demand-  http://bit.ly/OkgrjJ     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! Elisabeth Paine's #Caregiving Story. Join us on Tuesday, September 11th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/SxqJ63     
    
    
    Hand Massage Helps Caregivers Manage Challenging Behavior http://nblo.gs/BXrXZ     
    
    
    Tune in now for Caregivers Speak! Elisabeth Paine's Caregiving Story http://bit.ly/SxqJ63     
    
    
    If you missed Elisabeth Paine's #Caregiving Story, it's now on-demand.  Get inspired- http://bit.ly/Oq4XQ2     
    
    
    Harriet Tramer, author of the book, "Rounding the Circle of Love" also has a blog on aging- check it out http://bit.ly/PbXPTO     
    
    
    Care Tools to Prevent Health Crises. Join us on Tuesday, 09/18 at 2:00 PM EDT http://bit.ly/TOI1Lh  #Caregiving #Caregivers    
    
    
    September is World #Alzheimer's Month. Go Purple to End Alzheimer's http://bit.ly/PILDYx     
    
    
    Care Tools to Prevent Health Crises. Join us on Tuesday, September 18th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/TOI1Lh  #Caregiving #Caregiver    
    
    
    Fall Awarness Day: 10 Tips to Prevent Falls http://nblo.gs/CfRVd     
    
    
    Test http://nblo.gs/ChXqF     
    
    
    test 2 http://nblo.gs/ChXqE     
    
    
    Care Tools to Prevent Health Crises with Author Melissa Kahn is live in 10 minutes-  http://bit.ly/TOI1Lh  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Care Tools to Prevent Health Crises with author, Melissa Kahn is now available on-demand- http://bit.ly/NBYRdU  #caregiving    
    
    
    Liz & Ett designs help loved ones maintain dignity & style when facing health challenges http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137736707/ …    
    
    
    Liz & Ett designs help loved ones maintain dignity & style when facing health challenges http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137736788/ …    
    
    
    Enrich Your Caregiving Journey http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137737258/ …    
    
    
    Healing and Wellness through the Arts with Gay Hanna. Join us on Tuesday, September 25th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/QmC4D1     
    
    
    I'm Still Here: A New Philosophy of Alzheimer's Care http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137745543/ …    
    
    
    Today eCareDiary was featured in USA Today and our co-founder, John Mills was quoted! http://bit.ly/PZxPgP  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Elisabeth Paine's Caregiving Story http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137746154/ …    
    
    
    Healing and Wellness through the Arts with Gay Hanna. Join us on Today, September 25th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/QmC4D1     
    
    
    Healing and Wellness through the Arts with Gay Hanna is broadcasting live in 8 minutes.  Listen in now at  http://bit.ly/QmC4D1     
    
    
    Healing and Wellness through the Arts with Gay Hanna is now available on-demand at
http://bit.ly/TwBA0B  #caregiving    
    
    
    eCareDiary Featured in USA Today http://nblo.gs/CIBh3     
    
    
    "OMG! My Parents are Getting OLD!" http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137811734/ …    
    
    
    eCareDiary to Attend Centers for Medicare & Medicaid Services’ Caregiving Conference http://nblo.gs/CQpTJ     
    
    
    15 Ways to Care for Our Aging Parents—and Ourselves. From A Bittersweet Season by Jane Gross http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137841736/ …    
    
    
    Hello #Caregivers!  Be sure to like eCareDiary on Facebook and help us get the word out about our great resources! http://on.fb.me/VovbCU     
    
    
    New Age of Caregiving Symposium 11/6- http://bit.ly/eAQoW2     
    
    
    Just when you think something has beaten you down...you find the strength within you to carry on. http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367137858692/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    How #Caregivers Can Use Storytelling to Bring Family Together. Join us on Tuesday, October 9th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/Wuh5iW     
    
    
    Art Can Be The Best Pill http://nblo.gs/Dbc6Z     
    
    
    Art Can Be The Best Pill http://nblo.gs/DbeWx     
    
    
    Great story on NPR today- When Should Seniors Hang Up The Car Keys? http://n.pr/R5X1CU     
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! How Caregivers Can Use Storytelling to Bring Family Together. Join us today! at 2PM EST - http://bit.ly/Wuh5iW     
    
    
    #Caregivers Speak! How Caregivers Can Use Storytelling to Bring Family Together is now available on-demand- http://bit.ly/Wuh5iW     
    
    
    eCareDiary Launches New Caregiver Message Board and Storytelling Page http://nblo.gs/DhIDJ     
    
    
    eCareDiary launched a new #Caregiver Message Board and Storytelling Page. Check it out! http://bit.ly/RmJ2Jd  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Making New Memories Through Art and Culture. Join us on Tuesday, October 16th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/SVXEzi  #Caregiving    
    
    
    New Hospital Care Transition Test Program Under Way by Affordable Care Act http://nblo.gs/DtWji     
    
    
    Making New Memories Through Art and Culture with Sean Caulfield- Tune in now! http://bit.ly/SVXEzi  #caregiving #alzheimer's    
    
    
    Resources for the #Caregiver Journey.  Join us on Tuesday, October 23rd at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/U33YXA  #Caregiving    
    
    
    Caregiver's Little Book of Hope-- Join us on Tuesday as we chat with the author Karen Truman! http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138004551/ …    
    
    
    eCareDiary was mentioned as a great resource for practical information for #caregivers by The Social Marketing ExChange http://bit.ly/T5eNqo     
    
    
    Fall-Proofing Ideas for the Bathroom http://nblo.gs/DMZrw     
    
    
        
    
    
    Aging Across America: A Photographic Journey. Join us on Tuesday, October 30th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/Xt4rC7  #caregivers    
    
    
    Today's show, Aging Across America: A Photographic Journey will not air today due to hurricane Sandy.  We will reschedule, stay tuned.    
    
    
    Happy Halloween, Everyone!  Take a walk down memory lane with some vintage candy- http://bit.ly/PH7m9S     
    
    
    Caregivers in the Workplace http://nblo.gs/EeTzJ     
    
    
    The Other Talk-- Join us on Tuesday as we speak with the author Tim Prosch! http://bit.ly/U3tDzW---  http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138171182/ …    
    
    
    It's Time for the Other Big Talk in Life with author Tim Prosch will air live in ten minutes-- http://bit.ly/U3tDzW  #babyboomers    
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's radio show with author Tim Prosch, don't worry!   Listen to it here: http://bit.ly/VSROMZ     
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's radio show with author Tim Prosch, don't worry! Listen to it here: http://bit.ly/VSROMZ     
    
    
    November is Family Caregivers Month!  A statement from the president honoring all of our family caregivers: http://1.usa.gov/Tw1WeP     
    
    
    10 Tips for Family Caregivers http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138200167/ …    
    
    
    Caregivers Speak!  Romance and the Caregiver: Intimacy in Caregiving.  Join us on Tuesday, November 13th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/STAZEk     
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! Romance and the Caregiver: Intimacy in Caregiving.  Join us on Tuesday, November 13th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/STAZEk     
    
    
    Intimacy: A Casualty of Caregiving http://ow.ly/f9T5V...is  it true?    
    
    
    A couple of tips for maintaining intimacy in caregiving: http://ow.ly/f9RD4  #caregiving    
    
    
    Some important information about Medicare enrollment for those affected by Hurricane Sandy: http://ow.ly/f9TUo     
    
    
    Medicare Coverage Change for Therapy Offers Ray of Hope for Caregivers http://ow.ly/f9VWV     
    
    
    Top 5 Qualities to Look for in a Nursing Home http://nblo.gs/EElCE     
    
    
    Join us today for Caregivers Speak! Romance and the Caregiver at 2:00 PM!  RT to invite your friends and colleagues! http://bit.ly/STAZEk     
    
    
    We had an amazing discussion on Caregivers Speak! yesterday.  Listen here: http://ow.ly/fhhDg     
    
    
    From Darkness to Light: Fighting Macular Degeneration in Seniors http://nblo.gs/EIGCV     
    
    
    Happy Family Caregiver's month!  Gary Marshall talks about caring for his mother with Alzheimer's: http://ow.ly/fhke2     
    
    
    Seniors Making Social Networking and Integral Part of Their Lives http://ow.ly/fdetS     
    
    
    Advice for family caregivers-- "Is this my mother?" http://ow.ly/fhm3L     
    
    
    Interesting interview with two individuals living with Alzheimer's http://ow.ly/fdfww     
    
    
    Inside the Dementia Epidemic.  Join us on Tuesday, November 20th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/TK5gmG  #Caregiving    
    
    
    What's a memory cafe?  Where can you find one?  How can you start?  Check out: http://www.thirdageservices.com/MemoryCafe.html     
    
    
    Respecting the Person with Dementia-- DementiaToday http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138291552/ …    
    
    
    Parkinson's Disease Foundation Hosts Expert Seminar for Care Partners http://nblo.gs/EOIHa     
    
    
    @sharpseniors Happy to help get you there!    
    
    
    Managing Caregiver Emotions http://ow.ly/flz89     
    
    
    Family Caregivers provide a unique kind of care.  The Surprising Health Benefit of Being Cared for by Family http://ow.ly/flye8     
    
    
    Why Taking Your Pills Can Stop You from Falling! http://nblo.gs/EVyAn     
    
    
    Communicating with Alzheimer's Patients: Tips for Family Caregivers http://ow.ly/foPqs     
    
    
    For Alzheimer's, Detection Advances Outpace Treatment Options http://ow.ly/foRZm     
    
    
    Inside the Dementia Epidemic radio show with Martha Stettinius is coming up at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/TK5gmG  #Caregiving #Dementia    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday with the author of Inside the Dementia Epidemic Martha Stettinius, listen here: http://ow.ly/fsY3M     
    
    
    Caregiver:  How To Turn Even The Crankiest Medical Personnel Into Buddies http://ow.ly/foSEc     
    
    
    Drug shortages persist in the U.S., Harming Care http://ow.ly/foRAn     
    
    
    Caregiver & Physician Conversations Radio Show.  Join us on Tuesday, November 27th at 2:00PM EST. http://bit.ly/SIz1CM  #Caregiving...    
    
    
    Read up on the  Alzheimer's Neuroimaging Initiative before our show with Dr. Michael Weiner on Tuesday: http://ow.ly/foT02     
    
    
    Th Earliest Indicators of Alzheimer's Disease: 20 Year Before Impairment http://ow.ly/foTTh     
    
    
    In The Begining.......... http://nblo.gs/F6QZC     
    
    
    Webniar this Thursday 2:00 PM EST: Avoiding the Trap of Caregiver Burnout http://ow.ly/fxaUD     
    
    
    Preparing for the holidays: Four-step Holiday Caregiving Checklist http://ow.ly/fxbtU     
    
    
    @HomeHealthTech thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Join us today at 2:00 PM EST as we discuss the Alzheimer's Disease Neuroimaging Initiative http://bit.ly/SIz1CM  #caregiving #alzheimers    
    
    
    Call Me Maybe:  Grandparents Day Edition http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138401765/ …    
    
    
    Definitely some things for caregivers to keep in mind...http://ow.ly/fDNFs     
    
    
    Join us tomorrow for our webinar at 2:00 PM EST:  Avoiding the Trap of Caregiver Burnout http://ow.ly/fxaUD     
    
    
    Practical Spirituality to Overcome Caregiving Challenges.  Join us on Tuesday, December 4th at 2:00PM EST. http://ow.ly/fGxTs ...    
    
    
    Rides for Apts http://nblo.gs/FoDnL     
    
    
    Rides for Apts http://nblo.gs/FoDnK     
    
    
    @taozen1121 Thanks for spreading the word!    
    
    
    A Caregiver's Spiritual Needs http://ow.ly/fJk27     
    
    
    Meaning, Purpose, and Caregiving: Spirituality and Religion's Role in Caregiving http://ow.ly/fJk6t     
    
    
    5 Health Benefits of Getting Older' to brighten your Saturday morning: http://ow.ly/fJks5     
    
    
    Really interesting article:  In Alzheimer's Disease, Maintaining connection and 'Saving Face' http://ow.ly/fJkKC     
    
    
    Last month's top ten most read #caregiving articles: http://ow.ly/fLLEW     
    
    
    eCareDiary Expert, Margery Pabst Launches New Caregiving Book, "Words of Care"! http://nblo.gs/FtToU     
    
    
    Join us at 2:00 PM EST today for Practical Spirituality to Overcome Caregiving Challenges http://ow.ly/fGxTs     
    
    
    If you missed our show Practical Spirituality to Overcome Caregiving Challenges yesterday, it's here! http://ow.ly/fQmFK     
    
    
    "Words of Care"--quick bites of information and affirmation for the busy caregiver. http://ow.ly/fQcrH     
    
    
    Addressing Questions Caregivers are Always Afraid to Ask.  Join us December 11th at 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/fSiw1  #caregiving...    
    
    
    Where and how to buy good quality cheap name brand clothes? http://nblo.gs/FEbHF     
    
    
    Find ways to be better prepared when your life's focus changes: 12 FAQs About Caregiving http://ow.ly/fUf3H     
    
    
    Questions and answers for long-distance caregivers...http://ow.ly/fUg5A     
    
    
    Submit your questions for AARP President Rob Romasco. 'Important Family Conversations' live chat this Thurs @ 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/fUgI3     
    
    
    Foods and Medications That Don't Mix http://ow.ly/fUi8M     
    
    
    Caregiving Strategies to Keep the Holiday Cheer http://ow.ly/fUniP     
    
    
    Recognizing Dementia When it Strikes! http://nblo.gs/FLUZy     
    
    
    @bstarcareeville thanks!  glad you're finding it interesting!    
    
    
    Today's radio show: Addressing Questions Caregivers are Always Afraid to Ask. Join us at 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/fSiw1  #caregiving    
    
    
    Check out yesterday's radio show addressing the questions caregiver's are afraid to ask: http://ow.ly/g2wa0  #caregiving    
    
    
    Moving Beyond the Leakages: Practical Strategies to Manage Incontinence via @CaregiverAlly Webinar tomorrow @ 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/g1aKj !    
    
    
    Family Caregiver Alliance Announces Webinar on Managing Incontinence among Seniors http://nblo.gs/FSFfj     
    
    
    a touching story about coping with loss this holiday season: http://ow.ly/g2wWf  via @ALZHEIMERSread    
    
    
    Caregiving Expert Margery Pabst Speaks about her New Book, "Words or Care". Join us December 18th at 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/g4e2C ...    
    
    
    Besse Cooper: A 116-Year-Old's Secrets for Longevity http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138546950/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Ultimate Grandparents Guide to Celebrating Chanukah (for the last few days, at least!) http://ow.ly/g6voX     
    
    
    Thoughts for caregivers to keep in mind: Spiritual Needs of the Dying http://ow.ly/g6v2c     
    
    
    @Caregiving_OW thanks for spreading the word!    
    
    
    A Caregiver's Recipe : Keep it Simple During the Holidays http://nblo.gs/G3TTd     
    
    
    very interesting article about caring for loved ones with Alzheimer's: http://ow.ly/g9Q8O  via @homespunholiday    
    
    
    eCareDiary expresses it's deepest condolences to the families of Sandy Hook Elementary School.    
    
    
    Today caregiving expert Margery Pabst will be speaking about her new book, "Words of Care".  Check it out at 2 PM EST http://ow.ly/g4e2C !    
    
    
    Check out yesterday's radio show with Margery Pabst on her new book "Words of Care" here: http://ow.ly/gdOEw !    
    
    
    When Caregivers Care Too much:  4 warning signs that caregiving is damaging you or your loved one http://ow.ly/gdPFU     
    
    
        
    
    
    A portrait journal photographed by a daughter, as she cared for her mother http://ow.ly/gguhh  #caregiving #family    
    
    
    Caregiving During the Holidays http://ow.ly/ghEfZ     
    
    
    7 Myths About Gout http://ow.ly/ghFYw     
    
    
    Easing the Added Stress of Caregiving During the Holidays http://ow.ly/ghFu7     
    
    
    Five Flu Myths Debunked http://ow.ly/ghFRS     
    
    
    Ingredients for a joyful season and a peaceful New Year http://ow.ly/ghHl9     
    
    
    Don't forget to rest this holiday season!  A midday nap may improve your memory and brain skills...http://ow.ly/ghG9l     
    
    
    Can Holiday Visits Prevent Falls? http://nblo.gs/Gl3Gx     
    
    
    'Study shows that Caregivers live longer then Non-Caregivers?  There must be a mistake' http://ow.ly/gmgVZ  via @seniorhomes #caregiving    
    
    
    #caregiving affirmation http://pinterest.com/pin/71776187782811452/ … via @pinterest    
    
    
    This infographic from Alert1 breaks #senior living & #caregiving down by the numbers. http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138663135/ …    
    
    
    Learning How to Communicate with Someone with Alzheimer's http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138663159/ …    
    
    
    Avoid Burnout When Caregiving An Aging Parent http://ow.ly/gq6Zf  via @BoomertoBoomerOnline    
    
    
    Wishing you a happy and healthy 2013!    
    
    
    11 Ways to Stop Caregiver-Related Depression #caregiver #depression http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138700853/ …    
    
    
    @brightstar_tuc thank you for sharing!    
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! Managing Home Health Workers. Join us on Tuesday, January 8th at 2:00PM EST.  http://ow.ly/gvsqi  #caregiving #homecare    
    
    
    The Connected #Caregiver Infographic http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138718547/ …    
    
    
    Top 15 Superfoods for People Over 50 http://ow.ly/gxm9d     
    
    
    7 Alzheimer's Myths Decoded http://ow.ly/gxsiL     
    
    
    Why a Caregiving Plan for Yourself Makes Sense http://nblo.gs/GOnmZ     
    
    
    The Practical Caregiver Guide: Organize Home Care http://ow.ly/gB1z1     
    
    
    Don't miss Caregivers Speak! Managing Home Health Workers today at 2:00PM EST. http://ow.ly/gvsqi  #caregiving #seniors #homecare    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on managing home health workers, you can catch it here: http://ow.ly/gFlds !  #caregiving #homecare...    
    
    
    Learn that the truth of the person with dementia, is now also your "truth". http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367138766057/ …    
    
    
    Dealing with Typical Fears That Arise for the #Caregiving Wife.  Join us Tues, Jan. 15th at 2:00 EST http://ow.ly/gHqoN !  #familycaregiver    
    
    
    Read up on Dr. Diana Denholm and her book "The Caregiving Wife's Handbook" in preparation for our show on Tuesday! http://ow.ly/gJTNP     
    
    
    Caregiving Wives And "The Big Talk" http://ow.ly/gJUtg     
    
    
    A Legal Checklist for Caregivers http://ow.ly/gJUJ9     
    
    
    'Tis the season!  9 Surprising Ways to Ward Off Colds and Flu http://ow.ly/gJUSx     
    
    
    What do Diabetes and Falling Have in Common? http://nblo.gs/H5tq0     
    
    
    Listen in on our show today at 2:00 PM EST!  We'll be talking about the challenges faced by #caregiving wives.  http://ow.ly/gHqoN     
    
    
    @unfrazzle Thank you for the suggestion!  We will definitely start doing that!    
    
    
    @_careinthehome_ thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    @traceyscriven1 and thank you for sharing!    
    
    
    We had a great show yesterday!  You can listen here: http://ow.ly/gRoRj     
    
    
    Helping Seniors with Daily Activities.  Join us Tues, Jan 22nd at 2PM EST/ 11AM PST http://ow.ly/gTJBR  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Interesting article from TIME...All in the Family: Siblings, Caregiving and Money http://ow.ly/gWrc9     
    
    
    Finding The Right Caregiver Support Group http://ow.ly/gWrGi     
    
    
    @caregivingcafe thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Beware of the Silent Threat! - A Look into Elder Abuse http://nblo.gs/HmuIX     
    
    
    Obamacare and the Modern Hospital Research Environment http://nblo.gs/Hp2tR     
    
    
    @caregivingcafe thanks! : )    
    
    
    @thistlecreekhc No problem!  You too!    
    
    
    Don't forget to tune in today for Helping Seniors with Daily Activities at 2PM EST/ 11AM PST http://ow.ly/gTJBR  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Keep your direction http://nblo.gs/HqAmi     
    
    
    Finding the Characteristics of a Great Wheelchair http://nblo.gs/HrokU     
    
    
    The Secret of Happy Baby Boomers (shhh) http://ow.ly/h3BKS  via @sharpseniors    
    
    
    Photographing Aging Around the World.  Join us Tues, Jan 29th at 2PM EST/ 11AM PST http://ow.ly/h5yHN     
    
    
    Could sleep position affect elders' health? http://ow.ly/h7NyX  via @RetireathomeBG    
    
    
    8 Ways to Beat the Winter Blues http://ow.ly/h7JSa     
    
    
    Accepting Help in Trying Times-The Big Test http://nblo.gs/HDJDc     
    
    
    @retireathomebg no problem : )    
    
    
    @carenovate Thanks!  Hope you had a great weekend too!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out our guest post on Confessions of a Master Caregiver! http://ow.ly/hfjLC     
    
    
    If you missed out show yesterday, you can check it out here http://ow.ly/hfjl1 !    
    
    
    An Aging World: Victory Day in Moscow http://ow.ly/hfjy5...as  we touched on in yesterday's show.    
    
    
    Therapeutic Storytelling & Music to Facilitate Healing.  Join us Feb 5 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST!  http://ow.ly/hiZx3     
    
    
    Caregivers Take Note-- Music as Therapy http://ow.ly/hj2p2     
    
    
    The Healing Power of Music http://ow.ly/hj2z4     
    
    
    Now Is the Time to Get In the Best Shape of Your Life.  The story of a great-grandmother who shaped up...http://ow.ly/hj2MG     
    
    
    The Sandwich Generation: Rising Financial Burdens for Middle-Age Americans http://ow.ly/hj3eN     
    
    
    @miajewishhealth thank you!    
    
    
    Alzheimer's disease facts and figures - infographic by activcareliving http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139003682/ …    
    
    
    How Much Exercise Do Seniors Need? http://nblo.gs/HUKjp     
    
    
    @_careinthehome_ thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    @drnanettej thanks for rting!    
    
    
    @KekeBev thank you for the retweet!    
    
    
    @NHARgirl thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    @BlakefordGH11 thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    Heart-wrenching but insightful...Weighing the End of Life http://ow.ly/hr55r     
    
    
    Therapeutic Storytelling & Music to Facilitate Healing. Join us TODAY @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/hiZx3     
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on therapeutic storytelling and healing music, you can listen here: http://ow.ly/hsYvv !    
    
    
    Life’s Most Basic Stress Reliever: Vitamin B http://nblo.gs/I1Oie     
    
    
    Caregivers Speak! Tough Questions You May be Hesitant to Ask Your Doctor.  Join us Tues, Feb 12 at 2PM EST/ 11AM PST http://ow.ly/hveD9 !    
    
    
    Always on Call: When Illness Turns Families into Caregivers http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139038232/ …    
    
    
    Inspiring. http://ow.ly/hxr75  via @AgingFamilies    
    
    
    The consolations of Alzheimer's http://ow.ly/hxrL5     
    
    
    What's next after caregiving?  http://ow.ly/hxs2L  via @AARP    
    
    
    @caregivingcafe thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    Are Adult Children Legally Responsible for Parents' Long Term Costs? http://nblo.gs/I9VkI     
    
    
    Plan for Mums Care http://nblo.gs/I9W9N     
    
    
    Waves of Faith-- Strength for Christian Caregivers http://ow.ly/hBBZR     
    
    
    @supportforhome thanks for the retweet!    
    
    
    Don't forget!  Tough Questions You May be Hesitant to Ask Your Doctor.  Today 2PM EST/ 11AM PST http://ow.ly/hveD9 !    
    
    
    Don't worry if you missed our show yesterday!  You can listen to it here: http://ow.ly/hGCD6     
    
    
    Resolving Issues Around Aging through Mediation.  Join us Tuesday, February 19th at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST http://ow.ly/hIL4X !  #caregiving    
    
    
    Caregiving with Your Siblings http://ow.ly/hKheI     
    
    
    Have any issues you'd like to be addressed on this week's radio show Resolving Issues Around Aging through Mediation?  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    eCareDiary's Margery Pabst's article has been nominated for a Best Caregiving Articles- ALTY Awards!  Congrats, Margery!...    
    
    
    @seniorcaring thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Legal Issues for LGBT Caregivers http://ow.ly/hKhoL     
    
    
    Confessions of a Worn-Out Alzheimer's Caregiver http://ow.ly/hKgH9     
    
    
    Reasons To Seek The Help Of An Attorney After A Personal Injury http://nblo.gs/IpHnq     
    
    
    Today, remember to breathe.  And if you're feeling really ambitious, take a few minutes to do nothing but.    
    
    
    Is it Possible to Fall Safely? http://nblo.gs/Iq87J     
    
    
    I'll be presenting at the Health 2.0 monthly meet-up this evening 6:30 PM EST in Pittsburgh. Sign up here: http://ow.ly/hQkrV  and join us!    
    
    
    Resolving Issues Around Aging through Mediation airs today at 2 PM EST/ 11 am EST! http://ow.ly/hIL4X ! #caregiving    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday, listen here: http://ow.ly/hT28y !    
    
    
        
    
    
    Caregivers and Health Care Reform - What You Need to Know.  Join us Tues, Feb 26 at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST http://ow.ly/hV9as  #caregiving    
    
    
    Any thoughts on this?  A Peek at Rising Health Care Costs in 5 Major Cities http://ow.ly/hX8y4  #affordablecareact #caregiving    
    
    
    A mostly unbiased break-down of health care reform for 2014: http://ow.ly/hXbZG  #affordablecareact #caregiving    
    
    
    Self-care for the Caregiver via @CaregivingCafe http://ow.ly/hXcKd     
    
    
    Governor's Fall Away in GOP Opposition to More Medicaid http://ow.ly/hXfwm     
    
    
    @johnjgarnand thank you!    
    
    
    10 Ways to Take Charge of Your Heart Health http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139184782/ …    
    
    
    Try Being a Ten Minute Caregiver http://nblo.gs/IFpF1     
    
    
    A heart-healthy shopping guide: http://ow.ly/i1ieJ .  What are you're favorite heart-healthy foods or recipes?    
    
    
    @vnsny_news Thank you for informing us.  We'll definitely be joining!    
    
    
    Don't forget to join us today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST http://ow.ly/hV9as !  We'll be discussing health care reform.    
    
    
    Getting Jazz-ed Up: The Pride Jazzy Power Chair http://nblo.gs/IIECk     
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on health care reform, listen here http://ow.ly/i5S4a     
    
    
    RT if you've ever felt this way http://caregiving.adcouncil.org/tv/     
    
    
    Dementia Behaviors & Resources to Assist Caregivers.  Join us Tues, March 5th at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/i87MN     
    
    
    10 Tips for Communicating with a Person with Dementia http://ow.ly/iaOtU     
    
    
    Dealing with Dementia http://ow.ly/iaOLP     
    
    
    How are you and your loved ones dealing with dementia?  #caregiving #dementia    
    
    
    Harvard Medical School discusses some common causes of memory loss at an early age http://celf.co/UWTN1     
    
    
    Women, have you been asking your doctor these questions?  http://ow.ly/iaPLZ  #caregiving #womenshealth #boomers    
    
    
    Masterbet88 Grand Opening Promo Bonus 50% Sportsbook dan Casino Online http://nblo.gs/ISfOq     
    
    
    Taking a Calculated Risk While Caregiving http://nblo.gs/IUwUu     
    
    
    Have you ever tried being a ten-minute #caregiver?  Here's how: http://ow.ly/icrbI     
    
    
    March is National Nutrition Month!  What are you planning to do to improve your daily diet?    
    
    
    Better #nutrition can mean better #health for #seniors http://ow.ly/icvbM     
    
    
    #Dementia Behaviors & Resources to Assist #Caregivers. Tune in for a show today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/i87MN  #caregiving    
    
    
    @guntakrumins Thank you for the RT a few days ago!    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on Dementia behaviors and resources for #caregivers, listen here: http://ow.ly/irkDA     
    
    
    Even though it's a Wednesday, we thought we would share this with you...www.AlzheimersCareResourceCenter.com http://celf.co/4Ybpt     
    
    
    What does #caregiving mean for you? http://ow.ly/i/1DmuH  #caregiverspecialneeds    
    
    
    @careneverquits We thought so too!    
    
    
    @CaregivingJobs Thanks for the RT the other day!    
    
    
    @RightAtHomeFS Thank you for the RT!    
    
    
    Stop Anger and Keep Your Brain Relax http://nblo.gs/IZOpl     
    
    
    How Creating a Caregiving Plan Can Secure Your Future.  Join us Tues, March 12 @ 2PM EST/ 11 AM PST http://ow.ly/ivcp6  #caregiving...    
    
    
    Rimless Spectacle Structures http://nblo.gs/J2Lmo     
    
    
    they are available in diverse designs and shades from which to choose http://nblo.gs/J2LV3     
    
    
    7 Overlooked Tips for Nailing and Retaining a Dental Career http://nblo.gs/J3f6g     
    
    
    How to Add Psychosocial Problems to Your Care Plan http://ow.ly/ivlNh  #caregiving    
    
    
    Do you have a caregiving plan for yourself or a loved one? #caregiving    
    
    
    Feeling a little stressed this tax season? Good news! There may be some ways to ease that stress for caregivers: http://celf.co/XNieR     
    
    
    Mayo Clinic and Alzheimer's Association meet this weekend to share latest Alzheimer's progress  http://celf.co/wncV  #alzheimers    
    
    
    RAYBAN etched under the words fake oakley sunglasses http://nblo.gs/J73b4     
    
    
    Cheap Oakley Sunglasses a tendency to heat up http://nblo.gs/J73b3     
    
    
    Can Fall Monitoring Technology Keep Elders Safe? http://nblo.gs/J8yyb     
    
    
    @gloveoftheirown thank you!    
    
    
    Listen in today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for How Creating a Caregiving Plan Can Secure Your Future! http://ow.ly/iNI8n     
    
    
    @irwin_brenda thank you!    
    
    
    @caremerge thank YOU!    
    
    
    @SummerBreeze58 Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    #Caregiving plans can include anything from living wills and #healthcare to a daily serving of Cheetos. http://ow.ly/iRwrT     
    
    
    Next week's show is entirely devoted to your #healthcare and #AffordableCareAct questions.  Tweet questions to @eCare_Diary! #caregiving    
    
    
    Caregiving is complicated http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139319439/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    What questions do you have about #TheAffordableCareAct? #healthcare #caregiving    
    
    
    #Caregivers & #Health Care Reform Part 2.  Join us Tues March 19 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST!  Tweet questions before the show!...    
    
    
    @cancerhawk thank you for sharing!    
    
    
    Your Personalized Caregiving Plan - Part 2 http://nblo.gs/Jnsvd     
    
    
    Tomorrow we'll discuss #caregivers and #healthcare reform.  Any last minute questions?    
    
    
    Tune in in and hour for our show on #Caregivers and #Health Care Reform! http://ow.ly/j9JCk     
    
    
    Longterm Care: Costs, Caregiving and Choices http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139363084/ …    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on #caregiving and #healthcare reform, check it out! http://ow.ly/jf1FY     
    
    
    Join us Tues March 26 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Holistic Approaches for the Memory Impaired #caregiving #alzheimers http://ow.ly/jhkA6     
    
    
    Home Alone: #Family #Caregivers Providing Complex Chronic #Care.  Webinar this Thurs, March 28 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/jkf7z     
    
    
    One Third of Seniors Die With Dementia http://ow.ly/jmB1F  http://TIME.com     
    
    
    The Best Exercise for Your Brain is Exercise for Your Body http://nblo.gs/JBNJv     
    
    
    Wow.  What do you think about this?  86-year-old woman with dementia facing voting fraud charge...http://ow.ly/jmAX2     
    
    
    @distinctivept Likewise!    
    
    
    Join us in an hour for #Holistic Approaches for the Memory Impaired! http://ow.ly/jmAIS  #caregiving #dementia #alzheimers    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday on #holistic approaches for the memory impaired, listen in here: http://ow.ly/jsAu1  #caregiving...    
    
    
    All in the Family: Siblings, Caregiving and Money http://ow.ly/jsFYq     
    
    
    Home Alone: #Family #Caregivers Providing Complex Chronic Care begins in one hour! http://ow.ly/juOUA  #caregiving    
    
    
    Yesterday's webinar about #family #caregivers can be found here! http://ow.ly/jzmPR     
    
    
    Fighting #Mesothelioma: Guiding Tips from a Husband #Caregiver. Tues April 2 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST http://ow.ly/jzsrZ  #caregiving    
    
    
    6 Tax Tips for Caregivers http://ow.ly/jAA8t  #caregiving    
    
    
    7 Ways to Keep Your Mind Sharp http://ow.ly/jAAbc  #seniors    
    
    
    Mesothelioma: A Dormant Threat http://ow.ly/jAAsX  via @CaregivingCafe Blog    
    
    
    #Mesothelioma & #Caregiving http://ow.ly/jAEHD     
    
    
    Fighting #Mesothelioma: Guiding Tips from a Husband #Caregiver begins in one hour! http://ow.ly/jAETB  #caregiving    
    
    
    Listen to yesterday's show here!  http://ow.ly/jI6tu  #caregiving #mesothelioma    
    
    
    @mesothelioma thank you for the RT!    
    
    
    Caregivers Speak!  What I Have Learned About Myself While #Caregiving.  Join us Tues April 9 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/jJXWY     
    
    
    #caregiver http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139479415/ …    
    
    
    Fill in the blank with as few or as many words as you need: Today #caregiving makes me feel ________________.    
    
    
    Dementia Care Costs Are Soaring...http://ow.ly/jM6uP  via @NYTIMES    
    
    
    Fighting Chronic Pain via @AARP http://ow.ly/jM6nd     
    
    
    Don't forget to join us in an hour for Caregivers Speak! http://ow.ly/jRgvl     
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday, we talked about our personal #caregiving journeys.  Listen here! http://ow.ly/jVrTu     
    
    
    What do you think? 'Creating Company Culture that Cares about #Caregivers' http://ow.ly/jVuhA  #caregving    
    
    
    Co-founder of eCareDiary Susan Baida will be speaking at the Global #Health and Humanitarian Summit this Saturday! http://ow.ly/jWAcu     
    
    
    #Caregiving Ties That Bind.  Join us Tues, April 16 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/k0B6G     
    
    
    #Caregiving Ties That Bind begins in one hour! http://ow.ly/k0B6G     
    
    
    @brightstar_tuc Thank you for sharing!    
    
    
    What did you find most interesting about yesterday's show? If you missed it, listen here: http://ow.ly/k9yv3  #caregiving    
    
    
    Don't forget to dance in the rain! http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139569305/ …    
    
    
    Let's all be caregivers to Boston right now.    
    
    
    The "AAA" Dilemma of #Caregivers.  Join us Tues April 23 @ 2PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/ke8gf  #caregiving    
    
    
    @brightstar_tuc thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Can you prevent #Alzheimers? How you can keep your brain healthy. http://ow.ly/kfGB7     
    
    
    Happy Monday! What #caregiving successes did you make over the weekend?    
    
    
    7 Ways to Prevent Arthritis...some may suprise you! via @AARP http://ow.ly/kgHe2     
    
    
    How to Handle Criticism From Your Family via @CaregivingCafe @AgingCare http://ow.ly/kgIcz     
    
    
    Don't forget about our radio show "The 'AAA' Dilemma of #Caregivers" today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/kgGSf  #caregiving    
    
    
    @carriebiancoabc Thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday about the "AAA" Dilemma of #Caregivers, find the recording on our site! http://ow.ly/knpWT  #caregiving    
    
    
    Granddaughter charts her #caregiving journey with grandmother suffering from #dementia.  Living With An #Aging Mind. http://ow.ly/knrWt     
    
    
    What #Caregivers Need to Know About Research.  Join us Tues April 30 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST!  http://ow.ly/kpRrW  #caregiving    
    
    
    eCareDiary's in AARP today! Thank you Sally Abrahms for mentioning us! http://lnkd.in/ukDKSj     
    
    
    It's Friday!  Have a good weekend and make sure to find some time to relax and appreciate yourself!    
    
    
    Cholesterol Medication:  Do You Need It? http://ow.ly/ksmBi     
    
    
    Hope and Resolve on Capitol Hill:  The Voice of an Alzheimer's Advocate http://ow.ly/kslxJ  #alzheimers #caregiving    
    
    
    Happy Monday!  Start this week off with a promise to find at least 30 minutes of time for yourself.  What will you do? #caregiving    
    
    
    18 fashion tips from #seniors to brighten your Monday! http://ow.ly/kwroA     
    
    
    5 Ways to Help Elderly Loved Ones Age Independently http://ow.ly/kuTGn     
    
    
    Join us in an hour!  We'll be talking about the #Alzheimers Disease Neuroimaging Initiative! http://ow.ly/kuSB9  #caregiving    
    
    
    What did you think of the show yesterday?  If you missed it, listen here: http://ow.ly/kBgNj     
    
    
    5 Ways to Deal With Your Loved One's Embarrassing Behavior...http://ow.ly/kBh54  #alzheimers #caregiving via @BoomertoBoomerOnline    
    
    
    Join us Tuesday, May 7th at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Helping a Challenging Senior Prepare a Care Plan! http://ow.ly/kG6DO     
    
    
    Join us Tuesday, May 7th at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Helping a Challenging Senior Prepare a Care Plan! http://lnkd.in/ZgDx9S     
    
    
    Helping a Challenging #Senior Prepare a Care Plan.  Join us Tues May 7 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/kG6DO  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    The 10 Commitments of #Caregiving http://ow.ly/kHDn6  via @Unfrazzle    
    
    
    Looking to relieve stress?  Here are 5 tips: http://ow.ly/kHDMg  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    @unfrazzle No problem!    
    
    
    Let's start this week off on the right foot!  "Some days there won't be a song in your heart. Sing anyway." -- Emory Austin #caregiving    
    
    
    5 tips for creating your #caregiving team... http://ow.ly/kJ827     
    
    
    Helping a Challenging Senior Prepare a Care Plan starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/kJ86E  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    No need to worry if you missed our show yesterday!  You can listen to it on our website! http://ow.ly/kP25U  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    Interesting article about what you may not know about long term care http://ow.ly/kP3cU  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    When the Carer Becomes the "Cared-for."  Join us Tues, May 14th @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/kUuSt  #caregiving    
    
    
    #Mothers are #caregivers 24 hours a day, 365 days a year.  Happy Mothers Day!    
    
    
    From the archives: "Missy Buchanan discusses her book 'Talking With God in Old Age'" http://ow.ly/kYGGN  #seniors #caregivings    
    
    
    When the Carer Becomes the "Cared-For"  starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/kYFbR  #caregiving    
    
    
    You can still listen to When the Carer Becomes the "Cared-for" on our website! http://ow.ly/l3fqk  #caregiving    
    
    
    On watching caregiving and illness from afar. A beautiful post. http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139765277/ …    
    
    
    Wigs: Ruth & Erica-- an interesting web series about a daughter caring for her mother. http://ow.ly/l3i6c  #caregiving    
    
    
    Alerting Devices for #Seniors with Hearing and Vision Impairments.  Join us Tues May 21 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/l6iHi     
    
    
    Respect the old when you are young http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139780494/ …    
    
    
    A beautiful #caresharing analogy http://ow.ly/l8rEF  #caregiving    
    
    
    Exercises that Improve Your Balance http://ow.ly/l8vIw     
    
    
    Do you need an emotions check-up? http://ow.ly/l8xrT  via @AARP    
    
    
    Our next radio show starts in one hour!  Alerting Devices for Seniors with Hearing and Visual Impairments http://ow.ly/leOOH ...    
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday, you can listen to it here: http://ow.ly/lhu81  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Creating an #Alzheimers -Friendly Healthcare Workforce.  Join us Tues May 28 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/lkz8e  #caregiving    
    
    
    The #Alzheimer's Epidemic... http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367139839996/ …    
    
    
    What are you doing this holiday weekend?  The Ultimate Grandparent's Guide to Memorial Day http://ow.ly/lohdj  #grandparents #seniors    
    
    
    Answers to your #Alzheimers and #Dementia Questions http://ow.ly/lohCT  #caregiving    
    
    
    Thank you to all who have served and all who continue to serve.    
    
    
    Creating an #Alzheimers - Friendly #Healthcare Workforce starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/lquZs  #caregiving    
    
    
    You can listen to yesterday's show about creating and #Alzheimers - friendly healthcare workforce on our website!  http://ow.ly/lvF04 ...    
    
    
    Questions to ask when interviewing a new home #caregiver http://ow.ly/lvH8t  #caregiving #seniors via @SeniorsGuide    
    
    
    Tips to help you and your siblings manage the finances of #caregiving http://celf.co/9PoXV     
    
    
    Wow. What do you think about this? 86-year-old woman with dementia faces felony.  You' http://celf.co/vbB8H     
    
    
    One Third of Seniors Die With Dementia: http://Time.com  http://celf.co/B7Z9g     
    
    
    One goes through so many emotions as a #caregiver... http://celf.co/QDczm     
    
    
    A family caregivers training program.  Do you have anything like this in your area? http://celf.co/oGazC     
    
    
    Online Counseling for #Caregivers.  Join us Tues, June 4 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 Am PST! http://ow.ly/lxZdL  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    @cmaaging thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    Your Best Advice for Living a Long, Happy Life http://ow.ly/lBM2V     
    
    
    10 Medications that May Cause Memory Loss http://ow.ly/lBMH5     
    
    
    Happy Monday!  What #caregiving lessons did you learn this past week?    
    
    
    This week's radio show starts in an hour! Online Counseling for #Caregivers! http://ow.ly/lH88C  #caregiving @seniors #boomers    
    
    
    If you missed our show about online #caregiving counseling yesterday, you can listen to it on our website! http://ow.ly/lJ9n9     
    
    
    How Palliative Care Enhances Your Quality of Life.  Join us Tues, June 11 @ 2PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/lOve9  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    #caregiving inspiration http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140032170/ …    
    
    
    #Hospice versus #Palliative Care-- an informative over-view. http://ow.ly/lPUUv  #caregiving    
    
    
    To a new Monday! http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140077355/ …    
    
    
    What do you think of this?  Brain #aging May Depend on Childhood Intelligence.  http://ow.ly/lSY5V  via @TIMEHealthland    
    
    
    How Palliative Care Enhances Your Quality of Life starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/lSXje  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    If you missed out on How Palliative Care Enhances Your Quality of Life yesterday, make sure to check it out on our website!...    
    
    
    How to Combat Senior Depression http://ow.ly/lX8Z4  #seniors #boomers via @SharpSeniors    
    
    
    A show from the annals: Dealing with Elderly Suicide and Depression http://ow.ly/lX9y4  #seniors #boomers-- first aired March 1, 2011    
    
    
    Funding for Respite Care.  Join us Tues June 18 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/m2QYv  #caregiving    
    
    
    Shout out to the dads who care. Fathers of all ages are caregivers-- in fact, men make up almost 40% http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140168401/ …    
    
    
    You're not alone - take support where you can find it. My husband is my daily rock. We are interchan http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140168404/ …    
    
    
    Happy Monday!  What are you looking forward to this week? #caregiving #seniors #boomers    
    
    
    Join us in one hour (2 PM EST) for Funding for Respite Care! http://ow.ly/m8EDM  #caregiving    
    
    
        
    
    
    A show from the archives!  Rewards and Pitfalls of #Family #Caregiving http://ow.ly/mb48n     
    
    
    @caregivercards Yes, we are on facebook.  Just dropped by your page and gave you a like!    
    
    
    What Really, Really Matters to #Caregivers... Join us Tues June 25 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/me1GY  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Communicating With People In Late Stages of #Dementia...What do you think? http://ow.ly/me781  #alzheimers #caregiving    
    
    
    The Importance of Becoming Computer Saavy in Our #Aging and #Boomer Population...and a couple making it happen. http://ow.ly/me7pA     
    
    
    What Really, Really Matters to #Caregivers begins in one hour! http://ow.ly/mmpka  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's show, listen in on our website! http://ow.ly/moUGe  #caregiving #seniors #boomers    
    
    
    Join us tomorrow at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Walking Towards Safety: Fall Prevention for #Seniors! http://bit.ly/11IJXJ5  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us in an hour for Walking Towards Safety: Fall Prevention for #Seniors! http://bit.ly/11IJXJ5  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us Tues July 2nd at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for How to Hire Quality Care Providers! http://ow.ly/muCyr  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Why It's Scary Being the #Grandparent http://ow.ly/muE4c     
    
    
    How to Hire Quality Care Providers starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/mAnvI  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Listen to yesterday's radio show, as well as any of our radio shows on our website!  http://ow.ly/mCpzN  #caregiving #seniors #boomers    
    
    
    RT Coping with life after #caregiving...http://ow.ly/mDeNS  via @Hospicecny    
    
    
    Have a mindful, peaceful, and celebratory Independence Day!    
    
    
    Do You Want to Be Happy?  Develop A Personal Plan.  Join us Tues July 9 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/mGYwq  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    #Caregivers choosing acceptance, not resentment, build happiness http://ow.ly/mI7jl  #caregiving #boomers    
    
    
    Beautiful young people are accidents of nature, beautiful old people are works of art. - E. Roosevel http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140284245/ …    
    
    
    Do You Want to Be Happy? Develop A Personal Plan. starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/mMOlb  #caregiving #boomer #seniors    
    
    
    Listen to yesterday's show on our website! http://ow.ly/mI7jl  #caregiving #seniors #boomers    
    
    
    Pew Research Study released:  39% of U.S. adults are #caregivers. http://ow.ly/mPW3a  #caregiving #seniors #boomers    
    
    
    Cognitive Stimulation for #Seniors with #Dementia.  Join us Tues July 16th @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST! http://ow.ly/mRNGb  #caregiving    
    
    
    25 Thing I Know About Life Now That I'm 60 http://ow.ly/mVCba  #aging #boomers    
    
    
    #Caregivers do what has to be done #caregiving http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140325646/ …    
    
    
    Cognitive Stimulation for #Seniors with #Dementia start in an hour! 
 http://ow.ly/mXX3Q  #caregiving    
    
    
    If you missed Cognitive Stimulation for #Seniors yesterday, listen on our website!  http://ow.ly/mRNGb  #caregiving    
    
    
    @eemmerich It's true.  Sometimes #caregiving statistics can be startling.  However, at least we know we're not alone!    
    
    
    What do you think about paid family leave? http://ow.ly/n63wQ  #caregiving    
    
    
    Partners in #Care-- what you can do to help prevent injury and care for joints http://ow.ly/n9vCd  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us tomorrow @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Caregiving Strategies to Engage with #Seniors with #Alzheimers http://ow.ly/nc3y9     
    
    
    #Caregiving Strategies to Engage with #Seniors with #Alzheimers starts in one hour.  Please join us!  http://ow.ly/nek0d     
    
    
        
    
    
    If you missed the show yesterday, listen here!  http://ow.ly/ngLzN  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    @brandkarmavoice thank you for sharing!    
    
    
        
    
    
    How valuable is #family #caregiving? http://ow.ly/nm4O8     
    
    
    We've been experience some pretty high temps lately!  Something #caregivers should be thinking about: How to survive a heat wave:...    
    
    
    Everyday is a new beginning, take a deep breath and start again.  Happy Monday! http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140409724/ …    
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's show, check it out on our website along with all of our other archived shows! http://ow.ly/nuu34  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us tomorrow @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Healthcare Reform: What it Really Means for You! http://ow.ly/nv9J3  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    New Facebook group 4 people w/ #Alzheimer's or other #dementias, caregivers, friends & advocates! http://ow.ly/nxqXg  @usagainstalz    
    
    
    Join us in one hour for a free webinar: #Healthcare Reform: What it Really Means for You. http://ow.ly/nv9J3  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Managing #Caregiving Stress http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140435814/ …    
    
    
    6 Surprising #health benefits of walking http://ow.ly/nAaVR  #caregiving    
    
    
    New developments in #Alzheimers detection and #care http://ow.ly/nAbd2  #caregiving    
    
    
    Coping With the Death of a Parent, Everyone does it differently.  http://ow.ly/nB4C6  #caregiving #boomers #seniors    
    
    
    We know it's Tuesday, but we just found 'Me Time Monday'  for #caregivers and couldn't help but share http://ow.ly/nB82J  #caregiving    
    
    
    Very interesting: People with early-stage #Alzheimers mentor medical students http://ow.ly/nB8DW  What do you think?    
    
    
    #Caring is doing what has to be done and not expecting anything in return. http://ow.ly/i/2MAZd  #caregiving    
    
    
    Encouraging Eating: Advice for at-home #dementia #caregiving http://ow.ly/nB4UN     
    
    
    About living with #Alzheimers and care for the disease http://ow.ly/nB52O  #caregiving    
    
    
    #Sibling Squabbles over Mom?  7 Tips for Getting Along: http://ow.ly/nB4Hn  #caregiving    
    
    
    Let's end the week with some #caregiving inspiration...http://ow.ly/nB72J     
    
    
    Strength for the Moment: Inspiration for #Caregivers http://ow.ly/nB7wG  #caregiving    
    
    
    5 Things I've Learned as a #Caregiver.  #caregiving http://ow.ly/nB4MW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Helpful bit of knowledge for this monday... #caregiving http://ow.ly/i/2R0eF     
    
    
    What does The Affordable Care Act Mean for You! starts in one hour!  #caregiving http://ow.ly/nTnom     
    
    
    #Caregiving: the remedy http://ow.ly/i/2R0bL     
    
    
    #caregiving: the tipping point http://ow.ly/nQbfu     
    
    
    long distance #caregiving and home health care http://ow.ly/nQO1j     
    
    
    end #senior loneliness http://ow.ly/nQQ0c  #boomer RT @PBS    
    
    
    A healthy attitude is contagious.  Be a carrier.  http://ow.ly/i/2RaFG  #caregiving #motivationmonday #onthursday    
    
    
    #creativity and #caregiving http://ow.ly/nQRC0     
    
    
    interesting thought for #alzheimers #caregiving http://ow.ly/nQSiQ     
    
    
    Building Your #Caregiving Team http://ow.ly/nR0Os     
    
    
    Real life strategies for coping with #dementia #caregiving http://ow.ly/nR7nd     
    
    
    #caregiving and true happiness...happy monday! http://ow.ly/i/2UMb5     
    
    
    The Affordable Care Act and You http://ow.ly/o5tZE     
    
    
    #Caregiving: The Ultimate Lesson http://ow.ly/o5C8Y     
    
    
    Join us Tues Aug 27 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for How Medical Professional Can Be Better Listeners! http://ow.ly/o9WN6  #caregiving    
    
    
    @tendercaring thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    positivity...try it http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140562829/ …    
    
    
    Scientists link copper to #Alzheimers http://ow.ly/ocqlb     
    
    
    Making Sense of #Alzheimers: 9 Books for Kids http://ow.ly/ocnCW  #caregiving    
    
    
    A thought and strategy for your Monday. Happy Monday! http://ow.ly/i/2YvCB     
    
    
    Join us in one hour for How Medical Professionals Can be Better Listeners!  http://ow.ly/ogBmP  #caregiving    
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's show, you can catch it again on our website!  http://ow.ly/ogC4D  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    How #Senior #Caregiving Affects #Family Relationships http://ow.ly/ogHgN     
    
    
    Interesting read: How #Alzheimers Changes Appetite http://ow.ly/ogCWj  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us Tues Sept 9 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Veterans Affairs #Caregiver Support Program http://ow.ly/ogDqQ     
    
    
    Some FAQs for #veterans and #caregivers http://ow.ly/ogI4p     
    
    
    A Little Known Benefit for #Aging #Veterans http://ow.ly/ogICx  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    Who will care for baby #boomers? http://ow.ly/ogJ5Y  #caregiving    
    
    
    Dealing With Conflicting #Caregiving Feelings http://ow.ly/ogOn6     
    
    
    Happy Monday! http://ow.ly/ogR7s     
    
    
    The Truth About #Dementia and #Depression http://ow.ly/ogO1l  #caregiving    
    
    
    #Veterans Affairs #Caregiver Support Program starts in an hour! http://ow.ly/ogJrA  #caregiving    
    
    
    Past radio shows are always available on our website!  Listen to yesterday's on #veterans affairs and #caregiving http://ow.ly/ogJGK     
    
    
    @telikincomputer thanks for the RT!    
    
    
    @seniorsdiscount definitely!    
    
    
    @insidedementia thank you for the mention!    
    
    
    Join us Sept 10 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for The Story of a #Mesothelioma Cancer Survivor http://ow.ly/oDkSU  #caregiving    
    
    
    Buying a car with #Alzheimer's? http://ow.ly/oEAWQ  #caregiving    
    
    
    Happy Monday!  It is not the strength of the body that counts, but the strength of the spirit. http://ow.ly/i/35uNZ     
    
    
    #Grandmas raising grandkids struggle with #depression http://ow.ly/oEB0w  #caregiving #seniors    
    
    
    A great resource for those living with #Mesothelioma http://ow.ly/oEBwg  #caregiving    
    
    
    The Story of a #Mesothelioma Cancer Survivor starts in one hour! http://ow.ly/oEBJ1     
    
    
    #Caregiving From a Guy's Perspective http://ow.ly/oLz6b  RT @MichelleSeitzer    
    
    
    @michelleseitzer definitely!    
    
    
    Join us Tues Sep 17th  @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Dealing with Conflicting #Caregiving Feelings http://ow.ly/oQalc     
    
    
    Whatever You Do, Don't Call Them #Senior Centers http://ow.ly/oQ9ow  #successfulaging    
    
    
    Challenging story that aired this week on NBC about an #Alzheimer's #caregiver http://ow.ly/oQ9T8  #caregiving What do you think?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Read Dr. Barry Jacob's article in preparation for tomorrow's show!  Dealing with Conflicting #Caregiving Feelings. http://ow.ly/oQb6U     
    
    
    Dealing with Conflicting #Caregiving Feelings starts in one hour!  Please join us!  http://ow.ly/oQaGq     
    
    
    If you missed our show yesterday, you can always listen to it on our website! http://ow.ly/oDkSU  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us Tues Sept 24 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Creating Support Teams to Assist #Caregivers and their #Families! http://ow.ly/p4hPO ...    
    
    
        
    
    
    Skyrocketing #Alzheimers Rates-- what does this mean for #caregivers? http://ow.ly/p4Z6D  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us this Thurs Sept 26 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Caregivers Are More Techno Savvy:Pew Research Center Study! http://ow.ly/p8V4W     
    
    
    Creating Support Teams to Assist #Caregivers and their #Families starts at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST today!  Join us!  http://ow.ly/parBi     
    
    
    If you miss a radio show, you can always listen to it on our website at anytime! http://ow.ly/pc93m  #caregiving    
    
    
    Making Sense of #Caregiving: Focusing on Key Issues http://ow.ly/pc9fp     
    
    
    Join us Tues Oct 1 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for How the Arts Provide Engagement and Respite for #Caregivers! http://ow.ly/phFrG     
    
    
    A pill bottle that tells you when to take your pills... http://ow.ly/pcqsl     
    
    
    9 Awkward #Grandparenting Moments to lighten your weekend! http://ow.ly/pcqHD  #aging #boomers    
    
    
    Join us at 2 PM EST today for How the Arts Provide Engagement and Respite for #Caregivers and Their Loved Ones! http://ow.ly/po1v4     
    
    
    We apologize that today’s show did not air due to technical complications.  The show will be rescheduled as soon as possible.  Date and...    
    
    
    @InsideDementia Thank you!    
    
    
    #Boomers don't want to live with their adult kids either http://ow.ly/pvuNs  #caregiving    
    
    
    #Caregiving Stories:  It's okay to ask for help http://ow.ly/pvuZZ     
    
    
    Join us tomorrow @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Ear it Out: Understanding Hearing Loss http://ow.ly/pAwng  #caregiving    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ear it Out: Understanding Hearing Loss is starting! Go to: http://ow.ly/pBMH3  #caregiving    
    
    
    If you missed yesterday's show on #hearing loss, check it out on our website! http://ow.ly/pEstZ  #caregiving    
    
    
    Are You at Risk for #Stroke?: Tests to Help Prevent starts  today @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST!   http://ow.ly/pEsN6  #caregiving    
    
    
    Excited for today's video chat on #caregiver burn-out!  Join us at 3 pm EST.  http://ow.ly/pHx1b     
    
    
    Join us Tues Oct 15 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Caregiving for #Lewy Body #Dementia! http://ow.ly/pJAum     
    
    
    Life After #Caregiving....a lovely blog post http://ow.ly/pJDmA     
    
    
    Traveling with Frail Parents http://ow.ly/pJE3y  via @AARP #caregiving    
    
    
    @jlschuster827 Glad you enjoyed it as much as we did!    
    
    
    Signs, Symptoms, Treatment, #Caregiving, and Support for #LewyBody #Dementia http://ow.ly/pNouM     
    
    
    Don't forget to join us today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for #Caregiving for #Lewy Body #Dementia!  http://ow.ly/pNo7x     
    
    
    @LBDAssoc Thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    Join us Tues Oct 22 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Enhancing the Travel Experience for #Aging Loved Ones http://ow.ly/pUjap  #caregiving    
    
    
    Candid question: 'How can I possibly love my husband and think of him as I did before #Alzheimers?' http://ow.ly/pXdWh  #caregiving    
    
    
    #Memory boosting #superfoods that fight #Alzheimers http://ow.ly/pXeEs     
    
    
    Does #caregiving help you live longer? http://ow.ly/pXdJg  via @AARP blog    
    
    
    Catch our radio show today at 2 PM EST!  Enhancing the Travel Experience for #Aging Loved Ones.  http://ow.ly/q1KcR  #caregiving    
    
    
    If you missed the show yesterday, you can always listen to it and all other past shows on our website! http://ow.ly/q66TB     
    
    
    Empower Yourself with Laughter http://ow.ly/q67ar  #caregiving    
    
    
    @CaregivingCafe thank you for sharing!  Hope you enjoyed the show!    
    
    
    Join us Tues Oct 29 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Getting to the Root of the Problem with Loved Ones! http://ow.ly/qb28U  #caregiving    
    
    
    The closest thing to being cared for is to care for someone else.  Happy Monday! #caregiving http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367140924767/ …    
    
    
    #Caregiving: the remedy http://ow.ly/i/3y9h9     
    
    
    Join us today at 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Getting to the Root of the Problem with Loved Ones!  http://ow.ly/qhzw2  #caregiving    
    
    
    Great show yesterday!  If you missed it, check it out on our website!  http://ow.ly/qb28U  #caregiving    
    
    
    Join us Tues Nov 5 @ 2 PM EST/ 11 AM PST for Managing a Bad Day During #Caregiving! http://ow.ly/qmsEW     
    
    
    Happy #Family #Caregivers Month!    
    
    
    Join us for Managing a Bad Day during Caregiving http://bit.ly/16AdYNp  with Denise Brown @caregiving 2pm 11/5/2013
#Caregiving    
    
    
    Join us today at 2pm EDT/11am PDT for Managing a Bad Day During #Caregiving
with Denise Brown @caregiving http://bit.ly/16AdYNp     
    
    
    Great Show yesterday!  If you missed it, check it out on our website! http://bit.ly/1bbiFLE  #caregiving    
    
    
    Palliative Care; What #Caregivers should know.  eCareDiary interviews Diane Meier, CEO of CAPC 11.12.2013 @ 2pm EST http://bit.ly/Xot9FQ     
    
    
    Thanks to all that have sacrificed ensuring our country is safe!  We express our gratitude!  Happy Veterans Day! pic.twitter.com/8AjYuQTETk    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Great Show yesterday on Palliative Care!  If you missed it, check it out on our website.  http://bit.ly/1bDm5IV  #caregiving    
    
    
    November is National Alzheimer’s Awareness Month. #Caregivers, know that we support you. http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141013440/ …    
    
    
    Suspect Financial Elder Abuse; Tips to Spot, Stop/Report.  11.14.2013 @ 2pm EST w/Chris Cooper http://bit.ly/TsRiYU  pic.twitter.com/9ihtg241IJ    
    
    
    Please join us TODAY for Suspect Financial Elder Abuse?  Tips to Spot, Stop & Report @ 2pm EST with  http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141019117/ …    
    
    
    TODAY @ 2pm EST!  Register now @ http://bit.ly/TsRiYU   Suspect Financial Elder Abuse?  Tips to Spot, Stop & Report! pic.twitter.com/sOS1wOdEWk    
    
    
    Kudos to EmblemHealth at being at the forefront with #caregiving with their video series! You Are No http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141019823/ …    
    
    
    “There are only four kinds of people in this world—those who have been caregivers,  those who curren http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141045088/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Joy Boosters: Ways to Encourage Older Adults  11/19/2013 2:00 PM EST.  #caregiving http://www.ecared http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141045264/ …    
    
    
    Be a rainbow in someone's cloud.                  - Maya Angelo -                                    http://pinterest.com/pin/19140367141050612/ …    
    
    
    Don't miss today's show with Missy Buchanan.  Joy Boosters: Ways to Encourage Older Adults @ 2PM EST.  #caregiving pic.twitter.com/Qx5RiS5AGS    
    
    
    everyday to the people you talk to... #caregiving pic.twitter.com/v4xCT3zCed    
    
    
    Changes in Medicare Policy for Home-Based Medical Equipment.  TODAY @ 2pm EST.  Register:   http://bit.ly/1fVcakN  pic.twitter.com/cdOCuBCfjX    
    
    
    #caregivers Our friend Denise Brown w/Caregiving.com started a crowd funding campaign. http://lnkd.in/bBXcbfG  pic.twitter.com/9zypCheixR    
    
    
    Great show yesterday!  If you missed it, check it out on our website.  http://bit.ly/1atTkzU  pic.twitter.com/oWxqWVYCDq    
    
    
    The gift of giving...#caregiving November, National Caregivers Month pic.twitter.com/RNEH4Yfb0E    
    
    
    To avoid problems later, start talking now about health care decisions and estate planning  Read more: http://bit.ly/1hdrMDs 
#caregiving    
    
    
    Managing Caregiver Stress by Learning about Compassion Fatigue 11/26 2pm EST. eCareDiary speaks to Dr. David Decker. pic.twitter.com/flloHFWpde    
    
    
    Be a Caregiver and Live Longer: New Study Reveals Caregivers Lead Healthier Lives.  # caregiving   http://bit.ly/1dw62SG     
    
    
    JOIN us today @ 2pm EST. for our Radio Show with Dr. David Decker. #caregiving http://bit.ly/Xot9FQ  pic.twitter.com/wzwiQRWGJ2    
    
    
    Always give thanks... #caregiving pic.twitter.com/8UBiFqhY58    
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving!  # caregiving pic.twitter.com/698LuNU0wP    
    
    
    Great show 11/26.  In case you missed it, check it out on our website.  #caregiving http://bit.ly/18URGqT     
    
    
    Enjoy the little things... #caregiving pic.twitter.com/cj8rwtYxrq    
    
    
    Today's Radio Show: Empowering Family Caregivers. Journaling to Cope with #Caregiving Challenges today 2:00 PM EST pic.twitter.com/GiPL6GvGqT    
    
    
    You know about Black Friday & are familiar with Cyber Monday. BUT, did you know that today is #GivingTuesday? pic.twitter.com/kqpNowlm8J    
    
    
    Great show yesterday "Journaling to Cope with #Caregiving Challenges"  If you missed it, check it out on our website. http://bit.ly/1bIfRLD     
    
    
    Register now for our upcoming Webinar tommorrow on "Protecting Your Family with Long Term Care Planning" @ http://bit.ly/1bgkppS     
    
    
    REGISTER for today's Webinar 2pm EST. @ http://bit.ly/1bgkppS   Protecting Your Family with Long Term Care Planning pic.twitter.com/UyvyJ2EFKT    
    
    
        
    
    
    Protecting Your Family with Long Term Care Planning 
Webinar @ 2PM EST 
10 Worst Places to Retire  http://t.usnews.com/a46367  via @usnews    
    
    
    How Holiday Traditions can be Enjoyed during #‎Caregiving  Tues, Dec 10 @ 2pm EST w Margery Pabst & Dr. John Guarneri pic.twitter.com/WkpocPcOjR    
    
    
    How Holiday Traditions can be Enjoyed during #Caregiving By Margery Pabst w guest Dr. John Guarneri. TODAY @2pm EST. pic.twitter.com/zII4z91Ibk    
    
    
    Great show yesterday!  In case you missed it, check it out on our website.  http://bit.ly/1kztw77  pic.twitter.com/G8S1ci8T1g    
    
    
    Register for tmrw's Webinar @2pm w/Claim Jockey."How to File LTC INS Claims Successfully".  http://bit.ly/1iWWPVR  pic.twitter.com/qsSUHsmW0q    
    
    
        
    
    
    Out of Memory Loss Comes the Unforgettable 12/17/2013 2PM EST w/Cathie Borrie, author  http://bit.ly/1kOXzrF  pic.twitter.com/gDq1uBGtbB    
    
    
    Don't forget TODAYs Radio Show @2PM EST Out of Memory Loss Comes the Unforgettable #caregiving http://bit.ly/1kOXzrF  pic.twitter.com/Pzw7bva1c6    
    
    
        
    
    
    Merry Christmas!  #caregiving pic.twitter.com/GLyqf0mTPI    
    
    
    Happy New Year!  #caregiving pic.twitter.com/yS95buMwyM    
    
    
    Did you know? Be a Caregiver and Live Longer: New Study Reveals #Caregivers Lead Healthier Lives! Read here...http://bit.ly/IERimg     
    
    
    