Congratulations Kevin, well-deserved win! Enjoy. (YouTube http://youtu.be/I9SsOphmx-o?a)    
    
    
    Helmets matter, no matter what ur riding Courtney King Dye's video address - HorseChannel.com: http://www.horsechannel.com/horse-news/2011/07/30/courtney-king-dye-riders4helmets.aspx?cm_mmc=4941116#.TkJsgkH62cU.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    I subscribed to masterlock77's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/masterlock77?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to HorsemartVideos's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/HorsemartVideos?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    My favorite farrier finally on the web, check him out http://www.AndrewElsbree.com  -- the best for all disciplines, sound feet = happy horses!!!    
    
    
    @WilliamShatner Hey Bill -- how about getting Unbridled with Susan Kayne for HRTV. Check out the vids http://www.YouTube.com/UnbridledTV     
    
    
    @Debbie_Ford amen to that!    
    
    
    Getting in the kitchen to make Vegan Thanksliving dishes -- yeah a day of restoration. It's been a rough weekend, had to put ET to sleep :(.    
    
    
    A Vegan Thanksgiving Celebrates Good Food, Activism and Hope http://shar.es/o708E     
    
    
    Must watch b4 u shop 2day http://youtu.be/gLBE5QAYXp8  #BlackFriday    
    
    
    Headed to Pump, Chisel & Sizzle to care of overindulging on vegan thanksgiving!    
    
    
    This Saturday, Greenville, NY - 7 horses shipping in from Saddlebred Rescue http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S_PSixSTenY&feature=share … via @youtube UnbridledTV will be there.    
    
    
    It’s a shoe-in: Andrew Elsbree & Susan Kayne’s Clermont Farm is known for its expert farrier service http://www.hudsonvalleyalmanacweekly.com/it%e2%80%99s-a-shoe-in-andrew-elsbree-susan-kayne%e2%80%99s-clermont-farm-is-known-for-its-expert-farrier-service/ …    
    
    
    #WarHorse GREAT group of still pics. http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/war_horse/pictures/ … via @RottenTomatoes    
    
    
    Horses Never Forget Human Friends : Discovery News http://news.discovery.com/animals/horse-friends-memory-trainers.html …    
    
    
    Get your Thoroughbred featured on Unbridled! Call for Submissions. http://icont.ac/PkgA     
    
    
    Powerful, meaningful Poems - Eavan Boland: http://youtu.be/UFvVlhKa8O8  via @youtube Famine Roads...I rode on them in Connemara with Willie Leahy.    
    
    
    Another reason I so love horses -- A long ride but it was worth it  - http://bit.ly/aJPFhA via @addthis    
    
    
    in my heart you and Z take top prize always. with empathy xo (YouTube http://youtu.be/iyO3tuwRAIc?a)    
    
    
    Eight-year-old painting prodigy is seen - Yahoo! News Photos http://yhoo.it/ayaZRS    
    
    
    Learning life lessons on Super Soul Sunday with Oprah. Author of Simple Abundance Sarah Ban Breathnach sharing her rise-fall-rise journey!    
    
    
    Cat Adoption Fees Waived, Town Board Meeting - Mineola, NY Patch http://mineola.patch.com/articles/cat-adoption-fees-waived-town-board-meeting … CATS ARE THE BEST PETS, LOYAL, FUN, LOVING :)    
    
    
    Keep away from people who try 2 blittle ur ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really gr8 make U feel that U, 2, can Bcome gr8    
    
    
    Animal cruelty should be a felony in EVERY state. Sign the #NDStopCruelty pledge: http://bit.ly/MaLBuI  (via @HumaneSociety) I SIGNED THIS    
    
    
    things-you-shouldnt-be-paying-for: Personal Finance News from Yahoo! Finance http://yhoo.it/cbfafa    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Unbridled Race Horse Report 20Aug2010 http://youtu.be/XESTCtvCgIg?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Kurt Vonnegut http://youtu.be/x3ikvCT3858?a    
    
    
    Produced By Faith http://www.3lwtv.com/3LWTV/Bookshelf/Entries/2012/7/4_Devon_Franklin_-_Produced_By_Faith.html …    
    
    
    Your VOICE Matters! Speak up for thoroughbreds by liking and commenting on video link. http://icont.ac/1b0Lq     
    
    
    MUST WATCH VIDEO if you have a heartbeat.....Why Vegan? Lessons From An Animal Scientist: http://youtu.be/5ZYQnt-67vs  via @youtube    
    
    
    Russell Brand in the zone on Piers Morgan tonight...bright guy.."i'm like a farmer, my product is a TV show instead of a tomato"    
    
    
    I subscribed to natpe's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/natpe?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to WestPointTBreds's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/WestPointTBreds?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Carrots have a “secret” weapon against cancer : :: Natural Health 365 :: http://www.naturalhealth365.com/food/carrots.html …    
    
    
    dear friends these three little kitties Ava, Eve, and Emily,  who bless me every day were adopted from death row... http://fb.me/1LRL5xEqa     
    
    
    Speedy at Saratoga this morning with jockey Shaun Bridgmohan in the irons, with commentary by trainer Carlos... http://fb.me/GlpoP9Dn     
    
    
    How many times has that certain something only a horse can offer saved your life? I've lost count.... http://fb.me/2dLZVSBY1     
    
    
    Interesting... http://fb.me/1inJUKBO8     
    
    
    seriously, Victoria's secret would have more business if they would present their lingerie on realistic untouched... http://fb.me/24mJcsouK     
    
    
    Michelle Obama: Tell Barack to honor his campaign promise to label GMOs http://signon.org/s/zSIoy8  @signon    
    
    
    In 2007, Obama promised, “We’ll let folks know whether their food has been genetically modified, because... http://fb.me/19I7ilUAE     
    
    
    My little kitties getting big!  Emily, Ava, and Eve enjoying the warmth of our glorious sunshine this morning. http://fb.me/2m1zVnz0K     
    
    
    Hey friends I'll be attending this. When I learned about people in jeopardy of losing their pets and realized I... http://fb.me/1qilTLfKu     
    
    
    Reader supported jounalism...YES! http://fb.me/1Zn3jOT4l     
    
    
    WOAH! I cant believe you can already see who is viewing your profile! I just saw my Top 10 Profile Viewer and I... http://fb.me/20CotVny4     
    
    
    Time for a change at Saratoga.... http://fb.me/1ZW3JbWo0     
    
    
    Nice article... http://fb.me/GIXUmbQR     
    
    
    Fancy schmancy (did I spell that right?!).... http://fb.me/1CRlWnEkf     
    
    
    My experience with cats give me cause for PAWS.... http://fb.me/2pXqR4oIO     
    
    
    What kind of democracy do we live in ?!?!? Watch ETHOS (Netflix) with Woody Harrelson and Noam Chomsky...and get an education.    
    
    
    What a fancy shoe! http://fb.me/24aGz6smT     
    
    
    EQUINE VACCINATIONS MORE IMPORTANT THAN EVER..... http://fb.me/1BEnEvdOA     
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Thoroughbred Weekly - Trainer Jimmy Jerkens http://youtu.be/DqiU0L3jw0M?a    
    
    
    Congratulations Jimmy -- so happy for you! (YouTube http://youtu.be/DqiU0L3jw0M?a)    
    
    
    “I've come to believe that each of us has a personal calling that's as unique as a fingerprint and that the best... http://fb.me/1SYGH3hus     
    
    
    Meanwhile horses get hurt, the betting public is duped, and veterinarians get rich... http://fb.me/1bH5oCpJU     
    
    
    Mark your calendar! Sept 30th..what a beautiful way to spend a day in the Hudson Valley :)...I'll be there, will you? http://fb.me/24XCp8tcs     
    
    
    another Unbridled headline!… Having been thrice married and twice unbridled I get it… http://fb.me/1TvBbEyaM     
    
    
    WOW....sign of the times...a lot of wonderful coverage over the years from dedicated journalists.... http://fb.me/1ef2EEBtR     
    
    
    I'm famous for my UNBRIDLED life ....... love you Resident! XXOO (YouTube http://youtu.be/ecbbcg5247c?a)    
    
    
    So Excited! Thank you FB friends for your support in getting this out of the editing suite into the limelight on... http://fb.me/1dXRIOQV3     
    
    
    hey friends…  I'm so excited to share with you an all new episode of Ireland Unbridled this coming Monday the 24th... http://fb.me/Eah6Ta4J     
    
    
    Aaaaaah to be the daughter of a rock star! Sweet. I am being sarcastic :). All the best Jessica, I hope you'll sit... http://fb.me/wppOFRVv     
    
    
    A video preview of the next episode of Ireland Unbridled! http://youtu.be/dFjbzXYys78  http://fb.me/1Whrx4xRf     
    
    
    Wow.....quite a connection....and another example of how a horse inspires a human.... http://fb.me/2qqqhpbhD     
    
    
    So sweet... http://fb.me/1if8jG14B     
    
    
    I am so humbled to have had the opportunity to share Bandit's story with the NY Times. It is this type of... http://fb.me/1GnjXIaMd     
    
    
    Wow...it took science to determine that...how arrogant of humanity. http://fb.me/1CUJ6Rz5N     
    
    
    Cian, behind the scenes! http://fb.me/23EmNz9sh     
    
    
    Friends, Bandit is OK. Here are few words with him. Thanks for all of the emails, calls and support. Susan http://fb.me/OymS4QSV     
    
    
    Susan Kayne and Bourbon Bandit: http://youtu.be/IbipL33pxF8  via @youtube Follow up on BB    
    
    
    90 minutes to Ireland Unbridled showtime on the eastcoast. Tune in at 9:30 PM ET on HRTV :)... http://fb.me/1DuOZWWZY     
    
    
    @ss0325JP What does your country do with all the horses that do not race?    
    
    
    “Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any... http://fb.me/1UXG0Fd7h     
    
    
    In NJ on Saturday? Check this out.....looks like a really fun horse-centric day :)... http://fb.me/1wFcMxfsI     
    
    
    HRTV ALERT: MINNESOTA and KENTUCKY Tune-in to HRTV, The Best Network for Horse Sports. Home to Ireland Unbridled... http://fb.me/1jGRMISQT     
    
    
    REDEMPTION!  the Gov.'s task force  investigation revealed exactly what I experienced with Bourbon Bandit.  Thank... http://fb.me/1VW7VhwBs     
    
    
    Gov. Cuomo making good changes to NY Racing ...Faults Officials in Horse Fatalities at Aqueduct http://nyti.ms/Q7b7BB     
    
    
    “Be not simply good; be good for something.”

Henry David Thoreau (1817-1862); naturalist, author, philosopher    
    
    
    Watching LIVE PRESS CONFERENCE on RACING in NY findings by New York State Office of the Governor http://livestre.am/xXXE  via @livestream    
    
    
    I had the privilege of sharing Bandit's story on WAMC Hud Valley horse owner puts spotlight on drugging http://bit.ly/PL1YyI  via @WAMCRadio    
    
    
    mickeyd8's comment on Aqueduct Racing Officials Faulted in Horse Deaths via @nytimes http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/28/sports/aqueduct-racing-officials-faulted-in-horse-deaths.html?comments#permid=34 …    
    
    
    All the Missing Horses: What Happened [...] Gov’t? SICKENING - ProPublica http://www.propublica.org/article/missing-what-happened-to-wild-horses-tom-davis-bought-from-the-govt … via @propublica    
    
    
    This makes my stomach turn.... http://fb.me/1HMXSLYum     
    
    
    Informative, articulate beautiful woman advocating for good...... http://fb.me/1MTsjBmOv     
    
    
    Girl Power! Q & A with Jill Abramson and Jane O'Connor http://www.publishersweekly.com/pw/by-topic/childrens/childrens-book-news/article/54025-q--a-with-jill-abramson-and-jane-o-connor.html … via @publisherswkly    
    
    
    Here is a great example as to why I love Luna 61 so much… Not only is it my favorite vegetarian restaurant… But... http://fb.me/1N7ElBYa8     
    
    
    aaaaahhhh...a touch of Eire for your fingertips...a good read... http://fb.me/2cs15PnB8     
    
    
    Soaking in every word of smokin'hot LIAM NEESON on Bravo, Inside Actors Studio. BRilliant actor, deep dialogue. Privilege to listen in.    
    
    
    Paul Nolan is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on HRTV,... http://fb.me/vBOzVucT     
    
    
    Willie Mullins is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on... http://fb.me/1kqRMcmse     
    
    
    Champion Ruby Walsh is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival... http://fb.me/1SOFkouVE     
    
    
    Rory Sheridan is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on... http://fb.me/IxUsUD5y     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry...

racehorses...by susan kayne

They run for the love of it.
On what, they do not... http://fb.me/24v1uzzpy     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry...

racehorses...by susan kayne

They run for the love of it.
On what, they do not know…... http://fb.me/1iJ1jnWam     
    
    
    My new eco-dress....hope i don't hungry while i am wearing it!!!!! go green girlfriends xxoo http://fb.me/1BXSwvZnE     
    
    
    Modern Day Trojan Horse Made From Over 18,000 Salvaged Computer Keys | http://inhabitat.com/amazing-modern-day-trojan-horse-made-from-over-18000-salvaged-computer-keys/ … via @ThinkDevGrow    
    
    
    THE HORSE STORY OF THE DAY !!! "To create something out of nothing pushes me more, so this is how it was born the... http://fb.me/2ig0CuoE9     
    
    
    MAGNIFICENT STORY: Stick-to-it-ive-ness: Unwavering pertinacity; perseverance by Richard Morse, @artprize entry http://www.artprize.org/richard-morse/2012/sticktoitiveness-unwavering-pertinacity-perseverance …    
    
    
    INCREDIBLE -- more pictures of stunning art "The visual representation of horses running on the river's surface,... http://fb.me/1DBBYePst     
    
    
    I am absolutely adamant that hydrofracking will mean death to people and properties in New York.  this is a... http://fb.me/1LYwqLFqm     
    
    
    May heaven greet you with joy of riding free from any restrictions. Thank you for coming to earth and sharing... http://fb.me/13vS2Sn86     
    
    
    The joy of kitties. The girls, almost three months now since adopting from Manhattan AC&C. Felicia tiger in back,... http://fb.me/HABny9r0     
    
    
    NOW is the time to adopt...save a life and add years to yours :). Pets On Death Row need you the most now. http://fb.me/1j9qcE1Ly     
    
    
    Fitting tribute to three extraordinary men who have dedicated their lives to bettering everything equestrian.... http://fb.me/222URkwkc     
    
    
    The best use of tattered wool horse coolers....recycle them for kitty warmers. Emily, adopted from Manhattan AC& C... http://fb.me/VOAYLSo5     
    
    
    An advocate for dignity, clean living for horses http://www.registerstar.com/news/article_03fd36d0-1356-11e2-b64d-0019bb2963f4.html#.UHbf6yfZ9E8.twitter … via @tweetmeme    
    
    
    @jvelezmitchell Foxy a vegan too :)    
    
    
    CUTE ALERT: Meet a cat who sleeps in pants; household pet hazards: http://bit.ly/UIIHDV  (via @HumaneSociety)    
    
    
    On the radio with Jamie and Glenn this AM. about #IREunbridled click the link to listen and escape to the Emerald Isle  http://www.horsesinthemorning.com/hitm-for-10-15-2012-by-omega-alpha-equine-unbridled-ireland-rescues-rejects-chips-poo/ …    
    
    
    My thoughts on incentivizing breeding in NY.... http://youtu.be/bRWHc-pLTjM  http://fb.me/1Z4M0kevq     
    
    
    “Do you know the difference between education and experience? Education is when you read the fine print;... http://fb.me/1W3t211Oe     
    
    
    I like this…THE COMMON SENSE PARTY... http://fb.me/1zS20u6nk     
    
    
    WARNING: GRAPHIC, DISTURBING PICTURES ....This is WHY AFTERCARE programs need to be in place before incentivizing... http://fb.me/1JH1VheEf     
    
    
    Next stop on Ireland Unbridled... http://fb.me/2m0sTMXrz     
    
    
    Another magnificent example of how our fellow beings help us....imagine if we could get shelter cats into the... http://fb.me/2k1IenZ1f     
    
    
    Great video of Kitty helping little boy to communicate, lets get shelter cats homes like this: Jessi-Cat: http://youtu.be/_vNM-bWf0oM  via @youtube    
    
    
    An extra from our next episode on HRTV (Monday, 9:30PM ET).... http://fb.me/1kNoKk7Pb     
    
    
    Ireland Unbridled: Why are Irish Horses so Special?: http://youtu.be/omSHXQv7frE  via @youtube    
    
    
    Find out why Irish horses are....
http://youtu.be/omSHXQv7frE  http://fb.me/XgVMMtLj     
    
    
    gotta love my girlfriend Lori...she nailed this one... http://fb.me/IPu7PoM2     
    
    
    Get fit, strong, and healthy...it is your birthright! http://fb.me/2s6QICqll     
    
    
    Relieved to learn Cuvee's Girl is now safe thanks to Mike Metzger    
    
    
    Watching Hallmark Channel HONEYMOON FOR ONE --lots of IRISH HORSES!!!! Beautiful Memories of Emerald Isle :) #IREunbridled    
    
    
    @sandyabrams @DeVon_Franklin great read so real    
    
    
    @tonyrobbins wow nice gig!    
    
    
    bill maher on target now prop 37 TRUTH in LABELING GMO foods!!!! Gary from Stonyfield, Matt Taibbi..rock on Bill    
    
    
    Most GMOs corn, soy, canola, sugar beets,   insecticide pesticide f(*&g MONSANTO pure evil.Gary Hirshberg. 527 mm pnds of poison    
    
    
    24d agent orange CHEMICAL INFLATION in food chain. 527 more millions of pesticides. $587mm lobbying so americans won't know whats in food!    
    
    
    SaddleBred Rescue today in Greenville, NY...some fortunate horses will find forever homes this day :)    
    
    
    Three little sisters growing up day-by-day! All rescued from death row three and a half months ago :). http://fb.me/zKQ0TElt     
    
    
    getting ready to escape to Adare in an hour. #IREunbridled at 9:30 PM ET on HRTV tunie in for a little R & R & to brush up on your riding    
    
    
    Check out SADDLEBRED RESCUE ADOPTION DAY IN NEW YORK: http://youtu.be/6iUE_GUwfT4  via @youtube    
    
    
    So glad to be able to share this event -- hope it helps horses in need of forever homes...have a look... http://fb.me/2i3KzQQ7b     
    
    
    Are humans the only species complicit in their own demise..and that of the environment  that supports their life..grrrrrr    
    
    
    Enjoyed the best dinner at Luna 61 -- my fave hangout in Tivoli :). Thanks Debra Maisel for a rejuvenating dinner... http://fb.me/2dUc6kRst     
    
    
    This is a special group, over 125 years of helping horses :).....thank you. http://fb.me/2jCSYgWV8     
    
    
    Little Eve and Nanny Felicia! http://fb.me/1muIHYHjE     
    
    
    Yummy dinner at Gigi's in Rhinebeck tonight, love the Husdon Valley eateries!    
    
    
    For Deborah Jones ... http://fb.me/Vwn8W7N5     
    
    
    Hello, fellow Cat slaves! The original copy of the "Basic Rules for
Cats who Have a House to Run" was uncovered... http://fb.me/1K2Tyip5B     
    
    
    UPDATED 10-28-12: Maryland Park Service (MPS) will be providing safe haven for horses at Fair Hill (Cecil County)... http://fb.me/1y4Icp1QW     
    
    
    Association by Seth Godin:
Who you hang out with determines what you dream about and what you collide with.
And... http://fb.me/2wrlLeeWm     
    
    
    Friends, during the hectic rush of Sandy please don't abandon your pets and other animals. Your cats, dogs,... http://fb.me/1nJMscDLl     
    
    
    Friends, this is yet another example of why horse breeding [of all breeds] needs to take a time out.... http://fb.me/tdAEZNFt     
    
    
    Thank you NYT for shedding light on the divine mission of Deborah Jones http://fb.me/1xAYlAK0X     
    
    
    Little Brook sharing the love of horses in a meaningful way ... http://fb.me/2vKBqoTtX     
    
    
    @CVFPartnerships @joedrape As long as 1 TB goes to slaughter, 1 too many is being bred.#BC12 is a perfect venue to show the plight of TBs.    
    
    
    @sidfernando @nythoroughbred do these people have names?    
    
    
    My thoughts during racing's biggest day... http://fb.me/1KkYtdGBn     
    
    
    Go where you are celebrated ... not where you are tolerated.
 -- Joel Osteen    
    
    
    Stop Using Dogs and Cats As Live Bait in French Controlled Islands http://fb.me/235kja0y4     
    
    
    Pledge Not to Shop at Pet Stores That Sell Puppies http://fb.me/1EAX67DTs     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry....

racehorses ... 

They run for the love of it,
Powered by strength they know.... http://fb.me/1IYVtm2Zk     
    
    
    Beautiful young lady, lovely role model.... http://fb.me/ubpPNGYr     
    
    
    My all time favorite quote...."You better LOVE what you do, because YOU ARE TRADING YOUR LIFE for it"    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2achqhSOV     
    
    
    “Walk with the dreamers, the believers, the courageous, the cheerful, the planners, the doers, the successful... http://fb.me/2hg5BqtW0     
    
    
    Little Ava prefers fresh cooked....!!!! She is not vegan like her human Susan. http://fb.me/215HZ2Js8     
    
    
    Great lecture Friday night at NYS Museum by Lincoln Scholar Harold Holzer to kick-off a two-day exhibition of... http://fb.me/1QUsS6YWX     
    
    
    WOW! Guess this doesn't apply to Racetrack Veterinarians..... http://fb.me/16ZNSF95w     
    
    
    A snippet of my interview with Mark Molloy of Crossogue in Ireland. A genuine horse lover, and incredible host at... http://fb.me/1JIlDI8M1     
    
    
    The coolest lady I met in all of Ireland. Pippa is gorgeous, rich, and earthy. I enjoyed every moment with her at... http://fb.me/1lUz5FlMY     
    
    
    Little kitty fur balls -- Eve & Ava cat-napping in the office :) http://fb.me/24HgTJyII     
    
    
    Congrats Eric! http://fb.me/22khU8JG6     
    
    
    A kindle and kittens! Sunday AM on my therapy couch :). http://fb.me/28Ri13Pdk     
    
    
    A Misty Monday Morning...four beauties safe in my yard. http://fb.me/1oFhi0WVY     
    
    
    And so [blood-stained] I write...... Where Do Ideas Come From? http://www.pw.org/content/where_do_ideas_come_from … via @poetswritersinc    
    
    
    Saw #LINCOLN in the cinema tonight. Deep and inspiring. Should sweep the Awards. A must see, say no to war movie. pic.twitter.com/zxlA9IXF    
    
    
    @WilliamShatner @ThomasGorz1 A VEGAN ThanksLiving!    
    
    
    Sweet (tooth) deal! http://fb.me/v6Zsu39S     
    
    
    The best part about Thanksgiving for me (a Vegan) is sharing what would have been my portion of the Turkey with... http://fb.me/2mVpTqvt9     
    
    
    Love my turkey-loving friends....rock on vegans, and veggies...here is to your health and animal liberation...... http://fb.me/1R2Ac5m81     
    
    
    HAPPY STORY: Inmates, horses, meet a standardbred named Lincoln. help each other get a second chance http://soc.li/K9yvzYi     
    
    
    Review: 'Saving America's Horses' is a disturbing documentary http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/movies/moviesnow/la-et-mn-saving-america-capsule-20121123,0,3772054.story …    
    
    
    too funny.... http://fb.me/1kS2gzARr     
    
    
    It all starts in the breeding shed.... http://fb.me/141d1y7ts     
    
    
    “Rock bottom became the solid foundation on which I rebuilt my life.” J.K. Rowling (born 1965); novelist    
    
    
    It's snowing in Tivoli! 1st of the season in the Hudson Valley.    
    
    
    Inherent in the desire are the mechanics to its fulfillment. I first heard this from Deepak Chopra.    
    
    
    Gratitude... http://fb.me/1qMV0oYS8     
    
    
    Speak up for Animals tonight in Albany, NY....... http://fb.me/xyGPVZSV     
    
    
    “Be soft. Do not let the world make you hard. Do not let pain make you hate. Do not let the bitterness steal your... http://fb.me/1JR4SY0Lm     
    
    
    Just learned HRTV is playing my interview with James Burns tomorrow, Saturday [Dec 1st], at 9PM ET and midnight.... http://fb.me/1Zb86dcas     
    
    
    James Burns, Dolphin Bay, Life On The Curragh: http://youtu.be/GVMqRY4IaMQ  via @youtube    
    
    
    Life on The Curragh in 40 mins on @HRTVHorseSports Tune in to see Life on The Curragh.    
    
    
    Imagine if the last things to grace your eyes on this earth was the most beautiful thing in the world to you... What a blessing to behold.    
    
    
    Imagine if the last things to grace your eyes on this earth was the most beautiful thing in the world to you...?... http://fb.me/2gLth8Zv4     
    
    
    #supersoulsunday Who is the Brain on the show with Jill Bolte Taylor. Is anyone else curious? It was a real person too.    
    
    
    TONITE on @HRTVHORSESPORTS 9:30 PM ET see my cross country lesson and interview with Eleanor Dwan @ Mt. Juliet Estate. pic.twitter.com/mFr1AHDD    
    
    
    @DeepakChopra I spent a week with Debbie Ford at Omega!    
    
    
    Sneak peek #IREunbridled tonite on HRTV Meet Eleanor Dwan at the Mount Juliet Estate in Kilkenny Ireland: http://youtu.be/m0ynGpKaEe0  via @youtube    
    
    
    "How we treat this planet and everything on it is a very important measure of of our love and…" — stacey graham http://disq.us/8bvqvs     
    
    
    Another reason to love Debbie Ford ... http://fb.me/y2QY9wq3     
    
    
    Writing the wrongs! Bandit's Story at the halfway point. Be inspired writers by JK Rowling [hour with Charlie Rose] http://www.charlierose.com/view/interview/12612 …    
    
    
    THE BEST ARTICLE: Ashley Judd Slaps Media in the Face for Speculation Over Her ‘Puffy’ Appearance http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2012/04/09/ashley-judd-slaps-media-in-the-face-for-speculation-over-her-puffy-appearance.html … via @thedailybeast    
    
    
    When you feel hurt by others opinions, remind yourself that it is not you they are really seeing, but a... http://fb.me/2qmQ56hgP     
    
    
    An excerpt from the Cat Rules, especially important in winter: Attention all fellow CATS --- Do not allow closed... http://fb.me/2jb1Z3ulh     
    
    
    Emmy didn't read the sign on the dryer door! Friends, PLEASE, ALWAYS look in your dryer if you live with kitties.... http://fb.me/x8VljQla     
    
    
    OMG Vegan Food Bliss ... I'll be making this :) http://fb.me/2hH0ZCtn5     
    
    
    Love Renegade Health! http://fb.me/1bLjXzEnn     
    
    
    Exquisite... http://fb.me/DeyDO4VM     
    
    
    Contemplate my friends, live while you are alive. Treasure every breath, every moment, every touch and expression... http://fb.me/FmNk97sP     
    
    
    Be a proactive parent.... http://fb.me/yJ17KNks     
    
    
    Watching Harold & Me at beautiful Mt. Juliet in County Kilkenny #IREunbridled on @HRTVHORSESPORTS. Tune-in Dish 404.    
    
    
    A blast from the past, 2006 WCBC at Calgary Stampede... http://fb.me/1o4OxlxoV     
    
    
    Little Lizzie on big stakes horse Stalwart Member! A happy Holiday memory in the barn, circa 2005. http://fb.me/1q0TzoXqc     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1ququHUwW     
    
    
    Alan Chartock...In Conversation with Susan Kayne and Andrew Elsbree http://fb.me/2m5XJM2mE     
    
    
    Doping at Devon....and so it goes.... http://fb.me/15koTTqft     
    
    
    Doping at Devon....Sudden Death of Show Pony Clouds Image of Elite Pursuit http://nyti.ms/10q3Y6S     
    
    
    “Sometimes things get so rough in your life that the the dream has to do the dreaming for you” Tyler Perry on Piers Morgan NOW. LOVE HIM :)    
    
    
    Exquisite.... http://fb.me/Ao2lTOb6     
    
    
    C'est la Vie... http://fb.me/xLA26qup     
    
    
    Wow...here is an empowering perspective to what can otherwise be a sad and troubling time. Letting go and... http://fb.me/27eXfVgsl     
    
    
    Jennifer Gralow Says it all....beautiful, succinct, from the heart.... http://fb.me/1p1lj9Cc0     
    
    
    I couldn't imagine a better way to start the New Year than helping another in need.....MISO needs an angel...NOW http://fb.me/WCKBKZrW     
    
    
    ANIMAL RESCUERS/ADVOCATES UNDER ATTACK BY FACEBOOK http://fb.me/1P4ioVTUh     
    
    
    “The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.” Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi... http://fb.me/2862N4L5E     
    
    
    No need to frack NY. http://fb.me/28yws2Vcz     
    
    
    Beautiful girl, needs an angel... http://fb.me/23IVdxNHi     
    
    
    “The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.”
Ralph Waldo Emerson (1803-1882);... http://fb.me/1sH5zPCuz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1O5lDzy6i     
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Backstretch Buzz: New York-breds http://youtu.be/zk2razTwQDY?a    
    
    
    Time to own a NY-Bred! Get UR own horse today. (YouTube http://youtu.be/zk2razTwQDY?a)    
    
    
    “I didn't lose the gold. I won the silver.” Michelle Kwan (born 1980); figure skater, Olympic Medalist, United... http://fb.me/1wg7P1g9V     
    
    
    Amen.... http://fb.me/2nwgskvRI     
    
    
    Just like Horse Racing -- Armstrong admits doping to Oprah http://bigstory.ap.org/article/armstrong-admits-doping-oprah-0 …    
    
    
    Hey Friends, I'd value your feedback on my blogpost about Dutrow suspension. No doubt it will take a huge effort... http://fb.me/2sDhUzN4Y     
    
    
    100% correct Nathan. http://fb.me/Jd8ODbcm     
    
    
    Here is a thought to contemplate this week....“…memory is fragile and the space of a single life is brief,... http://fb.me/1ROOTztjR     
    
    
    Tonight on HRTV 9:30 PM ET watch my interviews with racing stars at the Galway Festival on Ireland Unbridled!... http://fb.me/1OjZVg0bj     
    
    
    SO TRUE, TRUE, TRUE: “If I made it, it's half because I was game enough to take a lot of punishment along the way... http://fb.me/SWCK9EQt     
    
    
    love this! great way to rock the midday of the week! Yes, yes, yes...... http://fb.me/1xbfKLK2y     
    
    
    In Miami at #NATPE to share the unbridled joy of horses. if you'd like to see more of our beloved 4-legged friends on TV- tweet up please!    
    
    
    Cuteness Award! http://fb.me/1n9N9EqXd     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1wzYEdwhs     
    
    
    TIME TO GET CREATING !!!!!  “We are not creatures of circumstance; we are creators of circumstance.”  Benjamin... http://fb.me/2gfHgmQut     
    
    
    TIME TO GET CREATING !!!!!  “We are not creatures of circumstance; we are creators of circumstance.”  Benjamin... http://fb.me/GYCnKVPD     
    
    
    @HRTVHORSESPORTS 10:30AM ET 2day #IREunbridled Eleanor Dwan @ the Mt Juliet Estate in Kilkenny Ireland: http://youtu.be/m0ynGpKaEe0  via @youtube    
    
    
    “If you don't stick to your values when they are being tested, they're not values: they're hobbies.” -- Jon... http://fb.me/1UkoNBtZ6     
    
    
    Where did 2,439,000 horses--almost 500,000 horses per year for the past five years--go? http://fb.me/1TEecHTGT     
    
    
    #natpe 2011 begins, learning so much already. Fantastic! http://twitgoo.com/1tvvyx    
    
    
    Rocking at #natpe with Daryl Hall! http://twitgoo.com/1tx7yw    
    
    
    Beef lasagne found to contain up to 100 per cent horse meat ... and so it goes in the Land of The Horse .... so... http://fb.me/WlOV86iN     
    
    
    And yet the breeding without a plan continues..... http://fb.me/1KHDaIvhf     
    
    
    Here is something I would have never guessed --- is this a scam? Did every LinkedIn member receive this accolade? http://fb.me/2rOklcngj     
    
    
    OK -- did you all get this too??? Hurray! I have one of the top 10% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. http://www.linkedin.com/pub/profile/0/728/3b7?trk=200tw …    
    
    
    the reality of numbers in horseracing -- Moran: Addition by subtraction http://espn.go.com/horse-racing/story/_/id/8917928/addition-subtraction …    
    
    
    RACHEL UPDATE: Updated Release on Rachel Alexandra’s Procedure and Current Condition...
 
After foaling Rachel... http://fb.me/1Tc2xg85t     
    
    
    Someone chose to breed each one of these horses....Where are the "breeders" now? http://fb.me/1yriFxKSO     
    
    
    History repeats itself .... why do we eat cows, pigs, chicken, and bison -- each of which have the same desire to... http://fb.me/2sgyzswb0     
    
    
    WHY HASN'T BREEDING BEEN BANNED? http://fb.me/AXf08R0s     
    
    
    This is why Unbridled stopped racing and breeding. People this is what happens to the majority of thoroughbreds... http://fb.me/2IdmXHXI2     
    
    
    Together the louder we can shout to be the horses' voice, the more chance we'll have to put an end to this... http://fb.me/28BOa9kGB     
    
    
    DOG TREAT RECALL -- READ TO PROTECT YOUR BELOVED PETS FROM SICKNESS: http://fb.me/2ADlsZP8W     
    
    
    DOG TREAT RECALL - MULTIPLE BRANDS - READ TO PROTECT YOUR BELOVED PETS FROM SALMONELLA, READ: http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-recall/kasel-recalls-numerous-brands-of-dog-treats-due-to-salmonella/ …    
    
    
    “Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn't do than by the ones you did. So... http://fb.me/1JMUY5nxA     
    
    
    Here is a refreshing quote from one of our leaders, sometimes the loneliest place of all is standing on... http://fb.me/2ueC21TcQ     
    
    
    China exports the most horse meat to the global market: http://fb.me/2OnFZPl5T     
    
    
    Fellow equine TV hostess  Darley Newman  gets the cover of this month's Chronicle Connection.... once you get... http://fb.me/1zuskxwEQ     
    
    
    hey.....it's all vegan ;)! http://amzn.com/k/HLzPQbJXTZiegTp1TG6now … Beer, then later bread, were the inspiration for modern civilization.    
    
    
    “The longest journey you will ever take is the 18 inches from your head to your heart.” Andrew Bennett (born 1939); British politician    
    
    
    This is an excellent article.  The author asks great questions.... http://fb.me/2GlFdkTBP     
    
    
    Love Hot Yoga Saratoga! http://fb.me/2f8jVszMB     
    
    
    I do not understand how or why being adorned in dead animal skins makes one feel good about themselves or serves... http://fb.me/1lKDKm3Fa     
    
    
    DEAD ANIMAL SKINS, A FASHION STATEMENT... Seriously! Beyonce: Stop making exotic animal skins cool. via @Care2 http://www.thepetitionsite.com/123/599/293/ask-beyonce-to-stop-using-exotic-animal-skins-to-make-shoes/ …    
    
    
    Urge NIH to Retire All Government-Owned Chimpanzees to Sanctuary - The Humane Society of the United. http://fb.me/Cf7dd4XN     
    
    
    Experience the raw beauty of Eire's westcoast on horseback watch the Connemara Trail 8:30PM/ET WED @HRTVHORSESPORTS pic.twitter.com/yhzRhOgHxv    
    
    
    My guy...can't wait for Season 2 of The Newsroom! http://fb.me/1ZGupTYiv     
    
    
    Health is a choice ... http://fb.me/weczWVE8     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1DYwhh2ic     
    
    
    ME...In The Field w/ Mark Molloy @ blissful Crossogue House in bucolic Tipperary, Ireland: http://youtu.be/9Z6g6bqfLMY  via @youtube    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2vWETDNlZ     
    
    
    Fond memories in Tipperary...... http://fb.me/27eG164Wy     
    
    
    For all my farrier friends...thinking about Calgary? Here is a peak at what you are in for! Practice,... http://fb.me/1cB0YKkMe     
    
    
    The unconscionable acts of humanity to the beautiful creatures we charge ourselves with looking after never... http://fb.me/222bLE5wg     
    
    
    Check this out in Grand Central Station in NY -- sooo totally cool...love it! http://vimeo.com/58803818  http://fb.me/2hlTpoktk     
    
    
    FDA...Franken-Food & Death Administrators... http://fb.me/1XQNRuq6q     
    
    
    @TheResident so happy you are on the air daily!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2i3h1q3R9     
    
    
    “Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed citizens can change the world; indeed, it's the only thing that ever has” M. Mead    
    
    
    @cookingquinoa @alyssarimmer wow... what an awesome combo..luv the texture too! delish, delish, delish...thank you Wendy xo    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2ibB3mG12     
    
    
    Little Girl Cat all grown up!    
    
    
    Any change in a single dewdrop becomes reflected in the whole....the secret dharma of women Justine Musk http://fb.me/Flivs4v0     
    
    
    The best Easter honors the bunny .... try some delicious recipes that don't require animals.... http://fb.me/223cKLo0o     
    
    
    5 Recipes to Veganize Your Easter Brunch Menu http://www.care2.com/greenliving/5-recipes-to-veganize-your-easter-brunch-menu.html …    
    
    
    Join me at the @IrishNatStud on @HRTV at 10 PM ET 2nite, 1 AM ET Sunday. Tour the grounds, meet the stallions, see real Irish horse heroes!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/I4Slc5pp     
    
    
    NZ looking after OTTBs.... http://fb.me/2rimfHJQK     
    
    
    We lost a great creative genius in Phil Ramone...he made beautiful music for the masses, may he now be among the... http://fb.me/1YDxBFSIN     
    
    
    please... http://fb.me/17kbtuhiH     
    
    
    Beautiful filly with a big heart, like her daddy Wild Desert ;)! Congratulations to all connections. http://fb.me/2j4STbUqs     
    
    
    Only in New York kids....gotta love this..... http://fb.me/23PLRFVh8     
    
    
    Every year thousands of people die. Sometimes it’s expected and sometimes it’s not. When these people die, they... http://fb.me/1X8yeDMvW     
    
    
    Not surprising.... http://fb.me/2T8IFymXY     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/16wZkPyLB     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/TDlQ3xlj     
    
    
    SO SAD, SO YOUNG: Roger Ebert Dead: Chicago Sun-Times Film Critic Passes Away at Age 70 http://huff.to/14Hsrqv  via @Moviefone    
    
    
    "Cats can work out mathematically the exact place to sit that will cause most inconvenience."- Pam Brown .... YA THINK!!!!!    
    
    
    A Life and Death Plea for HELP from our Braying Buddies http://fb.me/Ahjgxsid     
    
    
    diabolical... http://fb.me/21pmWBD3e     
    
    
    INTERESTING: From strip clubs to theaters, Google Glass won't be welcome everywhere http://www.nbcnews.com/technology/technolog/strip-clubs-theaters-google-glass-wont-be-welcome-everywhere-1B9231620 … via @NBCNewsTech    
    
    
    SO SAD: BBC News - Ex-Prime Minister Baroness Thatcher dies http://bbc.in/16HWcnt     
    
    
    Friends for a lifetime filled with love. http://fb.me/2g0JNQxdy     
    
    
    Have you ever.... http://fb.me/zi3mB2mx     
    
    
    Gorgeous beauty with a lifetime of love to give an adopting human. http://fb.me/2j4dURQVd     
    
    
    Important issue facing all New Yorkers... http://fb.me/zPXXWS15     
    
    
    Debunking the protein myth...one veggie at a time, read on... http://fb.me/PWuG8tg0     
    
    
    Enormously fun and for a good cause Old Friends thanks again to Susan Salk for yet another great bit of blogging! http://fb.me/K1KgFPR8     
    
    
    Penn Kill Buyers revealed -- spread the word, protect your horses... http://fb.me/1ARd6SzSM     
    
    
    SHARE: Penn Kill Buyers revealed -- spread the word, protect your horses.. http://fb.me/14uyW0ruL     
    
    
    Speaks for itself..... http://fb.me/2jzVXwUbh     
    
    
    “It was only a sunny smile, and little it cost in the giving, but like morning light it scattered the night and... http://fb.me/ssqFD7W9     
    
    
    This duo won the International Grand Prix at the Dublin Horse Show in 1960! David Broome and Sunslave. http://fb.me/2ESyDPNKn     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2iUHa41aG     
    
    
    INSPIRATION: "You cannot hit a target you cannot see" How Daymond John Billion $$$ Biz frm His Liv'g Rm: http://youtu.be/TieCr9CW7so  via @youtube    
    
    
    Please help if you can. I adopted 5 death row kitties in July 2012 and they are a total joy. http://fb.me/OMsJ2Myi     
    
    
    Beautiful kitties -- adopt or foster if you can help. Please share. http://fb.me/2NrdUlJOB     
    
    
    Words of wisdom.... http://fb.me/TMTVEiv3     
    
    
    This works! I cover my cats with this mix and NO Ticks latch on. http://fb.me/1qlKkYukF     
    
    
    Dear friends… Last year I adopted five cats from NYC ACC, it has been one of the most rewarding experiences I've... http://fb.me/2juJ0wHK5     
    
    
    TODAY: 3PM !!!! Exciting day for Writers | The Pulitzer Prizes | 2013 Winners and Finalists announced April 15 http://www.pulitzer.org/node/8501     
    
    
    Heather Brandt, Leah Halsdorf, Erin Looman ... a remembrance of our friend. http://fb.me/OY9yUEiz     
    
    
    Friends, Speak-up for horses.... http://fb.me/2qa3N63pS     
    
    
    To all my starving artist and soon-to-be-published friends....we are not alone... http://fb.me/2XzOtBVUa     
    
    
    <3ichokes...love them! http://fb.me/23xkDsBEg     
    
    
    Animals in need.... http://fb.me/ET1RR0mR     
    
    
    Blissful morning with friends James Kullander et al in my favorite little town on the Hudson Tivoli, New York.... http://fb.me/NpPlZSYa     
    
    
    A gift from the earth ..... http://fb.me/23ckwmfcY     
    
    
    Snowed in, 12 inches so far, watching Courage Under Fire with my Honey.    
    
    
    @LFDHcom Met Daryl in person, real deal, authentic in every way. Great to see LFDH growing on the networks. Thanks for the picture !!    
    
    
    I subscribed to LiveFromDarylsHouse's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/LiveFromDarylsHouse?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2VT0L681X     
    
    
    EVENT ALERT: SPEAK-UP FOR HORSES -- THIS WEEKEND at  Equine Advocates... http://fb.me/SYIzvKFO     
    
    
    Profoundly poignant..... http://fb.me/2j7M5wrVf     
    
    
    Colt and running Horses at Trader Joe's in Albany, New York...getting ready to celebrate Saratoga Race Course... http://fb.me/Qq0PogEs     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/19NgSsWow     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/C7y6S8jg     
    
    
    CAT LOVER ALERT!!! BOOK REVIEW: Good Grief, Tibby: Wendy MacNaughton And Caroline Paul's  http://www.lareviewofbooks.org/article.php?id=1565&fulltext=1#.UXu9DKV2m_M.twitter …    
    
    
    CAT LOVERS MUST READ!!!! Lost Cat is an incredibly endearing work, a snapshot of the madness of loving and... http://fb.me/1IdPrqu0E     
    
    
    KaChing, KaChing..... http://fb.me/1uCAfPRwG     
    
    
    Speaks to the desperation of many --- we live in the best of times and the worst of times... real meaning is hard... http://fb.me/2fYKRwEP9     
    
    
    “If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way.” 
~ Napoleon Hill (1883-1970); motivational author http://fb.me/HJ7diwxO     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1JfbMaJPw     
    
    
    DIET SODA DRINKS contain an artificial sweetener known as aspartame, which is broken down into phenylalanine,... http://fb.me/1xgdLKaRB     
    
    
    HOW TO WRITE COPY THAT GOES VIRAL by Seth Godin

The best thing is to not try to write things that will go viral.... http://fb.me/1Eh8BYFlv     
    
    
    Inspirational lady .... http://fb.me/1jMKVaKhe     
    
    
    “Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be... http://fb.me/1ZI6Syt0J     
    
    
    Favorite healthy food photo of the day:  http://drweil.smugmug.com/DrWeilsDailyLife/My-Organic-Vegetable-Garden-in/15513814_2aWLj#1161984344_HWHaq …    
    
    
    What a great way to turn a wrong into a right...way to go Jeffrey... http://fb.me/AIOW36X7     
    
    
    Study: Why Seahorses Look Like Horses http://aol.it/hCpkVQ  via @AOL    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://youtu.be/UeSA2j4oiDA?a    
    
    
    Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UeSA2j4oiDA … via @youtube You rock Ellen xoxo! Read EatingAnimals, Watch Earthlings    
    
    
    I favorited a YouTube video -- Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://youtu.be/UeSA2j4oiDA?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- @katiecouric: Ellen DeGeneres http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a    
    
    
    I favorited a YouTube video -- @katiecouric: Ellen DeGeneres http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a    
    
    
    Great dialogue, two amazing women. THank you Katie & Ellen! (YouTube http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a)    
    
    
    I subscribed to KatieCouric's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/KatieCouric?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to RawRadiantHealth's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/RawRadiantHealth?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    TV ALERT: TUES, THURS, FRI on HRTV watch my interview with the amazing Anne Kursinski at HITS Horse Shows. Anne... http://fb.me/2qomOesIi     
    
    
    Getting ready for the official debut of Unbridled TV[2013] on HRTV 10 PM ET THURSDAY. 1st episode features Anne... http://fb.me/TiRNWP68     
    
    
    A Horseman and a Gentleman -- thanks NYRA for bringing us this treasure of a ... (YouTube http://youtu.be/8rLoVbLJEVA?a)    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- John Nerud "Lasting Impressions" - The Breeders' Cup (Part 2) http://youtu.be/8rLoVbLJEVA?a    
    
    
    “Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.”
Sir Winston Churchill... http://fb.me/2GWYkbFsx     
    
    
    Watch my interview with Anne Kursinski online at HRTV... http://fb.me/1mPcyAnJG     
    
    
    TV ALERT TONIGHT: 10PM ET join me on #UnbridledTV in conversation w/ iconic show jumper Anne Kursinski on @HRTVHORSESPORTS  Tune-In & Enjoy!    
    
    
    Starry-eyed...my interview with Todd Pletcher at Saratoga...hard to believe it was ten years ago!... http://fb.me/2AP93Msy4     
    
    
    For all my DIEt soda drinking friends..... http://fb.me/2H7TkvfAw     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1OcjvIyNm     
    
    
    I don't remember my father, he passed when I was 1 1/2 years onto this planet. I think of him often, and can only... http://fb.me/1HFUgqMiF     
    
    
    “Go confidently in the direction of your dreams! Live the life you've imagined.”
Henry David Thoreau (1817-1862);... http://fb.me/27tQSU8IC     
    
    
    A gal after my own heart... http://fb.me/33JXpJg6j     
    
    
    Brooke Burke-Charvet: My Cats 'Rule the House' http://www.people.com/people/pets/article/0,,20708696,00.html …    
    
    
    My suspicions confirmed...haven't used a microwave in 25 years...... http://fb.me/1B4AeIv0F     
    
    
    PLEASE read, act, and share..... http://fb.me/2qR4nCd9F     
    
    
    A trip down memory lane...I visited with Merv at this property --- the barns and sheds had mosaic chandeliers! It... http://fb.me/NUVqrI6k     
    
    
    PLEASE READ, ACT, AND SHARE.... http://fb.me/1L9MJkgmn     
    
    
    PETITION ALERT: Remove humane officer that shot kittens in front of children from his position  https://www.change.org/petitions/remove-humane-officer-that-shot-kittens-in-front-of-children-from-his-position?share_id=yHemXMDfKP&utm_campaign=twitter_link_action_box&utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=share_petition … via @change    
    
    
    “Be fearless. Have the courage to take risks. Go where there are no guarantees. Get out of your comfort zone even... http://fb.me/2lGrGZV0g     
    
    
    I took the pledge. Will you? http://fb.me/2erFBwHbs     
    
    
    ATTN: CRazy Cat Lady Friends....purrrfect summer fashion top is in the house, check it out.... http://fb.me/CX2meR4l     
    
    
    En route to slaughter...purposefully bred, INNOCENT horses....WHERE are their "Breeders" NOW? http://fb.me/2IBZzGBBu     
    
    
    Best place to practice, and smarten up too ;) --  Hot Yoga Saratoga http://fb.me/6na2WdMEh     
    
    
    Nearsighted as I am I have tried all of the solutions short of Lasik surgery ... BioTrue is definitely the best... http://fb.me/VOoBMsQq     
    
    
    “Compassion is the keen awareness of the interdependence of all things.”
Thomas Merton (1915-1968); theologian,... http://fb.me/6n8Kk8L1G     
    
    
    INCREDIBLE EDIBLE VEGAN MAC + CHEEZE: Vegan Panko-Crusted Mac + Cheeze  http://veganmiam.com/recipes/vegan-panko-crusted-mac-cheeze …    
    
    
    THE TRUTH ABOUT PATRIOTISM: The #1 Reason to Eat a Veggie Dog on July 4th http://huff.to/1cwdjvw  via @HuffPostGreen    
    
    
    ShyBoy's favorite place...an arm's length to my computer, coffee, and box of work! http://fb.me/1hCXik44L     
    
    
    TOO FUNNY! http://fb.me/LOUHSbhl     
    
    
    OMG!!!! My kinda sweet treat..... http://fb.me/6kjHwACQ8     
    
    
    One year ago today I rescued 5 cats from death at Manhattan AC & C thanks to a post by Pets on Death Row - Urgent... http://fb.me/2GlymkHug     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/MXhqpSzG     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1x7as9MGO     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2e0ER2WDV     
    
    
    GIRLFRIENDS MUST_READ! Obesogens: Poser Hormones that Make You Fat | Healthy Bitch Daily http://www.healthybitchdaily.com/2013/07/09/obesogens-poser-hormones-that-make-you-fat/?utm_source=Healthy+Bitch+Daily&utm_campaign=a58b190238-Dirty_Dirty_Diet_Soda5_6_2013&utm_medium=email&utm_term=0_cdc09a4e44-a58b190238-182851541 …    
    
    
    LADIES ALERT .... Please read and share..... http://fb.me/2qvMPvwAW     
    
    
    Yum, yum, tis the season..... http://fb.me/1XOTzV1id     
    
    
    Four-legged friends in need...pls help if can <3 http://fb.me/2GgYgmqaS     
    
    
    “Again, you can't connect the dots looking forward; you can only connect them looking backwards. So you have to... http://fb.me/2wqNDsE7F     
    
    
    @GGGranola 1 - 4 PM samples at @HWFC stop-in and taste how cereal should really dance on the palette. Healthy, delectable, delicious :)    
    
    
    Big day for @GGGranola Squirrel Bait at @HWFC - exhausted, I got the last bite! Great granola, local, organic, FRESH. pic.twitter.com/WPz99kowr7    
    
    
    Whooped from serving up Gatherer's Granola at Honest Weight Food Co-op today. I got the last crunch of vegan... http://fb.me/KwMuU7uq     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1CvGql3GI     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2Zmujbg0P     
    
    
    @Complexions love Complexions Spa, appreciate the girls Klara and Valerie making me look so pretty ;)! -- back in a week to my place of Zen.    
    
    
    “Take a stand for what's right. Raise a ruckus and make a change. You may not always be popular, but you'll be... http://fb.me/2uqnt2CwO     
    
    
    I don't like to fly .... but this is a really amazing video from the cockpit of humongous A380's first landing at... http://fb.me/2MiHdHzJK     
    
    
    GREAT INTERVIEW Kathy Stevens    Catskill Animal Sanctuary LISTEN & SHARE <3 http://fb.me/2bH5X52eS     
    
    
    GREAT INTERVIEW -- PLEASE SHARE!!!!! 51% Show #1252 Kathy Sevens #Vegan Catskill Animal Sanctuary http://bit.ly/14ZkKdw  via @WAMCRadio    
    
    
    Great info for more effective workout......<3 this guy! http://fb.me/26pr7HAJl     
    
    
    “Faith is daring to put your dream to the test. It is better to try to do something and fail than to try to do... http://fb.me/OAllwNiC     
    
    
    "It's OK to be wrong about yourself" Debbie Ford in session @Omega 2008. 

“Rather than admit a mistake, nations... http://fb.me/11rPrpWLg     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/ETh5fUTe     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6qLMIXJo1     
    
    
    When you find vibrational alignment with You, you personally thrive. You feel good; you look good; you have... http://fb.me/IydM6haF     
    
    
    Your permanent record .....

"I'm going to record this conversation, okay?"

How Nixonian! The idea of being... http://fb.me/1POaD0A1G     
    
    
    Never stop and take a snapshot of what you think your life IS... from a vantage point of it not being what you... http://fb.me/Xo3Npffl     
    
    
    @TierraFarm @HWFC BEST PLACE 2 GO NUTS! Customers <3 CASHEWS. Garlic/Herb sold out :). Restocked now :).  So good :) pic.twitter.com/YKwaSPfv2X    
    
    
    I posted 10 photos on Facebook in the album "Honest Weight Food Coop 07.26.2013" http://fb.me/1rQJD2Z6D     
    
    
    A new visitor on the cat tower! Did you know it’s National Moth Week...it is, for real! Primitive moths appeared... http://fb.me/1LZIGiJRI     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2b4St0ftH     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6pjoUot3e     
    
    
    My friend LenKu aka MeatMan...with me the Vegan! At Honest Weight Food Co-op we all get along ;) <3! http://fb.me/Q3XhlYSe     
    
    
    Happiness for Indoor Kitties is just a pot away, have a look..... http://fb.me/2LuDuoaXB     
    
    
    Thank you to all who care enough to speak up, speak out, and live the change this world so desperately needs .... http://fb.me/Ip5SX3ac     
    
    
    FOOD FOR THOUGHT: So because we can,  should we? http://fb.me/2WL9Tz2SJ     
    
    
    “Turn your face to the sun and the shadows fall behind you.”
Maori proverb http://fb.me/1oyyjEdqI     
    
    
    I posted 19 photos on Facebook in the album "Wedding Day Memories on Our 4th Anniversary" http://fb.me/GN91UBTy     
    
    
    I posted 35 photos on Facebook in the album "Elsbree Family Annual Picnic" http://fb.me/39YFe1q0S     
    
    
    Staking out the future........ http://fb.me/2I2s8TNnD     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1GbTPvDWA     
    
    
    Thank you friends for the Birthday wishes <3. Happy to report it was an enjoyable one .... hard to fathom how... http://fb.me/2IFaL5C4Q     
    
    
    One of my very favorite quotes: “You must be the change you wish to see in the world...” Mohandas Karamchand... http://fb.me/X4R10Hgy     
    
    
    “Getting over a painful experience is much like crossing monkey bars. You have to let go at some point in order... http://fb.me/2nAl23sLv     
    
    
    BEAUTIFUL: This Doctor Welcomes New Babies to the World by Doing the Sweetest Thing, Aww - Cute Video http://www.godvine.com/This-Doctor-Welcomes-New-Babies-to-the-World-by-Doing-the-Sweetest-Thing-Aww-3800.html#.UhC5esQxaTg.twitter …    
    
    
    Funny, and.....very true...From a house 7 feline rulers! http://fb.me/2ZbLsxSnt     
    
    
    Yet another reason to Go Vegan and say NO to Hydro-F**cking!.......... http://fb.me/1EDFdZOr6     
    
    
    “To be beautiful means to be yourself. You don’t need to be accepted by others. You need to accept yourself.”... http://fb.me/2cO7M6hYR     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/YA9xKEWP     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1I6Mv2IpY     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/IG530Zao     
    
    
    LIGHTING DEAL FOR KITTIES!!! I just bought: 'Drinkwell 360 Pet Fountain, Stainless Steel' by Drinkwell via @amazon http://www.amazon.com/dp/B002SB91QS/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_asp_sKD3G.05JKDZ9 …    
    
    
    We are what we pretend to be, so we must be careful what we pretend to be.
~Kurt Vonnegut [My Favorite Writer!]... http://fb.me/2kmdkP7Yi     
    
    
    Horse trainer arrested in Stillwater http://fb.me/OENmftkz     
    
    
    THIS IS LOVE...... http://fb.me/15L9EfrNt     
    
    
    @BeaElliott AWESOME MOVIE - @EarthlingsMovie HELP MAKE IT HAPPEN @kickstarter - PROVOKED: Unity for All Earthlings http://beaelliott.blogspot.com/2013/06/unity-for-all-earthlings.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    What's fashionable about wearing dead foals? Friends, step-up and sign this petition..... I did.... http://fb.me/2FRWMJn0v     
    
    
    Sailing in the The Hudson Valley beautiful night on the River with Friends.... http://fb.me/1lYMqBiyH     
    
    
    Light-hearted fun.... http://youtu.be/czEwBbaDce8  Angie Airdo http://fb.me/1E4pPrguC     
    
    
    Amazing woman....paved the way for so many ladies in finance....RIP <3.... http://fb.me/2ONSI3f3P     
    
    
    Friends, please join me to help make a world of difference for beautiful, intelligent pigs.  I signed the... http://fb.me/12xzLBYwY     
    
    
    Join me to MAKE A DIFFERENCE FOR BEAUTIFUL, INTELLEGENT PIGS... Do it! #helpfarmanimals today: http://bit.ly/13xbdx3  via @HumaneSociety    
    
    
    "You are always communicating something about who you are and your belief in your own value. If you do not find... http://fb.me/14k7pC2G9     
    
    
    Please share.....animals need homes NOW <3 http://fb.me/2X4tHlpjz     
    
    
    :/ such a kind sweet man ..... be in peace Mr. Touhey <3 http://fb.me/N3gGYz1G     
    
    
    @Venuseswilliams great interview on @YESNetwork Center Stage.    
    
    
    Our deepest fear is not that we are inadequate. Our deepest fear is that we are powerful beyond measure. It is our... http://fb.me/XRoDLHBv     
    
    
    Beautiful <3....must read.... http://fb.me/2loznXkDk     
    
    
    QUOTE: “Set your life on fire. Seek those who fan your flames.” Jalal ad-Din Rumi (1207-1273); Persian poet, mystic    
    
    
    an inside voice for horses...... http://fb.me/KtZY4A4p     
    
    
    PERSPECTIVE: enjoying recollections of Margaret and Edward Gehrke of Nebraska on @WMHTPubMedia touring National Parks.....IT'S YOURS!!!!    
    
    
    @JennyOzLeRoy @DANNIJO so pretty xo    
    
    
    HOME HEALTH ALERT: 12 highly toxic chemicals to banish from ur home, another reason for the rise in cancer in pets!  http://j.mp/19oIsBa     
    
    
    STOP THE ROUNDUP OF WILD HORSES ACROSS THE NAVAJO RESERVATION NOW http://fb.me/2dd3zmLtS     
    
    
    Just bought my ticket to @CASanctuary #Shindig http://casanctuary.org/getinvolved/programs/events-list/shindig-a-festival-of-vegan-living/ … get yours today for a great #vegan day in the #catskills    
    
    
    ARROGANCE AND INDIFFERENCE: Etsy, Stop Promoting “Pony Skin” products, the Skins of Slaughtered http://fb.me/1tzfWk8YL     
    
    
    So excited. Headed to #Bcon2013 [A NY State of Crime] with worlds best sweets in hand from @LifeByChocolate learning to WRITE the WRONGS!    
    
    
    @Elizjhaynes thanks for your time at #Bcon2013 today. I learned so much from you and the forensics team ;)! Much appreciated.    
    
    
    @pchorsedoc what is this about? Any action taken to help horses?    
    
    
    Thrilled to meet one of my real life heroes @ #Bcon2013 the incredible @thatMarciaClark I'm reading Killer Ambition! pic.twitter.com/wDa6GaKPRj    
    
    
    Met featured #Bcon2013 author @SaraJHenry thanks to @MarkVLaPolla who charged me to deliver @LifeByChocolate sweets. pic.twitter.com/OB534ItuAk    
    
    
    I just bought: 'Black Fridays: A Novel by Michael Sears  via @amazonkindle. Met @MSearsAuthor at #BCon2013 today! http://www.amazon.com/dp/B007T8G3WU/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_ask_0zCDG.0K1AJXN …    
    
    
    @NorbVonnegut great to meet you today at #Bcon2013 thanks for sharing your experiences on the panel this AM. Appreciated your candid advice.    
    
    
    On the phone bank at my favorite radio station today @WAMCRadio call in and pledge to keep the best news and info on the air #WAMC    
    
    
    Yay! Made the halfway mark @wamcradio <3 #wamc I am here to take your call for the stretch run 1-800-323-9262! pic.twitter.com/erXwKBjpVc    
    
    
    My writing hero KURT VONNEGUT: The Importance of Creating Desire | The New York Writers’ Intensive http://newyorkwritersintensive.com/the-importance-of-creating-desire/ …    
    
    
    Fantastic article. Be sure to read Gilbert King's 5 practical writing tips at the end. No matter what stage of devel…http://lnkd.in/buvFrsb     
    
    
    #FEMME Sharon Stone & @marwilliamson  on @piersmorgan NOW..Are u watching? POWERFUL women, great document'y, watch FEMME meet amaz'g people.    
    
    
    Here is link to trailer #FEMME Women Healing The World http://youtu.be/0u3HOxsbUMU  watch, share, be empowered and be INSPIRED! Your work matters.    
    
    
    This stylish hat could be yours! David models live from the #WAMC studio. Call now 1-800-323-9262. pic.twitter.com/3n2b7z4uTN    
    
    
    @WAMCradio #nightcrew Ian Pickus in the house!    
    
    
    @WAMCRADIO #nightcrew Ian Pickups on the air. Tune in #wamc pic.twitter.com/fVmwFCnDip    
    
    
    C'mon friends lets end the @WAMCradio fund drive 2day with Joe and Selma 1-800-323-9262 pic.twitter.com/sKhEwrghus    
    
    
    Familiar voices behind the mic at @wamcradio fund drive. On the air now. Tune in #wamc 1-800-323-9262 pic.twitter.com/RMvSkMQkxT    
    
    
    The very sexy @wamcradio #nightcrew hottie Ian Pickus modeling #wamc hoodie behind the mic. Tune in now. pic.twitter.com/z4a9kcZVNw    
    
    
    NOT TOO LATE: Crossogue House in Thurles, Cty Tipperary, Ire -http://www.jetsetextra.com/destinations/europe/ireland/thurles/crossogue-house-in-thurles-county-tipperary-ireland …    
    
    
    Incredible new salad @HWFC. Butternut with Kale and Pomegranate. Stop in and try a sample until 1pm today! pic.twitter.com/DqzbH7U4gp    
    
    
    Must read "life-saving" article. "As a society we have to find the means to underwrite reporting of this magnitude."…http://lnkd.in/b8CVqAx     
    
    
    ENOUGH SAID: Wryly charming, impeccably acted, and ultimately quite bittersweet, Enough Said is a grown-up movie in the best possible way.    
    
    
    Was all set for a night of Rockin' in Albany...but :/, sadly, under the weather on this beautiful day, so I am... http://fb.me/MkM1Mt3f     
    
    
    @nythoroughbred sadly, horses met their ends all over the country http://horseracingwrongs.com/2013/10/13/breakdown-saturday/ …    
    
    
    The neighbors.....left off my fav Jann Wenner! http://fb.me/2z3sZ53zT     
    
    
    The neighbors...... http://lnkd.in/bYvEfeN     
    
    
    MUST READ FOR HORSE and PET OWNERS: Euthansia...The Right Time? http://wp.me/p2mXR0-1kK  via @HClemenceau    
    
    
    GIRL POWER! LOVE THIS Women Over 60 & Beautiful...[stunning, gorgeous, inspirational!!!] http://huff.to/1cJqnA4  via @HuffPostCeleb    
    
    
    MUST WATCH FUN Dogs and Cats VIDEO: Compilation of Cats Stealing Dog Beds http://www.pawbonito.com/compilation-of-cats-stealing-dogs-bed/ … via @pawbonito    
    
    
    Well.....this should be interesting! Thanks Jyl DeGiovine !!! http://fb.me/2p1MITjRw     
    
    
    know where your pet food comes from.... http://fb.me/6tn7XyR03     
    
    
    http://fb.me/18uqJZYBj     
    
    
    About 27 percent of the seafood Americans eat comes from China — and the shipments that the FDA checks are... http://fb.me/19445OC67     
    
    
    Watching #HeroDogAwards on @hallmarkchannel @BettyMWhite Amazing four-legged TRUE stories. Tune in!    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2DZvzThDE     
    
    
    Emily, my sweet companion rescued as an itty bitty kitty from death at NYC AC&C near a year and a half ago via... http://fb.me/6uhTPObbK     
    
    
    "What does the meat industry give us? “Food” we don’t need, that is [.....] & supports horrid abuse" Bruce Friedrich. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/bruce-friedrich/does-eating-meat-support-_b_773166.html …    
    
    
    TIME TO WRITE: NaNoWriMo Tip #1: Establish a Writing Schedule http://www.mediabistro.com/galleycat/nanowrimo-tip-1-establish-a-writing-schedule_b79612 … via @galleycat    
    
    
    YES!!! Still time to plant Garlic! Read, dig, and reap..... http://fb.me/2JAs111G1     
    
    
    SAFETY ALERT: Cats and Car Wheels....tis' the season....tap hood, look under wheels, and please start off... http://fb.me/2LpDD2PcU     
    
    
    Sunday Joys: Enjoying one of my all time faves FIRST WIVES CLUB before delving into @mroachsmith's The Memoir Project!    
    
    
    Contemplating the meaning of this perplexing poem "Tell All The Truth" by Emily Dickson, just learned of it while... http://fb.me/2ZjBsvrjT     
    
    
    Just in from the garden, got my garlic bulbs planted thanks to a reminder by A Way to Garden, from Margaret Roach!    
    
    
    PACK OF TWO by Caroline Knapp on http://audible.com  : Behind the Scenes with Hilary Swank http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R4h7_sN3BqE&sns=tw … via @youtube    
    
    
    Everything begins with a word on a page...what's your story today? pic.twitter.com/zZh6GNQD1K    
    
    
    Are you separated from that which you are called to? What completes you that you are not doing?  A Way to Garden,... http://fb.me/M1eistI5     
    
    
    THE POWER OF SHAME | Writing Lessons: How Vulnerable To Be When Writing Memoir http://marionroach.com/2013/11/how-vulnerable-to-be-when-writing-memoir/ … via @mroachsmith    
    
    
    When Genius Gets Tattoo http://fb.me/1DsWwuWL9     
    
    
    PLASTIC KILLS Time to change. Midway Atoll: Plastic Plight of the Albatross | Pacific Voyagers http://shar.es/IF7th  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Love this woman! "You can’t afford the luxury of a negative thought." ~ Susan Novotny. http://fb.me/LDL4VDrT     
    
    
    “Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will.”
Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi... http://fb.me/NI9NWZjt     
    
    
    Feeding time! http://fb.me/15fGpuMMQ     
    
    
    NEED TO REV-UP YOUR DEAL MAKING MOJO? WATCH: Inventing David Geffen Amazon Instant Video ~ David Geffen http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00AX84C76/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_dp_5T8Esb0G69PTX … via @amazon    
    
    
    "Writing isn't about picking the right topic; it's about finding the right voice." —@JeffGoins http://bit.ly/RssFNs     
    
    
    First paragraph of this heartwarming story in the DRF sums of American thoroughbred racing perfectly: On any... http://fb.me/6zLALni8M     
    
    
    Watching @hallmarkchannel. Dialogue, "What is/was your best day EVER?" I added, "and why?" Heavy stuff for a light-hearted Christmas movie..    
    
    
    Friends at Equine Affaire, Inc. (Official) this is an incredible impassioned account of true love in action. Be... http://fb.me/2IKtbnefr     
    
    
    Friends, 
 
I am reaching out to see if any of you know who enforces the NY Ag & Mkts 353 anti-cruelty statute at... http://fb.me/11akxNpEi     
    
    
    Friends in the saddle have listen here with an open mind..... http://fb.me/OhvxtPXR     
    
    
    Today, I had the privilege of meeting my hero, the beautiful, articulate, and authentic Jo Anne Normile, author... http://fb.me/100sbzEHo     
    
    
    URGENT ACTION NEEDED TODAY: It is extremely urgent that you contact your legislators on Monday and urge them to... http://fb.me/2tFUe5b9Y     
    
    
    ACTION ALERT: Horses & other animals are in danger of losing protections afforded under state animal welfare laws.   http://bit.ly/1fxJXmh     
    
    
    @docfonda @noonan_tom No surprise here, #NYRA has nothing to do with equine safety. Sad for horses, jockeys, and bettors. More $$$$ for vets    
    
    
    Couldn't say it better myself: " The owners, buying and selling at a frenzied and historic rate, are chasing... http://fb.me/2HoPyYhUE     
    
    
    @CVFPartnerships @NYRAwing @docfonda @noonan_tom it's all the same...any of you guys ever see the "morning vet check" --- it is a joke.    
    
    
    A brother to E Dubai....not even his beautiful pedigree could save him.... http://fb.me/6jY0IGT54     
    
    
    $525,000 @KeenelandSales yearling "The Man Himself" [1/2 to E Dubai] DEAD at Parx http://wp.me/p2D6F3-NZ   @horseracingwrongs    
    
    
    Excited to start @TheMemoirProject tonight. ......looking forward to writing the.... http://fb.me/2im1TNQqV     
    
    
    Hmmmm.......doesn't look like my feral cat friend! http://fb.me/2YIu2sUpu     
    
    
    Kitchen helpers...Emmy, Rabbit, Hen! http://fb.me/6tes0GDJo     
    
    
    Incredible read: Let's Take The Long Way Home by Gail Caldwell. Thank you @MRoachSmith pic.twitter.com/CIK4p3ktJk    
    
    
    OTTB REPORT! Thoroughbreds strut their stuff at Equine Affaire  @offtrackhorse http://offtrackthoroughbreds.com/2013/11/14/thoroughbreds-strut-their-stuff-at-equine-affaire/ …    
    
    
    rockin' with heart: Joan Jett Kicked Off Thanksgiving Day Parade Float Because She's A Vegetarian http://huff.to/1bDoIwj  via @HuffPostCeleb    
    
    
    For sure.... http://fb.me/ZpnmBfhx     
    
    
    Ava! http://fb.me/2gmNUR5nX     
    
    
    FRIENDS, I AM NOT INTERESTED IN YOUR DEAD DEER PHOTOS ON MY WALL. IF YOU ARE PROUD OF MURDERING SENTIENT BEINGS... http://fb.me/1RZErhQIy     
    
    
    Not so little Eve, taking over Emmy's post this morning! http://fb.me/2Hz0NbX0U     
    
    
    Happy sisters Eve & Emmy <3 http://fb.me/1aU3RjYFO     
    
    
    Congress, Horseracing, Integrity http://fb.me/6zoVBUdDC     
    
    
    LIVE VIDEO: http://energycommerce.house.gov/hearing/hr-2012-bill-improve-integrity-and-safety-interstate-horseracing-and-other-purposes …    
    
    
    BEST WAY TO ENJOY THANKSGIVING: The Vegan Thanksgiving table http://blog.timesunion.com/animalrights/the-vegan-thanksgiving-table/4302/ …    
    
    
    Dr Sheila Lyons in today's hearing on H.R. 2012. A real horse hero and role model <3. Of the entire panel, she... http://fb.me/2v2v9Zm3F     
    
    
    Throwback Thursday: 1972, Me & My beloved pony SnowFlake, I was 6. Seems like yesterday. http://fb.me/3ePqoAaaR     
    
    
    Justice Department's info on arrests at Penn National: 
http://www.justice.gov/usao/pam/news/2013/PNRC_11_22_2013.htm … http://fb.me/2FADCQKud     
    
    
    SPEAKS FOR ITSELF: Despite the Evidence, Trainers Deny a Doping Problem http://nyti.ms/1dq41HE  #DOPING #HORSERACING    
    
    
    Eve and Emmy enjoying some winter Sun. http://fb.me/2a9gHU0Ym     
    
    
    TRAGIC: Woman chasing loose horses struck and killed by car http://po.st/iuWEWV  via @kslcom    
    
    
    READ, BEWARE, and SHARE....... Amanda Vance, Heather Brandt, Fiona Farrell, Fay Spargo, Capital District... http://fb.me/Lkm2YYx5     
    
    
    Seasonal vegan brunch at home... Came out looking Christmasy! Organic wild rice, pomegranate seeds, last of the... http://fb.me/KXVNvV5d     
    
    
    Emmy! Soaking up some sunshine. Good day to be inside: ) http://fb.me/1760E9eSQ     
    
    
    Shy Boy sacked out ;) http://fb.me/3yzjO8CVe     
    
    
    Emmy helping me read for an audio book rehearsal by keeping the paperwork warm this frigid morning! #Cats http://fb.me/2koH7dgJN     
    
    
    Friends, Please support The American College of Veterinary Sports Medicine and Rehabilitation and Dr. Sheila... http://fb.me/2NnIkxBdO     
    
    
    #ANIMALSWEREHARMED dreadful report: http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/feature/  http://fb.me/6okyzE3oE     
    
    
    Friends of Ireland Unbridled -- right now this book is a free download on Amazon! http://fb.me/6IEE5muX2     
    
    
    OMG...Love this beautiful art...... http://fb.me/3riA0OIeS     
    
    
    Oh yeah....my kinda three-way! @AndrewElsbree where are you?!?! http://fb.me/2uQJ05vcu     
    
    
    How sad, NY-Bred FLIGHT OF FANTASY, daughter of slaughtered NY-resident mare RAVISHLY now dead.... Cardiac event?... http://fb.me/1NmhpveQP     
    
    
    Unreal... http://fb.me/2RlwkBkBL     
    
    
    Old saddle pads make the best cat beds on cold winter days. Emmy is sacked out on my previously prized Hadfield's... http://fb.me/6oSX55uQx     
    
    
    For all my American Farrier's Association friends.. a look back as Reno is just a few months away!... http://fb.me/6mZU0NBgB     
    
    
    I signed to help voice a halt to this unconscionable cruelty ... will you join me? http://fb.me/1V9lHVDWp     
    
    
    Eve's turn today on my once prized Hadfields saddle cloth! http://fb.me/PUac7FCH     
    
    
    Star quality for HRTV! http://fb.me/PZTVEIqF     
    
    
    Handsome fellow, alive and well as he should be. http://fb.me/2iUA8sGKE     
    
    
    Hindsight with a master at his sport.... http://fb.me/6mhIFGOmg     
    
    
    Shy Boy found a quiet corner in the sound studio! http://fb.me/262bzfFE9     
    
    
    Quiet as a mouse ... Shy Boy still passed out in the sound studio! http://fb.me/6xmdSai6B     
    
    
    Tough day in the office for editor Emmy! http://fb.me/X1yh4gqh     
    
    
    Congratulations http://fb.me/1f4T8zPw7     
    
    
    TOO, TOO MUCH! Not even enough coffee by 10AM for this one LOL!!! http://fb.me/2ze0HqiK4     
    
    
    Watching TODAY, waiting for Christie Brinkleys daughter Alexa Ray Joel. Friends, tune-in, listen...beautiful... http://fb.me/159lPsioj     
    
    
    Take a Stand for Animals, join me in supporting a change in their legal status: http://clanimal.com/2013/11/28/petition-favor-specific-legal-status-animals/ …    
    
    
    Loving my Friday night at home getting ready for the snow storm ;) http://fb.me/2XP0H6Ta6     
    
    
    http://twitgoo.com/1zvl2g    
    
    
    FREE KINDLE DOWNLOAD: Common Sense HORSEMANSHIP: A Safe And Simple Approach To Riding Horses by...via @amazonkindle http://www.amazon.com/dp/B00FJI22DG/ref=cm_sw_r_tw_ask_uCCfG.0EX3224 …    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/161vOg0dl     
    
    
    Oh poor kitties stuck inside for the day ;)    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6BgNgy2fQ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1ecZRrgoU     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2LystfFza     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/LativQU9     
    
    
    Friends with Ferals please read and share...Excellent tips from The Humane Society of the United States to help... http://fb.me/3fmFNoScJ     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/24si76rva     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/18cVr6TVs     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2Ux95I84M     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/3iTwgoJ8P     
    
    
    A snowed in Sunday! Got a jump on the work week once I got Chelsea off her favorite spot... What's up with cats & keyboards?    
    
    
    OMG, I have totally become a @hallmarkchannel junkie. Love it that I can always count on the happy endings <3.    
    
    
    Chelsea & Emmy have their eyes on the sweet little birds outside . Note the nice fleece Emmy is a perched on....a... http://fb.me/2aPMtg2C9     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/38hWP5MOa     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/6yP2Sjpts     
    
    
    Oh let it snow let it snow let it snow..... http://fb.me/322tVWr5a     
    
    
    I'm going to save my public voice largely for the issues where I have some depth. ~ Bill Gates    
    
    
    Your mind knows only some things. Your inner voice, your instinct, knows everything. If you listen to what you... http://fb.me/19nnglkZd     
    
    
    Not so little anymore Ava on her chair! http://fb.me/2PuhMMBw1     
    
    
    Takin'the leap into the world of VO! Two audiobooks in production on ACX. Keep me in mind if you have a project I... http://fb.me/2gvC2aCIB     
    
    
    Good Monday morning of Christmas week I hope you all get some R & R as we gear up for 2014 <3. http://fb.me/1IqTi6Zc1     
    
    
    Progress in albany... http://fb.me/1fXSyWkdv     
    
    
    The best gifts in life will never be found under a Christmas tree, those gifts are friends, family, children &... http://fb.me/3cUZxSHU4     
    
    
    Holiday Cheer!!! http://fb.me/1eranPxtg     
    
    
    Emmy and little friend... http://fb.me/2kjWzmhgC     
    
    
    Awesome New Year Celebration. Thank you Len & Jyl DeGiovine <3 http://fb.me/16rbdH61b     
    
    
    With conscience.....excellent read... http://fb.me/15GemsVgq     
    
    
    friends....it only takes a moment..... http://fb.me/1T2nior8H     
    
    
    Beautiful.... http://fb.me/3DeRSZH7p     
    
    
    My wish for all who know life.....“May the sun bring you new energy by day, may the moon softly restore you by... http://fb.me/2lbYk6TTC     
    
    
    Should You Go Vegetarian? 5 Women Who Went Meatless - Prevention.com http://www.prevention.com/health/nutrition/healthy-eating-tips/should-you-go-vegetarian-5-women-who-went-meatless/article/09abab3b786bf210VgnVCM10000030281eac____ …    
    
    
    Nominate an ordinary person doing extraordinary things in the "Hero Next Door" contest @Care2: http://tinyurl.com/yajxde3 #hero    
    
    
    Check out: Great post on Paw Nation! http://bit.ly/5xwWED via @paw_nation    
    
    
    Honor your Horse Care Professionals -- 2010 EQUUS Professional Horseman Award Contest: http://bit.ly/5SVveu via @addthis    
    
    
    You don't need to be sick...The Future Of Food on @hulu: http://www.hulu.com/watch/67878/the-future-of-food …    
    
    
    INSPIRATIONAL TRUE STORY From @walletpopper: http://www.walletpop.com/blog/2010/01/01/joy-mangano-invents-her-way-to-success/    
    
    
    What it's all about http://www.humanesociety.org/news/multimedia/index.html?fr_story=9b0edfc00d7d6d96d1c3db406573f16fe71bbe33    
    
    
    I watched 'For My Wife' and @SnagFilms donated $1 to @TheTaskForce for me! Do the same: http://www.snagfilms.com/films/support_taskforce …    
    
    
    MUST WATCH Morning Joe video: Humane Society Wayne Pacelle -   http://on.msnbc.com/ix3u2d  via @msnbc    
    
    
    SARATOGA RACE COURSE: Retirement funding should come from within racing industry - saratogian.com http://saratogian.com/articles/2011/08/02/sports/doc4e386e86a1a95309005758.txt?viewmode=comments … via @Saratogian_news    
    
    
    Congratulations Kevin, well-deserved win! Enjoy. (YouTube http://youtu.be/I9SsOphmx-o?a)    
    
    
    Helmets matter, no matter what ur riding Courtney King Dye's video address - HorseChannel.com: http://www.horsechannel.com/horse-news/2011/07/30/courtney-king-dye-riders4helmets.aspx?cm_mmc=4941116#.TkJsgkH62cU.twitter … via @AddThis    
    
    
    I subscribed to masterlock77's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/masterlock77?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to HorsemartVideos's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/HorsemartVideos?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    My favorite farrier finally on the web, check him out http://www.AndrewElsbree.com  -- the best for all disciplines, sound feet = happy horses!!!    
    
    
    @WilliamShatner Hey Bill -- how about getting Unbridled with Susan Kayne for HRTV. Check out the vids http://www.YouTube.com/UnbridledTV     
    
    
    @Debbie_Ford amen to that!    
    
    
    Getting in the kitchen to make Vegan Thanksliving dishes -- yeah a day of restoration. It's been a rough weekend, had to put ET to sleep :(.    
    
    
    A Vegan Thanksgiving Celebrates Good Food, Activism and Hope http://shar.es/o708E     
    
    
    Must watch b4 u shop 2day http://youtu.be/gLBE5QAYXp8  #BlackFriday    
    
    
    Headed to Pump, Chisel & Sizzle to care of overindulging on vegan thanksgiving!    
    
    
    This Saturday, Greenville, NY - 7 horses shipping in from Saddlebred Rescue http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=S_PSixSTenY&feature=share … via @youtube UnbridledTV will be there.    
    
    
    It’s a shoe-in: Andrew Elsbree & Susan Kayne’s Clermont Farm is known for its expert farrier service http://www.hudsonvalleyalmanacweekly.com/it%e2%80%99s-a-shoe-in-andrew-elsbree-susan-kayne%e2%80%99s-clermont-farm-is-known-for-its-expert-farrier-service/ …    
    
    
    #WarHorse GREAT group of still pics. http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/war_horse/pictures/ … via @RottenTomatoes    
    
    
    Horses Never Forget Human Friends : Discovery News http://news.discovery.com/animals/horse-friends-memory-trainers.html …    
    
    
    Get your Thoroughbred featured on Unbridled! Call for Submissions. http://icont.ac/PkgA     
    
    
    Powerful, meaningful Poems - Eavan Boland: http://youtu.be/UFvVlhKa8O8  via @youtube Famine Roads...I rode on them in Connemara with Willie Leahy.    
    
    
    Another reason I so love horses -- A long ride but it was worth it  - http://bit.ly/aJPFhA via @addthis    
    
    
    in my heart you and Z take top prize always. with empathy xo (YouTube http://youtu.be/iyO3tuwRAIc?a)    
    
    
    Eight-year-old painting prodigy is seen - Yahoo! News Photos http://yhoo.it/ayaZRS    
    
    
    Learning life lessons on Super Soul Sunday with Oprah. Author of Simple Abundance Sarah Ban Breathnach sharing her rise-fall-rise journey!    
    
    
    Cat Adoption Fees Waived, Town Board Meeting - Mineola, NY Patch http://mineola.patch.com/articles/cat-adoption-fees-waived-town-board-meeting … CATS ARE THE BEST PETS, LOYAL, FUN, LOVING :)    
    
    
    Keep away from people who try 2 blittle ur ambitions. Small people always do that, but the really gr8 make U feel that U, 2, can Bcome gr8    
    
    
    Animal cruelty should be a felony in EVERY state. Sign the #NDStopCruelty pledge: http://bit.ly/MaLBuI  (via @HumaneSociety) I SIGNED THIS    
    
    
    things-you-shouldnt-be-paying-for: Personal Finance News from Yahoo! Finance http://yhoo.it/cbfafa    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Unbridled Race Horse Report 20Aug2010 http://youtu.be/XESTCtvCgIg?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Kurt Vonnegut http://youtu.be/x3ikvCT3858?a    
    
    
    Produced By Faith http://www.3lwtv.com/3LWTV/Bookshelf/Entries/2012/7/4_Devon_Franklin_-_Produced_By_Faith.html …    
    
    
    Your VOICE Matters! Speak up for thoroughbreds by liking and commenting on video link. http://icont.ac/1b0Lq     
    
    
    MUST WATCH VIDEO if you have a heartbeat.....Why Vegan? Lessons From An Animal Scientist: http://youtu.be/5ZYQnt-67vs  via @youtube    
    
    
    Russell Brand in the zone on Piers Morgan tonight...bright guy.."i'm like a farmer, my product is a TV show instead of a tomato"    
    
    
    I subscribed to natpe's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/natpe?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to WestPointTBreds's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/WestPointTBreds?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    Carrots have a “secret” weapon against cancer : :: Natural Health 365 :: http://www.naturalhealth365.com/food/carrots.html …    
    
    
    dear friends these three little kitties Ava, Eve, and Emily,  who bless me every day were adopted from death row... http://fb.me/1LRL5xEqa     
    
    
    Speedy at Saratoga this morning with jockey Shaun Bridgmohan in the irons, with commentary by trainer Carlos... http://fb.me/GlpoP9Dn     
    
    
    How many times has that certain something only a horse can offer saved your life? I've lost count.... http://fb.me/2dLZVSBY1     
    
    
    Interesting... http://fb.me/1inJUKBO8     
    
    
    seriously, Victoria's secret would have more business if they would present their lingerie on realistic untouched... http://fb.me/24mJcsouK     
    
    
    Michelle Obama: Tell Barack to honor his campaign promise to label GMOs http://signon.org/s/zSIoy8  @signon    
    
    
    In 2007, Obama promised, “We’ll let folks know whether their food has been genetically modified, because... http://fb.me/19I7ilUAE     
    
    
    My little kitties getting big!  Emily, Ava, and Eve enjoying the warmth of our glorious sunshine this morning. http://fb.me/2m1zVnz0K     
    
    
    Hey friends I'll be attending this. When I learned about people in jeopardy of losing their pets and realized I... http://fb.me/1qilTLfKu     
    
    
    Reader supported jounalism...YES! http://fb.me/1Zn3jOT4l     
    
    
    WOAH! I cant believe you can already see who is viewing your profile! I just saw my Top 10 Profile Viewer and I... http://fb.me/20CotVny4     
    
    
    Time for a change at Saratoga.... http://fb.me/1ZW3JbWo0     
    
    
    Nice article... http://fb.me/GIXUmbQR     
    
    
    Fancy schmancy (did I spell that right?!).... http://fb.me/1CRlWnEkf     
    
    
    My experience with cats give me cause for PAWS.... http://fb.me/2pXqR4oIO     
    
    
    What kind of democracy do we live in ?!?!? Watch ETHOS (Netflix) with Woody Harrelson and Noam Chomsky...and get an education.    
    
    
    What a fancy shoe! http://fb.me/24aGz6smT     
    
    
    EQUINE VACCINATIONS MORE IMPORTANT THAN EVER..... http://fb.me/1BEnEvdOA     
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Thoroughbred Weekly - Trainer Jimmy Jerkens http://youtu.be/DqiU0L3jw0M?a    
    
    
    Congratulations Jimmy -- so happy for you! (YouTube http://youtu.be/DqiU0L3jw0M?a)    
    
    
    “I've come to believe that each of us has a personal calling that's as unique as a fingerprint and that the best... http://fb.me/1SYGH3hus     
    
    
    Meanwhile horses get hurt, the betting public is duped, and veterinarians get rich... http://fb.me/1bH5oCpJU     
    
    
    Mark your calendar! Sept 30th..what a beautiful way to spend a day in the Hudson Valley :)...I'll be there, will you? http://fb.me/24XCp8tcs     
    
    
    another Unbridled headline!… Having been thrice married and twice unbridled I get it… http://fb.me/1TvBbEyaM     
    
    
    WOW....sign of the times...a lot of wonderful coverage over the years from dedicated journalists.... http://fb.me/1ef2EEBtR     
    
    
    I'm famous for my UNBRIDLED life ....... love you Resident! XXOO (YouTube http://youtu.be/ecbbcg5247c?a)    
    
    
    So Excited! Thank you FB friends for your support in getting this out of the editing suite into the limelight on... http://fb.me/1dXRIOQV3     
    
    
    hey friends…  I'm so excited to share with you an all new episode of Ireland Unbridled this coming Monday the 24th... http://fb.me/Eah6Ta4J     
    
    
    Aaaaaah to be the daughter of a rock star! Sweet. I am being sarcastic :). All the best Jessica, I hope you'll sit... http://fb.me/wppOFRVv     
    
    
    A video preview of the next episode of Ireland Unbridled! http://youtu.be/dFjbzXYys78  http://fb.me/1Whrx4xRf     
    
    
    Wow.....quite a connection....and another example of how a horse inspires a human.... http://fb.me/2qqqhpbhD     
    
    
    So sweet... http://fb.me/1if8jG14B     
    
    
    I am so humbled to have had the opportunity to share Bandit's story with the NY Times. It is this type of... http://fb.me/1GnjXIaMd     
    
    
    Wow...it took science to determine that...how arrogant of humanity. http://fb.me/1CUJ6Rz5N     
    
    
    Cian, behind the scenes! http://fb.me/23EmNz9sh     
    
    
    Friends, Bandit is OK. Here are few words with him. Thanks for all of the emails, calls and support. Susan http://fb.me/OymS4QSV     
    
    
    Susan Kayne and Bourbon Bandit: http://youtu.be/IbipL33pxF8  via @youtube Follow up on BB    
    
    
    90 minutes to Ireland Unbridled showtime on the eastcoast. Tune in at 9:30 PM ET on HRTV :)... http://fb.me/1DuOZWWZY     
    
    
    @ss0325JP What does your country do with all the horses that do not race?    
    
    
    “Believe in yourself and all that you are. Know that there is something inside you that is greater than any... http://fb.me/1UXG0Fd7h     
    
    
    In NJ on Saturday? Check this out.....looks like a really fun horse-centric day :)... http://fb.me/1wFcMxfsI     
    
    
    HRTV ALERT: MINNESOTA and KENTUCKY Tune-in to HRTV, The Best Network for Horse Sports. Home to Ireland Unbridled... http://fb.me/1jGRMISQT     
    
    
    REDEMPTION!  the Gov.'s task force  investigation revealed exactly what I experienced with Bourbon Bandit.  Thank... http://fb.me/1VW7VhwBs     
    
    
    Gov. Cuomo making good changes to NY Racing ...Faults Officials in Horse Fatalities at Aqueduct http://nyti.ms/Q7b7BB     
    
    
    “Be not simply good; be good for something.”

Henry David Thoreau (1817-1862); naturalist, author, philosopher    
    
    
    Watching LIVE PRESS CONFERENCE on RACING in NY findings by New York State Office of the Governor http://livestre.am/xXXE  via @livestream    
    
    
    I had the privilege of sharing Bandit's story on WAMC Hud Valley horse owner puts spotlight on drugging http://bit.ly/PL1YyI  via @WAMCRadio    
    
    
    mickeyd8's comment on Aqueduct Racing Officials Faulted in Horse Deaths via @nytimes http://www.nytimes.com/2012/09/28/sports/aqueduct-racing-officials-faulted-in-horse-deaths.html?comments#permid=34 …    
    
    
    All the Missing Horses: What Happened [...] Gov’t? SICKENING - ProPublica http://www.propublica.org/article/missing-what-happened-to-wild-horses-tom-davis-bought-from-the-govt … via @propublica    
    
    
    This makes my stomach turn.... http://fb.me/1HMXSLYum     
    
    
    Informative, articulate beautiful woman advocating for good...... http://fb.me/1MTsjBmOv     
    
    
    Girl Power! Q & A with Jill Abramson and Jane O'Connor http://www.publishersweekly.com/pw/by-topic/childrens/childrens-book-news/article/54025-q--a-with-jill-abramson-and-jane-o-connor.html … via @publisherswkly    
    
    
    Here is a great example as to why I love Luna 61 so much… Not only is it my favorite vegetarian restaurant… But... http://fb.me/1N7ElBYa8     
    
    
    aaaaahhhh...a touch of Eire for your fingertips...a good read... http://fb.me/2cs15PnB8     
    
    
    Soaking in every word of smokin'hot LIAM NEESON on Bravo, Inside Actors Studio. BRilliant actor, deep dialogue. Privilege to listen in.    
    
    
    Paul Nolan is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on HRTV,... http://fb.me/vBOzVucT     
    
    
    Willie Mullins is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on... http://fb.me/1kqRMcmse     
    
    
    Champion Ruby Walsh is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival... http://fb.me/1SOFkouVE     
    
    
    Rory Sheridan is a feature interview on the next episode of Ireland Unbridled at The Galway Racing Festival on... http://fb.me/IxUsUD5y     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry...

racehorses...by susan kayne

They run for the love of it.
On what, they do not... http://fb.me/24v1uzzpy     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry...

racehorses...by susan kayne

They run for the love of it.
On what, they do not know…... http://fb.me/1iJ1jnWam     
    
    
    My new eco-dress....hope i don't hungry while i am wearing it!!!!! go green girlfriends xxoo http://fb.me/1BXSwvZnE     
    
    
    Modern Day Trojan Horse Made From Over 18,000 Salvaged Computer Keys | http://inhabitat.com/amazing-modern-day-trojan-horse-made-from-over-18000-salvaged-computer-keys/ … via @ThinkDevGrow    
    
    
    THE HORSE STORY OF THE DAY !!! "To create something out of nothing pushes me more, so this is how it was born the... http://fb.me/2ig0CuoE9     
    
    
    MAGNIFICENT STORY: Stick-to-it-ive-ness: Unwavering pertinacity; perseverance by Richard Morse, @artprize entry http://www.artprize.org/richard-morse/2012/sticktoitiveness-unwavering-pertinacity-perseverance …    
    
    
    INCREDIBLE -- more pictures of stunning art "The visual representation of horses running on the river's surface,... http://fb.me/1DBBYePst     
    
    
    I am absolutely adamant that hydrofracking will mean death to people and properties in New York.  this is a... http://fb.me/1LYwqLFqm     
    
    
    May heaven greet you with joy of riding free from any restrictions. Thank you for coming to earth and sharing... http://fb.me/13vS2Sn86     
    
    
    The joy of kitties. The girls, almost three months now since adopting from Manhattan AC&C. Felicia tiger in back,... http://fb.me/HABny9r0     
    
    
    NOW is the time to adopt...save a life and add years to yours :). Pets On Death Row need you the most now. http://fb.me/1j9qcE1Ly     
    
    
    Fitting tribute to three extraordinary men who have dedicated their lives to bettering everything equestrian.... http://fb.me/222URkwkc     
    
    
    The best use of tattered wool horse coolers....recycle them for kitty warmers. Emily, adopted from Manhattan AC& C... http://fb.me/VOAYLSo5     
    
    
    An advocate for dignity, clean living for horses http://www.registerstar.com/news/article_03fd36d0-1356-11e2-b64d-0019bb2963f4.html#.UHbf6yfZ9E8.twitter … via @tweetmeme    
    
    
    @jvelezmitchell Foxy a vegan too :)    
    
    
    CUTE ALERT: Meet a cat who sleeps in pants; household pet hazards: http://bit.ly/UIIHDV  (via @HumaneSociety)    
    
    
    On the radio with Jamie and Glenn this AM. about #IREunbridled click the link to listen and escape to the Emerald Isle  http://www.horsesinthemorning.com/hitm-for-10-15-2012-by-omega-alpha-equine-unbridled-ireland-rescues-rejects-chips-poo/ …    
    
    
    My thoughts on incentivizing breeding in NY.... http://youtu.be/bRWHc-pLTjM  http://fb.me/1Z4M0kevq     
    
    
    “Do you know the difference between education and experience? Education is when you read the fine print;... http://fb.me/1W3t211Oe     
    
    
    I like this…THE COMMON SENSE PARTY... http://fb.me/1zS20u6nk     
    
    
    WARNING: GRAPHIC, DISTURBING PICTURES ....This is WHY AFTERCARE programs need to be in place before incentivizing... http://fb.me/1JH1VheEf     
    
    
    Next stop on Ireland Unbridled... http://fb.me/2m0sTMXrz     
    
    
    Another magnificent example of how our fellow beings help us....imagine if we could get shelter cats into the... http://fb.me/2k1IenZ1f     
    
    
    Great video of Kitty helping little boy to communicate, lets get shelter cats homes like this: Jessi-Cat: http://youtu.be/_vNM-bWf0oM  via @youtube    
    
    
    An extra from our next episode on HRTV (Monday, 9:30PM ET).... http://fb.me/1kNoKk7Pb     
    
    
    Ireland Unbridled: Why are Irish Horses so Special?: http://youtu.be/omSHXQv7frE  via @youtube    
    
    
    Find out why Irish horses are....
http://youtu.be/omSHXQv7frE  http://fb.me/XgVMMtLj     
    
    
    gotta love my girlfriend Lori...she nailed this one... http://fb.me/IPu7PoM2     
    
    
    Get fit, strong, and healthy...it is your birthright! http://fb.me/2s6QICqll     
    
    
    Relieved to learn Cuvee's Girl is now safe thanks to Mike Metzger    
    
    
    Watching Hallmark Channel HONEYMOON FOR ONE --lots of IRISH HORSES!!!! Beautiful Memories of Emerald Isle :) #IREunbridled    
    
    
    @sandyabrams @DeVon_Franklin great read so real    
    
    
    @tonyrobbins wow nice gig!    
    
    
    bill maher on target now prop 37 TRUTH in LABELING GMO foods!!!! Gary from Stonyfield, Matt Taibbi..rock on Bill    
    
    
    Most GMOs corn, soy, canola, sugar beets,   insecticide pesticide f(*&g MONSANTO pure evil.Gary Hirshberg. 527 mm pnds of poison    
    
    
    24d agent orange CHEMICAL INFLATION in food chain. 527 more millions of pesticides. $587mm lobbying so americans won't know whats in food!    
    
    
    SaddleBred Rescue today in Greenville, NY...some fortunate horses will find forever homes this day :)    
    
    
    Three little sisters growing up day-by-day! All rescued from death row three and a half months ago :). http://fb.me/zKQ0TElt     
    
    
    getting ready to escape to Adare in an hour. #IREunbridled at 9:30 PM ET on HRTV tunie in for a little R & R & to brush up on your riding    
    
    
    Check out SADDLEBRED RESCUE ADOPTION DAY IN NEW YORK: http://youtu.be/6iUE_GUwfT4  via @youtube    
    
    
    So glad to be able to share this event -- hope it helps horses in need of forever homes...have a look... http://fb.me/2i3KzQQ7b     
    
    
    Are humans the only species complicit in their own demise..and that of the environment  that supports their life..grrrrrr    
    
    
    Enjoyed the best dinner at Luna 61 -- my fave hangout in Tivoli :). Thanks Debra Maisel for a rejuvenating dinner... http://fb.me/2dUc6kRst     
    
    
    This is a special group, over 125 years of helping horses :).....thank you. http://fb.me/2jCSYgWV8     
    
    
    Little Eve and Nanny Felicia! http://fb.me/1muIHYHjE     
    
    
    Yummy dinner at Gigi's in Rhinebeck tonight, love the Husdon Valley eateries!    
    
    
    For Deborah Jones ... http://fb.me/Vwn8W7N5     
    
    
    Hello, fellow Cat slaves! The original copy of the "Basic Rules for
Cats who Have a House to Run" was uncovered... http://fb.me/1K2Tyip5B     
    
    
    UPDATED 10-28-12: Maryland Park Service (MPS) will be providing safe haven for horses at Fair Hill (Cecil County)... http://fb.me/1y4Icp1QW     
    
    
    Association by Seth Godin:
Who you hang out with determines what you dream about and what you collide with.
And... http://fb.me/2wrlLeeWm     
    
    
    Friends, during the hectic rush of Sandy please don't abandon your pets and other animals. Your cats, dogs,... http://fb.me/1nJMscDLl     
    
    
    Friends, this is yet another example of why horse breeding [of all breeds] needs to take a time out.... http://fb.me/tdAEZNFt     
    
    
    Thank you NYT for shedding light on the divine mission of Deborah Jones http://fb.me/1xAYlAK0X     
    
    
    Little Brook sharing the love of horses in a meaningful way ... http://fb.me/2vKBqoTtX     
    
    
    @CVFPartnerships @joedrape As long as 1 TB goes to slaughter, 1 too many is being bred.#BC12 is a perfect venue to show the plight of TBs.    
    
    
    @sidfernando @nythoroughbred do these people have names?    
    
    
    My thoughts during racing's biggest day... http://fb.me/1KkYtdGBn     
    
    
    Go where you are celebrated ... not where you are tolerated.
 -- Joel Osteen    
    
    
    Stop Using Dogs and Cats As Live Bait in French Controlled Islands http://fb.me/235kja0y4     
    
    
    Pledge Not to Shop at Pet Stores That Sell Puppies http://fb.me/1EAX67DTs     
    
    
    Trying my hand at poetry....

racehorses ... 

They run for the love of it,
Powered by strength they know.... http://fb.me/1IYVtm2Zk     
    
    
    Beautiful young lady, lovely role model.... http://fb.me/ubpPNGYr     
    
    
    My all time favorite quote...."You better LOVE what you do, because YOU ARE TRADING YOUR LIFE for it"    
    
    
    http://fb.me/2achqhSOV     
    
    
    “Walk with the dreamers, the believers, the courageous, the cheerful, the planners, the doers, the successful... http://fb.me/2hg5BqtW0     
    
    
    Little Ava prefers fresh cooked....!!!! She is not vegan like her human Susan. http://fb.me/215HZ2Js8     
    
    
    Great lecture Friday night at NYS Museum by Lincoln Scholar Harold Holzer to kick-off a two-day exhibition of... http://fb.me/1QUsS6YWX     
    
    
    WOW! Guess this doesn't apply to Racetrack Veterinarians..... http://fb.me/16ZNSF95w     
    
    
    A snippet of my interview with Mark Molloy of Crossogue in Ireland. A genuine horse lover, and incredible host at... http://fb.me/1JIlDI8M1     
    
    
    The coolest lady I met in all of Ireland. Pippa is gorgeous, rich, and earthy. I enjoyed every moment with her at... http://fb.me/1lUz5FlMY     
    
    
    Little kitty fur balls -- Eve & Ava cat-napping in the office :) http://fb.me/24HgTJyII     
    
    
    Congrats Eric! http://fb.me/22khU8JG6     
    
    
    A kindle and kittens! Sunday AM on my therapy couch :). http://fb.me/28Ri13Pdk     
    
    
    A Misty Monday Morning...four beauties safe in my yard. http://fb.me/1oFhi0WVY     
    
    
    And so [blood-stained] I write...... Where Do Ideas Come From? http://www.pw.org/content/where_do_ideas_come_from … via @poetswritersinc    
    
    
    Saw #LINCOLN in the cinema tonight. Deep and inspiring. Should sweep the Awards. A must see, say no to war movie. pic.twitter.com/zxlA9IXF    
    
    
    @WilliamShatner @ThomasGorz1 A VEGAN ThanksLiving!    
    
    
    Sweet (tooth) deal! http://fb.me/v6Zsu39S     
    
    
    The best part about Thanksgiving for me (a Vegan) is sharing what would have been my portion of the Turkey with... http://fb.me/2mVpTqvt9     
    
    
    Love my turkey-loving friends....rock on vegans, and veggies...here is to your health and animal liberation...... http://fb.me/1R2Ac5m81     
    
    
    HAPPY STORY: Inmates, horses, meet a standardbred named Lincoln. help each other get a second chance http://soc.li/K9yvzYi     
    
    
    Review: 'Saving America's Horses' is a disturbing documentary http://www.latimes.com/entertainment/movies/moviesnow/la-et-mn-saving-america-capsule-20121123,0,3772054.story …    
    
    
    too funny.... http://fb.me/1kS2gzARr     
    
    
    It all starts in the breeding shed.... http://fb.me/141d1y7ts     
    
    
    “Rock bottom became the solid foundation on which I rebuilt my life.” J.K. Rowling (born 1965); novelist    
    
    
    It's snowing in Tivoli! 1st of the season in the Hudson Valley.    
    
    
    Inherent in the desire are the mechanics to its fulfillment. I first heard this from Deepak Chopra.    
    
    
    Gratitude... http://fb.me/1qMV0oYS8     
    
    
    Speak up for Animals tonight in Albany, NY....... http://fb.me/xyGPVZSV     
    
    
    “Be soft. Do not let the world make you hard. Do not let pain make you hate. Do not let the bitterness steal your... http://fb.me/1JR4SY0Lm     
    
    
    Just learned HRTV is playing my interview with James Burns tomorrow, Saturday [Dec 1st], at 9PM ET and midnight.... http://fb.me/1Zb86dcas     
    
    
    James Burns, Dolphin Bay, Life On The Curragh: http://youtu.be/GVMqRY4IaMQ  via @youtube    
    
    
    Life on The Curragh in 40 mins on @HRTVHorseSports Tune in to see Life on The Curragh.    
    
    
    Imagine if the last things to grace your eyes on this earth was the most beautiful thing in the world to you... What a blessing to behold.    
    
    
    Imagine if the last things to grace your eyes on this earth was the most beautiful thing in the world to you...?... http://fb.me/2gLth8Zv4     
    
    
    #supersoulsunday Who is the Brain on the show with Jill Bolte Taylor. Is anyone else curious? It was a real person too.    
    
    
    TONITE on @HRTVHORSESPORTS 9:30 PM ET see my cross country lesson and interview with Eleanor Dwan @ Mt. Juliet Estate. pic.twitter.com/mFr1AHDD    
    
    
    @DeepakChopra I spent a week with Debbie Ford at Omega!    
    
    
    Sneak peek #IREunbridled tonite on HRTV Meet Eleanor Dwan at the Mount Juliet Estate in Kilkenny Ireland: http://youtu.be/m0ynGpKaEe0  via @youtube    
    
    
    "How we treat this planet and everything on it is a very important measure of of our love and…" — stacey graham http://disq.us/8bvqvs     
    
    
    Another reason to love Debbie Ford ... http://fb.me/y2QY9wq3     
    
    
    Writing the wrongs! Bandit's Story at the halfway point. Be inspired writers by JK Rowling [hour with Charlie Rose] http://www.charlierose.com/view/interview/12612 …    
    
    
    THE BEST ARTICLE: Ashley Judd Slaps Media in the Face for Speculation Over Her ‘Puffy’ Appearance http://www.thedailybeast.com/articles/2012/04/09/ashley-judd-slaps-media-in-the-face-for-speculation-over-her-puffy-appearance.html … via @thedailybeast    
    
    
    When you feel hurt by others opinions, remind yourself that it is not you they are really seeing, but a... http://fb.me/2qmQ56hgP     
    
    
    An excerpt from the Cat Rules, especially important in winter: Attention all fellow CATS --- Do not allow closed... http://fb.me/2jb1Z3ulh     
    
    
    Emmy didn't read the sign on the dryer door! Friends, PLEASE, ALWAYS look in your dryer if you live with kitties.... http://fb.me/x8VljQla     
    
    
    OMG Vegan Food Bliss ... I'll be making this :) http://fb.me/2hH0ZCtn5     
    
    
    Love Renegade Health! http://fb.me/1bLjXzEnn     
    
    
    Exquisite... http://fb.me/DeyDO4VM     
    
    
    Contemplate my friends, live while you are alive. Treasure every breath, every moment, every touch and expression... http://fb.me/FmNk97sP     
    
    
    Be a proactive parent.... http://fb.me/yJ17KNks     
    
    
    Watching Harold & Me at beautiful Mt. Juliet in County Kilkenny #IREunbridled on @HRTVHORSESPORTS. Tune-in Dish 404.    
    
    
    A blast from the past, 2006 WCBC at Calgary Stampede... http://fb.me/1o4OxlxoV     
    
    
    Little Lizzie on big stakes horse Stalwart Member! A happy Holiday memory in the barn, circa 2005. http://fb.me/1q0TzoXqc     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1ququHUwW     
    
    
    Alan Chartock...In Conversation with Susan Kayne and Andrew Elsbree http://fb.me/2m5XJM2mE     
    
    
    Doping at Devon....and so it goes.... http://fb.me/15koTTqft     
    
    
    Doping at Devon....Sudden Death of Show Pony Clouds Image of Elite Pursuit http://nyti.ms/10q3Y6S     
    
    
    “Sometimes things get so rough in your life that the the dream has to do the dreaming for you” Tyler Perry on Piers Morgan NOW. LOVE HIM :)    
    
    
    Exquisite.... http://fb.me/Ao2lTOb6     
    
    
    C'est la Vie... http://fb.me/xLA26qup     
    
    
    Wow...here is an empowering perspective to what can otherwise be a sad and troubling time. Letting go and... http://fb.me/27eXfVgsl     
    
    
    Jennifer Gralow Says it all....beautiful, succinct, from the heart.... http://fb.me/1p1lj9Cc0     
    
    
    I couldn't imagine a better way to start the New Year than helping another in need.....MISO needs an angel...NOW http://fb.me/WCKBKZrW     
    
    
    ANIMAL RESCUERS/ADVOCATES UNDER ATTACK BY FACEBOOK http://fb.me/1P4ioVTUh     
    
    
    “The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others.” Mohandas Karamchand Gandhi... http://fb.me/2862N4L5E     
    
    
    No need to frack NY. http://fb.me/28yws2Vcz     
    
    
    Beautiful girl, needs an angel... http://fb.me/23IVdxNHi     
    
    
    “The only person you are destined to become is the person you decide to be.”
Ralph Waldo Emerson (1803-1882);... http://fb.me/1sH5zPCuz     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1O5lDzy6i     
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Backstretch Buzz: New York-breds http://youtu.be/zk2razTwQDY?a    
    
    
    Time to own a NY-Bred! Get UR own horse today. (YouTube http://youtu.be/zk2razTwQDY?a)    
    
    
    “I didn't lose the gold. I won the silver.” Michelle Kwan (born 1980); figure skater, Olympic Medalist, United... http://fb.me/1wg7P1g9V     
    
    
    Amen.... http://fb.me/2nwgskvRI     
    
    
    Just like Horse Racing -- Armstrong admits doping to Oprah http://bigstory.ap.org/article/armstrong-admits-doping-oprah-0 …    
    
    
    Hey Friends, I'd value your feedback on my blogpost about Dutrow suspension. No doubt it will take a huge effort... http://fb.me/2sDhUzN4Y     
    
    
    100% correct Nathan. http://fb.me/Jd8ODbcm     
    
    
    Here is a thought to contemplate this week....“…memory is fragile and the space of a single life is brief,... http://fb.me/1ROOTztjR     
    
    
    Tonight on HRTV 9:30 PM ET watch my interviews with racing stars at the Galway Festival on Ireland Unbridled!... http://fb.me/1OjZVg0bj     
    
    
    SO TRUE, TRUE, TRUE: “If I made it, it's half because I was game enough to take a lot of punishment along the way... http://fb.me/SWCK9EQt     
    
    
    love this! great way to rock the midday of the week! Yes, yes, yes...... http://fb.me/1xbfKLK2y     
    
    
    In Miami at #NATPE to share the unbridled joy of horses. if you'd like to see more of our beloved 4-legged friends on TV- tweet up please!    
    
    
    Cuteness Award! http://fb.me/1n9N9EqXd     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1wzYEdwhs     
    
    
    TIME TO GET CREATING !!!!!  “We are not creatures of circumstance; we are creators of circumstance.”  Benjamin... http://fb.me/2gfHgmQut     
    
    
    TIME TO GET CREATING !!!!!  “We are not creatures of circumstance; we are creators of circumstance.”  Benjamin... http://fb.me/GYCnKVPD     
    
    
    @HRTVHORSESPORTS 10:30AM ET 2day #IREunbridled Eleanor Dwan @ the Mt Juliet Estate in Kilkenny Ireland: http://youtu.be/m0ynGpKaEe0  via @youtube    
    
    
    “If you don't stick to your values when they are being tested, they're not values: they're hobbies.” -- Jon... http://fb.me/1UkoNBtZ6     
    
    
    Where did 2,439,000 horses--almost 500,000 horses per year for the past five years--go? http://fb.me/1TEecHTGT     
    
    
    #natpe 2011 begins, learning so much already. Fantastic! http://twitgoo.com/1tvvyx    
    
    
    Rocking at #natpe with Daryl Hall! http://twitgoo.com/1tx7yw    
    
    
    Beef lasagne found to contain up to 100 per cent horse meat ... and so it goes in the Land of The Horse .... so... http://fb.me/WlOV86iN     
    
    
    And yet the breeding without a plan continues..... http://fb.me/1KHDaIvhf     
    
    
    Here is something I would have never guessed --- is this a scam? Did every LinkedIn member receive this accolade? http://fb.me/2rOklcngj     
    
    
    OK -- did you all get this too??? Hurray! I have one of the top 10% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. http://www.linkedin.com/pub/profile/0/728/3b7?trk=200tw …    
    
    
    the reality of numbers in horseracing -- Moran: Addition by subtraction http://espn.go.com/horse-racing/story/_/id/8917928/addition-subtraction …    
    
    
    RACHEL UPDATE: Updated Release on Rachel Alexandra’s Procedure and Current Condition...
 
After foaling Rachel... http://fb.me/1Tc2xg85t     
    
    
    Someone chose to breed each one of these horses....Where are the "breeders" now? http://fb.me/1yriFxKSO     
    
    
    History repeats itself .... why do we eat cows, pigs, chicken, and bison -- each of which have the same desire to... http://fb.me/2sgyzswb0     
    
    
    WHY HASN'T BREEDING BEEN BANNED? http://fb.me/AXf08R0s     
    
    
    This is why Unbridled stopped racing and breeding. People this is what happens to the majority of thoroughbreds... http://fb.me/2IdmXHXI2     
    
    
    Together the louder we can shout to be the horses' voice, the more chance we'll have to put an end to this... http://fb.me/28BOa9kGB     
    
    
    DOG TREAT RECALL -- READ TO PROTECT YOUR BELOVED PETS FROM SICKNESS: http://fb.me/2ADlsZP8W     
    
    
    DOG TREAT RECALL - MULTIPLE BRANDS - READ TO PROTECT YOUR BELOVED PETS FROM SALMONELLA, READ: http://www.dogfoodadvisor.com/dog-food-recall/kasel-recalls-numerous-brands-of-dog-treats-due-to-salmonella/ …    
    
    
    “Twenty years from now you will be more disappointed by the things you didn't do than by the ones you did. So... http://fb.me/1JMUY5nxA     
    
    
    Here is a refreshing quote from one of our leaders, sometimes the loneliest place of all is standing on... http://fb.me/2ueC21TcQ     
    
    
    China exports the most horse meat to the global market: http://fb.me/2OnFZPl5T     
    
    
    Fellow equine TV hostess  Darley Newman  gets the cover of this month's Chronicle Connection.... once you get... http://fb.me/1zuskxwEQ     
    
    
    hey.....it's all vegan ;)! http://amzn.com/k/HLzPQbJXTZiegTp1TG6now … Beer, then later bread, were the inspiration for modern civilization.    
    
    
    “The longest journey you will ever take is the 18 inches from your head to your heart.” Andrew Bennett (born 1939); British politician    
    
    
    This is an excellent article.  The author asks great questions.... http://fb.me/2GlFdkTBP     
    
    
    Love Hot Yoga Saratoga! http://fb.me/2f8jVszMB     
    
    
    I do not understand how or why being adorned in dead animal skins makes one feel good about themselves or serves... http://fb.me/1lKDKm3Fa     
    
    
    DEAD ANIMAL SKINS, A FASHION STATEMENT... Seriously! Beyonce: Stop making exotic animal skins cool. via @Care2 http://www.thepetitionsite.com/123/599/293/ask-beyonce-to-stop-using-exotic-animal-skins-to-make-shoes/ …    
    
    
    Urge NIH to Retire All Government-Owned Chimpanzees to Sanctuary - The Humane Society of the United. http://fb.me/Cf7dd4XN     
    
    
    Experience the raw beauty of Eire's westcoast on horseback watch the Connemara Trail 8:30PM/ET WED @HRTVHORSESPORTS pic.twitter.com/yhzRhOgHxv    
    
    
    My guy...can't wait for Season 2 of The Newsroom! http://fb.me/1ZGupTYiv     
    
    
    Health is a choice ... http://fb.me/weczWVE8     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/1DYwhh2ic     
    
    
    ME...In The Field w/ Mark Molloy @ blissful Crossogue House in bucolic Tipperary, Ireland: http://youtu.be/9Z6g6bqfLMY  via @youtube    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2vWETDNlZ     
    
    
    Fond memories in Tipperary...... http://fb.me/27eG164Wy     
    
    
    For all my farrier friends...thinking about Calgary? Here is a peak at what you are in for! Practice,... http://fb.me/1cB0YKkMe     
    
    
    The unconscionable acts of humanity to the beautiful creatures we charge ourselves with looking after never... http://fb.me/222bLE5wg     
    
    
    Check this out in Grand Central Station in NY -- sooo totally cool...love it! http://vimeo.com/58803818  http://fb.me/2hlTpoktk     
    
    
    FDA...Franken-Food & Death Administrators... http://fb.me/1XQNRuq6q     
    
    
    @TheResident so happy you are on the air daily!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2i3h1q3R9     
    
    
    “Never doubt that a small group of thoughtful, committed citizens can change the world; indeed, it's the only thing that ever has” M. Mead    
    
    
    @cookingquinoa @alyssarimmer wow... what an awesome combo..luv the texture too! delish, delish, delish...thank you Wendy xo    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2ibB3mG12     
    
    
    Little Girl Cat all grown up!    
    
    
    Any change in a single dewdrop becomes reflected in the whole....the secret dharma of women Justine Musk http://fb.me/Flivs4v0     
    
    
    The best Easter honors the bunny .... try some delicious recipes that don't require animals.... http://fb.me/223cKLo0o     
    
    
    5 Recipes to Veganize Your Easter Brunch Menu http://www.care2.com/greenliving/5-recipes-to-veganize-your-easter-brunch-menu.html …    
    
    
    Join me at the @IrishNatStud on @HRTV at 10 PM ET 2nite, 1 AM ET Sunday. Tour the grounds, meet the stallions, see real Irish horse heroes!    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/I4Slc5pp     
    
    
    NZ looking after OTTBs.... http://fb.me/2rimfHJQK     
    
    
    We lost a great creative genius in Phil Ramone...he made beautiful music for the masses, may he now be among the... http://fb.me/1YDxBFSIN     
    
    
    please... http://fb.me/17kbtuhiH     
    
    
    Beautiful filly with a big heart, like her daddy Wild Desert ;)! Congratulations to all connections. http://fb.me/2j4STbUqs     
    
    
    Only in New York kids....gotta love this..... http://fb.me/23PLRFVh8     
    
    
    Every year thousands of people die. Sometimes it’s expected and sometimes it’s not. When these people die, they... http://fb.me/1X8yeDMvW     
    
    
    Not surprising.... http://fb.me/2T8IFymXY     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/16wZkPyLB     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/TDlQ3xlj     
    
    
    SO SAD, SO YOUNG: Roger Ebert Dead: Chicago Sun-Times Film Critic Passes Away at Age 70 http://huff.to/14Hsrqv  via @Moviefone    
    
    
    "Cats can work out mathematically the exact place to sit that will cause most inconvenience."- Pam Brown .... YA THINK!!!!!    
    
    
    A Life and Death Plea for HELP from our Braying Buddies http://fb.me/Ahjgxsid     
    
    
    diabolical... http://fb.me/21pmWBD3e     
    
    
    INTERESTING: From strip clubs to theaters, Google Glass won't be welcome everywhere http://www.nbcnews.com/technology/technolog/strip-clubs-theaters-google-glass-wont-be-welcome-everywhere-1B9231620 … via @NBCNewsTech    
    
    
    SO SAD: BBC News - Ex-Prime Minister Baroness Thatcher dies http://bbc.in/16HWcnt     
    
    
    Friends for a lifetime filled with love. http://fb.me/2g0JNQxdy     
    
    
    Have you ever.... http://fb.me/zi3mB2mx     
    
    
    Gorgeous beauty with a lifetime of love to give an adopting human. http://fb.me/2j4dURQVd     
    
    
    Important issue facing all New Yorkers... http://fb.me/zPXXWS15     
    
    
    Debunking the protein myth...one veggie at a time, read on... http://fb.me/PWuG8tg0     
    
    
    Enormously fun and for a good cause Old Friends thanks again to Susan Salk for yet another great bit of blogging! http://fb.me/K1KgFPR8     
    
    
    Penn Kill Buyers revealed -- spread the word, protect your horses... http://fb.me/1ARd6SzSM     
    
    
    SHARE: Penn Kill Buyers revealed -- spread the word, protect your horses.. http://fb.me/14uyW0ruL     
    
    
    Speaks for itself..... http://fb.me/2jzVXwUbh     
    
    
    “It was only a sunny smile, and little it cost in the giving, but like morning light it scattered the night and... http://fb.me/ssqFD7W9     
    
    
    This duo won the International Grand Prix at the Dublin Horse Show in 1960! David Broome and Sunslave. http://fb.me/2ESyDPNKn     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2iUHa41aG     
    
    
    INSPIRATION: "You cannot hit a target you cannot see" How Daymond John Billion $$$ Biz frm His Liv'g Rm: http://youtu.be/TieCr9CW7so  via @youtube    
    
    
    Please help if you can. I adopted 5 death row kitties in July 2012 and they are a total joy. http://fb.me/OMsJ2Myi     
    
    
    Beautiful kitties -- adopt or foster if you can help. Please share. http://fb.me/2NrdUlJOB     
    
    
    Words of wisdom.... http://fb.me/TMTVEiv3     
    
    
    This works! I cover my cats with this mix and NO Ticks latch on. http://fb.me/1qlKkYukF     
    
    
    Dear friends… Last year I adopted five cats from NYC ACC, it has been one of the most rewarding experiences I've... http://fb.me/2juJ0wHK5     
    
    
    TODAY: 3PM !!!! Exciting day for Writers | The Pulitzer Prizes | 2013 Winners and Finalists announced April 15 http://www.pulitzer.org/node/8501     
    
    
    Heather Brandt, Leah Halsdorf, Erin Looman ... a remembrance of our friend. http://fb.me/OY9yUEiz     
    
    
    Friends, Speak-up for horses.... http://fb.me/2qa3N63pS     
    
    
    To all my starving artist and soon-to-be-published friends....we are not alone... http://fb.me/2XzOtBVUa     
    
    
    <3ichokes...love them! http://fb.me/23xkDsBEg     
    
    
    Animals in need.... http://fb.me/ET1RR0mR     
    
    
    Blissful morning with friends James Kullander et al in my favorite little town on the Hudson Tivoli, New York.... http://fb.me/NpPlZSYa     
    
    
    A gift from the earth ..... http://fb.me/23ckwmfcY     
    
    
    Snowed in, 12 inches so far, watching Courage Under Fire with my Honey.    
    
    
    @LFDHcom Met Daryl in person, real deal, authentic in every way. Great to see LFDH growing on the networks. Thanks for the picture !!    
    
    
    I subscribed to LiveFromDarylsHouse's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/LiveFromDarylsHouse?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/2VT0L681X     
    
    
    EVENT ALERT: SPEAK-UP FOR HORSES -- THIS WEEKEND at  Equine Advocates... http://fb.me/SYIzvKFO     
    
    
    Profoundly poignant..... http://fb.me/2j7M5wrVf     
    
    
    Colt and running Horses at Trader Joe's in Albany, New York...getting ready to celebrate Saratoga Race Course... http://fb.me/Qq0PogEs     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/19NgSsWow     
    
    
    I posted a new photo to Facebook http://fb.me/C7y6S8jg     
    
    
    CAT LOVER ALERT!!! BOOK REVIEW: Good Grief, Tibby: Wendy MacNaughton And Caroline Paul's  http://www.lareviewofbooks.org/article.php?id=1565&fulltext=1#.UXu9DKV2m_M.twitter …    
    
    
    CAT LOVERS MUST READ!!!! Lost Cat is an incredibly endearing work, a snapshot of the madness of loving and... http://fb.me/1IdPrqu0E     
    
    
    KaChing, KaChing..... http://fb.me/1uCAfPRwG     
    
    
    Speaks to the desperation of many --- we live in the best of times and the worst of times... real meaning is hard... http://fb.me/2fYKRwEP9     
    
    
    “If you cannot do great things, do small things in a great way.” 
~ Napoleon Hill (1883-1970); motivational author http://fb.me/HJ7diwxO     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1JfbMaJPw     
    
    
    DIET SODA DRINKS contain an artificial sweetener known as aspartame, which is broken down into phenylalanine,... http://fb.me/1xgdLKaRB     
    
    
    HOW TO WRITE COPY THAT GOES VIRAL by Seth Godin

The best thing is to not try to write things that will go viral.... http://fb.me/1Eh8BYFlv     
    
    
    Inspirational lady .... http://fb.me/1jMKVaKhe     
    
    
    “Character cannot be developed in ease and quiet. Only through experience of trial and suffering can the soul be... http://fb.me/1ZI6Syt0J     
    
    
    Favorite healthy food photo of the day:  http://drweil.smugmug.com/DrWeilsDailyLife/My-Organic-Vegetable-Garden-in/15513814_2aWLj#1161984344_HWHaq …    
    
    
    What a great way to turn a wrong into a right...way to go Jeffrey... http://fb.me/AIOW36X7     
    
    
    Study: Why Seahorses Look Like Horses http://aol.it/hCpkVQ  via @AOL    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://youtu.be/UeSA2j4oiDA?a    
    
    
    Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UeSA2j4oiDA … via @youtube You rock Ellen xoxo! Read EatingAnimals, Watch Earthlings    
    
    
    I favorited a YouTube video -- Ellen DeGeneres on being vegan http://youtu.be/UeSA2j4oiDA?a    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- @katiecouric: Ellen DeGeneres http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a    
    
    
    I favorited a YouTube video -- @katiecouric: Ellen DeGeneres http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a    
    
    
    Great dialogue, two amazing women. THank you Katie & Ellen! (YouTube http://youtu.be/loZJpWEMJAE?a)    
    
    
    I subscribed to KatieCouric's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/KatieCouric?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    I subscribed to RawRadiantHealth's channel on YouTube. http://www.youtube.com/user/RawRadiantHealth?feature=autoshare    
    
    
    TV ALERT: TUES, THURS, FRI on HRTV watch my interview with the amazing Anne Kursinski at HITS Horse Shows. Anne... http://fb.me/2qomOesIi     
    
    
    Getting ready for the official debut of Unbridled TV[2013] on HRTV 10 PM ET THURSDAY. 1st episode features Anne... http://fb.me/TiRNWP68     
    
    
    A Horseman and a Gentleman -- thanks NYRA for bringing us this treasure of a ... (YouTube http://youtu.be/8rLoVbLJEVA?a)    
    
    
    I liked a YouTube video -- John Nerud "Lasting Impressions" - The Breeders' Cup (Part 2) http://youtu.be/8rLoVbLJEVA?a    
    
    
    “Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts.”
Sir Winston Churchill... http://fb.me/2GWYkbFsx     
    
    
    Watch my interview with Anne Kursinski online at HRTV... http://fb.me/1mPcyAnJG     
    
    
    TV ALERT TONIGHT: 10PM ET join me on #UnbridledTV in conversation w/ iconic show jumper Anne Kursinski on @HRTVHORSESPORTS  Tune-In & Enjoy!    
    
    
    Starry-eyed...my interview with Todd Pletcher at Saratoga...hard to believe it was ten years ago!... http://fb.me/2AP93Msy4     
    
    
    For all my DIEt soda drinking friends..... http://fb.me/2H7TkvfAw     
    
    
    http://fb.me/1OcjvIyNm     
    
    
    I don't remember my father, he passed when I was 1 1/2 years onto this planet. I think of him often, and can only... http://fb.me/1HFUgqMiF     
    
    
    “Go confidently in the direction of your dreams! Live the life you've imagined.”
Henry David Thoreau (1817-1862);... http://fb.me/27tQSU8IC     
    
    
    A gal after my own heart... http://fb.me/33JXpJg6j     
    
    
    