Today we launched FDA's Innovation Pathway: http://www.fda.gov/NewsEvents/Newsroom/PressAnnouncements/ucm299339.htm …    
    
    
    Looking fwd to Leslie Saxon's talk at #TEDMED    
    
    
    Bud Frazier asks, do we need a pulse? Welcome artificial heart technology at #TEDMED    
    
    
    Cancer cells are "selfish" and want to grow at the expense of the host. Dr Michor, #TEDMED    
    
    
    There's no "death gene" which gives us latitude to find solutions to aging. Dan Perry, #TEDMED    
    
    
    No publication has ever cured a patient. Lynda Chin lamenting the personalized medicine pipeline. #TEDMED    
    
    
    Need goal oriented engineers working as a team to design solutions in targeted drug therapies. Lynda Chin, #TEDMED    
    
    
    Atul Butte - hard to do colonoscopy on a rat! #TEDMED    
    
    
    Smoking gun for psychiatric disorders may be the immune system. Jay Lombard #TEDMED    
    
    
    Leslie Saxon talking about data downloads from implantable devices directly to docs. Those patients live longer! #TEDMED    
    
    
    Mark Hyman tackling the big issue of chronic disease thru peer support and human connection. #TEDMED    
    
    
    Mark Hyman gets a standing ovation for his evangelical message: health will come through social support of healthy lifestyles. #TEDMED    
    
    
    National Bioeconomy Report announced today: our future in medicine, energy, agriculture, and environment.    
    
    
    Rina Singh says in the future we will add sugar and water to enzymatic technologies to get our fuel. #whostp    
    
    
    UCSF vice chancellor Keith Yamamoto sees value of FDA's Innovation Pathway to move artificial kidney forward. #ostp    
    
    
    Ramesh Raskars app to assess eyesight is amazing #nasahealth    
    
    
    Interesting possibilities for 12-lead ECG being developed by NASA #nasahealth holds hope for personal health.    
    
    
    Fatigue risk management system developed at NASA can help trucking industry #nasahealth Jeff Sutton reports.    
    
    
    Scott Snyder talks about the "last foot" - changing human behavior in a mobile world, shaping decisions on the fly. #NASAhealth    
    
    
    Scott Snyder "if you dont create the innovations people want they will innovate around you" #NASAhealth    
    
    
    Scott Snyder on horizon scanning: "Dont scan for technologies, scan for use cases." #NASAhealth    
    
    
    Todd Park exciting the audience with ways to liberate patient data and incite innovators to create value with it. #NASAhealth    
    
    
    Felt the love today - kudos to my agency, the FDA, from the audience at #NASAhealth    
    
    
    Waiting for the Collaborative Innovation Public Sector Prizes sessions to start.  Great agenda!    
    
    
    Jean Case says organizations have to be fearless, take risks and not fear failure at #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Tom Kalil jokes he's going to talk for 3 hours about tax reform #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Agencies need to be bolder!  Support more ambitious prizes using the America COMPETES Act, says Tom Kalil. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Agencies: train people on the unique methods in prize development. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Cristin Dorgelo, Jean Case about to announce award for excellence in advancing public sector prizes...#PublicPrizes    
    
    
    ...And the winner is...#PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Health and Human Services wins award for excellence in advancing public sector prizes!#PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Robyn Sturm Steffen - a rock star for incentive prizes run from fed govt agencies. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    Can't wait to test drive America COMPETES Act in my agency, the FDA. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    @CaseFoundation. Yes, I will!  Learned I can use appropriated funds to operate the prize as well as create prize purse. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    My thought is to put out a challenge for how we can bring patient perceptions into FDA's regulatory decision-making. Thoughts?#PublicPrizes    
    
    
    NASA is our fed gov't leader - serving as a scout for the rest of us on innovation prizes. @jasoncrusan, @nasa. #PublicPrizes    
    
    
    In case you want to follow the discussion on the Supreme Court's decision on ACA live: http://www.scotusblog.com/cover-it-live/     
    
    
    Peter Levin makes great case for blue button. #innovategov    
    
    
    Gimme My DaM Data on Vimeo http://vimeo.com/48221070 . This is great. Who can argue with these guys!    
    
    
    Monitor and Find Everything in Your Home or Office from the Internet - Wireless Sensor Tags http://wirelesstags.net/     
    
    
    Interesting potential: Crowd-sourcing health conditions and comparisons
http://bit.ly/STYVq2 .  Love it on two levels - as art and science.    
    
    
    Finally found a bag I LOVE! Jump from Paper Bags and Satchels - Perfect for iPad/Tablets / Home http://www.jumpfrompaper.us/     
    
    
    Visiting the White House, "Anytime, Anywhere, and on Any Device". Here's a blog I'd like to follow for the next 4 years http://www.whitehouse.gov/blog/2012/09/04/visiting-white-house-anytime-anywhere-and-any-device …    
    
    
    iTypewriter http://flpbd.it/vPCDH/ . I strongly feel the need to own this.    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson. Better?  Kickstarter campaign needed. http://www.macrumors.com/2012/08/20/one-off-keyboard-prototype-turns-ipad-into-typewriter/ …    
    
    
    SymbolWorld visits EEOB. pic.twitter.com/Tolt3KiC    
    
    
    @daniel_kraft Stunning! Keep the pics coming    
    
    
    Feeling bolder already after this: We’re All Cowards - UnSectored http://flpbd.it/rAMSL     
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson give mom and dad a big hug from me. Yikes!    
    
    
    Weekend photo, a day late #oaklandmd pic.twitter.com/ehWrzgFi    
    
    
    Uber: When Innovation Outpaces The Law http://www.fastcompany.com/node/3001169  via @FastCompany    
    
    
    Amazing Animated Optical Illusions! #5 http://flpbd.it/MEXwe     
    
    
    More good news for the introverts.  Must Great Leaders Be Gregarious? http://nyti.ms/O5Zeiv     
    
    
    We need to improve the doctor-pt relationship. HFSA studies: | http://theheart.org  http://www.theheart.org/article/1448291.do?280515198e9b8f63e158dbebc95dc28b …    
    
    
    “@Kimberly_Gerson: Hey, here's a picture of that new cloud species Undulatus Asperatus. http://bit.ly/QAABq0  looks like #vangogh    
    
    
    Kickstarter project? Gentler Pocket Knife Has Animals, Not Blades http://flpbd.it/VVfOY     
    
    
    A marriage of data and caregivers gives Dr. Atul Gawande hope for health care http://radar.oreilly.com/2012/08/a-marriage-of-data-and-caregivers-gives-dr-atul-gawande-hope-for-health-care.html#.UGSRn9pDoDU.twitter …    
    
    
    Follow this hashtag for updates on our newest Entrepreneurs in Residence project at FDA, Innovation Pathway 3.0 #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    We're about three weeks away from starting up our next Entrepreneurs in Residence program at FDA #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    Tweeting at 60,000 feet. Thank you Southwest for #wifi    
    
    
    In flight to #BCC6, hosted by @DrLeslieSaxon. Looking forward to tomorrow's session.    
    
    
    And tweeting is about all you can do at 60,000 feet. #slowpageloads    
    
    
    Sound-canceling earbuds not canceling sound of screaming baby behind me.  Southwest air wifi take me away.    
    
    
    How can  we "skate to where the puck is going" to stay out in front of connected health. @thomasjackiewicz of USC.    
    
    
    #bcc6 David Agus showing data that sitting all day causes disease. Get up and walk!    
    
    
    #bcc6 @davidagus economic motivators work. What's the ROI on exercise in the workplace?    
    
    
    @kenpersen demonstrating the current state of the art in implantable pacemaker monitoring technology. Wow!  Give patients access to data!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @kenpersen patients get a new pacemaker AND a new smartphone that talks to the device and their doctor. Love it! #BCC6    
    
    
    Congrats to Cameron, Boston Sci for FDA approval of subcutaneous defibrillator. #BCC6    
    
    
    Great questions for my colleagues at FDA:  how can we divorce the hardware from the software through the regulatory process? #BCC6    
    
    
    @EricHorvitz: leading the next discussion #BCC6  on big data.  @navingovind, @evaho, @rajivMaheswaran, @ChrisWadsen on the panel.    
    
    
    Surprise model. Don't tell docs what they already know, use big data to bring them something new. @erichorvitz #BCC6    
    
    
    @ChrisWadsen:  Big Data will pull from multiple sources and give multiple "answers" that together create a clearer picture.    
    
    
    @Eva_Ho:  data is the oxygen that will fuel the mobile devices. #BCC6    
    
    
    Don't just want "big piles of numbers" we want insight from that. @RajivMaheswaran at #BCC6    
    
    
    How can we light the fire in healthcare to have predictive modeling drive behaviors?  @eric_horvitz #BCC6    
    
    
    90% of time is spent cleaning the data, in Big Data efforts. Not trivial. @rajivMaheswaran. #BCC6    
    
    
    Need a "single patient view" to show the healthcare experience from the patients perspective, says audience member at #BCC6. Yes!    
    
    
    #FDAInnovation one of our projects got $3M funding. http://www.ucsf.edu/news/2012/10/12810/artificial-kidney-project-ucsf-receives-3-million-new-funding …    
    
    
    Do patients want beat to beat info?  My question to panel: why don't we know that answer? #BCC6 panel discussion    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja @alivecor what did you learn from your analysis?    
    
    
    Here's cool technology for physiological monitoring. http://www.zephyr-technology.com/  #BCC6    
    
    
    Glad to hear about so many FDA approved devices #BCC6 #phew!    
    
    
    @DavidAlbert: if you want to start new company, attack big problems. Hear, hear! #BCC6    
    
    
    @drdave01. if you want to start new company, attack big problems. Hear, hear! #BCC6    
    
    
    Love the HouseChatter idea #BCC6 built on http://Force.com .    
    
    
    “@marisareinoso: #BCC6 liking changamcare!!” Yes, there's so much to like about this. What a refreshing approach.    
    
    
    @SamAgutu. Micro insurance by using mobile money is an incredible concept that is working in Kenya. Can it work in US? #BCC6    
    
    
    “@rosinasam: I nominate Sam Agatu of Changamka for a @tedmed talk next year. Please consider it @tedmedjay ! Cc@DrLeslieSaxon #bcc6” me too!    
    
    
    Sports monitoring will be the cutting edge for health monitoring. Next session coming up at #BCC6    
    
    
    Monitoring athletes, #biosports, could push new sensors and systems that consumers can use. Love it!    
    
    
    “@ManeeshJuneja: @DrLeslieSaxon 'will biosports be a driver of mHealth?' - the expert panel say YES! #BCC6 #mhealth”. Great!  Applaud!    
    
    
    Games!  The next session up at #BCC6.    
    
    
    @Ayogo builds apps that motivate healthy behavior. #BCC6    
    
    
    @Avery's Metria technology is tailored for consumers and intended to improve quality of life. #BCC6    
    
    
    @rosinasam thanks!  Ok, hoping my photo from today can be my new avatar!    
    
    
    @DrLeslieSaxon. Incredible line up of speakers today. I'm honored and humbled to be part of it. Hope to stay connected going forward #BCC6    
    
    
    In 2015, half the world population will be under age 25. @TedSexton #BCC6    
    
    
    Ouch!  Was that the FDA getting thrown under a bus?  Got it, @TedSexton: it's good business sense to do good work, create better world #BCC6    
    
    
    @MarkWinter from #XPrize says they are in the disruption business. You think...? #BCC6    
    
    
    Could @AdrianHon's app "Zombies run!"get ME up and running? #couchpotato. #BCC6    
    
    
    SimCoach. I'm blown away by the possibilities. #BCC6    
    
    
    Gamification is a temporary steroid. Doesn't permanently change behaviors. @MichaelKim #BCC6    
    
    
    Now over 260 challengers for the #XPrize #Tricorder. Yo, FDA team, are you ready?? #BCC6    
    
    
    Doctors are not the chief behavior coaches for people. Moms are. @MichaelKim #BCC6    
    
    
    Yes, I agree! “@DrLeslieSaxon: @MisfitWearables -- Thank you for being at #BCC6. Your talk and conference app were fantastic!”    
    
    
    At FDA we are excited to continue our work with the folks from #XPrize on the #Tricorder project. Thanks, @MarkWinter. #BCC6    
    
    
    Agreed @rosinasam: Honestly #bcc6 changed my view of @usc - great intellectually inspiring day and great to see that @usc this competitive    
    
    
    Tweets going silent. It's martini time! #BCC6    
    
    
    Something for real engineer-designers. RT @FastCoDesign: Why James Dyson Invested $8,000,000 In A Student Incubator http://flpbd.it/tGoRa     
    
    
    @sonnyvu @drlesliesaxon @rosinasam @longmiremd thx. The whole event was amazing!    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja, dang, wish I was there!    
    
    
    If they can do it, so can FDA: 4 Innovation Strategies From Big Companies That Act Like Startups   http://www.fastcodesign.com/node/1670960  via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    The science behind this is astounding.  They've considered everything. #livejump http://win.gs/QPw1rf     
    
    
    Egress checklist starting now. #livejump http://win.gs/QPw1rf     
    
    
    Never mind the debate: FDA Entrepreneurs in Residence getting down to business at OPM Innovation Lab #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/qbHmSrFu    
    
    
    #OPMInnovationLab totally rocks!  Big thank you from the FDA Entrepreneurs in Residence team pic.twitter.com/VLSCOq3c    
    
    
    Somehow this explains how we're going to tackle clinical trials costs!. #FDAInnovation, #EIRkickoff event pic.twitter.com/ogBQr6u4    
    
    
    My whiteboard - gearing up to lead this year's Entrepreneurs in Residence program at FDA. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/qQ1KPS4v    
    
    
    Hate to say it, but the latest batch of TED talks sounded kinda like this. https://www.youtube.com/embed/DkGMY63FF3Q …    
    
    
    A weekend of inspiration with @sethgodin and a great group of entrepreneurs. Great food, great conversation. pic.twitter.com/nsVUOBPf    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson you hooked me. Great story!    
    
    
    Medical students develop EHR system targeting homeless, uninsured http://www.modernhealthcare.com/apps/pbcs.dll/article?AID=/20121023/NEWS/310239949&AllowView=VW8xUmo5Q21TcWJOb1gzb0tNN3RLZ0h0MWg5SVgra3NZRzROR3l0WWRMVGFWUDhDRWxiNUtpQzMyWmFyNVg4WUpiaW8=?trk=share … via @modrnhealthcr    
    
    
    You'll be itching to read this one! Of Mites and Men http://kimberlygerson.com/2012/10/of-mites-and-men/ … via @Kimberly_Gerson    
    
    
    These guys were awesome this weekend at @sethgodin event in NYC. http://hurrayfortheriffraff.com/  pic.twitter.com/Y5IwJy7W    
    
    
    Talk about cool!  Students have a place to innovate @CWRU at thinkbox. http://engineering.case.edu/thinkbox/     
    
    
    Today's philosophy:  if it doesn't sound like "YES", then it's "NO". Brings instant clarity to discussions.    
    
    
    “@whitehouseostp: Ultrathin dissolving #electronics...set to music. http://science.dodlive.mil/2012/10/22/electronics-dissolved-by-drops-of-liquid/ … @DARPA via @ArmedwScience <- loved the Chopin, too    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson yes, and she'll be frisked at the border, too.    
    
    
    @DrLeslieSaxon, woman, you deserve it!    
    
    
    “@Kimberly_Gerson: Nevermind Frankenstormzilla! JUST LOOK at this baby gazelle bouncing around. http://bit.ly/UNRzqE ” <- reincarnation wish!    
    
    
    “@FastCompany: This Week In Bots: The New Pet-Proto Video Will Creep You Out http://trib.al/rWYyWB ” <- could they make it less human, please?    
    
    
    Preparing for #Frankenstorm. pic.twitter.com/ManFQQZo    
    
    
    Preparing for #Frankenstorm <- people unclear on concept #neatpiles pic.twitter.com/pJjsPD7R    
    
    
    Preparing for #Frankenstorm. Calibrated rain catcher accurate to two decimal places. #not pic.twitter.com/YgPczPki    
    
    
    Flashlights. Check.  Batteries. Check. Preparing for #Frankenstorm. pic.twitter.com/5MYoYNQc    
    
    
    “@DrDave01: Do we need a specific mHealth regulator instead of the FDA? http://www.thedoctorweighsin.com/possible-office-of-mobile-health-proposed-to-regulate-mhealth/ …” <- Raises interesting implications.    
    
    
    @DrDave01 hard to answer because we still don't know what users will tolerate w.r.t. benefit-risk trade-off. And who r users? Consumers?    
    
    
    @DrDave01 but why don't we know the answer?  So many working on mobile apps nobody thought to explore user expectations? I'm incredulous.    
    
    
    Listening to Debussy creates a dreamy mindscape that is at odds with the technical writing I'm trying to get done today. #procrastination    
    
    
    @DrDave01 Excellent!  I'll follow the twitter feed.    
    
    
    “@Cascadia: #HCSM Don't forget to develop an emergency plan that includes your pets too - @CDCgov http://1.usa.gov/QOXGa6 ”<-mmm. Pets are tasty    
    
    
    Love the fact that the official spelling is, "nor'easter".  Argh, mateys!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Making its way to a medical device near you. Ready, FDA? http://www.fastcompany.com/3001739/ibms-watson-learning-its-way-saving-lives?utm_source=twitter …    
    
    
    How to Blow Away a Reporter...Literally http://kimberlygerson.com/2012/10/how-to-blow-away-a-reporter-literally/ … via @Kimberly_Gerson    
    
    
    I note no reference to #Frankenstorm  MT @whitehouse: Obama receives update on Hurricane #Sandy in the Situation Room: pic.twitter.com/JEdNtn11    
    
    
    @redheadlefthand We started hours ago in DC. You need to catch up!    
    
    
    He wanted a closer look-> “@Kimberly_Gerson: A shark swims through ... a Wildwood, NJ neighborhood- http://on.fb.me/S9Yupj  @WhySharksMatter)”    
    
    
    @Greggersh. Improvise. http://funtimeshad.com/2011/07/improvise/ … via @twitter_username    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson it's cuz the weather stops at the Canadian border, just like the map indicated.    
    
    
    @KimGerson hair disarranged, Beaufort 4! Hurricane Sandy Already Wreaking Havoc on NYC Landmarks http://funtimeshad.com/2012/10/hurricane-sandy-already-wreaking-havoc-on-nyc-landmarks/ … via @twitter_username    
    
    
    Putting the finishing touches on my talk for the American Academy of Orthopedic Surgeons, Sunday night in DC. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    Looking forward to presenting to the folks at #AAOS on Sunday!  http://www.orthopaedicdeviceforum.org/index.html     
    
    
    I'm using my extra hour to finish my talk for @AAOS1 Orthopedics Device Forum, tomorrow at 7 pm. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    I'm on the *ahem* young end of this, but it hits home! MT “@healthtechhatch: "Why Older Entrepreneurs Have an Edge" | http://bit.ly/SiNZQm ”    
    
    
    Its ok, but there's something I dislike #NOTart: “@FastCompany: Spray Paint Cans Hacked To Do Everything But Paint http://trib.al/Dr1y3Q ”    
    
    
    Its true *sob*.  I work in a turtle farm. @FastCompany: How Treating Your Employees Like Turtles Can Smother Innovation http://trib.al/R74maU     
    
    
    “@SCRAInnovation: CreatiVasc is one of only three companies to be selected for the FDA Innovation Pathway fasttrack program. @SoutheastBio.    
    
    
    Thank you @AAOS1 for inviting me to speak to your Ortho Device forum. Great group, great questions.    
    
    
    Oh, and not to press you too hard, @AAOS1, but I would really love one of your members to join my Entrepreneurs in Residence Strategic Team!    
    
    
    Taking this course today and loving it. Casting off the strictures of Powerpoint.  http://www.edwardtufte.com/tufte/courses     
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson THAT'S a wombat?!  Huh...    
    
    
    Culture change comes from changing the minds of individuals, allowing them to hold the old and new thoughts simultaneously. #wantanewFDA    
    
    
    @joachimkohn repeat entrepreneur now speaking at Rutgers Collaborative Innovation.    
    
    
    Great questions from audience at #rutgers collaborative innovation.    
    
    
    @harlan_weisman thank you for inviting me to be a panelist today. #rutgers collaborative innovation.    
    
    
    Me and some rock stars: Stephen Jones, Robert DiPaola at @Rutgers Collaborative Innovation.  https://mail-attachment.googleusercontent.com/attachment/u/0/s/?view=att&th=13b051747fc84cf4&attid=0.1&disp=attd&safe=1&zw&saduie=AG9B_P9yxK7pxj8E-cipNQ9xu8eq&sadet=1353000305522&sads=nyvLNlrXU05cZAEcDiCrMIfMfbs&sadssc=1 …    
    
    
    Great panel discussion this morning @Rutgers on how to strengthen the medical device ecosystem in @NJ and in the US. Rutgers innovation    
    
    
    @harlanweisman excellent job moderating our session - honored to be invited to represent @FDADeviceInfo #RutgersCollaborativeInnovation    
    
    
    “@Kimberly_Gerson: Once again @deborahblum grabs me by the heart. Please read this  -> Your Daughter Died  http://bit.ly/SZ5ndt  #crying    
    
    
    Me with a couple rock stars: Stephen Jones, Robert DiPaola at @Rutgers Collaborative Innovation. pic.twitter.com/CNtSX9ML    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson yesh, me too, alsho...want a koala baby.    
    
    
    I'm channeling 350 years of my pilgrim heritage in the kitchen today. #boilinggiblets    
    
    
    “Don’t try to win over the haters; you’re not the jackass whisperer.” Favorite line in @BreneBrown's "Daring Greatly" https://itunes.apple.com/us/book/daring-greatly/id512395427?mt=11 …    
    
    
    Another reason I love my dad: he got me my first subscription to OMNI magazine starting with issue No. 1 back in 1978!  http://www.omnimagonline.com/     
    
    
    “@BreneBrown: Good news! The final Daring Greatly Read-Along podcasts finally uploaded to iTunes. Sorry for the delay. http://bit.ly/PK1JTE ”    
    
    
    “@TheTweetOfGod: Retweeting this violates federal law.”  Allow me to be the first, then...    
    
    
    “@Kimberly_Gerson: Ha! The Polar Bears - A Colouring and Activity Book - http://bit.ly/X6gwip ” <- everyone on my list is getting this.    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson now you know where to "go"...    
    
    
    US CTO and Rockstar @todd_park  will be plugging our EIR program at http://www.leanstartup.co/speakers-mentors … #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    Watching "It's a Wonderful Life" for the umpteenth time and still loving it. "Buffalo gals won't you come out to niiiiight..." #classic    
    
    
    @Amsowers check this out, changes to DSM around autism dx. http://bigstory.ap.org/article/psychiatrists-ok-vast-changes-diagnosis-manual …    
    
    
    Spending the afternoon working on my @TED talk. I haven't been invited, but it's never too early to get started. #optimist    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson thanks for doin'...    
    
    
    Cutting through bureaucracy today. "Vulnerability is the birthplace of innovation, creativity & change" @BreneBrown <- tell that to @FDA.    
    
    
    "I see no advantage to these new clocks.  They run no faster than the ones made 100 years ago."  --Henry Ford, spoofing bureaucrats #sotrue    
    
    
    Yesterday's trauma: getting horribly lost in the mixing bowl of SE DC's detour-ridden morass of lane changes with a GPS last updated in 2010    
    
    
    Saying too much about this (the power of quiet) defeats the point. http://bit.ly/UvJFCb  #gointroverts!    
    
    
    The cat's obviously been busy lately. pic.twitter.com/tx3WkAnM    
    
    
    To truly understand the impact of a spinal cord injury, please read Ross Mason's personal narrative: http://bit.ly/YKW6gB  #Inspiring    
    
    
    @JohnFugelsang Clarence was the reason I bought a fake ID at age 16 in DC. Had to see him.    
    
    
    Hey everyone! Here is my lunch availability - http://letslunch.com/MeganM .  Let’s get together soon. @letslunch    
    
    
    @rmichaelg you inspired me, so I signed up, too!    
    
    
    Passing along to my musical colleagues. A film about an amazing "recycled orchestra" - Landfill Harmonic. http://vimeo.com/52711779 . #amazing.    
    
    
    Berwick's points hit close to home. Painful to watch bureaucracies + vested holders of staus quo stifle innovation. http://bit.ly/WZpwku     
    
    
    @ericries @wsj congrats, that's super!    
    
    
    @daniel_kraft Agreed!  Remember when I was first taken to see it as a kid.    
    
    
    “@DrJenGunter: UGH -> Tainted human body parts prompt FDA warning http://nbcnews.to/UkZvLF ”. Just a warning...?    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson can I follow you twice?    
    
    
    Super job by my three entrepreneurs-in-residence teams on their briefing with Center leadership at FDA.  You guys rock! #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    Team 1 from my entrepreneurs in residence group is studying why clinical trials take so long and how we can streamline them. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    EIR Team 2 is tackling the gnarly issue of how to get reimbursement for innovative devices. Big theme was: fear of FDA+CMS. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    Is FDA getting the balance right between pre- and post-market?  EIR Team 3 is tackling that. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    My team of rock stars, this year's entrepreneurs in residence at FDA: http://1.usa.gov/Sly8FS . #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    @DrDave kinda takes the fear out of filing with FDA doesn't he? http://bit.ly/Rt4U7H     
    
    
    @DrDave01 taking the mystery (and fear) out of filing with the FDA. C'mon in, the water's fine!  http://bit.ly/Rt4U7H     
    
    
    Heart is breaking over this. #CTshooting    
    
    
    Country needs to start a new dialog without the partisan buzz words. Start over, everybody. #CTshooting    
    
    
    Start the dialog over. Don't stake your positions at the outset, try to understand what's going on. We have to stop this. #CTshooting    
    
    
    What he said:  http://boingboing.net/2012/12/14/what-science-says-about-gun-co.html#more-200655 …    
    
    
    Finding a small amount of solice listening to Gabriel Faure's Cantique    
    
    
    Finding some solace in Faure's Cantique, http://bit.ly/TihzHA . #CTshooting    
    
    
    @DrDave01 Thanks for taking the FDA message to mHealth world. Folks, you don't HAVE to test your device on Dr Shuren! http://bit.ly/SrnKMI     
    
    
    “@DrDave01: @MegMoynahan @DrLeslieSaxon did the demo on him, not me ;)”. Story still cracks me up!  Maybe it will be part of our guidance..?    
    
    
    @TheTweetOfGod It's not you. It's us.    
    
    
    I'm reading this again, for about the fifth time, this time out loud to the kids. Starting a new Xmas ritual. http://bit.ly/UPYXwg     
    
    
    You must read this. Start the dialog on mental illness NOW. http://anarchistsoccermom.blogspot.com/2012/12/thinking-unthinkable.html …    
    
    
    FDA is not the only agency with a successful Entrepreneurs in Residence program!  Check this out from USCIS: http://1.usa.gov/114WRQ7     
    
    
    See you in San Diego for Frost+Sullivan MindXChange.  I'm giving the opening address March 12: Can FDA spur innovation?http://www.frost.com/prod/servlet/cpo/271050891 …    
    
    
    See you in San Diego for Frost+Sullivan MindXChange.  I'm giving the opening address March 12: Can FDA spur innovation? http://www.frost.com/prod/servlet/cpo/271050891 …    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson Ewww!    
    
    
    MT “@OpenNotion: Is there benchmark for future? #BigData will be mistake-prone iterative process not replacement of official stats.” Agree!    
    
    
    “@Paul_Sonnier: UCLA doctors remove man's heart, replace it with total artificial heart (wow!) http://newsroom.ucla.edu/portal/ucla/man-s-heart-removed-and-replaced-241430.aspx …” <- No app for that!    
    
    
    “@redheadlefthand: Look what I just found in the bathroom #nyc #pickyourself pic.twitter.com/iQwNvn1f” The invisible hand of @sethgodin    
    
    
    “@DrDave01: Analysis: 75 FDA-cleared mobile medical apps http://shar.es/hYDZj  via @sharethis” <- You rock, FDA!  I mean, "we"...    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson dwarf seahorse!  *snort*!    
    
    
    @TheTweetOfGod you don't think he's a little old for all that?    
    
    
    Wanna keep kids safe?  Ignore dumb @webMD list of dangerous toys and browse this http://1.usa.gov/TNOwfm .  2,456 trampoline injuries in 2012?!    
    
    
    I'm fascinated by the NEISS registry of injuries. http://1.usa.gov/TNOwfm . 2 yo runs after bubbles, into brambles, cuts leg. #howkidsgethurt    
    
    
    Dumb @webmd "toxic toys" http://on.webmd.com/1070qGu  thinks slightly higher lead content is worth yr worry. #nodata. Real info http://1.usa.gov/TNOwfm     
    
    
    Holiday wishes to everyone! pic.twitter.com/v4xJc815    
    
    
    Super science blogger (and my sister!) @Kimberly_Gerson makes a great point about "science" toys in today's NYT http://nyti.ms/ZxIvcW     
    
    
        
    
    
    Watching the Odd Couple Christmas special ("Scrooge Gets an Oscar") in honor of our fav Jack Klugman. #misshim    
    
    
    @FiftyThree I would love it if you could invent a "tracing paper" option where you bring up a photo, put tracing paper over, then interpret    
    
    
    “@FastCompany: An ICU Monitor That Fits On Your Wrist http://trib.al/vsaHHrO ” <- @FDADeviceInfo cool new technology coming our way!    
    
    
    @ProjectMyGov totally love this. A must read for anyone trying to change the culture.    
    
    
    Good news for me!  I should live to be 100...  http://on.today.com/U3v8er     
    
    
    @GoCareSimple I'm with you! Trying to nudge you over the top!    
    
    
    Sure, Big Data Is Great. But So Is Intuition. http://nyti.ms/YYhHRL     
    
    
    Congrats to big sister @Kimberly_Gerson for making Scientific American's list of top animal stories for 2012! http://bit.ly/WehBza     
    
    
    'The Icarus Deception' By Seth Godin Wants Readers To 'Make A Ruckus' And 'Stand Out' http://huff.to/YGSuGH  via @HuffPostBooks    
    
    
    @DanielPink here's how one blogger suggested doing it: http://kimberlygerson.com/2012/12/head-off-the-holidays-with-kims-solstice-step-up-challenge/ …    
    
    
    @thefda wow, 140 seconds of unbridled enthusiasm!  You go!    
    
    
    In top med tech stories, @todd_park and @vkhosla bringing new thinking and insights, among others. http://venturebeat.com/2012/12/30/health-tech/ …    
    
    
    FDA's Center for Drugs gets all to approve all the cool new stuff!  Dragons Blood, really? http://bloom.bg/UHSxnG     
    
    
    @alexgoldfayn Thanks for the follow. You've got a great message worth spreading.    
    
    
    Here's my reading list for early 2013. Crash course in philanthrocapitalism. http://www.philanthrocapitalism.net/2012/12/books-of-the-year-2/ …    
    
    
    “@TEDMED: First 10 @TEDMED speakers announced for 2013!  http://bit.ly/TLcrfG ” I'm not on the list THIS year, but ever optimistic!    
    
    
    “@TEDMED: First 10 @TEDMED speakers announced for 2013!  http://bit.ly/TLcrfG ” congrats to good friend @ElazerEdelman    
    
    
    @redheadlefthand Michelle, do you have a "clone" here in DC who does what you do?    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson did it!    
    
    
    Polar bear stymied by latest technology: human vending machine. http://bit.ly/137r4Ph     
    
    
    I'll be speaking at the Nat'l Academies Biomed Eng Materials and Applications Roundtable on Wed. Hope to see you there! http://sites.nationalacademies.org/deps/nmmb/deps_060366 …    
    
    
    My talk Wed at Nat'l Academies BEMA Roundtable: FDA's Innovation Pathway - can the FDA spur innovation?    
    
    
    @TEDMED anxiety    
    
    
    FDA's Entrepreneurs in Residence program picked as one of Gray Sheet's top stories for 2012.  http://bit.ly/UvMBef  #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    @TheTweetOfGod I predict a surge in hits to this Wikipedia site http://bit.ly/TZthHU     
    
    
    Every person living with spinal cord injury has a unique story to tell. @ReeveFoundation has them here. http://bit.ly/TJR5Aw  @illwalk    
    
    
    @nancyduarte congrats, well deserved!    
    
    
    There is a society for EVERYTHING!  rock, paper, scissors, anyone?  http://www.worldrps.com/game-basics     
    
    
    “@tgraydar: Turn your kids' three-legged elephant drawings into 3-D printed sculpture with Crayon Creatures. http://www.fastcompany.com/3004577/designer-uses-3-d-printing-turn-your-childs-drawings-sculptures …” #iwant!    
    
    
    Quote heard at BEMA mtg yesterday: "Now that @todd_park is running the federal government..."  Yeah, I believe I voted in that election!    
    
    
    CES: Scanadu Tracks Your Vitals The Non-Invasive Way (VIDEO) - Forbes http://lnkd.in/-qBptr     
    
    
    Designers wanted:  check out @ThisIsSethsBlog opportunity: http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/01/designing-for-growth.html …    
    
    
    Congratulations to good friend Scott Bruder on his new position at Stryker! http://yhoo.it/13kOn8n     
    
    
    FDA approves new IUD http://huff.to/VWdUP4     
    
    
    The FDA entrepreneurs in residence teams are chugging along! Next step: inside view from staff. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/jKwbHvlo    
    
    
    The @whitehouseostp response to Death Star petition is hilarious and going viral. Remember to fill out online feedback. http://1.usa.gov/10oVuy1     
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson would love to read it but boingboing apparently can't handle the traffic. #crashing    
    
    
    Until you commit to "all in" youre not really a startup founder. MT @tendayiviki: 
http://buff.ly/UCbcU2  by Steve Blank in WSJ #leanstartup    
    
    
    @kwameulmer yeah that book totally rocks! ("War of Art")    
    
    
    “@nancyduarte: A peek inside @IDEO's David Kelley's unique home & workspace. I *heart* him! http://cbsn.ws/TVivlH  via @CBSNews” <- huge fan!    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson funny: I got two tweets BETWEEN those back to back posts"!    
    
    
    Follow my tweets today on FDA's entrepreneurs in residence program. Three challenging projects. Six months to solve. #FDAInnovation    
    
    
    EIR Team 1 is figuring out how we can speed clinical trials for medical devices. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/yGXZPFVM    
    
    
    Breaking down the device development process so we can fix it. EIR open house at FDA. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/NgTqJhE6    
    
    
    EIR team 2 will tackle the FDA approval to reimbursement pathway. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/h7dohB7Q    
    
    
    EIR Team 3 asks how to get the balance right between pre- and post-market for med devices. #FDAInnovation pic.twitter.com/ti2jGa6p    
    
    
    @patientslikeme awesome mention!    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson I'm starting late, but now I'm ready to tackle my #couchpotato lifestyle. 20 minutes on treadmill, one-third jogging. #sigh    
    
    
    X Prize Foundation CEO Peter Diamandis reminds us of the power of incentive prizes and grand challenges. http://bit.ly/Wn9HoF     
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson can't wait to read the result!    
    
    
    @greeneggxanham so sorry to hear!    
    
    
    MT “@Kimberly_Gerson: I'm abt to be interviewed for the 34th yr in a row for this longitudinal study. http://www.bls.gov/nls/nlsy79.htm ” <- me too!    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson ahhhggh, just brings me to tears to read your last post. So sorry.  :-(    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson @greeneggxanham well my interview took 2 hours, so that's probably a deterrant for an online form.    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson I suppose it could have been some other kind of asshole. #eitherway.    
    
    
    @stevenvDC testifies that federal IT programs are "at an inflection point" http://fedscoop.com/vanroekel-testifies-on-the-state-of-federal-it/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @DrJenGunter If this comes to pass, I will end my personal boycott of all-things-Oprah    
    
    
    Today's big news: I've announced I'll be leaving the #FDA. Have enjoyed my 17 years here and I'm looking forward to my next gig. Stay tuned!    
    
    
    Today's jog felt different.  I actually ... jogged?  Felt better. #startingfromzero    
    
    
    Leaving FDA. HR person: "Why didn't you fill out this form before you came to see me?" Me: "How would I have known...? Wha..?" #firsttime    
    
    
    MT “@DrWeidner: “@HITNewsTweet: FDA gives OK to first telemedicine robot http://ow.ly/h6uho  |" <-- not sure why we regulated it, but cool!    
    
    
    @greeneggxanham ugh, it sounds awful!  Feeling any better?    
    
    
    @waldojaquith huh?  Maybe federal highways could keep government hours, too.    
    
    
    @FDADeviceInfo  Why aren't we tweeting about this? http://bit.ly/XBVDpY . Everybody else is.    
    
    
    “@PLOSONE: A perspective on Cervical Health Awareness Month, at the EveryONE blog http://blogs.plos.org/everyone/2013/01/25/cervical-health-awareness-month/ …” <-- is this necks, or...?    
    
    
    @DanielPink I'm feeling a little Mamihlapinatapai as we speak...    
    
    
    @kwameulmer excellent, thanks!    
    
    
    @ThisIsSethsBlog Points 2-11 follow directly from point #1    
    
    
    “@Kimberly_Gerson: Croat has elephant trunk tattooed onto his penis - http://bit.ly/XfyETg  #allgood #nopics” <-- #ripoff    
    
    
    Don't be a know-it-all, at least not when pitching your awesone idea to the esteemed @tomfogarty: http://bit.ly/XQJuht     
    
    
    MT “@WSJ: Who is to blame if a driverless car gets into a wreck? http://on.wsj.com/XQetub ” <- let's cross that bridge when we get there    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja I'll be with you in spirit, but not in person!    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja wish I were there!  Former colleague of mine from FDA will be speaking, though.    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja Dude, you can totally get me a speaking gig and I will be there!    
    
    
    @daniel_kraft @singularityu Wish I were there!  Maybe next year.    
    
    
    “@Christianassad: @Daniel_Kraft showing his Vital Signs Live at #futuremed on Vimeo http://ht.ly/hpWM7 ” <- dude, you've been working out!    
    
    
    @todd_park The PIF teams totally ROCK!  Thank you for making it cool to work for the Feds. We do great stuff, and these guys really help.    
    
    
    “@ManeeshJuneja: @vkhosla #Innovation never happens without experimentation. That requires some tolerance of failure #futuremed” <- Agree!    
    
    
    @CaliforniaKara it was awesome!    
    
    
    “@ManeeshJuneja: @thefda Can we move from a century of regeneration to a decade of regeneration? A visionary! pic.twitter.com/5IoVyMfK” AGREE!    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja @thefda Now you know why I love this guy!  Truly rocks!    
    
    
        
    
    
    “@ManeeshJuneja: @thefda FDA & DARPA: An optimal marriage? #futuremed pic.twitter.com/hvc1aUxy” Yes!  That partnership is great!    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja @thefda @farzad_onc Any pics, Maneesh?    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja Well, thanks for your other pics. They were great.    
    
    
    @Yahya1399Yahya @maneeshjuneja @thefda ... But I think it was the FDA that proposed...!    
    
    
    Hey everyone! Here is my lunch availability - http://letslunch.com/MeganM .  Let’s get together soon. @letslunch    
    
    
    Love this guy, shattering peoples view of disability. Get Armed & Ready http://www.travelchannel.com/video/get-armed-and-ready …    
    
    
    “@healthtechhatch: HealthTechHatch: The Doctor Is Not In [INFOGRAPHIC] http://tinyurl.com/af8kfsr ” < I love infographics, here's a great example    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fox with late stage mange trying to keep warm and scratching like crazy in our back yard. (Hard to see pic) pic.twitter.com/Z0SDOK3l    
    
    
    “@DanielPink: A powerful warning to college profs from a high school teacher . . .  http://ow.ly/hAw3z ” << Factory education is so wrong    
    
    
    @Kimberly_Gerson great question!    
    
    
    @brainpicker So simple and so beautiful.    
    
    
    “@brainpicker: Best thing ever: Mathemusician Vi Hart explains space-time with a music box and a Möbius strip http://j.mp/WYOuUP ”    
    
    
    Dear  @MarsCuriosity Rover, I would like a ventifact for Christmas this year.  I've been good.  http://www.jpl.nasa.gov/images/msl/20130211/ventifacts.pdf …    
    
    
    “@vkhosla: Google X Head on Moonshots: How 10X Is Easier Than 10 Percent ; 10X is definitely worth trying!  http://bit.ly/V1tRce ” << YES!    
    
    
    Not surprisingly, young people find the pace of the federal government too slow and opt out of that career track. http://bit.ly/WqbXgo     
    
    
    “@DanielPink: 6 new pitches for selling your product, your idea, or yourself . . . http://ow.ly/hI6cq  (via The Pink Blog)” << Love this!    
    
    
    MT “@ManeeshJuneja: Beyond the hype of the FDA’s approval of the first bionic eye | MedCity News: http://medcitynews.com/2013/02/beyond-the-hype-of-the-fdas-approval-of-the-first-bionic-eye/#.UR15pxoB3kE.twitter … < urges patience    
    
    
    Today's weather: sunny and warm with a 30% chance of meteor showers...    
    
    
    @kwameulmer It would be cool to write a bio with your aspirations for your future self!    
    
    
    John Cleese on creativity: "Nothing will stop you being creative so effectively as the fear of making a mistake.”
http://bit.ly/YgWlJB     
    
    
    ACA is based on flawed assumptions about doctor and patient behavior. The coming failure of #ACO's http://on.wsj.com/12Fw5jV ”    
    
    
    "The only way for a woman...to know herself as a person, is by creative work of her own." Betty Friedan http://j.mp/136ogPy     
    
    
        
    
    
    Save date: March 20 #FDA will seek advisory panel input on Abbott's MitraClip for mitral regurgitation. http://1.usa.gov/WaiwXH     
    
    
    I just love this article SO much: Larry Page on moon shots and why 10X   is easier than 10%.  http://bit.ly/Xsv1vO     
    
    
    Let's hope #FDA doesn't decide to regulate enhanced sensory experience products like this cool "Spidey Sense" suit: http://bit.ly/Xsvuhx     
    
    
    "And the only thing people regret is that they didn’t live boldly enough, that they didn’t invest enough heart, didn’t love enough." THughes    
    
    
    Take a look: How the sequester will shake out for grants to states.  An infographic.  http://bit.ly/UXhbSt     
    
    
    MT E Zerhouni on imminent sequestration. http://wapo.st/YPqAJF .   Sequestration affects a LOT more than NIH.  8.2% cuts for most agencies.    
    
    
    “@HRSonline: Novel ICD programming reduces mortality, http://ow.ly/hNhyB ”<< Very cool!  Reduces inappropriate shocks from ICDs.    
    
    
    @kwameulmer Yes, that's fantastic advice.  A must read.    
    
    
    Nice dinner last night with good friends Paul Sobotka and @frankbaitman, reminiscing about hanging out in #FDA's #bullpen last year.    
    
    
    Two big names in mHealth, Kerry McDermott and Harry Greenspun, explaining how mHealth can save money for feds. http://bit.ly/WguEXg     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @brainpicker you may enjoy this:  http://bit.ly/12ddPyT , first film of seahorses, nice story.    
    
    
    Cool new mHealth masters degree at Case Western's San Diego campus, courtesy of corporate sponsor Qualcomm: http://bit.ly/XmMTY2     
    
    
    Paralympian Jen French receives Rolex Yachtswoman of the Year Award, standing with electrical stim system. http://bit.ly/9rTL0p     
    
    
    @greeneggxanham @kim_moynahan Whhhaaaaaat!  OMG, OMG!  Does that make me a great aunt!?    
    
    
    @MegMoynahan @greeneggxanham @kim_moynahan oh...wait... NOT a grandmother. Crikey woman, you had me all worked up!    
    
    
    Jackie Acho asks, have you hugged an intrapreneur today? Heres why you should! http://bit.ly/15yVyKj     
    
    
    Catch me at Frost and Sullivan MindXChange in San Diego.  My keynote is tomorrow morning.    
    
    
    Ray Cohen from (former) Vessix Vascular: set unreasonable expectations to get your team inspired. #dev13    
    
    
    Do you grow people or replace them?  "Growing is for farmers" - Ray Cohen. #dev13    
    
    
    Sadly, I will miss Luck o' the Irish Casino Night tonite. I feel I'd have a big advantage, too.  #dev13    
    
    
    @dangents I'm on tomorrow.  Wish me luck!    
    
    
    Tomorrow my keynote will be my first time speaking about the FDA from my new vantage outside of the agency. #dev13 #feelingbold    
    
    
    @dangents I prefer your royal highness...    
    
    
    @dangents my fervent wish...    
    
    
    @dangents ahh,that was CMS I had to disparage.    
    
    
    @dangents scarves and lavalier mikes do not mix.    
    
    
    Joe Kiani strongly urging industry not to get complacent in accepting the current ecosystem for medical devices. #dev13    
    
    
    @dangents pacemaker hacking is a whole lotta misplaced effort and angst.    
    
    
    The Little Book of Leadership http://lnkd.in/FqpU2k     
    
    
    I sneezed on my iPad and it briefly stopped working. Snot and touch screens are a bad combo. #coldfromhell    
    
    
    Makers of automatic external defibrillators will now pay $250K to file with #FDA, up from $5K, thanks to new ruling. http://1.usa.gov/YoimgN     
    
    
    New #FDA ruling means higher cost, longer time to bring AEDs to market, http://1.usa.gov/YoimgN     
    
    
        
    
    
    Excellent post by Jackie Acho: asking how to get more women in science is the wrong question. http://bit.ly/10Subrl     
    
    
    @waldojaquith I use an app called stopwatch+    
    
    
    @ManeeshJuneja congratulations!    
    
    
    @jackieacho thanks!    
    
    
    “@jackieacho: #Innovation culture at FDA?  Yes! Because of #intrapraneurs like @megmoynahan http://bmctoday.net/evtoday/2013/03/article.asp?f=fda-response-to-medical-device-regulatory-challenges …”    
    
    
    Help remember young victims of sudden cardiac arrest.  http://www.c-r-y.org.uk/northeast_postcard_launch_2009.htm …    
    
    
    @Kim_Moynahan @torontostar what planet are the writers from?!    
    
    
    Can we focus on empathy and identity to stem the violence of young men?  @jackieacho's compelling ideas put forward: http://bit.ly/14EHH8O     
    
    
    @Bethmg1286 sorry I'm slow getting back to you. Would live to chat about AEDs.    
    
    
    "Empathy is a contact sport - must be done one relationship at a time" Excellent post by @jackieacho http://bit.ly/19M3kAT     
    
    
    Wondering what an exponential technology of the future might be?  Im finding out tonight, here: http://bit.ly/16zMER2     
    
    
    Walter deBrouwer of @scanadu  at #singularity Fox Studios event. Future of innovation. pic.twitter.com/MEZKSbnekY    
    
    
    What the frack?  Get FACTS about shale gas at this meeting sponsored by the National Academy of Engineering and CWRU: http://naeshalegas.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Our project can run instead of walk now, thanks to our recently-award $3M grant from Ohio Third Frontier: http://www.crainscleveland.com/article/20130612/FREE/130619901# …    
    
    
    What's the most critical component in many medical devices?  Batteries!  Today's FDA workshop on this topic:  http://1.usa.gov/17R6Avo     
    
    
    Fires and explosions in the hospital?  Trace back to battery problems. Learn more at FDA workshop today. http://1.usa.gov/17R6Avo     
    
    
    Awesome!  Guy with prosthetic hand can feel again.  More kick-ass results from the group in Cleveland: http://bit.ly/14bjpwi     
    
    
    Hi @dontgetcaught - I'd love to learn how I can work with you on my TEDx talk.    
    
    
    @dontgetcaught Will do!    
    
    
    It's official!  I'll be on stage at @TEDxBrussels on October 28, joining some really amazing talent. Looking forward to it, @samialounis.    
    
    
    @katedrane, looks like we will be sharing the @TEDxBrussels stage in a few weeks. Can't wait to meet you! Would love to talk in advance.    
    
    
    New mobile apps guidance from FDA has some folks excited. http://bit.ly/1fcFHcB   I'm reserving judgement, but stay tuned.    
    
    
    My thoughts on @FDADeviceInfo 's #mobileappsguidance: still over-reaches and stifles innovation. http://1.usa.gov/nKd3bA     
    
    
    P 11 of #FDA #Apps guidance says your app won't be regulated if used for "research, teaching or analysis"  Go forth! http://1.usa.gov/nKd3bA     
    
    
    P.16 of #FDA #Apps FDA takes a hands-off approach to mobile apps that "help patients...self-manage their disease" http://1.usa.gov/nKd3bA     
    
    
        
    
    
    I timed my @TEDxBrussels talk tonight. Coming in just under the 18 minute limit. #talkfaster? pic.twitter.com/J8Xgk66JMQ    
    
    
    30 promising young professionals to watch: http://case.edu/think/fallwinter2013/30under30/ …
Great collection of talent here!    
    
    
    My age 14 science project: activate frog muscles from signals picked up from my muscles.  Hear more @TEDxBrussels. We've come a long way!    
    
    
    Why are mother ducks better leaders than most Fortune 500 CEO's?  Find out in @jackieacho's Currency of Empathy post: http://bit.ly/1eg2oIZ     
    
    
    My #furloughed husband just coined a new term:  "furloafing". It's how he's spending his time.    
    
    
    Great pic! Who says people living with paralysis / spinal cord injury, should be pitied? Hear more at @TEDxBrussels pic.twitter.com/gV2564nElx    
    
    
    How does Galvani's frog experiment (pic) fit into current medical management of SCI?  Find out @TEDxBrussels pic.twitter.com/IaoENVHBsq    
    
    
    The @TEDxBrussels schedule has posted. http://bit.ly/16lnqGs  My talk is "Engineering the Human Nervous System" - can't wait to give it!    
    
    
    @jackieacho TY, I'm psyched up for next week - thanks for all your helpful comments, and - more importantly - your caring support.    
    
    
    @Amalyamusic @TEDxBrussels can't wait to meet you!    
    
    
    Big thanks to @dontgetcaught Denise Graveline for helping me prep for @TEDxBrussels ! I'm ready to go!    
    
    
    At Dulles airport heading out to Brussels. On my way to #TEDxBrussels   Chocolate and beer, here I come!    
    
    
    @Amalyamusic let me know when you get in and we can catch up. I'm here doing some sightseeing today.    
    
    
    Enjoying Brussels at its best -  with an excellent beer. #tedxbrussels pic.twitter.com/cO0lTgU0Ye    
    
    
        
    
    
    View from my hotel. The rain stopped!  Countdown to #tedxbrussels. pic.twitter.com/owBfCTx3fR    
    
    
    Great sky for dramatic pics today. #brussels pic.twitter.com/arnhRiNfJ3    
    
    
    @SiMcKeag @TEDxBrussels Thank you for all your work to make it happen!    
    
    
    The red circle. It really exists. @TEDxBrussels pic.twitter.com/uqnUNmAYgI    
    
    
    Rehearsing in the empty Bozar. @TEDxBrussels pic.twitter.com/8npX45Fy7a    
    
    
    View from the stage at Bozar theater. #tedxbrussels pic.twitter.com/q5CUr9rCLC    
    
    
    @NeelieKroesEU "you have to have failures, it shows that you are taking risks" @TEDxBrussels    
    
    
    @simplescott showing us the power of a universal pictorial language. @TEDxBrussels    
    
    
    Diana Reiss telling humorous story about how she got a time-out from her research subject: a bottle nosed dolphin. @TEDxBrussels    
    
    
    Yay, shout out to Case Western Reserve University at @TEDxBrussels    
    
    
    @Rozxtar count me in!    
    
    
    @dontgetcaught @TEDxBrussels Thank YOU for the awesome coaching on my talk.    
    
    
    @sam_debrouwer and @walterdebrouwer Thank you for the opportunity to reach an awesome audience with my talk. @TEDxBrussels    
    
    
    @andy_cornwell @ClevelandFES thanks!  It was a great honor to represent our work today to this awesome audience.    
    
    
    Thank you, @TEDxBrussels, for hosting a wonderful event!  I enjoyed reaching the crowd with my message: http://youtu.be/Nsxw5_Iz7mY     
    
    
    @BorgFest TY for the  mention.    
    
    
    @BorgFest you might appreciate this one!  It inspired me... pic.twitter.com/Q1UXXcMeBE    
    
    
    Hey, @TEDMED, where does kick-ass biomedical engineering fit into your program?  Here's my offering:  http://www.tedxbrussels.eu/megan-moynahan#.Un_KleBDRG8 …    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @FDA gets it wrong again.  Consumers are NOT like patients.  FDA is using the wrong model to assess @23&Me http://on.wsj.com/1hwOG8J     
    
    
    #FDA is supposed to be evidence-based but they are not considering the evidence provided by @23andMe that shows consumers don't overreact    
    
    
    @23andMe - consumers are NOT patients.  @US_FDA is using the wrong risk-benefit model to assess this product.    
    
    
    @dgmacarthur @23andMe Agreed. This was a thoughtful article and laid out the legal angles in play right now.    
    
    
    @23andMe As a former FDA-er I can say that it is absolutely imperative that you establish a NEW path as the front-runner. Happy to help.    
    
    
    Attending @NANS2013Meeting today. Off to a great start with Allan Basbaum.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Kevin Kilgore explains how kilohertz frequency stimulation breaks the basic paradigm for neural and muscular effects. @NANS2013Meeting    
    
    
    Kevin Kilgore gives a plea to researchers to report accurate technical descriptions of high frequency stimulation studies. @NANS2013Meeting    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wow!  Cherry destruction has dropped to an all-time low with new sensory-feedback prosthetics:  http://bit.ly/1cqCiTz     
    
    
    