Looking for #business books to read, check the suggestions at #SheOwnIt - You'll get mine + 21 others (in good co.) http://ow.ly/o94K5     
    
    
    e-Commerce 101: Simple Tips to Convert Shoppers into Buyers http://ow.ly/oaSCQ  #ecommercetips    
    
    
    Hi @fionacartolina, with your new beautiful online store, I thought that you might enjoy my latest post on ecommerce http://ow.ly/oaWZc     
    
    
    Good morning! We have a nice sunny day here in Montreal to finish the work week. What about you?    
    
    
    If you read my experience trying to buy online a bowl for my @Kitchenaid food processor, it arrived this morning http://ow.ly/ocIwv     
    
    
    They have a fascinating story RT @mitchjoel: @theminimalists show you how to start a successful blog today http://bit.ly/1dzkkPm     
    
    
    @pinkbathtub I'll take a wonderful Saturday over a nice Friday.    
    
    
    Happy to be helpful. Have a great Friday. RT @fionacartolina: @KimVallee Thank you - you are so smart  :-)    
    
    
    Same 2 u RT @jeanpierrelevac: #FF @karinefrigon @seetsirbas @letechnophile @MarmaladesApp @_Celestia_ @MelanieGhanime @DerekJen @toddyflores    
    
    
    Long meetings are a waste of time. @Janine Popick shared how to structure yours as a 30 Minute Meeting http://ow.ly/ocSz7  #businesstips    
    
    
    How do you like it? RT @evanpro: My first @breather experience (@ Breather at Notman House) [pic]: http://4sq.com/14pCO1x     
    
    
    We need to RT @gsquare_offices: @KimVallee when time is limited, people become more productive. would you agree?    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @vast_media: Happy #FF back! :) @Seevibes @MariaSanz @KimVallee @CJDLTV @benmenson @mvargasgarro @AstridRory    
    
    
    @contributorweek Awesome! Keep me posted on what the @twitter cards did for you.    
    
    
    New on Balancing Act: Why Kids Need Day Care in Top of a Family Life #worklifebalance http://ow.ly/oejq7     
    
    
    Having fun building and destroying Playbrix structures #toy #familyfun http://instagram.com/p/dZp3DaNHz3/     
    
    
    I saw why on LinkedIn. Congratulations! RT @evanpro: @KimVallee I'm biased! /cc @breather    
    
    
    @Stammy Just read this article.    
    
    
    Dear @inc, adding the post URLs would be useful. On the Fast Track: @paulg Paul Graham's Top Tips for Start-ups http://ow.ly/ohmms     
    
    
    Why our brains can’t handle negative thoughts and 4 tips for cultivating positive thinking by @bellebethcooper http://ow.ly/ohnyH     
    
    
    For the right reasons RT @joelgascoigne: "Looking 4 Startup Ideas? 1st, Pick Market u Want to Serve" http://buff.ly/19UsxPn  by @kevindewalt    
    
    
    @kevindewalt Simply want to help in telling you a typo in 1st FAQ of @sohelpful. It's written somone instead of someone. Nice concept!    
    
    
    Love that! RT @fastcompany: "...companies with at least one woman on their board tend to be the strongest performers."...    
    
    
    @marianneprairie Bon retour! Mon bébé n'en ait plus un à près de 2 ans et demi. Ce que j'aime mieux à cet âge est le début des conversations    
    
    
    Any sales cuz of it? RT @fionacartolina: Cartolina iPhone cases featured on Macworld's website this morning http://www.macworld.com/article/2047260/the-week-in-iphone-cases-hogtown.html …    
    
    
    @fionacartolina That is great!    
    
    
    Former Ticketmaster exec will develop shopping experience on @Twitter. Want to team up w/ merchants 'n paymt services http://adage.com/u/uEshaa     
    
    
    My first experience. Love the rocking chair (not in my photo). @breather has the best room at Notman House for sure http://4sq.com/15f1Enx     
    
    
    A acheté de beaux casse-tête pour Zack. Ils ont aussi de belles boîtes à Lynch pour les enfants (@ Papillotte) [pic]: http://4sq.com/17mIGr4     
    
    
    J'ai acheté un beau coussin hibou et une jetée pour soit la chambre de Zack ou notre salon. Il était ds la vitrine... http://4sq.com/1dro0Fo     
    
    
    Before I went shopping for my son, Allen made me prettier. I have a new hair style: a sexy short look http://4sq.com/1dnF52f     
    
    
    Zack's new owl cushion #kidsroom http://instagram.com/p/dlHHLOtH4C/     
    
    
    The same owl cushion without effects http://instagram.com/p/dlHRZftH4O/     
    
    
    @pushinteriors I could not resist when I saw it.    
    
    
    At @montreal_cm #mtlcm -this month theme is about urbanism. Popular, as you can see (at @ccawire) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16WconN     
    
    
    Superb mask for @montreal_cm #mtlcm for the conference by Louise Guay @louiseguay @ Centre Canadien… http://instagram.com/p/doz085tH9l/     
    
    
    On doit amener la campagne à la ville (ex. les petites forêts) et rendre les rues accessibles aux citoyens pas seul. Aux autos #mtlcm    
    
    
    Le pouvoir du citoyen a grandi grâce à la technologie. Une plus grande collaboration ds la planification de la ville est possible #mtlcm    
    
    
    Le message final #mtlcm est #Montreal plateforme collaborative.    
    
    
    La qualité de vie part de la vie dans son quartier. Le fait de travailler près de chez-soi ou le télé-travail y contribue beaucoup. #mtlcm    
    
    
    @marielefebvre La photo de la montagne d'asphalte avec la borne fontaine est comique.    
    
    
    Brands need to rethink brand ownership. It can be shared with their customers and followers @HarvardBiz http://ow.ly/oqiS6  #socialmedia    
    
    
    Good Saturday morning! A mix of clouds and t-storms all day and night.    
    
    
    Inspiring when having a latte RT @nikastewart: Behind every successful woman is a substantial amount of coffee.    
    
    
    Sauf l'hiver quand il y a de la poudrerie RT @marianik1968: Ma partie favorite de l'Autoroute 10. http://instagram.com/p/dsMKP9op9e/     
    
    
    @jennbrouwer I saw that, at last, you're inside.    
    
    
    Movie night for a date with my @JeromeParadis tonight.    
    
    
    Make your emails really easy to reply to RT @claire: Why Every Email Should be 5 Sentences Long: http://bit.ly/154umBA  #businesstips    
    
    
    Including a look at the big data landscape RT @michellelaberge: How small businesses can mine big data http://lnkd.in/TF9Dvb  #businesstips    
    
    
    I do! RT @glamamama: @NinaLjutic @JennBrouwer @vanessajfrancis @kimberleyseldon @NicholasRosaci @rad3sixty @damask_dentelle Happy Hump Day!    
    
    
    Preparing Our Kids for the Job Market of Today and Tomorrow http://ow.ly/ozLCL  #education #innovation    
    
    
    @martinlessard Mon dernier billet pourrait t'intéresser http://ow.ly/ozLJx  - Je reprends des idées de ta balado sur le iPad à l'école    
    
    
    @adelemcalear Have you see that @sparksandhoney are naming Digital Death Manager as one of the 20 jobs of the future? http://ow.ly/ozNht     
    
    
    @martinlessard Tout à fait vrai.    
    
    
    Good morning! It starts to feel like autumn. 10° C this morning.    
    
    
    The lesson: need to treat your products like a client- Insight That Changed the Way I’m Building My Business http://alexisgrant.com/2013/09/04/insight-on-products/ …    
    
    
    @eventbrite expands offering by acquiring Lanyrd, Eventioz #businessnews http://agbeat.com/social-media/eventbrite-acquires-lanyrd-eventioz/ …    
    
    
    For back to school, I discussed the challenges of the #education system and how I think we could change http://ow.ly/oAulh     
    
    
    Article by @salon argued that biggest problem in #education is the school itself. They teach that learning is work http://ow.ly/oB4fO     
    
    
    BTW homeschooling your kids is not the answer. Too many kids will be left down by the system + your kids will lack the social interactions    
    
    
    5 Fun DIY Camera Kits that take 35mm film http://on.mash.to/1ak4bPb  via @mashable #photography    
    
    
    I like #4 and #5 - The 5 Worst Pieces of Advice for Small Business Owners http://on.mash.to/1dHLVQ0  via @mashable    
    
    
    Indeed! I look forward to see what people will say RT @suzlortie: Video: Moment Factory’s latest project is off the wall...    
    
    
    A product that geeks will buy for the WAF (Wife Acceptance Factor) - Fake Book Covers Conceal Video Games http://on.mash.to/19kxrRb  #etsy    
    
    
    My framework doesn't necessary follow this order but overall an #entrepreneur must answer these 5 essential questions http://ow.ly/oBeVI     
    
    
    @clarashih Congrats Clarah for the new money you raised for @HearsaySocial!    
    
    
    Any suggestions of what to do (with kids) in New york City this weekend. #travel    
    
    
    @stevey it was great! Maybe next time we  will have the chance to chat.    
    
    
    @hi_catherine  you are the second person who suggested the Museum of National History. I'll check it out    
    
    
    @hi_catherine early might be hard for me. I'm not a morning person :-)    
    
    
    Beautiful day in New York http://instagram.com/p/d9yzrDNHz0/     
    
    
    A hotshot at corner of Ninth Ave and W 14th Street for #CottonOrNothing http://instagram.com/p/d9zkDANH1T/     
    
    
    On the High Line #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d92IHWNH5k/     
    
    
    Human statue by Frank Benson #highline #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d93woxtH9G/     
    
    
    The assortment of artisanal soda at the Brooklyn Soda Works stand on the High Line #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d96-TXNHz8/     
    
    
    @KimVallee This tweet should have said a photo shoot not a hotspot    
    
    
    My son made his mom proud. He wanted to explore the @Anthropologie store. He knows how to win my heart. #priceless    
    
    
    @coffeeandcouch plus, he understood that I wanted to buy a book. So, we took a copy and remembered that we had to give it to the cashier    
    
    
    @coffeeandcouch how are you?    
    
    
    @NinaLjutic thanks for the #ff. I was off the grid for most of the day yesterday    
    
    
    Mingling with the locals on a gorgeous day (@ Street Fair w/ @jeromeparadis) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1cVHzSG     
    
    
    Good morning! Another sunny day in New York. Currently 18° C. Perfect for a day in Central Park with my toddler boy    
    
    
    While search and customized landing pages could improve #mobile #shopping, the biggest pain remains the checkout. http://ow.ly/oHmG8     
    
    
    Did it! RT @iconversations: @KimVallee vote for @iConversations six times per day. #Award Nominee. http://www.marthastewart.com/americanmade/nominee/82975 … @MarthaStewart    
    
    
    Taking a walk in Central Park #NewYork pic.twitter.com/X9sKaABiSh    
    
    
    @CustomMade yes! But don't give me spoilers about yesterday race. I'm in vacation. I will watch it when we came back    
    
    
    Having lunch outside #priceless    
    
    
    No more pine cone. Admiring the turtles and boats at boathouse #newyork http://instagram.com/p/eDVszZtHzw/     
    
    
    A classic Central Park view #newyork http://instagram.com/p/eDepKVNHwc/     
    
    
    Prend une pause-thé vert  pendant la sieste de fiston    
    
    
    @kimberleyseldon @damask_dentelle @NinaLjutic @raleighseldon @GlamaMama @nylafree I'm relaxing in New York and enjoying an end of summer day    
    
    
    @damask_dentelle Buying a house keeps busy. In the same neighbourhood?    
    
    
    Congrats Gini! You are a great read. RT @ginidietrich: Seven Years of Blogging. Happy Birthday, Spin Sucks! http://buff.ly/17n1nw6     
    
    
    @hostgatorcodes Thanks for sharing my post. I appreciate it.    
    
    
    What do u think? Talking about people expectations and many facets of modern executive women http://ow.ly/oJJZp  #business #women    
    
    
    @RBC_Canada  big #fail Today.. Are you on the business of ruining vacation with dumb process?    
    
    
    Leaving the Big Apple    
    
    
    Good morning! A gorgeous sunny day in Montreal. #ilovesummer    
    
    
    @damask_dentelle @kimberleyseldon @nylafree Happy for you! Now, you have it all. #loveatfirstsight    
    
    
    More kids will want their own tablet - Disney Wants You to Bring Your iPad to ‘The Little Mermaid’ Movie http://on.mash.to/1b5OwlU  #ipad #movie    
    
    
    More women still want to go back to their career after giving birth RT @melissaonline: Modern Woman's Defn of Success http://www.business2community.com/infographics/modern-womans-definition-success-0611691 …    
    
    
    I second that!
 RT @socialdave: @KimVallee @MelissaOnline And should be welcomed back! #worklife #women    
    
    
    Simple tips for cold-calls and email pitches from @inc - Sales Rule No. 1: Start a Simple Conversation http://ow.ly/oMrdO  #businesstips    
    
    
    So true! RT @phdinparenting: If you're pitching me on a family vacation destination, I don't want high res pics. I want tickets.    
    
    
    A sign that I'm back in #montreal : my iPhone runs on 3G instead of 4G    
    
    
    @ReCreativeWorks my pleasure, Renee. Have a great day!    
    
    
    Don't forget that a logo should pass the test of time @B2Community: Don’t Do These 5 Things When Writing a Logo Brief http://goo.gl/fb/ICjpJ     
    
    
    Women Securing a Greater Share of VC Funding than in the past. Mostly in the retail and consumer services space http://ow.ly/oMSky     
    
    
    Neither. Must quickly produce quality content RT @janinepopick: Quality vs. Quantity? Content Mrtg Pros Pick Sides http://dlvr.it/3xvy5r     
    
    
    No, sadly RT @jowyang: If you were born in the 70s the population will over double during your natural lifetime. Do you think we are ready?    
    
    
    @adebold Every entrepreneurial couple with (young) kids needs a way to make it works for their business and their family #worklifebalance    
    
    
    Les chanceux. RT @marianik1968: La fin des frais d'itinérance pour les Européens ? #luckythem http://plus.lapresse.ca/screens/4689-02b8-522f3be8-a2fa-2276ac1c6068%7C_0.html …    
    
    
    Good morning! After all the sunshine, it's a rainy day. Welcome to fall!    
    
    
    Why Everybody's Going Freelance and a talk on the 3 things that motivate people by @drake_baer http://ow.ly/oOtDa  #career    
    
    
    Content Marketing: How to Produce Quality and Quantity. No need to choose between one and the other http://ow.ly/oOWia  #contentmarketing    
    
    
    13 Places Brilliant Start-up Ideas Are Born | http://Inc.com  http://www.inc.com/young-entrepreneur-council/13-places-brilliant-start-up-ideas-are-born.html …    
    
    
    She is young and inspired by tech. Lucky Editor Eva Chen Wants To Build A Magazine You Can Talk To By @davidburstein http://ow.ly/oPajf     
    
    
    @ambercadabra Nice reference to the ultimate question.    
    
    
    I hope not. RT @cotedetexas: Back to the dr.  Not recuperating    Scared to death. http://instagram.com/p/eLLnuIlMcd/     
    
    
    50 Creative Ideas To Make Better Cities, Presented On Gorgeously Designed Posters By Ben Schiller http://www.fastcoexist.com/3016824/50-creative-ideas-to-make-better-cities-presented-on-gorgeously-designed-posters … via @FastCoExist    
    
    
    @emilyleldridge Canada already switched to polymer bills. It felt strange the 1st time that I held one in my hand. They grew on me.    
    
    
    Your competitors are not always the usual suspects. How iOs has disrupted Nintendo http://hypercritical.co/2013/09/02/nintendo-in-crisis … #business    
    
    
    Can never go wrong with a classic. RT @camillestyles: @daniellamarie_c I love that @Gap trench!! Such a classic.    
    
    
    Apporte indépendance économique (personnel + collectif) RT @duhamelp: Pourquoi les entrepreneurs sont si importants http://www.lactualite.com/lactualite-affaires/les-leaders-croissance/pourquoi-les-entrepreneurs-sont-si-importants/ …    
    
    
    @MariaSanz @EatStTweet @Chauddogs It's because you didn't check enough @FoodNetwork shows before :-)))    
    
    
    Good morning! A cool 8° C this morning. Summer is gone.    
    
    
    Leave Nothing to Chance – Tactics to Super Power Your Launch - Tips from @PasswordBox http://ow.ly/oUXq8   via @Ecquire #marketing    
    
    
    Adapt, connect and let others build on your products, ideas RT @jowyang: Meet the Resilient Corporations http://www.web-strategist.com/blog/2013/09/15/meet-the-resilient-corporations/ …    
    
    
    @flooringcanada Thank you!    
    
    
    London #design studio @industrialfacil designs desk organizers for the digital age for @HermanMiller via @psfk http://ow.ly/oYb10     
    
    
    15 Things Inspiring Leaders Do Differently | http://Inc.com  http://www.inc.com/lee-colan/15-things-inspiring-leaders-do-differently.html …    
    
    
    I updated the Sidekick Labs. What do you think about the new content? http://sidekicklabs.com  #digitalmarketing    
    
    
    @torontolouise I stopped having business cards cuz too many salepersons and consultants think that giving them my card is opting in    
    
    
    Why taxi cab drivers cannot put down their smartphones - http://FT.com  http://on.ft.com/16Fdqp6  via @FT    
    
    
    Bravo! RT @byosko: Just found out that Lean Analytics will be translated into Chinese, Korean, Polish, Spanish, Russian and Japanese!    
    
    
    I would add relevance, usefulness and some fun RT @ambelinaaa: Quality content + consistency = engaged community #cision    
    
    
    I go 90/10 RT @tobifairley: Interact/post correctly. Remember 80/20 rule: 80% of time post content relevant to your audience. #DesignerMBA    
    
    
    @ambelinaaa :-) Agree! #cision    
    
    
    C'est pas encourageant comme statistiques RT @duhamelp: Le modèle québécois: à bout de souffle… http://bit.ly/19kFPhD  via @Antagoniste_net    
    
    
    It had been a while. You can go wrong with a miso soup, edamame and shrimp with my son [pic]: http://4sq.com/19lFNaL     
    
    
    My last tweet should have said can't go wrong    
    
    
    startup Zero Bound helps graduates crowdfund their own student loan debt in exchange for community tasks http://www.thedailymuse.com/lifestyle/can-you-crowdfund-your-life/ …    
    
    
    @SJAbbott I hear it more and more. Sad!   When that happened, I didn't rate them. I refuse to be told what to give as a rating    
    
    
    Me too “@ErinBlaskie: @Steph_Montreuil you can do custom columns in Tweetdeck. I use it for Twitter all the time. #blogchat”    
    
    
    @ErinBlaskie I learned to like @hootsuite . I alternate between it and @TweetDeck    
    
    
    Look for disruption opps where big players exist. Best Advice I Ever Got: Matt Ehrlichman of @porchdotcom http://ow.ly/p7Cdp  #startup    
    
    
    Similar idea http://ow.ly/p7CZy  RT @psfk: Portable humidifier from @umbra_ltd perches on top of any water bottle: http://bit.ly/14feVtg     
    
    
    Like many, I am disappointed by the end of SHO_Dexter. Some argued that it was not predictable but I think it was. #tv #dexter    
    
    
    No matter how much you exercise you do, the only way to lose weight is to stop eating too much via @FastCoExist http://ow.ly/paJEZ     
    
    
    Part of my fall cleaning process, remove all the clothes that are now too small for my toddler from his closets and drawers #homeliving    
    
    
    Bon YulBiz! RT @michelleblanc: He oui, en route pour le Yulbiz Montréal au @LaikaMontreal http://facebook.com/events/1713107 … :-)    
    
    
    Now that I have a toddler, I can relate to that video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Aflrbwna44 … #fun    
    
    
    For the battle of the app meetup (at @TP1 w/ @fharper @nvanderv) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1baoQpj     
    
    
    You bet! I'm glad that he likes passing time with me RT @t_burrows: @KimVallee I love that clip...living it, even better!    
    
    
    Creativity in the age of the Maths Men – by Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP http://po.st/ZO3HyR  via @thedrum    
    
    
    When looking for investors or partners ditch traditional #business plan in favor of a pitch deck. Get more tips at http://ow.ly/pcLWo     
    
    
    Cela fait peur de savoir que des bêtes qui ont du mal à se mouvoir ou se déplacer arrivent à l'abattoir http://ow.ly/pcNj3  #sante    
    
    
    Design impacts our life and how your #business can compete. And I'm not talking only abt the pretty things. http://ow.ly/pd7KZ  #design    
    
    
    Pratique mais dommage que sera si long à déployer RT @pgmartin: Annonce d’un réseau mobile ds métro de MTL http://bit.ly/16J5AHP  #QCTechno    
    
    
    Better than most retailers RT @entmagazine: REI's "Rent Every Item" are over as a 1-year return policy begins. Good or bad? Vote at...    
    
    
    Why don't you? Best occasion to test the couch for a nap. RT @julien: I could literally fall asleep right here right now #breather    
    
    
    @mrf12t Moi aussi! C'était Denis Paul van Chestein @denispaulvc    
    
    
    @pgmartin J'imagine que collaborer entre des 4 grosses machines prend du temps. Trop de personnes sur le projet pour être efficace. :-)))    
    
    
    D'accord avec son affirmation que la nostalgie est trop présente RT @indexdesg: Entrevue avec KARIM RASHID  http://fb.me/3m3NCoU0h  #design    
    
    
    "How Google's Flexible Workspace Ignites Creative Collaboration (On Wheels)"  http://www.fastcompany.com/3017824/work-smart/how-googles-flexible-workspace-ignites-creative-collaboration-on-wheels …    
    
    
    Need a few books for my toddler in French. Sadly, I didn't find anything that suits me. I settled for a break instead http://4sq.com/16CRyqc     
    
    
    And notify that Android and iOS grew to have more in common than differences. What do u think? - http://pulse.me/s/qI7is     
    
    
    1st time I heard of it RT @TheEconomist: Could Formula E, a new all-electric grand prix, ever rival Formula 1? http://econ.st/173jasP ...    
    
    
    With a list of great dried alternatives RT @BlogHer: Don’t Like Barilla’s Anti-Gay Statements? http://ow.ly/pgQUJ  -Momo    
    
    
    @MelissaOnline Good morning! Any fun plans for the weekend?    
    
    
    It finishes the look. RT @atubanos: Wore lipstick today. Feel like a true lady. Inspired by @HelenAndrolia #FancyFriday    
    
    
    Focus on the relevant info RT @karonwarren: Your media kit doesn't have to be fancy for it to be effective! -- @JollyMom #typeacon    
    
    
    Forget the clouds that you currently see in the sky. It will be sunny all weekend. #montreal    
    
    
    @atubanos I prefer the feel of a lipstick to a gloss.    
    
    
    @jdunham This is normal since we always have it with us. #mobilephone    
    
    
    Learn abt the dynamics of modern #business from being a startup to handling growth “Breaking Bad” via @TheEconomist http://econ.st/190GVhT     
    
    
    <3 RT @atubanos: Ask and ye shall receive, mes amis! @HelenAndrolia #lipstick #fancyfriday @ DRAFTFCB Toronto http://instagram.com/p/exeBRsQ1yl/     
    
    
    My two-and-a-half-year-old toddler who will do his first fundraising walk this Monday. #learningyoung    
    
    
    @HelenAndrolia @atubanos It was a great suggestion. + Anastasia knows how to look at the camera ;-)    
    
    
    @atubanos @HelenAndrolia The digital camera is one of the best innovation. #wouldnotgoback    
    
    
    Follow-up series to the Glasscape bowl RT @PSFK: Nature-Inspired Design Creates Mini Terrariums In A Tumbler http://bit.ly/1fr62nB     
    
    
    It's sunny outside, quiet in the house, and I'm enjoying my morning coffee. Great way to start a slow day.    
    
    
    @MaximSaini You are welcome! Enjoy your weekend.    
    
    
    Working on the editorial schedule for my entrepreneurship and work-life balance blog. You can read Balancing Act at http://kimvallee.com/     
    
    
    Enjoying one of the last brunch on a terrace on the season. (@ Laïka - @laikamontreal w/ @jeromeparadis) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1bQksLy     
    
    
    Equipped our toddler for alpine ski (@ La Poubelle du Ski w/ @jeromeparadis) http://4sq.com/163G4Ar     
    
    
    Nice look! RT @tinalovespinot: Manicure Love #42 :) show time = shellack time! http://instagram.com/p/e0apAnMOhI/     
    
    
    My coffee delight http://instagram.com/p/e40EAMNH73/     
    
    
    Kids are never too young to be exposed to art. Read my toddler's reactions when he saw a painting http://ow.ly/pm8VT  #education #art    
    
    
    A post for you @MyVisualVoice http://ow.ly/pm9mS     
    
    
    Good morning! Anything special on your agenda today?    
    
    
    @Mafamal Il faut profiter du beau temps.    
    
    
    I am working on social media post but I have to stop to meet someone for lunch. Bon appétit!    
    
    
    Facebook lets developers customize their mobile app install ads to drive user engagement http://lnkd.in/b2ccZ2Y     
    
    
    Bought more books for my toddler today. It is important to read stories to kids before they go to sleep #parentingtips    
    
    
    @SophieCLaplante C'est une excellente cause. Je ne connaissais pas cette fondation. Merci de m'avoir fait découvrir @FondationAlpha's...    
    
    
    @macbella2 You are right about being one of the nicest moments in our daily routine. #readingtokids    
    
    
    @SophieCLaplante The cut and paste...    
    
    
    Stopped for a green ice tea while taking a walk with my toddler (@ Starbucks) http://4sq.com/18PUsuE     
    
    
    My first time (@ Brooklyn Café Showroom) http://4sq.com/1aS0egK     
    
    
    Today on my blog, I discussed what's wrong with most store locator tools and how to fix them. http://ow.ly/pvkXn  #retail #userexperience    
    
    
    Stylish! RT @somawater: The most beautiful water filter is now for sale! http://drinksoma.com  #DrinkSoma    
    
    
    @rsmediaonline Thanks, Robert, for sharing my post.    
    
    
    @rsmediaonline It feels good to hear that. Don't worry, there is more to come. Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    Happy weekend to @NinaLjutic @SophieCLaplante @damask_dentelle @aquaovo @buk_nola @GlamaMama @kimberleyseldon @nylafree @EmilieIggiotti #FF    
    
    
    @moderncellars I like the fact that it looks sophisticated and it hides its purpose.    
    
    
    Had a gr8 week. The highlights: 3 inspired meetings - thanks to @myvisualvoice, @julien and @mocoloco. + 2 awesome days with my little boy    
    
    
    Thinking of making a Totoro costume for my toddler this #Halloween. If you never saw the film, I recommend it http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0096283/ …    
    
    
    It's a much appreciated compliment. RT @MyVisualVoice: @KimVallee you were equally inspiring! You're a fantastic ideas catalyst.    
    
    
    I want one with butter please RT @meredithheron: Ummmmm http://instagram.com/p/fD4Ss9iVw9/     
    
    
    @meredithheron You are right. I will eat at least 2.    
    
    
    You are a star! RT @onehundredjobs: New cute glasses. http://instagram.com/p/fEJPeIL3Pz/     
    
    
    How I spend my afternoon http://instagram.com/p/fGG6uctH54/     
    
    
    En effet! “@Emergent007: @KimVallee Le kimikaze du vélo ! ;-)”    
    
    
    @Emergent007 j'avais pensé que tu avais un jeu de mot avec mon autre pilote préféré    
    
    
    @Emergent007 je suis loyal ;-))    
    
    
    While our son @zackaparadis Is havons histoire movie night, we are havons ours (@ Cinéma Banque Scotia) http://4sq.com/1htdpXd     
    
    
    @Emergent007 Mon #iceman a bien fait en Corée.    
    
    
    Marketers destroy review system RT @martinlessard: Inauthenticity Is Big Business -Social Media’s Dirty Little Secret http://zite.to/1aZXVrY     
    
    
    A Handsome Bluetooth Speaker That Moonlights as a Karaoke Machine | Gadget Lab | http://Wired.com  http://www.wired.com/gadgetlab/2013/10/singing-machine-karaoke/ …    
    
    
    @BarrettABrooks Wishful thinking! He wants to offset the negative effects of smoking by eating organic food.    
    
    
    @BarrettABrooks We all have our own set of contradictions.    
    
    
    Funny to keep receiving emails from marketers who want to guest post on a blog that I stopped writing several months ago. #failed    
    
    
    More than ever it's time to make content that matters RT @jaybaer: Why Google is Forcing Your Content to Get Better http://ar.gy/5MLl     
    
    
    @TinyStepsMommy It took me so long to decide to start a new blog instead of repositioning one that I won't change my mind.    
    
    
    I planned to go to the grocery early today instead of at 5 PM. Don't seem that the weather wants to collaborate. Still raining,1 hour later.    
    
    
    @TinyStepsMommy Good luck in your new venture. Stay focus!    
    
    
    @Longzero I know! I checked 45 minutes ago thinking that it should be Ok by now but the rain is heavier than before.    
    
    
    @TinyStepsMommy Moments of doubts come when I check my Google stats. Thanks to my a 2 years old, I developed more patience ;-)    
    
    
    When I buy beef, I prefer beef raised without antibiotics and hormones. #food    
    
    
    You received your new iPhone. Should I upgrade mine? RT @Damdam: Champagne is the new Gold. http://instagram.com/p/fL_k6WuLZz/     
    
    
    @alexaclark lucky you. Love to see @jamieoliver re: @sobeys #JamieInTO    
    
    
    @lindametzger It is getting more and more complicated to do our grocery.    
    
    
    I had to talk about #Halloween. Look at my ideas for making a costume for my son http://ow.ly/pCEFw     
    
    
    I decorated my toddler's room with their alphabet print RT @mortsnodgrass: Check out our new @petitcollage goodies: http://bit.ly/19fM8GT     
    
    
    Did you know that my new blog is a mix of topics about running a business, innovating, work-life balance, parenting? http://kimvallee.com     
    
    
    This is what I will make for dinner. Fast and tasty. A big thanks to @jamieoliver http://ow.ly/pCJIR  @whatsfordinner    
    
    
    @NinaLjutic yes, it was. What was the highlight of your day?    
    
    
    I do! And it helps a lot. RT @carlayoung: #MOMeo Tip: Keep a notebook by your bedside so those ideas don't keep you up at night!    
    
    
    I am talking about entrepreneurs and startup founders can learn from building your own custom home. http://ow.ly/pEZoG  #businesstips    
    
    
    A person commuting 2 hours a day has to make 40% more money to be as satisfied w/ life as a person living near work http://ow.ly/pFaPf     
    
    
    Seeing the results takes time and u must be relevant RT @missrogue: Facebook Doesn't Work for Business http://limefoundry.com/facebook-doesnt-work-for-business/ … #1999    
    
    
    Should have said helpful instead of relevant RT @missrogue: Facebook Doesn't Work for Business http://limefoundry.com/facebook-doesnt-work-for-business/ … #1999    
    
    
    nice! RT @joy_ever_after: A mysteriously spooky invitation is yours for the taking (on the blog today) http://instagram.com/p/fQ0DvypUn7/     
    
    
    @scottymomo @GretchenA @needcaffeine My ideal is a 10-20 min walk. Since I work from home, my commute is driving my son to daycare (12 min)    
    
    
    @scottymomo I wish I could do that. You are lucky! On my side, I would too much in traffic. Plus, we are harsh weather in winter.    
    
    
    Je connais HotMetal Pro. Que de souvenirs d'une autre époque RT @Emergent007: MAJ: Parti d’un tweet que j’ai cliqué http://emergenceweb.com/blog/2013/09/tout-est-parti-dun-tweet-et-malgre-lenormite-de-levidence-jai-clique/ …    
    
    
    @MariaSanz Congratulations! Where it is? Or do you keep it a secret until the opening?    
    
    
    @MariaSanz Good luck with your soft opening on Saturday. I may stop by if we take a walk in the neighbourhood.    
    
    
    Who is going to Mesh Marketing (@meshcon) in Toronto this year? #meshcon    
    
    
    Same can be said about Starbucks RT @mortsnodgrass: giving directions to the store from tim horton's is all relative #timmyhooneverycorner    
    
    
    Break a leg RT @MariaSanz: Testing recipes in my brand new kitchen #ceviches #baraceviches #epicerielatine #montreal http://instagram.com/p/fWMEQ3j2Y3/     
    
    
    Good Saturday! It is gorgeous outside. What are you planning for the long weekend?    
    
    
    My toddler behave like a teenager. I had to woke him up at almost 11 AM. #priceless    
    
    
    I'm going. @TheMinimalists Everything That Remains Tour will be in Montreal next June. Tickets at http://ow.ly/pKS4t     
    
    
    Very busy today! (@ Laïka - @laikamontreal w/ @jeromeparadis) http://4sq.com/1egDBVm     
    
    
    Same belief here. RT @CarlaYoung: #MOMeo Tip: Use your lifestyle goals to drive your business goals, not the reverse!    
    
    
    Zack and I are playing restaurant owners RT @MariaSanz: @JeromeParadis thk you for dropping by! Your boy is adorable, cutest client ever :)    
    
    
    Taking a stroll with my beautiful son on a sunny day #familyfun http://instagram.com/p/fauBXbtH3q/     
    
    
    @lindadessau see you at @meshcon, Linda.    
    
    
    Apple hires Angela Ahrendts, CEO of Burberry, to head its retail efforts http://on.wsj.com/170Minx  #businessnews    
    
    
    Forget about generating billions: Why entrepreneurs should create $1,000 startups http://thenextweb.com/entrepreneur/2013/10/15/why-entrepreneurs-should-create-a-1000-startups/ … via @thenextweb    
    
    
    Reading Creative Intelligence by @BruceNussbaum let me talk about what needs to change in the way we run businesses http://ow.ly/pQCAm     
    
    
    @NikeFuel Can you tell me what is new with the  #FuelBandSE ? How is it better than the current model?    
    
    
    @wisewomenmtl Thank you Lisa and Liz.    
    
    
    North african mint organic tea by @davidstea helps me feel better. Also drank ginger and lemon tea #StomachAche http://ow.ly/pRmgm     
    
    
    After Creative Intelligence - see my review at http://ow.ly/pRmtU . I now read Youtilty by @jaybaer #book    
    
    
    I just googled it. It's ugly! From a Subaru owner RT @sarahintampa: Will someone pls tell my husband that the Subaru Brat is not cool? Pls?    
    
    
    Good morning! It's cloudy and 15° C outside. Chances are a late afternoon shower.    
    
    
    The Importance of Fostering Kids’ Creative Confidence and a new book about unleashing the creativity in all of us http://ow.ly/pSm7y     
    
    
    Thnks! RT @NikeSupport: Here to help. Nike+ FuelBand SE will share many characteristics of the Nike+ FuelBand  (cont) http://gonike.me/l/6012bbY4     
    
    
    In case that you miss the news, @Square Cash easily lets you send money by email http://kimvallee.com/square-cash/     
    
    
    Bravo @tryghost for your launch. Why bloggers should consider #Ghost as their blogging platform http://ow.ly/pSXVZ  #blogging    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA I will check them. Thanks for the tips since I am not back to 100%. I might go shopping later today.    
    
    
    @NinaLjutic I need to fix the house for a small party this weekend but I am not feeling well. So, I postponed the cleaning until tomorrow.    
    
    
    @carlospache_co I bought one earlier this year. Kept it for a week and returned it cuz fuel counts via arm movements is misleading    
    
    
    @carlospache_co I earned more fuels on a 20-minute drive or when making dinner than when I did 20 minutes of yoga. Feels strange    
    
    
    Merci Philippe. RT @PhilippeMartin: Square Cash easily lets you send money by email http://kimvallee.com/square-cash/  via @KimVallee    
    
    
    @dianebourque Que penses-tu de Ghost? Je veux l'essayer. Voici pourquoi http://ow.ly/pSZpa  #blogging    
    
    
    @HPQcArtdevivre Un banc pour mettre sur la toilette est préférable pour se simplifier la vie. Mon bébé a un iPad mais pas à la toilette.    
    
    
    Many of you in my circle know @Minted. Crowdsourced stationery site Minted draws an amazing $41M Bravo! http://ow.ly/pT2de     
    
    
    My answer is at http://ow.ly/pT2ne  RT @MelissaOnline: Content Creators: Quality or Clicks? http://goo.gl/SuHuuy  via @lorirtaylor    
    
    
    I'm accepting new clients in needs of a digital content strategy, or clients who want to make their content marketing more meaningful    
    
    
    @robynski Once @TryGhost is set up, your productivity will go up. Just not today. I am glad that you like it.    
    
    
    @LineAtallah @WyndhamEstate Sorry to not being able to see you, Line, at the event. I am sick. #wyndhamwine    
    
    
    @LineAtallah we should plan lunch in a week or two    
    
    
    Working hard ;-)RT @iweb Lunch will be served at the office. http://instagram.com/p/fksxSkCSoT/     
    
    
    @savvymomdotca Yes, too soon! We don't have celebrated Halloween yet.    
    
    
    Superb #photos. Have a look at the winners of Wildlife Photographer of 2013 http://ow.ly/pUH3a     
    
    
    They understand what tech can do and can use it better RT @mitchjoel: Are engineers+coders the future of marketing? http://bit.ly/16SzmOg     
    
    
    There is an untapped market in greeting cards market. I visited 4 stores to find a suitable birthday card for my husband.    
    
    
    @foodiePrints it depends for whom you shop. Greeting cards for women and children are easier. Otherwise, it's car shopping    
    
    
    Un très beau parc RT @marianik1968: Le Central Park d'Amsterdam. @ Vondelpark http://instagram.com/p/fnXyV5Ip9I/     
    
    
    What I do before hosting a dinner party: clean up the fridge to find space for all the ingredients that I will need #entertaining    
    
    
    Good advice. http://lnkd.in/bVFNruz     
    
    
    @Longzero Ce doit être les mêmes qui ont rénovés la super mini bâtisse du Parc Jeanne-Mance, qui ne sert à rien en passant, pour $550,000    
    
    
    Eat French toasts for breakfast. Easy way to the baguette that we did eat last night at the dinner party #entertainingtips    
    
    
    I made some changes RT @PhilippeMartin: 7 Ways to Stop iOS 7 From Killing Your iPhone Battery http://on.mash.to/15tncdN  via @mashable    
    
    
    My toddler son goes so fast when he rides his balance bike that I need to run to keep up with him. Maybe he will convert me to jogging.    
    
    
    @briansolis Glad to know that you like their new speaker. We have two PLAY:3 in our main room. I want a @Sonos PLAY:1 for my master bedroom    
    
    
    @Fionacartolina Enjoy your night out. Whenever you decide to do (with or w/out), at least bring your specs with you.    
    
    
    Plastic Party Cups With Looks And Class By Margaret Rhodes http://www.fastcodesign.com/3017886/plastic-party-cups-with-looks-and-class … via @FastCoDesign    
    
    
    This Is What Happens When Top Architects Design Doll Houses http://www.fastcocreate.com/3020029/this-is-what-happens-when-top-architects-design-doll-houses …    
    
    
    “10 things I’ve learnt about lean startup” by @welovelean https://medium.com/p/f530f4b7974f     
    
    
    Cool #Halloween costume that simulates having a hole in your torso - made with 2 iPad2 http://youtu.be/V6p5mbp_M98     
    
    
    It feels like fall outside. Have a good Sunday! My plan is to have fun with my husband and our toddler.    
    
    
    I used to be the queen of spreadsheets (my old old job) RT @julien: Spreadsheets are my new best friend.    
    
    
    Good morning! It's chilly outside. 6° C. At least, we have the sun and yellow and red foliage to cheer us.    
    
    
    @dcostadesign: The Plastic Party Cups will be a hit.  #xmaslist2013    
    
    
    Starts my week day slowly. I stopped for a chocolatine and coffee on my way to buy the rewards for my son's potty training #familylife    
    
    
    @designpublic my problem with all open shelving is about the dust since you don't use some of your dishes often    
    
    
    "“Start small, find a mentor & don’t be afraid” says SuperJam founder Fraser Doherty"  http://thehappystartupschool.wordpress.com/2013/10/21/start-small-find-a-mentor-dont-be-afraid-says-superjam-founder-fraser-doherty/ …    
    
    
    "Kids' Drawings Of The Future Brought To Life By Peter Blake And Other Top Artists"  http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/fastcocreate/feed/~3/u_rmiZu5-Sc/kids-drawings-of-the-future-brought-to-life-by-peter-blake-and-other-top-artists …    
    
    
    Parents go easier on their second and next kids - First Children Get Better Grades Why  http://pulse.me/s/t4Ot8     
    
    
    Different viewpoints -  Advice to a Younger Me   Female Leaders on Starting Out http://pulse.me/s/sCgXg     
    
    
    The title of my new blog (Balancing Act) tells more about me than I thought. I have a balanced brain (50-50). http://ow.ly/q23jx     
    
    
    Intelligent Working Women Leaning Back? Why This One is For Leaning Back [Infographic] http://www.momeomagazine.com/intelligent-working-women-leaning-back-why-this-one-is-for-leaning-back-infographic/ …    
    
    
    Creative No Carve Pumpkin Ideas at http://spoonful.com/crafts/creative-no-carve-pumpkin-ideas … #halloween    
    
    
    Innovate with your packaging and a stylish way to serve soup at a dinner party http://ow.ly/q2qBe  - for you @suzlortie    
    
    
    Just read the last page of #Youtility by @jaybaer. Now reading @briansolis What's the Future of Business #book #business    
    
    
    @jaybaer I did! I had a pretty good idea of what it was about. I attended your talk in Montreal (by Casacom). See u at Mesh in Toronto    
    
    
    @jaybaer I just realized that my previous reply almost sounded like a groupie ;-)    
    
    
    I am happy about the angle for my next post. Walking outside inspired me. There is nothing like it to free your mind from distractions    
    
    
    Helpful tip! RT @EdenSpodek: RT @alexgrunwald: I love what Lowes has done with Vine. http://vine.co/v/bU61aqq2YOp  #digitaledu    
    
    
    @WestQueenWest I am a fan of the C'est Moi brand    
    
    
    Brrrzzz! It was 4° C when I woke up this morning. Only reached 5° C by now.    
    
    
    I like the coworking days idea RT @kevindewalt: Building A Startup Culture When You Work Alone http://kdewa.lt/1aELmAm  via @Chikodi #startup    
    
    
    I'm experiencing technical problems with @linkedin today. Do you?    
    
    
    Me demande so @PhilippeMartin a lu cela RT @Damdam: “Pourquoi je ne retournerai jamais, jamais aux États-Unis” http://www.huffingtonpost.fr/niels-gerson-lohman/story_b_4137115.html …    
    
    
    on my shopping list http://www.apple.com/ca/ipad-air/  #ipad    
    
    
    Good morning! It is colder than yesterday. 0° C right now in Montreal. At least, the current clear sky (that will change later) cheer me up.    
    
    
    "If the SEC Restricts How Startups Solicit Money, What Will Happen to Demo Days?"  http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/j1ki09u1yZg/story01.htm …    
    
    
    How to Disrupt the Workday for Fun and Profit #businesstips http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/Ny5cHJBmLwU/story01.htm …    
    
    
    À découvrir: HOSPI RT @duhamelp: Japon : Panasonic fait entrer ses robots à l'hôpital   Avec Vidéo  http://echo.st/622345  via @LesEchos    
    
    
    And give them the freedom to do it RT @CameronHerold: You r more effective when u r leveraging your time and teaching your team how to think    
    
    
    Starbucks debuts Teavana bar, and it's a doozy http://usat.ly/1gEYoX7  via @usatoday    
    
    
    How a Web series made me think of how to break down silos http://ow.ly/qbvaZ  #businesstips    
    
    
    How a Web series made me think of how to break down silos with the return of my "food for thought" commentary
http://lnkd.in/b2CEYda     
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA Do you know if there is a store who still have The Stout Teapot? It is no longer available online.    
    
    
    If you can read this, you are eligible. Medium opens up to everyone, but you'll need a @Twitter account to post http://ow.ly/qc8nU     
    
    
    "A world where computing is embedded in everyday devices will cause a huge shift in how we advertise..." http://ow.ly/qc8qO  via @gigaom    
    
    
    Tips about learning how to prioritize how to spend your time as a founder  http://pandodaily.com.feedsportal.com/c/35141/f/650422/s/32f7b2cf/sc/21/l/0Lpandodaily0N0C20A130C10A0C270Cavoid0Enetworking0Eevents0Emarketed0Elike0Ea0Ecrappy0Eapartment0Eon0Ecraigslist0Eand0Eother0Epro0Etips0C/story01.htm …    
    
    
    What to Say Instead of “I Don’t Know” #businesstips http://www.thedailymuse.com/toolsskills/what-to-say-instead-of-i-dont-know/ …    
    
    
    Entrepreneurship => impact. You should aim to change things according to @sethgodin http://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/48994895/0/sethsblog~Entrepreneurship-gt-impact.html …    
    
    
    What Fortune’s Most Power Women Have to Say On Culture of #innovation http://nilofermerchant.com/2013/10/23/what-fortunes-most-power-women-have-to-say-on-culture/ …    
    
    
    Good morning! We start the week under the rain. #itsfall    
    
    
    Why I expose my toddler to #design and modern #architecture http://ow.ly/qg0Bn  - and a new book about skyscraper design for kids    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA Montreal or Toronto - I'm going to TO soon.    
    
    
    @NataBoutique_ Have a great day! It is sunny right now.    
    
    
    My series about educating young kids for the job market of today and tomorrow continue with
http://lnkd.in/biRkwJZ     
    
    
    Plans for the rest of the afternoon: grocery shopping and putting the finishing touch to my son's #Halloween costume #worklifebalance    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA Yes, Saint-Viateur would be the easiest place for me. Otherwise, Westmount    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA Yes, I can go around 10-11 AM. Thank you so much for your help    
    
    
    I played my first game of #ankidrive (@anki) tonight. The boys at home won. #game #innovation    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA Yes, I ended up spending $140. I took advantage of the sale of tea mugs to get ahead on my #Christmas shopping    
    
    
    I'm proud of the teamwork that @jeromeparadis and I did to create/produce on our turtle costume design for our little boy #halloween #family    
    
    
    Fab #Halloween ideas from last year: Grossly Realistic Brain Cakes http://kim.tl/SdJbis  - Spooky Forest Party Food http://kim.tl/S9Y4ld     
    
    
    @Debbie_Travis I second that. Enjoy!    
    
    
    At #yulbiz    
    
    
    You will never imagine how pretty this bunker house can be. Make sure to see all the pictures. http://www.viralnova.com/zombie-house/  #design #modern    
    
    
    write about this http://amzn.com/k/84fhTdPVTUiZn_5SsAt_ww … Measuring ROI is the least of your worries here. Customer disappointment is the unintentional...    
    
    
    @anki No pics yet. Tonight, my toddler (2.5 yrs old) beats me. I guess that he inherited the gaming skills of his dad (@jeromeparadis)    
    
    
    Nice work by @joe_harrison RT @digibomb: Responsive Icons http://www.responsiveicons.co.uk/  super cool!    
    
    
    Bad answer from @potterybarn. Halloween costumes are abt make believe. Nothing wrong w/ sushi chef costume. Japan sells kimonos to tourists    
    
    
    @anki Well said!    
    
    
    @anki We will see if it was beginner luck. I should film him when he's helping my husband rolling the carpet and after, spin it back.    
    
    
    Happy Halloween everyone!    
    
    
    The little monster trick-or-treat bag that we made for our toddler. #halloween http://instagram.com/p/gJcbLqNH9_/     
    
    
    My toddler's first Halloween treats. @zackaparadis starts to eat it while he relaxes before bedtime http://instagram.com/p/gJoqHMNH13/     
    
    
    5 Legal Ways to Contact Facebook Contest Winners http://shar.es/IJLCc  via @shortstacklab    
    
    
    FAA clears the way for use of devices to watch movies or read during take off and landing http://thenextweb.com/sessions/2013/10/31/prepare-take-faa-clears-way-use-devices-take-landing/ …    
    
    
    Got my #iPadAir. I arrived at the perfect hour. There was no line. Now, there is since it's lunch time    
    
    
    After shopping at the @Apple store, I had to check what's next in tableware and the Holidays collection http://4sq.com/1aNe7MX     
    
    
    It's my Foursquare-versary! I joined 4 years ago today. (@ Anthropologie) http://4sq.com/1aNe7MX  pic.twitter.com/b0W7lYbCcf    
    
    
    I am dreaming of a gift wrapping station @ Anthropologie http://instagram.com/p/gLY16ItH0h/     
    
    
    A book that would be perfect for Vanessa @damask_dentelle #modern #rustic @ Anthropologie http://instagram.com/p/gLZVOBNH1T/     
    
    
    Last stop: buying Holiday gifts for my son @ Centre Canadien d'Architecture / Canadian Centre for… http://instagram.com/p/gLexWANH9C/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Here is the link of the advent calendars that I like http://www.johnlewis.com/john-lewis-rural-advent-boxes/p463502 …. I know that I could try to make one but would prefer buying one    
    
    
    My toddler saw me with my new #iPadAir. He immediately hit the videos buttons and was disappointed when he saw no films were available.    
    
    
    À vs aussi RT @damask_dentelle: #FF Bon weekend! @madeinblog @AvenueDesignCA @GenevieveMoreau @mortsnodgrass @LietteLamonde @MarcLajambe...    
    
    
    I switched from a 1st generation iPad. So, I am in heaven. RT @ClassySharelle: @KimVallee How do you like it! #iPadAir    
    
    
    I like that it is extendable. REK Bookcase Junior by Reinier de Jong http://www.dezeen.com/2013/10/30/rek-bookcase-junior-by-reinier-de-jong/ … via @dezeen #furniture #kids    
    
    
    Sushi night with my two favorite guys @jeromeparadis and @zackaparadis (@ Bistro Japonais Furusato) [pic]: http://4sq.com/HyS0BA     
    
    
    Just stole the mayorship of Bistro Japonais Furusato on @foursquare! Crown me! http://4sq.com/HyS0BA  pic.twitter.com/nuRWAj4mPJ    
    
    
    Good night!    
    
    
    My toddler is giving us a helping hand with fall cleaning. Thank you, @zackaparadis #familytime http://instagram.com/p/gQw4D2NH3y/     
    
    
    "Five Prevalent Pitfalls when Prototyping"  http://feedly.com/k/17yxpqt  #ux    
    
    
    Me too! RT @TanMcG: I like companies that make it as easy for me to return products as it is to purchase them.    
    
    
    One million kids signed up for the Hour of Code. Let the geeking out commence http://pandodaily.com/2013/10/31/one-million-kids-have-signed-up-for-the-hour-of-code-let-the-geeking-out-commence/ … via @pandodaily    
    
    
    Design & Thinking' Team to Release 'Maker,' Full-Length Doc Charting the Maker Movement  http://feedly.com/k/1azQn2l  #documentary #makers    
    
    
    how light affects your creativity. "Why Creativity Thrives In The Dark"  http://feedly.com/k/1amUxVm     
    
    
    old news but it's good to know business wise. How Steve Jobs Made the iPad Succeed When All Other Tablets Failed http://feedly.com/k/17z5J72     
    
    
    Otherwise, u won't have any energy left @AlexTheis: Some people have a remarkable ability to see the negative in any situation. Avoid them.    
    
    
    Making your own helps too New at @ProBlogger: The ONE thing your written content needs. It’s not what you think! http://problo.gr/1bSLspW     
    
    
    Upgrading 1st generation iPad to the #iPadAir means that I do more research sitting on a lounge chair instead of at my desk #freemymind    
    
    
    “@jowyang: Radical:  This walking mechanized creature was 3D printed (not assembled, it was just printed like that) https://www.shapeways.com/model/247069/animaris-geneticus-parvus-5.html?li=productGroup&materialId=6 …”    
    
    
    @martinlessard Est-ce que les tannants sont assis à l'arrière? #grps2013    
    
    
    Contente que Stéphane Bureau précise que la petite enfance et l'éducation primaire sont importants pour la #persévérancescolaire #grps2013    
    
    
    @martinlessard Aussi! Tiens moi au courant d'autres événements comme celui-là. Je veux mieux comprendre les enjeux et le système éducatif.    
    
    
    This family house makes great use of the space that they have. A 15–Foot–Wide House You'd Kill To Live In http://www.fastcodesign.com/3020868/innovation-by-design/a-15-foot-wide-house-youd-kill-to-live-in …    
    
    
    Bon point sur le fait que le Québec forme beaucoup de diplômés universitaires mais malheureusement en embauche peu #grps2013    
    
    
    Notre voisin, un médecin formé à McGill, est allé à Vancouver pr son internat car pas de place ici. On a payé pr son éducation mais il...    
    
    
    (suite de mon tweet précédent) ... mais il ira pratiquer ailleurs. Le pire , c'est qu'il aurait aimer rester ici  #grps2013    
    
    
    @martinlessard Je n'en doute pas    
    
    
    À quoi peuvent ressembler des aptitudes entrepreneuriales chez un enfant ? http://kimauclair.ca/blog/a-quoi-peuvent-ressembler-des-aptitudes-entrepreneuriales-chez-un-enfant/ … via @kimauclair    
    
    
    Available at participating stores. Target will give you at least $200 for trading in any old iPad http://gigaom.com/2013/11/05/target-will-give-you-at-least-200-for-trading-in-any-old-ipad/ …    
    
    
    How Content and Social Media Fit into a CEO’s Day http://spinsucks.com/entrepreneur/how-content-and-social-media-fit-into-a-ceos-day/ … via @Spinsucks    
    
    
    @cc_chapman Mine was a 1st generation. You can imagine how much faster and happier I am with my new one.    
    
    
    @KimAuclair Je vais bien. Cela fait si longtemps que l'on s'est vu. On devrait se céduler un lunch.    
    
    
    5 Steps to a Millennial-Friendly Workplace. Includes a mix of home-style furniture and isolated phone booths http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/1XZ3S95-19s/story01.htm …    
    
    
    @KimAuclair ce serait super.    
    
    
    Why I think that it is a good thing to be able to print a 2,500 sq. ft house in 20 hours. http://ow.ly/qww34  #innovation #3dprinting    
    
    
    Quel projet architectural mérite de gagner? Vous avez jusqu'au 14 nov. pour voter pour le Prix du public. http://www.oaq.com/pea/prix_du_public.html …    
    
    
    It makes your customers happy and provides product feedback/insights. Why Startups Should Prioritize Customer Service http://onforb.es/18qlGWp     
    
    
    How regular women can become “Brands” in 4 easy steps. It starts with #blogging http://www.forbes.com/sites/larissafaw/2013/10/30/how-regular-women-can-become-brands-in-four-easy-steps/ …    
    
    
    How Automattic Grew Into A Startup Worth $1 Billion With No Email And No Office Workers http://www.businessinsider.com/automattic-no-email-no-office-workers-2013-11 … #businesstips #wordpress    
    
    
    I'm looking for someone who work at @shutterfly who can help me with a project that I am doing for my son's daycare. Any suggestions?    
    
    
    @shutterfly I'll need 50 calendars. Is it true that shipping costs would be $300 for a delivery in Montreal? http://ow.ly/qyIGU     
    
    
    @alexaclark Will you attend Mesh marketing tomorrow, Alexa? I will be there. #meshcon    
    
    
    Cute! RT @Will_UK: I love how this sunset picture I took in Santorini looks displayed inside this vintage glass jar: http://ow.ly/qve5k     
    
    
    Wonderful! If #TravelBunny is going, I'll like my pic w/ him RT @alexaclark: @KimVallee I will, looking forward to seeing u! #meshmarketing    
    
    
    @alexaclark Thank you!    
    
    
    I commented RT @onehundredjobs: I got my son to answer the same questions about #politics at 7 and 13 years-old :)... http://fb.me/YZKj7ms8     
    
    
    @DianeBourque J'ai regardé ta présentation sur Slideshare. Tu as fais un beau tour d'horizon des capacités de #wordpress.    
    
    
    En recyclant un modèle de vente RT @martinlessard: Comment se faire des couilles en or dans l’industrie du vêtement http://andrebelanger.wordpress.com/2013/11/04/vetements_innovation/ …    
    
    
    On my way to #meshcon (@ Montréal Int'l Airport Pierre-Elliott-Trudeau (YUL) w/ 7 others) http://4sq.com/17Gr9iQ     
    
    
    Good morning! It doesn't happen often that I woke up at 4:45 and greets you this early    
    
    
    Just landed to a sunny sky in Toronto. Better than the pouring rain of when I left (at @bbishopairport) http://4sq.com/16J0Zcj     
    
    
    Instead of redesigning your Website every 5 years go for ongoing, evolutionary updates @peeplaja #meshcon    
    
    
    Apply the lean startup approach and measure everything if your goal is to increase conversion rate #meshcon    
    
    
    Ad copy and design should match. #meshcon    
    
    
    @square homepage is a good example where visuals tell the story and is easy to understand for people #meshcon    
    
    
    Sliders always hurt conversion rate because they distract the users #meshcon    
    
    
    @mcorsano thank you @alexaclark for introducing us    
    
    
    @EdenSpodek where are you? I would like to say hello ?    
    
    
    @Karen_C_Wilson we are now connected. Looking forward to chat more with you    
    
    
    Influence marketing is about knowing your customers. A repeating theme of #meshcon re: @DannyBrown @samfiorella    
    
    
    Influence marketing concentrates on the  friends of your customers. #meshcon    
    
    
    Need to understand buying stages and who/what stop them from buying #meshcon    
    
    
    @atubanos yes, I'm. I flew in TO for the day. Are you here?    
    
    
    @atubanos I guess so from your timeline. We have to catch up at lunch    
    
    
    You will be even more jealous: @jaybear sits at my table “@jenswartley: Jealous! Wish I was there :) 
@jaybaer @dannybrown @samfiorella”    
    
    
    @atubanos I am also at the back. You can't miss me with my orange skirt    
    
    
    @atubanos we will!    
    
    
    As publishers, have a separate advertising team - with journalists to produce branded content - from the editorial team #meshcon #nativead    
    
    
    @alexaclark @PaulObeda @gerrythorpe - @TravelBunnyis25 deserves it from his 25th    
    
    
    Listening to the last speaker of the day: @jaybaer talks about #youtility #meshcon pic.twitter.com/rxc1BJhPoq    
    
    
    According to a @google study in 2011, customers need 10.4 sources of information before making a decision #meshcon    
    
    
    Power of self-serve -when answer every single question customers have - takes away uncertainties. Role of salesmen is changing #meshcon    
    
    
    Trust is the prism through which all business success must pass. Without trust, you are nothing #meshcon    
    
    
    Marketers should teach, educate more their customers instead of trying so hard  to sell to them #meshcon    
    
    
    @julien you have written a popular book about that, don't you? ;-)    
    
    
    The best utilities are not about your products and services but about something that is relevant yo your customers #meshcon @jaybaer    
    
    
    Thank you @martinwaxman and @EdenSpodek for the RT #meshcon    
    
    
    @EliseOndet moi aussi    
    
    
    “@HonestToddler: "But we gained an hour!" At what cost? I need night vision goggles to eat breakfast.”    
    
    
    Food was delicious and the convo was awesome “@missrogue: Dinner with the lovely @kimvallee! (@ Sukhothai) http://4sq.com/HDpsGE ”    
    
    
    Having a coffee to keep me awake while I am waiting for my flight. It's late! (@ Porter Lounge w/ 2 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1bbvhpv     
    
    
    @missrogue I was afraid to be late cuz the shuttle took almost 15 minutes to arrive. I'm Ok since my flight is delayed    
    
    
    Introducing Ink: The New Responsive Email Framework by @zurb #forcoders #responsive http://feedly.com/k/17QDAX4     
    
    
    Student hacks Raspberry Pi to run college bar from managing the liquor inventory to automate his @sonos http://feedly.com/k/19HVVGe     
    
    
    Starting my work day with a breakfast think session @ Olive Et Gourmando http://instagram.com/p/gdY4xMtHxw/     
    
    
    Styling ideas for your next brunch #entertaining @ Olive Et Gourmando http://instagram.com/p/gdaPq5tH0B/     
    
    
    Every presentation worth doing has just one purpose. You should seek to trigger a change http://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/49773396/0/sethsblog~Every-presentation-worth-doing-has-just-one-purpose.html …    
    
    
    Thks! RT @AlexTheis: More outstanding follows @BillCortright @DrTraci @LukeDancy @Carl_Eidson @NikaStewart @TheBResource @MeghanmBiro #FF    
    
    
    @RogersElise je pense que je vais en faire une habitude au moins mensuel    
    
    
    Digital marketing and communications #ff @EdenSpodek @martinwaxman @jaybaer @ready2spark @missrogue @mcorsano    
    
    
    Sweet! RT @TheBResource: Brown Sugar Frosted Butter Pecan Cupcakes for these #FF gems! @SpitToonsSaloon @CoxRobbie @AlexTheis @JFHilborne    
    
    
    Our comfort food RT @eatlivtravwrite: You know you're in the province of Québec when .... #Montreal http://instagram.com/p/gdzhRRqZFj/     
    
    
    Personnes à suivre au Québec #ff @DianeBourque @ChristianMasson @philippemartin @suzlortie @martinlessard @zelaurent #mediasociaux    
    
    
    @ready2spark It is well-deserved!    
    
    
    A weird mix of food and drink if you ask me. RT @evablue: Beer and donuts #toronto @ Extreme Startups http://instagram.com/p/gd9GqhvUZi/     
    
    
    I'm younger than @alexaclark in Twitter years - TwBirthday of @kimvallee is on 22 June 2007 http://twbirthday.com/kimvallee/  - via @TwBirthday    
    
    
    "The first lie..." @sethgodin talks about what it takes in the connection economy http://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/49906389/0/sethsblog~The-first-lie.html …    
    
    
    @nanananini Unless you pay a lot, most coat racks are too fragile for coats. They are more for scarfs and hats. Wall hooks are sturdier.    
    
    
    @nanananini Zone and Anthropologie have nice hooks. Also check at quincallerie Hogg in Westmount (u'll be surprised) or at Crate & Barrel.    
    
    
    Why we gave our baby a digital identity and how we manage it http://kimvallee.com/digital-identity-baby/ … #socialmedia #parenting    
    
    
    Why when u sent an email to customer service, all they do is referred to Web pages that you visited and that don't answer your question :-((    
    
    
    @canadapostcorp @postescanada Found in my mailbox today, 4 letters with addresses other than mine. Why ppl don't use your services anymore.    
    
    
    @canadapostcorp I know but I can't right now. The Canada Post Web site is experiencing technical difficulties.    
    
    
    @canadapostcorp Sloppy delivery is the norm here. Two letters were returned to my bank with mention: wrong address. The address were right.    
    
    
    It feels like winter today. That reminded me that my son needed a new pair of winter boots. I hope the ones I got him will fit well.    
    
    
    I was able to find a craft project to do with the kids at my son's daycare for the Holiday workshop, thanks to @pinterest    
    
    
    @Artstrada I am glad that you like it.    
    
    
    The Secret to Innovation: Think Like a Kid | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131113135819-10842349-the-secret-to-innovation-think-like-a-kid …    
    
    
    What I've Learned as an Entrepreneur (and Didn't Know as a Corporate Exec) | LinkedIn http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20131113113439-174077701-from-corp-exec-to-entrepreneur-14-things-i-ve-learned …    
    
    
    We are going! RT @anki: .@KimVallee Will we see you and the family at #AnkiDrive event at 6 pm tonight (11/14) at Montreal Apple Store?    
    
    
    @s_ilberg I will! I will be with a cute 2 years old    
    
    
    It is fun to hear my husband @JeromeParadis talking about how cool I am    
    
    
    Dad and son @jeromeparadis and @zackaparadis are racing @anki (@ Apple Store w/ 5 others) [pic]: http://4sq.com/175TZGm     
    
    
    We had a blast at #ankidrive at the Montreal @apple store. - photo with @s_ilberg and @zackaparadis pic.twitter.com/u9kSJWr1gO    
    
    
    If you are near the @Apple store on Sainte-Catherine W., you have until 8 PM to try the @anki DRIVE. You'll want 1 for Christmas. #ankidrive    
    
    
    @staceyined I understand why. Which one is your car? Mine is Kourai (yellow)    
    
    
    @staceyined Yes, the tech is awesome. Nice comparison with SKYNET. I also need to practice more. but I enjoy playing it even if I lose.    
    
    
    @s_ilberg We played last night with the two cats sitting next to the track. They well-behaved, watching the cars go around.    
    
    
    Good morning! It is a gorgeous day in Montreal. 6°C and sunny    
    
    
    Merci @Emergent007 #FF Yulbiz @MichelleBlanc @PhilippeMartin @boutotcom @patriceleroux @JeromeParadis @Damdam @Charles_Nouyrit...    
    
    
    An easy way to make a winter wonderland -,Ideas to steal for Holiday decorations #Christmas @ La… http://instagram.com/p/gv19NnNHze/     
    
    
    Introducing @edenspodek to our favorite little Japanese restaurant with @zackaparadis (@ Bistro Japonais Furusato) http://4sq.com/I7RrOj     
    
    
    Good food! RT @EdenSpodek: Last night's at Bistro Japonais Furusato with @KimVallee @JeromeParadis and Zack. http://instagram.com/p/g067KslTl2/     
    
    
    The company was the best. RT @EdenSpodek: @KimVallee @JeromeParadis And great company!    
    
    
    Thanks to @edenspodek who gave me a sample of @whoosh, all my screens are cleaned #techhygiene    
    
    
    Watching the #F1 race #familyfun    
    
    
    Les serveurs de Facebook réchauffent une ville glacée de Suède | Internet http://techno.lapresse.ca/nouvelles/internet/201311/16/01-4711365-les-serveurs-de-facebook-rechauffent-une-ville-glacee-de-suede.php … via @lp_techno    
    
    
    "Teach Fractions with Legos"  http://feedly.com/k/I6Qndv     
    
    
    Good morning! Dress well when you will go outside. It feels colder than it is. 10° C, cloudy. and windy.    
    
    
    Useful info "10 Surprising Social Media Statistics That Will Make You Rethink Your Social Strategy" http://feeds.fastcompany.com/~r/fastcompany/headlines/~3/ZNLEAdGAEyI/10-surprising-social-media-statistics-that-will-make-you-rethink-your-social-stra …    
    
    
    Merci @dianebourque et @dumontchristian pour le RT!    
    
    
    @s_ilberg No need for fur! Youngest cat already uses his paw to kindly hit the car. I don't complain since there were my opponent cars ;-)    
    
    
    It's no secret that I enjoy our @anki Drive. I shared here why they are the future of car racing http://ow.ly/qXnXI  #connectedobjects    
    
    
    Solve problems in words, images, videos that they understand. RT @jeffbullas: Why Solving Problems Beats Marketing http://bit.ly/brwid5     
    
    
    @EdenSpodek There pics look awful. Martha should be more selective esp., since she told in an interview that bloggers aren't good enough.    
    
    
    @zoonini @EdenSpodek In business, it is often in knowing what and when to delegate.    
    
    
    A post about asking for help - if you don't ask, the answer is always no http://heartheather.com/2013/11/07/if-you-dont-ask-the-answer-is-always-no-a-free-printable/ …    
    
    
    A post by @hwatterworth about having a support system - if you don't ask, the answer is always no http://heartheather.com/2013/11/07/if-you-dont-ask-the-answer-is-always-no-a-free-printable/ …    
    
    
    @hwatterworth @ONEGuelph Congratulations Heather! It is fun to work at a place with a great mission.    
    
    
    @SocialDave Le plaisir des Lego.    
    
    
    @bsofman Thanks! You and your team did a great job. You are on the right track with @anki.    
    
    
    @EdenSpodek @zoonini To her defence, it is hard to take pictures on a restaurant. Lighting is rarely ideal.    
    
    
    @JuliaDiSano Reading it, gave me a few ideas for future posts and to better market myself.    
    
    
    5 Great Content Quotes to Use In Your Next Meeting http://rbl.ms/1bYsE91  via @RebelMouse    
    
    
    Which #book is on your night table? I'm currently reading Avogrado by William @Hertling. It's a suggestion from @jeromeparadis (my husband)    
    
    
    @alexaclark @BauliCanada Lucky you!    
    
    
    Based on a study done in Finland - Why Can't We Walk And Wear Google Glass At The Same Time? | Co.Design  http://www.fastcodesign.com/3021668/evidence/google-glass-and-the-rise-of-distracted-walking?partner=rss …    
    
    
    "Three Common Social Media Fears and How to Overcome Them" #businesstips #socialmedia http://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/50508375/0/spinsucks~Three-Common-Social-Media-Fears-and-How-to-Overcome-Them/ …    
    
    
    Best tip: design with purpose -Facebook’s Mark Zuckerberg And Kate Aronowitz On Social Design | Co.Design  http://www.fastcodesign.com/3018672/design-50/dynamic-duos-facebooks-mark-zuckerberg-and-kate-aronowitz-on-social-design?partner=rss&utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=feedburner+fastcodesign&utm_content=feedburner …    
    
    
    Made a typo on book title on prev. tweet - Which #book is on your night table? I'm currently reading Avogadro Corp. by William @hertling.    
    
    
    @alexaclark This is good customer service from the delivery guy! Maybe, he wanted a piece :-)) @BauliCanada    
    
    
    @alexaclark Don't worry! I would probably have not thought of it either.    
    
    
    "Apple Now Accepts Water-Damaged iPhones for Its Trade-In Program" http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/Mashable/~3/S8CzAi3AJww/ …    
    
    
    "Vancouver’s ban on the humble doorknob likely to be a trendsetter" #buildingcode http://www.vancouversun.com/Vancouver+humble+doorknob+likely+trendsetter/9173543/story.html …    
    
    
    I started to use a new editorial calendar tool today for WordPress. I will tell you in a few days how I like it. #blogging    
    
    
    Who invited winter. It's 0 deg. But feels like -9 #freezing    
    
    
    My latest post talks about whether or not you should publish a post, a tweet or a comment. http://ow.ly/r1H4o  Inspired by #oreo #meshcon    
    
    
    @SocialDave Nous avons acheté des ensembles #LEGO à Zack comme cadeaux de Noël. Je me suis prise tôt cette année. Et j'ai magasiné en ligne.    
    
    
    @amritachandra Thanks you for the shout-out. I appreciate it.    
    
    
    @seanmcdonald We share the same philosophy.    
    
    
    Tried a new recipe that got my son's approval. Personnally, I like it cuz it cook while I am picking him up at daycare. #worklifebalance    
    
    
    @chrisbrogan At my house tonight, it was goodnight Gruffalo.    
    
    
    @Nathalie_B An oven chicken flavoured with garlic, olives, lemon zest, cherry tomatoes, parsley and olive oil. On the side, arugula salad    
    
    
    @Nathalie_B It's an early Donna Hay recipe. Since it is made with a whole chicken cut in 8,  I got leftovers in the freezer.    
    
    
    @amritachandra @seanmcdonald Art too! Have you read about my toddler's reaction when we hung a painting in his room? http://ow.ly/r27sT     
    
    
    @Nathalie_B I am looking for more recipes that will enable to multitask. Any suggestions?    
    
    
    @amritachandra I will be glad to answer your questions. DM me when you are ready. I'll send you my email address.    
    
    
    Bonjour! Good morning! Another cold sunny day in Montreal.    
    
    
    Besides problem-solving, elf-direction is worth promoting in schools. - How will tech shape the future of education? http://techpageone.dell.com/business/will-tech-shape-future-education/ …    
    
    
    @kimvallee In my last tweet, I meant self-direction, not elf-direction.    
    
    
    I went shopping this afternoon for the supplies I need to host the Holiday workshop at my son's daycare. I'll test my craft project this w-e    
    
    
    @Ldillonschalk Thank you for sharing my post. Your session was a hit for many people. Have a great day, Laurie.    
    
    
    August raises $8M as it tries to avoid the hardware revolution's scalability problem http://pandodaily.com/2013/11/19/august-raises-8m-as-it-tries-to-avoid-the-hardware-revolutions-scalability-problem/ … via @pandodaily    
    
    
    From @Uber Blog, London, your UberEXEC is arriving now! A category between X and LUX. http://ish.re/4YWC     
    
    
    Thks! RT @Carl_Eidson:Follow #marketing pros & innovators who help others build brands, gain market share @Britty_Wagner @AIMERmarketing #FF    
    
    
    @alexaclark I know what you mean.    
    
    
    @NinaLjutic Happy week-end to you, Nina.    
    
    
    Happy Monday! It is freezing down here. How is it where you live? #winter    
    
    
    Authority as an excuse for complacency http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/11/authority-as-an-excuse-for-complacency.html …    
    
    
    Read the last 3 paragraphs. Big promises can lead to better experiences http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/11/big-promises-lead-to-better-experiences.html …    
    
    
    @EliseOndet we are supposed to have soon tonight. Mentally, I'm not ready for snow, yet. At least, temperature will get over 0 the next day    
    
    
    Bravo! RT @zelaurent: Deux start-ups Web de Montréal achètent des joueurs internationaux http://ow.ly/r9yYH  via @sebprovencher ;)    
    
    
    @Sucreconfetti It is too brutal. I hope that it is not a presage of what is coming all winter.    
    
    
    For my #retail case study #1, I talked about how @davidteas uses Twitter to generate more sales http://kimvallee.com/how-retailer-can-use-twitter-generate-sales/ …    
    
    
    Prepared to pay extra. RT @MarketingProfs: Three Marketing Tactics to Tap Into the Emerging Apple Demographic http://www.marketingprofs.com/articles/2013/12158/three-marketing-tactics-for-the-emerging-apple-demographic …    
    
    
    @boutotcom Merci Bruno pour le RT!    
    
    
    A good example of how a retailer should use Twitter - I shared my excellent customer experience with @DAVIDsTEA http://kimvallee.com/how-retailer-can-use-twitter-generate-sales/ …    
    
    
    RT@EdenSpodek: Make people laugh says @MarkRaganCEO. People expect to be entertained. #ragancontent #omligold    
    
    
    @communicable @EdenSpodek @MarkRaganCEO I'm reading a book titled Contingeous that talked about emotions can trigger sharing online    
    
    
    @theurbanmode just a quick mention that went I used to live in Toronto, twenty years ago, you were my favorite home design store    
    
    
    @communicable @EdenSpodek @MarkRaganCEO the exact book title is Contagious: why things catch on - sorry for the mistake    
    
    
    Yes, it is myth! RT @nilofer: A great piece on Silicon Valley "meritocracy" myth. http://www.wired.com/opinion/2013/11/silicon-valley-isnt-a-meritocracy-and-the-cult-of-the-entrepreneur-holds-people-back/ …    
    
    
    @communicable I'll check it!    
    
    
    Good morning! It's way more comfortable today at 1° C.    
    
    
    @emiliesenecal Merci Émilie du compliment. J'ai d'autres articles en tête qui je l'espère seront aussi utile. #useful    
    
    
    Two mini-cakes for Dr. Who fans: First a TARDIS http://ow.ly/reEv3  and for a Dalek cake http://youtu.be/3wohlCHIANM  #DrWho #cakedecorating    
    
    
    "VC: Please Don't Try to Build a Billion-Dollar Company" good read http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/YH_UlY8yuo8/story01.htm …    
    
    
    @DAVIDsTEA My pleasure!    
    
    
    @emiliesenecal Cette date a été choisi pour satisfaire les snowbirds. La proposition initiale, si je me souviens bien été le 15 novembre.    
    
    
    C'est beau vu de haut. RT @marianik1968: Lorsque le Square Phillips revêt son tapis blanc. #Mtlmoments http://instagram.com/p/hOockgIp7y/     
    
    
    @providehome Congratulations on turning 6.    
    
    
    "How clutter affects your productivity (and what you can do about it)" good read http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheNextWeb/~3/eNjpddxDhR8/ …    
    
    
    @emiliesenecal Je suis bien d'accord avec toi. De toute façon, plusieurs partent en novembre pour éviter nos premières journées froides.    
    
    
    @emiliesenecal J'ai choisi ma voiture ne fonction de l'hiver. Je la chausse d'excellents pneus d'hiver et elle a une traction intégrale.    
    
    
    Dear @ClarksCanada, I am sad that you don't produce a women version of the ARCHEO ZIP. It would to walk on a day filled with slush    
    
    
    For last minute ideas to make your Thanksgiving a success, check out http://athome.kimvallee.com/tag/thanksgiving/ … #thanksgiving    
    
    
    5-Minute Martha: Greet Your Guests with Tasty Grazing Boards http://kim.tl/tqmXFW  #thanksgiving    
    
    
    @georgiasap My pleasure! I heard that you gave a good talk at #3TYYZ. The winter Olympics are my favorite. #sochi2014    
    
    
    I will brave the cold weather. On @Accuweather, it says that our -6° C really feels like -18°.    
    
    
    Bonne approche RT @valerialandivar: #Youtility, comment gagner et fidéliser des clients tout en aidant http://ow.ly/qF21d  #MédiasSociaux    
    
    
    I'm creating new consulting packages for retailers & brands who want to grow their business w/ social media & meaningful content #business    
    
    
    @Fionacartolina I'm glad that you like the idea. I feel that having packages will enable retailers to easily grasp what I can do for them.    
    
    
    Hello ladies! Did you take advantages of the Black Friday sales? #ff @damask_dentelle @NinaLjutic @SophieCLaplante @nylafree    
    
    
    @ValaAfshar I think that a great mentor also teaches you how to prioritize and determine which actions will lead to your goals    
    
    
    @SophieCLaplante I bought some hair products at @Aveda (20% off) + 2 sweaters and a pink skirt at 40% off at @bananarepublic #blackfriday    
    
    
    @SophieCLaplante Good buy!    
    
    
    I can say: I've been there, I done that! Legendary Akihabara Radio Store closing its doors after six decades http://www.japantimes.co.jp/news/2013/11/25/national/legendary-akihabara-radio-store-closing-its-doors-after-six-decades …    
    
    
    How we turned a world record in journalism crowdfunding into an actual publication and we run it differently http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/TheNextWeb/~3/F_7gVcrkJlE/ …    
    
    
    Is there a reason for the friction? http://sethgodin.typepad.com/seths_blog/2013/11/is-there-a-reason-for-the-friction.html …    
    
    
    @jaybaer I agree with you. A case where repetitions don't win customers.    
    
    
    Cooked tonight a recipe that I didn't make in the last 15 years. Is it good sometimes to revisit old classic. FYI, it is a French recipe.    
    
    
    Defining the touchpoint:  “at this point in time, how do we meet the need of this person?” http://www.adaptivepath.com/ideas/un-sucking-the-touchpoint/ … #ux    
    
    
    Apple Buys Twitter Analytics Company Topsy http://mashable.com/2013/12/02/apple-buys-topsy/ … #businessnews    
    
    
    Why Conversion Rate is a Horrible Metric to Focus On http://www.smartinsights.com/goal-setting-evaluation/goals-kpis/why-conversion-rate-is-a-horrible-metric-to-focus-on/ … via @smartinsights #digitalmarketing    
    
    
    Coming soon: Facebook Tweaks News Feed for More 'High Quality' Content http://mashable.com/2013/12/02/facebook-news-feed-high-quality-content/ … #socialmedia    
    
    
    More tips for retailers. How smartphones transform the in-store shopping experience http://kimvallee.com/mobile-shopping/ … #retail #mobile    
    
    
    My toddler is watching @youtube. He found a series of fun train videos for toddlers. The best part: we showed him how to skip ads.    
    
    
    18 Tech Tools To Make You More Efficient At Work https://www.openforum.com/articles/18-tech-tools-to-make-you-more-efficient-at-work … via @OPENForum #smallbusiness    
    
    
    How 3 Startups Use Data to Improve Ecommerce Sales http://mashable.com/2013/12/02/product-conversion-metrics/ … #ecommerce #drivesales    
    
    
    Looking for retail tips to grow your business? I got some for you at http://kimvallee.com/tag/retail/  #retail    
    
    
    How to Make Star Wars Snowflakes With Paper, Scissors, and the Force http://www.wired.com/underwire/2013/12/star-wars-paper-snowflakes/ … #christmas #scifi    
    
    
    Many views and ways to explain it RT @jaybaer: B2B Experts: The Difference Between Social Media and Content Marketing http://bit.ly/1cWDsVD     
    
    
    @Fionacartolina Good morning Fiona. I feel great. And it is a gorgeous day outside. What about you?    
    
    
    It feels weird to not write about Holiday decorating and entertaining tips this year. Kinda miss my old blog http://athome.kimvallee.com/?s=holiday     
    
    
    Surviving Cold and Flu Season in Modern Style http://www.dwell.com/we-recommend/slideshow/surviving-cold-flu-season-modern-style#1 …    
    
    
    Quick & Easy Appetizer Recipes http://bit.ly/WyqQdl  #entertaining #recipes    
    
    
    What can you learn from this campaign? Uber to deliver Christmas trees on-demand for one day only http://ow.ly/rsi82  #marketing    
    
    
    @sethgodin talks about how to use our fear like fuel when we are nervous at important moments http://feeds.feedblitz.com/~/51531135/0/sethsblog~Trash-talking-important-work.html …    
    
    
    The 10 Smartest Cities In North America By Boyd Cohen http://www.fastcoexist.com/3021592/the-10-smartest-cities-in-north-america … via @FastCoExist    
    
    
    A treat for Valentine Day: it will be the premiere of "House of Cards" season 2 #tv    
    
    
    @anki @ShawnKing @jimmynewton I'ld love accessories to tailor the look of my #Anki Drive car. Could we repaint them? If yes, any advice?    
    
    
    @anki Thanks! I want to brighten the blue of Katal    
    
    
    More abt art and kids w/ a study that showed that kids learned critical-thinking skills from an art museum tour http://kimvallee.com/kids-learn-critical-thinking-skills-at-art-museum/ … #art    
    
    
    On-demand tree delivery from @uber is today only. See what I said about this convenient #marketing initiative http://ow.ly/rulZm     
    
    
    Nice name! RT @margotaustin: Learning about 2014 #benjaminmoore palette. This is Colour of the Year (in cookie form!) http://instagram.com/p/hjK7z6ym_Z/     
    
    
    The American way: super size :-)) RT @JeromeParadis: #rvmeetup monster limo ride http://vine.co/v/hxEjHHYVe3b     
    
    
    Great Canadian design girls #ff @damask_dentelle @SophieCLaplante @nylafree @Fionacartolina @poppytalk    
    
    
    10 festive party cakes that you can make this holiday http://ow.ly/rwFiT  #christmas #desserts via @poppytalk    
    
    
    It is easier to do when you start smiling during a stressful moment RT @inspiredtoshare: Life mantra: patience. The best is yet to come.    
    
    
    @inspiredtoshare I learned this trick from spending time with my toddler. Now, if I can learn to do it not just when I am with him ;-)    
    
    
    @DominicArpin C'est assez audacieux comme concept! C'est comique à regarder.    
    
    
    Just missing a huge felt piece for Christmas workshops that I'll do Monday at my son's daycare. My inspiration http://ow.ly/rwHJy  #diy    
    
    
    Game-changing services are coming - Nailing the Convenience Factor in Customer Service http://ow.ly/rwI65     
    
    
    thorough coverage @mathewi: well done RT @kirstinmckee: Really clever Nelson Mandela video from The Economist http://www.mandelaswalk.com/     
    
    
    @martinlessard Je devrais faire comme toi. Comme fan de design, suis découragée que #leonskriskringle soit ds mes "tendances" personnalisées    
    
    
    En effet! RT @le1518: Le Nelson Mandela Digital Archive Project : un très beau site pour connaître davantage #mandela http://bit.ly/1khipjb     
    
    
    Still love them! Simple (and Not So Simple) Christmas Cookie Ideas http://kim.tl/tLZH3W  #cookies    
    
    
    Ideal for small spaces. A Round-Up of DIY Wall Christmas Trees http://kim.tl/Vol4dZ     
    
    
    @maddy_smiles This year will be the first year since my toddler's birthday that I put a Christmas tree. Already have cat friendly ornaments    
    
    
    @maddy_smiles My cats broke a few baubles over the years. I put the more fragile at the top of the tree. Kittens would be even more curious    
    
    
    It is passed my bed time. Good night!    
    
    
    Want less stress? Fix your bottleneck! http://kimvallee.com/want-more-time-fix-bottleneck/ …    
    
    
    Christmas tree. Done! http://instagram.com/p/ho-nQpNH6t/     
    
    
    @JeromeParadis which ones did you play?    
    
    
    Want less stress? Fix your bottleneck! I fixed mine. http://kimvallee.com/want-more-time-fix-bottleneck/ … #worllifebalance    
    
    
    More work-life balance tips. How I can my kid's advent calendar and all our Christmas preparation manageable http://kimvallee.com/keeping-advent-calendar-manageable/ …    
    
    
    Nice 2 know that! I hope that you soon find a solution RT @fabricevil: @KimVallee what a great advice. I currently have major stress issues!    
    
    
    Good morning! At -5 C, it feels like winter here. Light snor is forecast for today    
    
    
    Ouups, light snow , not snor    
    
    
    A fun tree decorating project for toddlers. What my son and his daycare class did with me this morning… http://instagram.com/p/htbJ_RtH0r/     
    
    
    @nylafree Happy Monday!    
    
    
    Waiting with other parents for my son's Christmas party    
    
    
    The Christmas concert is about to begin #familyfun    
    
    
    Sweet! Molly's Sketchbook: Taffy Twist Felt Garland http://www.purlbee.com/the-purl-bee/2013/12/8/mollys-sketchbook-taffy-twist-felt-garland.html … #christmastree #diy    
    
    
    Note to myself for next year: Putting fabric birds and deers on my Christmas is not a great idea when we live with two cats.    
    
    
    Just received a call from a new provider who didn't read my tips for more meaningful customer satisfaction surveys http://ow.ly/rDGa7     
    
    
    I wrote two posts with tips to reduce your daily stress last weekend. #worklifebalance http://ow.ly/rDIdT  http://ow.ly/rDIjQ     
    
    
    We can all learn from this list. 10 ways to get a tougher mind and be more successful http://feedly.com/k/1d8ndVr     
    
    
    @lizardnladybug a nice present!    
    
    
    Twitter Users Can Now Send, Receive Images in Direct Messages http://mashable.com/2013/12/10/twitter-images-direct-messages/ …    
    
    
    @gypsybandito When you think about it, it feels weird that they didn't implement it sooner.    
    
    
    @theurbanmode Thank you for the RT!    
    
    
        
    
    
    At the #technoel2013 party (@ 3643 St. Laurent Apt. 200 w/ @cedricfontaine @fharper @diana_fyaz @evanpro) http://4sq.com/18D6nLQ     
    
    
    @AJKandy it would have been great to chat with you    
    
    
    Décrochage scolaire: une île, deux mondes http://www.lapresse.ca/actualites/education/201312/11/01-4720160-decrochage-scolaire-une-ile-deux-mondes.php … #education #montreal    
    
    
    Spotify sets mobile music free. What took so long? http://cnet.co/1h2x3Lt  via @CNET    
    
    
    Blacklisted the garage where I bought my car. Unacceptable to send a promo email where I can see all the customers' emails #failed    
    
    
    @cc_chapman I told their customer service rep. that next time they should use a newsletters service instead. Will help their quality control    
    
    
    @sometimesicing Ppl don't double-check enough b4 hitting the send button. BCC is a simple but prone to errors. Must be careful w/ mass email    
    
    
    People with young children will recognize themselves in the first story. I promise you a good laugh http://youtu.be/uFQfylQ2Jgg  #parenting    
    
    
    <3 it RT @martinwaxman: On @Inside_PR 3.58, @ginidietrich @thornley and I talk abt new business + how we approach it http://ht.ly/rIwQ1     
    
    
    My favorite flower. Lucky you! My cats eat them. So, I gave up. RT @EdenSpodek: Tulips http://instagram.com/p/h1hTU-FTjB/     
    
    
    5 things you can do to enjoy your job more (by thinking about it a little less). http://feedly.com/k/1j3by1v     
    
    
    5 tips for publishing content that matters to your audience. Illustrated by how @Lotus_F1Team uses social media http://ow.ly/rKvJP     
    
    
    WordPress has gotten a facelift. Discover WordPress 3.8 "Parker" at http://wordpress.org/news/2013/12/parker/ … #wordpress    
    
    
    Tuyau pr passer à RDI. Tenez votre conférence de presse un vendredi PM. La pause de Georges St-Pierre ne mérite pas une couverture à #RDI    
    
    
    Getting ready for visiting Santa with my little boy.    
    
    
    All dressed up to see Santa Claus @ Complexe Desjardins http://instagram.com/p/h4VSBUNH1o/     
    
    
    Good morning! Try to stay warm today. It's -21° C right now, feels like -32° C. There will be a fire in the fireplace.    
    
    
    Bonne idée RT @MichelleBlanc: C'est vrai c'est frette pr couper un sapin de Noël. Je vais faire plaisir @BibitteElectric et en acheter un    
    
    
    @Fionacartolina Congrats!    
    
    
    @Fionacartolina That is awesome! I'm not surprised they are so pretty.    
    
    
    @evemartel Je vais de regarder la boutique. Ils ont de belles choses.    
    
    
    L'hiver a décidé d'en profiter maintenant que nous devons tous avoir nos pneus d'hiver pour étendre un… http://instagram.com/p/h8gsIDNH-z/     
    
    
    Guess what? It's winter and I caught a cold. It's cold but beautiful outside, thank to a keep snow carpet.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Malheureusement, ils sont situés trop loin pour moi RT @marianik1968: CUISINE DE RUE même en hiver! #lapresseplus http://plus.lapresse.ca/screens/472e-1c38-52a62ef3-8f95-6517ac1c606d%7C_0.html …    
    
    
    Cher Reno-Depot, si vous pensez que je vais me déplacer à un de magasins ne sachant pas si vous avez un produit en magasin, vous vs trompez    
    
    
    Pelleter devient beaucoup plus le fun lorsque tu partages ce moment avec un bambin qui s'amuse comme un petit fou dans la neige.    
    
    
    @KimAuclair Chapeau au personnel des Rona. J'ai en appelé plusieurs car ce dont je veux est en rupture de stock. Tous très serviables!    
    
    
    Reading a business book while my car gets its winter check-up. Practical to have an @AmazonKindle    
    
    
    @erinmclaughlin1 @TheDogTackShop @LaMaisonmmx @annmariefavot Nice shot! My toddler discovered the joy of chocolate last weekend    
    
    
    @phuongly I switched between Jab. Jab, Jab, Right Hook from @garyvee and Contagious: why things catch on from @j1berger    
    
    
    @phuongly I brought my Kindle with me. It fits better than my iPad on my handbag    
    
    
    @phuongly I now have an iPad Air which is nice for reading book. B4 my iPad was the 1st generation, which is why my husband gave me a Kindle    
    
    
    Have you finish your Christmas shopping? I don't!    
    
    
    @ohhappyday @PhilipsLight We switched to more efficient lamps earlier this year. Surprising how much lighting they provide at lower wattage    
    
    
    On the menu tonight: my mom's salmon sauce served on vol-au-vent with broccoli #whatsfordinner    
    
    
    @EdenSpodek Regardless of the new law, it is plain, good PR to put an Unsubscribe link at the end of every email pitch. #digitaledu #PR    
    
    
    @Nathalie_B It's not so bad, as a leftover. I like the simplicity of serving pasta on Monday.    
    
    
    @hostpitalitysc Thanks for the shout-out.    
    
    
    Good morning! It's another cold cold day in Montreal.    
    
    
    We booked our winter vacation yesterday: a mix of beach and the first time of our little boy to @DisneyParks.    
    
    
    @jonesypapery Snow is scheduled for this afternoon. We received plenty of the white powder Sunday.    
    
    
    @kimberleyseldon Agree! It doesn't sound like Christmas otherwise.    
    
    
    I did it again! Bought a pair of shoes for my toddler that is too big. I need to bring him shopping with me next time.    
    
    
    @kimberleyseldon Are you ready for the holiday? I had a head start by shopping early but then, I forgot to continue. Happy Holidays!    
    
    
    Fast, Free, No need to sign in Wi-Fi for a 3-Mile Stretch in San Francisco http://mashable.com/2013/12/17/san-francisco-free-wi-fi/ …    
    
    
    Want people to share your posts more often? 8 Simple Scientifically Proven Ways to Improve Your Writing http://www.fastcompany.com/3023616/work-smart/8-simple-scientifically-proven-ways-to-improve-your-writing?partner …    
    
    
    I understand the need for visual aids but do they made it ugly? Apple Takes A Step Backwards From Flat Design http://www.fastcolabs.com/3023552/apple-takes-a-step-backwards-from-flat-design …    
    
    
    10 Scientifically Proven Ways to Be Incredibly Happy and increase your productivity http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/Vf0fdeTpu7E/story01.htm …    
    
    
    I don't check my inbox 1st thing in the morning. What abt u? Case For / Against Checking Emails When Wake Up http://www.fastcompany.com/3023610/how-to-be-a-success-at-everything/the-case-for-and-against-checking-your-email-when-you-wake?partner=rss&utm_source=feedburner&utm_medium=feed&utm_campaign=feedburner+fastcompany&utm_content=feedburner …    
    
    
    @EliseOndet Planned a trip this week. In general, don't watch the news, walk instead of driving whenever I can and balancing life and work.    
    
    
    Like the plywood tree card holder RT @CentsationalGrl: Creative Christmas card displays, today on the blog!  http://bit.ly/1dNHJvb     
    
    
    At my home, the cats, not my toddler, destroy my tree ornaments. @DwellStudio @ScooterTraffic @TheLandofNod @RestoHardware    
    
    
    Enjoy your delicious lunch. RT @marianik1968: I'm at @Fbarmtl (Montréal, QC) http://4sq.com/1dmZvoA     
    
    
    @EliseOndet Bright choice! I lived w/out a car for a while. I walk more than I drive. I bought my car in spring 2008; it has < 35,000 km    
    
    
    @aliofish My son adores the shoes, after all. I thought that they would be too big by comparing to other shoes he has.    
    
    
    Way more practical then carrying a shoe with me. RT @aliofish: @KimVallee trace his foot on a piece of paper and bring that with you.    
    
    
    @ScooterTraffic Felines are a tough crowd. They love the plush and knitted ornaments too much    
    
    
    Photo Booth Props Holiday Grab Bag Mustache by tweedledeeaz. Sadly for us, Canadians, shipping is limited to USA. http://etsy.me/1c1lzqv     
    
    
    @EliseOndet I want the convenience of having the car when I need it. Since I keep it for 10 yrs and sell it w low mileage, it's not that bad    
    
    
    @EliseOndet These days, I use it every day to bring my son to daycare. It's too far and not easily accessible by public transit.    
    
    
    If I was a baker, this would be on my Christmas wish list #kitchenaid @ Costco http://instagram.com/p/iG96INNH0M/     
    
    
    @QQMPS Je résiste car je n'ai plus de place dans mes armoires. Trop d'accessoires de cuisine.    
    
    
    Nice pic! RT @alexaclark: RT @aprildunford: Ah - we are just so cool. @barsoomcore @alexaclark #hohoto pic.twitter.com/G87iFSgFZ4    
    
    
    Joyeuses Fêtes! @suzlortie @Emergent007 @MichelleBlanc @PhilippeMartin @boutotcom @Damdam @Charles_Nouyrit @martinlessard @fharper #ff    
    
    
    Happy Holidays! @alexaclark @missrogue @EdenSpodek @Nathalie_B @meredithheron @EliseOndet @kimberleyseldon @jonesypapery #ff    
    
    
    Holiday cheers to @Fionacartolina @poppytalk @apartment_34 @Melissact @littlehouseblog @houseandhome @styleathome @hgtvcanada #ff    
    
    
        
    
    
    On the agenda this afternoon is to complete my Christmas shopping. Sad that I didn't stock a few versatile gifts for the last minute gifts.    
    
    
    You've Been Elf-ed!  Start A Neighborhood Holiday Tradition. This should be fun! via @cynthiaewer http://shar.es/OyzKD     
    
    
    @GEMonogram thanks! Before I started shopping, I checked how long is the cashier line.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @rlangdon I will check next time if we can still buy a mug. That would be awesome for our boy    
    
    
    @adebold Glaze rain that destroyed the deep snow we received last week. We were hoping to ski but the weather decided otherwise    
    
    
    A friendly pirate is attacking me #familyfun #lego http://instagram.com/p/iPEDoKtH36/     
    
    
    Had fun this afternoon skiing with my toddler. Sadly, there was no time to take a picture #familyfun    
    
    
    Une tradition du temps des Fêtes:la tarte au sirop d'érable des Sucreries de l'érable http://instagram.com/p/iSlMvONH_O/     
    
    
    @Nathalie_B Est-ce    
    
    
    @Nathalie_B Est-ce qu'elle t'a enseignée son secret?    
    
    
    Good morning! It's very cold this morning with tiny snow falling from the sky    
    
    
    The large window is delightful @chevronseclairs: {inspiring to work in a place like this} http://pinterest.com/pin/261490322088047411/ …    
    
    
    Christmas party is starting on a great note. #champagne #oysters http://instagram.com/p/iUtX_ONH4I/     
    
    
    My little prince à la table de Noël #christmas http://instagram.com/p/iUyp-RtHyV/     
    
    
    Merry Christmas! Love and joy @damask_dentelle @NinaLjutic @nylafree @aquaovo @odile_ab @buk_nola @VaBenee @poppytalk @kelly_albert    
    
    
    I wish you a Merry Christmas! I wish you a Merry Christmas! http://instagram.com/p/iWPi51tH38/     
    
    
    From immersive experiences to remixing traditions. What Will Make Consumers Tick in 2014? http://mashable.com/2013/12/25/consumer-ticks/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    Kids' Belief in Santa Myth Is Healthy (and like pretend play, it promotes their creativity), Psychologists Say http://mashable.com/2013/12/25/believing-in-santa/ …    
    
    
    A look at the service providers of the Kickstarter industry http://pando.com/2013/12/25/the-hidden-kickstarter-industry/ …    
    
    
    A look at the future of Content Marketing http://contentmarketinginstitute.com/2013/12/next-big-question-content-marketing/ … via @CMIContent    
    
    
    @DianeBourque Joyeux Noël, Diane! La dinde du réveillon était délicieuse. Ce soir, c'est le ragoût de dinde et de boulettes. x0x    
    
    
    tricky bit is to turn proud new owners into people buying apps. Why Christmas is an agonizing time for app developers http://qz.com/161320     
    
    
    They are having fun. RT @matthewburpee: Secret fort under the Japanese maple http://fb.me/6j7DixBnz     
    
    
    "3 Tips to Combat Anxiety Before a Presentation"  http://feeds.inc.com/~r/home/updates/~3/FEe_llTdwlc/story01.htm …    
    
    
    Awesome! "When Simon Beck Goes on a Winter Walk, He Leaves Behind the Most Beautiful Footprints"  http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/core77/blog/~3/1xcoYRSAUiY/when_simon_beck_goes_on_a_winter_walk_he_leaves_behind_the_most_beautiful_footprints_26157.asp …    
    
    
    What not to do when reaching influencers pic: http://ow.ly/i/495de . See @pattonoswalt response to @BA_Influencers http://ow.ly/s6NiY     
    
    
    Happy last weekend of the year @NinaLjutic @damask_dentelle @nylafree @aquaovo @odile_ab @buk_nola @VaBenee @poppytalk @kelly_albert #FF    
    
    
    Awesome idea: Skype in the Classroom projects get students more engaged http://f-st.co/j0POgML  #education    
    
    
    ARCHITECT Staff Picks for Best New Buildings of 2013 - Architect Magazine http://fw.to/swtLo1W     
    
    
    Space-saver! Star-shaped clothes horse by Aaron Dunkerton http://www.dezeen.com/2013/12/27/star-shaped-clothes-horse-by-aaron-dunkerton/ … via @dezeen    
    
    
    Good Sunday morning! Enjoy the warmth today because it will get cold the rest of the week. CUrrently -1° C.    
    
    
    And it is all quiet in the house right now. RT @markwschaefer: Nice cold rainy morning to do some blogging!    
    
    
    Mine is better customer service RT @hbaskas: In progress: a wish list of new #airport amenities for 2014. Add yours http://ow.ly/s725g     
    
    
    Very useful if you plan a last minute dinner party http://kimvallee.com/bring-something-new-by-repackaging-your-products/ … http://ow.ly/i/49BGv     
    
    
    An article to understand 2014 LATCH changes in the USA starting January 1st. http://ow.ly/s8fms  #babygears    
    
    
    @enkerli Je la trouve à l'épicerie Métro de mon quartier. J'imagine qu'il y en a aussi à La Vieille Europe sur le boul. Saint-Laurent.    
    
    
    Good Monday morning! Put your warmest coat and boots before heading out. You'll need them all week!    
    
    
    @matthewburpee I know the feeling. I took comfort from fact that it slows online during Christmas and New Year. I was happy to get it back!    
    
    
    Same to you. What are your plans? RT @EdenSpodek: Good morning on this last day of 2013. Make the most of today.    
    
    
    Pour être encore belle ce soir RT @marianik1968: 5 meilleurs spots à Montréal pour se faire faire les ongles.  http://www.nightlife.ca/mode-design/les-5-meilleurs-spots-montreal-pour-des-ongles-au-top …    
    
    
    @EdenSpodek We will celebrate with some friends. It should be fun. Zack will celebrate with us.    
    
    
    Before you make your New Year resolution, two things to consider http://ow.ly/sb3d6  http://ow.ly/sb3ea     
    
    
    Which one that you care about? 7 Huge Tech Trends to Expect in 2014 http://mashable.com/2013/12/31/tech-predictions-2014/ … #tech #innovation    
    
    
    Frequency of use is key RT @PamMktgNut: 73% U.S. Adults Use Social Networks, Pinterest Passes Twitter In Popularity http://techcrunch.com/2013/12/30/pew-social-networking/?ncid=twittersocialshare …    
    
    
    Possiblement plus de PinterestRT @SophieGiroux: Une de mes résolutions médias sociaux 2014: plus de Twitter, moins d'Instagram.    
    
    
    Happy New Year to my design fabs! @damask_dentelle @nylafree @NinaLjutic @anile @meredithheron @SamanthaPynn @LakeJaneBlog @poppytalk    
    
    
    @MichelleBlanc Une belle façon de terminer l'année!    
    
    
    I freshen up my Web Site for the New Year. What do you think of the small changes I made? http://kimvallee.com     
    
    
    @kristalamb Thank you, Krista! This is what I was aiming for. Happy New Year!    
    
    
    Although it failed to remain relevant, sad that an old friend will be sent to the graveyard #notmorebump http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/OmMalik/~3/2P9I2naiOso/ …    
    
    
    AllThingsD shuts down as Mossberg and Swisher introduce Re/code http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/OmMalik/~3/4sXkHhY0Wn4/ …    
    
    
    Good morning! It's freezing cold outside. On the bright side, it will only get warmer from this point on.    
    
    
    N'ose imaginer porter cela RT @CindyLou_: Ma montée de lait contre 5 tendances mode qui doivent disparaître avec 2013 http://ow.ly/sccbp     
    
    
    Une journée comme aujourd'hui, tu es contente que ta batterie d'auto est neuve! #ilfautfroiddddddd    
    
    
    They choose the perfect day to wear flannel RT @haaf: Flannel lords #flannel #menswear http://instagram.com/p/irPHaAiweO/     
    
    
    @haaf A comfy wool sweater does the job for me. It is a brutal return, for you two.    
    
    
    Have you set your goals for 2014, yet? Here is what I had to say about mine http://ow.ly/sdIbH  #newyear    
    
    
    Still one day and a half of freezing cold.    
    
    
    Less daily & weekly uses http://ow.ly/segxy  RT @MelissaOnline: LinkedIn and Pinterest more popular than Twitter? http://fw.to/cwtm79D     
    
    
    @Nathalie_B Pour un instant, j'ai pensé faire comme toi. Puis, j'ai opté pour un cognac.    
    
    
    I should try #6 more often RT @MelissaOnline: 13 Simple Ways Business Women Can Make A Difference In 2014 http://onforb.es/1l55qEx  via @Forbes    
    
    
    @Nathalie_B Cheers!    
    
    
    Why Philips Flattened The Light Bulb - and there is a desirable effect for your wallet http://feedly.com/e/WvAJwWkU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Happy to sleep in a warm bed. #harshweather http://instagram.com/p/ism3bQNH9q/     
    
    
    I was better in my warm bed. #toocold #montreal #weather pic.twitter.com/uiS3nAK0ih    
    
    
    Designer Norman Foster imagines a stunning 137-mile cycling track Floating Above London's Rail Lines http://ow.ly/sf8Ul  #design #urban    
    
    
    Happy New year to women who help us cook more often @CannelleVanille @tartinegourmand @simplebites @dinnerwithjulie @zoebakes @foodandstyle    
    
    
    Happy New Year to great designers and design lovers @SusanSerraCKD @meredithheron @decor8 @designsponge @casslavalle @UrbanDecorSue    
    
    
    Happy New Year to fun and modern moms @designmom @moderntwist @stephmodo @LeighAnnAllaire @YummyMummyClub @tomkatstudio @phdinparenting    
    
    
    It didn't change much #wearingmysnowsuit pic.twitter.com/lkOZ0OIMgd    
    
    
    Bonne Année et Bonne Bouffe à @LineAtallah @katerinerollet @eatdrinkbcarrie @indigonat @sweetisabelle1 @catlefebvre @calliope27 @alloannie    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    And it's a tall order RT @chrisbrogan: You need to read this, bloggers. From @copyblogger - http://copyblogger.com/ingredients/     
    
    
    @MichelleBlanc @JeromeParadis Je marche pas si vite! Je te le dirais si je m'aventure avec un froid sibérien sur des pistes.    
    
    
    @devilliersvv À aller chercher en fin de semaine.    
    
    
    I'm looking forward to tomorrow http://ow.ly/i/4cdf2  #atlast    
    
    
    @MichelleBlanc @JeromeParadis C'est un plan!    
    
    
    My reveal what my 3 words for 2014 are at http://ow.ly/sgVuh . What are yours? #resolutions #businessgoals    
    
    
    On peux enfin reprendre les activités hivernales. Demain, on va initier fiston au patin à glace. #videdefamille    
    
    
    @zenzizi tellement l'opposé de ce que je voulais dire    
    
    
    Looking for #business books to read, check the suggestions at #SheOwnIt - You'll get mine + 21 others (in good co.) http://ow.ly/o94K5     
    
    
    e-Commerce 101: Simple Tips to Convert Shoppers into Buyers http://ow.ly/oaSCQ  #ecommercetips    
    
    
    Hi @fionacartolina, with your new beautiful online store, I thought that you might enjoy my latest post on ecommerce http://ow.ly/oaWZc     
    
    
    Good morning! We have a nice sunny day here in Montreal to finish the work week. What about you?    
    
    
    If you read my experience trying to buy online a bowl for my @Kitchenaid food processor, it arrived this morning http://ow.ly/ocIwv     
    
    
    They have a fascinating story RT @mitchjoel: @theminimalists show you how to start a successful blog today http://bit.ly/1dzkkPm     
    
    
    @pinkbathtub I'll take a wonderful Saturday over a nice Friday.    
    
    
    Happy to be helpful. Have a great Friday. RT @fionacartolina: @KimVallee Thank you - you are so smart  :-)    
    
    
    Same 2 u RT @jeanpierrelevac: #FF @karinefrigon @seetsirbas @letechnophile @MarmaladesApp @_Celestia_ @MelanieGhanime @DerekJen @toddyflores    
    
    
    Long meetings are a waste of time. @Janine Popick shared how to structure yours as a 30 Minute Meeting http://ow.ly/ocSz7  #businesstips    
    
    
    How do you like it? RT @evanpro: My first @breather experience (@ Breather at Notman House) [pic]: http://4sq.com/14pCO1x     
    
    
    We need to RT @gsquare_offices: @KimVallee when time is limited, people become more productive. would you agree?    
    
    
    Thanks! RT @vast_media: Happy #FF back! :) @Seevibes @MariaSanz @KimVallee @CJDLTV @benmenson @mvargasgarro @AstridRory    
    
    
    @contributorweek Awesome! Keep me posted on what the @twitter cards did for you.    
    
    
    New on Balancing Act: Why Kids Need Day Care in Top of a Family Life #worklifebalance http://ow.ly/oejq7     
    
    
    Having fun building and destroying Playbrix structures #toy #familyfun http://instagram.com/p/dZp3DaNHz3/     
    
    
    I saw why on LinkedIn. Congratulations! RT @evanpro: @KimVallee I'm biased! /cc @breather    
    
    
    @Stammy Just read this article.    
    
    
    Dear @inc, adding the post URLs would be useful. On the Fast Track: @paulg Paul Graham's Top Tips for Start-ups http://ow.ly/ohmms     
    
    
    Why our brains can’t handle negative thoughts and 4 tips for cultivating positive thinking by @bellebethcooper http://ow.ly/ohnyH     
    
    
    For the right reasons RT @joelgascoigne: "Looking 4 Startup Ideas? 1st, Pick Market u Want to Serve" http://buff.ly/19UsxPn  by @kevindewalt    
    
    
    @kevindewalt Simply want to help in telling you a typo in 1st FAQ of @sohelpful. It's written somone instead of someone. Nice concept!    
    
    
    Love that! RT @fastcompany: "...companies with at least one woman on their board tend to be the strongest performers."...    
    
    
    @marianneprairie Bon retour! Mon bébé n'en ait plus un à près de 2 ans et demi. Ce que j'aime mieux à cet âge est le début des conversations    
    
    
    Any sales cuz of it? RT @fionacartolina: Cartolina iPhone cases featured on Macworld's website this morning http://www.macworld.com/article/2047260/the-week-in-iphone-cases-hogtown.html …    
    
    
    @fionacartolina That is great!    
    
    
    Former Ticketmaster exec will develop shopping experience on @Twitter. Want to team up w/ merchants 'n paymt services http://adage.com/u/uEshaa     
    
    
    My first experience. Love the rocking chair (not in my photo). @breather has the best room at Notman House for sure http://4sq.com/15f1Enx     
    
    
    A acheté de beaux casse-tête pour Zack. Ils ont aussi de belles boîtes à Lynch pour les enfants (@ Papillotte) [pic]: http://4sq.com/17mIGr4     
    
    
    J'ai acheté un beau coussin hibou et une jetée pour soit la chambre de Zack ou notre salon. Il était ds la vitrine... http://4sq.com/1dro0Fo     
    
    
    Before I went shopping for my son, Allen made me prettier. I have a new hair style: a sexy short look http://4sq.com/1dnF52f     
    
    
    Zack's new owl cushion #kidsroom http://instagram.com/p/dlHHLOtH4C/     
    
    
    The same owl cushion without effects http://instagram.com/p/dlHRZftH4O/     
    
    
    @pushinteriors I could not resist when I saw it.    
    
    
    At @montreal_cm #mtlcm -this month theme is about urbanism. Popular, as you can see (at @ccawire) [pic]: http://4sq.com/16WconN     
    
    
    Superb mask for @montreal_cm #mtlcm for the conference by Louise Guay @louiseguay @ Centre Canadien… http://instagram.com/p/doz085tH9l/     
    
    
    On doit amener la campagne à la ville (ex. les petites forêts) et rendre les rues accessibles aux citoyens pas seul. Aux autos #mtlcm    
    
    
    Le pouvoir du citoyen a grandi grâce à la technologie. Une plus grande collaboration ds la planification de la ville est possible #mtlcm    
    
    
    Le message final #mtlcm est #Montreal plateforme collaborative.    
    
    
    La qualité de vie part de la vie dans son quartier. Le fait de travailler près de chez-soi ou le télé-travail y contribue beaucoup. #mtlcm    
    
    
    @marielefebvre La photo de la montagne d'asphalte avec la borne fontaine est comique.    
    
    
    Brands need to rethink brand ownership. It can be shared with their customers and followers @HarvardBiz http://ow.ly/oqiS6  #socialmedia    
    
    
    Good Saturday morning! A mix of clouds and t-storms all day and night.    
    
    
    Inspiring when having a latte RT @nikastewart: Behind every successful woman is a substantial amount of coffee.    
    
    
    Sauf l'hiver quand il y a de la poudrerie RT @marianik1968: Ma partie favorite de l'Autoroute 10. http://instagram.com/p/dsMKP9op9e/     
    
    
    @jennbrouwer I saw that, at last, you're inside.    
    
    
    Movie night for a date with my @JeromeParadis tonight.    
    
    
    Make your emails really easy to reply to RT @claire: Why Every Email Should be 5 Sentences Long: http://bit.ly/154umBA  #businesstips    
    
    
    Including a look at the big data landscape RT @michellelaberge: How small businesses can mine big data http://lnkd.in/TF9Dvb  #businesstips    
    
    
    I do! RT @glamamama: @NinaLjutic @JennBrouwer @vanessajfrancis @kimberleyseldon @NicholasRosaci @rad3sixty @damask_dentelle Happy Hump Day!    
    
    
    Preparing Our Kids for the Job Market of Today and Tomorrow http://ow.ly/ozLCL  #education #innovation    
    
    
    @martinlessard Mon dernier billet pourrait t'intéresser http://ow.ly/ozLJx  - Je reprends des idées de ta balado sur le iPad à l'école    
    
    
    @adelemcalear Have you see that @sparksandhoney are naming Digital Death Manager as one of the 20 jobs of the future? http://ow.ly/ozNht     
    
    
    @martinlessard Tout à fait vrai.    
    
    
    Good morning! It starts to feel like autumn. 10° C this morning.    
    
    
    The lesson: need to treat your products like a client- Insight That Changed the Way I’m Building My Business http://alexisgrant.com/2013/09/04/insight-on-products/ …    
    
    
    @eventbrite expands offering by acquiring Lanyrd, Eventioz #businessnews http://agbeat.com/social-media/eventbrite-acquires-lanyrd-eventioz/ …    
    
    
    For back to school, I discussed the challenges of the #education system and how I think we could change http://ow.ly/oAulh     
    
    
    Article by @salon argued that biggest problem in #education is the school itself. They teach that learning is work http://ow.ly/oB4fO     
    
    
    BTW homeschooling your kids is not the answer. Too many kids will be left down by the system + your kids will lack the social interactions    
    
    
    5 Fun DIY Camera Kits that take 35mm film http://on.mash.to/1ak4bPb  via @mashable #photography    
    
    
    I like #4 and #5 - The 5 Worst Pieces of Advice for Small Business Owners http://on.mash.to/1dHLVQ0  via @mashable    
    
    
    Indeed! I look forward to see what people will say RT @suzlortie: Video: Moment Factory’s latest project is off the wall...    
    
    
    A product that geeks will buy for the WAF (Wife Acceptance Factor) - Fake Book Covers Conceal Video Games http://on.mash.to/19kxrRb  #etsy    
    
    
    My framework doesn't necessary follow this order but overall an #entrepreneur must answer these 5 essential questions http://ow.ly/oBeVI     
    
    
    @clarashih Congrats Clarah for the new money you raised for @HearsaySocial!    
    
    
    Any suggestions of what to do (with kids) in New york City this weekend. #travel    
    
    
    @stevey it was great! Maybe next time we  will have the chance to chat.    
    
    
    @hi_catherine  you are the second person who suggested the Museum of National History. I'll check it out    
    
    
    @hi_catherine early might be hard for me. I'm not a morning person :-)    
    
    
    Beautiful day in New York http://instagram.com/p/d9yzrDNHz0/     
    
    
    A hotshot at corner of Ninth Ave and W 14th Street for #CottonOrNothing http://instagram.com/p/d9zkDANH1T/     
    
    
    On the High Line #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d92IHWNH5k/     
    
    
    Human statue by Frank Benson #highline #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d93woxtH9G/     
    
    
    The assortment of artisanal soda at the Brooklyn Soda Works stand on the High Line #newyork http://instagram.com/p/d96-TXNHz8/     
    
    
    @KimVallee This tweet should have said a photo shoot not a hotspot    
    
    
    My son made his mom proud. He wanted to explore the @Anthropologie store. He knows how to win my heart. #priceless    
    
    
    @coffeeandcouch plus, he understood that I wanted to buy a book. So, we took a copy and remembered that we had to give it to the cashier    
    
    
    @coffeeandcouch how are you?    
    
    
    @NinaLjutic thanks for the #ff. I was off the grid for most of the day yesterday    
    
    
    Mingling with the locals on a gorgeous day (@ Street Fair w/ @jeromeparadis) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1cVHzSG     
    
    
    Good morning! Another sunny day in New York. Currently 18° C. Perfect for a day in Central Park with my toddler boy    
    
    
    While search and customized landing pages could improve #mobile #shopping, the biggest pain remains the checkout. http://ow.ly/oHmG8     
    
    
    Did it! RT @iconversations: @KimVallee vote for @iConversations six times per day. #Award Nominee. http://www.marthastewart.com/americanmade/nominee/82975 … @MarthaStewart    
    
    
    Taking a walk in Central Park #NewYork pic.twitter.com/X9sKaABiSh    
    
    
    @CustomMade yes! But don't give me spoilers about yesterday race. I'm in vacation. I will watch it when we came back    
    
    
    Having lunch outside #priceless    
    
    
    No more pine cone. Admiring the turtles and boats at boathouse #newyork http://instagram.com/p/eDVszZtHzw/     
    
    
    A classic Central Park view #newyork http://instagram.com/p/eDepKVNHwc/     
    
    
    Prend une pause-thé vert  pendant la sieste de fiston    
    
    
    @kimberleyseldon @damask_dentelle @NinaLjutic @raleighseldon @GlamaMama @nylafree I'm relaxing in New York and enjoying an end of summer day    
    
    
    @damask_dentelle Buying a house keeps busy. In the same neighbourhood?    
    
    
    Congrats Gini! You are a great read. RT @ginidietrich: Seven Years of Blogging. Happy Birthday, Spin Sucks! http://buff.ly/17n1nw6     
    
    
    @hostgatorcodes Thanks for sharing my post. I appreciate it.    
    
    
    What do u think? Talking about people expectations and many facets of modern executive women http://ow.ly/oJJZp  #business #women    
    
    
    @RBC_Canada  big #fail Today.. Are you on the business of ruining vacation with dumb process?    
    
    
    Leaving the Big Apple    
    
    
    Good morning! A gorgeous sunny day in Montreal. #ilovesummer    
    
    
    @damask_dentelle @kimberleyseldon @nylafree Happy for you! Now, you have it all. #loveatfirstsight    
    
    
    More kids will want their own tablet - Disney Wants You to Bring Your iPad to ‘The Little Mermaid’ Movie http://on.mash.to/1b5OwlU  #ipad #movie    
    
    
    More women still want to go back to their career after giving birth RT @melissaonline: Modern Woman's Defn of Success http://www.business2community.com/infographics/modern-womans-definition-success-0611691 …    
    
    
    I second that!
 RT @socialdave: @KimVallee @MelissaOnline And should be welcomed back! #worklife #women    
    
    
    Simple tips for cold-calls and email pitches from @inc - Sales Rule No. 1: Start a Simple Conversation http://ow.ly/oMrdO  #businesstips    
    
    
    So true! RT @phdinparenting: If you're pitching me on a family vacation destination, I don't want high res pics. I want tickets.    
    
    
    A sign that I'm back in #montreal : my iPhone runs on 3G instead of 4G    
    
    
    @ReCreativeWorks my pleasure, Renee. Have a great day!    
    
    
    Don't forget that a logo should pass the test of time @B2Community: Don’t Do These 5 Things When Writing a Logo Brief http://goo.gl/fb/ICjpJ     
    
    
    Women Securing a Greater Share of VC Funding than in the past. Mostly in the retail and consumer services space http://ow.ly/oMSky     
    
    
    Neither. Must quickly produce quality content RT @janinepopick: Quality vs. Quantity? Content Mrtg Pros Pick Sides http://dlvr.it/3xvy5r     
    
    
    No, sadly RT @jowyang: If you were born in the 70s the population will over double during your natural lifetime. Do you think we are ready?    
    
    
    @adebold Every entrepreneurial couple with (young) kids needs a way to make it works for their business and their family #worklifebalance    
    
    
    Les chanceux. RT @marianik1968: La fin des frais d'itinérance pour les Européens ? #luckythem http://plus.lapresse.ca/screens/4689-02b8-522f3be8-a2fa-2276ac1c6068%7C_0.html …    
    
    
    Good morning! After all the sunshine, it's a rainy day. Welcome to fall!    
    
    
    Why Everybody's Going Freelance and a talk on the 3 things that motivate people by @drake_baer http://ow.ly/oOtDa  #career    
    
    
    Content Marketing: How to Produce Quality and Quantity. No need to choose between one and the other http://ow.ly/oOWia  #contentmarketing    
    
    
    13 Places Brilliant Start-up Ideas Are Born | http://Inc.com  http://www.inc.com/young-entrepreneur-council/13-places-brilliant-start-up-ideas-are-born.html …    
    
    
    She is young and inspired by tech. Lucky Editor Eva Chen Wants To Build A Magazine You Can Talk To By @davidburstein http://ow.ly/oPajf     
    
    
    @ambercadabra Nice reference to the ultimate question.    
    
    
    I hope not. RT @cotedetexas: Back to the dr.  Not recuperating    Scared to death. http://instagram.com/p/eLLnuIlMcd/     
    
    
    50 Creative Ideas To Make Better Cities, Presented On Gorgeously Designed Posters By Ben Schiller http://www.fastcoexist.com/3016824/50-creative-ideas-to-make-better-cities-presented-on-gorgeously-designed-posters … via @FastCoExist    
    
    
    @emilyleldridge Canada already switched to polymer bills. It felt strange the 1st time that I held one in my hand. They grew on me.    
    
    
    Your competitors are not always the usual suspects. How iOs has disrupted Nintendo http://hypercritical.co/2013/09/02/nintendo-in-crisis … #business    
    
    
    Can never go wrong with a classic. RT @camillestyles: @daniellamarie_c I love that @Gap trench!! Such a classic.    
    
    
    Apporte indépendance économique (personnel + collectif) RT @duhamelp: Pourquoi les entrepreneurs sont si importants http://www.lactualite.com/lactualite-affaires/les-leaders-croissance/pourquoi-les-entrepreneurs-sont-si-importants/ …    
    
    
    @MariaSanz @EatStTweet @Chauddogs It's because you didn't check enough @FoodNetwork shows before :-)))    
    
    
    Good morning! A cool 8° C this morning. Summer is gone.    
    
    
    Leave Nothing to Chance – Tactics to Super Power Your Launch - Tips from @PasswordBox http://ow.ly/oUXq8   via @Ecquire #marketing    
    
    
    Adapt, connect and let others build on your products, ideas RT @jowyang: Meet the Resilient Corporations http://www.web-strategist.com/blog/2013/09/15/meet-the-resilient-corporations/ …    
    
    
    @flooringcanada Thank you!    
    
    
    London #design studio @industrialfacil designs desk organizers for the digital age for @HermanMiller via @psfk http://ow.ly/oYb10     
    
    
    15 Things Inspiring Leaders Do Differently | http://Inc.com  http://www.inc.com/lee-colan/15-things-inspiring-leaders-do-differently.html …    
    
    
    I updated the Sidekick Labs. What do you think about the new content? http://sidekicklabs.com  #digitalmarketing    
    
    
    @torontolouise I stopped having business cards cuz too many salepersons and consultants think that giving them my card is opting in    
    
    
    Why taxi cab drivers cannot put down their smartphones - http://FT.com  http://on.ft.com/16Fdqp6  via @FT    
    
    
    Bravo! RT @byosko: Just found out that Lean Analytics will be translated into Chinese, Korean, Polish, Spanish, Russian and Japanese!    
    
    
    I would add relevance, usefulness and some fun RT @ambelinaaa: Quality content + consistency = engaged community #cision    
    
    
    I go 90/10 RT @tobifairley: Interact/post correctly. Remember 80/20 rule: 80% of time post content relevant to your audience. #DesignerMBA    
    
    
    @ambelinaaa :-) Agree! #cision    
    
    
    C'est pas encourageant comme statistiques RT @duhamelp: Le modèle québécois: à bout de souffle… http://bit.ly/19kFPhD  via @Antagoniste_net    
    
    
    It had been a while. You can go wrong with a miso soup, edamame and shrimp with my son [pic]: http://4sq.com/19lFNaL     
    
    
    My last tweet should have said can't go wrong    
    
    
    startup Zero Bound helps graduates crowdfund their own student loan debt in exchange for community tasks http://www.thedailymuse.com/lifestyle/can-you-crowdfund-your-life/ …    
    
    
    @SJAbbott I hear it more and more. Sad!   When that happened, I didn't rate them. I refuse to be told what to give as a rating    
    
    
    Me too “@ErinBlaskie: @Steph_Montreuil you can do custom columns in Tweetdeck. I use it for Twitter all the time. #blogchat”    
    
    
    @ErinBlaskie I learned to like @hootsuite . I alternate between it and @TweetDeck    
    
    
    Look for disruption opps where big players exist. Best Advice I Ever Got: Matt Ehrlichman of @porchdotcom http://ow.ly/p7Cdp  #startup    
    
    
    Similar idea http://ow.ly/p7CZy  RT @psfk: Portable humidifier from @umbra_ltd perches on top of any water bottle: http://bit.ly/14feVtg     
    
    
    Like many, I am disappointed by the end of SHO_Dexter. Some argued that it was not predictable but I think it was. #tv #dexter    
    
    
    No matter how much you exercise you do, the only way to lose weight is to stop eating too much via @FastCoExist http://ow.ly/paJEZ     
    
    
    Part of my fall cleaning process, remove all the clothes that are now too small for my toddler from his closets and drawers #homeliving    
    
    
    Bon YulBiz! RT @michelleblanc: He oui, en route pour le Yulbiz Montréal au @LaikaMontreal http://facebook.com/events/1713107 … :-)    
    
    
    Now that I have a toddler, I can relate to that video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Aflrbwna44 … #fun    
    
    
    For the battle of the app meetup (at @TP1 w/ @fharper @nvanderv) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1baoQpj     
    
    
    You bet! I'm glad that he likes passing time with me RT @t_burrows: @KimVallee I love that clip...living it, even better!    
    
    
    Creativity in the age of the Maths Men – by Sir Martin Sorrell, CEO of WPP http://po.st/ZO3HyR  via @thedrum    
    
    
    When looking for investors or partners ditch traditional #business plan in favor of a pitch deck. Get more tips at http://ow.ly/pcLWo     
    
    
    Cela fait peur de savoir que des bêtes qui ont du mal à se mouvoir ou se déplacer arrivent à l'abattoir http://ow.ly/pcNj3  #sante    
    
    
    Design impacts our life and how your #business can compete. And I'm not talking only abt the pretty things. http://ow.ly/pd7KZ  #design    
    
    
    Pratique mais dommage que sera si long à déployer RT @pgmartin: Annonce d’un réseau mobile ds métro de MTL http://bit.ly/16J5AHP  #QCTechno    
    
    
    Better than most retailers RT @entmagazine: REI's "Rent Every Item" are over as a 1-year return policy begins. Good or bad? Vote at...    
    
    
    Why don't you? Best occasion to test the couch for a nap. RT @julien: I could literally fall asleep right here right now #breather    
    
    
    @mrf12t Moi aussi! C'était Denis Paul van Chestein @denispaulvc    
    
    
    @pgmartin J'imagine que collaborer entre des 4 grosses machines prend du temps. Trop de personnes sur le projet pour être efficace. :-)))    
    
    
    D'accord avec son affirmation que la nostalgie est trop présente RT @indexdesg: Entrevue avec KARIM RASHID  http://fb.me/3m3NCoU0h  #design    
    
    
    "How Google's Flexible Workspace Ignites Creative Collaboration (On Wheels)"  http://www.fastcompany.com/3017824/work-smart/how-googles-flexible-workspace-ignites-creative-collaboration-on-wheels …    
    
    
    Need a few books for my toddler in French. Sadly, I didn't find anything that suits me. I settled for a break instead http://4sq.com/16CRyqc     
    
    
    And notify that Android and iOS grew to have more in common than differences. What do u think? - http://pulse.me/s/qI7is     
    
    
    1st time I heard of it RT @TheEconomist: Could Formula E, a new all-electric grand prix, ever rival Formula 1? http://econ.st/173jasP ...    
    
    
    With a list of great dried alternatives RT @BlogHer: Don’t Like Barilla’s Anti-Gay Statements? http://ow.ly/pgQUJ  -Momo    
    
    
    @MelissaOnline Good morning! Any fun plans for the weekend?    
    
    
    It finishes the look. RT @atubanos: Wore lipstick today. Feel like a true lady. Inspired by @HelenAndrolia #FancyFriday    
    
    
    Focus on the relevant info RT @karonwarren: Your media kit doesn't have to be fancy for it to be effective! -- @JollyMom #typeacon    
    
    
    Forget the clouds that you currently see in the sky. It will be sunny all weekend. #montreal    
    
    
    @atubanos I prefer the feel of a lipstick to a gloss.    
    
    
    @jdunham This is normal since we always have it with us. #mobilephone    
    
    
    Learn abt the dynamics of modern #business from being a startup to handling growth “Breaking Bad” via @TheEconomist http://econ.st/190GVhT     
    
    
    <3 RT @atubanos: Ask and ye shall receive, mes amis! @HelenAndrolia #lipstick #fancyfriday @ DRAFTFCB Toronto http://instagram.com/p/exeBRsQ1yl/     
    
    
    My two-and-a-half-year-old toddler who will do his first fundraising walk this Monday. #learningyoung    
    
    
    @HelenAndrolia @atubanos It was a great suggestion. + Anastasia knows how to look at the camera ;-)    
    
    
    @atubanos @HelenAndrolia The digital camera is one of the best innovation. #wouldnotgoback    
    
    
    Follow-up series to the Glasscape bowl RT @PSFK: Nature-Inspired Design Creates Mini Terrariums In A Tumbler http://bit.ly/1fr62nB     
    
    
    It's sunny outside, quiet in the house, and I'm enjoying my morning coffee. Great way to start a slow day.    
    
    
    @MaximSaini You are welcome! Enjoy your weekend.    
    
    
    Working on the editorial schedule for my entrepreneurship and work-life balance blog. You can read Balancing Act at http://kimvallee.com/     
    
    
    Enjoying one of the last brunch on a terrace on the season. (@ Laïka - @laikamontreal w/ @jeromeparadis) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1bQksLy     
    
    
    Equipped our toddler for alpine ski (@ La Poubelle du Ski w/ @jeromeparadis) http://4sq.com/163G4Ar     
    
    
    Nice look! RT @tinalovespinot: Manicure Love #42 :) show time = shellack time! http://instagram.com/p/e0apAnMOhI/     
    
    
    My coffee delight http://instagram.com/p/e40EAMNH73/     
    
    
    