Hi back to you, @giselahausmann. Thx for the tweet and for browsing our site. What kind of ebook are you coming out with?    
    
    
    Hi @CurefoReading. Here's some place for you to start. Browse our collection of international & African books here http://www.worldreader.org/our-books/ .    
    
    
    Hi @twliterary. Thanks for thining of us. We would love to get your book. Ping @lizzywoood... she may be able to help sort out the #DCMA.    
    
    
    Thx @flynny1. @VassiliouEU - Would love to tell u more abt how we're transforming reading in the developing world. http://www.worldreader.org/     
    
    
    Congrats @giselahausmann! Keep us posted. Ping @lizzywood if you'd like to donate them to #booksforall.    
    
    
    Kakenya Ntaiya: A fearless girl who demanded school. http://ow.ly/iyLkb . Worth a watch on #IWD. #Empowerment via #education.    
    
    
    Great thanks, @VassiliouEU cc:ing @ColinMcElwee and @soozmoody. Let's try to schedule a call soon. What's the best way to reach you?    
    
    
    Welcome #booksforall fans! @CynthiaLive @yamiechess @alispagnola @colortheory @dcn_news @thebenlandis @ZulamaLearn @johnkin @jmpilz    
    
    
    Welcome new followers! @doklitfest @FHDN @nancygeer @AlisonMCaiola @Dixiemomx2 @liarsleague @mbaprojsearch @johnleedumas @IAMPHILLYCHASE    
    
    
    Hi new followers! @EstellaStar1 @hacettepecna @Rat_Skates @VE_Global    
    
    
    Don't they look happy w/ their new Kindles? New Dawn Educational Centre #Kenya pix: http://bit.ly/XDtQKS  pic.twitter.com/PJ2X6ZccEn    
    
    
    Thanks @brightonwriters for getting the word out! We're always on the lookout for #ebooks for kids & young adults.    
    
    
    Don't they look happy w/ their new Kindles? Here's a new pix from New Dawn Educational Centre #Kenya: pic.twitter.com/iMNKLPV4Qf    
    
    
    Thanks @SherillEwings for being our 4,000th follower! BOOKS FOR ALL! pic.twitter.com/8X1sl8MkN8    
    
    
    Welcome new #booksforall followers: 
@DebraBeck @imlostinbooks @markobrienwrite @S4KApps @geeksgalaxy @DidJaHearTheOne @mllemondegreen    
    
    
    Hi new followers: @couragedarling
@moderowo @Efiaula @MCAETorg @jmwachi @Oriol32torres @1STLADIESAFRICA
@LlucPalerm @davepea    
    
    
    And, what a nice photo it is @hi_from_abhi! Kids gathered around #reading on mobile phone. Images like that make our hearts melt. #ThankYou    
    
    
    Thx @Nanpolo for your kind words and for being a #booksforall fan. We're curious - how'd you hear about us?    
    
    
    What a great idea @onedegreesolar! Powering up for night classes! Feel free to email us at info@worldreader.org with other great ideas.    
    
    
    @DavinaCameron2 Which picture are you referring to? The New Dawn Educational Centre one? It's here: pic.twitter.com/ndzWH3MBls    
    
    
    Great! Thx, @Nanpolo! Happy 2 hear you're checking the site (http://worldreader.org ). Stay tuned. We'll have some fun, innovative news soon    
    
    
    Ja és oficial! @bookmovies ens ajudarà a portar #booksforall!! A la foto, @ColinMcElwee i Gabriel Pena. pic.twitter.com/AyI9txhp0y    
    
    
    It's official! @bookmovies is helping @worldreaders to bring #booksforall!! In the pic, @ColinMcElwee & Gabriel Pena. pic.twitter.com/D4hNHbRboK    
    
    
    Hi @Schools4Salone ... we'll see what we can do. @lizzywood, @ColinMcElwee- this may of interest to you.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the mention @g33kmate. @kachwanya - Here's what we're doing w/ #binu re: mobile reading: http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz . More news coming soon    
    
    
    Will Mobile Education Arrive in the Developing World? @PBSMediaShift http://to.pbs.org/WmHhxQ . Yes, it already has: http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz     
    
    
    Safe travels @Jazi_eu. We're very much looking forward to showing you our #booksforall programs.    
    
    
    Happy weekend. Take our poll, tell us your favorite #reading spot: http://www.facebook.com/worldreader .    
    
    
    .@Jazi_eu Keep us posted. We definitely want to hear your impressions.    
    
    
    Thanks for including us, @RedaLearning.    
    
    
    Great job @ty_pearl! You've read 5 books over the weekend on @worldreaders mobile. We're impressed. What will you read next?    
    
    
    Thx to all that came for our #socialenterprise happy hour in #sf. We'll be holding more in the coming months. PICS: http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10151280339616534.1073741825.329424311533&type=1 …    
    
    
    We're impressed "@Kiva has officially reached 1 MILLION borrowers with loans worldwide! http://blog.kiva.org/kivablog/2013/03/18/1-million-borrowers …." Huge impact. Congrats.    
    
    
    10,000 kids and families impacted in #Africa via ebooks. @EmWatson would be the perfect spokesperson for @worldreaders. Will you join us?    
    
    
    How does @medgestore, #booksforall and stickers on ereader cases inspire reading? Find out in our new blog http://shar.es/eZu0R .    
    
    
    Inspiring #QUOTE: ‎"I want to write books that unlock the traffic jam in everybody's head." -John Updike (American novelist & poet)    
    
    
    Hi @MBuffenoir. Are you referring to our e-reader or mobile readers?    
    
    
    A great @TheEconomist article about the energy, hope and buzz of "#Africa: A hopeful continent." http://econ.st/13uMzH8     
    
    
    FACT: Societies with educated children prosper. RT if you agree that #education can change the world. #booksforall pic.twitter.com/WttwTgh0mH    
    
    
    Happy Father's Day. We love this @pintrest photo: http://pinterest.com/pin/546765210980633103/ …. Will you spend time reading with your father today?    
    
    
    March is #NationalReadingMonth. What book are you reading today?    
    
    
    That's a great one, @chazmonster26. #Happy #reading!    
    
    
    another question for you @chazmonster26 - reading it on paper or digitally? just curious :-)    
    
    
    @chazmonster26 Cool, enjoy. Paper, digital -  just keep reading!    
    
    
    We love it @osarpong! See Okanta Kate's beautiful poetry writing here: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/changing-kids-lives-one-e-book-at-a-time-okanta-kates-story/ … BTW, she's our star student from #Ghana!    
    
    
    We can relate :-). It's ours, too. MT @chazmonster26 Reading is the love of my life.    
    
    
    $10B project near Accra #Ghana promises #ICT growth, university & hospital. We hope it helps spur #education, too. http://www.cnn.com/2013/03/20/tech/hope-city-ghana/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Thanks for including us, @barcampghana!    
    
    
    Thx for the heads up, @welovebold. Nice site. Thx for including us. Ping us if u have any follow-up questions or are looking for story ideas    
    
    
    Good one, @buddingreader. It's a pretty building, but more the Hope City #Ghana project seems to show what the country is moving towards    
    
    
    Happy #WorldPoetryDay! Celebrate all poets of this world including our very own student Okanta Kate. Please Retweet. pic.twitter.com/j2MCiJxPgf    
    
    
    We were so thrilled to learn that Monday was #Malala's first day back in school http://bbc.in/10nWoIJ  #inspiring #girlsmatter #bookforall    
    
    
    Poem by student Okanta Kate. "The Greatest Victory"-girls like Kate & #malala improve our world. #worldpoetryday pic.twitter.com/kjz8fzAKRP    
    
    
    Thinking you may like poem from Okanta Kate, @osarpong. Pls pass it along on #worldpoetryday pic.twitter.com/kjz8fzAKRP    
    
    
    Thanks for coming by @Jazi_eu. Glad you enjoyed the visit. Ping us if you have any questions.    
    
    
    "Things Fall Apart" author Chinua Achebe dies at 82 via @nytimes http://nyti.ms/Z7aDjI . #booksforall honors this great #African writer.    
    
    
    In memory of 'The Father of Modern African Writing', Chinua Achebe who passed away today at the age of 82. PIC: pic.twitter.com/7ZNDmLgnHz    
    
    
    Thank you new followers! @PraskiBookNews @shubbless @TAGAsia @lovliving @tix4cause @nolimitsforme @tesEnglish @Grant_Perry @UNESCO_Centre    
    
    
    Healthy, wealthy and wise girls infographic by @GPforEducation. Worth seeing. Educated Girls=Better Economies. https://www.educationforallblog.org/media/2013/03/3-8-2013-educating-girls-infographic.png …    
    
    
    Welcome new followers! @ElanaWinfrey @kbielecki_ @SeeMiracles @CALEntertainmnt @RichardJWood @ReadyForHillary @erichollreiser    
    
    
    Thx for asking, @parklandcommlib. Let's swap ideas via email comms [at] http://worldreader.org .  @soozmoody @NadjaBoz may have ideas.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the heads up @NosyCrow, & @BKGKristen, thx always for your shoutouts. #tocbologna ping us w/ ?s re: mobile reading & ebooks in Africa    
    
    
    Good point, @JulieFHedlund. Similar #ereader & #ebook need in Africa, a gap #booksforall is closing. http://worldeader.org  #tocbologna    
    
    
    Hi @princeboadu... No, we're not in #Kumasi... yet ;-). But we are in Accra and other parts of #Ghana. cc: @ColinMcElwee    
    
    
    Unfortunately we are not @iamgrowney @FableKids. Feel free to send us an email. Info at http://worldreader.org . Thx. @nancygeer    
    
    
    Absolutely. Would you mind sending us a note? Info at http://worldreader.org  or we can DM @princeboadu. When is the event?    
    
    
    Around the world in 80 books! Very cool list. Thanks @scholasticTeach for sharing. http://ow.ly/c99fe  #readeveryday #booksforall    
    
    
    Impressive! @taylorswift13 supports @scholastic #readeveryday campaign-spreads the message of the power of #literacy. http://www.scholastic.com/readeveryday/taylor-swift-live-webcast.htm …    
    
    
    Wonderful @princeboadu. And response sent. We're excited about the possiblity of #booksforall at #TEDxKNUST.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the support @ericrumsey. Stay tuned for more exciting news about Worldreader Mobile. http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ … @drew @africatechie    
    
    
    MT @usembassymanila: @StateDept & WR team up 2 provide English language learning content on mobile phones @binuMobile #TESOL2013 #mLearning    
    
    
    You are most welcome @EHsleeps. Small actions can do big things in this world. Keep up your effort raise awareness for #girleducation.    
    
    
    Sent to us by @Aalyel. Another beautiful quote by Chinua Achebe: "My weapon is literature." #inspiration    
    
    
    MUST READ by @sarahtierney: The $100bn mobile bullet train called Africa http://wp.me/p1BZSj-eL  "More ppl have cell phone than electricity."    
    
    
    Great article @sarahtierney! We provide #books 2 people in dev world via #kindles & mobile phones @binumobile. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz  (cont)    
    
    
    @sarahtierney 1/2 MILLION unique readers reading 20 MILLION PAGES a month on Worldreader Mobile-and we have more data. If interested, DM us.    
    
    
    Hi @MotherTongueSL! We're thrilled you are interested in supporting #booksforall. Could you send a note to publishing@worldreader.org? Thx.    
    
    
    And we're honored to be working with you, too @GreyGeckoPress. Serving the #worldcommunity and bringing #bookstoall = #goodmatch    
    
    
    hi @buddingreader.. thanks for the heads up. we'll check out @Benetech and keep @lizzywood @binu in the loop.    
    
    
    Hi @ulbrichalmazan. Thx for including us. Indie publishers certainly can get involved. Here's how http://ow.ly/jtiUA     
    
    
    THANKS @MayiNgwala & Genet Press for being part of the #booksforall community & donating your book to our kids! More: http://ow.ly/jtjCg     
    
    
    Worldreader supports #marriageequality. RETWEET if you do too! @HRC pic.twitter.com/t5HXyPWMeI    
    
    
    Thank you @sarahtierney! We truly appreciate it. Do you use a feature or android phone? We'll send a note in a few weeks with our updates.    
    
    
    Thanks @ulbrichalmazan. We read your piece. We're interested in all #books: indie, children's titles, romance, fiction, text books (cont.)    
    
    
    If you are interested in donating @ulbrichalmazan, please contact @lizzywood or email our publishing team-(publishing@worldreader.org). Thx.    
    
    
    .@JulieOwono, @Angeles_Jurado great @el_pais interview. You may like, too: 1/2M phone users reading 20M pages/month on Worldreader Mobile...    
    
    
    .@JulieOwono @Angeles_Jurado Would love to tell you more abt our ereader & phone reading programs being used in #Africa. Can we DM you?    
    
    
    Can you send is samples to read through? Are they in digital form already? @ulbrichalmazan @lizzywood @DanieZacarias    
    
    
    @ai1_electronics We'll DM you some tips for interactive content. Thx!    
    
    
    From Slums to Superstars. New blog: http://shar.es/d2ItK  #inspiration and #girlpower in #Kenya    
    
    
    Big reader @Berusphillip. We're impressed that you are reading so much on Worldreader Mobile via @biNuMobile. What's your favorite book?    
    
    
    NEW LAUNCH: 130 girls in #slums of Kenya now have access to over 10,000 e-books they need and love to read. Details: http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    In @nairobi_kenya this week at the next EdTech MeetUp: feature on Worldreader. To join visit: http://dlvr.it/37xzrD . #Africa #innovation.    
    
    
    Hey @nuttyxander! Can you tell us where we can find this quote? :) Thanks so much and #booksforall.    
    
    
    How do we measure our success? By monitoring & evaluating our programs aka #research. Visit this page to learn more: http://www.worldreader.org/learnings/     
    
    
    FUN FACT: William Shakespeare invented the word hurry. U can read his classics using your cell on Worldreader Mobile: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ …    
    
    
    Literacy Rates of the World. See how your country fairs: http://world.bymap.org/LiteracyRates.html …. RT if u think access 2 books can increase literacy rates.    
    
    
    .@AllenAndUnwin! We provide ebooks 2 children/families in dev world using #kindles & mobiles. Might u be interested in donating content?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Hans Christian Andersen. We love that it's also International Children's Book Day. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hans_Christian_Andersen …    
    
    
    Cool #infographic shared by @cultureslurp: The World As 100 People: 17 cannot read or write. LINK: http://visual.ly/world-100-people … #literacy    
    
    
    Our commitment to transparency has garnered the approval of @GuideStarUSA. For our full profile visit: http://www.worldreader.org/worldreader-guidestar/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @thereason_ezu! We're glad you like the new look on Worldreader Mobile. More updates to come soon. What book are you reading now?    
    
    
    We'll be watching @gatesfoundation @TEDxChange talking about girls & women as catalysts of change. Starts 6 pm PST. http://gates.ly/YuDCiJ     
    
    
    .@gatesfoundation. 130 girls in Kenyan #slums now have a chance for a better future with access to 10,000 e-books. http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    130 #girlrising in slums of Kibera, Kenya via access to 10,000 e-books. #inspiring story you will love @10x10act: http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    'Words resonate, they can transform. Believing in people creates possibilities'. Halima Hima at #TEDxChange    
    
    
    By @BBC: Mobile phone celebrates 40th birthday-http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-22013228 …. We'll be showing our appreciation next week with some exciting news.    
    
    
    New book for all you mobile phone readers on Worldreader Mobile: "No Straight Lines". Thank you @alansmlxl 4 making #booksforall a reality.    
    
    
    Alan Moore's "No Straight Lines" now available for #reading on Worldreader Mobile: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ …. Big thanks to @alansmlxl.    
    
    
    FACT: According to @UNESCO 31 MILLION children in sub-Sahran Africa are out of school. READ the presentation here: http://bit.ly/YVv8AU .    
    
    
    Great job on finishing #atomstoMolecules on Worldreader Mobile @DrewHacjre. Did you learn something new? @biNuMobile    
    
    
    "Study after study shows that the earlier a child begins learning, the better he/she does down the road"-ow.ly/jHuBo via @NYTimes    
    
    
    Thanks for following us @seymoursimon! Would you be interested in donating some of your wonderful books to our program? #booksforall    
    
    
    Thank you @SuzanneDiBianca for following us! Just curious, how did you hear about #booksforall http://www.worldreader.org ?    
    
    
    Thx very much @HilaMehr! We're thrilled to be included in this excellent report on EDUTECH in #India. We'll share it! http://onbuff.ly/16r1xQ5     
    
    
    EDTECH India report on #Worldreader: A few co. working in devworld w/ potential 4 real impact on learning outcomes. http://onbuff.ly/16r1xQ5     
    
    
    We agree @buddingreader. We're impressed with your work and the work of @FirstLangBooks @ReadingHamlets @WorldLiteracy. Any ideas in mind?    
    
    
    We employ Early Grade Reading Assessment tool 2 improve student #reading & teaching programs. Learn more on our BLOG: http://bit.ly/17h0J3y     
    
    
    Thanks @ExcelAfrica for sharing our recent story on how we monitor & evaluate our programs! #booksforall http://shar.es/di66f     
    
    
    Can you name 10 countries in Asia? 
Ummi can! This 10 year old girl loves the World Atlas. So cool! RT if you agree. pic.twitter.com/8wA27KswFq    
    
    
    Can you name 10 countries in Asia? 
Ummi can! This 10 year old girl loves the World Atlas. So cool! RT if you agree. pic.twitter.com/DESRIYByBW    
    
    
    Correct @CamiloDeza. Ummi named 10 countries in Asia & moved on to learning about DR of CONGO on her #kindle. ;) Isn't she adorable?    
    
    
    @seymoursimon Thx. Liz, let us know how to best reach you. Our @lizzywood @DanieZacarias can explain more about #booksforall. @StarWalkKids    
    
    
    Our condolences to the family of Anne Smedinghoff, killed in Afghanistan while delivering books to students. #NotFair http://bit.ly/10LCX9k     
    
    
    BIG NEWS: We've launched Worldreader Mobile, an app that allows millions to read books on a cell phone. Details here http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    FACT: 500,000 children & adults read 17,000 books via Worldreader Mobile on feature phones. A true #readingrevolution http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Thank you @HargeisaLibrary. We're excited about the possiblity of bringing #booksforall to Somalia.    
    
    
    Let us know if u have more Qs @NVKYN. Cell penetration in #Africa=about 60%. 1/2 million are already reading on app. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    We're on 5 million phones in the developing world & 0.5 MILLION are actively reading. Get all the facts here: http://on.fb.me/ZkFfv0 .    
    
    
    Have you heard? We've extended #booksforall w/ partner @biNuMobile via mobile phones. 0.5 MILLION readers/month. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Thanks @laurahazardowen! RT @paidContent: "Worldreader counts 500,000 users of its e-reading app on feature phones http://dlvr.it/3CKqVN "    
    
    
    FACT: 70% of active readers on Worldreader Mobile are females, reading over 17 books a month. #girlrising #girlpower http://ow.ly/jU0RH     
    
    
    We love this by @Maddybeckmann: "Today a reader, tomorrow a leader!" #literacy #edtech #quoteoftheday    
    
    
    Watch our VIDEO on how mobile phones & books will improve #literacy in the developing world. http://ow.ly/jU1Fg     
    
    
    FACT:Teachers, caregivers, older siblings, parents use Worldreader Mobile. 88% would use it as learning tool w/ kids. http://ow.ly/jU2uU     
    
    
    And what's really cool @julietrell @10x10act is that 70% of our active readers are females! Check out this VIDEO: http://bit.ly/ZgT3rr .    
    
    
    See photos of @curiouslee reading e-books on our mobile phone book application: http://j.mp/YbZ20m . Way cool!    
    
    
    Nice poem @TheArchcardinal! Do you have more? More poetry is available on Worldreader Mobile book app via @biNuMobile.    
    
    
    Support @unitetolight #fundraiser for solar chargers so people in developing countries can charge their e-readers. http://goo.gl/gwbZr     
    
    
    :) Let us know if you are interested showcasing some of your poetry on Worldreader Mobile @TheArchcardinal.    
    
    
    @melindagates Tech in developing world means #booksforall. Our cell phone book app has 0.5 MILLION active readers. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Worldreader Mobile on @Forbes @gigaom @VentureBeat @CNNMoney & more. Visit our press page 4 all the latest articles. http://bit.ly/LBFxI7     
    
    
    Have you seen our VIDEO about our new platform for expanding #booksforall? Learn about Worldreader Mobile here: http://ow.ly/jU1Fg .    
    
    
    We've got news to share w/ @BON_EDUCATION-0.5 MILLION people reading on mobile phones via Worldreader Mobile. New #booksforall platform-cont    
    
    
    More details on our announcement here: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q . Let us know if you have Q's or DM us. Thx @BON_EDUCATION.    
    
    
    FACT: In January, Worldreader Mobile users read the equivalent of 17,000 books on their feature phones. Details: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    Our twitter community has grown in the last few days. We just want to say thanks to all our new members.#booksforall pic.twitter.com/ETLYPHifIv    
    
    
    Can you name this author? And his real name too? Something fun. Something quick on #friday. Hit reply w/ your answers pic.twitter.com/z5Q5V1bnnY    
    
    
    @GdnDevelopment 500,000 in the developing world are actively reading on their mobile phone. Tech+Books=Improved Lives http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Bingo @HallidayMiller! Great job. We'd love to send you a Worldreader t-shirt. Can you DM us to get your details? #booksforall    
    
    
    An estimated 250 million children are not able to read or write. Via @WBeducation http://twitpic.com/cii8nz  #educationfirst #booksforall    
    
    
    Have an android phone? Access free books via Worldreader Mobile on Google Play. http://bit.ly/1236cbN     
    
    
    Hi @Techzim. 180,000 people in #Africa are reading books on their mobile phone. More info here: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q  @biNuMobile    
    
    
    Thx @CSMonitor 4 visiting our site & writing this: "Worldreader, a nonprofit, brings e-books to developing countries" http://bit.ly/ZlN7gT     
    
    
    Last week we launched Worldreader Mobile w/ @biNuMobile, an app that allows millions to read books on a mobile phone. http://youtu.be/KTGD1FluEcg     
    
    
    Our thoughts are with the city of #Boston today.    
    
    
    Hi @BrettWSimpson. That revolution is happening via #kindles & #mobilephones. 500,000 ppl reading on WR Mobile. Visit http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/     
    
    
    Hi @johntraxler. We read your piece on mobile learning in Africa. Thought you might be interested in this: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    mLearning is happening in Africa @AfricanBrains. 500,000 people are reading on mobile phones. See http://bit.ly/XBkH7q . @biNuMobile    
    
    
    We say yes @WISE_Tweets: "Can mobile technologies extend the reach of #education in #Africa? http://bit.ly/LbJoP8 "    
    
    
    Infographic: What Will It Take to Achieve Learning For All? http://www.worldbank.org/en/news/feature/2013/04/15/what-will-it-take-to-achieve-learning-for-all …    
    
    
    Look what would happen if all students in low-income countries acquired basic reading skills. Infographic: http://ow.ly/k9tdI  @WorldBank    
    
    
    MT ‏@WBPubs 61M children are not in school; 32M are girls. Development leaders discuss putting #educationfirst, 4/18: http://ow.ly/k99gj     
    
    
    Just published @mashable: Mobile Phones Deliver Millions of E-Books to Developing World http://on.mash.to/YVgFGJ  w/ @binumobile by @zoebfox.    
    
    
    Team @mashable @mashablemobile @zoebfox @petecashmore, thx for focusing on the #readingrevolution in the dev. world. http://on.mash.to/Zyj0mq     
    
    
    .@ThinkAfrica - To your point "digital innovators using smartphone apps are earning global attn." U may like this: http://ow.ly/kbICO     
    
    
    Hi @lincolnavy. Did you enjoy #CanLoveHappenTwice on @Worldreaders Mobile  @biNuMobile app? What will you read next?    
    
    
    Hi @AmankonaHinne - What did you like most about the book #FacetoFace? Which books will you read next? #booksforall #biNu    
    
    
    Next-generation ebooks introduced at London Book Fair http://gu.com/p/3f7fc/tw  via @guardian #Reading #Fun    
    
    
    For millions in developing world, feature phones updates can be an #education game changer ~ @mashable http://on.mash.to/YVgFGJ  #empower    
    
    
    Hi @SalhaKaitesi Thx for including us! #FridayLove to you :-)    
    
    
    FRIDAY Read: The 40 coolest characters in literature http://shortlist.com/entertainment/the-40-coolest-characters-in-literature … via @ShortList.    
    
    
    171 million ppl could be out of poverty if students acquired basic reading skills. Via @WorldBank @HuffPostImpact http://huff.to/17rr5wM     
    
    
    Thx @ChelseaClinton for spreading the message about WR Mobile and the #readingrevolution in the developing world. http://on.mash.to/YVgFGL     
    
    
    Happy #WorldBookDay everyone! Take our Book DNA quiz & win 1 of 5 Kindles loaded with our best African books. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Wondering what book you belong in? Take our Book DNA quiz to find out & you might win a Kindle! #WorldBookDay http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Happy World Book Day @GPforEducation! Thx for featuring #booksforall. Join the celebration & take our Book DNA quiz. 
http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    MT @colinmcelwee: World Book Day and the Power of Choice and Technology @worldreaders http://tinyurl.com/cb2afvu  Thanks to @GPforEducation    
    
    
    "World Book Day and the Power of Choice and Technology" @ColinMcElwee via @GPforEducation. Books change everything! http://ow.ly/kjwbm     
    
    
    Thx @SMWBarcelona for celebrating #WorldBookDay with us. Have u taken our Book DNA Quiz? What book do you belong in? http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Celebrate #WorldBookDay. Take this quiz & you may win a Kindle, like the one our kids have. Please RT. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Happy #WorldBookDay! Celebrate #booklove by taking this quiz. You could win a Kindle loaded with African books! http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Let's have some fun on #WorldBookDay! Take our Book DNA Quiz & discover your book match. Maybe win a Kindle, too. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Moto to live by: "Enjoy life's simple pleasures." Happiness is key. Thanks @CocaColaCo for following us. #booksforall    
    
    
    Thx @MoorthyBBM for the tweet & passing the link to @CocaColaCo. You may also like this post by @ColinMcElwee http://ow.ly/knBrj     
    
    
    Hi @smallbutfeisty... Not sure what happened, but this link should take you to the quiz: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . Let us know if it works.    
    
    
    @kenkenhimself awww... just between us, u could belong in Gone with the Wind instead. Sounds like u have a romantic side :-) cc: @soozmoody    
    
    
    Ever wondered what book you belong in? Take this quiz & you may win a Kindle, like the one our kids have. Please RT. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Thanks @asenkut! For more information you can also visit our website. http://www.worldreader.org  #booksforall    
    
    
    Calling all book lovers - Pls help #booksforall grow. Take a 30-sec quiz & share this link http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . #booklove to you. Thx!    
    
    
    Hi @moCZARella_ @smallbutfeisty. Sorry to hear this.Are you using a mobile phone? Try w/ a computer & use this link: https://apps.facebook.com/easypromos-premium/promotions/13997 …    
    
    
    Excited for our interview with GoodCauseTV today. The interview with @tweetpete & @soozmoody will be posted here: http://goodcausetv.tumblr.com .    
    
    
    Hi @moCZARella_  were you able to take the quiz when you got home? Fingers crossed that it worked. Thx for your dedication and support.    
    
    
    Hi @Believe_Bateyes. Thx for the tweet. Here's info abt partnering w/ #booksforall http://ow.ly/kpEFs . Good luck w/ the Esperanza prgm.    
    
    
    "The dearest ones of time, the strongest friends of the soul – BOOKS." ~ Emily Dickinson #foodforthought #booklove    
    
    
    30 seconds of #bookfun happening here: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . You could be the lucky winner of a Kindle loaded with #African ebooks!    
    
    
    Fun @moCZARella_ Happy to hear that our book quiz is working! So you are just like Hermione from Harry Potter. Kind, smart, fun!    
    
    
    @slim_alger in what book do you belong?    
    
    
    @anitakapten what book are you?    
    
    
    @AlonEchelon in what book do you belong?    
    
    
    Thank you new followers: @cloeimg @LaneDebra @IAm_BMA @AfricanDreamOrg @americadiaspor @AlexFoundation1 @chintan2425 @RegimeRecords    
    
    
    Hi @Believe_Bateyes. Info on how to launch an e-reader program in your school is here: http://bit.ly/KNQ16n . Let us know if you have Qs.    
    
    
    Wow! 6.8M new teachers needed globally to get every child in school by 2015. INFOGRAPHIC: http://tinyurl.com/bkttoo6  via @GPforEducation    
    
    
    Thank you for your support, @NatFairFax! What kind of book have you written? We're always looking 4 stories to share with kids in our prgm.    
    
    
    .@JayOdeo yes, 1400 ebooks on the #biNu #WorldreaderMobile phone app. So now your phone nows works as a portable library! Happy reading!    
    
    
    Looking for some #FridayFun? Here you go! Take the Book DNA quiz here  http://on.fb.me/10vQubD  & enter our Kindle giveaway sweepstakes.    
    
    
    Inspiring pics via @GPforEducation's Reading Changed My Life e-album http://ow.ly/ksbMf . Fav: 101-yr-old Maria learns to read & write    
    
    
    Nice article @ApolloJoab: http://bit.ly/11TSSqh . Kindles are impacting #education in Kenya via 25 schools/libraries. Interested? DM us.    
    
    
    Look who's making headlines...@soozmoody! She's swimming 22K for #booksforall & is in @Diario_SPORT today: http://ow.ly/kwIQN  cc @Swim4G    
    
    
    Really, you could win a Kindle loaded w/ #African ebooks! No clear winner yet & 2 days left to take our quiz: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Watch live now as GoodCauseTV's @tweetpete interviews @soozmoody, http://www.spreecast.com/events/goodcausetv-interviews-worldreaderorg--3 …    
    
    
    We loved talking to goodcausetv today. Watch the entire interview between @tweetpete & @soozmoody here: http://sprc.st/g0JqN . @IndyWorld    
    
    
    Thanks for taking our Book DNA quiz @AmethystToeShoe. In what book do you belong? :)    
    
    
    Great @kenkenhimself! Get your friends to participate in the Quiz too and your chances of winning go up. The playing field is wide open!    
    
    
    We sure do @carlhinrichsen! @unitetolight is one of our great partners. Great project, great idea, great organization.    
    
    
    One of Brazil's biggest newspapers @JornalOGlobo covers our efforts to improve global literacy: http://glo.bo/145pv7H . #booksforall    
    
    
    Hurry! Last chance to win a Kindle! Our Book DNA Quiz ends today. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Engagement is the rocket fuel that decodes words & is the foundation of what we call literacy ~ @ColinMcElwee Blog: http://shar.es/lpLrY     
    
    
    Hey @kurtgrela. Here's a link to @Forbes piece on Worldreader Mobile. 1/2 MILLION readers a month. http://onforb.es/10OxIaC . #booksforall    
    
    
    Not yet but we're working on it @Marvin_Mathew! Stay tuned. @ConnectStateGov @StateDept @Raspberry_Pi. http://www.worldreader.org .    
    
    
    #AmericanEnglish learning content now available via Worldreader Mobile thx to @StateDept @biNuMobile. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz . #booksforall    
    
    
    MT @soozmoody: Woot! We just broke $53,000 for our fundraising effort 4 @Worldreaders. Pls help us get to $100,000 http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    The winners of our Book DNA Quiz are: http://bit.ly/18eFcJl . For everyone that participated, thx for helping us fight global illiteracy.    
    
    
    Way cool! @GuideStarUSA is using one of our #booksforall photos to show #nonprofitluv. http://guidestar.org/  http://www.worldreader.org .    
    
    
    Most welcome @SALVEint! Where in Uganda are you located? We have some project there too. #dogoodtogether #greatnonprofits    
    
    
    MT @mobile_movement How many of you use your mobile phones to read? 2G networks connect ppl to <1000 ebooks for free: http://ow.ly/kDkub     
    
    
    Hugely humbled by this great piece from @Jazi_eu about their visit to our #ghana office & kindle projects. http://bit.ly/131IyMi . Thanks!    
    
    
    More reading in #Africa: #booksforall comes to Kenyan HIV/AIDS Orphans http://shar.es/lhsQE .    
    
    
    #Booksforall hellos 2 Suzy Peacock Memorial Secondary School & Christian Relief Fund. #FridayLove 4 the work they do http://shar.es/lhv7b     
    
    
    FRIDAY #quote: 'The direction in which #education starts a man will determine his future in life', by Plato. pic.twitter.com/SSsQhqBox2    
    
    
    New #Kindle project in Tanzania & we'll be at the World Economic Forum in SA. Stay close to our co-founders @davidrisherWR & @ColinMcElwee.    
    
    
    Proud to be working with the Nelson Mandela Institue on our upcoming Tanzania e-reader launch. @EcoLabArusha http://arushalivinglab.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    Have you heard? The Prime Minister & the Minister of Education of Tanzania will be attending our next #kindle launch. #bookforall going big.    
    
    
    We're in schools in Kenya, Tanzania and Zimbabwe this week launching new projects and visiting current ones. Stay close for the details.    
    
    
    Our new project in Tanzania is managed w/ help of masters & PHD students from Nelson Mandela Institute. #ICTStudy http://arushalivinglab.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    We're thrilled to be one of the winners of this year's Innovations in Reading Prizes by @nationalbook. http://bit.ly/aU91Te     
    
    
    Thanks @POETSorg! We're honored to be winners with @CityNational @LtlFreeLibrary @findtheuni @UpriseBooks. #readingrevolution    
    
    
    MUST READ on @GSMAm4d: An Opportunity for Mobile Operators to Promote Literacy & Improve Bottom Lines by @lizzywood. http://ow.ly/kMesv     
    
    
    V. Cool! Etisalat partners with @biNuMobile  to give subscribers 10 times faster browsing experience in #Nigeria. http://www.360nobs.com/2013/05/etisalat-partners-with-binu-to-give-subscribers-10-times-faster-browsing-experience/comment-page-1/ …    
    
    
    The Leaders of Tomorrow! Nambala & Nganana Primary students in Tanzania getting ready for the e-reader launch. PHOTO: http://twitter.com/worldreaders/status/332566897155518465/photo/1pic.twitter.com/EIRO85tTkh     
    
    
    Leaders of Tomorrow! Nambala & Nganana Primary students in Tanzania getting ready for the e-reader launch. PHOTO: pic.twitter.com/29KOV629hZ    
    
    
    Key report on Africa progress launched by Kofi Annan, @CarolineKende. Available on WR Mobile worldwide. Congrats! pic.twitter.com/IaQBlv0FS6.    
    
    
    Thats right @ColinMcElwee! We're moving south in our effort to make #booksforall a reality. How was your meeting with Pravim Gordham?    
    
    
    Something BIG just happened on Friday! E-reader launch in Tanzania. See the pictures here: http://on.fb.me/10l7YV6     
    
    
    The Prime Minister of Tanzania backs recent e-reader launch in Arusha & endorses more projects to come! @dailynewstz http://bit.ly/12tbdZD     
    
    
    Our very own @DanieZacarias was on the radio in Zimbabwe talking about Worldreader Mobile & our e-reader projects. http://fb.me/QY40rTfU     
    
    
    Thanks for the article about our book app - Worldreader Mobile @Luludotcom! We truly appreciate it. #ReadingRevolution is happening!    
    
    
    MT @i_am_TRANCE95: "@DanieZacarias I must tell you that I've gained alot from #WorldReader #App on #biNu. Keep it up!" Thx!    
    
    
    Tanzania's PM on the value of #booksforall program launched w/ Nelson Mandela Institute: http://dailynews.co.tz/index.php/local-news/17349-pm-unveils-pioneer-e-book-library … via @dailynewstz    
    
    
    Kofi Annan: Unprecedented opportunity to use #Africa's vast resource wealth & lift millions out of poverty http://nyti.ms/10tYrZ0     
    
    
    .@SALVEint 1st ebook read by kids @ #Tanzania launch: Kanuki, story abt a giraffe w/ a short neck, in Kiswahili http://ow.ly/kYANT     
    
    
    Mobile operators in emerging economies in a unique position to promote #education #literacy. @lizzywood explains http://ow.ly/kYCJh  #ICT    
    
    
    *The real opportunity in 
Africa is the youth.*~ Arif M. Naqvi, co-chair, World Economic 
Forum on Africa http://bit.ly/128s0kf  #wefafrica    
    
    
    MT @VUSaskia Worldreader brengt via gsm-applicatie meer dan 1000 boeken naar Derde wereld. Via @datanews_nl http://ow.ly/l0TxW     
    
    
    Reading on Worldreader Mobile via #binu app? Check out the Africa Progress Report, recently launched by Kofi Annan.  #wefafrica    
    
    
    The Girl Who Will Teach Tanzania to Read http://shar.es/Z3NBy . #inspiration in #Africa!    
    
    
    Merci beaucoup, @morganetual. Ping us if you have any additional questions or continue to write about digital reading trends in Africa.    
    
    
    .@TechnoMagZw - Thx for the tweets.  Worldreader's @NadjaBoz & @RothwellSmith are the King George launch, if you have questions.    
    
    
    Thx for the post, @WebTrendsNG. We'll update you when we have more news to share about #booksforall in Nigeria!    
    
    
    Congrats #booksforall partner @pubslush on the @aliberlinski debut book! http://amzn.to/10mrFMn     
    
    
    Should students be given laptops or e-readers in Kenya? http://www.businessdailyafrica.com/Should-students-be-given-laptops-or-e-readers/-/1248928/1853674/-/5tj65b/-/index.html … via @BD_Africa    
    
    
    Big #Booksforall thank you to @nationalbook for selecting us for the #InnovationInReading. We're honored & humbled. http://bit.ly/10B8xX5     
    
    
    Congratulations to fellow @nationalbook award winners: @CityNational @LtlFreeLibrary @findtheuni @UpriseBooks. #innovation #reading    
    
    
    SNEAK PEEK: We launched our first ever #Kindle program in Zimbabwe yesterday at a very special school. More to come. pic.twitter.com/6CdnFVPkPa    
    
    
    Kids on Zimbabwe’s fringe love ebooks, too http://shar.es/ZvHPo...Yes , we just launched in Zimbabwe! #booksforall    
    
    
    Low reading culture threatens country’s literacy rate ~ Zimbabwe Minister of Ed. http://j.mp/10y0HBz  via @ChronicleZim    
    
    
    Thank you kindly @pubslush. Right back at you #FF    
    
    
    Thank you @judyannetM. We intend to ...one school at a time!    
    
    
    How's this for cool: #booksforall in Ghana, Kenya, Uganda, Tanzania, Rwanda & as of this week...Zimbabwe, too http://j.mp/10xykn9 .    
    
    
    Love it! MT @GSMA_mEducation Literacy through Mobile Phones in #Afghanistan http://ow.ly/l7KgG  #mLearning #edchat #edtech #ict4e #ict4d    
    
    
    Ahmad Shafi talks abt literacy via mobile phones http://ow.ly/l7KgG . This may help, too #booksforall #binu app http://j.mp/10D2rFq .    
    
    
    NEW POST: Going Public-On working with Governments to Achieve Scale by co-founder @davidrisherWR http://bit.ly/11STZcT .    
    
    
    Worldreader Kit: out-of-box, easy-to-launch reading program designed to have an immediate impact & improve literacy. http://bit.ly/11STZcT     
    
    
    Why working with governments & private sector is key to #booksforall. A must read by co-founder @davidrisherWR. http://bit.ly/11STZcT     
    
    
    Looking for your next read? Check out WR partner @pubslush first book Beautiful Mess by @aliberlinski http://amzn.to/10mrFMn .    
    
    
    Ready, Set...Pull out that pocket of change. Coins for #booksforall starts June 1! http://shar.es/ZkbkP . Please RT!    
    
    
    Hi @pjhay12. See that you're reading a lot on the @worldreaders @biNuMobile app. Way to go! Which book do you like the most?    
    
    
    @Mbwana it was very nice to meet you today! We learned so much from you about the Africa Tech landscape. Come see us soon!    
    
    
    @ciie_boston Thank you, we're so happy to be in Zimbabwe!    
    
    
    Coins for Books. Support #booksforall by donating your change via a @coinstar kiosk thx to @cmcfund starting June 1. http://shar.es/ZkbkP     
    
    
    BIG NEWS: @FCBarcelona Midfielder Alex Song joins #booksforall to fight illiteracy worldwide. Details here: http://bit.ly/18ul84H .    
    
    
    He's got 27 siblings, is a midfielder @FCBarcelona, believes #reading improves the world & is now our ambassador-Who? http://bit.ly/18ul84H     
    
    
    MUST WATCH: Behind scenes w/ @songalexandre @SkySports. @FCBarcelona midfielder wants to give back via #booksforall. http://bit.ly/16kFvnz     
    
    
    Have you heard @kenyanpundit? We've digitized 500 Kenyan books & have deployed e-readers in 25 schools in Kenya. More-http://bit.ly/17zSmlc     
    
    
    Thx @umutonidarla for the mention. U may also like this: 500 Kenyan books digitized, e-readers in 25 Kenyan schools: http://bit.ly/13WU7pq     
    
    
    @NathanDetroitEd Thx for reaching out. You'll find more info at http://www.worldreader.org , or eml us your questions at info@worldreader.org.    
    
    
    Thanks @FaturotiK for spreading the word about the #booksforall app. You'll also find other science books there, too. cc: @biNuMobile    
    
    
    Getting close to 5,000 followers! Please RT & help us cross this big milestone. #booksforall love to you all. THANK YOU!    
    
    
    Nice job @AtomAdeyemi! You finished another book on Worldreader Mobile via @biNuMobile. How many have you read on your mobile phone?    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow back @GCE_US! We admire your mission to provide quality education for all children.    
    
    
    Thx @OurVillageIs for this: 'Like' #worldreader on Facebook http://on.fb.me/TPUTLO  Worldreader gets eBooks to children in developing nations    
    
    
    Senator @DavidColtart, Minister of Education in #Zimbabwe, on our recent e-reader launch. http://davidcoltart.com/?p=5837 . #Booksforall is growing!    
    
    
    In June, donate your coins & change lives. Thx to @cmcfund via @coinstar kiosks you can help us send books to Africa http://shar.es/ZkbkP .    
    
    
    A beautiful #quote to make your Wednesday even better. pic.twitter.com/LL6q501RfD    
    
    
    Thank you @Hesperian! Happy 40th Anniversary to #wherethereisnodoctor. #booksforall excited abt our partnership! #lookingahead    
    
    
    You're going to love this: Hesperian's Where There Is No Doctor now free for kids & families. #booksforall http://shar.es/wbRTC .    
    
    
    Cool! @LUISENRIQUE21 supports @Swim4G effort to swim across straight of Gibralter for #bookforall. PIC: pic.twitter.com/w6oUhFEhBv.    
    
    
    Ready, Set...Pull out that pocket of change. Coins for #booksforall via @coinstar machines starts today! http://j.mp/17IQx6C     
    
    
    Team @Swim4G is 3/4 of way to raising $100K for #bookforall by swimming from Europe to Africa. We're so impressed! http://bit.ly/X8ccg4     
    
    
    Got change? Want to help kids fall in love with reading? Donate to Worldreader via @coinstar machines Today. http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    A #booksforall Kit: A promise of reading packed up in a box! But…What’s a Kit? And, how can partners get them? http://shar.es/wcEWQ     
    
    
    Thx for the tip, @carlawellington. cc: @lizzywood on this. Elizabeth have you of http://monkeytailsbooks.com ?    
    
    
    *Got a little change in my pocket going jingle lingle ling*...Well, then, head to a @coinstar machine & do this http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    .@mwebafrica! We provide #bookforall via ereaders & mobile phones. Our book app has 1/2 MILLION active readers. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz     
    
    
    Muchas gracias @conchibadillo por apoyar a @Swim4G y a #bookforall.    
    
    
    Muchas gracias Mireia por vuestro apoyo! @miss_belmont @Swim4G    
    
    
    During the entire month of June you can donate your change to Worldreader via a @coinstar kiosk near u. Details here: http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    Wondering how to bring an e-reader program to your school? It's called Worldreader Kits. Read about it here -->http://bit.ly/186DcoT     
    
    
    We are 5,000 times thankful to have all of you as our followers. THANK YOU! pic.twitter.com/CP1lCjz51V    
    
    
    Got change? Follow Erica's lead. Take your coins to a Coinstar machine and help kids fall in love with reading. pic.twitter.com/pEaF20QmdQ    
    
    
    We're looking for an Education Specialist in #Ghana! Want to apply or know someone that would interested? Details: http://bit.ly/15R76sf     
    
    
    SUPER DATA by @GSMAm4d: Between 2011 and 2012 over 400 million #mobile connections were made in the developing world. http://ow.ly/lJ6Ir     
    
    
    "Why I am investing my time in education." A woman in Tanzania rallies her community for schools. http://bit.ly/1693Jxv  @TheCitizenTZ    
    
    
    Thank you @RafaelNadal for supporting @Swim4G & Worldreader. Your support will help provide even more books to kids in Africa! #inspiration    
    
    
    Look @usainbolt-@RafaelNadal is supporting @Swim4G & helping kids in Africa fall in love with reading. Will you join? pic.twitter.com/wimSNUc75i    
    
    
    Superstar @RafaelNadal supports @Swim4G so that kids in Africa get books they need! @Shakira will you join Rafa? pic.twitter.com/wimSNUc75i    
    
    
    #booksforall now in South Africa & Malawi! The reading revolution is spreading fast. http://j.mp/1bwhMxK     
    
    
    If you have any #booksforall questions, find @blaqhaq at #LibraryBox @PirateBoxCamp in #Berlin or ping us here.    
    
    
    Spread #booklove. Donate spare change to #booksforall via @cmcfund. Super easy: http://j.mp/17IQx6C . Please retweet.    
    
    
    Come #volunteer in #Ghana with us and help make a difference in many children's lives. http://on.fb.me/PItCLb . pic.twitter.com/YzK0BcbtIV    
    
    
    @drmarobi Hi Dr. Mary. You can find more info here about our Volunteer Reading Program. http://bit.ly/11KkVIL  Thanks for your interest!    
    
    
    Win a volunteer vacation with us this summer thanks to @Opodo_UK & @KLM. Enter sweepstakes here: http://ow.ly/m08ky .    
    
    
    Help kids fall in love with reading. Make a #booksforall difference right now! @cmcfund, @coinstar & this: http://j.mp/17IQx6C     
    
    
    Here's how Lisa joined the #booksforall #readingrevolution http://j.mp/11Rwvlw  Honoring kids like her today #AfricanChild.    
    
    
    Tanzania: Where a girl, a prime minister & the fight against illiteracy meet. via @ColinMcElwee & @GPforEducation http://j.mp/13NMAsk     
    
    
    10 Benefits of Reading: Why You Should Read Every Day http://www.lifehack.org/articles/lifestyle/10-benefits-reading-why-you-should-read-everyday.html … via @lifehackorg    
    
    
    Thank you so much @CLeboffe for supporting Worldreader and the @Swim4G team. We truly appreciate your generous donation. #bookforall    
    
    
    Where does social innovation & literacy cross? Tanzania. New blog by @ColinMcElwee @GPforEducation http://j.mp/13NMAsk  #AfricanChild    
    
    
    Live the magic of a Worldreader Kit Launch. Follow @kimeejohnson this week as she reports live from #Uganda. DAY 1: http://bit.ly/13YvkPD .    
    
    
    Would you like to spend a week in Ghana where you can mentor children? Win a volunteer trip with us. Participate now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz     
    
    
    Wow! @HYFR_tz_Rusty, you're on a #booksforall reading streak! How do you like the science books on @biNuMobile Worldreader Mobile app?    
    
    
    Spread #booklove in June. Donate spare change to Worldreader via a @coinstar machine near you. Super easy: http://j.mp/17IQx6C . Pls RT.    
    
    
    What happens when a young girl & a prime minister stand for literacy? @davidrisherWR blogs @HuffPostImpact http://huff.to/19OIZPF     
    
    
    VIDEO: e-reader launch at King George VI school in #Bulawayo #Zimbabwe. Made by school, music by students. MUST SEE. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HevF0YL4xy8&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Spend a week in Ghana mentoring children. Win a volunteer trip with us thanks to @Opodo_UK and @KLM. Participate now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz     
    
    
    Hey @bettrvolunteer. Aptitude, drive & motivation is what we look for. See this and let us know if you have Qs. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/heres-your-chance-change-a-life-in-ghana/ …    
    
    
    Whoa! @Swim4G raised $80K so far for #booksforall. You can fundraise to change the lives of kids in Africa too. http://www.worldreader.org/support-us/get-involved-2/ …    
    
    
    Brown Bag session on our work in Kenya led by Worldreader Operations Manager @jmwachi happening now in #BCN office. pic.twitter.com/LAkWYmkt2F    
    
    
    "Each child in our program in Kisumu #Kenya has 160 e-books to themselves," @jmwachi at Brown Bag session happening now. ICT changing lives.    
    
    
    Country Director Michael Sam now leading a session on impact of our #Kindle programs in #Ghana. pic.twitter.com/Y0a3en5xBi    
    
    
    "The device will change but what we are doing is eternal. We are putting knowledge into hands." @davidrisherWR pic.twitter.com/gRPG2HwiTk    
    
    
    Thank you @KeriannePayne for supporting @Swim4G and #bookforall! You're all role models to follow.    
    
    
    Kindle cases that help kids in #Africa get books. Check it out @ebookfriendly: http://www.worldreader.org/support-us/ . PIC: pic.twitter.com/y9JCiyDwve    
    
    
    STAT by @USAID: There would be a 12% drop in #globalpoverty if all students in low-income countries left school with basic reading skills.    
    
    
    Hey @BldgTomorrow! We like what your're about. We have two #Kindle school programs in Uganda. See here: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/our-projects/ …    
    
    
    Join international authors & publishers @sleeperspublish to help children/families in Africa fall in love w/ reading. http://www.worldreader.org/partner-with-us/for-authors-publishers/ …    
    
    
    We're excited too @BookLoversMark: "Black Letter Media partners with Worldreader." http://ow.ly/mhs6E     
    
    
    Got change? Want to help kids fall in love with reading? Donate to Worldreader via @coinstar machines in the US. http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    GET THIS: @Swim4G is swimming from Gibraltar to Africa & they've raised 90K for books. Help them get to 100K. Donate: http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    Great @ebookfriendly! Let us know if you need more info. Thank you.    
    
    
    Thank you @SVPSeattle for featuring @davidrisherWR. A truly personal account of the foundations of #booksforall. http://bit.ly/19D8TXw     
    
    
    Come and change lives this summer by mentoring children in our ereader programs. Participate in our sweepstakes now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz .    
    
    
    NEWS: Thanks to a partnership w/ @DwankhoziHope we launched the first e-reader program in Zambia. #bookschanginglives pic.twitter.com/wtizKNwvBg    
    
    
    Today is the last chance to win an all paid volunteer trip to #Ghana with us. Don't miss this opportunity. Enter now: http://ow.ly/mt1SO     
    
    
    Countdown begins! @Swim4G is 5 days away from crossing strait of Gibraltar for #booksforall. Talk about #inspiring! http://owswimming.com/     
    
    
    Empowering children and families with knowledge is our passion & now we're doing it in #Zambia with @DwankhoziHope: http://bit.ly/11UvZni .    
    
    
    Thanks very much @Hamomi. We're thrilled to be in Zambia and partnering with @DwankhoziHope.    
    
    
    "You've awakened the thirst for knowledge in them!" @KilgorisProject co-founder Caren McCormack says to WR staff. pic.twitter.com/r0rdn9Gj0g    
    
    
    Juliana Rotich: Meet @brcknet, Internet access built for #Africa on @tedtalks http://bit.ly/17VJLd5     
    
    
    We have a winner for our Travel for Books Sweepstakes! See more at: http://bit.ly/12GuXqt     
    
    
    Thank you all for participating in the Travel for Books sweepstakes and special thanks to our partners @Opodo_UK and @KLM! #booksforall    
    
    
    MUST SEE: How Mobile Technology is Transforming Africa by @mtrends http://www.nyotamedia.com/how-mobile-technology-is-transforming-africa/ … #innovation #startups #education    
    
    
    How do you get kids to read more, better and for life? Here's one idea: http://j.mp/12f8P6C  http://shar.es/AtV8p     
    
    
    Wow! $100,000 raised for #booksforall. Swim strong @soozmoody, @mauprieto, @Swim4G. Cheering you on from BCN, SF & all over Africa!    
    
    
    #Kenya's Imbuko Primary School is off and running, Matt Chang tells us: http://j.mp/14PQlwP . #booklove pix: pic.twitter.com/94GNy9Y2jC    
    
    
    Team @Swim4G reached their $100K fundraising goal & are about to swim the strait of Gibraltar. Want to fundraise too? http://bit.ly/WoXcZx     
    
    
    Our @zevlowe is in Malawi leading a digital publishing workshop. Cool fact: we've helped digitize 1000 African books. http://www.worldreader.org/our-books/     
    
    
    Thanks for the kind words @Outcastotter! We like what you are about too. Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    Great @HileDesmond. We're glad you enjoyed reading *The Girl with the Magic Hands*. What are you reading now on #worldreadermobile?    
    
    
    The weekend is upon us. Enjoy it everyone and we hope you'll be doing some of this. #readtorelax pic.twitter.com/hG7Qh7cItn    
    
    
    Now anyone can help bring books to those that need them the most! It's called a Worldreader Kit. VIDEO: https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=DXPb7exST2A ….    
    
    
    Thanks @engineer4change for believing in #booksforall. We appreciate your support. Have a great week!    
    
    
    In our latest blog post learn about Worldreader’s Out of Classroom Experience (OCE) reading program by @simplekay. http://bit.ly/1aRPUZ6 .    
    
    
    Her poems touched us all & now she's inspiring others to fall in love w/ books.Student Okanta Kate is changing lives: http://bit.ly/1aRPUZ6     
    
    
    There are over 10,429 books on Worldreader Mobile ready for you to read. Download it today! http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ … pic.twitter.com/bUgYHE3x2w    
    
    
    Whoohoo! @Swim4G is about to make the crossing from Europe to Africa. Swimming 20km against a strong wind. Stay tuned pic.twitter.com/XBsBS0f7Gn    
    
    
    Confessions of an African Author Fan: read all about @lizzywood's trip to #London last week for #AfricaWrites. http://bit.ly/14L5a53     
    
    
    Thanks @tomfurt for recommending us! @ksammyg let us know if you need more information. And @doctorow thanks for supporting #booksforall.    
    
    
    Look at them go!! @Swim4G is 20 min into their swim to reach Africa. We'll keep you posted! #swim4good #booksforall pic.twitter.com/LmDMRJQ7oF    
    
    
    2 hours & halfway to Africa! @Swim4G is crossing the Strait of Gibraltar as we write. GO TEAM, GO! #inspiration pic.twitter.com/prrpuaKijh    
    
    
    For you @RafaelNadal: @Swim4G is in the water right now & halfway to Africa! Thx for supporting them & us. pic.twitter.com/bO7zHJtE8g    
    
    
    They did it! @Swim4G has crossed the Strait of Gibraltar in 4h 51min & raised $105,251 for #booksforall! THANK YOU! pic.twitter.com/WuvDciRRoH    
    
    
    Hats off to Malala Yousafzai: "One child, one teacher, one book and one pen can change the world." We're proud to be celebrating #MalalaDay.    
    
    
    Introducing Worldreader Showcase: our 11 best #African books. For the next 11 days discover them with us. Details: http://bit.ly/12rSM6N .    
    
    
    Starting tomorrow you can download 1 book/day for the next 11 days via our African collection http://bit.ly/12rSM6N . pic.twitter.com/1meInyi6vF    
    
    
    We've joined forces with @BooksForAfrica to provide even more life-changing ebooks to communities in Africa. Details: http://bit.ly/17i03te     
    
    
    That's right @Biztechafrica! We've partnered w/ @BooksForAfrica to send ebooks & ereaders to students across #Africa. http://bit.ly/17i03te     
    
    
    SHOWCASE BOOK 1: Kanuki & The Wishing Tree, Meredith Kennedy. A notable favorite from our kids. Get #free copy here: http://amzn.to/15Hobq8 .    
    
    
    11 days, 11 books, 11 ways to #discoverAfrica has started! Get your first free ebook, Kanuki & the Wishing Tree, now: http://amzn.to/15Hobq8     
    
    
    .@pragmaticmom. 1st #freebook of our 11 days to #discoverAfrica can now be downloaded: http://amzn.to/15Hobq8 . Kids in our programs love it!    
    
    
    Books Help Empower Zimbabwe’s Children, All of Them: http://ow.ly/n0wlm . Via @GPforEducation by @ColinMcElwee. #bookschanginglives    
    
    
    @DavidColtart, here's a @GPforEducation article on how books are empowering Zimbabwe’s children, all of them: http://ow.ly/n0wlm . Enjoy!    
    
    
    BOOK 2 of #DiscoverAfrica is here: http://amzn.to/11QqqrV . Short Stories by @chikaunigwe give us insight into Nigerian & Dutch life. Enjoy!    
    
    
    Remember, we're giving a #freebook a day from our amazing African collection. Here's today's book by @chikaunigwe : http://amzn.to/11QqqrV .    
    
    
    Thanks to our authors/publishers our top 11 African books are free for 11 days. Today's #freebook is by @chikaunigwe. http://amzn.to/11QqqrV     
    
    
    Thanks for letting us know @royafrisoc! We are now following you. All the best.    
    
    
    You are on fire @rapperhazard. We've counted over 20 books that you are currently reading on Worldreader Mobile via @biNuMobile. Very cool!    
    
    
    You are & always will be a role model for all. Happy Birthday @NelsonMandela. We're celebrating #Mandeladay everyday! pic.twitter.com/TTKWQcgfyt    
    
    
    Today's FREE BOOK to #DiscoverAfrica: Beem Explores Africa by Simidele Dosekun. Perfect for kids and their parents! http://amzn.to/1anEfyl     
    
    
    Get a free copy of Beem Explores Africa by @SimiDos. Enjoy it w/ kids through the eyes of an adventurous little girl: http://amzn.to/1anEfyl     
    
    
    Big Smiles As More Kids in Kenya Fall in Love With Reading: http://shar.es/kgGq2  by @sglangevin. New project, more #bookschanginglives.    
    
    
    Friday's #FREEBOOK: 'Let Me Tell You' - a look into the lives of Kenyan girls & challenges they face. Happy Reading! http://amzn.to/1bCdwQ7     
    
    
    Thanks to our partnering publisher @Storymoja today's way to #DiscoverAfrica is via #freebook 'Let Me Tell You' http://amzn.to/1bCdwQ7 .    
    
    
    'The Cross Drums', by Meshack Asare is today's #freebook - A beautiful story of friendship despite tribal conflict: http://amzn.to/16DR17V     
    
    
    What happens when two boys from tribes in conflict have to work together? #DiscoverAfrica w/ Meshack Asare: http://amzn.to/16DR17V  #freebook    
    
    
    Lazy Sunday? Feel like reading? Get your #freebook of the day that will help you #discoverAfrica: Beneath the Rainbow http://amzn.to/15fx6Nn     
    
    
    Thanks for the smart words @Branakooko. Are you a Worldreader Mobile user? #bookschanginglives    
    
    
    FREE BOOK today: Beneath the Rainbow, a collection of short stories & poems that will delight all ages! Download now: http://amzn.to/15fx6Nn     
    
    
    Top African Books & #Free. Today, download Living Memories by Al Kags & discover Kenya’s reality before independence http://amzn.to/13dtyfE .    
    
    
    MILESTONE: 1,000 books digitized and we're only getting started! Find out what this means for #booksforall: http://bit.ly/18stH3D .    
    
    
    A technology revolution in Kenya's schools http://aje.me/16QEnSW  via @AJEnglish    
    
    
    Check it out @carmenmccain! @elmasuen's To Saint Patrick is spreading #booksforall. Everyone can enjoy TODAY 4 FREE: http://amzn.to/18xkJyX .    
    
    
    Thanks @jnxyz for the shout out. @LifelineEnergy Here's more on the power/electricity question: http://bit.ly/1dStwMm . cc @biNuMobile    
    
    
    So kind @lxy247: instant love for WR & the work they are doing to bring #ebooks to those who are without. Glad to have discovered this org.    
    
    
    MUST READ & FREE TODAY: To St Patrick. A gripping crime story by Nigerian author @eimasuen via @farafinabooks. LINK: http://amzn.to/18xkJyX     
    
    
    Today's free ebook to #DiscoverAfrica: "Grandmother's Winning Smile" by award-winning author @stangazemba -> http://amzn.to/1bCehZp .    
    
    
    Worldreader Kits highlighted on @ICT_works. Huge thanks @wayan_vota for this amazing piece! http://bit.ly/18zIOVQ     
    
    
    Jane Austen is to feature on the next £10 note, the Bank of England announces http://bbc.in/19hYekf  via @BBCBreaking    
    
    
    Second to last #FREE African Book! Fall in love with Africa, if you haven't yet w/ Baobabs of Tete by Kari Dako: http://amzn.to/17FBIOi .    
    
    
    Baobabs of Tete, by Kari Dako, offers a glimpse into a reality filled w/ complex characters & it's #FREE TODAY! http://amzn.to/17FBIOi .    
    
    
    We love this: "25 hilarious street art and mural works about books, libraries and reading" http://ebks.to/11FYUqy  by @ebookfriendly.    
    
    
    Last ebook of #discoverAfrica is by praised Nigerian author @chumanwokolo: The Ghost of Sani Abacha. #FREE for 48hrs. http://amzn.to/14PXPne     
    
    
    Absolutely wonderful @barugahara. Thank you for sharing the picture from parents day! We can't wait to hear more about it.    
    
    
    Worldreader Kits: Our know-how boxed so that anyone can bring books to children and families in remote places. VIDEO: http://bit.ly/1cgJQsa     
    
    
    Thank you @NewRootsDev. You also made our day with your kind words. #inspiration #bookschanginglives    
    
    
    @likeoftheday Thank you very much for promoting #booksforall today!    
    
    
    Parents Join Tanzania’s Reading Wave at Nganana & Nambala schools. See how the entire community is now impacted: http://bit.ly/18Mz22E     
    
    
    Watch & hear our kids in #Ghana via @GrahamBM. He's visiting our e-reader schools. LINK: http://boo.fm/b1529390  #bookschanginglives    
    
    
    Thanks for the visit @GrahamBM. Enjoy your time with @MobileWebGhana & thanks for supporting #booksforall.    
    
    
    Vacation School in #Ghana was in full force yesterday. Look at the serious reading happening by our young students: pic.twitter.com/KsZWK637py    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great article by @GrahamBM on a very special country: Ghana. http://bit.ly/14tEw4i     
    
    
    Kofi Annan, Nelson Mandela, @vargas_llosa. What all they have in common? They're now available on Worldreader Mobile: http://bit.ly/13T47we     
    
    
    @joyjordanlake Thank you Joy!    
    
    
    Toni Morrison, Octavio Paz Lozano, Martin Luther King are inspirational & available on Worldreader Mobile: http://bit.ly/13T47we     
    
    
    Meet 12-yr-old Grace:She's read all 44 books of the Magic Tree House Series, so she can "travel to different places." pic.twitter.com/Mqqrg9UsTg    
    
    
    @LC_Brady And we're excited to have you on the field! Enjoy and #Booksforall!    
    
    
    Meet Teacher Idah:"Since students use e-readers, attendance has improved so much.They now have a lot of information!" http://twitter.com/worldreaders/status/365515860422578176/photo/1pic.twitter.com/QFf5OnvmtK     
    
    
    Have a nice weekend and remember: “#Books are the quietest and most constant of friends..." #FridayQuote pic.twitter.com/UgO0aN2RzA    
    
    
    Today is International Youth Day! Read this article on @Forbes where Kofi Annan states 'Let The Young Lead': http://onforb.es/19dzaZ5     
    
    
    We're hiring a Partnership Development Manager. Spread the word and share it with your friends! Details here: http://bit.ly/10DWM2I     
    
    
    Heard from a teacher about WR Mobile: "Great app for teachers in schools where there are no books. Now I can read books- impossible before."    
    
    
    Update from partner @KilgorisProject about how Kindles in one of their schools help kids write better and read more. http://j.mp/14xLxdz     
    
    
    @AigyMulat Hi Agar! We're sorry to hear that. Please try this link and let us know if it works. http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/jointheteam/ …    
    
    
    Today on @HuffingtonPost: 'The Impact of Innovative Technology in Developing World' w/ @binumobile & Worldreader app http://zite.to/16gbPVz     
    
    
    @craigmod We are looking forward to seeing you there! Safe travels!    
    
    
    What a nice shot of one of our e-reader charging station in #Ghana. http://buff.ly/13yDsva . Captured by @craigmod.    
    
    
    Did you know that basic reading skills could lift 171 million people out of poverty? via @EFAReport #EducationCounts pic.twitter.com/MLNUdfeCsP    
    
    
    "You discover you have wings when you open a book." So read and fly to wonderous places. Happy Weekend everyone! #QuoteOfTheDay #Booksforall    
    
    
    Thank you very much @Shem85. We are humbled by your kind words. Just out of curiosity, how did you hear about us?    
    
    
    Meet @stangazemba, a rising star in Kenya's literary scene and learn what inspires his writing and life: http://bit.ly/153pFqE     
    
    
    It's #backtoschool. Teachers & students: make an impact this year, bring books to children who have no books. How: http://www.worldreader.org/kits .    
    
    
    Technology for social good: Q&A with @davidrisherWR on UK's @guardian. http://gu.com/p/3taf9/tw .    
    
    
    A Teacher’s Tale: How Hope Arrived in the Shape of an Ereader. New blog: http://j.mp/15aFoVS  #backtoschool #ict4edu    
    
    
    Thanks Girl Rising team for highlighting our #IDG2012 celebration via @10x10Act. http://bit.ly/1adA23Z  #ICT4Change #booksforall    
    
    
    We're working towards a world in which every child has a book she needs & wants to read. We can't do it without you. http://www.worldreader.org/support-us/     
    
    
    We voted for our awesome #booksforall partner @pubslush on Who is NYC's Hottest Showcasing Startup? http://wedgi.es/19ZZud7  via @TechCocktail    
    
    
    .@teachercorner We're calling all teachers, students & schools to help students in #Africa get the books they need. http://www.worldreader.org/kits     
    
    
    Good question, @Shem85. Luckily now with @Worldreaders Mobile on @biNuMobile folks can read all the time and make it a daily habit :-)    
    
    
    Your feature phone as a handheld library? Yes! A post penned by #booksforall's @DanieZacarias http://ow.ly/ozIef  via @Asia_Foundation    
    
    
    Curious how #booksforall sweepstakes winner @LC_Brady's trip to #Ghana turned out? Here you go: http://j.mp/17yat5T     
    
    
    The wonderful world of Dr. Seuss in ebook format! Partner @randomhouse announces 3 wave release starting Sept 24th.  http://on.cnn.com/15EIGjm     
    
    
    You can't miss @DanieZacarias's post on phones as personal libraries & our exciting partnership w/ @Asia_Foundation: http://ow.ly/ozIef     
    
    
    It's World #LiteracyDay & we've got good news: we're closer than you think to stomping out illiteracy with m-reading. http://on.fb.me/15GKBVH     
    
    
    So very true @peterrazaq and mobile technology is helping us reach areas of this world where books simply did not arrive. #possibilities    
    
    
    Get this: 6 billion have access to mobile devices. People who start reading on M devices read more than before. #Possibilities #LiteracyDay    
    
    
    We're thrilled about this piece in the @guardian. E-readers: the best way to get the world's children reading http://gu.com/p/3tfae/tw  .    
    
    
    Good question @helenmfj. But glad that we know each other now. Let us know if you have questions about #bookforall. http://www.worldreader.org     
    
    
    Full report on mReading will be out in early 2014 but preliminary findings show: 1/3 surveyed use mobile device to read books to children.    
    
    
    Great talking to you as well @amyahearn11! We're excited about the possibilities with you & @IREXintl. #booksforall    
    
    
    Thx very much @BcKoforidua. We are also looking forward to working with you on #NVDay. Our volunteers keep the mission going!  @Ghanathink    
    
    
    What a beautiful phrase by @MahindraRise: "There are those who accept things as they are, and there are those who RISE to change."    
    
    
    MUST READ: Why digital publishers are targeting Africa http://shar.es/ic0lJ   via @sharethis MT @lizzywood #booksforall    
    
    
    Nearly a billion people entered the 21st century unable to read a book or sign their name. We're changing this via #booksforall #technology.    
    
    
    "To read is to ponder, reflect, & contemplate"--wise words of Diane Frankenstein. Wonderful having her in our office! pic.twitter.com/yGkQuI4UsJ    
    
    
    See how two of our youngest brother volunteers, Julien & Sebastien, were spreading book love this summer in #Ghana. http://j.mp/184AKsD     
    
    
    Hi @MahindraRise. Pictures can be found here: http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/mediaroom/photos/ …. Let us know if you need more! Thanks for supporting #booksforall.    
    
    
    Great insights into Nigerian media @cchukudebelu @kaluaja. We appreciate the feedback as does the team at the @USEmbassyAbuja. Thanks!    
    
    
    Thanks for the shout out @EDCtweets! #literacychampions @RoomtoRead_Lon @BasicEdtweets @SRI_Intl @MCNFound @gbceducation @carrieschneider    
    
    
    Wonderful article about our partners @DwankhoziHope in The Seattle Times. Read here: http://bit.ly/1aOCDlk . #Booksforall in #Zambia.    
    
    
    Elmo on Worldreader Mobile? Yes! Kids in Nigeria can now enjoy Sesame Street #EDU content thanks to @SesameWorkshop. http://shar.es/iTqsh     
    
    
    Simply wonderful advice by François Marie Arouet -aka Voltaire. Happy weekend everyone! #FridayQuote pic.twitter.com/0Sxmccxnm6    
    
    
    Our thoughts are with everyone in Nairobi and Kenya. May this all end peacefully and soon! #SupportforNairobi    
    
    
    Religious leaders condemn #Westgate attack, ask Kenya not to be divided along religious line http://bit.ly/15OeWp8  via @dailynation.    
    
    
    A salute to all involved in helping contain the situation in Nairobi. #WeAreOne with #Westgate.    
    
    
    More African books for kids thanks to new partnering publishers! Get the scoop here: http://bit.ly/16l6JV0 . #booksforall    
    
    
    Evocative piece by @stangazemba, one of our authors, on the tragedy of #Westgate in Nairobi. @nytimes: http://nyti.ms/15QdxhI .    
    
    
    Thanks very much @ssakiwa. We're glad you are following us as well. #HappyFriday    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow @UNHCRdc. We're thrilled about our future collaborations to provide #booksforall! Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    Our deepest condolences to everyone in #Ghana who mourn a poet & scholar killed at #Westgate: Kofi Awoonor. http://nyti.ms/1feaEgK     
    
    
    That's right @ColinMcElwee @mashable @melindagates! We use existing mobile technologies to provide #books so people can improve their lives.    
    
    
    Nice to see our name on this list! 30 Amazing Mobile Apps for Social Good: http://causeartist.com/30-mobile-apps-social-good/ …. Thanks @GrntWish.    
    
    
    @princekeny62! Are you reading this textbook on your mobile phone for pleasure or for use in a classroom? @biNuMobile    
    
    
    Thanks for sharing @africaprogress! We will be sure to read Kofi Annan's speech. http://bit.ly/14Mo8t7  #booksforall    
    
    
    David Bowie reveals his favourite 100 books @Telegraph http://fw.to/keMvtjU . @DavidBowieReal share your love for books. Join #bookforall?    
    
    
    Wonderful to have you as a #booksforall follower and fan @editorladySally. Welcome!    
    
    
    What do these women have in common? You'll find out next week. Stay tuned! Have a wondering weekend! pic.twitter.com/coSqfpNU4n    
    
    
    Do you want to learn more about our #sustainable reading revolution? Don't miss @ColinMcElwee's post! http://ow.ly/pBxNk  @GPforEducation    
    
    
    Our kids ARE #reading more and better! Check out our brand new study results here: http://bit.ly/1ffVSoN  #allchildrenreading    
    
    
    Another study shows that our kids, this time primary students in #Ghana, read more and better with Worldreader http://bit.ly/1ffVSoN     
    
    
    "People don't realize how a man's whole life can be changed by one book" - Malcom X. #truth #quoteoftheday    
    
    
    16-Year-Old Malala Leaves Jon Stewart Speechless With Comment About Pacifism http://read.bi/1fjL1Kw  via @BI_Defense #educationforall    
    
    
    Thanks @JelenaRisticNDF for the RT. We're big fans of what you do through the @novakfoundation. We'd love to work with you on EDU projects!    
    
    
    We love what Malala said too @ShagorikaP: "Don't fight, be compassionate!" She's a true role model for everyone.    
    
    
    @HPGoodNews Thanks for the RT. #IamMalala is now even more powerful. She will and already is changing our world. Amazing girl!    
    
    
    It's International Day of the Girl & we're honoring GIRL book characters. Take our quiz & enter to win a Kindle: http://bit.ly/WRGirlsRockQuiz .    
    
    
    Awesome @jenettedavies! Thanks for taking our 'Girls Who Rock Books' Quiz. #IDG2013 http://bit.ly/WRGirlsRockQuiz     
    
    
    We believe that every girl deserves an #education. Watch this VIDEO & see how we're empowering girls. #IDG2013 http://bit.ly/1g5sp2h .    
    
    
    7 Unconventional Reasons Why You Absolutely Should Be Reading Books http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/10/12/health-benefits-reading_n_4081258.html … @HealthyLiving    
    
    
    Pan African EMBA session at @iesebs with Nigerian and Kenyan leaders happening now. Led by cofounder @ColinMcElwee. pic.twitter.com/XlWNMGsLRV    
    
    
    Thanks to @QatarFoundation for the invitation for @ColinMcElwee to speak at @WISE_Tweets in Doha this month.    
    
    
    If you love books then you'll love our "Girls Who Rock Books" Quiz. You can win 1 of 4 Kindles w/ 100 African books. http://bit.ly/WRGirlsRockQuiz .    
    
    
    NEWS: We're providing 8 rural libraries in #Kenya with 50,000 e-books via @gatesfoundation grant: http://bit.ly/WRGatesFoundation …. #booksforall    
    
    
    We're thrilled Bill & Melinda @gatesfoundation said YES! Library e-reader program set to help eradicate illiteracy. http://bit.ly/WRGatesFoundation …    
    
    
    What a week! @gatesfoundation said yes & this study shows our kids read faster after 6 moths, especially girls! http://shar.es/EviR9     
    
    
    Last chance to win a #Kindle via our Book Quiz. It ends today. Take it today and tell a friend. http://bit.ly/WRGirlsRockQuiz .    
    
    
    "We shouldn't teach great books; we should teach a love of reading." --B.F. Skinner. #FridayQuote    
    
    
    We're pleased to announce the winners of our Girls Who Rock Books Quiz! Thanks to everyone who participated! pic.twitter.com/5EqdSygJyx    
    
    
    We're looking for an Internal Operations Director to join our #booksforall team in San Francisco. Interested? http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/jointheteam/ …    
    
    
    Our teams are currently in Uganda, Kenya and Malawi & in the process of launching new projects to provide #ebooks. We'll share more soon!    
    
    
    New pilot service Wikipedia-via-SMS service could connect millions of offline readers http://zite.to/1c3cbAQ  via @TheNextWeb    
    
    
    We're partnering with #hero Kakenya Ntaiya: http://huff.to/1dauS6J . More to come as we deliver books to girls at risk of genital mutulation.    
    
    
    Our summer reading program ended with motivated kids and great experiences for the volunteers. Read the report: http://bit.ly/1ePzsrG     
    
    
    Happy Halloween everyone! Check out this cool costume: pic.twitter.com/LEEXtBCngl    
    
    
    Thanks @dollarpermonth for the shout out of great November Charities. #Proud to be mentioned with the rest of the organizations.    
    
    
    Thank you @KakenyaN for being such an #inspiration and role model. We're honored to be changing lives with books with you @kenyagirlschool.    
    
    
    More to come on our launch with @KakenyaN at @kenyagirlschool but in the meantime help her become a CNN Hero, VOTE: http://heroes.cnn.com/ .    
    
    
    We’ve teamed with @Africactive to bring 5000 life-changing ebooks, 50 e-readers to a school in #Malawi. DETAILS: http://bit.ly/1azZ3Wy .    
    
    
    Hi @CarolAjema. Any school or organization can apply here to bring e-readers to their community. http://www.worldreader.org/kits . Thanks!    
    
    
    Google doodle celebrates Albert Camus's #birthday anniversary-winner of the 1957 Nobel Prize. http://www.google.fr  pic.twitter.com/rAqaTUgO6f    
    
    
    Don't you agree with Jane? #FridayQuote pic.twitter.com/ryFbkOx7TV    
    
    
    On this day and everyday, we extend our gratitude to all the women and men that have served. Happy #VeteransDay.    
    
    
    Our rockin' New York Chapter @agr3 @davidjrich @Andracke is holding it's inaugural fundraising event tonight! Come by http://bit.ly/1amR90g     
    
    
    .@MatthiasStrubel's #PirateBox talk cites @cogdog's StoryBox, @LibraryBoxen, @cowbox_isen & @worldreaders http://vimeo.com/79102951 .    
    
    
    Very cool @janremm. Thanks for telling us about @EfikoApp. Could be a fit for our mobile book app. Greetings @tech360ng @idrisayobello!    
    
    
    We think every day is different and special but today is just a little more. Can you guess why? pic.twitter.com/cbPJGRIOqb    
    
    
    Thank you @doubledaypub for bringing more attention to our mission: creating a literate world. You are #Booksforall champions!    
    
    
    Pretty cool fact from our friends at @WISE_Tweets. Downloads of education mobile apps increased x10 in only 5 years. pic.twitter.com/TPUjoFn1be    
    
    
    Working with the girl who demanded education: http://bit.ly/1bxbBwG . 5000 ebooks now in the hands of girls @KakenyaN's academy of girls.    
    
    
    The world is a better place today thanks to #batkid. You are our hero! #makeawish pic.twitter.com/ZLE4zbkkLm    
    
    
    7 Things to Remember on Universal Children’s Day http://tinyurl.com/nc96fu5  via @livbarton    
    
    
    Tune in now to watch our co-founder @davidrisherWR speak at @ActivateSummit hosted by @Guardian. #ActivateNYC2013 http://bit.ly/1jmwco2     
    
    
    In pecha kucha format, @davidrisherWR about to explain how Worldreader is eradicating illiteracy globally using technology. #activatenyc2013    
    
    
    "Our civic lives should be as rich and as personal as our social and our commercial ones." @katyetc #activatenyc2013    
    
    
    Internet can bring democracy to democracy! Great job @katyetc presenting @TurboVote at #ActivateNYC2013.    
    
    
    In 2010, 50 e-readers were sent to Ghana. Today over 12,000 children are reading ebooks though our programs @davidrisherWR at #activateNYC.    
    
    
    Hi @Jwalkerpress. We have big expansion plans via e-readers and mobile phones. We'd love to tell you more. Email us: info@worldreader.org.    
    
    
    .@BabyAttachMode. Africa's mobile phone penetration rate is as high as 80%. Where there's a cell phone, there's electricity/books. @noahWG    
    
    
    .@BabyAttachMode If you'd like to learn more about powering in our programs, here's a piece on our blog: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/powering-reading-empowering-lives/ … @noahWG    
    
    
    Bravo @prerana123 & @Help_Nepal. W/ @gatesfoundation we will bring 250 e-readers to 8 libraries in Kenya. #ICT4Change http://bit.ly/WRGatesFoundation …    
    
    
    Malala Yousafzai gets EU's Sakharov human rights prize http://bbc.in/1bCyStw  via @BBCWorld #educationforall    
    
    
    We recently launched the largest single deployment of e-readers! 350 e-readers/ 49000 ebooks. More next week. PIC: pic.twitter.com/LNcvZX2zJ9    
    
    
    Digital Futures: The changing landscape of African publishing-Review & Response   http://wp.me/p1X3Mw-16n  via @NaraImprota.    
    
    
    Thank you @Microsoft employees for supporting us and other youth causes. #GivingHeros. http://msft.it/6012bhnm  pic.twitter.com/83If3pRrCM    
    
    
    Thanks for following us @TeachForAll & nice to meet you! We're #BooksforAll & on a mission to eradicate illiteracy. http://www.worldreader.org     
    
    
    Happy Thanksgiving! We're #thankful for books, technology & for all of YOU helping us eradicate illiteracy. What are you thankful for?    
    
    
    Thanks @Joyfullylost! Honored to be mentioned with @ladygeek @RoomtoRead @samatlounge @SheilaB01 @rebecsmart. #bookforall    
    
    
    "Change is happening and successful businesswomen are blazing a trail." Watch @WorldBank film on women in Africa http://ow.ly/r9cTF .    
    
    
    @SimoneLaPray @davidrisherWR @pbsnewshour For sure!    
    
    
    @GadSaad @NewsHour @davidrisherWR thanks for the kind words and please tell the world about what we're doing!    
    
    
    @gantman @davidrisherWR @NewsHour Thanks so much for the shout out! And keep following our work!    
    
    
    @janetjoy Thanks so much for the shout out! Please follow our work!    
    
    
    @dfdcidberry so glad you're inspire! Follow us!    
    
    
    @jutanclan @davidrisherWR @NewsHour thank you so much-- keep following our work, ok?    
    
    
    @sandraphflowers @davidrisherWR Thanks!!! You can ask friends to donate for holiday gifts!    
    
    
    @Love4Burritos thanks so much for watching!    
    
    
    @guidegroup @davidrisherWR Thanks so much and please share what we're doing with your community!    
    
    
    @robsmariga thanks!    
    
    
    Thanks @PBS @NewsHour for giving us a larger voice. WATCH @davidrisherWR talk to Jeffrey Brown about our mission: http://video.pbs.org/video/2365131666/ ….    
    
    
    Inspired after watching Worldreader on @PBS @NewsHour? You can help us fill classrooms in #Ghana with ebooks: http://www.worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ ….    
    
    
    Great @Sarkodee! Thank you. Here's how everyone can help this holiday season: http://www.worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ …. @davidrisherWR @pbsnewshour    
    
    
    Thank you @TechExLab for the mention! #booksforall    
    
    
    MT @john_weeks: "kids in Stung Meanchey dump say 'I don't want food, I want an e-reader' #cambodia."    
    
    
    The @Guardian Xmas appeal theme: #FutureAfrica. Honored to be selected with @PracticalAction @SolarAid @FarmAfrica. http://ow.ly/riAEz     
    
    
    Future Africa charities transform lives- @Guardian chief @arusbridger on @SolarAid @FarmAfrica @PracticalAction & WR http://gu.com/p/3kz7j/tw .    
    
    
    Our partner @Puzzazz provides us with puzzle ebooks. Get your own (some for free) at their #CyberMonday #BOGO sale. http://puzzazz.com/blackfriday     
    
    
    Our Holiday Campaign has launched! Goal? #GiveKnowledge by filling more classrooms in #Ghana with e-books. Join us http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ ….    
    
    
    On #GivingTuesday, help children like Belinda have the books she needs to improve her life. http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ …. pic.twitter.com/8jNlzDO7bQ    
    
    
    Beautifully said @NatGeo: Today is about giving to something bigger than ourselves! #GivingTuesday #Booksforall    
    
    
    Happening now: #GivingTuesday Google+ Hangout-a-thon. Tune in here: http://bit.ly/1883sj9 .    
    
    
    Feel passionate about eradicating illiteracy too? Join our team. We're hiring in San Francisco: http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/jointheteam/ ….    
    
    
    Celebrating Nelson Mandela's life & legacy. Narrated video at http://youtu.be/X7i7xVrWzT0  via @NelsonMandela Foundation.    
    
    
    “It’s an important thing to bring happiness to people, you also become happy.” -Nelson Mandela pic.twitter.com/5idfJMmd0P    
    
    
    Inspiration from @KofiAnnan on a day highlighting the protection of human rights & dignity of all people everywhere. pic.twitter.com/An2pNdbnT9    
    
    
    Danke well for a great meeting today @RobertBoogaard and our first European chapter @WorldreaderNL. Reaching new horizons together!    
    
    
    Let us know if you would like more information about how we're eradicating illiteracy @ElevenInc. http://www.worldreader.org  cc:@kimeejohnson.    
    
    
    Kindles makes up for lack of #books in Ghana's reading revolution http://www.theguardian.com/world/2013/dec/13/kindle-ghana-reading-revolution-worldreader-guardian-christmas-appeal … via @guardian    
    
    
    Thanks @HuffPostPartner for sharing this great infographic about language acquisition. http://huff.to/IOHmqr     
    
    
    Bring some holiday cheer to kids in #Ghana. Join us to improve the lives of thousands of children with e-books: http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign .    
    
    
    Double your donation for classrooms in #Ghana! For every $1 you give, The Quest Foundation will match it. Join us: http://www.worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ ….    
    
    
    5 Things You Can Do to Promote Literacy Over the Holidays http://huff.to/1fz2CMg  via @BlackVoices @zettaelliot.    
    
    
    Excellent piece @zettaelliot on promoting #literacy. We provide culturally relevant ebooks to children in Africa. http://www.worldreader.org     
    
    
    And we're getting there @gayle_tomlinson. We operate in 9 countries in sub-Saharan Africa and growing. http://worldreader.org     
    
    
    Thank you @afuahirsch @guardian & @guardianworld for this great story about our programs in #Ghana: http://gu.com/p/3y7kf/tw . #booksforall    
    
    
    Beautiful photo @NickKristof. Here's a story about Kibera's Doris and her love of reading: http://youtu.be/lRCBUCRWMHE .    
    
    
    Thanks for the generous donation @one_khz. We appreciate your support! #bookforall #Chicago.    
    
    
    So thankful to @SenatorDurbin & all in #Illinois who donated! In 24hrs $4550 has been raised by 157 donors. Join: http://www.worldreader.org/donate-with-durbin ….    
    
    
    Jonathan Wareham, Worldreader Board Member and @Esade professor, on Tech Ecosystems. http://on.ft.com/1kgWn2L  via @FT    
    
    
    Partner @Publerati will donate all net proceeds to @Worldreaders until the 26th. Make a difference simply by reading! http://blog.publerati.com/     
    
    
    Shelfie: show a photo of your bookshelf via @guardianwitness. https://witness.theguardian.com/assignment/52af050de4b008af53c5c715 …    
    
    
    Help us get Ghanaian kids like Martin the e-books they need to learn and read all they want. http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ … pic.twitter.com/NjdiUtrCZE    
    
    
    .@lit_hum This holiday season, give the gift on knowledge. Help us fill classrooms in Ghana with e-books. http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ ….    
    
    
    Did you catch us in The Observer and @Guardian this weekend? We're part of the Future Africa UK Christmas Appeal. pic.twitter.com/C9EMJ9dgwb    
    
    
    Huge thanks to @GhanaMixTapes for helping us spread the word about our Holiday Campaign for Ghana! #booksforall http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ …    
    
    
    10 countries with most improved adult literacy rates are in #Africa. http://on.fb.me/1gbUU8Z  via @WBPubs @WBeducation.    
    
    
    The recent Guardian & Observer Christmas Appeal 2013 article highlights our work in #Ghana. READ: http://gu.com/p/3yd34/tw  via @guardian.    
    
    
    Pupils in Ghana are among thousands in Africa to benefit from e-readers & inspires them to become literate http://gu.com/p/3yd34/tw  @guardian.    
    
    
    One of the best tools we've used in 2013, seamlessly connecting our teams in San Francisco, Accra, Barcelona, Nairobi. Thank you @zoom_us!    
    
    
    "I would say that 90% of the children [with e-readers] have cultivated a culture of reading", says headteacher Yeboah http://gu.com/p/3yd34/tw     
    
    
    What do magic and e-readers have in common? Award-winning author @Nnedi Okorafor. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/magic-e-readers-common-nnedi-okorafor/ … via @worldreaders    
    
    
    "Knowledge is power" is Enoch's parents motto although they can't read or write and they don't own a single book. http://gu.com/p/3yd34/tw     
    
    
    . @BBC names Nigerian writer Chimamanda Adichie’s Americanah as best book of 2013 http://www.360nobs.com/2013/12/bbc-names-chimamanda-adichies-americanah-as-best-book-of-2013-see-top-10-inside/ …    
    
    
    The best gift that you can give lasts a lifetime. Help us send e-books to more children in Ghana. #giveknowledge http://worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ …    
    
    
    Merry Christmas to all on behalf of our entire teams! Make a difference by participating in our Holiday Campaign! http://www.worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ ….    
    
    
    On this Christmas Day, we wish you and yours a very happy and healthy holiday! pic.twitter.com/e1bdLAHchO    
    
    
    @GhanaMixTapes We're so intrigued! How can we find out what the surprise is? Thank you.    
    
    
    Join us to support literacy: http://bit.ly/1g77z1H . 2 days left to double your donation thanks to Quest Foundation! pic.twitter.com/aYR6K9ctJI    
    
    
    "I've heard doctors read a lot! I want to be a doctor so I will read about 10 books a day.” Help kids like Elizabeth: http://bit.ly/1g77z1H     
    
    
    We're hoping @PeterGreste and his team are released soon. Al-Jazeera journalists arrested in Egypt http://aje.me/19A2ESV  via @AJEnglish.    
    
    
    Thanks to you we've raised enough for a 26th classroom in #Ghana & we're so close to reaching our 27th! Join us: http://www.worldreader.org/holidaycampaign/ …    
    
    
    Why #books really CAN change your life http://dailym.ai/19nvpC7  via @MailOnline    
    
    
    Amazing things came this 2013 and more will come in 2014. THANKS for making this year unforgettable. HAPPY NEW YEAR! pic.twitter.com/jumrbkmStp    
    
    
        
    
    
    2014 Development forecast via @WBeducation: Girls will outperform boys as they enter secondary schools & universities http://wrld.bg/s4o4h     
    
    
    This 16-year-old nails it when she talks about children's rights! via @Upworthy found by @julietrell. http://www.upworthy.com/a-teenager-articulates-how-policies-should-be-created-better-than-most-adults-probably-could?g=3 …    
    
    
    Hi back to you, @giselahausmann. Thx for the tweet and for browsing our site. What kind of ebook are you coming out with?    
    
    
    Hi @CurefoReading. Here's some place for you to start. Browse our collection of international & African books here http://www.worldreader.org/our-books/ .    
    
    
    Hi @twliterary. Thanks for thining of us. We would love to get your book. Ping @lizzywoood... she may be able to help sort out the #DCMA.    
    
    
    Thx @flynny1. @VassiliouEU - Would love to tell u more abt how we're transforming reading in the developing world. http://www.worldreader.org/     
    
    
    Congrats @giselahausmann! Keep us posted. Ping @lizzywood if you'd like to donate them to #booksforall.    
    
    
    Kakenya Ntaiya: A fearless girl who demanded school. http://ow.ly/iyLkb . Worth a watch on #IWD. #Empowerment via #education.    
    
    
    Great thanks, @VassiliouEU cc:ing @ColinMcElwee and @soozmoody. Let's try to schedule a call soon. What's the best way to reach you?    
    
    
    Welcome #booksforall fans! @CynthiaLive @yamiechess @alispagnola @colortheory @dcn_news @thebenlandis @ZulamaLearn @johnkin @jmpilz    
    
    
    Welcome new followers! @doklitfest @FHDN @nancygeer @AlisonMCaiola @Dixiemomx2 @liarsleague @mbaprojsearch @johnleedumas @IAMPHILLYCHASE    
    
    
    Hi new followers! @EstellaStar1 @hacettepecna @Rat_Skates @VE_Global    
    
    
    Don't they look happy w/ their new Kindles? New Dawn Educational Centre #Kenya pix: http://bit.ly/XDtQKS  pic.twitter.com/PJ2X6ZccEn    
    
    
    Thanks @brightonwriters for getting the word out! We're always on the lookout for #ebooks for kids & young adults.    
    
    
    Don't they look happy w/ their new Kindles? Here's a new pix from New Dawn Educational Centre #Kenya: pic.twitter.com/iMNKLPV4Qf    
    
    
    Thanks @SherillEwings for being our 4,000th follower! BOOKS FOR ALL! pic.twitter.com/8X1sl8MkN8    
    
    
    Welcome new #booksforall followers: 
@DebraBeck @imlostinbooks @markobrienwrite @S4KApps @geeksgalaxy @DidJaHearTheOne @mllemondegreen    
    
    
    Hi new followers: @couragedarling
@moderowo @Efiaula @MCAETorg @jmwachi @Oriol32torres @1STLADIESAFRICA
@LlucPalerm @davepea    
    
    
    And, what a nice photo it is @hi_from_abhi! Kids gathered around #reading on mobile phone. Images like that make our hearts melt. #ThankYou    
    
    
    Thx @Nanpolo for your kind words and for being a #booksforall fan. We're curious - how'd you hear about us?    
    
    
    What a great idea @onedegreesolar! Powering up for night classes! Feel free to email us at info@worldreader.org with other great ideas.    
    
    
    @DavinaCameron2 Which picture are you referring to? The New Dawn Educational Centre one? It's here: pic.twitter.com/ndzWH3MBls    
    
    
    Great! Thx, @Nanpolo! Happy 2 hear you're checking the site (http://worldreader.org ). Stay tuned. We'll have some fun, innovative news soon    
    
    
    Ja és oficial! @bookmovies ens ajudarà a portar #booksforall!! A la foto, @ColinMcElwee i Gabriel Pena. pic.twitter.com/AyI9txhp0y    
    
    
    It's official! @bookmovies is helping @worldreaders to bring #booksforall!! In the pic, @ColinMcElwee & Gabriel Pena. pic.twitter.com/D4hNHbRboK    
    
    
    Hi @Schools4Salone ... we'll see what we can do. @lizzywood, @ColinMcElwee- this may of interest to you.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the mention @g33kmate. @kachwanya - Here's what we're doing w/ #binu re: mobile reading: http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz . More news coming soon    
    
    
    Will Mobile Education Arrive in the Developing World? @PBSMediaShift http://to.pbs.org/WmHhxQ . Yes, it already has: http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz     
    
    
    Safe travels @Jazi_eu. We're very much looking forward to showing you our #booksforall programs.    
    
    
    Happy weekend. Take our poll, tell us your favorite #reading spot: http://www.facebook.com/worldreader .    
    
    
    .@Jazi_eu Keep us posted. We definitely want to hear your impressions.    
    
    
    Thanks for including us, @RedaLearning.    
    
    
    Great job @ty_pearl! You've read 5 books over the weekend on @worldreaders mobile. We're impressed. What will you read next?    
    
    
    Thx to all that came for our #socialenterprise happy hour in #sf. We'll be holding more in the coming months. PICS: http://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.10151280339616534.1073741825.329424311533&type=1 …    
    
    
    We're impressed "@Kiva has officially reached 1 MILLION borrowers with loans worldwide! http://blog.kiva.org/kivablog/2013/03/18/1-million-borrowers …." Huge impact. Congrats.    
    
    
    10,000 kids and families impacted in #Africa via ebooks. @EmWatson would be the perfect spokesperson for @worldreaders. Will you join us?    
    
    
    How does @medgestore, #booksforall and stickers on ereader cases inspire reading? Find out in our new blog http://shar.es/eZu0R .    
    
    
    Inspiring #QUOTE: ‎"I want to write books that unlock the traffic jam in everybody's head." -John Updike (American novelist & poet)    
    
    
    Hi @MBuffenoir. Are you referring to our e-reader or mobile readers?    
    
    
    A great @TheEconomist article about the energy, hope and buzz of "#Africa: A hopeful continent." http://econ.st/13uMzH8     
    
    
    FACT: Societies with educated children prosper. RT if you agree that #education can change the world. #booksforall pic.twitter.com/WttwTgh0mH    
    
    
    Happy Father's Day. We love this @pintrest photo: http://pinterest.com/pin/546765210980633103/ …. Will you spend time reading with your father today?    
    
    
    March is #NationalReadingMonth. What book are you reading today?    
    
    
    That's a great one, @chazmonster26. #Happy #reading!    
    
    
    another question for you @chazmonster26 - reading it on paper or digitally? just curious :-)    
    
    
    @chazmonster26 Cool, enjoy. Paper, digital -  just keep reading!    
    
    
    We love it @osarpong! See Okanta Kate's beautiful poetry writing here: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/changing-kids-lives-one-e-book-at-a-time-okanta-kates-story/ … BTW, she's our star student from #Ghana!    
    
    
    We can relate :-). It's ours, too. MT @chazmonster26 Reading is the love of my life.    
    
    
    $10B project near Accra #Ghana promises #ICT growth, university & hospital. We hope it helps spur #education, too. http://www.cnn.com/2013/03/20/tech/hope-city-ghana/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Thanks for including us, @barcampghana!    
    
    
    Thx for the heads up, @welovebold. Nice site. Thx for including us. Ping us if u have any follow-up questions or are looking for story ideas    
    
    
    Good one, @buddingreader. It's a pretty building, but more the Hope City #Ghana project seems to show what the country is moving towards    
    
    
    Happy #WorldPoetryDay! Celebrate all poets of this world including our very own student Okanta Kate. Please Retweet. pic.twitter.com/j2MCiJxPgf    
    
    
    We were so thrilled to learn that Monday was #Malala's first day back in school http://bbc.in/10nWoIJ  #inspiring #girlsmatter #bookforall    
    
    
    Poem by student Okanta Kate. "The Greatest Victory"-girls like Kate & #malala improve our world. #worldpoetryday pic.twitter.com/kjz8fzAKRP    
    
    
    Thinking you may like poem from Okanta Kate, @osarpong. Pls pass it along on #worldpoetryday pic.twitter.com/kjz8fzAKRP    
    
    
    Thanks for coming by @Jazi_eu. Glad you enjoyed the visit. Ping us if you have any questions.    
    
    
    "Things Fall Apart" author Chinua Achebe dies at 82 via @nytimes http://nyti.ms/Z7aDjI . #booksforall honors this great #African writer.    
    
    
    In memory of 'The Father of Modern African Writing', Chinua Achebe who passed away today at the age of 82. PIC: pic.twitter.com/7ZNDmLgnHz    
    
    
    Thank you new followers! @PraskiBookNews @shubbless @TAGAsia @lovliving @tix4cause @nolimitsforme @tesEnglish @Grant_Perry @UNESCO_Centre    
    
    
    Healthy, wealthy and wise girls infographic by @GPforEducation. Worth seeing. Educated Girls=Better Economies. https://www.educationforallblog.org/media/2013/03/3-8-2013-educating-girls-infographic.png …    
    
    
    Welcome new followers! @ElanaWinfrey @kbielecki_ @SeeMiracles @CALEntertainmnt @RichardJWood @ReadyForHillary @erichollreiser    
    
    
    Thx for asking, @parklandcommlib. Let's swap ideas via email comms [at] http://worldreader.org .  @soozmoody @NadjaBoz may have ideas.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the heads up @NosyCrow, & @BKGKristen, thx always for your shoutouts. #tocbologna ping us w/ ?s re: mobile reading & ebooks in Africa    
    
    
    Good point, @JulieFHedlund. Similar #ereader & #ebook need in Africa, a gap #booksforall is closing. http://worldeader.org  #tocbologna    
    
    
    Hi @princeboadu... No, we're not in #Kumasi... yet ;-). But we are in Accra and other parts of #Ghana. cc: @ColinMcElwee    
    
    
    Unfortunately we are not @iamgrowney @FableKids. Feel free to send us an email. Info at http://worldreader.org . Thx. @nancygeer    
    
    
    Absolutely. Would you mind sending us a note? Info at http://worldreader.org  or we can DM @princeboadu. When is the event?    
    
    
    Around the world in 80 books! Very cool list. Thanks @scholasticTeach for sharing. http://ow.ly/c99fe  #readeveryday #booksforall    
    
    
    Impressive! @taylorswift13 supports @scholastic #readeveryday campaign-spreads the message of the power of #literacy. http://www.scholastic.com/readeveryday/taylor-swift-live-webcast.htm …    
    
    
    Wonderful @princeboadu. And response sent. We're excited about the possiblity of #booksforall at #TEDxKNUST.    
    
    
    Thx 4 the support @ericrumsey. Stay tuned for more exciting news about Worldreader Mobile. http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ … @drew @africatechie    
    
    
    MT @usembassymanila: @StateDept & WR team up 2 provide English language learning content on mobile phones @binuMobile #TESOL2013 #mLearning    
    
    
    You are most welcome @EHsleeps. Small actions can do big things in this world. Keep up your effort raise awareness for #girleducation.    
    
    
    Sent to us by @Aalyel. Another beautiful quote by Chinua Achebe: "My weapon is literature." #inspiration    
    
    
    MUST READ by @sarahtierney: The $100bn mobile bullet train called Africa http://wp.me/p1BZSj-eL  "More ppl have cell phone than electricity."    
    
    
    Great article @sarahtierney! We provide #books 2 people in dev world via #kindles & mobile phones @binumobile. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz  (cont)    
    
    
    @sarahtierney 1/2 MILLION unique readers reading 20 MILLION PAGES a month on Worldreader Mobile-and we have more data. If interested, DM us.    
    
    
    Hi @MotherTongueSL! We're thrilled you are interested in supporting #booksforall. Could you send a note to publishing@worldreader.org? Thx.    
    
    
    And we're honored to be working with you, too @GreyGeckoPress. Serving the #worldcommunity and bringing #bookstoall = #goodmatch    
    
    
    hi @buddingreader.. thanks for the heads up. we'll check out @Benetech and keep @lizzywood @binu in the loop.    
    
    
    Hi @ulbrichalmazan. Thx for including us. Indie publishers certainly can get involved. Here's how http://ow.ly/jtiUA     
    
    
    THANKS @MayiNgwala & Genet Press for being part of the #booksforall community & donating your book to our kids! More: http://ow.ly/jtjCg     
    
    
    Worldreader supports #marriageequality. RETWEET if you do too! @HRC pic.twitter.com/t5HXyPWMeI    
    
    
    Thank you @sarahtierney! We truly appreciate it. Do you use a feature or android phone? We'll send a note in a few weeks with our updates.    
    
    
    Thanks @ulbrichalmazan. We read your piece. We're interested in all #books: indie, children's titles, romance, fiction, text books (cont.)    
    
    
    If you are interested in donating @ulbrichalmazan, please contact @lizzywood or email our publishing team-(publishing@worldreader.org). Thx.    
    
    
    .@JulieOwono, @Angeles_Jurado great @el_pais interview. You may like, too: 1/2M phone users reading 20M pages/month on Worldreader Mobile...    
    
    
    .@JulieOwono @Angeles_Jurado Would love to tell you more abt our ereader & phone reading programs being used in #Africa. Can we DM you?    
    
    
    Can you send is samples to read through? Are they in digital form already? @ulbrichalmazan @lizzywood @DanieZacarias    
    
    
    @ai1_electronics We'll DM you some tips for interactive content. Thx!    
    
    
    From Slums to Superstars. New blog: http://shar.es/d2ItK  #inspiration and #girlpower in #Kenya    
    
    
    Big reader @Berusphillip. We're impressed that you are reading so much on Worldreader Mobile via @biNuMobile. What's your favorite book?    
    
    
    NEW LAUNCH: 130 girls in #slums of Kenya now have access to over 10,000 e-books they need and love to read. Details: http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    In @nairobi_kenya this week at the next EdTech MeetUp: feature on Worldreader. To join visit: http://dlvr.it/37xzrD . #Africa #innovation.    
    
    
    Hey @nuttyxander! Can you tell us where we can find this quote? :) Thanks so much and #booksforall.    
    
    
    How do we measure our success? By monitoring & evaluating our programs aka #research. Visit this page to learn more: http://www.worldreader.org/learnings/     
    
    
    FUN FACT: William Shakespeare invented the word hurry. U can read his classics using your cell on Worldreader Mobile: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ …    
    
    
    Literacy Rates of the World. See how your country fairs: http://world.bymap.org/LiteracyRates.html …. RT if u think access 2 books can increase literacy rates.    
    
    
    .@AllenAndUnwin! We provide ebooks 2 children/families in dev world using #kindles & mobiles. Might u be interested in donating content?    
    
    
    Happy Birthday Hans Christian Andersen. We love that it's also International Children's Book Day. http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hans_Christian_Andersen …    
    
    
    Cool #infographic shared by @cultureslurp: The World As 100 People: 17 cannot read or write. LINK: http://visual.ly/world-100-people … #literacy    
    
    
    Our commitment to transparency has garnered the approval of @GuideStarUSA. For our full profile visit: http://www.worldreader.org/worldreader-guidestar/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @thereason_ezu! We're glad you like the new look on Worldreader Mobile. More updates to come soon. What book are you reading now?    
    
    
    We'll be watching @gatesfoundation @TEDxChange talking about girls & women as catalysts of change. Starts 6 pm PST. http://gates.ly/YuDCiJ     
    
    
    .@gatesfoundation. 130 girls in Kenyan #slums now have a chance for a better future with access to 10,000 e-books. http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    130 #girlrising in slums of Kibera, Kenya via access to 10,000 e-books. #inspiring story you will love @10x10act: http://bit.ly/168sBDA     
    
    
    'Words resonate, they can transform. Believing in people creates possibilities'. Halima Hima at #TEDxChange    
    
    
    By @BBC: Mobile phone celebrates 40th birthday-http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/technology-22013228 …. We'll be showing our appreciation next week with some exciting news.    
    
    
    New book for all you mobile phone readers on Worldreader Mobile: "No Straight Lines". Thank you @alansmlxl 4 making #booksforall a reality.    
    
    
    Alan Moore's "No Straight Lines" now available for #reading on Worldreader Mobile: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ …. Big thanks to @alansmlxl.    
    
    
    FACT: According to @UNESCO 31 MILLION children in sub-Sahran Africa are out of school. READ the presentation here: http://bit.ly/YVv8AU .    
    
    
    Great job on finishing #atomstoMolecules on Worldreader Mobile @DrewHacjre. Did you learn something new? @biNuMobile    
    
    
    "Study after study shows that the earlier a child begins learning, the better he/she does down the road"-ow.ly/jHuBo via @NYTimes    
    
    
    Thanks for following us @seymoursimon! Would you be interested in donating some of your wonderful books to our program? #booksforall    
    
    
    Thank you @SuzanneDiBianca for following us! Just curious, how did you hear about #booksforall http://www.worldreader.org ?    
    
    
    Thx very much @HilaMehr! We're thrilled to be included in this excellent report on EDUTECH in #India. We'll share it! http://onbuff.ly/16r1xQ5     
    
    
    EDTECH India report on #Worldreader: A few co. working in devworld w/ potential 4 real impact on learning outcomes. http://onbuff.ly/16r1xQ5     
    
    
    We agree @buddingreader. We're impressed with your work and the work of @FirstLangBooks @ReadingHamlets @WorldLiteracy. Any ideas in mind?    
    
    
    We employ Early Grade Reading Assessment tool 2 improve student #reading & teaching programs. Learn more on our BLOG: http://bit.ly/17h0J3y     
    
    
    Thanks @ExcelAfrica for sharing our recent story on how we monitor & evaluate our programs! #booksforall http://shar.es/di66f     
    
    
    Can you name 10 countries in Asia? 
Ummi can! This 10 year old girl loves the World Atlas. So cool! RT if you agree. pic.twitter.com/8wA27KswFq    
    
    
    Can you name 10 countries in Asia? 
Ummi can! This 10 year old girl loves the World Atlas. So cool! RT if you agree. pic.twitter.com/DESRIYByBW    
    
    
    Correct @CamiloDeza. Ummi named 10 countries in Asia & moved on to learning about DR of CONGO on her #kindle. ;) Isn't she adorable?    
    
    
    @seymoursimon Thx. Liz, let us know how to best reach you. Our @lizzywood @DanieZacarias can explain more about #booksforall. @StarWalkKids    
    
    
    Our condolences to the family of Anne Smedinghoff, killed in Afghanistan while delivering books to students. #NotFair http://bit.ly/10LCX9k     
    
    
    BIG NEWS: We've launched Worldreader Mobile, an app that allows millions to read books on a cell phone. Details here http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    FACT: 500,000 children & adults read 17,000 books via Worldreader Mobile on feature phones. A true #readingrevolution http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Thank you @HargeisaLibrary. We're excited about the possiblity of bringing #booksforall to Somalia.    
    
    
    Let us know if u have more Qs @NVKYN. Cell penetration in #Africa=about 60%. 1/2 million are already reading on app. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    We're on 5 million phones in the developing world & 0.5 MILLION are actively reading. Get all the facts here: http://on.fb.me/ZkFfv0 .    
    
    
    Have you heard? We've extended #booksforall w/ partner @biNuMobile via mobile phones. 0.5 MILLION readers/month. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Thanks @laurahazardowen! RT @paidContent: "Worldreader counts 500,000 users of its e-reading app on feature phones http://dlvr.it/3CKqVN "    
    
    
    FACT: 70% of active readers on Worldreader Mobile are females, reading over 17 books a month. #girlrising #girlpower http://ow.ly/jU0RH     
    
    
    We love this by @Maddybeckmann: "Today a reader, tomorrow a leader!" #literacy #edtech #quoteoftheday    
    
    
    Watch our VIDEO on how mobile phones & books will improve #literacy in the developing world. http://ow.ly/jU1Fg     
    
    
    FACT:Teachers, caregivers, older siblings, parents use Worldreader Mobile. 88% would use it as learning tool w/ kids. http://ow.ly/jU2uU     
    
    
    And what's really cool @julietrell @10x10act is that 70% of our active readers are females! Check out this VIDEO: http://bit.ly/ZgT3rr .    
    
    
    See photos of @curiouslee reading e-books on our mobile phone book application: http://j.mp/YbZ20m . Way cool!    
    
    
    Nice poem @TheArchcardinal! Do you have more? More poetry is available on Worldreader Mobile book app via @biNuMobile.    
    
    
    Support @unitetolight #fundraiser for solar chargers so people in developing countries can charge their e-readers. http://goo.gl/gwbZr     
    
    
    :) Let us know if you are interested showcasing some of your poetry on Worldreader Mobile @TheArchcardinal.    
    
    
    @melindagates Tech in developing world means #booksforall. Our cell phone book app has 0.5 MILLION active readers. http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Worldreader Mobile on @Forbes @gigaom @VentureBeat @CNNMoney & more. Visit our press page 4 all the latest articles. http://bit.ly/LBFxI7     
    
    
    Have you seen our VIDEO about our new platform for expanding #booksforall? Learn about Worldreader Mobile here: http://ow.ly/jU1Fg .    
    
    
    We've got news to share w/ @BON_EDUCATION-0.5 MILLION people reading on mobile phones via Worldreader Mobile. New #booksforall platform-cont    
    
    
    More details on our announcement here: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q . Let us know if you have Q's or DM us. Thx @BON_EDUCATION.    
    
    
    FACT: In January, Worldreader Mobile users read the equivalent of 17,000 books on their feature phones. Details: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    Our twitter community has grown in the last few days. We just want to say thanks to all our new members.#booksforall pic.twitter.com/ETLYPHifIv    
    
    
    Can you name this author? And his real name too? Something fun. Something quick on #friday. Hit reply w/ your answers pic.twitter.com/z5Q5V1bnnY    
    
    
    @GdnDevelopment 500,000 in the developing world are actively reading on their mobile phone. Tech+Books=Improved Lives http://bit.ly/XBkH7q     
    
    
    Bingo @HallidayMiller! Great job. We'd love to send you a Worldreader t-shirt. Can you DM us to get your details? #booksforall    
    
    
    An estimated 250 million children are not able to read or write. Via @WBeducation http://twitpic.com/cii8nz  #educationfirst #booksforall    
    
    
    Have an android phone? Access free books via Worldreader Mobile on Google Play. http://bit.ly/1236cbN     
    
    
    Hi @Techzim. 180,000 people in #Africa are reading books on their mobile phone. More info here: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q  @biNuMobile    
    
    
    Thx @CSMonitor 4 visiting our site & writing this: "Worldreader, a nonprofit, brings e-books to developing countries" http://bit.ly/ZlN7gT     
    
    
    Last week we launched Worldreader Mobile w/ @biNuMobile, an app that allows millions to read books on a mobile phone. http://youtu.be/KTGD1FluEcg     
    
    
    Our thoughts are with the city of #Boston today.    
    
    
    Hi @BrettWSimpson. That revolution is happening via #kindles & #mobilephones. 500,000 ppl reading on WR Mobile. Visit http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/     
    
    
    Hi @johntraxler. We read your piece on mobile learning in Africa. Thought you might be interested in this: http://bit.ly/XBkH7q .    
    
    
    mLearning is happening in Africa @AfricanBrains. 500,000 people are reading on mobile phones. See http://bit.ly/XBkH7q . @biNuMobile    
    
    
    We say yes @WISE_Tweets: "Can mobile technologies extend the reach of #education in #Africa? http://bit.ly/LbJoP8 "    
    
    
    Infographic: What Will It Take to Achieve Learning For All? http://www.worldbank.org/en/news/feature/2013/04/15/what-will-it-take-to-achieve-learning-for-all …    
    
    
    Look what would happen if all students in low-income countries acquired basic reading skills. Infographic: http://ow.ly/k9tdI  @WorldBank    
    
    
    MT ‏@WBPubs 61M children are not in school; 32M are girls. Development leaders discuss putting #educationfirst, 4/18: http://ow.ly/k99gj     
    
    
    Just published @mashable: Mobile Phones Deliver Millions of E-Books to Developing World http://on.mash.to/YVgFGJ  w/ @binumobile by @zoebfox.    
    
    
    Team @mashable @mashablemobile @zoebfox @petecashmore, thx for focusing on the #readingrevolution in the dev. world. http://on.mash.to/Zyj0mq     
    
    
    .@ThinkAfrica - To your point "digital innovators using smartphone apps are earning global attn." U may like this: http://ow.ly/kbICO     
    
    
    Hi @lincolnavy. Did you enjoy #CanLoveHappenTwice on @Worldreaders Mobile  @biNuMobile app? What will you read next?    
    
    
    Hi @AmankonaHinne - What did you like most about the book #FacetoFace? Which books will you read next? #booksforall #biNu    
    
    
    Next-generation ebooks introduced at London Book Fair http://gu.com/p/3f7fc/tw  via @guardian #Reading #Fun    
    
    
    For millions in developing world, feature phones updates can be an #education game changer ~ @mashable http://on.mash.to/YVgFGJ  #empower    
    
    
    Hi @SalhaKaitesi Thx for including us! #FridayLove to you :-)    
    
    
    FRIDAY Read: The 40 coolest characters in literature http://shortlist.com/entertainment/the-40-coolest-characters-in-literature … via @ShortList.    
    
    
    171 million ppl could be out of poverty if students acquired basic reading skills. Via @WorldBank @HuffPostImpact http://huff.to/17rr5wM     
    
    
    Thx @ChelseaClinton for spreading the message about WR Mobile and the #readingrevolution in the developing world. http://on.mash.to/YVgFGL     
    
    
    Happy #WorldBookDay everyone! Take our Book DNA quiz & win 1 of 5 Kindles loaded with our best African books. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Wondering what book you belong in? Take our Book DNA quiz to find out & you might win a Kindle! #WorldBookDay http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Happy World Book Day @GPforEducation! Thx for featuring #booksforall. Join the celebration & take our Book DNA quiz. 
http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    MT @colinmcelwee: World Book Day and the Power of Choice and Technology @worldreaders http://tinyurl.com/cb2afvu  Thanks to @GPforEducation    
    
    
    "World Book Day and the Power of Choice and Technology" @ColinMcElwee via @GPforEducation. Books change everything! http://ow.ly/kjwbm     
    
    
    Thx @SMWBarcelona for celebrating #WorldBookDay with us. Have u taken our Book DNA Quiz? What book do you belong in? http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Celebrate #WorldBookDay. Take this quiz & you may win a Kindle, like the one our kids have. Please RT. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Happy #WorldBookDay! Celebrate #booklove by taking this quiz. You could win a Kindle loaded with African books! http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Let's have some fun on #WorldBookDay! Take our Book DNA Quiz & discover your book match. Maybe win a Kindle, too. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Moto to live by: "Enjoy life's simple pleasures." Happiness is key. Thanks @CocaColaCo for following us. #booksforall    
    
    
    Thx @MoorthyBBM for the tweet & passing the link to @CocaColaCo. You may also like this post by @ColinMcElwee http://ow.ly/knBrj     
    
    
    Hi @smallbutfeisty... Not sure what happened, but this link should take you to the quiz: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . Let us know if it works.    
    
    
    @kenkenhimself awww... just between us, u could belong in Gone with the Wind instead. Sounds like u have a romantic side :-) cc: @soozmoody    
    
    
    Ever wondered what book you belong in? Take this quiz & you may win a Kindle, like the one our kids have. Please RT. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Thanks @asenkut! For more information you can also visit our website. http://www.worldreader.org  #booksforall    
    
    
    Calling all book lovers - Pls help #booksforall grow. Take a 30-sec quiz & share this link http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . #booklove to you. Thx!    
    
    
    Hi @moCZARella_ @smallbutfeisty. Sorry to hear this.Are you using a mobile phone? Try w/ a computer & use this link: https://apps.facebook.com/easypromos-premium/promotions/13997 …    
    
    
    Excited for our interview with GoodCauseTV today. The interview with @tweetpete & @soozmoody will be posted here: http://goodcausetv.tumblr.com .    
    
    
    Hi @moCZARella_  were you able to take the quiz when you got home? Fingers crossed that it worked. Thx for your dedication and support.    
    
    
    Hi @Believe_Bateyes. Thx for the tweet. Here's info abt partnering w/ #booksforall http://ow.ly/kpEFs . Good luck w/ the Esperanza prgm.    
    
    
    "The dearest ones of time, the strongest friends of the soul – BOOKS." ~ Emily Dickinson #foodforthought #booklove    
    
    
    30 seconds of #bookfun happening here: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD . You could be the lucky winner of a Kindle loaded with #African ebooks!    
    
    
    Fun @moCZARella_ Happy to hear that our book quiz is working! So you are just like Hermione from Harry Potter. Kind, smart, fun!    
    
    
    @slim_alger in what book do you belong?    
    
    
    @anitakapten what book are you?    
    
    
    @AlonEchelon in what book do you belong?    
    
    
    Thank you new followers: @cloeimg @LaneDebra @IAm_BMA @AfricanDreamOrg @americadiaspor @AlexFoundation1 @chintan2425 @RegimeRecords    
    
    
    Hi @Believe_Bateyes. Info on how to launch an e-reader program in your school is here: http://bit.ly/KNQ16n . Let us know if you have Qs.    
    
    
    Wow! 6.8M new teachers needed globally to get every child in school by 2015. INFOGRAPHIC: http://tinyurl.com/bkttoo6  via @GPforEducation    
    
    
    Thank you for your support, @NatFairFax! What kind of book have you written? We're always looking 4 stories to share with kids in our prgm.    
    
    
    .@JayOdeo yes, 1400 ebooks on the #biNu #WorldreaderMobile phone app. So now your phone nows works as a portable library! Happy reading!    
    
    
    Looking for some #FridayFun? Here you go! Take the Book DNA quiz here  http://on.fb.me/10vQubD  & enter our Kindle giveaway sweepstakes.    
    
    
    Inspiring pics via @GPforEducation's Reading Changed My Life e-album http://ow.ly/ksbMf . Fav: 101-yr-old Maria learns to read & write    
    
    
    Nice article @ApolloJoab: http://bit.ly/11TSSqh . Kindles are impacting #education in Kenya via 25 schools/libraries. Interested? DM us.    
    
    
    Look who's making headlines...@soozmoody! She's swimming 22K for #booksforall & is in @Diario_SPORT today: http://ow.ly/kwIQN  cc @Swim4G    
    
    
    Really, you could win a Kindle loaded w/ #African ebooks! No clear winner yet & 2 days left to take our quiz: http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Watch live now as GoodCauseTV's @tweetpete interviews @soozmoody, http://www.spreecast.com/events/goodcausetv-interviews-worldreaderorg--3 …    
    
    
    We loved talking to goodcausetv today. Watch the entire interview between @tweetpete & @soozmoody here: http://sprc.st/g0JqN . @IndyWorld    
    
    
    Thanks for taking our Book DNA quiz @AmethystToeShoe. In what book do you belong? :)    
    
    
    Great @kenkenhimself! Get your friends to participate in the Quiz too and your chances of winning go up. The playing field is wide open!    
    
    
    We sure do @carlhinrichsen! @unitetolight is one of our great partners. Great project, great idea, great organization.    
    
    
    One of Brazil's biggest newspapers @JornalOGlobo covers our efforts to improve global literacy: http://glo.bo/145pv7H . #booksforall    
    
    
    Hurry! Last chance to win a Kindle! Our Book DNA Quiz ends today. http://on.fb.me/10vQubD     
    
    
    Engagement is the rocket fuel that decodes words & is the foundation of what we call literacy ~ @ColinMcElwee Blog: http://shar.es/lpLrY     
    
    
    Hey @kurtgrela. Here's a link to @Forbes piece on Worldreader Mobile. 1/2 MILLION readers a month. http://onforb.es/10OxIaC . #booksforall    
    
    
    Not yet but we're working on it @Marvin_Mathew! Stay tuned. @ConnectStateGov @StateDept @Raspberry_Pi. http://www.worldreader.org .    
    
    
    #AmericanEnglish learning content now available via Worldreader Mobile thx to @StateDept @biNuMobile. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz . #booksforall    
    
    
    MT @soozmoody: Woot! We just broke $53,000 for our fundraising effort 4 @Worldreaders. Pls help us get to $100,000 http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    The winners of our Book DNA Quiz are: http://bit.ly/18eFcJl . For everyone that participated, thx for helping us fight global illiteracy.    
    
    
    Way cool! @GuideStarUSA is using one of our #booksforall photos to show #nonprofitluv. http://guidestar.org/  http://www.worldreader.org .    
    
    
    Most welcome @SALVEint! Where in Uganda are you located? We have some project there too. #dogoodtogether #greatnonprofits    
    
    
    MT @mobile_movement How many of you use your mobile phones to read? 2G networks connect ppl to <1000 ebooks for free: http://ow.ly/kDkub     
    
    
    Hugely humbled by this great piece from @Jazi_eu about their visit to our #ghana office & kindle projects. http://bit.ly/131IyMi . Thanks!    
    
    
    More reading in #Africa: #booksforall comes to Kenyan HIV/AIDS Orphans http://shar.es/lhsQE .    
    
    
    #Booksforall hellos 2 Suzy Peacock Memorial Secondary School & Christian Relief Fund. #FridayLove 4 the work they do http://shar.es/lhv7b     
    
    
    FRIDAY #quote: 'The direction in which #education starts a man will determine his future in life', by Plato. pic.twitter.com/SSsQhqBox2    
    
    
    New #Kindle project in Tanzania & we'll be at the World Economic Forum in SA. Stay close to our co-founders @davidrisherWR & @ColinMcElwee.    
    
    
    Proud to be working with the Nelson Mandela Institue on our upcoming Tanzania e-reader launch. @EcoLabArusha http://arushalivinglab.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    Have you heard? The Prime Minister & the Minister of Education of Tanzania will be attending our next #kindle launch. #bookforall going big.    
    
    
    We're in schools in Kenya, Tanzania and Zimbabwe this week launching new projects and visiting current ones. Stay close for the details.    
    
    
    Our new project in Tanzania is managed w/ help of masters & PHD students from Nelson Mandela Institute. #ICTStudy http://arushalivinglab.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    We're thrilled to be one of the winners of this year's Innovations in Reading Prizes by @nationalbook. http://bit.ly/aU91Te     
    
    
    Thanks @POETSorg! We're honored to be winners with @CityNational @LtlFreeLibrary @findtheuni @UpriseBooks. #readingrevolution    
    
    
    MUST READ on @GSMAm4d: An Opportunity for Mobile Operators to Promote Literacy & Improve Bottom Lines by @lizzywood. http://ow.ly/kMesv     
    
    
    V. Cool! Etisalat partners with @biNuMobile  to give subscribers 10 times faster browsing experience in #Nigeria. http://www.360nobs.com/2013/05/etisalat-partners-with-binu-to-give-subscribers-10-times-faster-browsing-experience/comment-page-1/ …    
    
    
    The Leaders of Tomorrow! Nambala & Nganana Primary students in Tanzania getting ready for the e-reader launch. PHOTO: http://twitter.com/worldreaders/status/332566897155518465/photo/1pic.twitter.com/EIRO85tTkh     
    
    
    Leaders of Tomorrow! Nambala & Nganana Primary students in Tanzania getting ready for the e-reader launch. PHOTO: pic.twitter.com/29KOV629hZ    
    
    
    Key report on Africa progress launched by Kofi Annan, @CarolineKende. Available on WR Mobile worldwide. Congrats! pic.twitter.com/IaQBlv0FS6.    
    
    
    Thats right @ColinMcElwee! We're moving south in our effort to make #booksforall a reality. How was your meeting with Pravim Gordham?    
    
    
    Something BIG just happened on Friday! E-reader launch in Tanzania. See the pictures here: http://on.fb.me/10l7YV6     
    
    
    The Prime Minister of Tanzania backs recent e-reader launch in Arusha & endorses more projects to come! @dailynewstz http://bit.ly/12tbdZD     
    
    
    Our very own @DanieZacarias was on the radio in Zimbabwe talking about Worldreader Mobile & our e-reader projects. http://fb.me/QY40rTfU     
    
    
    Thanks for the article about our book app - Worldreader Mobile @Luludotcom! We truly appreciate it. #ReadingRevolution is happening!    
    
    
    MT @i_am_TRANCE95: "@DanieZacarias I must tell you that I've gained alot from #WorldReader #App on #biNu. Keep it up!" Thx!    
    
    
    Tanzania's PM on the value of #booksforall program launched w/ Nelson Mandela Institute: http://dailynews.co.tz/index.php/local-news/17349-pm-unveils-pioneer-e-book-library … via @dailynewstz    
    
    
    Kofi Annan: Unprecedented opportunity to use #Africa's vast resource wealth & lift millions out of poverty http://nyti.ms/10tYrZ0     
    
    
    .@SALVEint 1st ebook read by kids @ #Tanzania launch: Kanuki, story abt a giraffe w/ a short neck, in Kiswahili http://ow.ly/kYANT     
    
    
    Mobile operators in emerging economies in a unique position to promote #education #literacy. @lizzywood explains http://ow.ly/kYCJh  #ICT    
    
    
    *The real opportunity in 
Africa is the youth.*~ Arif M. Naqvi, co-chair, World Economic 
Forum on Africa http://bit.ly/128s0kf  #wefafrica    
    
    
    MT @VUSaskia Worldreader brengt via gsm-applicatie meer dan 1000 boeken naar Derde wereld. Via @datanews_nl http://ow.ly/l0TxW     
    
    
    Reading on Worldreader Mobile via #binu app? Check out the Africa Progress Report, recently launched by Kofi Annan.  #wefafrica    
    
    
    The Girl Who Will Teach Tanzania to Read http://shar.es/Z3NBy . #inspiration in #Africa!    
    
    
    Merci beaucoup, @morganetual. Ping us if you have any additional questions or continue to write about digital reading trends in Africa.    
    
    
    .@TechnoMagZw - Thx for the tweets.  Worldreader's @NadjaBoz & @RothwellSmith are the King George launch, if you have questions.    
    
    
    Thx for the post, @WebTrendsNG. We'll update you when we have more news to share about #booksforall in Nigeria!    
    
    
    Congrats #booksforall partner @pubslush on the @aliberlinski debut book! http://amzn.to/10mrFMn     
    
    
    Should students be given laptops or e-readers in Kenya? http://www.businessdailyafrica.com/Should-students-be-given-laptops-or-e-readers/-/1248928/1853674/-/5tj65b/-/index.html … via @BD_Africa    
    
    
    Big #Booksforall thank you to @nationalbook for selecting us for the #InnovationInReading. We're honored & humbled. http://bit.ly/10B8xX5     
    
    
    Congratulations to fellow @nationalbook award winners: @CityNational @LtlFreeLibrary @findtheuni @UpriseBooks. #innovation #reading    
    
    
    SNEAK PEEK: We launched our first ever #Kindle program in Zimbabwe yesterday at a very special school. More to come. pic.twitter.com/6CdnFVPkPa    
    
    
    Kids on Zimbabwe’s fringe love ebooks, too http://shar.es/ZvHPo...Yes , we just launched in Zimbabwe! #booksforall    
    
    
    Low reading culture threatens country’s literacy rate ~ Zimbabwe Minister of Ed. http://j.mp/10y0HBz  via @ChronicleZim    
    
    
    Thank you kindly @pubslush. Right back at you #FF    
    
    
    Thank you @judyannetM. We intend to ...one school at a time!    
    
    
    How's this for cool: #booksforall in Ghana, Kenya, Uganda, Tanzania, Rwanda & as of this week...Zimbabwe, too http://j.mp/10xykn9 .    
    
    
    Love it! MT @GSMA_mEducation Literacy through Mobile Phones in #Afghanistan http://ow.ly/l7KgG  #mLearning #edchat #edtech #ict4e #ict4d    
    
    
    Ahmad Shafi talks abt literacy via mobile phones http://ow.ly/l7KgG . This may help, too #booksforall #binu app http://j.mp/10D2rFq .    
    
    
    NEW POST: Going Public-On working with Governments to Achieve Scale by co-founder @davidrisherWR http://bit.ly/11STZcT .    
    
    
    Worldreader Kit: out-of-box, easy-to-launch reading program designed to have an immediate impact & improve literacy. http://bit.ly/11STZcT     
    
    
    Why working with governments & private sector is key to #booksforall. A must read by co-founder @davidrisherWR. http://bit.ly/11STZcT     
    
    
    Looking for your next read? Check out WR partner @pubslush first book Beautiful Mess by @aliberlinski http://amzn.to/10mrFMn .    
    
    
    Ready, Set...Pull out that pocket of change. Coins for #booksforall starts June 1! http://shar.es/ZkbkP . Please RT!    
    
    
    Hi @pjhay12. See that you're reading a lot on the @worldreaders @biNuMobile app. Way to go! Which book do you like the most?    
    
    
    @Mbwana it was very nice to meet you today! We learned so much from you about the Africa Tech landscape. Come see us soon!    
    
    
    @ciie_boston Thank you, we're so happy to be in Zimbabwe!    
    
    
    Coins for Books. Support #booksforall by donating your change via a @coinstar kiosk thx to @cmcfund starting June 1. http://shar.es/ZkbkP     
    
    
    BIG NEWS: @FCBarcelona Midfielder Alex Song joins #booksforall to fight illiteracy worldwide. Details here: http://bit.ly/18ul84H .    
    
    
    He's got 27 siblings, is a midfielder @FCBarcelona, believes #reading improves the world & is now our ambassador-Who? http://bit.ly/18ul84H     
    
    
    MUST WATCH: Behind scenes w/ @songalexandre @SkySports. @FCBarcelona midfielder wants to give back via #booksforall. http://bit.ly/16kFvnz     
    
    
    Have you heard @kenyanpundit? We've digitized 500 Kenyan books & have deployed e-readers in 25 schools in Kenya. More-http://bit.ly/17zSmlc     
    
    
    Thx @umutonidarla for the mention. U may also like this: 500 Kenyan books digitized, e-readers in 25 Kenyan schools: http://bit.ly/13WU7pq     
    
    
    @NathanDetroitEd Thx for reaching out. You'll find more info at http://www.worldreader.org , or eml us your questions at info@worldreader.org.    
    
    
    Thanks @FaturotiK for spreading the word about the #booksforall app. You'll also find other science books there, too. cc: @biNuMobile    
    
    
    Getting close to 5,000 followers! Please RT & help us cross this big milestone. #booksforall love to you all. THANK YOU!    
    
    
    Nice job @AtomAdeyemi! You finished another book on Worldreader Mobile via @biNuMobile. How many have you read on your mobile phone?    
    
    
    Thanks for the follow back @GCE_US! We admire your mission to provide quality education for all children.    
    
    
    Thx @OurVillageIs for this: 'Like' #worldreader on Facebook http://on.fb.me/TPUTLO  Worldreader gets eBooks to children in developing nations    
    
    
    Senator @DavidColtart, Minister of Education in #Zimbabwe, on our recent e-reader launch. http://davidcoltart.com/?p=5837 . #Booksforall is growing!    
    
    
    In June, donate your coins & change lives. Thx to @cmcfund via @coinstar kiosks you can help us send books to Africa http://shar.es/ZkbkP .    
    
    
    A beautiful #quote to make your Wednesday even better. pic.twitter.com/LL6q501RfD    
    
    
    Thank you @Hesperian! Happy 40th Anniversary to #wherethereisnodoctor. #booksforall excited abt our partnership! #lookingahead    
    
    
    You're going to love this: Hesperian's Where There Is No Doctor now free for kids & families. #booksforall http://shar.es/wbRTC .    
    
    
    Cool! @LUISENRIQUE21 supports @Swim4G effort to swim across straight of Gibralter for #bookforall. PIC: pic.twitter.com/w6oUhFEhBv.    
    
    
    Ready, Set...Pull out that pocket of change. Coins for #booksforall via @coinstar machines starts today! http://j.mp/17IQx6C     
    
    
    Team @Swim4G is 3/4 of way to raising $100K for #bookforall by swimming from Europe to Africa. We're so impressed! http://bit.ly/X8ccg4     
    
    
    Got change? Want to help kids fall in love with reading? Donate to Worldreader via @coinstar machines Today. http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    A #booksforall Kit: A promise of reading packed up in a box! But…What’s a Kit? And, how can partners get them? http://shar.es/wcEWQ     
    
    
    Thx for the tip, @carlawellington. cc: @lizzywood on this. Elizabeth have you of http://monkeytailsbooks.com ?    
    
    
    *Got a little change in my pocket going jingle lingle ling*...Well, then, head to a @coinstar machine & do this http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    .@mwebafrica! We provide #bookforall via ereaders & mobile phones. Our book app has 1/2 MILLION active readers. http://bit.ly/Xlkgdz     
    
    
    Muchas gracias @conchibadillo por apoyar a @Swim4G y a #bookforall.    
    
    
    Muchas gracias Mireia por vuestro apoyo! @miss_belmont @Swim4G    
    
    
    During the entire month of June you can donate your change to Worldreader via a @coinstar kiosk near u. Details here: http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    Wondering how to bring an e-reader program to your school? It's called Worldreader Kits. Read about it here -->http://bit.ly/186DcoT     
    
    
    We are 5,000 times thankful to have all of you as our followers. THANK YOU! pic.twitter.com/CP1lCjz51V    
    
    
    Got change? Follow Erica's lead. Take your coins to a Coinstar machine and help kids fall in love with reading. pic.twitter.com/pEaF20QmdQ    
    
    
    We're looking for an Education Specialist in #Ghana! Want to apply or know someone that would interested? Details: http://bit.ly/15R76sf     
    
    
    SUPER DATA by @GSMAm4d: Between 2011 and 2012 over 400 million #mobile connections were made in the developing world. http://ow.ly/lJ6Ir     
    
    
    "Why I am investing my time in education." A woman in Tanzania rallies her community for schools. http://bit.ly/1693Jxv  @TheCitizenTZ    
    
    
    Thank you @RafaelNadal for supporting @Swim4G & Worldreader. Your support will help provide even more books to kids in Africa! #inspiration    
    
    
    Look @usainbolt-@RafaelNadal is supporting @Swim4G & helping kids in Africa fall in love with reading. Will you join? pic.twitter.com/wimSNUc75i    
    
    
    Superstar @RafaelNadal supports @Swim4G so that kids in Africa get books they need! @Shakira will you join Rafa? pic.twitter.com/wimSNUc75i    
    
    
    #booksforall now in South Africa & Malawi! The reading revolution is spreading fast. http://j.mp/1bwhMxK     
    
    
    If you have any #booksforall questions, find @blaqhaq at #LibraryBox @PirateBoxCamp in #Berlin or ping us here.    
    
    
    Spread #booklove. Donate spare change to #booksforall via @cmcfund. Super easy: http://j.mp/17IQx6C . Please retweet.    
    
    
    Come #volunteer in #Ghana with us and help make a difference in many children's lives. http://on.fb.me/PItCLb . pic.twitter.com/YzK0BcbtIV    
    
    
    @drmarobi Hi Dr. Mary. You can find more info here about our Volunteer Reading Program. http://bit.ly/11KkVIL  Thanks for your interest!    
    
    
    Win a volunteer vacation with us this summer thanks to @Opodo_UK & @KLM. Enter sweepstakes here: http://ow.ly/m08ky .    
    
    
    Help kids fall in love with reading. Make a #booksforall difference right now! @cmcfund, @coinstar & this: http://j.mp/17IQx6C     
    
    
    Here's how Lisa joined the #booksforall #readingrevolution http://j.mp/11Rwvlw  Honoring kids like her today #AfricanChild.    
    
    
    Tanzania: Where a girl, a prime minister & the fight against illiteracy meet. via @ColinMcElwee & @GPforEducation http://j.mp/13NMAsk     
    
    
    10 Benefits of Reading: Why You Should Read Every Day http://www.lifehack.org/articles/lifestyle/10-benefits-reading-why-you-should-read-everyday.html … via @lifehackorg    
    
    
    Thank you so much @CLeboffe for supporting Worldreader and the @Swim4G team. We truly appreciate your generous donation. #bookforall    
    
    
    Where does social innovation & literacy cross? Tanzania. New blog by @ColinMcElwee @GPforEducation http://j.mp/13NMAsk  #AfricanChild    
    
    
    Live the magic of a Worldreader Kit Launch. Follow @kimeejohnson this week as she reports live from #Uganda. DAY 1: http://bit.ly/13YvkPD .    
    
    
    Would you like to spend a week in Ghana where you can mentor children? Win a volunteer trip with us. Participate now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz     
    
    
    Wow! @HYFR_tz_Rusty, you're on a #booksforall reading streak! How do you like the science books on @biNuMobile Worldreader Mobile app?    
    
    
    Spread #booklove in June. Donate spare change to Worldreader via a @coinstar machine near you. Super easy: http://j.mp/17IQx6C . Pls RT.    
    
    
    What happens when a young girl & a prime minister stand for literacy? @davidrisherWR blogs @HuffPostImpact http://huff.to/19OIZPF     
    
    
    VIDEO: e-reader launch at King George VI school in #Bulawayo #Zimbabwe. Made by school, music by students. MUST SEE. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HevF0YL4xy8&feature=youtu.be …    
    
    
    Spend a week in Ghana mentoring children. Win a volunteer trip with us thanks to @Opodo_UK and @KLM. Participate now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz     
    
    
    Hey @bettrvolunteer. Aptitude, drive & motivation is what we look for. See this and let us know if you have Qs. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/heres-your-chance-change-a-life-in-ghana/ …    
    
    
    Whoa! @Swim4G raised $80K so far for #booksforall. You can fundraise to change the lives of kids in Africa too. http://www.worldreader.org/support-us/get-involved-2/ …    
    
    
    Brown Bag session on our work in Kenya led by Worldreader Operations Manager @jmwachi happening now in #BCN office. pic.twitter.com/LAkWYmkt2F    
    
    
    "Each child in our program in Kisumu #Kenya has 160 e-books to themselves," @jmwachi at Brown Bag session happening now. ICT changing lives.    
    
    
    Country Director Michael Sam now leading a session on impact of our #Kindle programs in #Ghana. pic.twitter.com/Y0a3en5xBi    
    
    
    "The device will change but what we are doing is eternal. We are putting knowledge into hands." @davidrisherWR pic.twitter.com/gRPG2HwiTk    
    
    
    Thank you @KeriannePayne for supporting @Swim4G and #bookforall! You're all role models to follow.    
    
    
    Kindle cases that help kids in #Africa get books. Check it out @ebookfriendly: http://www.worldreader.org/support-us/ . PIC: pic.twitter.com/y9JCiyDwve    
    
    
    STAT by @USAID: There would be a 12% drop in #globalpoverty if all students in low-income countries left school with basic reading skills.    
    
    
    Hey @BldgTomorrow! We like what your're about. We have two #Kindle school programs in Uganda. See here: http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/our-projects/ …    
    
    
    Join international authors & publishers @sleeperspublish to help children/families in Africa fall in love w/ reading. http://www.worldreader.org/partner-with-us/for-authors-publishers/ …    
    
    
    We're excited too @BookLoversMark: "Black Letter Media partners with Worldreader." http://ow.ly/mhs6E     
    
    
    Got change? Want to help kids fall in love with reading? Donate to Worldreader via @coinstar machines in the US. http://bit.ly/coinsforgood     
    
    
    GET THIS: @Swim4G is swimming from Gibraltar to Africa & they've raised 90K for books. Help them get to 100K. Donate: http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    Great @ebookfriendly! Let us know if you need more info. Thank you.    
    
    
    Thank you @SVPSeattle for featuring @davidrisherWR. A truly personal account of the foundations of #booksforall. http://bit.ly/19D8TXw     
    
    
    Come and change lives this summer by mentoring children in our ereader programs. Participate in our sweepstakes now: http://ow.ly/m6Jlz .    
    
    
    NEWS: Thanks to a partnership w/ @DwankhoziHope we launched the first e-reader program in Zambia. #bookschanginglives pic.twitter.com/wtizKNwvBg    
    
    
    Today is the last chance to win an all paid volunteer trip to #Ghana with us. Don't miss this opportunity. Enter now: http://ow.ly/mt1SO     
    
    
    Countdown begins! @Swim4G is 5 days away from crossing strait of Gibraltar for #booksforall. Talk about #inspiring! http://owswimming.com/     
    
    
    Empowering children and families with knowledge is our passion & now we're doing it in #Zambia with @DwankhoziHope: http://bit.ly/11UvZni .    
    
    
    Thanks very much @Hamomi. We're thrilled to be in Zambia and partnering with @DwankhoziHope.    
    
    
    "You've awakened the thirst for knowledge in them!" @KilgorisProject co-founder Caren McCormack says to WR staff. pic.twitter.com/r0rdn9Gj0g    
    
    
    Juliana Rotich: Meet @brcknet, Internet access built for #Africa on @tedtalks http://bit.ly/17VJLd5     
    
    
    We have a winner for our Travel for Books Sweepstakes! See more at: http://bit.ly/12GuXqt     
    
    
    Thank you all for participating in the Travel for Books sweepstakes and special thanks to our partners @Opodo_UK and @KLM! #booksforall    
    
    
    MUST SEE: How Mobile Technology is Transforming Africa by @mtrends http://www.nyotamedia.com/how-mobile-technology-is-transforming-africa/ … #innovation #startups #education    
    
    
    How do you get kids to read more, better and for life? Here's one idea: http://j.mp/12f8P6C  http://shar.es/AtV8p     
    
    
    Wow! $100,000 raised for #booksforall. Swim strong @soozmoody, @mauprieto, @Swim4G. Cheering you on from BCN, SF & all over Africa!    
    
    
    #Kenya's Imbuko Primary School is off and running, Matt Chang tells us: http://j.mp/14PQlwP . #booklove pix: pic.twitter.com/94GNy9Y2jC    
    
    
    Team @Swim4G reached their $100K fundraising goal & are about to swim the strait of Gibraltar. Want to fundraise too? http://bit.ly/WoXcZx     
    
    
    Our @zevlowe is in Malawi leading a digital publishing workshop. Cool fact: we've helped digitize 1000 African books. http://www.worldreader.org/our-books/     
    
    
    Thanks for the kind words @Outcastotter! We like what you are about too. Have a great weekend.    
    
    
    Great @HileDesmond. We're glad you enjoyed reading *The Girl with the Magic Hands*. What are you reading now on #worldreadermobile?    
    
    
    The weekend is upon us. Enjoy it everyone and we hope you'll be doing some of this. #readtorelax pic.twitter.com/hG7Qh7cItn    
    
    
    Now anyone can help bring books to those that need them the most! It's called a Worldreader Kit. VIDEO: https://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=DXPb7exST2A ….    
    
    
    Thanks @engineer4change for believing in #booksforall. We appreciate your support. Have a great week!    
    
    
    In our latest blog post learn about Worldreader’s Out of Classroom Experience (OCE) reading program by @simplekay. http://bit.ly/1aRPUZ6 .    
    
    
    Her poems touched us all & now she's inspiring others to fall in love w/ books.Student Okanta Kate is changing lives: http://bit.ly/1aRPUZ6     
    
    
    There are over 10,429 books on Worldreader Mobile ready for you to read. Download it today! http://www.worldreader.org/what-we-do/worldreader-mobile/ … pic.twitter.com/bUgYHE3x2w    
    
    
    