Ron Burgendy covered Canadian curling on TV. Every single talking head seat is for sale to advertisers for the right price.    
    
    
    @chadstanton He's not an idiot, he's skilled in the soundbyte seeding &knows he'll be the talk of the town. I quote him & you got cranky.    
    
    
    @gtbernstein we're aware. @adtothebone showed us. :)    
    
    
    @kidsleepys My bad. I forgot to have my coffee break.    
    
    
    @chadstanton Hopefully he'll save Adidas from doing dumb stuff like: http://adland.tv/content/jeremy-scott-shoes-not-racist-just-inspired-my-pet-monster …   we KNOW they're brave enough to try new things    
    
    
    @jetpacks I know. @kidsleepy already slapped my typo-ing hands.    
    
    
    @chadstanton I'm sure I will. The tone seems to have been the same ever since Absolut teamed up with him and Be Kanye in '08    
    
    
    @chadstanton yes, it might have been, but that's also part of Jeremy Scott's "thing". The pop-irony design and oopsie-controversy.    
    
    
    @chadstanton Well, Ima let you finish, but Kanye is his own meme-legend long before she was ;)    
    
    
    @hiballenergy We drink way more than you supply. pls supply more. :P @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @chadstanton Now THIS gets interesting, are they teaming with Kanye for his skillz or with Kanye for magic attracting press talent?    
    
    
    @chadstanton :D I mean, is his talent to be the one who attracts press by name alone, or do they want him for product development?    
    
    
    @chadstanton .. it gets a bit weird when Kanye (or any other artist) is used like a half-naked lady draped on a car in the 1950s.    
    
    
    @chadstanton Probably.    
    
    
    @chadstanton Yeah, that's what I always wonder about. If the creative control is limited to "smile for the cameras" it's a stinky deal.    
    
    
    @chadstanton Hmm. I recall dressing my baby girl in baby phat jeans despite the toddler-unfriendly cut. I am a sucker.    
    
    
    @chadstanton (that brain-jump came from "phat" obviously)    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional [Adland is currently on a forced coffee-break due to too many typos. Please leave your tweet after the beep]    
    
    
    @its_elliott We're good. Real good. @kidsleepys @hiballenergy    
    
    
    @SocialHerwig heeey-o    
    
    
    @hiballenergy As the beancounter here, I have to say there has to Peach & Wild Berry involved or no deal.  @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor That does not help! @babiejenks    
    
    
    @luckthelady ooh le Monde. I can picture the handwaving coffee-fueled cigarette scented little debates going on in Cafés all over Paris now.    
    
    
    Is this even real? Am I in a Mad magazine universe? RT @JRMcGrail: Worst Person in the World. pic.twitter.com/bJgC8glwfW    
    
    
    @SimonJamesLee1 We're aware: https://twitter.com/adland/status/406831500315721728 … @cindygallop    
    
    
    @allygreer Sure, sure. But the NYP thought this was a great headline. That. @JRMcGrail    
    
    
    @allygreer Yep yep. Godawful headlines. @JRMcGrail    
    
    
    @luckthelady :)    
    
    
    I'm signing all my secret santa packages "from Diane in 7A"    
    
    
    Interesting! RT @AndrewGirdwood: Bug or feature? This is how you can get the traffic stats for your Google+ profile http://j.mp/INGjre     
    
    
    No RT @KimBhasin: Guess what today is? http://twitpic.com/dd1nau     
    
    
    @KimBhasin *shoots Kim with Nerf-dart*    
    
    
    The best ad BIC pens made all year. Wait for the signoff. pic.twitter.com/FTlLG89EYN    
    
    
    http://present.knowledgevision.com/account/ftc/link/Live_Webcast … FTC Should Ensure That Online ‘Sponsored Content’ Is Clearly Identified as What It Is: Advertising (Live workshop)    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets I thought I couldn't hate them more. I was wrong.    
    
    
    @bicpens look what your mates in the Uk did https://twitter.com/adland/status/408305876429045760 …    
    
    
    @kidsleepys DAMMIT I FELL FOR IT YOU BASTARD    
    
    
    Pass over here, I'll take care of them... RT @withfilm: awww man these are addictive.  gonna have the jitters soon pic.twitter.com/4xfE78Q9K9    
    
    
    @deeped hang in there    
    
    
    @deeped http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_DJn8fkKa8E#t=29 …    
    
    
    @deeped vice VD    
    
    
    Freebie: Hey advertisers.. wanna know what really builds your brand? The ambassador to the consumer? Wanna know what it is? Your product.    
    
    
    So you go right ahead and concentrate on making good product™ and we'll make sure people know that you have good product™. Mmmm'k?    
    
    
    Google is your friend.

Your only friend.    
    
    
    All super bowl ad spots have been sold out. Expect the usual groinkicking, football referensing, puppet & celebrity containing ads.    
    
    
    @fairuse TOO LATE there's a few.    
    
    
    @fairuse uh-oh.    
    
    
    Borrowed interest galore RT @CommArts Artworks & artists are increasingly becoming elements of advertising campaigns http://goo.gl/5r3XLd     
    
    
    @ShireenDew we can but hope *prays* @theseaguy    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM Please tell me they're feeding you with beers @mccannmcr    
    
    
    @tblockley rly ? @Spitfire  ? HOLD THE DOOR I'M JOINING YOU @BOC_ATM @McCannMcr    
    
    
    @tblockley the dissapoint on my face when I found @Spitfire wasn't the beer. @BOC_ATM @McCannMcr    
    
    
    @tblockley Of course it's the twitter apps fault @BOC_ATM @McCannMcr you see @spitfireale can only make everything and you awesome.    
    
    
    @tblockley @BOC_ATM The brewery doesn't know it (nor care afaik) but Bishops Finger is the official Adland.tv beer @spitfireale    
    
    
    @gtbernstein talking animal babies @DanGoldgeier    
    
    
    @tblockley This is the superbowl couple years ago @BOC_ATM @spitfireale pic.twitter.com/gcg9qLf4ek    
    
    
    @ShepherdNeame Woot! That's awesome. I had to fly to Boston carrying Bishops for our US based writers years ago. We take this seriously. ;)    
    
    
    @ShepherdNeame "Ma'am, what's in the suitcase?" "Lots of proper beer, sir. Lots of proper beer." "Well then carry on."    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets :) Not sure if they were "traditionalist" but some people said coined the term "politically correct taliban" over that    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets also, the girl behind Lucia is dressed as a stjärngosse = boy outfit :) Headline:" let the kids wear their favorite .."    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets No. Not really. It's a bit odd. Like putting on a nativity play and having Maria played by a boy and a girl play Joseph.    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets But as long as I get to torture the world with Lucia videos, I'm happy to write about it. :P    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets That's it. COMMENCE LUCIA VIDEO TORTURE https://www.google.com/url?sa=t&rct=j&q=&esrc=s&source=web&cd=7&sqi=2&ved=0CFMQtwIwBg&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DViPj_MsU3hg&ei=urCgUp_VD4nqoASmw4HQDQ&usg=AFQjCNH7q0AMvwIl8_JMnNV8_vgMOt8jwg&sig2=1tPfwc0OTqHQg_R1lZT9jQ&bvm=bv.57604443,d.cGU …    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets teh kyoot, right? It's the awesome.    
    
    
    These days I only visit my personal email inbox to unubscribe from spam and bacn    
    
    
    @strawberrycough Is it even trademarked? No reason to enforce something that was never ™:ed to begin with. @griner @realjohngreen    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets Yep. I hear that. First Lucia my girl was a gingerbread and I was weeping at their wee singing. Or "singing".    
    
    
    @griner Yeah halfway through it, I wouldn't be trademarking that either. @strawberrycough @realjohngreen    
    
    
    @kidsleepys They're always one step behind. These days, kids aren't sharing like they used to.    
    
    
    I wonder what #Nissan will make of the story of man being arrested for charing his LEAF while taking tennis lessons http://abcnews.go.com/Business/ga-man-arrested-charging-electric-car-local-middle/story?id=21098590 …    
    
    
    An icon has passed. RIP Nelson Mandela. Throwback: The Specials AKA "Free Nelson Mandela" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AgcTvoWjZJU …    
    
    
    @iboy that song is going to stick to your brain for the rest of the day, you know.    
    
    
    @LauraAmyPell You get a gold star for that.    
    
    
    David Lowery: Silicon Valley must be stopped, or creativity will be destroyed http://www.salon.com/2013/12/04/david_lowery_silicon_valley_must_be_stopped_or_creativity_will_be_destroyed/ …    
    
    
    @fairuse Source?    
    
    
    @kidsleepys I'm still not seeing how labels made the government mandated lets make webcasting popular unless I get a source @fairuse    
    
    
    @fairuse I'm having large problems deciphering what you're saying this evening.    
    
    
    @fairuse 'K    
    
    
    @_Baylink I thought maybe that was it, but he said was labels not government mandate and that's where I got lost. @fairuse    
    
    
    @fairuse Now you're losing me again. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @fairuse Did labels? @_Baylink    
    
    
    @fairuse See, I don't know this, which is why I asked for a source so I may read that RIAA had major input. Link? @_Baylink    
    
    
    @fairuse What game? Which hearings? @_Baylink    
    
    
    @fairuse Peace out guys, I gotta get a few zzz's while I have a shot at it still. @_Baylink    
    
    
    @fairuse If I'm following you, you're saying the opposite of what Lowery is saying. I'm asking you to back up what you're saying.    
    
    
    I've only sworn 6 times on Twitter in languages Santa speaks, so I'm on Santa's nice list. YAY! ->  http://socialsanta.co/     
    
    
    http://illusionofmore.com/adlandtv-schools-goldieblox/ … "AdlandTV Schools GoldieBlox" - thanks @DavidLNewhoff    
    
    
    @MissParkerMarie You're making it WORSE now, naughty.    
    
    
    @MissParkerMarie You know, the reason santa is so jolly is because he knows where all the naughty girls live.    
    
    
    "No one is born hating another person, for the color of their skin" Nelson Mandela CBS 2006 & in our archive http://adland.tv/commercials/cbs-cares-nelson-mandela-2006-30-usa …    
    
    
    SANTA IS REAL (at least we can tell the kids that with http://www.kringlapp.com  - the magic santa app, all proceeds go to charity)    
    
    
    http://adage.com/article/guest-columnists/goldiblox-v-beastie-boys-marketers-learn/245538 … What we can learn from Goldieblox kerfluffle - legal commentary by @briheidelberger via @adage    
    
    
    This is suddenly getting RTed. Yo, if I don't see @Sionemaraschino doing the step in a super bowl ad, Ima be pissed. https://twitter.com/adland/status/380057174908469249 …    
    
    
    @its_elliott what the actual f*ck? @The_RGA @kidsleepys @SpaghettiOs    
    
    
    So many wrongs. RT @SpaghettiOs: Take a moment to remember #PearlHarbor with us. http://twitter.com/SpaghettiOs/status/409162874184298496/photo/1pic.twitter.com/vHSrLQewZn     
    
    
    It's like...... brands are trolling us now, aren't they?    
    
    
    @leelubarsky YESSSSSSS, & I thought we all signed off on this when mama taught us to be decent people.    
    
    
    @MaryToves Did you know I saved 100% on stress by not giving a fuck?    
    
    
    @MaryToves :D wait hang on that was ajoke, it sortof seemed like an answer to, oh never mind. *buys next round of scotch*    
    
    
    @leelubarsky Oh yeah. The big fat "DO NOT CROSS" line people seem to be blind to recently. Yikes.    
    
    
    Yes! @ltlblkdress It's disturbing. "Real Time Marketing" does not mean jump on all breaking news of deaths & celebrate tragedy @leelubarsky    
    
    
    @MaryToves Good. But it helps to have scotch. Truuuuust me.    
    
    
    You winz the internet RT @DanGoldgeier: @kidsleepys This is a day that will live in @spaghettiOs infamy.    
    
    
    @leelubarsky That white paper will have Doge on the cover. @ltlblkdress    
    
    
    Christmas came early: Spaghetti-O's makes a Pearl Harbor tweet. | adland.tv http://po.st/XdHeCg  via @adland    
    
    
    @richard_larue I'm not so sure people gawking at the traffic accident is a major win @SpaghettiOs    
    
    
    @glukkake I'm putting my money on this is happening because eggnog @Jeevesmeister    
    
    
    #anotherbrandtoavoid RT @GrodieApeman: Ron Burgundy Ben & Jerry's? Sweet Jesus let's take it down a notch.    
    
    
    @richard_larue #trollingforsales is an interesting strategy @SpaghettiOs @StephenAtHome @jimmykimmel @jimmyfallon    
    
    
    Which will trend first, spaghettios or misspelled spagettios?    
    
    
    @PixieSlasher I have nothing to offer but blood, toil, tears and sweat @richard_larue @SpaghettiOs @StephenAtHome @jimmykimmel @jimmyfallon    
    
    
    @MaryToves Or Spagetthoes. Foodies with cheap pasta-lust late nights when they're alone.....    
    
    
    @fairuse interesting, thanks.    
    
    
    http://adage.com/article/digital/facebook-admits-organic-reach-brand-posts-dipping/245530/?utm_source=buffer&utm_campaign=Buffer&utm_content=bufferd1f1e&utm_medium=twitter … 

Facebook Admits Organic Reach Is Falling Short, Urges Marketers to Buy Ads - read: they're hiding you    
    
    
    @jfouts I think small businesses will find G+ more useful to them soon.    
    
    
    Adland will go offline for a moment in order to move servers. Enjoy your Saturday!    
    
    
    @jfouts Good idea.    
    
    
    @jfouts I do find G+ userfriendly but archaic in that I have to have a personal acct when really I just want the brand account.    
    
    
    @jfouts As a result nearly 5000 people follow my personal account and everyone ignores the brand account actually used.    
    
    
    @jfouts send us the link when you're done.    
    
    
    @jfouts Yes, I've noticed. I tried to teach a friend running a small business. The constant updates on the g+ app was throwing him off.    
    
    
    @jfouts If there was a away I could move these people to my brand account, I would be happy.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor tx, fingers crossed and pray plz :P    
    
    
    @jfouts I do that on a regular basis. It's practically the only thing my personal account has ever said in public.    
    
    
    @jfouts :) Yeah, I do on occasion, I have made an effort to do it more often now (every time I post an animated gif joke). It's catching on.    
    
    
    @jfouts .. and I circle everyone back so I can see what my readers are sharing. :)    
    
    
    @collierplus Don't I know you guys? I know you guys. Hi guys.    
    
    
    Stocking stuffer tip! The #agencylife shirts come with built in (beer) bottle openers. http://adland.spreadshirt.com/  - Verrrrry practical.    
    
    
    @jmitchem it's not the writing when drunk that's hard, it's the deciphering it when sober    
    
    
    @patricenatalie Yeah that made me jelly too. I miss korean bbq haven't had a good one in years. @lukashMAYYN    
    
    
    @Jeevesmeister Two "Erik" Williamson in Gotheburg, neither called Erik as their first name. #bullshitstory http://www.birthday.se/sok/?f=Erik&l=Williamson&c=G%F6teborg …    
    
    
    @Jeevesmeister OH LOLZA I've been reading so many fawning bitcoin stories lately I didn't spot it being snark.    
    
    
    @Jeevesmeister There was a very low coffee-level over here. Yes. That's it. Not enough coffee......    
    
    
    @adtothebone Not very often though.    
    
    
    OH: "I'm looking at peoples linkedin's to see what kind of bullshit they're spewing"    
    
    
    Yes @themoonunitHQ & I like the "I worked at X agency as writer/AD", while job lasted 2 months during summer in college. YOU WERE AN INTERN.    
    
    
    New ECD announcement in inbox.That aAd agency now has A handful of ECD's, a dozen CD's, a couple of GCD's and nobody else. #titleinflation    
    
    
    @ArikSharon oh snap.    
    
    
    @JonnyStark HA! That's a good one. :)    
    
    
    @JGNapurano Is it just me or did that sound like an Upworthy style title? @kidsleepys @adage    
    
    
    Trending prediction #funeralselfie    
    
    
    @thebandfrom totally unrelated, I have a business project I need a fashion geeky smart partner in. You look like it. :-)    
    
    
    @_Baylink no idea... ?    
    
    
    Were gonna save the world with our food selfies , yo.    
    
    
    What @montiero has said at #aeasf is important. The whole creative class should look at what they're doing.    
    
    
    http://www.adweek.com/adfreak/beastie-boys-countersue-goldieblox-seeking-profits-earned-viral-girls-ad-154429 … Beastie Boys Countersue GoldieBlox - seeking profits earned off the viral ad. Ooops.    
    
    
    For the legal nerds http://www.scribd.com/doc/190846300/Beastie-Boys-Response-to-GoldieBlox … Beastie Boys countersues Goldieblox for acting intentionally with "oppression, fraud, and malice"    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Okay, just.. stooooop. Stop stop. Stop stop stop.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor ok, now breatheeeee....    
    
    
    Super bowl ad? RT @W2Optimism: This year feels like, as they say, a marathon that is ending with a sprint.    
    
    
    Stocking stuffer tip: http://www.theadpad.co.uk  - > pic.twitter.com/fsTIYTjMAC    
    
    
    Best thing I've read all day: "Remove typo's."    
    
    
    @snyggstyle Godspeed on your treasure hunt today.    
    
    
    @t5war "Mental" too.@sbadsgood    
    
    
    @snyggstyle Holy shit, that's awesomely freaky.    
    
    
    @jmitchem I kind of want that job.    
    
    
    This is epic. RT @jamesostafford: one for the #Bowie fans: pic.twitter.com/lUG961jhw8    
    
    
    @Elika It's gonna disrupt your head all the way to tomorrow morning, don't forget to drink water. ;)    
    
    
    @hotdogdynamite *hic* Best christmas miracle ever. More Eggnog?    
    
    
    & if you run after midnight ..it eats your feet RT @PSFK: Shoes created from living material regenerate themselves..  pic.twitter.com/ElKEc2q7my    
    
    
    Peace, yo. #fail  RT @WhiteHouse #GetCovered because your mom will have peace of mind. http://HealthCare.gov  , pic.twitter.com/xwBE8Hehco    
    
    
    is this a "your mom" joke?  RT @WhiteHouse #GetCovered because your mom will have peace of mind.  pic.twitter.com/xwBE8Hehco    
    
    
    @jmitchem *headbanging comeback* *AIR GUITAR* Oh yeaaaaaaaahhhh @WhiteHouse    
    
    
    @badtaglines I just said "your mom" in a tweet. It feels like I summoned you to follow me.    
    
    
    @badtaglines your bio, yo.    
    
    
    Hey look, it's Brazil! RT @we_love_ad:  Abandoned Places by Bart Synowiec | Toronto-based photographer Bart .. http://twitpic.com/dohl74     
    
    
    @LiamBradley I have a sudden urge to pinch your little rosy cheeks. @Skippy2204    
    
    
    @LiamBradley Please tell me this photo is going to go in your headshot-file. @Skippy2204    
    
    
    @FD There's also lipstick electric stun guns... #forreal @tim    
    
    
    Did YOU end up on @adweeks naughty or nice (ad) list? http://www.adweek.com/news/advertising-branding/nudds-naughty-and-nice-2013-video-154450 …    
    
    
    That "nutcracker" pun is putting you on my naughty list, @Nudd.    
    
    
    .@180LA Who is the guy in the back who seems to be worried that the ceiling is gonna cave in?    
    
    
    @nikkelin Jag sitter fortfarande och väntar på TV på nätet. Hört att ni var asbra. :)  @annatroberg    
    
    
    @delucare Give them an out. Like; pretend you're concerned you forgot to send first one, and resend. Or say "I forgot to mention X"...    
    
    
    @delucare :)    
    
    
    More tweeting madness: @stealingsand a.k.a Colleen favorited what @heytrace said (and she's protected) and I see it! #nopenopenope    
    
    
    .@180LA I think Charles is planning his escape route.    
    
    
    @a0k Dibs for "I bite"    
    
    
    @hollybrocks Sucks, don't it?    
    
    
    @hollybrocks Right? The layers of dumb go deep here.    
    
    
    @curlydena Love the cup!    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Well, to be fair, public tweeting isn't "safe" if you have a real stalker, obvs, but yes, it's creepy for opinionated folks...    
    
    
    @curlydena I have "D" earrings you would totally rock in.    
    
    
    @mikeharari No. In fact yo can be chief serious asshole if you play your cards right. @a0k    
    
    
    @snyggstyle You might need an assistant in a white lab coat. Call the missus.    
    
    
    @lpbiesty As @OneMinuteBriefs constantly proves, sometimes the simple fast ideas are the best ones.    
    
    
    @nudd my naughty list is the best list, it's where the booze is.    
    
    
    5 employees at Mother London lived without internet for a month and made a film about it.... that they put on the internet.    
    
    
    @stealingsand No, I can't see @heytrace replies, at least. I know she follows me and can see me though. And if you favorite her, I see it :(    
    
    
    heh, @kidsleepys I saw the London map moment in the Vimeo screenshot and decided I needn't visit my college years again.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys There are people who live without the internet right now. Maybe we should make a song about it. "Do they know there's internet?"    
    
    
    @ItsTheBrandi Far be it for me to guess their reasoning.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Live RAID /geekjoke    
    
    
    I am. Hold me. RT @W2Optimism: Be afraid. pic.twitter.com/bUFNdlwHDU    
    
    
    I love that guy. RT @adtothebone: Mel Blanc's marvelous tombstone. pic.twitter.com/b0meDfNDPP    
    
    
    http://adland.spreadshirt.com/brief-ladies-agencylife-A12472508/customize/color/2/customize/color/2 … On the first day of Xmas my CD gave to me... #agencylife pic.twitter.com/620PTRIC9U    
    
    
    Perfect want ad, seeks you, only with 7 years experience of HTML5 http://adland.spreadshirt.com/perfect-want-ad-agencylife-A12472414/customize/color/2 … now on t-shirts pic.twitter.com/VomNiSUEIG    
    
    
    @jimmy0x52 I did it for 20 years. Oh gawsh, I totally dated myself there. @verge    
    
    
        
    
    
    Beyoncé knows to zig when others zag. Instead of like Gaga promoting her new album, she just releases it to iTunes, & we all tweet about it.    
    
    
    @PlanBstudio Agreed.    
    
    
    @PlanBstudio It's called "climate change" now. #rebranding    
    
    
    @LeslieBAP note eyebrow-raising line; "obvious fair use and protected expression under the First Amendment" https://www.eff.org/deeplinks/2013/12/dancing-baby-files-opening-brief-dmca-abuse-appeal …    
    
    
    'Total Market' Gets Lots of Buzz, but Multicultural Agencies Will Suffer - Pepper Miller shoutouts #blacktwitter http://adage.com/article/the-big-tent/total-market-shoves-multicultural-agencies/245657 …    
    
    
    Is this an office or a really large game of RISK? RT @darrellwhitelaw "Artillery is the new Eames." - @jimschachterle pic.twitter.com/pdMLeIQVDC    
    
    
    .... there should be a comma before Batkid. I guess no kids are wishing to be grammar-nazis? pic.twitter.com/vVTYwnRYl9    
    
    
    @Saatchi_Norway Nicely done, boys. God Jul og Gott Nyt på er.    
    
    
    Some idiot scheduled a meeting with only the free coffee drinkers and "ooh great question!"-nodders. Less work than usual got done.    
    
    
    @spslferg They forgot to alert bagel-person!    
    
    
    @GoodChillHuntin *Booming God Voice* "It shall be so!" ... eh.. sorry, been dipping into the eggnog all day, *hic* @LiamLoanLack @Jcubed_    
    
    
    @jaredbkeller 'sup?    
    
    
    Beyoncé is everyones secret Santa. Well played, girl.    
    
    
    *roflmaiuw* RT @GooglesView: +15° 33' 54.3271, +80° 49' 48.5612 pic.twitter.com/lXRJBc5Kxi    
    
    
    I see that chelsea haircut in "Flawless" Beyoncé, and serenade you with: She was my skinhead girl... http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pE2eBU9jVfw …    
    
    
    Ow, now my ears hurt.    
    
    
    @ShadFiasco1017 Good luck mate. :)    
    
    
    @MissParkerMarie Did we cut bangs and get a dye-job? That looks nice. Suits you.    
    
    
    @johncarneyau Most people aren't that smart. All "pics" accounts are gearing up to sell tweets as adspace x to followers @Myrmecos    
    
    
    @johncarneyau YES, that bothers me almost as much. Grar! @MabandeOpenBeta @Myrmecos @Earth_Pics    
    
    
    @CopywriterKat He's a genius. @strawberrycough    
    
    
    "It's only advertising" they say, "It's not like we're curing cancer" - Can we PLEZ remember that and NOT work 30 hours straight? Ktxbai.    
    
    
    I hate when we can't take things at face value anymore.    
    
    
    @kenrearley This is in relation to a story unfolding now. It's not what it seems.    
    
    
    Indonesian copywriter dies after working three days straight. | adland.tv http://po.st/SY61pk  via @adland    
    
    
    There's something very wrong about a non-surgeon/life-saving job expecting you to be there 30 hours straight.    
    
    
    @aleixitu Yeah (considering how hard people work), but... why?    
    
    
    @kenrearley might take a while. Need proof. ;)    
    
    
    @aleixitu triple-rate after 6 PM would make meetings suddenly super-effective.    
    
    
    @CheyenneB ... in reality we spend our weekends at the office waiting for feedback and going back to our desks to just "try a few more"    
    
    
    @CheyenneB People need to say "your poor planning does not constitute my emergency". I'm told to re-do at 6PM what I turned in at 8AM.    
    
    
    @GzzAtmr Advertising business needs to be restructured, clearly. @aleixitu    
    
    
    @aleixitu Lets hope it's not all put on her for being ambitious and drinking too many red bulls.  @mitdoq    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Yep.  @CheyenneB    
    
    
    @BellHappe This is a disease in adland. Like a nick in a nylon stocking, it starts in one end and spreads all over the agency. Fire culprit.    
    
    
    @CheyenneB I walked out once, laughing, they forgot I was unpaid. They called me to come back the next week. @JoeyMotional    
    
    
    @GeorgeTakei BLESS TREKKIES @_Baylink    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional I was young and a hothead. Also, I was right. @CheyenneB    
    
    
    Lets all in adland take three days off, see family. Recalibrate what's important. RT @mitdoq: 30 hours of working and still going strooong.    
    
    
    @aleixitu Of course there is, but it's a strange biz. People work on rumors and handshakes instead of clear briefs & objectives @GzzAtmr    
    
    
    @DaveGian Daym. He was swell. And that's young. @MartinAgency @Adweek @mcmains1965    
    
    
    @mpawlo It was basically an infomercial for the NSA and journalism is officially dead.    
    
    
    @mpawlo See @yrindonesia timeline and their facebook and the other things we linked.    
    
    
    @LenKendall NO you are sadly misinformed and must now watch this, in full screen with NO LOOKING AWAY OR BLINKING http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=D8Ymd-OCucs …    
    
    
    @LenKendall Yeah she's 16. And the Royals song is going to compete with Moby's record in being used in ads. ;)    
    
    
    @LenKendall ps, you blinked.    
    
    
    @mpawlo Transcript of 60 minutes http://www.cbsnews.com/news/nsa-speaks-out-on-snowden-spying/ …    
    
    
    Don't Drink & Drive message from Kenya Breweries Ltd  - with a twist. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pl5LDx0pMGM …    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Are you wearing Lórèal?    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN You need to cut back on the rap-music, son.    
    
    
    @Drtmpkns I'm so glad at least it's just the fingers tweeting. @strawberrycough    
    
    
    @VenusBuzz are we having site issues?    
    
    
    @VenusBuzz Good good. We experienced a thick bump in traffic too.    
    
    
    OH: "He's a freelance Creative Director" "Oh, which ad agency is he from?" "He's never worked at an ad agency." #titleconfusion    
    
    
    Live in the UK? Your taxes are supporting piracy. | adland.tv http://po.st/N7YD1H  via @adland    
    
    
    Nutters! ;) RT @jessicakiang: I WANNA BE PART OF THE DANISH FILM CRITICS ASSOC. Stupid cool Danes. pic.twitter.com/V7DOfvXm09    
    
    
    @caff They're spoofing the Lars von Trier posters. I posted them a month or so ago on adland somewhere. And yes O-face has been done before.    
    
    
    @jessicakiang The pun is the worst. "De kommer til" (They are "coming" to the awards...)    
    
    
    @joelapompe aaah yes http://adland.tv/node/156111  @caff    
    
    
    @pascalrossini What a nice Ikea-like name too (Tydlig means clear)    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional No, we wouldn't.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional See DM    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional can we be up in arms due to the ads terrible-ness, though? That whole campaign is a horror.    
    
    
    @kerryanntweet Somewhere there's an idea here, in using facebooks mistargeting as a self-promo....    
    
    
    WORD TO THE WISE RT @vinnywarren: Lesson to all younger guys out there:  Tiffany.  Thus ends the lesson.    
    
    
    http://www.shortoftheweek.com/2013/12/16/howardcantour-com/ … http://HowardCantour.com 
- short film.    
    
    
    Sorry, the film clip can be seen here on Buzzfeed next to comic so you can judge for yourself http://www.buzzfeed.com/jordanzakarin/shia-labeouf-rip-off-daniel-clowes-howard-cantour …    
    
    
    @eskimon Ojdå. Råkade blocka dig när jag skulle lägga dig på lista. Fixat. Sorry.    
    
    
    @lordFredruk Det hänger på slutspurten, vettu @SJ_AB    
    
    
    This is our G+ page. https://plus.google.com/+AdlandTv     
    
    
    @jason_fox Yes. Lets have some more of that.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood & fluid perceptions. I see myself as a little red TV and I want everyone to treat me as one. @jason_fox    
    
    
    @jason_fox I like to beat people to the punch. @marktrueblood    
    
    
    @kerryanntweet Well, don't use that example. Use the odd "Jewish Dating" and "Refinance your loans" that I get (not jewish, own no home)    
    
    
    @kerryanntweet Maybe mock them with looking like them but saying "Need help with getting your ads seen by your target?"    
    
    
    @aronsolomon Careful, you'll be starting a war with Canada... @adtothebone    
    
    
    Trending term after everyone gets Google glass for xmas: Glasshole    
    
    
    @Bohellberg Hur lever livet?    
    
    
    @WilliamMutama Not sure what we're talking about here.    
    
    
    @curlydena heh. :)    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Ask them for a raise & a title to match theirs. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional ZING! @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Consenting adults do whatever they want but when there's power positions involved, hitting on lower rung is wrong @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional So she's not "delightful" at all, she's sleazy. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @kidsleepys You're not a lower rung, and it's actually in my job description to hit on you check the small print  @JoeyMotional    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Also see the other side there's a huge part about back rubs. @JoeyMotional    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail Is it the people who are misunderstanding mistunderstood who are hating on it? I see nothing but applause here. And some kleenex.    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail Oh for the love of.. "that's boy is not a monster, he's just been creeping.." If I shake my head any harder it's gonna fall off.    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail To be honest, my eyes rolled so hard they fell out of my head already in the beginning of last week.    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail "controversial" takedowns of ads has always been popular content, ppl share & it's widely read. It's what advertiser wants.    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail so, sites that live off advertising, but it's not their topic, I trust less when they come with an (odd) take on ad. #advertorial    
    
    
    @JRMcGrail Yep. And it stinks to high heaven of paid content. They never pay US to talk about ads. #integrity    
    
    
    @jmitchem hear hear. Too often, the "twist" is lacking (or obvioius). We have a nice twist in "misunderstood" & "pen" that works @JRMcGrail    
    
    
    @jmitchem A nice good "aha" that you don't see coming always turns into a "I wish I'd done that". ;) @JRMcGrail    
    
    
    @WilliamMutama We noticed. ;)    
    
    
    "I think Kayne West secretly designed Helvetica." http://helveticasux.com/     
    
    
    @RogervonOech I would love one of those, because silent like a shark & pretty, but I wouldn't be kidding myself.    
    
    
    Little Drummer Boy, Sequenced by James Henley http://vimeo.com/82108869     
    
    
    @sshibad Yeah over seventy thousand people have read our post on that, which is here: http://adland.tv/adnews/indonesian-copywriter-dies-after-working-three-days-straight/1387151189 … #agencylife #adblogginglife    
    
    
    @sshibad It's interesting that it got picked up by Gawker.    
    
    
    @sshibad No.    
    
    
    @sshibad :D aw, thanks. I don't think they care/will do anything. It doesn't matter.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Oh man, that sucks. :( I'm so sorry @devhynes    
    
    
    The REAL Lee Clow is on twitter now, not just his beard. Welcome: @clow_lc 

His hair has left the building.    
    
    
    @S5J4 Ah, the hopefulness of youth. Yes you will. Lets hope there's better officials and smarter voters now. @coperightor    
    
    
    @jason_fox Maybe you stole his hair?    
    
    
    @coperightor Well, it might be an interesting things to do campaigns on. Informing ppl is hard. & you're in advertising.. ;) @S5J4    
    
    
    wat? RT @Tn_FuturHlel: Regardez le Grec qu'ils viennent d'Ouvrir a SaintDenis pic.twitter.com/jgxI7N4iZd    
    
    
    @dasVitamin Apparently @mmmelk just gave us this link http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-wales-south-east-wales-20325784 …    
    
    
    @jason_fox 

Ten reasons list posts should exist: #1 

.. I got nothing.

@bobknorpp    
    
    
    Here's a fun game. Fashion or porn? http://www.nssmag.com/fashion-or-porn     
    
    
    Guys, I wasn't exactly hiding that there's be PORN in the link called fashion or PORN....    
    
    
    @fairuse So does chrome, actually.    
    
    
    The ad that sells ACA (Obamacare) to LGBT people is... Four very fit eyecandy men in underwear + one singing lady https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=azoWedQH8zQ&feature=player_embedded …    
    
    
    Note, produced by Full Frontal Freedom -> http://www.facebook.com/fullfrontalfreedom …    
    
    
    @rwarrentaylor you gais. Is it the water or did you mom drop you on the head to cause permanent pun-damage? @rjamestaylor    
    
    
    @strawberrycough Noooooo. Nope. Not at all.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional ok in what sense? As in being a super duper camp ad?    
    
    
    aaaah! RT @lukashMAYYN: drake's most recent Instagram is why we can't have nice things. pic.twitter.com/YW2KG3gv9t    
    
    
    @BFSEsq Yeah, no not really. Sheriffs star = silver. That viking helmet with horns you're wearing tho, oy. #vikingshadnohorns    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional I think everyone should be offended about everything in that ad.    
    
    
    @BFSEsq ;) #vikinggeek    
    
    
    Guys, scroll down to the comments here and watch the "yes" table... http://www.hollywoodreporter.com/live-feed/duck-dynastys-phil-robertson-indefinite-666808 …    
    
    
    @patricenatalie Come here and have some tea and cookies, put your feet up, m'dear. We all have to take a load off sometime.    
    
    
    :D RT @adtothebone: You may have riches, looks, luck and success, but I have FROG jam! 

Ahhh, crud. pic.twitter.com/ZIBunFIEPa    
    
    
    Oh my.On life/work balance in advertising http://mumbrella.com.au/love-career-made-sick-197275 … check comment #45 asked to leave bcuz hours won't change H/T @ashadihopper    
    
    
    @adland whoa, when I tweeted that an hour ago, it was 6K yes, constantly moving, now it's 16K (slowed down)    
    
    
    @jackassletters The phone number works... @dcuthbert    
    
    
    @ryanfarkas Don't think so. Fascinating. @jmitchem    
    
    
    @jmitchem Wow, it just sped up again. Yeah, this is a bit cray... @ryanfarkas    
    
    
    @ryanfarkas Ah, good ol /b/ or maybe people think paraphrasing the Bible shouldn't be a fireable offense in the land of the free? @jmitchem    
    
    
    @ryanfarkas But hang on, I'm gonna check Reddit. One never knows with the Reddit posse. @jmitchem    
    
    
    Beware of filter bubbles RT @gpanger: Fun quotes from @elipariser's Filter Bubble talk. http://www.ted.com/talks/eli_pariser_beware_online_filter_bubbles.html … pic.twitter.com/ooLMXYGE6z    
    
    
    OH: "That's my next tweet"    
    
    
    Been on the vodka diet for about a month now. Already lost two weeks and a weekend.    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Jezebel still praise that MF    
    
    
    @studiopixie 'sup?    
    
    
    @MShocked Woah.    
    
    
    So @JimNorton's duck jokes made me netflix one of his gigs. Twitter actually worked as an advertising medium! He also has dick jokes.    
    
    
    @studiopixie Yeah man. Busy day after that maaaarning. :D    
    
    
    There are 10 people on the exotic set for this shoot.None of them wrote the script #agencylife http://adland.spreadshirt.com/ten-people-agencylife-A12472474/customize/color/2 … pic.twitter.com/ZDyBP5BfHW    
    
    
    For once they get you dinner when you're working late. It's vegetarian sushi. #agencylife http://adland.spreadshirt.com/working-late-dinner-agencylife-A12472432/customize/color/2 … pic.twitter.com/OPNAvSTZ7i    
    
    
    Don't forget the agencydog this christmas. http://adland.spreadshirt.com/dog-day-at-agencylife-A12472604/customize/color/1 … pic.twitter.com/tKvMF3rpnq    
    
    
    @chopsteak I'd watch that show.    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets That's a nice one. I've said F cancer so often, as I'm sure have others. Because F cancer.    
    
    
    Ooops, wrong dog pic. This is for the dog! Ain't he adorable? http://adland.spreadshirt.com/dog-day-at-agencylife-A12472604/customize/color/1 … pic.twitter.com/m5yZobFJaR    
    
    
    No kidding. RT @Digiday: Warning: Agency Hours Are Bad For Your Health: http://trib.al/NALEzJo     
    
    
    @CreativeTweets I'm sorry to hear that. F cancer.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Very interesting. Goldieblox has new lawyers in fight against Beastie Boys. Googles lawyers.  http://musictechpolicy.wordpress.com/2013/12/19/goldieblox-dismisses-case-against-universal-warms-to-task-of-destroying-artists/ …    
    
    
    "filed on behalf of GoldieBlox by registrant of http://orphanworks.com , a domain parked  at http://EFF.org " http://musictechpolicy.wordpress.com/2013/12/19/goldieblox-dismisses-case-against-universal-warms-to-task-of-destroying-artists/ …    
    
    
    @coperightor They didn't trust Orrick?    
    
    
    @coperightor So the conflict of interest may have not played a part at all... ?    
    
    
    a round of applause for this snazzy suit. Well played, sir. RT @hdrr_at: Bereit für die Weihnachtsparty... pic.twitter.com/63CuiXTI4a    
    
    
    @coperightor Do you find the detail that Joseph Gratz owns http://orphanworks.com  & has parked it at EFF.or an interesting detail?    
    
    
    @coperightor Which industry?    
    
    
    @musictechpolicy hey, MTP btw how did you know that Gratz owner Orphanworks? @coperightor    
    
    
    @musictechpolicy *owned (damyouautocorrect) @coperightor    
    
    
    Go, Kate! RT @TheDrum: Kate Winslet threatens to sue Fathers4Justice over attack ad http://po.st/LOHu7a     
    
    
    This is brilliant. RT @fursid: How to gift-wrap a lego? with LEGO! - http://f-st.co/IWmkG6c  http://twitpic.com/dp985h  v/ @FastCoCreate    
    
    
    The Adland christmas playlist. Because we hate jingle bells around here. http://8tracks.com/dabitch/i-don-t-like-xmas-mr-brown …    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets CANNI WAIT until you hear song #2 and smile. :P    
    
    
    @coperightor Wait wait wait, "can't claim ownership"? I'm really wondering what you mean here. Only one band member has recently passed btw.    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets :) see? I do do jingle bells i just don't do jingle bells like everyone else does jingle bells    
    
    
    @coperightor Why would it be orphan work? That's not even related, it's very clear who created the song.    
    
    
    @coperightor When you get out there, I was assuming you were a writer/creative. Am I right? Or are you going for planning/strategy?    
    
    
    @coperightor that would be hilarious if they did. Thats' a one-way ticket to fail.    
    
    
    @coperightor I think what MTP put forth was the reason. Google is footing the bill for Goldieblox.    
    
    
    @coperightor Yep. So, GB becomes the canary in the "Fair use!!! PARODY!1!! LOLZA!! FREE SPEAACHH" coalmine. (Sorry, I read too many forums)    
    
    
    @coperightor Me too. You can have some of my popcorn.    
    
    
    @mkarolian I've only seen you and a guy in the building next to it mention it. Is there one for real?    
    
    
    @mkarolian Oh wow. I hope it's a false alarm and sorted out soon. I hope your GF is able to go take lunch far away right now.    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets :) Me too. Man, I kinda miss theme DJ:ing. Was my thing for a while. (that belt I wear in the avatar I wear when I DJ)    
    
    
    such wow RT @mvdakers: Just a thought: Barclays' corporate goals read quite a lot like doge pic.twitter.com/FUWa7thgw3    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets MOAHA HA HA HA HA HA <- that's my evil laugh    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets You too. :)    
    
    
    @gabrielleshirdn By this month I'm assuming you mean this morning, and yeeeesss.    
    
    
    @coperightor Oh that is AWESOME *calls santa*    
    
    
    @gabrielleshirdn [muffled crunching nom nom noises] Mmm-hmmm! *thumbs up* Sod it, it's December. I'll hibernate in my fat pants.    
    
    
    No that's me with my HTC :P RT @iPhoneTeam: Android users be like check out my new samsung galaxy pic.twitter.com/3jnhGzkXYr    
    
    
    @mkarolian Swedish newspapers are on it now, as the official channel has told them there was a bomb threat. Not anything new. Hope GF is ok    
    
    
    @MusicTechPolicy It's a very interesting detail. @coperightor    
    
    
    @MusicTechPolicy ha ha ha, yes we do.    
    
    
    @MusicTechPolicy It's like we should voiceover this: "And now, it became PERSONAL..." as the remaining BBoys walk into frame @coperightor    
    
    
    @heyprofbow I missed the professor case. Who was this?    
    
    
    "It’s only advertising. Nobody dies." http://mumbrella.asia/2013/12/come-adland-going-respond-tragedy/ … Steve Elrick: "Come on, adland. How are you going to respond to this tragedy?"    
    
    
    @heyprofbow tx    
    
    
    uhm RT @Maf_Cab: Gente de publicidad: Les imploro regresen el factor artístico, cromático y de sutileza a las pautas. pic.twitter.com/yLTydxPShx    
    
    
    Congratulations #Goldieblox on SPIN's Hall Of Shame 2013 list. #12 http://www.spin.com/articles/spin-2013-hall-of-shame/?slide=9 …    
    
    
    dibs! RT @FastCompany: A shower pen and notepad, for those ideas that hit you in the shower: http://f-st.co/QH7TjgL  pic.twitter.com/S91lts2lkl    
    
    
    @kidsleepys This one for the office? http://aplusrstore.com/product.php?id=255 …    
    
    
    @fairuse Nerd! :) Yeah, remember when one could get stuff like this at army surplus?    
    
    
    @critiques4geeks Looking good there, missy!    
    
    
    @critiques4geeks God Jul to you too! :) Okidoki.    
    
    
    @_davidramsay So very yep yep yep. We've made several posts just like that.  @EpicallyHarshed    
    
    
    @_davidramsay (It's a shame that it's on medium. My personal opinion) @EpicallyHarshed    
    
    
    @_davidramsay The site has an 18 year history. We've pretty much covered everything, thrice.    
    
    
    @EpicallyHarshed Yes, I know. But, no, I don't.    
    
    
    @strawberrycough Oy.. @AdLawGuy @adtothebone    
    
    
    Expect movement on peoples Linkedin profiles in 3weeks after what happened at the agency christmas parties this week...    
    
    
        
    
    
    The irony of a medium post talking about ..."enough with business models exploiting user data" I don't even...    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Yeeep.    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN ... And you almost managed to stay out of every picture.    
    
    
    Yikes. A minute without a spam-captcha and 1000 spam comments. Hi guys, we decorated for Xmas. http://adland.tv     
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Don't.    
    
    
    Hidden Within The TPP: The RIAA's Secret Plan To Screw Musicians Out Of Their Rights http://www.techdirt.com/articles/20131217/11534325590/hidden-within-tpp-plan-help-riaa-complete-its-previously-failed-plan-to-screw-over-musicians.shtml …    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Well? Whaddyathink? http://adland.tv     
    
    
    This @JustineSacco PR pro at IAC is a troll/fake account, right.. Right? Please? Or maybe I'm missing something in the humor here..    
    
    
    @kateritchie It's either that or some injoke I don't understand... Some other tweets of hers seem to be a bit odd too, so it's consistent...    
    
    
    .@kateritchie My first thought was that someone at the pub nabbed her phone when she wasn't looking, and made that joke for her.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 You might be on to something.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 Oh, that's a good point.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 Wow.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 getting Internal Server Error on newsle now    
    
    
    @AnnB03 No, you didn't make an error, their server is simply having issues.    
    
    
    @radiumone do you have a phone number or an email where I can reach you asap?    
    
    
    @AnnB03 That many connections takes a while, even for spamscripts. She has to be real.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 It's good to take things with a grain of salt. I'm not sure any of these are real...    
    
    
    @mrbill This won't do. Do I need to mail you cookies?    
    
    
    @AnnB03 I bet a cookie and a bottle of eggnog that some shenanigans is going down. Can't find as many images of justine as you'd expect.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 Yeah, this stinks.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 Gosh, I wish I could put you on staff.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 She flying to Africa? :)    
    
    
    @AnnB03 I make awesome humble pie.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Seven. It's SEVEN. Like, oh emm gee.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor I KNO RITE?    
    
    
    @AnnB03 https://plus.google.com/105834722007421217753/posts … she has G+    
    
    
    @deeped De är väl rädda att de kanske "gör en Justine"    
    
    
    @deeped Oj oj OJ... Dagens värsting: https://twitter.com/JustineSacco/status/414052561248075776 …    
    
    
    @majedsafaee Hah. Jo, landar och inser att hon är avskedad. @deeped    
    
    
    Taking a break from Xmas music today. Going to Jamaica-around-the-world instead.  http://8tracks.com/dabitch/jamaica-is-everywhere-mr-brown …    
    
    
    @baskrud Man fattar asså inte... @deeped    
    
    
    @tinafredriksson Tänkte först att någon måste ha snott hennes telefon för att tweeta det där för vadih-v-e? @deeped    
    
    
    @adtothebone No he's just drunk.    
    
    
    @zarq2013 Yeah when she lands that's gonna be a real bad landing....    
    
    
    When your ECD makes a new linkedin connection & it's the Director of HR at a competing agency.... #agencylife    
    
    
    @thebandfrom You're a pro!    
    
    
    @anniemal I expect everyone to RUN to Linkedin and see who I'm talking about now.    
    
    
    & here we show off both our Vespa and our vinyl. (Playlist) http://8tracks.com/dabitch/25-bacon-lettuce-short-of-a-blort-mr-brown …    
    
    
    @square_tomato And everyone else you just followed, I see.    
    
    
    This just in: Eggnog does not make me any less snarky    
    
    
    @MabandeOpenBeta Pfft. Amatör!    
    
    
    @DijitalE Thanks.    
    
    
    She's got her own hashtag #JustineSacco but does she have her phone back on yet?    
    
    
    @mrbill :)    
    
    
    @armano More like ganked her phone while she was at Heathrow, but looking at her history this tweet doesn't look that out of form.    
    
    
    @mrbill oh.... and if you need swedish meatballs, I'm making that tomorrow night. :D    
    
    
    I have a feeling #JustineSacco won't be laughing so loud after she lands and finds what Twitter has been talking about...    
    
    
    @AlanEggleston Looked into that earlier. There's Linkedin and such connected. Very elaborate if prank. @chrisLrob @armano @LuisRAgostini    
    
    
    @JenniferLanders Oh if she went on a business-trip, her return ticket has been burned....    
    
    
    @snipeyhead Me: http://adland.tv/adnews/goldieblox-erasing-line-between-disruptive-and-douchebaggery/1385572187 … & @kidsleepys http://adland.tv/adnews/3-reasons-why-buzzfeed-poisoning-well/1362340980 …    
    
    
    @AlanEggleston They do. @chrisLrob @armano @LuisRAgostini    
    
    
    The Parody Account. We're done now. RT @JustineSaccoSUX: Really no twitter on that plane? #HasJustineLandedYet    
    
    
    @Mister_Wang True.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 Oh, if I had money to burn like that, I'd be buying Teslas like @justinesacco's mom.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 I don't think you sound like a conspiracy theorist, it's very odd. But, as plenty here will bear witness on, some ppl are like this.    
    
    
    Swedish trivia: Yes, we build a giant goat in Gävle every year. And yes, someone tries to burn it down too. Live feed http://www.visitgavle.se/sv/gavlebocken     
    
    
    Of course the goat has its own twitter account @Gavlebocken & a blog. "Burning the goat: an unauthorized tradition" http://www.slate.com/blogs/atlas_obscura/2013/12/16/burning_the_g_vle_goat_sweden_s_unauthorized_holiday_tradition_of_animal.html …    
    
    
    @DrewHollinshead I don't even know what a mankini is but PICS OR IT DIDN'T HAPPEN @Ogilvy    
    
    
    seems legit RT @nickbilton This has to be a joke: $1k a m for dormroom co-ed bunk beds in SF for entrepreneurs. pic.twitter.com/I73DuiPXFm    
    
    
    #HasJustineLandedYet is getting redonk funny, gais.    
    
    
    @AnnB03 I'm actually rather impressed by how much NOPE she managed to squeeze into only 140 chars. #madSMskillz #HasJustineLandedYet    
    
    
    If #HasJustineLandedYet / this thing turns out to be an elaborate way of advertising people to new BA service with wifi flights.....    
    
    
    Wise. MT @KathleenInCLE Has @British_Airways taken notice of all this twitter furor? Should have #JustineSacco on the radar.    
    
    
    Not the way she expected to make it to the NYT, I'm sure. #HasJustineLandedYet http://thelede.blogs.nytimes.com/2013/12/20/a-twitter-message-about-aids-africa-and-race/?_r=0 …    
    
    
    @patricenatalie I'd be BEYOND pissed off. The "lets make a scandal" school of PR has gone too far many times, I'm hoping for a deathknell    
    
    
    Lets interview passenger next to Justine; "What did she smell like?" #HasJustineLandedYet    
    
    
    @AnnB03 If this is the case, I'm sure we'll name it after her.    
    
    
    Also, we need to know if @British_Airways has the #worstserviceever ... #HasJustineLandedYet    
    
    
    Soon.     #HasJustineLandedYet pic.twitter.com/eJFUHx4ph1    
    
    
    @TatianaCasrti http://flightaware.com/live/flight/BAW43 … you can check here @jjaanneettt182    
    
    
    @KimDriedger Oy. that would be a bit much.    
    
    
    Her trackrecord. (Google Buzz) #HasJustineLandedYet pic.twitter.com/Yb3ckk2qgQ    
    
    
        
    
    
    She knows so much about the world. Bad teeth in the UK, AIDS in SA and uhmm... No L's in China. #HasJustineLandedYet pic.twitter.com/vDe0JFsKFg    
    
    
    @rakeshlobster This is why my android things kind of creep me out...    
    
    
    @anildash I see now that it is true what you said earlier.. You are hella funny. @_Baylink    
    
    
    @Mister_Wang Can I get you guys something in the dark brooding sullen corner?  Kool-aid? First round is on me. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @_Baylink He was commenting on Justine's tweet, saying that he's a v. funny guy but even he couldn't get away with such a joke.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Three beers coming up, then. @Mister_Wang    
    
    
    @Mister_Wang ooooh. Nice one.    
    
    
    @_Baylink PRYOR couldn't land that joke and he was, IMHO, the king of risque jokes. Why I saw him do 45 minutes on taking a shit once.    
    
    
    @_Baylink (That would Richard. Richard Pryor, of course.)    
    
    
    One of these days, autocorrect is gonna get me into so much trouble.    
    
    
    #HasJustineLandedYet may just be a way to show people that what the NSA don't know, Google does.    
    
    
    @_Baylink And on that Note, I'm gonna Netflix me some Richard!    
    
    
    @evcon I know, right?    
    
    
    @_Baylink oooh! Thanks!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ArikSharon I have a wave account under all that Google tumbleweed too. @strawberrycough @Ajsoti    
    
    
    #HasJustinelandedYet yep & she deleted her entire account. Must be shocking to find the internet threw you a surprise going away party.    
    
    
    @callen_ph Yes. Yes you have.    
    
    
    Oh dear...   RT @LauraKeeney: Well played, @GoGo. Well. Played. #SlowClap #HasJustineLandedYet pic.twitter.com/9Y5tPJEA1J    
    
    
    @Iagreewithjoe Oh, what pricks. @RebeccaTheim @AidforAfrica    
    
    
    I love all you guys. #eggnog #spiked #toomany #santahat c'mere give us a hug.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys This was the twitter holiday party, you guys. @oddsauce @mashable    
    
    
    @oddsauce Be careful what you tweet before a flight, girl... ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    *starts re-labelling pitchforks for the new mob forming, the mob that hates twitter mobs*    
    
    
    Twitter is kinda bipolar.    
    
    
    @mutlu82 A bit of a rollercoaster, wasn't it?    
    
    
    @meeterica When did you do that ah-may-zing thing to your hair? Love it.    
    
    
    .@Zac_R Just a tad wigged out now. Twitter sees all. @mathewi    
    
    
    Guys.... She's flying back to the US and apologizing the whole way. We might have ruined xmas. pic.twitter.com/BUMwERpFmN    
    
    
    Though, I don't know if @JustineSacco6 is the real deal, it's the same old image, and @Zac_R is showing her in ZA airport still    
    
    
    So, did anyone get @BuzzFeedAndrew his eggnog refilled yet?    
    
    
    @AdFreak .... *hangs head in shame... retreats to the eggnog corner and hiccups*    
    
    
    @deeped typ. Såg du hela grejen? Det var.. Lixom.. .. uhm.. det var. Kommer att föreläsas om.    
    
    
    @retrocampaigns .... woah.    
    
    
    @retrocampaigns Yeah, why would twitter delete her account. More likely she panicked and did. Also, re-use of old avatar = suspect.    
    
    
    @deeped Finns gott om kul bilder och animationer. Slutkläm: https://twitter.com/Mistressnancy/status/414279283729629187 …    
    
    
    @deeped det var en av de värre berg-och-dalbanor jag sett. Det var lite som en fest en stund, med en massa krassa skämt.    
    
    
    @deeped *asg*    
    
    
    @deeped https://twitter.com/awlilnatty/status/414291733157916672 …    
    
    
    @deeped Jo, vill du ha PDF'en på hennes tidigare G Buzz chattar? Den är det nog bara jag som har.    
    
    
    @deeped *ser jätteoskyldig ut*    
    
    
    @lordFredruk Godmorgon.    
    
    
    @lordFredruk Hennes farsa är värd $1.4 B. Hon klarar sig, du.    
    
    
    @lordFredruk Hon kan köpa nya!    
    
    
    @deeped http://www.forbes.com/profile/desmond-sacco/ … farsan @lordFredruk    
    
    
    @deeped Ja, men det var lite som en fest en stund, skojjigt, giffar, skämt. Det var först närmare landning som det kände råare.    
    
    
    @deeped Det och prickig-korvmacka, en bra start på dagen. #STARTMüsli @lordFredruk    
    
    
    @lordFredruk Det skulle kännas rätt jävigt om hela twitter vänt sig mot minimumlön-Lina. Men miss miljardär som har hög PR titel? @deeped    
    
    
    @lordFredruk ... NU ser du. Godmorgon. @deeped    
    
    
    @lordFredruk *jävligt @deeped    
    
    
    hello Keith Haring meets my kids! RT @FaithPopcorn: Shoe covers at Dover St Mkt. Wow Wheeeeeeee pic.twitter.com/hx8hQN9QYB    
    
    
    What did bloggers & news outlets write about before people joked around on twitter?    
    
    
    @jmitchem There's a lot worse musically to know out there, I say get them concert tickets.    
    
    
    The @FastCoExist site is like an ad against using @disqus with the many "copy the article as comment" spam comments they have.    
    
    
    It's an interesting phenomena. Not sure what the spammers get from it. If you comment on Fastco you will get a lot of mail-replies spam.    
    
    
    Here's an example of that spam phenomena. All these words are in the article above. http://www.fastcoexist.com/3021937/origami-inspired-cardboard-homeless-shelters-to-help-people-get-off-the-streets … pic.twitter.com/AQM3lMW6iJ    
    
    
    @FaithPopcorn Love the shoe covers. Can't get to Dover St Market. Who/What brand?    
    
    
    @MabandeOpenBeta Känns som om halva twitter vaknade med bakfylleångest, efter att ha sett alla bloggar om det nu....    
    
    
    @deeped Finns medier som skärmdumpade LOLJustinesacco och trodde det var den riktiga...    
    
    
    @ryanfarkas All in favor? YES! It's been decided. *noms*    
    
    
    @deeped Jo, och Globagrind gjorde samma. De *försöker* ju bli rumsrena.    
    
    
    @deeped Eller rumsrena, jag menar, tas på allvar som journalistisk publikation.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional David did not mean to tell an ableist joke and [insert standard apology here] @iowahawkblog    
    
    
    *phew* I'm safe. RT @iowahawkblog: Apparently the latest speechcrime is being insufficiently sarcastic.    
    
    
    I'll just have a bloody mary. I'm on a diet. pic.twitter.com/WCfJVw1PXO    
    
    
    @Diego440 I've noticed. What do they "earn" from that? Fastco earns another click from me, as I think someone actually replied for real.    
    
    
    If you missed the surprise party last night, @deeped collected tweets in a timeline, even if you don't read Swedish http://storify.com/deeped/the-justine-sacco-story?utm_campaign=website&utm_source=email&utm_medium=email …    
    
    
    @ellstar Yes. This is the nectar of gods.    
    
    
    @deeped Inte BRA sammanställningar, du fick ju med allt. Att det blev en trend kom sig ju av att hon inte visste vad vi visste. :)    
    
    
    @armano The millionaire daddy isn't confirmed. If it was, South African newspapers would be all over this. @Drtmpkns    
    
    
    @deeped Jag lämna kommentar. :)    
    
    
    @MabandeOpenBeta Kolla, @deeped gjorde en bra sammanställning här. http://digitalpr.se/2013/12/21/justine-sacco-och-att-krishantera-en-tweet/ …    
    
    
    @Drtmpkns Those don't say that he's the $1.4B guy, s'all I'm saying. @armano @deeped    
    
    
    @armano This is the earliest tweet I recall, if that helps: https://twitter.com/BuzzFeedAndrew/status/414105854476943360 … @alivingiano @voltaire @BuzzFeedBen @griner    
    
    
    @voltaire Buzzfeed Politics team and Twitchy-team were the first to notice and spread it. @alivingiano @BuzzFeedBen @griner    
    
    
    When Charmin is trying to be real time relevant in your twitters.    
    
    
    @hanelly touché!    
    
    
    .@griner The oddest thing too, is that I don't see that reply-tweet on @Gogo's timeline. Only when I search for it.    
    
    
    @portlandadfed People call ladies dude all the time, dude. @hanelly    
    
    
    @AdFreak aaaaah, indeed I was was. tx.    
    
    
    @hanelly Well, you know. it's kind of hard to tell the gender when you can't see my antennas. @portlandadfed    
    
    
    @hanelly Whoah slow down there, son, @AdFreak has to buy me dinner and a diamond ring first. Okay, maybe just dinner.    
    
    
    @Iagreewithjoe TIL I'm @AdFreak's mom @griner & maybe lover and there's greek plays about this, I'm sure.    
    
    
    @AdFreak *bwahahahaha* @hanelly    
    
    
    @purplesime Yeah. Same here. @griner    
    
    
    @Iagreewithjoe You need a cold shower, son. @AdFreak @griner    
    
    
    @BFSEsq .. yeah, It was something.    
    
    
    @BOC_ATM Next round is on him.    
    
    
    So many layers of STOP IT RT @diemkay: Manly yogurt for men pic.twitter.com/g6UjZIhNfI    
    
    
    We should be getting gendered toilet paper any day now.    
    
    
    @mathewi Twitchy was on it at eleven https://twitter.com/TwitchyTeam/status/414110442500661248 … @Digidave @samfbiddle    
    
    
    @alivingiano my bad, sent reply forgot to include you. Twitchy was tweeting it at 11AM for your research records https://twitter.com/TwitchyTeam/status/414110442500661248 …    
    
    
    @NorrbottenBD ♥!    
    
    
    @hi_its_nicola If he was, it would be all over the south african news, so I'd say no, we're not. @BlackCanseco @KashannKilson @deluxvivens    
    
    
    "Going to ██████! Hope I don't ██████! Just kidding. I'm ██████!" Is the new mad libs.    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Is it likely that SA papers would ignore story like this on their richest mans kin? @hi_its_nicola @KashannKilson @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Twitter guy @Zac_R greeted her at airport in Cape Town. It's not like people in South Africa didn't notice this.    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Sorry, but even the leading Swedish newspapers wrote about this today. @hi_its_nicola @KashannKilson @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @KashannKilson Right, no names his 2 kids have on usual bios. Know more about mineral collection. @BlackCanseco @hi_its_nicola @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @KashannKilson She made the Cape Times (ouch). No mention of rich daddy. http://www.iol.co.za/news/politics/outrage-over-aids-tweet-1.1625598 … @BlackCanseco @hi_its_nicola @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Media might have just realized they need this confirmed.  @hi_its_nicola @KashannKilson @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco Hive mind got carried away last night, Forbes Dad-article made rounds on twitter. @hi_its_nicola @KashannKilson @deluxvivens    
    
    
    @femfreq Ugh. Reported. @CreativeDynamix    
    
    
    @adfilmtv Are they?    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor The fall of the wall reached me long before the news. When Sky aired it live, it just affirmed "word on the street" @Drtmpkns    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor ..err, "confirmed". Anyway, when on telly I finally believed it was happening. The border-rush seemed so unreal @Drtmpkns    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Kids saw Challenger because the TV was rolled into classrooms... @Drtmpkns    
    
    
    o_0? MT @FastCoCreate Breast weights? Real product f real men w/workout routines=really creepy http://f-st.co/u7Fcfoe  pic.twitter.com/8PFQ7dtd98    
    
    
    Screendump f Daily Mail Facebook-© on Justine's pic. FB allows this? If u don't clear out acct http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2527330/Blonde-female-PR-executive-tweets-Going-Africa-Hope-I-dont-AIDS-Just-kidding-Im-white-causes-international-outrage-likely-fired.html … pic.twitter.com/XcZyCTO8vV    
    
    
    @Diego440 Ugh. Since Disqus doesn't tell you what the reply-comment says, it results in another hit for the website = more ad views.    
    
    
    Breaking the law, breaking the law. *shifty eyes* pic.twitter.com/v8pyHl9EaE    
    
    
    @Diego440 You get me.    
    
    
    @Diego440 Uhm... <*sideways glancing*> No. (̿▀̿ ̿Ĺ̯̿̿▀̿ ̿)̄    
    
    
    @adlandjones c'mere you *mwaaah* (づ￣ ³￣)づ    
    
    
    @nrose Ah, but can you tell I'm not really a red TV?    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Wait, that still exists?    
    
    
    @liamriddler oOh. This is fun. @Fiascoyrn @TheTumblrPosts    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Oh you, stawp. (Your check is in the mail, Robot).  @Zombie_Beach    
    
    
    TIL that you can fly without an actual ID in the US, as @zachklein got through TSA screening with his facebook profile. ¯\(º_o)/¯    
    
    
    @adfilmtv I like the way you think.    
    
    
    We'll post later, but FYI Justine Sacco has apologized for her tweets. Properly. Not a single weasel word in it.  #hasjustinelandedyet    
    
    
    @hotdogdynamite Well, it is refreshing to see a proper apology for once. That's class.    
    
    
    @hotdogdynamite Oh. :) The 'outrage' was more like a weird twitter-party, where the joke was "she's on a plane and trending! LULZ". Friday.    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 No this is the letter she sent to The Star, ABCNews and other media.  One does not apology on social media.    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 .. err I mean, via new accounts. Letters to old school media still have their place.    
    
    
    @hotdogdynamite But yes, I've seen more written about her tweet than I've seen written about massive news events, it got *weird*    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 Ugh, there were threats of that nature? That's disturbing. I'm not surprised, but as usual, I was only noticing the jokes.    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 "worse than Hitler", right? Tsssk. People need chill-pills.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 It's not a "twitter" mob thing. It's a human mob thing. Now worldwide-enabled via twitter. Hella creepy.    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 Yeah. I'd write about it tonight but I've been battling a php 5.4 bug and having christmas beers simaltaniously & spellingsux    
    
    
    @stevedouglas1 *hic*    
    
    
    The official Holiday beer of adland: Peculiar Yule from Nøgne Ø http://www.nogne-o.com/seasonal-beers/underlig-jul.html … & Holiday ale http://www.nogne-o.com/seasonal-beers/special-holiday-ale.html … = so very good.    
    
    
    Yeah, I just randomly recommended y'alls a beer. Because christmas.    
    
    
    @wheresspot aw shucks, we like you too. @doublejnyc yeah we cover if directors get signed - some PR has their own accts and post news on us.    
    
    
    @hotdogdynamite It was very much a Lord of the flies moment.    
    
    
    @daisykwan If you can get to Whole Foods on Rose they have it.    
    
    
    @Saatchi_Norway Det är bannemig GULD. Solklart skandinaviens bästa öl.    
    
    
    @Saatchi_Norway God jul på er. :)    
    
    
    @snorrem Och God Jul på dig. :)    
    
    
    @wheresspot Have a great holiday season you guys.    
    
    
    @RobKnopper1 LOLZ at Tanzanian Giraffe. @Malecopywriter @Gap    
    
    
    You are the grinch RT @Malecopywriter: Just left a bong packed with salvia out for Santa. #MerryChristmas    
    
    
    @michaelheiniger That's a great dress, she's so pretty.    
    
    
    Merry Christmas! Kanye West has been sued for infringement, as he lifted the music for Bound 2 from Ponderosa Twins http://adland.tv/adnews/kanye-west-sued-infringement/1591745081 …    
    
    
    @anniemal The twins deserve better, that album is like a raw Jackson 5 gem. So good.    
    
    
    @anniemal I bought the whole album the other day, been obsessed with that song.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Stawp it you grinch ;)    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Merry Christmas to you too!    
    
    
    Turning the server off for christmas, all y'alls now must spend time with your families instead of reading about advertising. So there! xo    
    
    
        
    
    
    "Intel inside" .. the tagline alerted us to the NSA all along...    
    
    
    @AaronSmarter BBC producers have 'offered the role of Doctor Who to a black actor' - :) http://www.dailymail.co.uk/tvshowbiz/article-2386932/BBC-offered-Doctor-Who-black-actor-past--turned-says-Neil-Gaiman.html … @BlackCanseco @elonjames    
    
    
    @anniemal Oh man, I'm sorry. That sucks. :(    
    
    
    @anniemal I will join you in the pacing. Also ill, not from fish though, but I came down with something. Lets be miserable together....    
    
    
    @BlackCanseco In the article they also mention a woman Doctor. I think it'll def. happen, and soon. @AaronSmarter @elonjames    
    
    
    @anniemal A bunch of aspirins & old school ginger ale to settle tummy. Need some gingers?    
    
    
    @anniemal Our hero. @csix    
    
    
    The branding of heroin - http://grahammacindoe.com/All-In-/15/  - images of heroin baggies collected http://grahammacindoe.com/All-In-/1/     
    
    
    Of course they do! RT @CloonanJ: In Australia, sharks use twitter to warn swimmers http://news.sky.com/story/1187066/australia-sharks-use-twitter-to-warn-swimmers …    
    
    
    @MusicTechPolicy Wait, what - Megavideo was allowed an Adsense account and we've been banned 3 times? That seems fair. @thetrichordist    
    
    
    @PlanBstudio All the alcohol.    
    
    
    Lee Clow changed his twitter name to @_clow - merry Xmas.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Mister_Wang You setting fire to Xmas trees too? Calm down! http://bigstory.ap.org/article/vegas-outdoor-malls-christmas-tree-catches-fire …    
    
    
    @thebandfrom No no, tea gets more complicated since it's done the teabag thing forever. Look for new teabag shapes, special teapots etc.    
    
    
    RIght now on Huffpo: "BNP Absurd Christmas Card Looks Quite Racist" Bing Crosby strikes again http://www.huffingtonpost.co.uk/2013/12/23/bnp-christmas-card_n_4492661.html … pic.twitter.com/cpQaxSitjS    
    
    
    @pamlau yep. Related: whenever I Search on Bing I croon out my search terms. Like "whiiiiiite christmaaaaaass" Yes I'm weird.    
    
    
    @msmarfinkle It's REALLY GOOD SOUP!  :p @noahax    
    
    
    http://articles.economictimes.indiatimes.com/2013-12-11/news/45080781_1_facebook-pages-facebook-profile-strawberryfrog … Spotted in 'Ventriloquism in social media and advertising: How it helps brands' w @trrippp @thisismyttt @scottfrog    
    
    
    @curlydena I wish I was there. Cheers, kids.    
    
    
    @phviljoen Why is Hulu showing ads as entertainment? @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @phviljoen That's your internet surfing habits and location that determines which ads you get. Try surfing incognito. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    @phviljoen Did you surf incognito yet? You can't blame the algorithm without testing. @kidsleepys    
    
    
    ███████▓▒░ 88% full of xmas food still    
    
    
    "BuzzFeed has about six months of relevance left. " http://digiday.com/publishers/7-media-predictions-others-wont-write/?utm_content=buffera2893&utm_source=buffer&utm_medium=twitter&utm_campaign=Buffer …
via @Digiday - promise?    
    
    
    http://adland.tv/adnews/did-iron-maiden-turn-piracy-paying-customers-no/1157588515 … Did Iron Maiden turn piracy into paying customers? No.    
    
    
    @FamousRob Sure. Gig musicians are totally rolling in it. Meet Claude Coleman Jr. http://adland.tv/adnews/more-artists-speaking-out-claude-coleman-jr/1385260692 …    
    
    
    ha! RT @adbroad surprise! RT @adweak After 6 m in the Business Jr. Art Director Admits He Really Thought Advertising Would be More Creative.    
    
    
    @FamousRob so which is it? They're either making a lot of money, or they've never been rich.    
    
    
    @FamousRob1)  gigs are fewer and further between 2) don't make up for CD loss 3) sux for fans who might not afford gigs = everybody screwed.    
    
    
    @FamousRob We write a lot about the general topic. You're welcome to comment on the posts. "Fake PR" has been going on for a while.    
    
    
    @FamousRob I think that has a lot to do with the middlemen (Ticketmasters) taking over sales, which is a topic in itself. Related,of course.    
    
    
    @TheSmarmyBum Most of the world is that mobile, it's the US that lags behind.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Wait, what? where are we looking at this list?    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor oy    
    
    
    @kalemeow yeah man, Honey Badger don't care and why are you interacting with a promoted tweet, fool? @rjamestaylor    
    
    
    @kalemeow Yeah,I mean him,the robot. :) If we start noticing these promoted tweets, twitter is suddenly worth that 40 billion @rjamestaylor    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ArikSharon Yet another business built on not paying content creators (read; photographers). Ain't that grand?    
    
    
    @kidsleepys only if you appreciate the humor in the little red TV producing technicolor yawns.    
    
    
    http://www.esquire.com/blogs/news/we-broke-the-internet … 2013 the year we broke the internet &  fact-checking has been outsourced to the readers    
    
    
    via @adland: Silicon Valley: where free labor is even better than cheap labor.  http://adland.tv/adnews/silicon-valley-where-free-labor-even-better-cheap-labor/2098325750 …    
    
    
    @patricenatalie your avatar even vanished. You're an egg.    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam AMEN!!    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam You saw that he got sued for it, right? http://adland.tv/adnews/kanye-west-sued-infringement/1591745081 …    
    
    
    Conan finds local variants of wire copy. Results funnier than expected. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TM8L7bdwVaA#t=81 …    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam OI, yeah and his job is as dangerous as beinga police officer or SOLDIER AT WAR *groan*! Tho, sampling legally is easy.    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam Well yeah, that's why we have it in the post I showed you. I have the album. I'm obsessed with it. The should win that suit.    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam .. They're like a raw diamond of jackson 5 that wasn't overproduced and it's so yuuuum.    
    
    
    @idle_flim_flam Tssk tssk. But seriously, the whole album is good. That thing should be re-released as part of the settlement.    
    
    
    So, does this mean MORE Sherlock shows?  MT @washingtonpost: Sherlock Holmes is officially in the public domain. http://wapo.st/1fPtW8w     
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN ;) https://twitter.com/adland/status/365194199836028928 …    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN :) I've often wished for that, but then all of it can and will be used against you at some point.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mmmelk Yep, & .se has unlimited data even on prepay. Roaming costs in EU on some networks don't exist either!  @TheSmarmyBum    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor I'd get into that flamefest if I wasn't so busy hacking.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Ah, no. I only skimmed it. The topic itself has been a flamefest that bored me already.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Yeah, Valleywag did make their corrections, which is too little too late now that the twitterflamefest has begun.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @rjamestaylor ... yeah some women in tech actually do more than just enter text ins somebody elses blogplatform.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor dammit, you be retweeting my spelläng errörs!    
    
    
        
    
    
    So yeah @mutlu82 just reminded us that it's almost 14 years ago that we interviewed @adweak -> http://adland.tv/content/adweak-heckles-strong …    
    
    
    @geekofallwork I DO. Pro: love support. Cons: can't do your own sendmail access list. But you're not into that, are you? @Rackspace    
    
    
    @geekofallwork Or maybe you are - that's the only thing I miss. @Rackspace    
    
    
    @snipeyhead I entertained the boy idea as a teen because they had posse, we had 1 catty BFF. Then I realized: FUCK RULES!    
    
    
    @snipeyhead but legit answer: No. I might have played my woman-card different knowing what I know now. I just wanted to be treated equal.    
    
    
    @pawal faboo pic.    
    
    
    @snorrem Man tackar. Jag har dock lite problem med den än. :/ Så här hackar jag vidare med flunsan. Yipii.    
    
    
    @snorrem tussen takk.    
    
    
    @snorrem Takk. Jo, det är the slow jag vil få fixat, samt videos loadar inte alls än. Fler categories etc kommer då.    
    
    
    @TheSweetKat I was 12-13, some BASIC class at school, if that counts (and it kinda doesn't)    
    
    
        
    
    
    "We're gonna need a bigger bucket" ...Oh, BMW, how much do you hate us?    
    
    
    ruh-roh RT @DaveGian: Attackers could match phone numbers to Snapchat accounts: http://ow.ly/s7dp3  - by @idg_news' @lconstantin    
    
    
    More ways to lie! RT @FastCoCreate: Why virtual reality journalism is the future http://f-st.co/7Rio4IZ  pic.twitter.com/6FiT0iVTTv    
    
    
    @cremefraiche Clearly.    
    
    
    @cmykmagazine Happy new year to you too! Long live CMYK.    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Let me guess. You have an iPhone.    
    
    
    @aronsolomon we've just been complaining about that all day here.... So awful.    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN cats @adtothebone    
    
    
    @adtothebone also, to asnwer your question: tjugonda knut http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Knut's_Day …    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Tssk tssk.    
    
    
    @lukashMAYYN Ha ha ha.    
    
    
    @deeped Yeah usually this is the first weekend after the new year that you can be bothered to deal with it. @adtothebone    
    
    
    @adtothebone I used to run a very strict Xmas household. 13th december 13th january, all xmas all the time.    
    
    
    @deeped You forgot to add sugar to the tree-water again, didn't you? @adtothebone    
    
    
    @aronsolomon So very welcome to the life of the 1% where we THROW AWAY CARS  egads, hatehatehate. Also, that elf-outfit.    
    
    
    @emilybinder None.@sillysampi    
    
    
        
    
    
    @gabrielleshirdn :D    
    
    
    @gabrielleshirdn laughing with you, m'dear.    
    
    
    @sillysampi Yeah, well I buy mens for my legs because the pink ones are more expensive and I'm no fool. @emilybinder    
    
    
    If we all do = DISRUPTION RT @anniemal: Not a bad idea. “@gotwalt: Delete all your apps and start fresh in the new year.”    
    
    
    My new years resolution is 1440x900    
    
    
    @adtothebone is that derailed train anywhere near you, mate?    
    
    
    @adtothebone Yep. Saw some pics, it went proper kabloeey.    
    
    
    @Drtmpkns [EXPLETIVE] ... not in the budget yet. Don't mock us.    
    
    
    Susan Cradle just picked the worst ad of the year as the best. Wall Street Journal forgets to mention any lawsuits. http://online.wsj.com/news/articles/SB10001424052702304591604579288643406741548 …    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood Yes it is. Very much so.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood I'm saddened that someone at the top in our biz is either unaware of that part, or worse thinks it's a good strategy.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood That makes it even worse.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood You know what I think though, if you read this (Erasing the line between disruptive and douchebaggery) http://adland.tv/adnews/goldieblox-erasing-line-between-disruptive-and-douchebaggery/1385572187 …    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood Sadly. Yes.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood Yes. Their entitlement to free labor/IP stretches far beyond music, and in the end affects our business as we sell creativity    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood Of course, that exactly the way it works now. Creator decides. I'm against any changes that removes this right.    
    
    
    @MarkTrueblood as it should be.    
    
    
    @mick_fiction Hey, happy new year, champ.    
    
    
    @mick_fiction Battling the flu. :D    
    
    
    @mick_fiction You playing anywhere tonight?    
    
    
    @lesliestaysup may you be happily ever after, or at least until the next cup.    
    
    
    Ultimate bromance MT @digitalspy: Sir Patrick & Sir Ian celebrating New Year probably the best thing you'll see today pic.twitter.com/K6czttiCNx    
    
    
    @kidsleepys At some point that agency needs to change its name to the Manifesto-agency.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys the lols.    
    
    
    @krystlekopacz That @wsj list shows a disturbing lack of talent at the top level of advertising.    
    
    
    @krystlekopacz or let me rephrase, a disturbing lack of RECOGNIZING what's good and what's shite at the top level of advertising.    
    
    
    @ArikSharon Don't forget the all important song that inspires... @kidsleepys    
    
    
    aaaw! so cute! RT @GammaCounter: BYTE imagines a smartwatch, ca 1978. Look at the sweet little floppy. pic.twitter.com/GPA0D7dWEI    
    
    
    ★ 🎇☆ ⑳⑭ ⓴⓮ ☆ 🎇★    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional well @MarkFiore may be reconsidering. If you need a hand moving to a amazon cloud server I'd be happy to help.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @hugokrantz Man skall låta lite på lyset straxt, har jag för mig.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @nudd The best to you, happy new year!    
    
    
    2014 - hopefully the year we retire the ECD's&CCO's who lack the ability to spot good work. In the with the new.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Oh hush, child. Your time will come.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Oh you.    
    
    
    @darrellwhitelaw amen!    
    
    
    @karllinder För att kunder begär idéer de känner igen.    
    
    
    @AlanMcQuaid3 Good! It deserves all praise. Exceptionally well done.    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor HA!    
    
    
    @karllinder Säg Coop kopierat tio gånger snabbt efter ett par glas champagne!    
    
    
    @MarkFiore Been a fan for years, anything I can do just holler.    
    
    
    @TheoFanning Too busy counting their monies? ;)    
    
    
    @TheoFanning Well, there's that too.    
    
    
    The future of advertising is in Australia. It's already 2 in the afternoon Jan 1st 2014 there.    
    
    
    @audiodesigndan *gigglesnort* Cheers.    
    
    
    @Mister_Wang o_0?    
    
    
    @Malecopywriter you too, madman!    
    
    
    @rjamestaylor Or perhaps, just the most annoying habit.    
    
    
    @shanestrudwick Also (hours later) it's Credle. Damn that autocorrect. Still, not agreeing with her choices at all. HNY!! @MarkTrueblood    
    
    
    Careful driving, be safe! RT @Schwartzie14: Fireworks on PCH. Happy New York New Year. @ Temescal Beach http://instagram.com/p/inUEd4lFkv/     
    
    
    Remind me to go outside. RT @WMittyAdvice: RETWEET if your New Years resolutions are influenced by my movie!!    
    
    
    @strawberrycough I LUV YOU GAIS /drunktweet @anniemal @WMittyAdvice    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @CarlosRiveroll Congrats.    
    
    
    @CarlosRiveroll Happy new Year!    
    
    
    @CarlosRiveroll Here's to new frontiers this year. *raises cup of steaming hot delish coffee*    
    
    
        
    
    
    @mikeharari You're a genius. Call some VC peeps now.    
    
    
    @kidsleepys Hmm. @JoeyMotional We know nothing about you, you know.    
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Ah yes. Just respect that @kidsleepys can't be all out there like me.    
    
    
    @t5war That might be exactly why he's there.    
    
    
    @t5war ouch    
    
    
    “Did MusicMetric have any role in pumping up this purportedly fabricated story?” Iron Maiden piracy bunk story http://thetrichordist.com/2014/01/01/fake-iron-maiden-story-raises-questions-about-musicmetric-and-illustrates-decline-in-quality-of-music-business-journalism/?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    @jeffsand Lovely!    
    
    
    @larmanius You bring the tar, I bring the feathers, lets hunt down the client.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @markmarkcheng Yes, happy new year to you as well. Lovely day for it. ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    Oh dear RT @VICE: Forget about Bitcoin and Dogecoin—there's a Kanye West themed cryptocurrency coming soon: http://bit.ly/1dWKav3     
    
    
        
    
    
    @JoeyMotional Check previous Vice article & take a number I'm sure we all wanna beat that guy up    
    
    
        
    
    
    @CreativeTweets http://adland.tv/adnews/evolution-evony-ads-or-more-boobies-makes-more-clicks/1247522926 …    
    
    
    @Syloc Beror på om du gillar reklam och sarkastika skämt. :) @deeped    
    
    
    @deeped SKYLL PÅ OSS, BA, LIXOM! @annika    
    
    
    @dellcreative ... also known as "creative teams..."? @thefoxisblack    
    
    
    @CreativeTweets *sigh* Depressing, isn't it?    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://thetrichordist.com/2014/01/02/sympathy-for-rapgenius/?utm_source=twitterfeed&utm_medium=twitter … Sympathy for Rapgenius - no license? Violating real law? Google OK. Bad SEO/ violating Googles Law = Google kills you    
    
    
    @chaosprime I see you read the article. Eh... @Jeevesmeister    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Ladies! The ultimate purse has just arrived. http://www.mighty-purse.com  It charges your phone. #want #gimme #waaaant    
    
    
    @deeped we are dissapoint... ;P    
    
    
    @deeped ha ha :)    
    
    
    @deeped Wow, nicely geeky find this.    
    
    
    I joined Twitter on the 26th of February 2007 (2,503 days ago). Find your Twitter age at http://www.twuration.com/     
    
    
    That's cold RT @heyfeifer: It's currently snowing INSIDE Brooklyn's Borough Hall stop. pic.twitter.com/eNJ9hqTao0    
    
    
    