@howden_africa @davidrisherwr Hi Daniel, he is on a boat in Turkey- what is your timing? I can help you.    
    
    
    @opuech @davidrisherwr Hi olivier! He is on a boat in Turkey- what is your timing? I'll help you figure it out.    
    
    
    I’ve just completed a new workout on the Speedo Pace Club. Try to beat my time at http://bit.ly/Ly2woE     
    
    
    Great summary of Hemingway- congrats @benmezrich RT @nprbooks: Bull Fights, Bankruptcy And A Damn Dangerous Book http://n.pr/Rl8EUt     
    
    
    Enjoying gin and tonics with @cultureslurp  @ El Canalla http://instagr.am/p/MtxMgGnkX3/     
    
    
    No. 8 made me chuckle. RT @NewYorker: An #heir cartoon of the night: http://nyr.kr/P1mSwc     
    
    
    Not sure how excited I am about this. RT @mashable: Here's What Facebook's 'Want' Button Will Probably Look Like http://on.mash.to/NEfbVA     
    
    
    Crystal clear 3K swim- only saw about 20 jellies  @ Sitges Ocean Swimming http://instagr.am/p/M2xq7iHkTw/     
    
    
    I just ousted @mauprieto as the mayor of Garraf Trail Lookout #1 on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/npNjPd     
    
    
    Love this. RT @Forbes: AdVoice: Being a Great Leader Means You Go First http://bit.ly/PGzCHT     
    
    
    Swimming in The Atlantic Ocean at @foursquare: http://4sq.com/LsGqTd     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Far Far Away" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/QiLGiT     
    
    
    Video RT @worldreaders: Hear what happened to Okanta Kate after reading The Shark by Ghanaian author Peggy Oppong: http://youtu.be/X4I1lbf4TKo     
    
    
    Tomorrow am I'll swim around the birthplace of NYC. http://bit.ly/N2zo8I     
    
    
    @DrWider You are my inspiration!  I don't know how you do it!    
    
    
    @davemorgannyc  missed you today!    
    
    
    Awesome @nycswim today around the birthplace of NYC with my BFF.  Every breath we saw Lady Liberty waving "Hi" to us! pic.twitter.com/ffszI7Zl    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Me too- Can't wait to meet you!  How's your week looking?    
    
    
    The world needs more people like @KatieLinendoll.  Awesome seeing you and can't wait to collaborate more.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Ski Bum" badge on @foursquare for checking in at ski spots! Slope city! http://4sq.com/McHOyo     
    
    
    Just completed a 12.93 km bike - Aspen is so beautiful! http://rnkpr.com/a1ttkpy  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    So very true! Do you agree? pic.twitter.com/ArdcsupV    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Menorca Ocean Swim on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/T6G7nB     
    
    
    I had loads of fun in this interview with @wendyhung @JetsetTimes http://ow.ly/dqA00   Cool publication!    
    
    
    @davemorgannyc I signed up to do Little Red Light House with @nycswim.  The name sounds quaint but it's a 10K! http://bit.ly/RkyjtC     
    
    
    @PdP_bcn @foursquare How is that possible?    
    
    
    @DidacLee The @FT loves what @LeoMessi1987 is doing with Kindles in Africa.  Let's get the word out! @FCB http://on.ft.com/Q0cO5l     
    
    
    @Kuhn Looking forward to talking with you later on today about @worldreaders.  Thanks again @zsniderman for hooking us up! #MillionBooks    
    
    
    If you're into Mobile Tech in Africa, this is a must read: http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20120823-what-africa-can-learn-from-phones …    
    
    
    Have a 20 old computer that needs fixing? Come to Spain! pic.twitter.com/U8BTWrLv    
    
    
    @jryoung Hi Jeff- I just sent you an email about Kindles in Africa- a game changer for literacy. Run by fellow P-ton folks. Hope to connect.    
    
    
    @mauprieto Why don't you tweet the harddrive question to @apple?    
    
    
    @nickwingfield I ♥ your article in @NYT today! Publishers step up for kids in Africa. Hooray @simonschuster @randomhousekids @worldreaders!    
    
    
    Major int'l publishers are joining @worldreaders cause to get great books in kids hands in Africa- Read more in @NYT: http://nyti.ms/TrlVgb     
    
    
    @RipleyWorld @EgmontUK Hooray for your work with @worldreaders!  Nice piece in today's @NYT //nyti.ms/TrlVgb #MillionBooks    
    
    
    @cultureslurp and you?    
    
    
    @NickKristof you'll love this! “@nytimesbits: Publishers Back African Literacy Effort With E-Books http://nyti.ms/SmGHQu ”    
    
    
    @TechCrunch pls see @nickwingfield: Bits: Publishers Back African Literacy Effort With E-Books   http://nyti.ms/Qcll73 ”    
    
    
    @cultureslurp must be cold down there...    
    
    
    @coopeydoop On a big day for #Kindle, pls see a great piece in the Times about publishers' support of @worldreaders http://nyti.ms/Qcll73 ”    
    
    
    Can't wait! RT @gigaom: Our @laurahazardowen is at Amazon's press conference in LA and will be live blogging. http://ow.ly/dw4hZ     
    
    
    Wow! “@paidContent #Amazon New Kindle Fire will be $159. Kindle Fire HD line includes 2 tablets, including a 10" http://ow.ly/dwiYu ”    
    
    
    @cultureslurp I'm thinking #ginandtonics    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Wino" badge on @foursquare for checking in at wine spots! Cheers! http://4sq.com/Q2unlb     
    
    
    @paidContent @laurahazardowen whispercast with voice will be so cool for @worldreaders kids. Immersion reading-yes!  Nice blogging Laura!    
    
    
    Worldreader: Taking the E-Book Revolution to Africa - Businessweek via @BW http://buswk.co/TophSJ     
    
    
    This week = a serious roll with both publishers and the press.  FT, NYT and now Business Week!  Read more and share: http://buswk.co/TophSJ     
    
    
    @MattSchofield @LibTechReplies @Liberationtech @web_forensics @shrutikhurana Love the Love!  All great folks- cheers!    
    
    
    Check out Great Breakthrough For Worldreader – Major Publishers Donate Hundreds of New ebooks http://bit.ly/NRhk7I     
    
    
    Check out Great Breakthrough For Worldreader – Major Publishers Donate Hundreds of New ebooks @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/09/08/great-breakthrough-for-worldreader-major-publishers-donate-hundreds-of-new-ebooks/ …    
    
    
    Read @davidrisherWR in @huffpost- the magic words that can change a kids life in Africa and who is already doing it. http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    New Blog: Meet Gabriel. He Wants to Change His World. Let’s Help Him. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/08/meet-gabriel-he-wants-to-change-his-world-lets-help-him/ …    
    
    
    “I have chance of becoming a better person when I learn from the lives of people in stories" says 14 yr old Gabriel. http://bit.ly/U1WJdA     
    
    
    On #intllitday, the magic words are:"Let's send digital books to the developing world." Awesome post @davidrisherWR! http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    @MattSchofield Did you see @davidrisherWR's post in @huffpostimpact today? THX for being our partner! #intllitday http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    @mshoebri See @davidrisherWR's post in @huffpostimpact- THX for being our partner in getting books into kids hands! http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    BLOG: Sending Kids in Africa Back to School With Great New Books http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/11/sending-kids-in-africa-back-to-school-with-great-new-books/ …    
    
    
    Brilliant! See @elpais about @fcbarcelona = the missing link between children and literacy #Africa via @GonzaloFanjul http://bit.ly/UaHtLE     
    
    
    @Xavi_Hernan Congrats on inspiring kids to read more in Africa!  Cuando el fútbol sirve para algo... más via @elpais http://bit.ly/UaHtLE     
    
    
    Cool article in Publishing Perspectives: Additional Publishers, Caine Prize Partners with Worldreader. http://publishingperspectives.com/2012/09/additional-publishers-partner-with-worldreader/#.UFMnHycTjw4.twitter …    
    
    
    Made me smile! @MattSchofield: FF #ICT4D @silvia_parra @arbeloa @WBPubs @soozmoody @SevincRende @meowtree @korusconsult @occupy_www”    
    
    
    Great idea! "@MattSchofield:your Barca promotion made ME smile! Get @Shakira to do a cover of Waka Waka with Kindles http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dzsuE5ugxf4 …”    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Great Outdoors" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different outdoor spots! http://4sq.com/Ntvevb     
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Swimmies" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different water spots! http://4sq.com/Ntvevd     
    
    
    Cadaques is windy and water is choppy, but Marnaton officials select the plan A route. Prettier but longer. I hope I don't freeze to death!    
    
    
    Marnaton Cadaques was cold and wavy, but nice. 650 people swimming a 6.5k! Lots happier to be @ the after- party! pic.twitter.com/m09S87Mt    
    
    
    I just ousted @javier_aguilar as the mayor of Reial Club de Tennis Barcelona on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dyoUXg     
    
    
    NEW BLOG: Read more our about how we charge #Kindles in #Africa: Powering Reading, Empowering Lives http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/17/powering-reading-empowering-lives/ …    
    
    
    If you like what we're doing: “Help unlock the power of books. Vote for @Worldreaders to speak at SXSWedu! http://shar.es/uZdvp ” RT    
    
    
    7 billion people, 6 billion cell phones in the world. RT @allthingsd: The Mobile Browser Dominates in Emerging Markets http://flpbd.it/9XBXC     
    
    
    So nervous for today's 10K swim in the Hudson with @NYCswim.  I've never swam a 10K race before- I guess it's good to try something new!    
    
    
    Holy crap- We start at 79th street and end past 190th. That's long! @NYCswim    
    
    
    Who knew that there is an adorable red light house underneath the George Washington bridge?  @NYCswim pic.twitter.com/hgvtWc9A    
    
    
    @biNu a hit: there's 484,000 mobile phone readers a month...and growing! http://businesstech.co.za/news/internet/22769/binu-a-hit/ … via @BusinessTechSA    
    
    
    New BLOG: Engendering the Reading Culture. 100's of titles read!  Awesome. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/26/engendering-the-reading-culture/ …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Back to School badge on @foursquare for checking in back on campus! Time to party! Er, study. http://4sq.com/SErCc7     
    
    
    I'm so gonna do this!  Become a Worldreader Fundraiser – Help Get Ebooks to Kids In Africa http://beforeitsnews.com/books/2012/09/become-a-worldreader-fund-raiser-help-get-ebooks-to-kids-in-africa-2446200.html … via @BeforeItsNews    
    
    
    Off to the pool to swim the 4.5k I need to login a total of 50k in September.    
    
    
    Swimming Gibraltar BLOG: Why did @carringtonm decide to swim from Europe to Africa?  It's wily @mauprieto's fault! http://bit.ly/U0JvDA     
    
    
    My goal was to swim 43 K this month and I did 50 K! 66% in Open Water.  Training to raise $ for @worldreaders. http://bit.ly/U0JvDA     
    
    
    I just ousted Colin M. as the mayor of http://Worldreader.org  on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/IM21Wr     
    
    
    I'm in physical pain after seeing Carles Puyol's arm break.  #AnimosPuyol!  You're the best and inspire many. #fcb    
    
    
    BLOG: Read 17 yr old Kate in her own words. Before I met Worldreader, I was writing, but it wasn’t easy for me. #Africa http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    @Oprah Read 17yr old Ghanaian student Kate on why she's writing. BLOG: The Heart of A Poet http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    @MichelleObama Please read 17yr old Ghanaian student, Kate, tell in her own words why she needs to write. #Kindle http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    BLOG Kate: "I wrote a poem called “Agony of a Woman,” which talks about the plight and problems women face in Africa" http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    As Lynn Sherr said: "skin is our largest organ, so swimming is the most sensual sport." I'll think about that tomorrow during the Sitges 10k    
    
    
    It was long but I'm happy it's over! @emilykunze and I both got 1st in our catagories in #marnaton 10k Sitges. pic.twitter.com/N165N4fs    
    
    
    New Blog: Girl Power: Worldreader and FC Barcelona Women’s Team http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/08/girl-power-worldreader-and-fc-barcelonas-womens-team/ …    
    
    
    BLOG: Read how @worldreaders sent African kids inspiring images of FC Barcelona women's soccer team on their Kindles.  http://bit.ly/R88NwG     
    
    
    Asked my daughters what Girls + Education equaled. Love their answer! #basicmath @worldreaders @10x10act pic.twitter.com/3p1TYKZi    
    
    
    @MattSchofield love all the girl power going on! You rock!    
    
    
    @didaclee See how @FCBarcelona Women's Team inspires students in Africa to read more. http://youtu.be/QCLV7n6iluk  #dayofthegirl @worldreaders    
    
    
    Day of the Girl: Honor Her. Motivate Her. Educate Her. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/11/day-of-the-girl-honor-her-motivate-her-educate-her/ … PLEASE RT    
    
    
    @newsdel Hi! I would like to pitch @worldreaders awesome work with Kindles in Africa.  Right up Brian's alley.  Any insight on how?    
    
    
    @BraddJaffy I would like to pitch @worldreaders awesome work with Kindles in African schools.  Any advice? http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2012-09-06/worldreader-taking-the-e-book-revolution-to-africa …    
    
    
    @NickKristof Couldn't agree more. And the key to getting educated girls is getting the reading materials they need. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/david-risher/on-international-day-of-t_b_1955180.html …    
    
    
    @MattSchofield Great! Thx! Just looked at my cc bill and calculated that they read on average 8 books a week! @Kindle    
    
    
    @Oprah We've seen that Kindles even the playing field between boys and girls in schools in Africa. Please see VIDEO http://www.huffingtonpost.com/david-risher/on-international-day-of-t_b_1955180.html …    
    
    
    @JuliadeCelis @worldreaders We're so happy to have you!    
    
    
    @RowdyGaines Met U when I was 12 at Ntls- inspiring! Retired after college, now 40 yr mom training to cross Gibraltar. http://bit.ly/Q2WOvT     
    
    
    Its a rainy day and I'm buried in Gone Girl: A Novel and can't put it down. #pageturner #kindle    
    
    
    Absolutely love this look by @nadjaboz pic.twitter.com/CJH0GwlI    
    
    
    BLOG POST: Mind Games: what seeing a 2 meter fish does to my head http://wp.me/p2MIAW-2Y     
    
    
    I finished Gone Girl: A Novel and highly recommend it to people who have 10 hours to lose themselves in an amazing read.    
    
    
    I just ousted @mauprieto as the mayor of Sausalito on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/d1aQF0     
    
    
    Check out Worldreader and Linda: Kindles Bring Solace To Young Girl In Africa @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/10/17/worldreaders-kindles-bring-solace-to-young-girl-in-africa/ …    
    
    
    Amazon Introduces Whispercast to Manage Large Fleets of Kindles.  And look who pioneered it! Go @Worldreaders!  http://dthin.gs/QrCbvS     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Shutterbug" badge on @foursquare for adding photos to my check-ins. Say cheese! http://4sq.com/T1OUDs     
    
    
    I just ousted @jcmelero as the mayor of Chiringuito Pizzeria Del Puerto on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dfA9b2     
    
    
    The Three Women on the Team http://wp.me/p2MIAW-3V  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    BLOG @carringtonmadden might hate me for this post.  The Three Women on the Team: we'd be 3 out of 25!  http://wp.me/p2MIAW-3V  W/ @emilykunze    
    
    
    I just bought: "Hardcore Swim Women's Scalliwag Cali Drag One Piece" via @swimoutlet http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/38776.htm?color=11590 … BLOG: http://swimminggibraltar.com/     
    
    
    I just bought: "Turbo Comic One Piece - Medium" via @swimoutlet http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/31629.htm?color= …  Read more: http://swimminggibraltar.com/     
    
    
    I just bought: "Dolfin Uglies Spiro Back One Piece".  1 for me, 1 for @emilykunze. @swimoutlet has great suits!  http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/41375.htm?color=37121 …    
    
    
    @RealTonyRocha Hey- I like that you liked this!  Do you know about @worldreaders?    
    
    
    Not a fan of @british_airways right now! BCN to LHR delayed. Missed flight to Dallas. Now going tomorrow via Houston.    
    
    
    I never knew that flying from Barcelona to Dallas takes 3 days.  With british_airways, apparently it does!  Delays delays delays!  Horrible.    
    
    
    @emilykunze and @mauprieto rock out in a 7.5 race in cold waters http://wp.me/p2MIAW-4B  Go Team!    
    
    
    @MysteryCoach thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan meaning hot air balloon? might have been faster.    
    
    
    Check out Amazon Promoting Worldreader On Its Homepage!  Great Publicity.  Well done @amazon! @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/11/01/amazon-promoting-worldreader-on-its-homepage-great-publicity/ …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Foodie" badge on @foursquare for checking in at five different places rated by Zagat! http://4sq.com/U1jXQD     
    
    
    Barcelona plaza  in after-school mode.  http://ligh.tt/dBR     
    
    
    Tanzania- awesome! Read more: @Worldreaders Brings Kindles To Yet Another African Country @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/11/07/worldreader-brings-kindle-ereaders-to-yet-another-african-country/ …    
    
    
    @Top_eReader thanks for the @worldreaders shout-out on #amazon!    
    
    
    I love Rafa! He's won 7 tournaments in Barcelona-right below my house.  http://ligh.tt/lD5     
    
    
    Hope to not see this in the ocean this weekend. #swimming http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rue-FIHkRt/     
    
    
    Big party tonight in one of my favorite stores in Barcelona. Gotta love a vegetarian rock heir! @stellamcCartney http://ligh.tt/bCR     
    
    
    Stella McCartney in Barcelona! I confess- I'm a bit star struck! http://ligh.tt/lD9     
    
    
    @davidrisherWR I tink so!    
    
    
    I like this highlight of Walt Mossberg twirling in a chair...  http://ligh.tt/aCd     
    
    
    @FranklinMissy Hey M- we're 4 old swimmers who are planning to swim the Strait of Gibraltar this summer. U inspire us! http://swimminggibraltar.com     
    
    
    Stella mcCartney- Colombian style! http://ligh.tt/mDY     
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney Congrats on your amazing party yesterday. It'll mark a before and after in Barcelona. I wanted to pitch in 1 minute an idea    
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney You designed outfits for the amazing UK Olympic team. Would you be interested in designing swim suits for....See next tweet    
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney for 3 average women swimming the Strait of Gibraltar to raise money for e-books to Africa? Pleeease?    
    
    
    @StellMcCartney please read more about our crazy swim for social good- http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rx9KacHkbt/     
    
    
    @MattSchofield only that she is Colombian.....think Gloria from Modern Family!    
    
    
    @MattSchofield indeed she is... But the pic I posted is of my Colombian friend in a @stellamccartney store! :-)    
    
    
    love u"@DrWider: could u b cuter? @stellamccartney pls read more about our swim for social good- http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rx9KacHkbt/ ”    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan thanks for the #ff!    
    
    
    About to do the 4x1000 relay! #swimming with @emilykunze http://ligh.tt/kEp     
    
    
    @MattSchofield thanks for the shout out! Have a great weekend....    
    
    
    Celebrating the 4k swim with @mauprieto @emilykunze #ginandtonics http://ligh.tt/lF5     
    
    
    @csutswim big fan of yours... Would love to interview you for http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  por favor!    
    
    
    Dog and beach = goodness http://ligh.tt/gEB     
    
    
    NEW BLOG: Why are we training so hard to swim from Europe to Africa?  We're Swimming for Books http://wp.me/p2MIAW-88  @emilykunze @mauprieto    
    
    
    BLOG: @worldreaders has been selected by @chase as 1 of 25 charities to win $1 million! But We Need You and You and You http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/14/we-need-you-and-you-and-you/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for the retweet! Will you help? Por favor?    
    
    
    @MelyNicolau_3, @M_unzue6, @anit82009= total studs who love @worldreaders! Go Barça Femenino! pic.twitter.com/OWNHWPun    
    
    
    The women's team from @FCB come into @worldreaders office and love what we're doing with e-books in Africa!  http://ligh.tt/gGp     
    
    
    @cultureslurp Thanks for your help with this!    
    
    
    No. 15 made me chuckle: Cartoons from the Issue of November 19th, 2012 : The New Yorker -  http://www.newyorker.com/humor/issuecartoons/2012/11/19/cartoons_20121112?slide=15?mbid=social_mobile_tweet …    
    
    
    @BeatrizTejeiro thanks so much for getting the word out! Vote @worldreaders!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo you are so awesome!    
    
    
    @mauprieto about to swim an 8k with @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/x3w0eavq    
    
    
    Trying to psych myself up to swim- but it's cold and dreary in Sitges! @mauprieto @emilykunze http://ligh.tt/dIf     
    
    
    Gangnam style by 2 little Spaniards. http://ligh.tt/nKY     
    
    
    I just ousted Alberto G. as the mayor of Chiringuito Pizzeria Del Puerto on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dfA9b2     
    
    
    @Oprah You love education, Africa, reading, and the Kindle.  This is MADE for you!  Will you help get the word out? http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/14/we-need-you-and-you-and-you/ …    
    
    
    BLOG: Peek into the mind of @emilykunze as she swims long distances... READ: Swimming for Something Bigger Than Me http://wp.me/p2RyIb-8k     
    
    
    Love this article: E-Books Advance Literacy in Africa http://blogs.edweek.org/edweek/bookmarks/2012/11/e-books_advance_literacy_in_africa.html?cmp=SOC-SHR-TW … via @educationweek    
    
    
    New Blog: "What Are You Thankful For?" Helping amazing young women like Linda achieve her dreams. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/21/what-are-you-thankful-for/ …    
    
    
    Learning how to make chocolate macaron- like La Duree! http://ligh.tt/fNg     
    
    
    Making pumpkin gnocchi- Italian style http://ligh.tt/aM8     
    
    
    BLOG: Richard- Ghanaian High Schooler: "Education is a superb institution that offers the individual something unique" http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/23/whats-an-education-worth/ …    
    
    
    @mauprieto @emilykunze you forgot to say... And cold!    
    
    
    Happy belated Thanksgiving! Gulp! pic.twitter.com/SEYJMl0K    
    
    
    HIV, genocide, human trafficking. W/out education nothing changes. Vote & Share http://vote4books.com/WR_SM  @worldreaders Please RT!    
    
    
    @joelleLw You are awesome!  Thanks for getting the word out about @worldreaders chance to win and empower a generation.    
    
    
    @KettlebellsBCN Thanks for getting the word out!    
    
    
    @KopoKopoInc @worldreaders Thanks for your support!  We'll need more in the coming days!    
    
    
    @buddingreader @amazon I know!  It's awesome! @worldreaders    
    
    
    @lizzie_nyc Thanks for the support!  http://vote4books.com !    
    
    
    @Chare11 Thanks for the support!  We can't do it without you!    
    
    
    @erikbl Seriously awesome!    
    
    
    @WackyMamaBear Awesome!    
    
    
    @cheekymommaof2 Thanks so much for your support!  Books For All!    
    
    
    @msafoundation @davidrisherWR Totally awesome!  Just one tiny thing: for the rest of the week when you tweet.. it's @worldreaders with an S.    
    
    
    @owenswims93 @mauprieto @emilykunze Absolutely!  You could hang with us. That is until you blow by us in the race- then you're on your own!    
    
    
    @msafoundation @worldreaders Perfect- thanks a million for your support!    
    
    
    This weekend I'm swimming from the Costa Brava around Islas Medas & back w/ @emilykunze & @mauprieto.  Scared of cold! pic.twitter.com/5PxYsWAB    
    
    
    @emilykunze is left handed and I'm deaf in one ear. It sounds so much better in Spanish: Zurda y Sorda. http://instagr.am/p/Skd35Rnkf5/     
    
    
    @shakira Pls help @worldreaders win a $1 mil grant from @ChaseGiving so they can bring education into rural Africa. http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    @shakira All you have to do is ask your fans to vote! Education change the world. @worldreaders #booksforall http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    @8hakiraa Help this BCN-based charity win $1 mill for education in Africa.  It's got Shakira written all over it! http://www.vote4books.com/WR_SM . RT!    
    
    
    @BarcelonaStat Pls support FCB collaborator @worldreaders- vote for them to win $1 mill for education in Africa! http://www.vote4books.com/WR_SM .    
    
    
    @teddevers @mauprieto Thanks for the support!  Can you ask the person next to you to vote too?    
    
    
    @Roman_barb Sylvia, share w/ your friends that @worldreaders needs votes to win a $1 mill grant from @ChaseGiving! http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @CornelWest Hi, from a Religion Major P'94.  Now working at @worldreaders to bring e-books into remote Africa. Pls see next tweet.    
    
    
    @CornelWest We need your help in getting out the vote to win $1 mill. from @ChaseGiving. Winning = e-readers for thousands in Africa. Next..    
    
    
    @CornelWest Pls ask your fans to vote for us: http://vote4books.com/WR_SM  so we can do more of this! #Education Empowers! THX! pic.twitter.com/dyu8TmxS    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Hey KL! Would you help us? @worldreaders can win $1 mill from @chasegiving but we need votes! VOTE: http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @PenguinClass @worldreaders So awesome!  Thanks!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo you are such a star!!!!    
    
    
    @bgurley @worldreaders @davidrisherWR Thanks for the support!    
    
    
    It's December 1st- 'Tis the season! http://ligh.tt/lSj     
    
    
    @ivankavisnjic Thanks for getting the word out!  Have you voted?  It only takes 20 seconds...http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @nautyinaccra @ameyaw112 Awesome! Have you voted?  It only takes 20 seconds...http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Thanks for helping spread the word! Today's the last day of voting!    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Its llike the 50 yard dash- we're sprinting to the finish line with 4 other fast runners neck and neck. Too close to tell!    
    
    
    @iesealumni Thanks so much for getting the word out! Today's the last day to vote!    
    
    
    @Pitbull Worldreader is close to winning a $1m grant that would allow education worldwide. Pls support us. Vote &share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @Pitbull Worldwide education. Kids all over Africa with books. Isn't that awesome? Pls support us today! Vote & share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @RealPaulWalker Kids all over Africa w/ books. Isn't that awesome? Pls support @worldreaders today! #ROWW Vote & share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @Diane_Keaton As an author yourself, you can help!  Pls vote for @worldreaders today! Books improve lives. #Africa http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    I'm at the #GivingAwards w/ @worldreaders & other amazing non-profits like @MoreThanMeORG @fugeesfamily @sproutup @shesthefirst! #Education    
    
    
    Those folks at @ChaseGiving know how 2 throw a great party!  Ate chez Joachim Splichal (@PatinaDTLA chef) w/ #americangiving charities. YUM!    
    
    
    Prepping for #americangiving awards by @ChaseGiving.  Representing @worldreaders: we're 1 of 25 amazing charities transforming the world!    
    
    
    @Samasource It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work. #inspire    
    
    
    @TimmyGlobHealth It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work. #inspire    
    
    
    @krochetkids It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and stay awesome. #inspire    
    
    
    @joelmchale It was great to see you at the #AmericanGiving Awards! You had us all laughing in spite of all the nervous energy in the room.    
    
    
    @TeamRubicon It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and stay awesome. #inspire    
    
    
    @TogetherWeRise It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Can't believe all those bikes! #inspire    
    
    
    @katiemeyler It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and congratulations. #inspire    
    
    
    @lalasheila I love my girl!    
    
    
    Read our wrap-up of the #AmericanGiving Awards.  We were Close, But…. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/12/09/close-but/ … via @jbaljko    
    
    
    @allysonfelix Great seeing you at The American Giving Awards.  You looked fab.  I loved the necklace- gold- b/c that's what you win!    
    
    
    @ColbieCaillat You were awesome at the American Giving Awards!  Thanks for entertaining us charities! #Inspire    
    
    
    @RylandKing Really enjoyed meeting you at AGA!  You're awesome.  Hey, can you send me a link to how you get people to open chapters?    
    
    
    @katiemeyler I am so happy for you!  Congrats.  xo    
    
    
    @mshoebri @lizzywood Sometimes the results don't go the way you want them to... but you learn and move on!  xo    
    
    
    @buddingreader @worldreaders You are so so right!    
    
    
    Who inspired me to swim from Europe to Africa?  My inspiration: Jen Schumacher http://wp.me/p2RyIb-a6  via the amazing @channelswimjen    
    
    
    @darrenemiller Are you in here?  Please read about My inspiration: Jen Schumacher http://wp.me/p2RyIb-a6  who are the others?    
    
    
    My rockstar colleague @nadjaboz gave my daughters the coolest pressie ever- signed @fcbarcelona shirts by @3gerardpique http://ligh.tt/mXX     
    
    
    @hale_a thanks so much for your support! #invaluable    
    
    
    @CatherinMcQuaid thanks for spreading the word about @worldreaders work!    
    
    
    I'm going to support @mauprieto's panel. Hot Startups In The City Of Gaudi — TechCrunch Barcelona http://techcrunch.com/2012/11/27/hot-startups-in-the-city-of-gaudi-techcrunch-barcelona-meetup-december-13/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    @mikebutcher hey Mike! I wanna tell you about BCN's hottest techy non-profit- @worldreaders. See ya today at hubby @mauprieto panel.    
    
    
    @kiwanja thanks so much for your support!    
    
    
    @RothwellSmith is this the first Nigerian publisher? You're rocking!    
    
    
    Watching @albertarmengol @pgelis @evavillaro @mauprieto at Tech Cruch Meet Up with @mikebutcher #barcelona pic.twitter.com/vGJ3wkrP    
    
    
    At #TCBarcelona- planned or by coincidence that there's the Barcelona chair on stage? pic.twitter.com/r4mB800t    
    
    
    Congrats 2 @cultureslurp and team for organizing #TCBarcelona- a great forum for a budding tech scene. And thanks 4 mentoring @worldreaders    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel Are you Melvin Stewart, the butterflier from NC? If so, I knew you years ago- WSY swimmer. #smallworld    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel thanks! Cool that you won a gold- somehow I didn't know that. I'm swimming again- training 2 cross the Strait of G this summer    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel We're raising $ 4 good with our trans-continental swim.  Have u done the Strait? http://www.owswimming.com . U could do it BTFLY    
    
    
    @mikebutcher you are a natural at leading a panel.  I wanted to connect w/ u  w/ @mauprieto but we had a weird dog- attack so we had 2 bolt.    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel got it- we hope you'll keep us non-prof swimmers doing crazy stuff for good causes on your radar.  xoxo SM (& join any time!!)    
    
    
    Happy 23rd @mauprieto! http://ligh.tt/aXp     
    
    
    @mijarosoft @worldreaders Thanks so much for the shout out!  Yes, a quiet e-book revolution is going on in Africa that will empower.  #Love!    
    
    
    @skrud I love that!    
    
    
    As usual, when I travel alone with my daughters, we get stranded due to late flights- but we make the best of it! http://4sq.com/ZdLNC1     
    
    
    @loreac hi there lovely! Leaving today, I hope. Girls are dying to ski and see cousins. How are things? Xo    
    
    
    Getting snowed in here in Denver. http://ligh.tt/fdG     
    
    
    @mauprieto take a look: http://dailynews.openwaterswimming.com/2012/12/who-is-trending-in-open-water-swimming.html … http://t.co/  via @darrenemiller    
    
    
    Wait- In Dec @InStyleMagazine I see that Yves Saint Laurent changed its branding to Saint Laurent.  Why? Read more: http://bit.ly/ZqP7d3     
    
    
    @owenswims93 Thanks for all your support, Owen- can we get you to guest blog?  From the best himself?    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Any ideas pop into your mind?  One thing I think is interesting is how small the sub-world of OW swimming is.  See next tweet    
    
    
    @owenswims93 I wonder if a true insider like you could tell the world about the global OW scene- a glimpse in for people who know nothing    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Although that might be too long- but it's one thing people repeatedly ask me about.    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Like: is it odd that u know both Damien & Jen Schumacher?  From Argentina and the US-- you from Ireland?  I think that's cool.    
    
    
    @DocumentDriven @ClintonGlobal @SusanUtley @writehedgebrook @worldreader @BookLoversInc @TheBookCellar Thanks and happy holidays!    
    
    
    @owenswims93 I know!  But I kinda think OW swimmers are a breed of their own...    
    
    
    Close your eyes & imagine what 200,000+ books for #Africa looks like.  Now open them: 877 #Kindles on their way! pic.twitter.com/jOI5FyVY    
    
    
    @dbudwin Hey man, good to hear from you!  How's it going?  Hope well- happy holidays to you!    
    
    
    @cultureslurp I had a very funny dream about you last night!  I'll tell you over a #ginandtonic back in Barcelona.  Remind me!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo Hope you're having a happy holiday! xo    
    
    
    @leila_c I loved your ad with @sorel- "Get your boots dirty."  Missed you at #AGA but nice to meet your colleagues. http://www.examiner.com/article/sorel-footwear-introduces-get-your-boots-dirty-fall-2012-campaign …    
    
    
    Favorite Christmas traditions- decorating gingerbread houses with primas. #awesome! http://ligh.tt/kdg     
    
    
    @lizzywood Merry merry to the best girl to work with ever!    
    
    
    @BrunoMars Your performance on SNL singing Michael Jackson, Katy Perry, Louis Armstrong etc. was a "Best of 2012"! http://vimeo.com/52406325     
    
    
    @mattiseman I do too!  No one ever taught me.  To wrap presents, that is.    
    
    
    @jcrew I am giving all my friends this genius thing! It's so tiny and perfect.  http://www.luuux.com/health-beauty/j-crew-mr-mrs-emergency-gold-emergency-kit …    
    
    
    Christmas cheer with the family....love this time of year! http://ligh.tt/odu     
    
    
    @mattiseman good thing you took it PDF! Merry x-mas!!    
    
    
    Love! @melindagates: The intellectual challenge of working together to solve the world’s biggest problems is uplifting. http://gates.ly/ZoyU8     
    
    
    @Andracke @jbaljko @NadjaBoz @JuliadeCelis Merry Christmas to AMAZING TEAM COMMS!!!!    
    
    
    First African Designed Smartphone, Tablet Hit Market http://mashable.com/2012/12/25/african-tablet-smartphone/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    @RedHourBen Your humor is my absolute favorite.  But it must be hard to be funny all the time- even on your tweets!  #IFeelForYa!    
    
    
    What does @worldreaders do w/ 365 days?  3 new African countries, 250,000 e-books, an Amazon home page, an app... shew! http://bit.ly/VlYAhu     
    
    
    @mijarosoft @cjbrandt @beckystraw @sloane @susangordo @CynthiaHellen @srudat @riaglo @rmack Thank you!  Happy New Year to you too!    
    
    
    A look back at an amazing year at Worldreader.  2012 was HUGE! But 2013 will only be bigger. http://bit.ly/VlYAhu     
    
    
    @Alexweir1949 over 1000 #kindles... In January we'll launch 1000 more! And there are half a million reading on our book app via @BiNu    
    
    
    New Years Resolution #1- Do a lot more of this! http://www.OWswimming.com  pic.twitter.com/2Gfm0Xbj    
    
    
    In 50 yrs, Gates will be remembered by philanthropic work. I bet Jobs could be forgotten! Read: How Giving Became Cool http://nyti.ms/ZBWjmG     
    
    
    @Zevlowe for you! RT @latimestravel: Gear: You can step out in style on a flight or on a beach walk http://flip.it/tEUXb     
    
    
    New Years Resolution #2- join a flash mob. Never even seen one!    
    
    
    @Kuhn Eric, sorry...that was me. Bummed to miss you but hope to connect soon!    
    
    
    @CherylStrayed I loved Wild. Would you consider donating it to @worldreaders kids in Africa? It'd be easy and high impact! #kindle    
    
    
    @Alexweir1949 @binu looks like am interesting project- best of luck and keep doing good!    
    
    
    @NadjaBoz send more pics of your adorable nephew!!!!    
    
    
    This trend will only grow! “@PublishersWkly: E-book Reading Rises, Print Reading Dips http://pwne.ws/V95Yug ”    
    
    
    The power of gift cards and omni-present devices @RWW: Christmas Day's online spending this year jumped 27% over 2011. http://flip.it/6wOuz     
    
    
    New Years Resolution #3- Learn how to make the perfect #GinandTonic and
serve it to all my friends pic.twitter.com/n0lDtOky    
    
    
    I love that @worldreaders adds local languages to its Kindle programs in #Africa- like Kinyarwanda, Kiswahili, & Twi http://eepurl.com/tsp_v     
    
    
    New Years Resolution #4- Don't sweat the small stuff, unless the small stuff is these two little thangs... pic.twitter.com/AEPpngkG    
    
    
    @emilykunze @mauprieto I swam a total of 210 Kilometers in 2012... but will need to double that before we cross Gibraltar! #OWswimming    
    
    
    Once again, Tom Ford kills it- I love Carnal Red for New Years! The Best Nail Polish Brands http://www.realsimple.com/beauty-fashion/skincare/hands-feet/nail-polish-brands-00100000080429/index.html … via @RealSimple    
    
    
    New Years Resolution #5- Make lots of magic happen with the amazing @worldreaders team in 2013! #NYE    
    
    
    Happy New Year to my fav @worldreaders helpers @cultureslurp @julietrell @MattSchofield @DidacLee @mauprieto @barakkassar    
    
    
    @EmWatson you would be a perfect ambassador for @worldreaders- giving African kids access to e-books! Can u imagine life w/out books?    
    
    
    To my 24 hour no-tmoo @DrWider...Happy New Years! Hope to see ya lots in 2013!    
    
    
    @mattiseman have you seen Girls on HBO? Very entertaining.    
    
    
    I’d rather be hit in the head by an iPad Mini than a 650-page book. The Hazards of E-Devices on Planes via @nickbilton http://nyti.ms/TqUioC     
    
    
    @stellakids The cutest dress ever- for a little vegetarian. pic.twitter.com/gy6YMbcL    
    
    
    Best pizza in the Rockies- Beau Jo's mountain pies (@ Beau Jo's Pizza w/ @mauprieto) [pic]: http://4sq.com/Wln4Eq     
    
    
    Awesome- was it helpful? “@AtomAdeyemi: I finished reading HIV/AIDS Prevention: Best Practices on @Worldreaders App http://goo.gl/iTyM1 ”    
    
    
    @NickKristof- U should take the winner to c how real change in education is a possibility- @worldreaders e-book programs in remote Africa    
    
    
    @julietrell send a link!    
    
    
    A discovery! La Villa Cockteleria- a #Gin&Tonic bar in the heart of Sitges. pic.twitter.com/B4GUWdZH    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong that's pretty good- 1:15.  I saw your Superfrog video and noticed u were passing bikers like they were tied 2 a fence pole.    
    
    
    @docphelan Hi Darren, what swim are you training for now?  Curious.    
    
    
    First OW swim of 2013 in Sitges. It's  16 degrees C and feels like May! #OWswimming http://ligh.tt/kgN     
    
    
    @owenswims93 The water was too warm for you- it was a sweltering 13.5 degrees C! I had a wetsuit, neoprene cap and shoes- still froze!    
    
    
    Los Reyes Magos don't bring gifts to the Prieto girls, but at least they get some cake! @ Sitges Beach http://instagr.am/p/UG9JNdHkWw/     
    
    
    @JuliadeCelis yes! When are you in? Can't wait to see ya!    
    
    
    @JuliadeCelis Yes- there is a team meet on Tuesday at 5- will you make it? xo    
    
    
    Yes, this guy's a stud. RT @allthingsd: Let Jason Kilar Take a Bow -by @pkafka http://flip.it/o4CY3     
    
    
    Another inflection point? When folks can get the reading material they need-- like 500K+ people a month on their cell. http://forumblog.org/2013/01/the-optimists-timeline/ …    
    
    
    @tammytibbetts @erinleighnyc @nikki_lynnn congrats rockstars!    
    
    
    Oh no! Praying all's ok. “@cnnbrk: Plane believed to be carrying head of Italy's Missoni fashion house missing. http://on.cnn.com/USqdiF ”    
    
    
    @docphelan @lancearmstrong love 2 read your swimming tweets. Come 2 Spain and we'll do some OW training in the med. I'll invite u 2 tapas.    
    
    
    @ErinLeighNYC @tammytibbetts It's good- thanks! Swam today in the Med. It was 55 degrees C- freezing 4 water temps. Keep up your good work!    
    
    
    @MichaelPhelps Pls RT to support 3 40 yr old moms who will swim from Europe to Africa 4 charity- Come join! :-) http://owswimming.com/     
    
    
    @ryanlochte Pls RT to support 3 40 yr old moms who will swim from Europe to Africa 4 charity. Wanna do it w/ us? http://owswimming.com/     
    
    
    @FranklinMissy Pls RT to support 3 40 yr old moms who will swim from Europe to Africa 4 charity. http://owswimming.com/     
    
    
    @Kuhn How was Aspen?  You caught the best snow we've seen in ages....Last year was depressing!    
    
    
    @zsniderman Happy new year- Hope you're well.  Let's do something cool together in 2013!    
    
    
    So far @mauprieto @emilykunze and I've raised $1,406 4 @worldreaders- we're gonna swim from Europe 2 Africa for books.  http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    Gotta love Sitges' http://ligh.tt/ohC     
    
    
    @GeorgesMunga good for you! How is it?    
    
    
    @TrentGrimsey just read about your Channel swim in @openwaterswim and heard about it too from @DamianBlaum.  Very impressive! What's next?    
    
    
    @TrentGrimsey Come to Spain 4 some @Marnaton races in 2013.  Me, @mauprieto & @emilykunze will organize.  Your bud @owenswims93 might come!    
    
    
    @AlexMeyerSwims What are you training for now?  Any swims in Spain in 2013?  We're training for Gibraltar. pic.twitter.com/nwXOYRQY    
    
    
    @donalbuckley My dad says that I don't need to outswim sharks, I just need 2 outswim @mauprieto. Have U ever seen one? pic.twitter.com/mVH7IYjo    
    
    
    While training 2 swim from Europe 2 Africa we've noticed that the #swimming world is small- @owenswims93 explains why- http://bit.ly/UxG73G     
    
    
    Rarely have I come across someone I admire more- pls c @owenswims93 blog w/ insights into the global OWswimming world http://bit.ly/UxG73G     
    
    
    @channelswimjen, @darrenemiller see once again how you've inspired folks! http://bit.ly/UxG73G     
    
    
    1 aspect of #OWswimming that separates it from other sports is swimmers are all connected! @owenswims93 - http://bit.ly/UxG73G     
    
    
    @jenniepete hi! We've not stopped- but you need to speak with @lizzywood who's just getting back today. Best of luck!!!    
    
    
    @vzain Thanks!  We're training all year for the big crossing.  Do u know about @worldreaders and their work bringing e-books 2 Africa?    
    
    
    @DamianBlaum I'm sure 2013 will be a great year for you too! :-)  Keep us posted....    
    
    
    @swimnewsonly Here's another great version: http://owswimming.com/2013/01/06/guest-post-owen-okeefe-on-the-close-knit-global-open-water-swimming-scene/ …    
    
    
    So, not only does it have strong currents and huge ships, but this?-RT @Earthquakecolin Tremors recorded 7 minutes ago- Strait Of Gibraltar    
    
    
    @OWSwimming Please see our latest post- everything u need to know about swimming the English Channel! http://owswimming.com/2013/01/06/guest-post-owen-okeefe-on-the-close-knit-global-open-water-swimming-scene/ …    
    
    
    @OpenWaterSC Check out our latest post- everything you need to know if you're considering swimming the English Channel- http://owswimming.com/2013/01/06/guest-post-owen-okeefe-on-the-close-knit-global-open-water-swimming-scene/ …    
    
    
    @jimjumpingfish Do you agree that the OW swimming world is so small? http://owswimming.com/2013/01/06/guest-post-owen-okeefe-on-the-close-knit-global-open-water-swimming-scene/ …    
    
    
    @TrentGrimsey What are your big 2013 goals? Hard to beat 2012! :-)  Huge Congrats.    
    
    
    @SpeedoUSA Do you think the OW global swimming scene is small? If any doubts, see: http://owswimming.com/2013/01/06/guest-post-owen-okeefe-on-the-close-knit-global-open-water-swimming-scene/ …    
    
    
    @owenswims93 @DamianBlaum- Crossing Gibraltar is my biggest goal.  Then I might do a @nycswim and then @Marnaton's Cadaques & Formentera. U?    
    
    
    I seriously love Moravian Sugar Cookies from my hometown- #Winston-Salem.  http://www.hanescookies.com/hanes_cs/default.asp ….  That and @krispykreme.    
    
    
    Hi @TheBigBlueSwim- @mauprieto and @emilykunze should sign up.  When is it?    
    
    
    @davemorgannyc Can't wait to hear about all you see.    
    
    
    @stevehargadon that's awesome! Remind @davidrisherWR to ask folks to follow @worldreaders. Signed, his Dir. of Comms:-)    
    
    
    @davidrisherWR I just spoke to @julietrell and we're cooking up some ideas for 2013. Stay tuned!    
    
    
    A great read- Antifragile by @nntaleb. And I love this review of it: You Are All Soft! Embrace Chaos! via @ActualNYTMK http://nyti.ms/TpC2KA     
    
    
    @IamAfricaStory great! Email me at Susan dot worldreader dot org and we'll connect!    
    
    
    For some reason, these trash bins in Barcelona remind me of minions from Despicable Me. http://ligh.tt/khI     
    
    
    But tonight, a 9 year old boy in Uganda is begging to stay up a little longer- to read on his Kindle. http://bit.ly/VR2BIv     
    
    
    @AtomAdeyemi did you like it?    
    
    
    @cs_lawson thanks for the shout-out!    
    
    
    @lsheehy you are so right! Publishers and authors contact @lizzywood to change the world!    
    
    
    Staggering!  See what @worldreaders has accomplished in a short amount of time!  All our newsletters in one place: http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/mediaroom/newsletters/ …    
    
    
    @topedutweets But tonight, a 9 year old boy in Uganda is begging to stay up a little longer- to read on his Kindle. http://bit.ly/VR2BIv     
    
    
    @GPforEducation But tonight, a 9 year old boy in Uganda is begging to stay up a little longer- to read on his Kindle. http://bit.ly/VR2BIv     
    
    
    @GOOD But tonight, a 9 year old boy in Uganda is begging to stay up a little longer- to read on his Kindle. http://bit.ly/VR2BIv     
    
    
    @mikelgustafson I'm swimming from Europe to Africa- need goggles that r clear, stay on and don't give me a headache! Suggestions? #swimming    
    
    
    @janetevans What are your favorite goggles? Looking for clear ones that stay on and don't give headaches while I swim from Europe to Africa.    
    
    
    @lululemon Do you make swim wear?    
    
    
        
    
    
    @lululemon Yes, PLEASE!  We're Lulu fans & are swimming from Europe 2 Africa 4 charity.  Need a cool look- we'd buy it! http://www.OWswimming.com     
    
    
    @ChattyMate You too- have a nice weekend!    
    
    
    @lululemon That just put a huge grin on my face.  Can't wait for Lulu Swimwear!    
    
    
    @emilykunze “@lululemon: Wow, what a crazy awesome goal!  here's a pretty good chance we'll see swimwear in 2013 so keep your eyes out.”    
    
    
    @loreac Hey! Coming to NYC during Semana Santa. Will u be there? Xo    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Greasy Spoon" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different diners! http://4sq.com/ZQQ5yG     
    
    
    This is heart warming- Love this video “@paulkbiba: Worldreader Featured on United Nations TV  http://bit.ly/13ojU8C ”    
    
    
    @loreac @mauprieto @davemorgannyc Let's make a dinner date for yummy fun place any night from april 1-4? Ours (tiny), yours (huge) or out?    
    
    
    @usmseditor Hi- I'm swimming the Strait of Gibraltar and need googles that are clear, stay on, and don't give me a headache.  Suggestions?    
    
    
    @Nickkristof see this video & lemme know if u wanna see it in person. Worldreader Featured on United Nations TV http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2013/01/11/worldreader-featured-on-united-nations-tv/ …    
    
    
    Hey open water swimmers, our blog got a new look. Do you like it? http://www.OWswimming.com     
    
    
    .@Jbaljko I especially like AAYFKMWTS. Twitter Abbreviations You Need To Know http://www.businessinsider.com/twitter-abbreviations-2010-8?0=sai … via @sai    
    
    
    @owenswims93 thanks!!! The water here in Barcelona was 10 degrees today. Your opinion- Hot or cold?    
    
    
    @socialgoodmoms Check out 3 moms swimming from Europe to Africa for more digital books for Africa. http://www.OWswimming.com  #FightIlliteracy    
    
    
    This kinda makes me feel like a whimp! "Introducing a precise open water swimming temperature scale" http://wp.me/pMhWJ-13E  via @donalbuckley    
    
    
    @speedo I'm swimming the Strait of Gibraltar and need normal googles that are clear, stay on, and don't give me a headache.  Suggestions?    
    
    
    @mauprieto @donalbuckley @owenswims93 except y'all are gonna think its freakishly warm- prob 18+ so Donal will think he's in a movie! :-)    
    
    
    100% Agree! "Because bad as it sometimes is to get in, staying out longer will only make it worse." http://wp.me/pMhWJ-1Hj  via @donalbuckley    
    
    
    @bpmilne I just enjoyed your 2012 Lessons Learned via @DidacLee. Nice observations- agree 100% on valuing people who tell u what they think!    
    
    
    @usmseditor THX! I will try.  The thing about fit is that it usually takes about 1 Hr to begin the headache, so hard to tell in the store.    
    
    
    @kimberleyswims Are you doing that with or w/out wetsuit?    
    
    
    .@Mauprieto RT @GOOD: Bartenders on bikes: G & Ts for London's unlikely corners http://flip.it/L4VGY     
    
    
    @donalbuckley @Michael5732 @owenswims93 This is a great video from Cadaques 2010- see all the wetsuits? @mauprieto http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QRw7Md1n4Bo …    
    
    
    I love all the @worldreaders volunteers!  Love the blue glasses @emilykunze- rockstar. http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/team/     
    
    
    @AtomAdeyemi that is seriously awesome!    
    
    
    @donalbuckley @owenswims93 @michael5732 I had to explain this tweet to @mauprieto :-)    
    
    
    @kimberleyswims hardcore! Go sister!    
    
    
    @cultureslurp you always have great advice! Thanks for picking me up!    
    
    
    @cultureslurp can we make it when I collect on the first bet?    
    
    
    Look who's playing tennis on the court next to me and @emilykunze! #Rafa! pic.twitter.com/zvp9MpSg    
    
    
    .@Lizzywood so glad we're ahead of the curve on M- things! RT @TechCrunch: M-Commerce Boom. http://flip.it/UGFAp  by @sarahintampa    
    
    
    @Lizzywood, u know about this? RT @mashable: Underdog Operating Systems to Shake Up Smartphone Scene http://flip.it/s1Xth  via @techreview    
    
    
    @lancearmstrong @oprah I have no idea what'll go down tomorrow, but I hope folks move on and appreciate @livestrong and an amazing athlete.    
    
    
    @alexmeyerswims Doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from u would be much appreciated!    
    
    
    @CassiePatten Doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from u would be greatly appreciated!    
    
    
    @HalSwims Doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from u would be appreciated!    
    
    
    @NatalieCoughlin Doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from u would be so appreciated!    
    
    
    @RebSoni Doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from you would be awesome!    
    
    
    @AmandaRayBeard Doing a 30 sec poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . A RT from you would be awesome!    
    
    
    @kimberleyswims would you mind doing a 30 second poll on how OW swimmers define "cold" water http://ow.ly/gRgr9 . And a RT please?    
    
    
    I'm enjoying reading Antifragile by @nntaleb so much. Typical book that I read too fast and hate when it's over.    
    
    
    @AtomAdeyemi you're reading a ton! Way to go!    
    
    
    @lizzywood “@UniqueVisitor: More people on the planet own a cell phone (5.1B) than a toothbrush (4.2B) ~ via Mobile Marketing Assoc Asia"    
    
    
    @Carcharius that's my point- I hope everyone can move on. He's already faced the music for cheating, and yes, he's an amazing athlete.    
    
    
    .@lizzywood @davidrisherWR I found it!  RT @NewsHour Helping Where 'There Are More Cell Phones Than Toothbrushes'  http://www.pbs.org/newshour/rundown/2012/09/helping.html …    
    
    
    Celebrity sighting- my hero Nadal hits with coach/ uncle. http://ligh.tt/sI     
    
    
    Happy to be representing @worldreaders this am at the Journee des ONG's au LFB. Along with other great ONG's like @vicenteferrer!    
    
    
    @deLame_97 glad you liked it! :-)    
    
    
    @PauZafra @montse_rivas_ Thank you both for listening!  If you wanna help our cause, visit http://www.worldreaders.org  THX!    
    
    
    Watching the @lancearmstrong interview on @oprah breaks my heart. I truly hope he can find a way to make right of a really bad wrong.    
    
    
    This is funny though- Lance Armstrong Admits To Using Performance-Enhancing Drugs To Show Remorse http://onion.com/V7gDKK  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    @danestrada9 Thanks!  I'm glad you liked it!  If you wanna know more, visit http://www.worldreader.org     
    
    
    Just used @shazam w/ a @katieperry song and saw LyricPlay. It's instant karaoke! pic.twitter.com/dCClrphk    
    
    
    .@Lizzywood RT @paidContent: This week in ebooks: Kobo ramps up, Book Country goes free, Inkling gets Googled http://flip.it/oXghe     
    
    
    Decorating cupcakes- Magnolia Bakery recipe! Yum! http://ligh.tt/ijz     
    
    
    There's some seriously big waves here in Sitges!  http://ligh.tt/r09     
    
    
    @cultureslurp so cool! Gotta say, I've not seen waves like that ever. @NadjaBoz get back here!    
    
    
    .@mauprieto posted results from cold water swimming poll- thx 4 participating! BTW, I come across like a total ass! http://bit.ly/VTGLYa     
    
    
    Just swam a 10K w/ @emilykunze. One word- long! But Gibraltar is double in length!    
    
    
    Watermelon toes-the best 9-yr-old birthday in Barcelona is at @thepinkpeonybcn pic.twitter.com/xtrJa8pZ    
    
    
    Trying out Ferran Adria's Barcelona restaurant: Tickets. Hope it's as interesting as El Bulli! pic.twitter.com/mdPZhBBf    
    
    
    Rafa Nadal hits with his bud Tommy Robrero while Alberto Costa watches.... http://ligh.tt/q0e     
    
    
    @donalbuckley hope to share a cool pic with you tomorrow.... Stay tuned!    
    
    
    @donalbuckley tell her that he's 100 times cuter in person than on TV. And his friend Tommy ain't bad either!    
    
    
    @mikebutcher I want to send you some more info on this.. RT @worldreaders Jeff Bezos has made a personal $500,000 pledge to our mission!    
    
    
    @mikebutcher can you send me your e- mail!?    
    
    
    @mikebutcher or you can email me with it at susan @worldreader.org.... Whichever works best! Thx.    
    
    
    A Cautionary Tale: Have you experienced anything strange while swimming in the sea? Spoiler Alert- like a submarine? http://wp.me/p2RyIb-fg     
    
    
    @lululemon- Pls get your swimwear made fast!  We need it for photo ops like this one w/ Rafa Nadal! http://owswimming.com/2013/01/25/our-new-friend-rafa/ …    
    
    
    Yesterday I had the privilege of sharing our plan of swimming Gibraltar 4 @worldreaders w/ my hero @RafaelNadal http://wp.me/p2RyIb-fs  Pls RT    
    
    
    @AliFenwick I had the privilege of sharing our plan of swimming from Europe to Africa 4 charity w/ Rafa Nadal! http://wp.me/p2RyIb-fs     
    
    
    @goodhealth I had the privilege of sharing our plan of swimming from Europe to Africa for charity w/ studly Rafa Nadal http://wp.me/p2RyIb-fs     
    
    
    @donalbuckley Wish the Mrs. would have been with us!  :-) pic.twitter.com/kSB4eqs9    
    
    
    @Rasiej thought you'd appreciate this! http://owswimming.com/2013/01/25/our-new-friend-rafa/ … pic.twitter.com/GbGkIFji    
    
    
    @ryanlochte Will U help Swim4Good raise $ for literacy in Africa? Rafa did! http://owswimming.com/2013/01/25/our-new-friend-rafa/ … pic.twitter.com/OZ5eqOmD    
    
    
    Lasted 46 minutes in 11degree swim this am. I don't see any sea critters anymore- must be too cold!    
    
    
    @owenswims93 did I mention it was with a wetsuit? I'm still a cold water wuss!    
    
    
    @owenswim93 I think @mauprieto is obsessed with water temperature. pic.twitter.com/yhFwaaiV    
    
    
    Go @DamianBlaum y @esthernunez! Today's the first event of the Open Water World Cup! We're thinking of you!    
    
    
    Uh, no way! RT Swimmers take the plunge at (very) cold water championships in Tooting | Metro News |  http://metro.co.uk/2013/01/26/swimmers-take-the-plunge-at-very-cold-water-championships-in-tooting-3367714/ … via @MetroUK    
    
    
    @owenswims93 happy birthday Owen! Wishing you the best!    
    
    
    @lauriewirgler Cool work you do- go girl!    
    
    
    @RJFriedlander that would be one tasty couscous!    
    
    
    My 10 year old daughter got a Mac for Christmas and now I get e-mails like this: "También he set up un iCloud email account!!!" #Spanglish    
    
    
    Swam a 5k today with @mauprieto and @emilykunze- closing out January's mileage at 45.5k. Decent. http://Www.owswimming.com     
    
    
    Happy Groundhog day!  Anyone know if the rodent came out or not?    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan So true!  So, wait- seeing his shadow means a short winter, right?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ok, not 88K-- but 57K.  Still, I can't imagine it. #hardcore  Best of luck to you guys!  @DamianBlaum @esthernunez via  @mauprieto    
    
    
    After reading this, I might try to swim around Manhattan.  Antonio Argüelles - Triple Crowner in a League of his Own http://wp.me/p2RyIb-j1     
    
    
    I'm in complete awe!  Love how he celebrates b-days.  Antonio Argüelles - Triple Crowner in a League of his Own http://wp.me/p2RyIb-j1     
    
    
    Want 2 #swim the Triple Crown?  This guy did it twice, in the same yr. Read what's harder #Catalina, #Manhattan or EC. http://wp.me/p2RyIb-j1     
    
    
    Today I lasted 10 mins in 10C water.  That's my breaking point= below 11, I'm a wimp.  Tomorrow 10K w/ @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/Hrs6G0qO    
    
    
    Totally grossed out by my pruney hands after a 9K this am with @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/VZGmQV6f    
    
    
    Are you a SEO-lovin' google analytics geek in Barcelona who wants to change the world? Apply now: http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/jointheteam/#seostr … Pls RT!    
    
    
    @Currofile Thanks!! :-)    
    
    
    Shew! Back to normal.... pic.twitter.com/5QoBzClX    
    
    
    Time to dive in! Gotta love Barcelona weather in February! Cc @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/TjT0zI2f    
    
    
    I adore these! pic.twitter.com/RdfmiF1e    
    
    
    A Gin & Tonic lovers' dream-  a rainbow of garnishes. @ cera 23 http://instagr.am/p/VcWbIdHkSp/     
    
    
    .@Lizzywood, we need this! RT @paidContent: What would a New York Times for the youngs look like? http://flip.it/daUVe     
    
    
    @martinvars Agreed! Imagine getting school books and other reading material into all those nooks and crannies, with bad infrastructure.    
    
    
    Finally! According to @mauprieto, I've mastered a great G&T! Fifty Pounds and ME Tonic plus some lime! pic.twitter.com/mbaJsN2L    
    
    
    @Carcharius July 6th! Have you done it?    
    
    
    @Carcharius training is good- we're doing about 20k a week. I wish it were tomorrow! What r u training for in 2013?    
    
    
    @donalbuckley @mauprieto @emilykunze ok, that's means on April 6th we're going dry!    
    
    
    @montsecuixart exactly, right?    
    
    
    @donalbuckley @emilykunze @mauprieto that's one more reason why I'll never be able to cross the channel.    
    
    
    @culturesport365 of course! Right now I'm swimming from Hotel Terramar hasta la iglesia en Sitges and back. Beautiful 5K.    
    
    
    @julietrell @koozooinc hell yea! When?    
    
    
    @matthewbecker82 Hey are you a photographer in SE Asia? We're looking 4 a freelancer for an amazing non-profit @worldreaders cc @lizzywood    
    
    
    @Aviralrajsharma We're looking for a photographer to take pics of kids reading on our phone app- interested? see @worldreaders cc @lizzywood    
    
    
    @babarsyed Hey! We're looking for a freelance photographer in India for the amazing @worldreaders.  Interested?  cc @lizzywood    
    
    
    @hi_from_abhi Hi! We're looking for a freelance photographer for an amazing non-profit @worldreaders Interested? cc @lizzywood    
    
    
    @Manjunathnair Are you a photographer, by chance?    
    
    
    I just unlocked the “Ciutat Comtal” Barcelona city badge on @foursquare! No fotis! http://4sq.com/U6lf2c     
    
    
    @hi_from_abhi @lizzywood Awesome!  Send me an email & I'll tell u more about it. Susan (at) worldreader (dot) org. We'd love to work w/ u!    
    
    
    @Manjunathnair Maybe! Send me an email & I'll tell u more about it. Susan (at) worldreader (dot) org.    
    
    
    Freezing 4K this am with @emilykunze.    
    
    
    @hi_from_abhi @lizzywood Just wrote you an email to your gmail account (got from web).  Hope to hear from you soon!    
    
    
    Happy big 3-0 to @worldreaders stud @nadjaboz! Thx @zevlowe @tinatam & co from SF! pic.twitter.com/nSdF6fGd    
    
    
    @lucidillusions_ @lizzywood hey- send me your email at Susan at worldreader dot org and I'll send you some info! Thx!    
    
    
    @althecat so beautifully said!    
    
    
    @matthewbecker82 cool! Well, we need  a photographer in India this week. Do you travel much? Good to know in the future...    
    
    
    @lucidillusions_ @lizzywood cool! Will write you later on today...    
    
    
    My husband @mauprieto's idea for a nice romantic valentines day is to swim in 15 degree water. Could anything be weirder?    
    
    
    @emilykunze too bad I was such a whimp!    
    
    
    Blown away by a recent $2000 donation to our swim across Gibraltar 2 raise funds 4 @worldreaders.  Feeling generous? http://bit.ly/X8ccg3     
    
    
    Fun Valentine's date with @mauprieto except the gorgeous Martina Klein was dining right behind us #wanderingeyemuch?    
    
    
    My two little artists! pic.twitter.com/dgww7Grw    
    
    
    Love SEO & analytics and wanna work at the funnest non-profit in Barcelona, @worldreaders? http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/jointheteam/ … pic.twitter.com/i72jdroy    
    
    
    What amazing news! BLOG: Worldreader’s Biggest Launch Yet: All Children Reading http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2013/02/15/worldreaders-biggest-launch-yet-all-children-reading/ …    
    
    
    I found this to be incredibly funny: Alaskan Gray Wolf Can't Believe No One Told Him He’s Got Snow On Nose http://onion.com/XC2j7J  @TheOnion    
    
    
    @harris_j_d It's betwen 18 and 22 kilometers depending on the currents.  We've gotta be ready to swim hard for 5 to 7 hours!    
    
    
    Inspiring photo alert! Some weekend reading captured at The Osborne Memorial Library in Kenya- via @worldreaders pic.twitter.com/K71g07mS    
    
    
    Just did our 10k Mondays with @emilykunze #LongAsCrap    
    
    
    @PixieRunning @emilykunze about 15:30 per kilometer. Felt nice, actually. But my co-worker @NadjaBoz just told me I smell like a pool!    
    
    
    Interview w/ @DamianBlaum re. FINA OW Championships. Imagine swimming 2x around NYC & losing 1st by .01 sec? OUCH! http://bit.ly/XTEuvW     
    
    
    There should be rules in OW swimming against winning like this- READ this interview w/ @damienblaum & RT if u agree. http://bit.ly/XTEuvW     
    
    
    Awesome!  The Weekly Good: Worldreader Wants To Put A Digital Book In Every Child's Hand http://techcrunch.com/2013/02/17/the-weekly-good-worldreader-wants-to-put-a-digital-book-in-every-childs-hand/ … via @techcrunch    
    
    
    @Beth_Barnes_LB you're so right about reading a right, not a privilege. Well said! Cc @worldreaders    
    
    
    @owenswims93 @donalbuckley did @mauprieto tell you re. his shoulder? A tear in the tendon- looks like tendinitis- any advice?    
    
    
    @owenswims93 regarding @sylvainswims- I can't believe it either! Is butterfly easier for you?    
    
    
    @donalbuckley @mauprieto wow- crazy that you should actually exercise it. My inclination is to tell him to rest it for a month. Thanks!!!    
    
    
    @SylvainSwims @owenswims93 That is totally crazy. Has anyone ever crossed it doing butterfly?    
    
    
    Headed to Paris for a day and of course Iberia is on strike. #Murphy'sLaw    
    
    
    Tried to go to Marrakech and had to cancel cuz a kid got sick. Tried to go to Paris and it got cancelled cuz of #IberiaStrike. What next?    
    
    
    The reading revolution in Africa continues! BLOG: News from Nairobi, @worldreaders latest launch impacts 500 children http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2013/02/22/a-new-project-in-nairobi/ …    
    
    
    Why do I ♥ my job? B/c we're changing the lives of girls in Africa like my friend & poet, Kate http://youtu.be/X4I1lbf4TKo  pic.twitter.com/x33sTvPXoW    
    
    
    @daveschappell Intriguing!  What are you doing?    
    
    
    @iesealumni thanks so much!    
    
    
    E-books for Twenty Schools in Kenya.  Count ‘em: 20! http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2013/02/25/e-books-for-twenty-schools-in-kenya-count-em-20/ …    
    
    
    We're over a third of the way there! Donate and help us raise $100,000 for @worldreaders. (And then we have to swim!) http://fundraise.worldreader.org/swim4good     
    
    
    Using @JobFluent, I found an awesome SEO specialist in Barcelona! Thanks!    
    
    
    Sunday am decisions: bike, swim or run? Or SUP? Can't decide... pic.twitter.com/01zzkSUmsH    
    
    
    @DanielUrquiza I went for a run but the whole time I was thinking how I'd rather be SUP-ing! :-)    
    
    
    @RantThird hey! Ended up running- too many sports, so little time! :-) what did you do today?    
    
    
    Hangin' w/ my @worldreaders colleague celebrating this: http://www.worldreader.org/about-us/mediaroom/annual-reports/ … It's dizzying, really! pic.twitter.com/mljIlCQf6o    
    
    
    Excuses that don't work for swimmers: "It's raining!" About to brave a cold 5K w/ @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/LmksBGajxM    
    
    
    Woah- the Barcelona waves are kinda kooky today- a great result of all this weird weather! http://ligh.tt/r9U     
    
    
    @DannyGermany I know, right! :-)    
    
    
    It costs $4K to ship a car from China to Tanzania, but another $5K to get it to Uganda http://www.economist.com/news/special-report/21572377-african-lives-have-already-greatly-improved-over-past-decade-says-oliver-august …    
    
    
    Thank you! “@mijarosoft: #FF (International Womens Day!) @kanter @mallarytenore @mmeckel @samanthaluy @HeatherHartnett @junecohen    
    
    
    Revolutionary tip from my friend Barbara: if you get water on your iPhone, put it in rice. 24 hours later- it works! pic.twitter.com/lREDkPg5sU    
    
    
    Overheard from my daughter: "everyone knows she can't sing, but can my mom dance?" Hmm...    
    
    
    Just swam 1.5k in 13 degree water with our new @Swim4G caps! Aren't they cool? pic.twitter.com/0HjlJIJT88    
    
    
    @jnelmccoy true! They keep you humble!    
    
    
    @owenswims93 we wanna send you and @donalbuckley a cap! cc. @mauprieto    
    
    
    New Blog: After A Day with the Master of Open Water Swimming, I realize I've gotta gain weight and I'm a total wimp: http://wp.me/p2RyIb-oy     
    
    
    @owenswims93 It's Antonio Arguelle's family company: read more here http://wp.me/p2RyIb-oy . Send us your address so we can mail a cap!    
    
    
    I just used #Shazam to discover Yo Te Esperaré by Cali & El Dandee. http://shz.am/t65637315     
    
    
    Hee hee... Arm & Hammer Representative Starting To Wonder What He's Doing At SXSW http://onion.com/Y7MytE  via @TheOnion    
    
    
    I just voted for @tammytibbetts cuz she rocks!  Please vote today so @shesthefirst can win $50,000! http://dvfawards.com/  RT    
    
    
    Inspiring! @davidrisherWR: "I want to create a world where every child has the books they need to change their lives. http://bit.ly/ZKtemG     
    
    
    Thank U @HamletsBB for your insightful book. I'm implementing your ideas now. Here's my ESL's 10 yr old's take on it: http://bit.ly/YbBGrt     
    
    
    From @paidContent: "“Friend” has a new meaning, “Web site” should be avoided, and some tech concepts still lack..." http://paidcontent.org/2013/03/10/e-mail-is-uncool-and-other-language-lessons-for-the-digital-age/ …    
    
    
    Thanks @medgestore!  One Partner’s Impact: Inspire Kids and Keep Kindles Safe http://shar.es/eZWZa  via @worldreaders    
    
    
    Bien!!! “@MikiDomenech: got my #Swim4Good cap!!! So excited to swim with it!!! Thanks @swim4g @mauprieto @soozmoody… http://instagram.com/p/XLM9byGySU/ ”    
    
    
    Can't believe that we're almost at half of our $100,000 goal for @worldreaders.  Please consider donating! http://fundraise.worldreader.org/swim4good     
    
    
    Swimmers: what do y'all think of this? Armstrong enters US masters swim event http://bit.ly/ZDRoeo     
    
    
    Back in Spain from NYC and greeted by the most beautiful rainbow ever! pic.twitter.com/itV7CaGBYm    
    
    
    Team @swim4g showing off our new @swimsailfish wetsuits. Excellent Gibraltar training- 1 hour in 13.5 degree water! pic.twitter.com/vVNSwZ8M31    
    
    
    @MysteryCoach I really enjoyed this article. Thanks for pointing it out to me!    
    
    
    @RafaelNadal Please have the loser swim the Strait of Gibraltar with us! If he can make it... :-)    
    
    
    New BLOG on our Gibraltar training: A tale of a pool and a sea http://wp.me/p2RyIb-qu     
    
    
    @osuanya gracias! :-)    
    
    
    Just swam a 3k with my new Dolphin Uglies Training Bikini to get rid of my insane onesie tan!    
    
    
    And here you have it: the future of reading in Africa!  http://gigaom.com/2013/04/09/worldreader-counts-500000-users-of-its-e-reading-app-most-in-india-and-nigeria/ …    
    
    
    @KevinCTofel @gigaommobile you're so right!    
    
    
    @StKonrath thanks for sharing this!    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan @cmdr_hadfield From a birds eye view, that looks terrifying. What kinda nut would think to swim it? :-) cc@mauprieto    
    
    
    Kinda can't believe it--we're $800 away from 1/2 mark!  $49,200 raised for @worldreaders. Help push us over the mark! http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    @JuliadeCelis @good way to go!    
    
    
    Bonjour tout le monde! pic.twitter.com/OAvXr4dBtx    
    
    
    My daughter has been studying Versailles in school. Nothing like taking an hour flight and seeing the real thing! pic.twitter.com/d2l0nBYUZd    
    
    
    Beautiful day in Par-ee! pic.twitter.com/pew1DWesek    
    
    
    I had a strong and strange impulse to jump in and swim in the Seine. pic.twitter.com/eBTBqJLLXB    
    
    
    @Michael5732 thank you! I'm sure we will... :-)    
    
    
    Just swam 10,050 meters with @emilykunze. Shew! Cc @mauprieto pic.twitter.com/F998wSlJbt    
    
    
    Read @mashable's coverage on M-Reading in Dev. World. "An inspiring finding for early childhood education"http://mashable.com/2013/04/17/worldreader-mobile/ … via @zoefox    
    
    
    Look who's in Mundo Deportivo today! @swimsailfish @mauprieto @emilykunze @Swim4G pic.twitter.com/JEdiTqhXxZ    
    
    
    @fhernanr gracias! :-)    
    
    
    @ChelseaClinton hey! Glad you shared the news on what we're doing with your  followers. I'd love to share more info on @worldreaders w/ you.    
    
    
    @tammytibbetts Thank you! Hey--- congrats on win!    
    
    
    Great quote: "Children create miracles when they read. That’s why children need books." Astrid Lindgren, author of Pipi Longstocking    
    
    
    Today we're sporting our new @Swim4G tees given by our sponsor @sailfishwetsuit.  Do you like them? cc@emilykunze pic.twitter.com/Wc8LABD0wy    
    
    
    Watching Ferrer from my living room. He's tied. pic.twitter.com/ECQutOC8zS    
    
    
    @kenkenhimself what book are you?    
    
    
    Fun to watch @RafaelNadal crush it. He's winning 6-4, 2-1. What a comeback!    
    
    
    @kenkenhimself I was Alice in Wonderland! Kinda true...    
    
    
    Thanks @Easypromos 4 donating @worldreaders Book DNA quiz to win a #Kindle.  It was both fun to make & fun to take! https://www.facebook.com/worldreader/app_154581087931912 …    
    
    
    Hey @aquasphereswim, See @emilykunze's musings on the best googles for OW swimming. @swim4g http://owswimming.com/2013/04/24/goggle-alert-aqua-sphere-kaiman-goggles/ …    
    
    
    Barcelona weather. No thanks! pic.twitter.com/1lINqNfTFW    
    
    
    @RJFriedlander @mauprieto it's always a pleasure! I'm just glad my guacamole keeps pleasing....    
    
    
    My interview in today's Sport actually puts my name on the same page as @RafaelNadal - huge honor! http://bit.ly/ZLUN0X     
    
    
    Hanging with my @swim4g better half @emilykunze. Why are men so scared of her? Oh yea- she swims faster than all them pic.twitter.com/40th9mqN6A    
    
    
    Woot! We just broke $53,000 in our fundraising effort 4 @worldreader.  Feeling generous?  Pls help us get to $100,000 http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    Swam a 5.2K with @mauprieto in glorious Sitges this am. Does swimming makes you hungry?  I could've eaten my hand afterwards.    
    
    
    Cheering on Alex Song- he's playing great!  #FCB http://owswimming.com/2013/04/27/our-friend-alex/ …    
    
    
    @buddingreader Thanks for your continued and amazing support!  You guys get why #booksforall is so important :-)    
    
    
    In May I've gotta swim 60K, Stressed b/c I'm going to Tanzania, Kenya, SF, and NYC this month,  Will log in 20K by Monday though.    
    
    
    Tomorrow we're swimming a 5 K with giant tunas! So friggin' scared!    
    
    
    Never felt so claustrophobic in my life. People were swimming on top of me! #tunarace    
    
    
    In our e-reader programs in Ghana, kids come to school on weekend to read. Their fav book? "The Stinky Giant"- PHOTO pic.twitter.com/MqPa6KMBeX    
    
    
    Just lost my purse in Heathrow 30 mins before my flight- someone found the Gate and rushed it to me. #GoodSamaritin    
    
    
    These little munchkins stole our hearts! What an awesome day at The Kibera Girls' Soccer Academy w/ @nadjaboz pic.twitter.com/0siYPbHJZ9    
    
    
    The world has shifted in Tanzania: The Prime Minister promises to back e-readers for its students via @worldreaders http://on.fb.me/10sXBL0     
    
    
    @Prof_Evans hmmm- not sure but I think technology, social connections, sports, health, toys, travel,  entertainment, and education.    
    
    
    New BLOG on my recent trip: The Girl Who Will Teach Tanzania to Read http://shar.es/ZWiPP  via @worldreaders    
    
    
    @forbeesta You'd love this! E-readers in Tanzanian schools capture interest of Prime Minister #ICT: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/the-girl-who-will-teach-tanzania-to-read/ …    
    
    
    @gettleman What do you think about laptops in Kenyan schools?  Look at what's happening next door: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/the-girl-who-will-teach-tanzania-to-read/ …    
    
    
    @loughrichard What do you think of the Kenyan laptop idea?  Look at what's happening just next door: http://www.worldreader.org/blog/the-girl-who-will-teach-tanzania-to-read/ …    
    
    
    @ChelseaClinton Our latest e-reader launch in a Tanzanian school attracts the attention of the PM. Pls see http://www.worldreader.org/blog/the-girl-who-will-teach-tanzania-to-read/ …    
    
    
    @brainpicker Could Tanzania be the country w/ the highest penetration of e-readers in public schools in the world? http://www.worldreader.org/blog/the-girl-who-will-teach-tanzania-to-read/ …    
    
    
    Wondering how to behave in the pool? @swim4g's @emilykunze explains how NOT to: http://owswimming.com/2013/05/14/swimming-etiquette/ …    
    
    
    @ChelseaClinton I thought you'd appreciate it- hey I'll be in NYC last week of May, can I tell you more about @worldreaders? Thanks.    
    
    
    We're stuck in the 50's!  Please help us reach $60K this weekend- anything you can give would be much appreciated! http://fundraise.worldreader.org/swim4good     
    
    
    Go @RafaelNadal! No one is as tough as you!    
    
    
    @Prof_Evans thank you! :-)    
    
    
    Huge thanks to all that donated this weekend- we passed the $60,000 for @worldreaders milestone thanks to you! #Happy http://fundraise.worldreader.org/swim4good     
    
    
    The month before swimming across Gibraltar I'm traveling for 3 weeks. I need to log in 70K swimming. This is tough.    
    
    
    A must-read: “@davidrisherWR: Going Public: On working with Governments to Achieve Scale.  http://shar.es/ZewZ8  via @worldreaders”    
    
    
    Just ran into my cutie hubby at the airport cc @mauprieto pic.twitter.com/13hAU0aCw1    
    
    
    @TRobredo You are amazing!  Felicidades!    
    
    
    Go @TRobredo- you can do it! We believe in you! @rolandgarros http://www.wimbledon.com/en_GB/news/articles/2013-06-02/201306021370208910989.html … #rg13”    
    
    
    Love this! “@tennishead: Picture of @rolandgarros so far? The Renaissance Man, aka @TRobredo, beating Gael Monfils pic.twitter.com/Sv22qbuDxn”    
    
    
    My team mate @emilykunze continued her Gibraltar training (and added a bit of debauchery) in Vegas. http://owswimming.com/2013/06/04/a-little-training-detour/ …    
    
    
    @conchibadillo @Swim4G @worldreaders AWESOME!    
    
    
    @LetHerBeGreater  thanks! :-)    
    
    
    #mixbooth just mixed @lizzywood and @DanieZacarias- go team publishing! pic.twitter.com/yTrLQUeVcG    
    
    
    @RafaelNadal Wow- thanks so much for this shout-out!  We're so inspired by your comeback and will be thinking of you! @Swim4G @worldreaders    
    
    
    I'll frame this & put it in my room, forever! Unbelievable to have stud @RafaelNadal's support @Swim4G @worldreaders pic.twitter.com/qSz912Yf2V    
    
    
    @ursalee @binu @worldreaders thank you guys so much!!! We'll need the support!    
    
    
    @Michael5732 we are well trained, now just need mother nature to be kind to us!    
    
    
    @SportDrinkV thanks for your follow and note- only, it's 22kms, not 2 km! And yes, always open to new things...    
    
    
    A new olympic sport? pic.twitter.com/vQkKObXZZh    
    
    
    Swam a 7K with @emilykunze and @mauprieto over the weekend in Sitges- the water is finally warm! pic.twitter.com/EILsfhFrRb    
    
    
    Meet Lisa, a student in Tanzania- she begged her school to skip a grade so she could study with a Kindle. #inspiring http://www.worldreader.org/blog/how-lisas-life-changed-when-books-came-to-her-school/ …    
    
    
    @mauprieto @Swim4G @emilykunze Should we retaliate by showing your geeky photos?  I've got reserves....    
    
    
    Can't believe it! @Swim4G just passed the $80K mark in our fundraising for @worldreaders! Woo hoo! http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 …    
    
    
    Buy a Kindle case and change the world-- at the same time! http://acaseforgood.com/products/coated-canvas-cover-for-kindle-and-kindle-paperwhite-black-green-with-dots …    
    
    
    Love this guest blog post by @MDrendel. Read his thoughts on crewing for @Swim4G during Gibraltar: http://owswimming.com/2013/06/22/guest-post-by-mark-our-crew/ … #inspiring    
    
    
    With less than a week to go, the weather is not behaving! Read our latest update: http://owswimming.com/2013/07/02/the-final-stretch-swim4good/ … #swim4good    
    
    
    I seriously love people.  Can't believe 184 people have raised $95,401 for @worldreaders. http://fundraise.worldreader.org/fundraise?fcid=186029 … #swim4good    
    
    
    We're constantly checking @WindGuru to see when we'll swim. Just asked 8 ball and not happy. #swim4good pic.twitter.com/WcdTCOkcoU    
    
    
    Athletes: do you get more superstitious close to races/games?  I'm wearing magic bracelets, checking 8 balls for answers...What do you do?    
    
    
    Update: weather in Tarifa is still bad but #Swim4Good will fly there tomorrow 4 the week. Looks like we might get lucky Wednesday or Thurs    
    
    
    Oh no! I've lost my favorite goggles- Aquasphere's. I've trained with them for a year. Feeling like I lost my good luck charm pre-Gibraltar!    
    
    
    On the way 2 #Gibraltar and look who we ran into @ the airport- @trobrero! It's a good luck sign. #swim4good pic.twitter.com/fkK77x6XnY    
    
    
    Check out the sand blowin' in the dunes in Tarifa! #swim4good http://ligh.tt/g2ok     
    
    
    @carringtonm nope, thank god I have those... I'll use them for the big G. Thx!    
    
    
    It is unbelievably windy- and the African coast looks unbelievably far away.  http://ligh.tt/r26Z     
    
    
    Guest Post by Team BlueDolphin: "You do not cross the Strait of Gibraltar. The Strait allows … http://wp.me/p2RyIb-w8  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    New blog: "Wait, we're supposed to swim across that!?" http://wp.me/p2RyIb-wz  cc@Trobredo    
    
    
    I believe I can fly! #swim #Gibraltar #swim4good pic.twitter.com/H34s7fnYeO    
    
    
    @OscarPRGirl I'd swim from Europe to Africa for #charity. Oh wait- I already am! http://www.swim4good.com     
    
    
    Giggling reading this update by @emilykunze http://owswimming.com/2013/07/08/briefing-curious-whales-currents-sprints-to-barcelona/ … #Swim4Good    
    
    
    Team @swim4g trains in Europe's oldest city- Cadiz. Winds are slowly subsiding! #swim4good. pic.twitter.com/1I3q4RMdvb    
    
    
    @channelswimjen Hey Jen! We're in Tarifa- Swimming Gibraltar tomorrow. Seeing y'alls video again for inspiration! #Swim4Good    
    
    
    @ultraswimmer Hey- we're in Tarifa about to face Gibraltar tomorrow. Love your video. Wish us luck! #Swim4Good    
    
    
    @CrosoigeMara @owenswims93 @eoin_oriordan @ccashell @lisaecummins @caitlin_desmond @l4lynne Thanks- you guys too!! :-)    
    
    
    Really? The wind finally died down and now- fog? Come on, let us swim to #Africa! http://www.swim4good.com  #Swim4Good pic.twitter.com/lFgN5yokZ3    
    
    
    @channelswimjen follow @Swim4G on Facebook! http://Facebook.com/swim4good ... We'll be updating! Xo    
    
    
    Fog is starting to lift- can see the tippy top of Africa. Hanging on 4 the final word if we swim or not #Swim4Good pic.twitter.com/mzPEN37iJx    
    
    
    Word from the Strait- we're headed to the port. Evidently there's a break in the weather. Will keep you posted! #Swim4Good    
    
    
    Marveling how those giant tankers are as big as my pinky nail from the Spanish coast. pic.twitter.com/ZSzdN579as    
    
    
    @soozmoody @crosoigemara @owenswims93 @eoin_oriordan @ccashell @lisaecummins @caitlin_desmond @l4lynne Goooooo Team!!!!    
    
    
    So happy about this- We Did It! Underwater accounts by Susan, Emily and Mauricio  http://wp.me/p2RyIb-x9  #Swim4Good    
    
    
    @drewwuwu @carringtonm reading these tweets now and giggling!    
    
    
    @Michael5732 thanks so much for all your support!    
    
    
    Totally doing this for both me and my daughters: 11 Days, 11 Books, 11 Ways to Discover Africa http://shar.es/AMI54  via @worldreaders    
    
    
    It's cold outside- bout to jump into the SF Bay with @emilykunze!    
    
    
    Go @swim4good! #alcatraz pic.twitter.com/78uDRn3G0d    
    
    
    Super fun & wavy swim from Alcatraz this am w/ @emilykunze- done in 29 mins! pic.twitter.com/dQIghp9mLt    
    
    
    Did a dumb SF Ferry move. Took the ferry to Vallejo instead of Tiburon! Made friends with the ferry captain. pic.twitter.com/XUEyUu1KKu    
    
    
    @strombo Wow, just moved here from Spain and saw you on TV. You're incredible!    
    
    
    Early morning swim in the SF Bay--Couldn't be a more fitting way to meet @kimberleyswims in person finally!    
    
    
    The Oracle boat is literally flying above the water. pic.twitter.com/yo7T7FTEaL    
    
    
    What does one Kenyan 4th grader say about her Kindle? http://j.mp/14xLxdz     
    
    
    SF's Open Water Swimming Scene: Meet Night Train and learn more about their crazy swims. http://wp.me/p2RyIb-Aw     
    
    
    Seen in Mill Valley: Prieto sister shops! http://instagram.com/p/dFb82Enkcz/     
    
    
    First time I laid eyes on my now hubby of 14 years. Princeton circa 1990. http://instagram.com/p/dFnyGvHkQZ/     
    
    
    Napa is pretty darn beautiful! Mo and I are enjoying some wine tasting & the girls are wondering why… http://instagram.com/p/dKoQp-HkYO/     
    
    
    Non-stop swimming is "having issues"? Farewell to Gus, Whose Issues Made Him a Star http://nyti.ms/190w0aB     
    
    
    @LaurenMcHale Loved that you used Journey in today's class!    
    
    
    WOW- Felicidades @TRobredo! Rodredo stuns Federer for first victory over the Swiss #usopen http://2013.usopen.org/en_US/news/articles/2013-09-02/201309031378167920050.html … via @usopen    
    
    
    Indeed the #possibilities are huge. Stomping Out Illiteracy One Reader at a Time http://shar.es/icHRO  via @worldreaders Stay tuned 4 more.    
    
    
    Quick! Buy stock in @apple. pic.twitter.com/UjqqtuDDsy    
    
    
    @kimberleyswims I hear we're swimming Bridge to Bridge Sunday! :-)    
    
    
    Swimming GG Bridge to Bay Bridge tomorrow with @mauprieto & @kimberleyswims! Yay! http://owswimming.com/2013/09/21/bay-area-swimming-from-bridge-to-bridge/ …    
    
    
    @Drewwuwu this is 4 u. RT @TheOnion: In Focus: Area Father Must Have Read Some Drug-Slang Brochure Or Something http://flip.it/un9XC     
    
    
    This box contains over 6,000 culturally relevant books- en route to Malawi! Go @worldreaders pic.twitter.com/bAFIBImijU    
    
    
    Wanna see what 400 @kindles looks like? Here's to changing the world, hundreds of e-books at a time! pic.twitter.com/gYAnx6F1Gw    
    
    
    So cool seeing @jcsnappy loading 400+ Kindles! Tomorrow they're being shipped to Kenya! Thx @dhl! pic.twitter.com/o3Cld28AWR    
    
    
    @NickKristof "More people now have cellphones than toilets." Good thing @worldreaders has great books on its app! http://bit.ly/17kIkmV     
    
    
    A must read: A Way of Life Is Ending. Thank Goodness. via @NickKristof http://nyti.ms/17cnia7     
    
    
    Thinking back to camp- how to sail.  Glad I paid attention! pic.twitter.com/SlKzL3WBGT    
    
    
    @caquilimongui aw, thanks!!!!    
    
    
    @aserto1 @worldreaders thanks!!! :-)    
    
    
    @colinpaterson @kindles thanks ! :-)    
    
    
    I'm never swimming in the bay again! @ultraswimmer -- this photo has freaked me out! pic.twitter.com/s4S8e6QQCq    
    
    
    This makes our swim feel even more urgent: Desperation Fuels Trips of Migrants to Spain http://nyti.ms/18YmRka     
    
    
    The Sis and niece comes to town= always a good thing! pic.twitter.com/5MwkFkDkuR    
    
    
    I'm Mateo's first @Uber client! Good luck, man!    
    
    
    Here's to every girl getting an education- all over the globe #IDG http://www.worldreader.org/blog/doris-surviving-in-the-slums-and-chasing-a-dream/ …    
    
    
    @wayan_vota are you in Bali now?    
    
    
    Happy to be with my man @mauprieto again! pic.twitter.com/ilJBqqEVDe    
    
    
    Transamerica! pic.twitter.com/sc5dXEiV3i    
    
    
    So awesome to see my  friend @zevlowe sporting a @swim4g cap! Lookin' hot, Z! Where you gonna wear that? pic.twitter.com/XCK4FjH3g2    
    
    
    What is Google building in San Francisco Bay? http://flip.it/IpTPt     
    
    
    @goldmedalmel Hey NC bud- thanks 4 the shout out in @swimswamnews: http://swimswam.com/swim4good-nominated-open-water-swimming-performance-year-award/ … Here's to bringing swimmers and charity together!    
    
    
    @mozziesf I'd love to! Do you have a free moment on Thursday? Xo    
    
    
    Swim the Strait of Gibraltar in July, African kids get thousands of e-books in October.  Technology=amazing. http://owswimming.com/2013/11/20/it-was-magical/ … @Swim4G    
    
    
    @mozziesf Hey!  Sorry, had a sick child today... was it fun?    
    
    
    Irish coffees after swimming in 53 degree water! Brrrrr! @ Buena Vista Cafe http://instagram.com/p/hB9ndEnkeb/     
    
    
    @DrKimMD Great reconnecting the other night!  Way to rock it, girl! xoxo    
    
    
    B-day fun in SF! Thanks for all the b-day wishes! Xo @ St. Vincent Tavern & Wine Merchant http://instagram.com/p/hK4LB2HkaL/     
    
    
    Mean old grandpa... @ NYC http://instagram.com/p/hPcMKgnkXT/     
    
    
    Tune into @pbsnewshour tonight to catch @worldreaders @davidrisherWR talk about eradicating illiteracy! Don't miss it!    
    
    
    Apparently @davidrisherWR crushed it- twitter feed is going wild with positive love. Will share link...    
    
    
    Really sad about @RealPaulWalker. Thinking about his friends and family-thinking of you all and sending support. It's such a loss.    
    
    
    Hey West Coasters... tune into @npratc now to hear more about @worldreaders work eradicating illiteracy in the developing world. #Inspiring    
    
    
    Love my new painting by my amazing friend laurasmithblairart. It's called Open Water, and it… http://instagram.com/p/hr2XOwHkWf/     
    
    
    First USA x-mas tree! pic.twitter.com/KXcofS89yG    
    
    
    Why Nokia Is Building an Android Phone and Why Microsoft Might Not Kill It http://flip.it/dwxv9     
    
    
    Get Busy: Pharrell's Productivity Secrets By Mary Kaye Schilling http://www.fastcompany.com/3021377/pharrell-get-busy … via @FastCompany    
    
    
    College roommates are unique- no matter where you are in your life, you just pick up where you last… http://instagram.com/p/h7pk5eHkeB/     
    
    
    Hey @jensuzols.  Did u c this? Stitch Fix: Reinventing Retail Through Personalization by @bgurley http://abovethecrowd.com/2013/10/17/stitch-fix-reinventing-retail-through-personalization/ …    
    
    
    Is it just me or do the Bills look like they're holding hands? Via @wired pic.twitter.com/KdrxGQeTuV    
    
    
    Merry Christmas from paradise! @ Punta Ixtapa http://instagram.com/p/iWWghenkaZ/     
    
    
    You Say Goodbye and We Say Hello http://flip.it/OkMxP     
    
    
    Big Sur sure is purdy! http://instagram.com/p/iute6MHkSV/     
    
    
    @McConnellCormac gosh- I hope they're just normal contrails! :-)    
    
    
    @colinpaterson veeery nice!    
    
    
    @1busyswimchick sure thing! Enjoyed the read! Happy new year!    
    
    
    @brainpicker thanks 4 covering @worldreaders! Remember about 3 yrs ago, you shared a WR video. Do u like the latest? http://youtu.be/lRCBUCRWMHE     
    
    
    Savoring the last days of family vacay and exploring ridiculously gorgeous Carmel. @ Point Lobos State… http://instagram.com/p/iw0e-1nkR3/     
    
    
    @colinpaterson two excellent places!    
    
    
    @howden_africa @davidrisherwr Hi Daniel, he is on a boat in Turkey- what is your timing? I can help you.    
    
    
    @opuech @davidrisherwr Hi olivier! He is on a boat in Turkey- what is your timing? I'll help you figure it out.    
    
    
    I’ve just completed a new workout on the Speedo Pace Club. Try to beat my time at http://bit.ly/Ly2woE     
    
    
    Great summary of Hemingway- congrats @benmezrich RT @nprbooks: Bull Fights, Bankruptcy And A Damn Dangerous Book http://n.pr/Rl8EUt     
    
    
    Enjoying gin and tonics with @cultureslurp  @ El Canalla http://instagr.am/p/MtxMgGnkX3/     
    
    
    No. 8 made me chuckle. RT @NewYorker: An #heir cartoon of the night: http://nyr.kr/P1mSwc     
    
    
    Not sure how excited I am about this. RT @mashable: Here's What Facebook's 'Want' Button Will Probably Look Like http://on.mash.to/NEfbVA     
    
    
    Crystal clear 3K swim- only saw about 20 jellies  @ Sitges Ocean Swimming http://instagr.am/p/M2xq7iHkTw/     
    
    
    I just ousted @mauprieto as the mayor of Garraf Trail Lookout #1 on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/npNjPd     
    
    
    Love this. RT @Forbes: AdVoice: Being a Great Leader Means You Go First http://bit.ly/PGzCHT     
    
    
    Swimming in The Atlantic Ocean at @foursquare: http://4sq.com/LsGqTd     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Far Far Away" badge on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/QiLGiT     
    
    
    Video RT @worldreaders: Hear what happened to Okanta Kate after reading The Shark by Ghanaian author Peggy Oppong: http://youtu.be/X4I1lbf4TKo     
    
    
    Tomorrow am I'll swim around the birthplace of NYC. http://bit.ly/N2zo8I     
    
    
    @DrWider You are my inspiration!  I don't know how you do it!    
    
    
    @davemorgannyc  missed you today!    
    
    
    Awesome @nycswim today around the birthplace of NYC with my BFF.  Every breath we saw Lady Liberty waving "Hi" to us! pic.twitter.com/ffszI7Zl    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Me too- Can't wait to meet you!  How's your week looking?    
    
    
    The world needs more people like @KatieLinendoll.  Awesome seeing you and can't wait to collaborate more.    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Ski Bum" badge on @foursquare for checking in at ski spots! Slope city! http://4sq.com/McHOyo     
    
    
    Just completed a 12.93 km bike - Aspen is so beautiful! http://rnkpr.com/a1ttkpy  #RunKeeper    
    
    
    So very true! Do you agree? pic.twitter.com/ArdcsupV    
    
    
    I just became the mayor of Menorca Ocean Swim on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/T6G7nB     
    
    
    I had loads of fun in this interview with @wendyhung @JetsetTimes http://ow.ly/dqA00   Cool publication!    
    
    
    @davemorgannyc I signed up to do Little Red Light House with @nycswim.  The name sounds quaint but it's a 10K! http://bit.ly/RkyjtC     
    
    
    @PdP_bcn @foursquare How is that possible?    
    
    
    @DidacLee The @FT loves what @LeoMessi1987 is doing with Kindles in Africa.  Let's get the word out! @FCB http://on.ft.com/Q0cO5l     
    
    
    @Kuhn Looking forward to talking with you later on today about @worldreaders.  Thanks again @zsniderman for hooking us up! #MillionBooks    
    
    
    If you're into Mobile Tech in Africa, this is a must read: http://www.bbc.com/future/story/20120823-what-africa-can-learn-from-phones …    
    
    
    Have a 20 old computer that needs fixing? Come to Spain! pic.twitter.com/U8BTWrLv    
    
    
    @jryoung Hi Jeff- I just sent you an email about Kindles in Africa- a game changer for literacy. Run by fellow P-ton folks. Hope to connect.    
    
    
    @mauprieto Why don't you tweet the harddrive question to @apple?    
    
    
    @nickwingfield I ♥ your article in @NYT today! Publishers step up for kids in Africa. Hooray @simonschuster @randomhousekids @worldreaders!    
    
    
    Major int'l publishers are joining @worldreaders cause to get great books in kids hands in Africa- Read more in @NYT: http://nyti.ms/TrlVgb     
    
    
    @RipleyWorld @EgmontUK Hooray for your work with @worldreaders!  Nice piece in today's @NYT //nyti.ms/TrlVgb #MillionBooks    
    
    
    @cultureslurp and you?    
    
    
    @NickKristof you'll love this! “@nytimesbits: Publishers Back African Literacy Effort With E-Books http://nyti.ms/SmGHQu ”    
    
    
    @TechCrunch pls see @nickwingfield: Bits: Publishers Back African Literacy Effort With E-Books   http://nyti.ms/Qcll73 ”    
    
    
    @cultureslurp must be cold down there...    
    
    
    @coopeydoop On a big day for #Kindle, pls see a great piece in the Times about publishers' support of @worldreaders http://nyti.ms/Qcll73 ”    
    
    
    Can't wait! RT @gigaom: Our @laurahazardowen is at Amazon's press conference in LA and will be live blogging. http://ow.ly/dw4hZ     
    
    
    Wow! “@paidContent #Amazon New Kindle Fire will be $159. Kindle Fire HD line includes 2 tablets, including a 10" http://ow.ly/dwiYu ”    
    
    
    @cultureslurp I'm thinking #ginandtonics    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Wino" badge on @foursquare for checking in at wine spots! Cheers! http://4sq.com/Q2unlb     
    
    
    @paidContent @laurahazardowen whispercast with voice will be so cool for @worldreaders kids. Immersion reading-yes!  Nice blogging Laura!    
    
    
    Worldreader: Taking the E-Book Revolution to Africa - Businessweek via @BW http://buswk.co/TophSJ     
    
    
    This week = a serious roll with both publishers and the press.  FT, NYT and now Business Week!  Read more and share: http://buswk.co/TophSJ     
    
    
    @MattSchofield @LibTechReplies @Liberationtech @web_forensics @shrutikhurana Love the Love!  All great folks- cheers!    
    
    
    Check out Great Breakthrough For Worldreader – Major Publishers Donate Hundreds of New ebooks http://bit.ly/NRhk7I     
    
    
    Check out Great Breakthrough For Worldreader – Major Publishers Donate Hundreds of New ebooks @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/09/08/great-breakthrough-for-worldreader-major-publishers-donate-hundreds-of-new-ebooks/ …    
    
    
    Read @davidrisherWR in @huffpost- the magic words that can change a kids life in Africa and who is already doing it. http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    New Blog: Meet Gabriel. He Wants to Change His World. Let’s Help Him. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/08/meet-gabriel-he-wants-to-change-his-world-lets-help-him/ …    
    
    
    “I have chance of becoming a better person when I learn from the lives of people in stories" says 14 yr old Gabriel. http://bit.ly/U1WJdA     
    
    
    On #intllitday, the magic words are:"Let's send digital books to the developing world." Awesome post @davidrisherWR! http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    @MattSchofield Did you see @davidrisherWR's post in @huffpostimpact today? THX for being our partner! #intllitday http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    @mshoebri See @davidrisherWR's post in @huffpostimpact- THX for being our partner in getting books into kids hands! http://huff.to/NSzk1w     
    
    
    BLOG: Sending Kids in Africa Back to School With Great New Books http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/11/sending-kids-in-africa-back-to-school-with-great-new-books/ …    
    
    
    Brilliant! See @elpais about @fcbarcelona = the missing link between children and literacy #Africa via @GonzaloFanjul http://bit.ly/UaHtLE     
    
    
    @Xavi_Hernan Congrats on inspiring kids to read more in Africa!  Cuando el fútbol sirve para algo... más via @elpais http://bit.ly/UaHtLE     
    
    
    Cool article in Publishing Perspectives: Additional Publishers, Caine Prize Partners with Worldreader. http://publishingperspectives.com/2012/09/additional-publishers-partner-with-worldreader/#.UFMnHycTjw4.twitter …    
    
    
    Made me smile! @MattSchofield: FF #ICT4D @silvia_parra @arbeloa @WBPubs @soozmoody @SevincRende @meowtree @korusconsult @occupy_www”    
    
    
    Great idea! "@MattSchofield:your Barca promotion made ME smile! Get @Shakira to do a cover of Waka Waka with Kindles http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dzsuE5ugxf4 …”    
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Great Outdoors" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different outdoor spots! http://4sq.com/Ntvevb     
    
    
    I just reached Level 2 of the "Swimmies" badge on @foursquare. I’ve checked in at 5 different water spots! http://4sq.com/Ntvevd     
    
    
    Cadaques is windy and water is choppy, but Marnaton officials select the plan A route. Prettier but longer. I hope I don't freeze to death!    
    
    
    Marnaton Cadaques was cold and wavy, but nice. 650 people swimming a 6.5k! Lots happier to be @ the after- party! pic.twitter.com/m09S87Mt    
    
    
    I just ousted @javier_aguilar as the mayor of Reial Club de Tennis Barcelona on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dyoUXg     
    
    
    NEW BLOG: Read more our about how we charge #Kindles in #Africa: Powering Reading, Empowering Lives http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/17/powering-reading-empowering-lives/ …    
    
    
    If you like what we're doing: “Help unlock the power of books. Vote for @Worldreaders to speak at SXSWedu! http://shar.es/uZdvp ” RT    
    
    
    7 billion people, 6 billion cell phones in the world. RT @allthingsd: The Mobile Browser Dominates in Emerging Markets http://flpbd.it/9XBXC     
    
    
    So nervous for today's 10K swim in the Hudson with @NYCswim.  I've never swam a 10K race before- I guess it's good to try something new!    
    
    
    Holy crap- We start at 79th street and end past 190th. That's long! @NYCswim    
    
    
    Who knew that there is an adorable red light house underneath the George Washington bridge?  @NYCswim pic.twitter.com/hgvtWc9A    
    
    
    @biNu a hit: there's 484,000 mobile phone readers a month...and growing! http://businesstech.co.za/news/internet/22769/binu-a-hit/ … via @BusinessTechSA    
    
    
    New BLOG: Engendering the Reading Culture. 100's of titles read!  Awesome. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/09/26/engendering-the-reading-culture/ …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the Back to School badge on @foursquare for checking in back on campus! Time to party! Er, study. http://4sq.com/SErCc7     
    
    
    I'm so gonna do this!  Become a Worldreader Fundraiser – Help Get Ebooks to Kids In Africa http://beforeitsnews.com/books/2012/09/become-a-worldreader-fund-raiser-help-get-ebooks-to-kids-in-africa-2446200.html … via @BeforeItsNews    
    
    
    Off to the pool to swim the 4.5k I need to login a total of 50k in September.    
    
    
    Swimming Gibraltar BLOG: Why did @carringtonm decide to swim from Europe to Africa?  It's wily @mauprieto's fault! http://bit.ly/U0JvDA     
    
    
    My goal was to swim 43 K this month and I did 50 K! 66% in Open Water.  Training to raise $ for @worldreaders. http://bit.ly/U0JvDA     
    
    
    I just ousted Colin M. as the mayor of http://Worldreader.org  on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/IM21Wr     
    
    
    I'm in physical pain after seeing Carles Puyol's arm break.  #AnimosPuyol!  You're the best and inspire many. #fcb    
    
    
    BLOG: Read 17 yr old Kate in her own words. Before I met Worldreader, I was writing, but it wasn’t easy for me. #Africa http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    @Oprah Read 17yr old Ghanaian student Kate on why she's writing. BLOG: The Heart of A Poet http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    @MichelleObama Please read 17yr old Ghanaian student, Kate, tell in her own words why she needs to write. #Kindle http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    BLOG Kate: "I wrote a poem called “Agony of a Woman,” which talks about the plight and problems women face in Africa" http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/03/the-heart-of-a-poet/ …    
    
    
    As Lynn Sherr said: "skin is our largest organ, so swimming is the most sensual sport." I'll think about that tomorrow during the Sitges 10k    
    
    
    It was long but I'm happy it's over! @emilykunze and I both got 1st in our catagories in #marnaton 10k Sitges. pic.twitter.com/N165N4fs    
    
    
    New Blog: Girl Power: Worldreader and FC Barcelona Women’s Team http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/08/girl-power-worldreader-and-fc-barcelonas-womens-team/ …    
    
    
    BLOG: Read how @worldreaders sent African kids inspiring images of FC Barcelona women's soccer team on their Kindles.  http://bit.ly/R88NwG     
    
    
    Asked my daughters what Girls + Education equaled. Love their answer! #basicmath @worldreaders @10x10act pic.twitter.com/3p1TYKZi    
    
    
    @MattSchofield love all the girl power going on! You rock!    
    
    
    @didaclee See how @FCBarcelona Women's Team inspires students in Africa to read more. http://youtu.be/QCLV7n6iluk  #dayofthegirl @worldreaders    
    
    
    Day of the Girl: Honor Her. Motivate Her. Educate Her. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/10/11/day-of-the-girl-honor-her-motivate-her-educate-her/ … PLEASE RT    
    
    
    @newsdel Hi! I would like to pitch @worldreaders awesome work with Kindles in Africa.  Right up Brian's alley.  Any insight on how?    
    
    
    @BraddJaffy I would like to pitch @worldreaders awesome work with Kindles in African schools.  Any advice? http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2012-09-06/worldreader-taking-the-e-book-revolution-to-africa …    
    
    
    @NickKristof Couldn't agree more. And the key to getting educated girls is getting the reading materials they need. http://www.huffingtonpost.com/david-risher/on-international-day-of-t_b_1955180.html …    
    
    
    @MattSchofield Great! Thx! Just looked at my cc bill and calculated that they read on average 8 books a week! @Kindle    
    
    
    @Oprah We've seen that Kindles even the playing field between boys and girls in schools in Africa. Please see VIDEO http://www.huffingtonpost.com/david-risher/on-international-day-of-t_b_1955180.html …    
    
    
    @JuliadeCelis @worldreaders We're so happy to have you!    
    
    
    @RowdyGaines Met U when I was 12 at Ntls- inspiring! Retired after college, now 40 yr mom training to cross Gibraltar. http://bit.ly/Q2WOvT     
    
    
    Its a rainy day and I'm buried in Gone Girl: A Novel and can't put it down. #pageturner #kindle    
    
    
    Absolutely love this look by @nadjaboz pic.twitter.com/CJH0GwlI    
    
    
    BLOG POST: Mind Games: what seeing a 2 meter fish does to my head http://wp.me/p2MIAW-2Y     
    
    
    I finished Gone Girl: A Novel and highly recommend it to people who have 10 hours to lose themselves in an amazing read.    
    
    
    I just ousted @mauprieto as the mayor of Sausalito on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/d1aQF0     
    
    
    Check out Worldreader and Linda: Kindles Bring Solace To Young Girl In Africa @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/10/17/worldreaders-kindles-bring-solace-to-young-girl-in-africa/ …    
    
    
    Amazon Introduces Whispercast to Manage Large Fleets of Kindles.  And look who pioneered it! Go @Worldreaders!  http://dthin.gs/QrCbvS     
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Shutterbug" badge on @foursquare for adding photos to my check-ins. Say cheese! http://4sq.com/T1OUDs     
    
    
    I just ousted @jcmelero as the mayor of Chiringuito Pizzeria Del Puerto on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dfA9b2     
    
    
    The Three Women on the Team http://wp.me/p2MIAW-3V  via @wordpressdotcom    
    
    
    BLOG @carringtonmadden might hate me for this post.  The Three Women on the Team: we'd be 3 out of 25!  http://wp.me/p2MIAW-3V  W/ @emilykunze    
    
    
    I just bought: "Hardcore Swim Women's Scalliwag Cali Drag One Piece" via @swimoutlet http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/38776.htm?color=11590 … BLOG: http://swimminggibraltar.com/     
    
    
    I just bought: "Turbo Comic One Piece - Medium" via @swimoutlet http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/31629.htm?color= …  Read more: http://swimminggibraltar.com/     
    
    
    I just bought: "Dolfin Uglies Spiro Back One Piece".  1 for me, 1 for @emilykunze. @swimoutlet has great suits!  http://www.swimoutlet.com/product_p/41375.htm?color=37121 …    
    
    
    @RealTonyRocha Hey- I like that you liked this!  Do you know about @worldreaders?    
    
    
    Not a fan of @british_airways right now! BCN to LHR delayed. Missed flight to Dallas. Now going tomorrow via Houston.    
    
    
    I never knew that flying from Barcelona to Dallas takes 3 days.  With british_airways, apparently it does!  Delays delays delays!  Horrible.    
    
    
    @emilykunze and @mauprieto rock out in a 7.5 race in cold waters http://wp.me/p2MIAW-4B  Go Team!    
    
    
    @MysteryCoach thanks for sharing!    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan meaning hot air balloon? might have been faster.    
    
    
    Check out Amazon Promoting Worldreader On Its Homepage!  Great Publicity.  Well done @amazon! @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/11/01/amazon-promoting-worldreader-on-its-homepage-great-publicity/ …    
    
    
    I just unlocked the "Foodie" badge on @foursquare for checking in at five different places rated by Zagat! http://4sq.com/U1jXQD     
    
    
    Barcelona plaza  in after-school mode.  http://ligh.tt/dBR     
    
    
    Tanzania- awesome! Read more: @Worldreaders Brings Kindles To Yet Another African Country @ http://www.ebookanoid.com/2012/11/07/worldreader-brings-kindle-ereaders-to-yet-another-african-country/ …    
    
    
    @Top_eReader thanks for the @worldreaders shout-out on #amazon!    
    
    
    I love Rafa! He's won 7 tournaments in Barcelona-right below my house.  http://ligh.tt/lD5     
    
    
    Hope to not see this in the ocean this weekend. #swimming http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rue-FIHkRt/     
    
    
    Big party tonight in one of my favorite stores in Barcelona. Gotta love a vegetarian rock heir! @stellamcCartney http://ligh.tt/bCR     
    
    
    Stella McCartney in Barcelona! I confess- I'm a bit star struck! http://ligh.tt/lD9     
    
    
    @davidrisherWR I tink so!    
    
    
    I like this highlight of Walt Mossberg twirling in a chair...  http://ligh.tt/aCd     
    
    
    @FranklinMissy Hey M- we're 4 old swimmers who are planning to swim the Strait of Gibraltar this summer. U inspire us! http://swimminggibraltar.com     
    
    
    Stella mcCartney- Colombian style! http://ligh.tt/mDY     
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney Congrats on your amazing party yesterday. It'll mark a before and after in Barcelona. I wanted to pitch in 1 minute an idea    
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney You designed outfits for the amazing UK Olympic team. Would you be interested in designing swim suits for....See next tweet    
    
    
    @StellaMcCartney for 3 average women swimming the Strait of Gibraltar to raise money for e-books to Africa? Pleeease?    
    
    
    @StellMcCartney please read more about our crazy swim for social good- http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rx9KacHkbt/     
    
    
    @MattSchofield only that she is Colombian.....think Gloria from Modern Family!    
    
    
    @MattSchofield indeed she is... But the pic I posted is of my Colombian friend in a @stellamccartney store! :-)    
    
    
    love u"@DrWider: could u b cuter? @stellamccartney pls read more about our swim for social good- http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  http://instagr.am/p/Rx9KacHkbt/ ”    
    
    
    @KeithWLogan thanks for the #ff!    
    
    
    About to do the 4x1000 relay! #swimming with @emilykunze http://ligh.tt/kEp     
    
    
    @MattSchofield thanks for the shout out! Have a great weekend....    
    
    
    Celebrating the 4k swim with @mauprieto @emilykunze #ginandtonics http://ligh.tt/lF5     
    
    
    @csutswim big fan of yours... Would love to interview you for http://www.swimminggibraltar.com  por favor!    
    
    
    Dog and beach = goodness http://ligh.tt/gEB     
    
    
    NEW BLOG: Why are we training so hard to swim from Europe to Africa?  We're Swimming for Books http://wp.me/p2MIAW-88  @emilykunze @mauprieto    
    
    
    BLOG: @worldreaders has been selected by @chase as 1 of 25 charities to win $1 million! But We Need You and You and You http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/14/we-need-you-and-you-and-you/ …    
    
    
    Thanks for the retweet! Will you help? Por favor?    
    
    
    @MelyNicolau_3, @M_unzue6, @anit82009= total studs who love @worldreaders! Go Barça Femenino! pic.twitter.com/OWNHWPun    
    
    
    The women's team from @FCB come into @worldreaders office and love what we're doing with e-books in Africa!  http://ligh.tt/gGp     
    
    
    @cultureslurp Thanks for your help with this!    
    
    
    No. 15 made me chuckle: Cartoons from the Issue of November 19th, 2012 : The New Yorker -  http://www.newyorker.com/humor/issuecartoons/2012/11/19/cartoons_20121112?slide=15?mbid=social_mobile_tweet …    
    
    
    @BeatrizTejeiro thanks so much for getting the word out! Vote @worldreaders!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo you are so awesome!    
    
    
    @mauprieto about to swim an 8k with @emilykunze pic.twitter.com/x3w0eavq    
    
    
    Trying to psych myself up to swim- but it's cold and dreary in Sitges! @mauprieto @emilykunze http://ligh.tt/dIf     
    
    
    Gangnam style by 2 little Spaniards. http://ligh.tt/nKY     
    
    
    I just ousted Alberto G. as the mayor of Chiringuito Pizzeria Del Puerto on @foursquare! http://4sq.com/dfA9b2     
    
    
    @Oprah You love education, Africa, reading, and the Kindle.  This is MADE for you!  Will you help get the word out? http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/14/we-need-you-and-you-and-you/ …    
    
    
    BLOG: Peek into the mind of @emilykunze as she swims long distances... READ: Swimming for Something Bigger Than Me http://wp.me/p2RyIb-8k     
    
    
    Love this article: E-Books Advance Literacy in Africa http://blogs.edweek.org/edweek/bookmarks/2012/11/e-books_advance_literacy_in_africa.html?cmp=SOC-SHR-TW … via @educationweek    
    
    
    New Blog: "What Are You Thankful For?" Helping amazing young women like Linda achieve her dreams. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/21/what-are-you-thankful-for/ …    
    
    
    Learning how to make chocolate macaron- like La Duree! http://ligh.tt/fNg     
    
    
    Making pumpkin gnocchi- Italian style http://ligh.tt/aM8     
    
    
    BLOG: Richard- Ghanaian High Schooler: "Education is a superb institution that offers the individual something unique" http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/11/23/whats-an-education-worth/ …    
    
    
    @mauprieto @emilykunze you forgot to say... And cold!    
    
    
    Happy belated Thanksgiving! Gulp! pic.twitter.com/SEYJMl0K    
    
    
    HIV, genocide, human trafficking. W/out education nothing changes. Vote & Share http://vote4books.com/WR_SM  @worldreaders Please RT!    
    
    
    @joelleLw You are awesome!  Thanks for getting the word out about @worldreaders chance to win and empower a generation.    
    
    
    @KettlebellsBCN Thanks for getting the word out!    
    
    
    @KopoKopoInc @worldreaders Thanks for your support!  We'll need more in the coming days!    
    
    
    @buddingreader @amazon I know!  It's awesome! @worldreaders    
    
    
    @lizzie_nyc Thanks for the support!  http://vote4books.com !    
    
    
    @Chare11 Thanks for the support!  We can't do it without you!    
    
    
    @erikbl Seriously awesome!    
    
    
    @WackyMamaBear Awesome!    
    
    
    @cheekymommaof2 Thanks so much for your support!  Books For All!    
    
    
    @msafoundation @davidrisherWR Totally awesome!  Just one tiny thing: for the rest of the week when you tweet.. it's @worldreaders with an S.    
    
    
    @owenswims93 @mauprieto @emilykunze Absolutely!  You could hang with us. That is until you blow by us in the race- then you're on your own!    
    
    
    @msafoundation @worldreaders Perfect- thanks a million for your support!    
    
    
    This weekend I'm swimming from the Costa Brava around Islas Medas & back w/ @emilykunze & @mauprieto.  Scared of cold! pic.twitter.com/5PxYsWAB    
    
    
    @emilykunze is left handed and I'm deaf in one ear. It sounds so much better in Spanish: Zurda y Sorda. http://instagr.am/p/Skd35Rnkf5/     
    
    
    @shakira Pls help @worldreaders win a $1 mil grant from @ChaseGiving so they can bring education into rural Africa. http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    @shakira All you have to do is ask your fans to vote! Education change the world. @worldreaders #booksforall http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    @8hakiraa Help this BCN-based charity win $1 mill for education in Africa.  It's got Shakira written all over it! http://www.vote4books.com/WR_SM . RT!    
    
    
    @BarcelonaStat Pls support FCB collaborator @worldreaders- vote for them to win $1 mill for education in Africa! http://www.vote4books.com/WR_SM .    
    
    
    @teddevers @mauprieto Thanks for the support!  Can you ask the person next to you to vote too?    
    
    
    @Roman_barb Sylvia, share w/ your friends that @worldreaders needs votes to win a $1 mill grant from @ChaseGiving! http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @CornelWest Hi, from a Religion Major P'94.  Now working at @worldreaders to bring e-books into remote Africa. Pls see next tweet.    
    
    
    @CornelWest We need your help in getting out the vote to win $1 mill. from @ChaseGiving. Winning = e-readers for thousands in Africa. Next..    
    
    
    @CornelWest Pls ask your fans to vote for us: http://vote4books.com/WR_SM  so we can do more of this! #Education Empowers! THX! pic.twitter.com/dyu8TmxS    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Hey KL! Would you help us? @worldreaders can win $1 mill from @chasegiving but we need votes! VOTE: http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @PenguinClass @worldreaders So awesome!  Thanks!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo you are such a star!!!!    
    
    
    @bgurley @worldreaders @davidrisherWR Thanks for the support!    
    
    
    It's December 1st- 'Tis the season! http://ligh.tt/lSj     
    
    
    @ivankavisnjic Thanks for getting the word out!  Have you voted?  It only takes 20 seconds...http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @nautyinaccra @ameyaw112 Awesome! Have you voted?  It only takes 20 seconds...http://vote4books.com/WR_SM     
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Thanks for helping spread the word! Today's the last day of voting!    
    
    
    @KatieLinendoll Its llike the 50 yard dash- we're sprinting to the finish line with 4 other fast runners neck and neck. Too close to tell!    
    
    
    @iesealumni Thanks so much for getting the word out! Today's the last day to vote!    
    
    
    @Pitbull Worldreader is close to winning a $1m grant that would allow education worldwide. Pls support us. Vote &share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @Pitbull Worldwide education. Kids all over Africa with books. Isn't that awesome? Pls support us today! Vote & share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @RealPaulWalker Kids all over Africa w/ books. Isn't that awesome? Pls support @worldreaders today! #ROWW Vote & share: http://vote4books.com/WR_Dani     
    
    
    @Diane_Keaton As an author yourself, you can help!  Pls vote for @worldreaders today! Books improve lives. #Africa http://vote4books.com/WR_TW     
    
    
    I'm at the #GivingAwards w/ @worldreaders & other amazing non-profits like @MoreThanMeORG @fugeesfamily @sproutup @shesthefirst! #Education    
    
    
    Those folks at @ChaseGiving know how 2 throw a great party!  Ate chez Joachim Splichal (@PatinaDTLA chef) w/ #americangiving charities. YUM!    
    
    
    Prepping for #americangiving awards by @ChaseGiving.  Representing @worldreaders: we're 1 of 25 amazing charities transforming the world!    
    
    
    @Samasource It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work. #inspire    
    
    
    @TimmyGlobHealth It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work. #inspire    
    
    
    @krochetkids It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and stay awesome. #inspire    
    
    
    @joelmchale It was great to see you at the #AmericanGiving Awards! You had us all laughing in spite of all the nervous energy in the room.    
    
    
    @TeamRubicon It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and stay awesome. #inspire    
    
    
    @TogetherWeRise It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Can't believe all those bikes! #inspire    
    
    
    @katiemeyler It was so great to meet you at the #AmericanGiving Awards!  Keep up your amazing work and congratulations. #inspire    
    
    
    @lalasheila I love my girl!    
    
    
    Read our wrap-up of the #AmericanGiving Awards.  We were Close, But…. http://www.worldreader.org/blog/2012/12/09/close-but/ … via @jbaljko    
    
    
    @allysonfelix Great seeing you at The American Giving Awards.  You looked fab.  I loved the necklace- gold- b/c that's what you win!    
    
    
    @ColbieCaillat You were awesome at the American Giving Awards!  Thanks for entertaining us charities! #Inspire    
    
    
    @RylandKing Really enjoyed meeting you at AGA!  You're awesome.  Hey, can you send me a link to how you get people to open chapters?    
    
    
    @katiemeyler I am so happy for you!  Congrats.  xo    
    
    
    @mshoebri @lizzywood Sometimes the results don't go the way you want them to... but you learn and move on!  xo    
    
    
    @buddingreader @worldreaders You are so so right!    
    
    
    Who inspired me to swim from Europe to Africa?  My inspiration: Jen Schumacher http://wp.me/p2RyIb-a6  via the amazing @channelswimjen    
    
    
    @darrenemiller Are you in here?  Please read about My inspiration: Jen Schumacher http://wp.me/p2RyIb-a6  who are the others?    
    
    
    My rockstar colleague @nadjaboz gave my daughters the coolest pressie ever- signed @fcbarcelona shirts by @3gerardpique http://ligh.tt/mXX     
    
    
    @hale_a thanks so much for your support! #invaluable    
    
    
    @CatherinMcQuaid thanks for spreading the word about @worldreaders work!    
    
    
    I'm going to support @mauprieto's panel. Hot Startups In The City Of Gaudi — TechCrunch Barcelona http://techcrunch.com/2012/11/27/hot-startups-in-the-city-of-gaudi-techcrunch-barcelona-meetup-december-13/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    @mikebutcher hey Mike! I wanna tell you about BCN's hottest techy non-profit- @worldreaders. See ya today at hubby @mauprieto panel.    
    
    
    @kiwanja thanks so much for your support!    
    
    
    @RothwellSmith is this the first Nigerian publisher? You're rocking!    
    
    
    Watching @albertarmengol @pgelis @evavillaro @mauprieto at Tech Cruch Meet Up with @mikebutcher #barcelona pic.twitter.com/vGJ3wkrP    
    
    
    At #TCBarcelona- planned or by coincidence that there's the Barcelona chair on stage? pic.twitter.com/r4mB800t    
    
    
    Congrats 2 @cultureslurp and team for organizing #TCBarcelona- a great forum for a budding tech scene. And thanks 4 mentoring @worldreaders    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel Are you Melvin Stewart, the butterflier from NC? If so, I knew you years ago- WSY swimmer. #smallworld    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel thanks! Cool that you won a gold- somehow I didn't know that. I'm swimming again- training 2 cross the Strait of G this summer    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel We're raising $ 4 good with our trans-continental swim.  Have u done the Strait? http://www.owswimming.com . U could do it BTFLY    
    
    
    @mikebutcher you are a natural at leading a panel.  I wanted to connect w/ u  w/ @mauprieto but we had a weird dog- attack so we had 2 bolt.    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel got it- we hope you'll keep us non-prof swimmers doing crazy stuff for good causes on your radar.  xoxo SM (& join any time!!)    
    
    
    Happy 23rd @mauprieto! http://ligh.tt/aXp     
    
    
    @mijarosoft @worldreaders Thanks so much for the shout out!  Yes, a quiet e-book revolution is going on in Africa that will empower.  #Love!    
    
    
    @skrud I love that!    
    
    
    As usual, when I travel alone with my daughters, we get stranded due to late flights- but we make the best of it! http://4sq.com/ZdLNC1     
    
    
    @loreac hi there lovely! Leaving today, I hope. Girls are dying to ski and see cousins. How are things? Xo    
    
    
    Getting snowed in here in Denver. http://ligh.tt/fdG     
    
    
    @mauprieto take a look: http://dailynews.openwaterswimming.com/2012/12/who-is-trending-in-open-water-swimming.html … http://t.co/  via @darrenemiller    
    
    
    Wait- In Dec @InStyleMagazine I see that Yves Saint Laurent changed its branding to Saint Laurent.  Why? Read more: http://bit.ly/ZqP7d3     
    
    
    @owenswims93 Thanks for all your support, Owen- can we get you to guest blog?  From the best himself?    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Any ideas pop into your mind?  One thing I think is interesting is how small the sub-world of OW swimming is.  See next tweet    
    
    
    @owenswims93 I wonder if a true insider like you could tell the world about the global OW scene- a glimpse in for people who know nothing    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Although that might be too long- but it's one thing people repeatedly ask me about.    
    
    
    @owenswims93 Like: is it odd that u know both Damien & Jen Schumacher?  From Argentina and the US-- you from Ireland?  I think that's cool.    
    
    
    @DocumentDriven @ClintonGlobal @SusanUtley @writehedgebrook @worldreader @BookLoversInc @TheBookCellar Thanks and happy holidays!    
    
    
    @owenswims93 I know!  But I kinda think OW swimmers are a breed of their own...    
    
    
    Close your eyes & imagine what 200,000+ books for #Africa looks like.  Now open them: 877 #Kindles on their way! pic.twitter.com/jOI5FyVY    
    
    
    @dbudwin Hey man, good to hear from you!  How's it going?  Hope well- happy holidays to you!    
    
    
    @cultureslurp I had a very funny dream about you last night!  I'll tell you over a #ginandtonic back in Barcelona.  Remind me!    
    
    
    @BeingUncosmo Hope you're having a happy holiday! xo    
    
    
    @leila_c I loved your ad with @sorel- "Get your boots dirty."  Missed you at #AGA but nice to meet your colleagues. http://www.examiner.com/article/sorel-footwear-introduces-get-your-boots-dirty-fall-2012-campaign …    
    
    
    Favorite Christmas traditions- decorating gingerbread houses with primas. #awesome! http://ligh.tt/kdg     
    
    
    @lizzywood Merry merry to the best girl to work with ever!    
    
    
    @BrunoMars Your performance on SNL singing Michael Jackson, Katy Perry, Louis Armstrong etc. was a "Best of 2012"! http://vimeo.com/52406325     
    
    
    @mattiseman I do too!  No one ever taught me.  To wrap presents, that is.    
    
    
    @jcrew I am giving all my friends this genius thing! It's so tiny and perfect.  http://www.luuux.com/health-beauty/j-crew-mr-mrs-emergency-gold-emergency-kit …    
    
    
    Christmas cheer with the family....love this time of year! http://ligh.tt/odu     
    
    
    @mattiseman good thing you took it PDF! Merry x-mas!!    
    
    
    Love! @melindagates: The intellectual challenge of working together to solve the world’s biggest problems is uplifting. http://gates.ly/ZoyU8     
    
    
    @Andracke @jbaljko @NadjaBoz @JuliadeCelis Merry Christmas to AMAZING TEAM COMMS!!!!    
    
    
    First African Designed Smartphone, Tablet Hit Market http://mashable.com/2012/12/25/african-tablet-smartphone/ … via @mashable    
    
    
    @RedHourBen Your humor is my absolute favorite.  But it must be hard to be funny all the time- even on your tweets!  #IFeelForYa!    
    
    
    What does @worldreaders do w/ 365 days?  3 new African countries, 250,000 e-books, an Amazon home page, an app... shew! http://bit.ly/VlYAhu     
    
    
    @mijarosoft @cjbrandt @beckystraw @sloane @susangordo @CynthiaHellen @srudat @riaglo @rmack Thank you!  Happy New Year to you too!    
    
    
    A look back at an amazing year at Worldreader.  2012 was HUGE! But 2013 will only be bigger. http://bit.ly/VlYAhu     
    
    
    @Alexweir1949 over 1000 #kindles... In January we'll launch 1000 more! And there are half a million reading on our book app via @BiNu    
    
    
    New Years Resolution #1- Do a lot more of this! http://www.OWswimming.com  pic.twitter.com/2Gfm0Xbj    
    
    
    