When Technologists are Challenged by Technology http://bit.ly/1cVDgtR   -- WiFi challenges reduced today's conference tweet stream #ILTA13    
    
    
    @robsaccone My pleasure. Thanks, Rob!    
    
    
    @planty Thanks, Jason. We'll try to do better tomorrow.    
    
    
    @johngillies You are too kind, John! Thanks so much for participating in the session.    
    
    
    Alternative Billing: What's Working and What's Not http://bit.ly/12krKRS  @KMHobbie's notes on #IDPG #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hallelujah! The WiFi is back.  Kudos to #ILTAs Clay Gibney and team. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Co-chair Skip Lohmeyer is introducing Rohit Talwar (Interviewed by Monica Bay). Topic: Law 2020 Emerging Biz & Tech opptys #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Rohit Talwar is the founder of fast future research. He is leading the #ILTA future tech project. He has #law firm clients. #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Rohit Talwar is a good sport! He is doing a great job of dealing with a small tech hiccough.  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Talwar on aging populations: How do you motivate an 190-year old network manager?  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Talwar: what's the extended human life span going to do to marriage? (You get shorter sentences for double murder!)  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    See "23 and me" -- it's website that can compare yr genetic profile w/ others. It will show how yr genetics affect yr daily choices.   #KEY2    
    
    
    Talwar: Airports are getting vertical farms. See O'hare. #key2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Keynote: Rohit Talwar – Law 2020: Emerging Business and Technology Opportunities http://bit.ly/181cwjC  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Listening to Tracey Smith as she leads #KMers and technologists in the art of storytelling. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @johngillies Science of storytelling: Broca's brain translates meaning. It stimulates every other part of brain affected. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Smith: Storytelling induces a sense of safety. That's why they show movies on an airplane. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    #Storytelling to Transform Your #KM Projects, Strategy and Culture http://bit.ly/14YTU8U  #KPMG2 #ILTA13 #KMers    
    
    
    Ginevra Saylor is singing the praises of "stealth #KM." Finding ways 2 incorporate KM into other functions. #KMPG3 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal 2 keys to #BigData - analytics & dark data (what's piled up in a room & you hv no idea what it is) - Galina #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal Galina Datskovsky - #BigData 4 most firms means keep everything 4ever. Need policies 4  mining & disposition. #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal It's maddening that we R still discuss'g how 2 gt attys 2 put info in CRM. #BigData can save CRM-Blain Banick #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    KM in Support of Firm Operations http://bit.ly/170VDGO  #KMPG3 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT “@tgnbibr: Quick poll of audience ranks 75% of firms R getting by, 24% failing & only 1% have visionary leadership. #SPEC16 #ILTA13”    
    
    
    MT “@tgnbibr: If you start defining your strategic goals within budgetary constraints, you’re already stuck in the box. #SPEC16 #ILTA13”    
    
    
    Bryan Cave focuses budget convos on (1) what has 2 B done & (2) what can we do that would make a real difference to the firm? #ORG7 #ilta13    
    
    
    Grok the Grid (Susskind's): matrix = External <--> Internal; Technology <--> Knowledge/Action #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman: The strategic opptys are client-facing. However, you have 2 master the internal projects since they R foundational. #org7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow What evidence did the panelists cite?    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow Stories like this raise huge barriers to entry for younger women, Who wants to live this way? #Misc2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    “@ShirleyCrow: #MISC2 #ILTA13 Networking: find out who your really excellent peers are and watch and follow them.” // Start w/ #ILTA    
    
    
    The path 2 strategic thinking, 2 differentiating your firm is NOT through the Sheep Pasture. (Sheep are blind followers.) #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman: Just b/c someone else did it does not necessarily make it useful 4 you & your firm. You need to think strategically. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @johnalber cautions against a "consumerist approach" to IT = "Now that I have a budget, what shall I buy??" #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: what decisions in the biz process most affect profitability? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: what info is necessary for optimal decision making? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: What information presentation & location is optimal for effective decision making? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow Thanks a million, Shirley and @TimGolden. I so appreciate your participation in the session & your kind words. #SPEC16 #ILTA13    
    
    
    How 2 make a direct connection to the profits of the firm? Focus on client-facing projects. @JohnAlber #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Citing @ronfriedmann's Do Less Law #ILTA talk, @michaelmillsny suggests that we do less IT. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Testing a new idea: Can you tie it to a measure currently in use by the firm? Are there metrics that matter? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman is explaining Bryan Cave's proprietary "octagon" = 8 metrics by which they measure EVERYTHING -- ppl, projects, etc. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @tgnbibr You are extravagantly kind, Ted! Thank you.    
    
    
    @VQab Thanks so much for attending and tweeting the session, Ann! #SPEC16 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Bryan Cave is cost-conscious & careful, bt their overwhelming preference is 2 focus on moving the needle on the revenue side. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Technologists who just happen to be attorneys -- that's how @AndrewMBaker describes most of his team. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Don't waste time creating documentation no one will read. Focus yr energy on creating real value 4 clients. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Why scrum? Speed allows U 2 stay on the cutting edge; projects R more complex & hard 2 plan 4.  @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    The @seyfarthshawLLP legal #innovation group is a "small development shop inside a #lawfirm". @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    For speedy wireframes, @seyfarthshawLLP  uses @balsamiqNext to help bring a concept 2 life. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    "User stories" = basis 4 a develop't project. They define who, what & why (biz value). Also a "definition of `doneness.'" #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    With over 1400 user stories, @seyfarthshawLLP always focuses on prioritizing & possibly combining projects. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @KMHobbie Curious. What are they saying about task codes & profitability analysis? Or is the problem that they are not saying anything?    
    
    
    @tgnbibr Does this means they do the first calculation on the basis of time and then adjust?    
    
    
    Soriano: Scrum is about fostering a sustainable pace 2 produce a good quality of work. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    They have a 15-minute daily status meeting on the projects - held standing up in front of their scrum board. Good communication btwn teams.    
    
    
    Moving from the old waterfall method 2 agile scrum is totally worth it, but isn't w/o challenges. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano: The developers love the new transparency that scrum provides. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Scrum has enabled even better communication between the developers & the legal innovations team. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @KMHobbie Interesting. Is a new methodology emerging? #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano:The @seyfarthshawLLP intranet looks NOTHING like #SharePoint b/c they have a brilliant in-house designer. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano: They have integrated Google calendar & Outlook with their SeyfarthLink extranets. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow  Thanks for the clarification, Shirley. It was a provocative claim. #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow I agree. It's important for junior women that senior women frame a more sustainable and sane path to success. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Serious cool #ILTA13 session. We're attending Using Virtual-World Technology in the Real World #SPEC14. We have presenters IRL & via avatar.    
    
    
    Presenters: Col. Scott Reid (CKO, USJAG), Dr. Paulette Robinson (Nat'l Defense University), Randy Hinriche (CEO, 2b3d)  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    This preso is being given simultaneously to #ILTA13 and the Serious Play Conference http://bit.ly/i6BljQ  #SPEC14    
    
    
    We R taking a virtual tour of the second life facility. It has configurable spaces & can incorporate biz apps & cloud tools. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    A room can be configured to create a permanent "war room" w/ all the legal resources/files U need 4 the matter. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    You cn reconfigure conference space w/ a couple clicks of mouse. No need 2 call hotel staff 4 extra chairs! @TJJohnsonILTA #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Virtual world conferences R more engaging. U feel present & experience what your avatar experiences. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Contrast this great sense of engagement w/ the continuous partial attention typical of webinars where everyone multitasks. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life has serious healthcare uses. See Snow World, which helps children w/ burns. http://slate.me/yjW9Tz  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life for business purposes is an emerging technology NOT a bleeding edge technology. (Would #LegalIT agree?) #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    2nd life has challenges w/ security & identity. However, these issues also exist IRL. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    We're about to see a rehearsal for a litigator preparing for a trial. It happens in a 2nd life courtroom. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: U have 2 make a personal investment 2 become "fluent" in any new technology. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    How did they create the 2nd life courtroom? It took their graphics designer 2 hrs after receiving a picture of a court. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    We're watching Scott Reid maneuver around the virtual courtroom 2 learn where 2 stand, how 2 move in IRL. Gr8 prep 4 court. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    A litigator can practice the blocking, flow & choreography necessary 4 a good courtroom preso. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    As in sports, you can visualize every step of the experience, so when U face it IRL, U know how 2 respond fluidly. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: we typically react 2 others in IRL based appearance, personality, etc. How will we react 2 each other's avatars? #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Since avatars can provide a little distance from volatile emotions. Wld 2nd Life B useful 4 resolving family law matters? #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    One audience member suggested that the US & Iranian governments should be negotiating via Second Life. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @StephKimbro Thanks for the feedback. Would love 2 hear more about your experience. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life has been used to help veterans with post traumatic stress http://1.usa.gov/132Bhz6  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Microsoft will soon B providing the means for users 2 move easily between IRL & the virtual world from their office apps. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Now meeting Dr. Don Workman on the PTSD Island. It is an immersive 3D enviro 2 provide PTSD resources. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Correction: PTSD Island is 4 active-duty personnel & their families, not veterans. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Watching T2 Virtual PTSD Experience http://t2health.org/vwproj  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    This virtual PTSD experience makes key resources available to military personnel who might not otherwise seek help IRL. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Military personnel can visit the PTSD Experience using an anonymous avatar, so they protect confidentiality. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @rightbrainlaw @StephKimbro Agreed. As the technology improves, the opportunities expand. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Now that you mention it, there is a striking resemblance! ;)    
    
    
    @GameOnLaw @StephKimbro Fair point. I hope the technology improves sufficiently 2 lower barriers 2 entry. Perhaps widespread gaming will too    
    
    
    The PTSD Experience includes #gamification elements to provide feedback 2 the user. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ldamon It was great to see you across the room during the @seyfarthshawLLP preso for the #ILTA13 Most Innovative #lawfirm award. Congrats!    
    
    
    One thrill for sci-fi fans: the presenters have been moving around their virtual world by teleporting. Cool! #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    From inception to beta of PTSD Island was abt 6 months. That's impressive speed! #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: DARPA brought us the internet and is bringing us these great virtual world applications. It's the future. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    The avatars ended the 2nd Life preso Gangnam Style. Lots of fun & lots of learning in this session. Thanks, Col.Scott Reid. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Glad we were able to wave at each other. Sorry we didn't have a chance to chat.    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Unfortunately not. I'm seated in 19A and about to depart.    
    
    
    @rmcclead @KMHobbie @johngillies @bren924 @tangledom @highqsolutions It was my pleasure, Ryan. It was great 2 see all of you.    
    
    
    @KatyMGeorge So glad to connect here. Welcome to the Twittersphere!    
    
    
    Keynote: Chris DeSantis – The Crucible of Experience as a Catalyst for Leading #ILTA13 http://bit.ly/14TAJYd  (Contains excellent advice)    
    
    
    Thank YOU, Jeff!! MT @jeffrey_brandt: RT They forgot @VMaryAbraham & @HackettInHouse: 25 women 2 follow on Twitter. http://www.fastcompany.com/3016225/dialed/25-of-the-smartest-women-on-twitter …    
    
    
    Chris DeSantis – The Crucible of Experience as a Catalyst for Leading #ILTA13 http://bit.ly/14TAJYd  (Contains excellent advice) #mgmt    
    
    
    Back at @Columbia University's Information & Knowledge Strategy Masters program. Glad to help teach new #KMers. #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    First session is on Strategy taught by Guy St. Clair (@smr_knowledge) and Kate Pugh (@katrinapugh), academic director of program #IKNS    
    
    
    1st Qs: Where do we compete? How do we win? How do we sustain our competitive advantage? #IKNS    
    
    
    Start by clarifying the client's vision, most fundamental goals. Then consider Michael Porter's 5 forces.  #IKNS    
    
    
    Here's a link to Michael Porter's Five Forces Analysis http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Porter_five_forces_analysis … #IKNS    
    
    
    @siftonpark (from @Microsoft) says us that we shldn't hv 2 leave our work 2 be social. We shld B able 2 B social in our work apps #e20 #IKNS    
    
    
    Listening to Susan Baktis (@Accenture) speaking on topic: "Technology isn't the answer, but it can help lead the way." #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: Sharing happens around a topic, around content, around people. You need to facilitate all of these. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They track extensive "transaction #metrics" on activity in their #e20 platform. It's harder to measure the value of content #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They try 2 help direct ppl 2 other other useful content by showing "more like" and Amazon-like suggestions. #IKNS    
    
    
    @pygkno @Columbia Hi there! Hope you're enjoying the residency.    
    
    
    Baktis: They are looking 4 new ways 2 help ppl find content w/o having to email a request 2 everyone. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: @Accenture is using a proprietary algorithm 2 power their content recommendation engine #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: The more data you have, the better the results from the recommendation engine. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They have simplified the "#SharePoint form. Instead, they created a little app 4 contributing content. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They also enabled contribution by email. They have a batch job that processes email attachments & adds them 2 #SharePoint #IKNS    
    
    
    Will do. Are the #IKns tweets appearing together w/ the tweets under #IKNS?    
    
    
    @mrs_wynn Just checked -- both tags are consolidated. You can use either #IKnS or    
    
    
    Baktis: SME (subject-matter experts) are expected 2 contribute content in their areas. It's part of their performance evaluation. #IKNS    
    
    
    Q from class: How 2 manage info overload via social activity streams? What if you miss something impt? A: FILTERS! #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They R exploring #gamification 2 help improve participation & 2 provide feedback 2 users. #IKNS    
    
    
    If you are interested, here is a quick overview of #gamification I wrote earlier this year: http://bit.ly/WPUii8  #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: Just as technology is not the complete answer, neither is #gamification. Use it help ppl learn or become more engaged. #IKNS    
    
    
    Here is more info on @Accenture's use of #gamification 2 improve knowledge sharing http://bit.ly/XSvXqJ  #KMers #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: @Accenture is using tools from @Badgeville 2 add #gamification 2 their #SharePoint platform. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They use @Wordpress to enable blogging in their #SharePoint environment. #IKNS    
    
    
    Next speaker: Tom Stewart (@BoozCompany) on Taking Knowledge to Market." #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If you are speaking 2 biz folks, it's impt that U use the language of money. #KMers #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: a good #KM system helps a knowledge worker answer the Q: what do I need 2 do 2day & how do I do it? #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: We can sell knowledge as a product. That's what @Accenture and @BoozCompany do. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Over time, the price of commodities declines, while the value of knowledge assets grows. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: The internet increases competition. In an online world, a reasonable substitute is just a click away. (Big strategic issue.) #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart cites stats that show that only 48% of executives believe that their strategies (that they wrote!) will succeed. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart's stats also show that 2/3 of executives believe they have too many conflicting priorities. This impedes strategic direction. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Don't settle for strategy on the margins. Demand strategy that matters. Key focus = how do we create value for our clients? #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: recommends 'Putting Leadership Back into Strategy" by Cynthia Montgomery http://bit.ly/17oEB5K  #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: What do we sell that is unique & valuable? Ask yr clients: why do you buy from us & not the other guy? #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Knowledge assets take inputs & transform them into something more valuable. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Differentiation lies in your knowledge assets: human capital, structural capital, relationship capital. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Customers don't buy human, structural or relationship capital. They buy what you do 4 them. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Create a competitive advantage based on what U know (knowledge assets) & what U do well (execution). #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Once U know how 2 differentiate your firm, U then need a clear way 2 play the game 2 win. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: looking at @Apple's Form 10-K. Their #strategy = to create the best #UX thru 6 specific capabilities.  #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: R&D is incredibly concentrated. 1000 companies account for 48% of all R&D spending. #Innovation #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: tech leader #strategy; fast follower strategy; needs seeker strategy (responding 2 customer needs early). 1/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Each of these strategies requires different types of knowledge assets & knowledge #strategy. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a tech leader, who is my best friend? Scientists @ a great university. I put my lab next 2 them. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a market reader/fast follower, who is most impt? My CFO, it's all about operations & guaranteed return. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a Needs Seeker, who's most impt? My CMO = the person who understands clients the best. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: As #KMers, it's impt 2 think 1st abt the type of #strategy yr firm is pursuing. Then ID the key knowledge assets 2 manage. #IKNS    
    
    
    @ValdisKrebs Yes -- those are wrapped up in your Human Capital.    
    
    
    “@jordan_law21: "If something cannot go on forever, it will stop." Stein's Law. |But it might linger too long on life support    
    
    
    Stewart: #KM needs 2 b like Janus. One face looks 2 the market 2 understand clients better; the other face understands internal needs. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: "Ideas are capital. Everything else is just money." #Innovation #strategy #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    “@OPENForum: The right way to ask for a coffee meeting: http://bit.ly/19ObvPi ” | @ClaudiaBatten -- this is an improvement.    
    
    
    “@ValdisKrebs: @VMaryAbraham ...and how they work together, learn, share, and grow knowledge is all about social capital! || BIngo!
#IKNS”    
    
    
    Next speaker is Bob Libbey, @Pfizer's Head of Digital & Social Communications #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey's topic: The Digital Communications Battle for User Attention  = A fight that's sure to grow. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: Communications is an arm of #KM. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: we started by "telling & selling." Now it's about engagement. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: we used to just put content out & hope 4 the best. Now we use targeted #metrics 2 plan & track our work. #IKNS    
    
    
    LIbbey: The competition in the content realm is tough. It's very hard 2 get ppl's attention. How 2 induce repeat traffic 2 yr site? #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: quoting EU survey that shows 1/3 of respondents say that their smartphone is their main source of digital content. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: In digital communications, don't confuse the means with the end. (Don't focus on an #FB or #Twitter strategy.) #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: How employees spend their time online? According to one study, 60-80% is "cyberloafing." You hv 2 compete for this attention. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: Self-syndication was key 4 @ESPN and works 4 @Pfizer as well. Create gr8 content & then push it out thru a variety of channels #IKNS    
    
    
    @zeapen How can this be a good thing? Wasn't that study revolutionary?    
    
    
    @miunger @sklososky Thanks for your kind words, Mark. I had good material to work with!    
    
    
    @ClaudiaBatten @nilofer @OPENForum That makes sense when U have beautiful mountains all around you. The scenery isn't quite the same in NYC    
    
    
    @ClaudiaBatten @nilofer @OPENForum Ha! How you're talking!!!    
    
    
    #ILTA13 - The tides are turning - HighQ http://highq.com/ilta13-the-tides-are-turning/ …    
    
    
    Harris: significant companies are hugely data driven -- Disney, P&G, Netflix, Progressive Insurance Company, etc. #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: Companies that build a good analytics capability can use that to stay one (or more) steps ahead of the competition. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: 60% of respondents to a recent survey say their organization lacks the skills needed 2 leverage #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris quotes @tdav who says that "a lot of #BigData is low analytics." Some major insights from data may B missed in the media hype. #IKNS    
    
    
    MT @jamesdavidsaul "Embedding analytics into core biz processes creates sustainable competitive advantage." - Jeanne Harris, Accenture #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: One challenge is that a significant number of decision makers in orgs are essentially innumerate. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris; Lack of trust [in data] remains the #1 barrier to the widespread adoption and impact of analytics. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    @VQab Thanks so much 4 including my materials in yr overview. Honored 2 B in such good company @jordan_law21 @HackettInHouse @ronfriedmann    
    
    
    Sad but true! RT @mloxton: @VMaryAbraham heck, most firms lack even rudimentary data skills even for #littledata, never mind #bigdata    
    
    
    Does the compensation model of your org reward a "we" focus or "me" focus? This will affect your #KM program. @KatrinaPugh #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    Pagani: Ppl see themselves as the center of their network OR as participants in a lot of networks. This colors their action & yr #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Pagani: There R many paths 2 a good #KM outcome. Start by understanding the person U R helping. Put them at the center. #IKNS    
    
    
    @orgnet @ValdisKrebs Thanks 4 the RT & the link 2 yr article. Stay tuned -- the next session is Practices of the 21st C. Learning Org #IKNS    
    
    
    @orgnet It's entirely my pleasure. Thanks for participating via Twitter. @ValdisKrebs #IKNS    
    
    
    Next Session: @KatrinaPugh is speaking on Practices of a 21st Century Learning Organization. #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    It helps when ppl in the org can think about issues in other "frames" besides their own. @KatrinaPugh #IKNS    
    
    
    A vast number of arguments arise from ppl looking at different (& incomplete) data. Ladder of Inference analysis can help avoid this. #IKNS    
    
    
    Argyris: If you've had a convo go south recently, review it 2 identify what was going on in your head during the convo. 1/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Argyris: How did your focus (distraction/subtext) affect the convo? 2/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Jeanne Harris: How High Performers Compete – and Win – with Analytics http://bit.ly/15znsU4  @Columbia #IKNS #KMers #KM #BigData    
    
    
    Recovering from ILTA 2013 http://www.geeklawblog.com/2013/09/recovering-from-ilta-2013.html … /by @rmcclead #ILTA13 #lawfirm #legalIT    
    
    
    MT @ronfriedmann: Can We See Scale & Experience Benefits in Law Practice? http://bit.ly/15wy8ns  //Ron raises sobering questions 4 #lawfirms    
    
    
    How will Amazon MatchBook upend the publishing industry? http://amzn.to/17nLaTS  It certainly strengthens brand loyalty 2 Amazon.    
    
    
    @newroccindy @legalerswelcome  I'd be happy to help, Cindy. Just let me know where and when. Thanks!    
    
    
    @legalerswelcome Glad this is starting up again, Natalie.    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy My pleasure, Deb. Hope all is well with you.    
    
    
    @KMHobbie @ronfriedmann Subcontracting works in other industries. Why not in legal too? Better 50 local experts than 1 over-stretched firm.    
    
    
    @LegalTypist  Thanks so much, Andea!    
    
    
    @LawTechLegalIT Thanks very much. I'll send DM with details.    
    
    
    Attending the Legal IT Forum at beautiful Hanbury Manor in England. #LIFT13    
    
    
    RT'd w/ correct hashtag: Attending the Legal IT Forum in beautiful Hanbury Manor in England. #LITF13    
    
    
    Keynote is by Mark Stevenson, a futurologist talking about the Future and What To Do About it.  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Stevenson … #LITF13    
    
    
    A huge added benefit this morning = Mark Stevenson is a bona fide comedian as well as a gr8 guide 2 the future. Challenging info + laughs    
    
    
    Stevenson: Talking about a "carbon-neutral oil refinery." Mind boggling. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: the Thingiverse has tons of downloadable prototypes available 4 immediate 3D printing. What will this do 2 manufacturing? #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Nanoscribe is a technology 2 watch. With nanoscribe, you can 3D print a 3D printer. Bye Bye manufacturing!  #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Why aren't people adopting the newer/better ideas? They R surrounded by "idea-proof fences." #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: How to handle the shift from the digital revolution to the future? Start w/ optimistic, ambitious goals. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Definition of happiness? Find something bigger than you are and devote your life to it. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Keep smashing yourself into new ideas. Stay curious. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: make sure your org is spending to engineer serendipity. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: You are what you do, not what you intend to do. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Making mistakes is ok. Not trying is irresponsible. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: The first mistake is a learning opportunity. A repeated mistake is incompetence. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Think like an engineer, not a politician. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Play the long game. (Inevitably, the early rounds will be failures.) #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson quotes the writer of The Sopranos: The road 2 success is littered w/ corpses. Most are suicides. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Cynicism is the ultimate enemy of the future. So police your own cynicism. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Be defined not by what you own, but by what you create. #LITF13    
    
    
    “@JoannaMG22: @LegalITForum #LITF13 following @VMaryAbraham for great live tweeting #legalit” // Thanks, Joanna.    
    
    
    Stevenson: Every technology is dual use = it can be used for good or evil. We need 2 B part of steering it in a positive direction. #LITF13    
    
    
    Next: Derek Southall, Janet Day & Neil Cameron speaking about the delivery gap btwn what we hv & what our clients need. #LITF13    
    
    
    @BenWightwick Just until tomorrow, unfortunately. I've got another speaking gig next week in NYC.    
    
    
    Southall: Most IT products R for the general market.They need to be customized heavily 2 work in the legal sector. This is the gap.  #LITF13    
    
    
    Janet disagrees w/ Derek Southall. She doesn't think the legal vertical is big enough 2 interest big vendors. #LITF13    
    
    
    Neil Cameron: 20 years ago, vendors really catered 2 law firms. However, even then they could only deliver 80% of req'ts = Gap. #LITF13    
    
    
    Cameron: Most firms aren't willing 2 pay 4 what it takes 2 deliver customized IT products. This is hard 4 vendors. #LITF13    
    
    
    Cameron: Another complication 4 IT vendors is that the bulk of their #legalIT customers don't agree on the req'ts of a product. #LITF13    
    
    
    Day: When law firms can't clearly articulate their req'ts, then the #LegalIT vendors can delivery only an approximate solution. #LITF13    
    
    
    Day: See example of Microsoft Office = every #lawfirm customizes an idiosyncratic version. No one uses it out of the box. #LITF13    
    
    
    Day: b/c of the idiosyncratic versions of MS Office, every #lawfirm has 2 waste time converting docs sent by another firm. #LITF13    
    
    
    Cameron: Sometimes the hardest part of an consultation w/ a #lawfirm is convincing lawyers that what they do is a process, not art. #LITF13    
    
    
    “@BenWightwick: Interesting following @VMaryAbraham tweets on #LITF13 #greatlivetweeting” // Thanks a million, Ben! These are great sessions    
    
    
    Cameron: Once a #lawfirm has ID'd its key processes, the next challenge is convincing them 2 bring clients in2 the convo. #LITF13    
    
    
    Cameron: Once you hv client input re: what needs 2 B changed in your #lawfirm processes, bring vendors in2 the convo. #LITF13    
    
    
    Chris Bull: we need to convince our #lawfirms that they are in the information biz & the technology biz #LITF13    
    
    
    Big Q: how to turn IT chiefs into stakeholders w/in a #lawfirm? A: create a CIO role w/ strategic focus #LITF13    
    
    
    Chris Bull: it isn't enough 2 have an IT dept strategy; it must connect closely w/ yr #lawfirm's strategy. #LITF13    
    
    
    Southall cites latest @richardsusskind book -- to what extent has yr #lawfirm IT dept shifted from old world 2 new world tech? #LITF13    
    
    
    Janet Day: #lawfirm IT depts need to deliver a professional level of service w/in a legal professional services firm. #LITF13    
    
    
    Day: a professional level of services means having appropriate mastery of new technology. #LITF13    
    
    
    Bull: nearly every firm in the room will be part of a merger/acquisition. Does everyone have an IT contingency plan for merger? #LITF13    
    
    
    @robsaccone You're so right, Rob. Are enough #lawfirms thinking this way? #LIFT13    
    
    
    A big challenge for #lawfirms is knowing exactly what it costs them to deliver client services. Bad metrics, bad data. #LITF13    
    
    
    Most recent tweets were from a session called New Game--Changing Methods & Technologies: Re-Engineering How Lawyers Deliver Services #LITF13    
    
    
    Speakers in last session: Alex Holt & Mike Touhey (Steria), Chris Bull (Kingsmead Square) & David Thorpe (Peppermint Technology) #LITF13    
    
    
    Next Session: Transforming Unstructured Data in2 Actionable Business Information. Speaker: Dan Wales, Legal Biz Manager, BIPB Legal #LITF13    
    
    
    Wales: He believes the #lawfirms are at least 5 years behind clients regarding using #BigData. Big problem = bad data. #LITF13    
    
    
    Wales: What's a #lawfirm's biggest asset? Not people-- it's the internal data, external data (client/competitor data); public data #LITF13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Hello Jeff! Long time no speak. Thanks for the RT.    
    
    
    Wales: Master data management is critical. #lawfirms must scrub, store and map their data if they want to be competitive. #LITF13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt They won't be able to connect the parents & daughter b/c of incorrect contact info in the CRM!    
    
    
    Wales: Data visualization is a powerful tool -- it allows U 2 communicates w/ big impact -- ppl can absorb a great deal of data. #LITF13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt It's a big challenge. Many #lawfirms are falling far behind their clients re: #BigData. #LITF13    
    
    
    @XyoneSecurity Thanks for participating! Looking forward to the awards ceremony tonight.    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt @XyoneSecurity Thank you kindly, Jeff. You are far too generous!    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt True. If anything, they are running in the opposite direction! #BigData #LITF13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Yes, thanks. Busy and happy!    
    
    
    @jasonmoyse @jeffrey_brandt Perhaps they have all the data they think they need?    
    
    
    @planty @jeffrey_brandt That's so smart -- and well within the reach of any #lawfirm that is serious about working smarter. #LITF13    
    
    
    Listening to Janet Day in convo w/ Alistair Killich, Head of IT, Legal, at Shell. The legal dept has thousands of lawyers worldwide #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: Deeply embedding the IT function helps mitigate resistance to change. #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: They favor using corporate group standard applications rather than customizing tools for the legal dept #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: Usability is far more important that customization. #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: Focus on where you want the business to be and then build legal IT strategy to support that.  #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: it's important to measure ROI so you can tie IT investments directly to specific biz results. #LITF13    
    
    
    Killich: within a large biz, both legal and IT are functions. They likely have the same strategy. #LITF13    
    
    
    Listening to Steven J. Harper, law partner, adjunct law prof, blogger at The Belly of the Beast: http://thelawyerbubble.com/  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirms focus on the metrics (billables) this year and don't give much thought 2 what comes later. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirm mgmt is a triumph of short-termism that endures b/c it is lucrative, embedded & easy. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: for every 20 associates a #lawfirm hires annually, it loses 16. What a waste of human capital. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: Associate morale is down, but so is partner morale. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: Lawyers are taught to distinguish adverse precedent. So, they ignore lessons from failures of other #lawfirms. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: consultants 2 #lawfirms say that there are no economies of scale in practicing law once you get too big. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper cites a Citi/Hildebrandt 2013 report that says that only 60% of lateral hires R successful. He thinks the number is higher. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirms are in a hiring frenzy, but they still don't know how 2 get lateral hiring right. Yet, they persist. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: the lateral partner hiring frenzy causes discontinuity and disappointment, yet the strategy endures. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: Why #lawfirm hiring frenzy? The leveraged pyramid model requires attrition +short-term thinking + the mythology of growth.  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirms are fearful of a talent void in the next generation + concerned that aging partners are hanging on.  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: short-term thinking leads #lawfirms 2 tighten partner admission standards. This makes talent shortage worse. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: There R opptys: top young lawyers want mentors, useful experiences, collegiality = better #lawfirms #ArkKM    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann Actually, do scale benefits work anywhere except in manufacturing?    
    
    
    @lizamadden Follow #ArkKM today and tomorrow for info on #KM in the Legal Profession. #lawfirms #KMers    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirm partners must suspend hubris (remember the firm culture that made their success possible) 1/3 #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirm partners must act the part -- press firm leaders 2 do the right thing; then model the right behavior themselves 2/3 #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper: #lawfirm partners should question stupid metrics AND help their firm reorder its priorities #ArkKM    
    
    
    Steven Harper just finished a speedy tour through the facts of #lawfirm life today. Gotta be honest -- it was depressing. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Harper's advice 2 college students considering life in #lawfirms: don't be enticed by the $$$. Be sure U understand the price U pay #ArkKM    
    
    
    @BenWightwick Hello, Ben. The next couple of days should provide a rich tweetstream.    
    
    
    @markgould13 It was great to see you.  Virtual is good, but f2f is better!    
    
    
    “@AnswerHub: See Y @NancyWhite @4KM @VMaryAbraham @jackvinson made list of 11 #KM people U shld follow http://bit.ly/GPvDa6 ” // Thank you!    
    
    
    In the face of these depressing facts, what can an indiv. in a #lawfirm do? Steven Harper says: "Do what U can do 2 make it better." #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next up: @BruceMacEwen on the topic "Growth is Dead, Now What?"    
    
    
    #lawfirms are fooling themselves if they believe they can do better than their clients in the long term. @AdamSmithEsq #ArkKM    
    
    
    @BenWightwick @rmcclead The more the merrier!    
    
    
    Suicidal pricing is the response of desperate industries that need 2 squeeze out additional revenue. @AdamSmithEsq #lawfirms #ArkKM    
    
    
    Dr. Larry Richards caliper test results show how lawyers R not wired 4 #innovation. They R abnormally skeptical & not resilient. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Keynes: bankers prefer 2 fail in a conventional, orthodox way so no one will blame them 4 failing. #lawfirms too. @AdamSmithEsq #ArkKM    
    
    
    What's the answer 4 #lawfirms? #INNOVATION!!! @AdamSmithEsq #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next: The Client's Perspective. Presenters = Matt Todd (JPMorganChase); Joelle Quilla (Cognizant Technology Solution); @Colangelolaw #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kevin Colangelo (Proskauer) is moderating this session. @Colangelolaw #ArkKM    
    
    
    Quilla's bio: http://linkd.in/1byxB8A ; Todd's bio: http://linkd.in/ISdcgy  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: spectrum of legal svcs  JPMorganChase purchases is huge. When hiring counsel they focus on outcomes = lawyers who can deliver #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: External counsel must work as a natural extension of the internal legal dept -- without friction! #ArkKM    
    
    
    Quilla & Todd: They are not too interested in the inner workings of a #lawfirm. They focus on it when reviewing outcomes & invoices. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: When reviewing #lawfirm invoices, he asks the relevant inside counsel: "Does this $ amount represent good value to you?" #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: B/c they value a frictionless interaction between internal & external counsel, they are concerned by high associate turnover. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: #lawfirms need to win the client's trust. It is incredibly difficult to gain and incredibly easy to lose. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Quilla: Feedback is impt. Lots of communication. No #lawfirm loses her biz w/o a conversation about what went wrong.  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: We will happily tell you what we want from our #lawfirms. However, very few ask for the info. (Only 1 since July!) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Colangelo recommends the Journal of Consumer Psychology b/c it provides gd insight in what clients want. http://bit.ly/MoIyAL  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: Page 2 of their Outside Counsel Manual shows the principles governing #lawfirms. It explains how 2 work w/ JPMorganChase.  #ArkKM    
    
    
    My Notes from Bruce MacEwen's preso: Growth is Dead, Now What? http://bit.ly/16fPyW8  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: the most impt value-added svcs offered by #lawfirms 2 clients = secondees and CLE courses. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Todd: He isn't interested in learning 2 use #lawfirm extranets. If the firms consolidated on a single platform... (Hey @BenWightwick) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next speaker: John E. Murdock III, partner, Bradley Arant. Topic = Reducing Waste in Legal Processes. He thinks this shld B #KMs goal #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: The big strategic failing of #lawfirms is that the legal industry has not ID'd reliable ways of realizing scale benefits #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: Some legal work needs 2 B managed like a project (#PM, #LPM); some legal work needs 2 B improved like a process. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: recommends the Theory of Constraints 4 #lawfirms. (This is not part of our regular reading.) @JackVinson, legal is slow! #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: Industrial engineers now hv an educational track re: the legal industry. Soon they will move in2 #lawfirms. Gr8 oppty! #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock recommends "Mastering the Unpredictable," whi says Knowledge Work cannot B hard coded. http://amzn.to/gHI4qM  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: According to "Mastering the Unpredictable," drafting a will is NOT knowledge work, since it can be hard coded. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    @jackvinson Thanks, Jack. I clearly need a crash course!    
    
    
    Murdock: Key ways 2 ID waste in a process: (1) Is this step really necessary? (2) Is this a better way 2 do this step? #lawfirm #Lean #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: Improve process before improving operations = eliminate unnecessary steps and only then perfect remaining steps. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: Examples of waste in #law practice = using 2 docs when 1 would do; unnecessary investigation or research. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Murdock: Other examples of waste: Excess Thought = hving lawyers make decisions that machines can make more reliably. See @NeotaLogic #ArkKM    
    
    
    @orgnet @jriversmn @rmcclead You are ABSOLUTELY right, but it appears to be a new thought for the legal industry.    
    
    
    Just overheard: "I don't hv a @Twitter handle b/c I don't want yet 1 more source of info 2 check." (What if it's a better source?) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Hunter: his #lawfirm is bringing the power of #BigData analytics 2 their clients. Clients love it. @thelihunter #ArkKM    
    
    
    Hunter: At companies like Intel & Oracle, employees hv 2 reinvent themselves every 18 months or so. What about #lawfirms? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next a debate between @ozbenamram & @pkrakaur. Topic: Social Knowledge Management #KM #KMers    
    
    
    @KMalexandrahall @ozbenamram Very true. I hope it's been helpful.    
    
    
    The problem w/ social biz w/in a #lawfirm is one of size. There aren't enough ppl 2 participate (if only 10% participate). @ozbenamram    
    
    
    Social can work w/in #lawfirms when they are part of work mgmt (not just project mgmt). @pkrakaur #e20    
    
    
    The problem w/ social #KM w/in a #lawfirm is one of size. There aren't enuf ppl 2 participate (if only 10% participate). @ozbenamram #ArkKM    
    
    
    Social can work w/in #lawfirms when they are part of work mgmt (not just project mgmt). @pkrakaur #e20 #ArkKM    
    
    
    #lawfirms used 2 B social (open comms, transparent), when they were smaller. How 2 achieve this in a bigger org? @ozbenamram #ArkKM    
    
    
    10 yrs ago, we cldn't find anything. Now search engines let us find too much. How can social help? @ozbenamram #ArkKM    
    
    
    Overheard: #Lawfirm associates are hoarding info in reaction 2 job insecurity since 2008. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @KMalexandrahall There's been no convo yet about the value of convo w/in #lawfirms ;) @ozbenamram @pkrakaur @ronfriedmann    
    
    
    Benamram: Imagine a (FB-like) "wall" that shows U activity from people & projects that interest U. This is a middle path 4 attn mgmt #ArkKM    
    
    
    Tomorrow's #lawfirm social system needs 2 incl: content objects, user interaction, system integration. @ozbenamram @pkrakaur #ArkKM    
    
    
    Overheard: "#SharePoint 2013 needs to play nice with my document management system. Vendors please help." #ArkKM #KMers    
    
    
    Hearing repeated comments about the need 4 vendors to help #lawfirms meet tech needs. #LegalIT folks R stuck in static systems (DMS) #ArkKM    
    
    
    @KMalexandrahall @ozbenamram @pkrakaur @ronfriedmann Yes, the filtering is key. Analytics help reduce the noise. #ArkKM    
    
    
    If U hv any ideas abt how 2 design a gd social system 4 #lawfirms, @ozbenamram & @pkrakaur ask that U tweet it using the tags #ArkKM & #SKM    
    
    
    Sally Gonzalez: If your #lawfirm CIO is focused on a Windows/Office upgrade, there won't B much time 4 #KM. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Gonzalez: as much as 80% of a CIO's time can be spent on #lawfirm infrastructure. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @sinclairKM Thanks for RT'g my blog post, Euan. Please wave -- I'm not sure I see someone here that looks like your Twitter avatar!    
    
    
    @sinclairKM Thanks! I was looking for the sunglasses!    
    
    
    @KMalexandrahall @BruceMacEwen Alexandra, you may want to use the following handle for Bruce: @AdamSmithEsq    
    
    
    Next Toby Brown will wrap up the day's session. His topic is "Everything #KM was never intended to be." @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    Brown: clients are under direct pressure to reduce their legal spend. #lawfirm #KMers must start feeling this direct pressure. @gnawledge    
    
    
    Brown: clients R under direct pressure 2 reduce their legal spend. #lawfirm #KMers must start feeling this direct pressure @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    Brown: The best place 2 find a direct sense of urgency in a #lawfirm? Focus on write-offs. Written off work needs gd #KM. @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    Brown: Focus on #lawfirm and individual lawyer revenue and profit. Stop obsessing about billable hours. @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    Brown: #Lawfirm #KM should focus on bringing KM disciplines 2 pricing -- the pricing function lacks optimal data & tools. @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    @AlexHamiltonRad Is anyone or any #lawfirm close to solving this riddle?    
    
    
    Brown: #KM can help surface all the critical info that helps analyze a #lawfirm's profitability & improve partner comp. @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    @JohnGrimley @KMalexandrahall John, do you have any theories as to why this is so?    
    
    
    @JohnGrimley @KMalexandrahall But little of that technology is directed at the underlying problem w/ the #lawfirm biz model.    
    
    
    @JohnGrimley @KMalexandrahall Where's the BigTech in the #lawfirm world? If anything, there may be a dearth of good tech.    
    
    
    Brown: His advice is to follow the money. That's where #KM should focus in #lawfirms. Learn to do the math. @gnawledge #ArkKm    
    
    
    @AlexHamiltonRad @radiantlaw You're welcome! ;)    
    
    
    @JohnGrimley @KMalexandrahall Not good, but I suspect that behavior is found in other industries too. (This is not an excuse, just context.)    
    
    
    Brown: a client RFP is a waste of time unless U have an established relationship w/ client OR a serious shot at the work. @gnawledge #ArkKM    
    
    
    Terrett: The root problem is the absence of enuf accurate data in #lawfirms. (So it's hard to have sensible convos.) @andrewterrett #ArkKM    
    
    
    @JohnGrimley @KMalexandrahall Yes, and it creates some interesting opptys...    
    
    
    Keynote: Bill Henderson, Professor, Indiana Univ School of Law. Topic: Special Change Mgmt Probls Confronted by #lawfirms #ArkKM    
    
    
    Henderson quoting Max Planck: The truth never prevails. Science advances (as critics die), one funeral at a time. #ArkKM #lawfirm #LegalIT    
    
    
    Quick poll of audience: how many of yr firms believe the platform is burning? Only 1 person admits this. Others say it's caught fire. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann it's not a sure thing. But we need to work to change their mental models. They need to be educated. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Audience Poll: the Legal Industry is at the innovators/early adopters stage. There is no early majority yet. #lawfirms #ArkKM    
    
    
    Henderson: recommends several books & notes that he is astonished by how little reading lawyers do 2 improve their biz acumen. #ArkKM    
    
    
        
    
    
    Henderson: #BigLaw's current strategy is to leverage its older lawyers. However, this is not sustainable. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Henderson: If U wait until the last funeral of the older generation, U leave too much time for too many dumb biz decisions. #ArkKM #lawfirm    
    
    
    Henderson quotes Cisco: No New Golf Clubs. (New clubs don't fix the probls in yr game. You nd 2 improve yr game.) #ArkKM #lawfirm    
    
    
    Henderson: Leadership is KEY. We need #lawfirm leaders w/ vision. (Henderson points 2 Stephen Poor of Seyfarth Shaw. #ArkKM    
    
    
    My notes on Bill Henderson's Keynote: Special Change Mgmt Problems Confronted by Law Firms http://bit.ly/16i0O4f  #ArkKM #lawfirm    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt @KMHobbie Thanks, gentlemen! Sorry 4 the radio silence - I was presenting & didn't have the bandwidth 2 tweet simultaneously    
    
    
    Speakers: Joe Morford (Tucker Ellis), Lisa Chamandy (McCarthy Tetrault), @DynamicAdaptatn (McMillan). Moderator: @JoshuaFireman    
    
    
    Speakers: Joe Morford (Tucker Ellis), Lisa Chamandy (McCarthy Tetrault), @DynamicAdaptatn (McMillan). Moderator: @JoshuaFireman #ArkKM    
    
    
    Panel's advice: "Fail Forward Fast." #ArkKM    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt @ronfriedmann Re: JPMorganChase not dealing w/ law firm extranets, see Dino, Dodo, Extranet: http://bit.ly/8p0yfB  #ArkKM    
    
    
    @HackettInHouse @kim_craig You are too kind, Susan. The 3 of us could do amazing things together!    
    
    
    Chamandy: SomeXs being bold is not best way 2 drive change. SomeXs it reqs being very understated bt aware of the vibe in yr firm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Q from @ronfriedmann whether any #lawfirms celebrate failures. 4 more info on this see: Host a Failure Party http://bit.ly/Eet59  #ArkKM    
    
    
    @JBordeaux @ronfriedmann You're absolutely right, John. Developing methodology 2 ensure real learning is critical. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Overheard: when an after action review ws judged 2 B too tough by 1 of the parties involved, the #KMer ws asked 2 delete the report. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @HackettInHouse @kim_craig I'm checking my calendar NOW!    
    
    
    1. Link what U do 2 biz model & strategy; 2. Give ppl tangible experiences (see, feel, think); 3. Build coalitions @DynamicAdaptatn #ArkKM    
    
    
    What's the lawyer's 1st Q re: #innovation = Who else is doing this? Morford says we need 2 change this culture/approach! #ArkKM    
    
    
    Audience Q: How 2 sell #innovation? Chamandy: Don't sell by scaring. Address an individual pain point & convert customer 2 champion. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Look 4 positive deviants, figure out what they R doing & then hv them explain their approach 2 their colleagues. @DynamicAdaptatn #ArkKM    
    
    
    Use organizational jiu jitsu = use a person's momentum to move them 2ward #innovation. @DynamicAdaptatn #ArkKM    
    
    
    Morford: They don't force #innovation. They hv high adoption rates b/c they focus on change that improves their professional lives. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Morford: Their #KM effort is focused on mining their results 2 derive insights that govern their practice. #lawfirm #ArkKM    
    
    
    Craig: Left 2 their own devices, few lawyers change. Use the power of clients to encourage #innovation in #lawfirms. @kim_craig #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next: @ozbenamram is giving a quick live demo of Expertise Search (powered by @Recommind). Impressive, as always! #ArkKM #search    
    
    
    Q 4 @ozbenamram: Do U hv any stats on usage? A: "Of course! What kind of Q is that?" (Unfortunately, not every #lawfirm has metrics) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next speakers: Stuart Kay (Director, Global Business Systems, Baker & McKenzie) & @JoshuaFireman. Topic: No-Stakes #KM. #ArkKM    
    
    
    In this session, we are 2 generate as many great #lawfirm #KM ideas as possible. Post yr ideas via Twitter using #ArkKM hashtag. #innovation    
    
    
    Kay: I'm a great believer in pragmatic solutions that address immediate needs. #lawfim #KM #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kay: Can we put a value on #lawfirm intellectual capital? Can we charge clients 4 it? Can we report/reward knowledge contributions? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kay is speaking abt the potential of social network analysis. Border-spanners R critical 4 #innovation & knowledge sharing. #SNA #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kay: wld like 2 take 1 of his practice groups & completely reengineer their biz processes.He sees the difference automation can make. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Krakauer: move beyond giving billable hr credit 4 content contribution. Give credit only when that content is used. @pkrakaur #ArkKM    
    
    
    Billable hour credit is an inadequate incentive when staffing levels are low & lawyers are stretched with billable work. @tmlittle #ArkKM    
    
    
    Provide a report 2 the Associate Evaluation Cttee re: #KM contributions. @ozbenamram #ArkKM #lawfirm    
    
    
    Morford: in their #lawfirm they don't provide incentives 4 ppl 2 make #KM contributions. It is considered part of the lawyer's job. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kay: You need 2 recognize the ppl who make #KM contributions AND ppl who use those contributions (2 improve efficiency in @lawfirm). #ArkKM    
    
    
    Corbett: focus on eliminating the need 4 #KM contributions. Find automated ways 2 harvest content. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Fireman: #KM & #lawfirms R part of the risk mgmt industry not the legal industry. @JoshuaFireman #ArkKM    
    
    
    Fireman: Methodology for risk mgmt can be found easily in Wikipedia. Look at it & see how #KM can help. @JoshuaFireman #ArkKM    
    
    
    Fireman: Be knowledge managers. Find ways 2 use #KM to manage risk -- in #lawfirms & for clients. @JoshuaFireman #ArkKM    
    
    
    Fireman: On Seyfarth's website, w/ a credit card U can purchase guidance on the Affordable Care Act = monetize #KM. @JoshuaFireman #ArkKM    
    
    
    Andrews: An intelligent system that pushes relevant info/materials 2 ppl while they R in the flow of their work. @_Sarah_Andrews_ #ArkKM    
    
    
    Hunter: Tech 2day cn mine unstructured data 2 enhance search results automatically. Better than manual metadata tagging @thelihunter #ArkKM    
    
    
    Overheard via @pkrakaur: "Metadata is the new plastics." (Move over Mrs. Robinson!) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Despite the best efforts of @JoshuaFireman, not many members of the audience were willing 2 offer #innovations 4 consideration. Why? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next speaker: Daniel B. Rodriguez, Dean, Northwestern University School of Law. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Law schools function essentially exactly as they did 50 years ago. But the world has changed significantly since then. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: The playbook that has allowed US law schools to prosper for many years no longer works. They have priced themselves out. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: the educational model is broken, as is the relationship of law schools 2 the legal profession. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Why distance btwn law schools & the legal profession? Law schools aren't training students 2 act like 21st C. lawyers. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: ppl w/ interdisciplinary skills (law, biz, STEM fields) will rule the roost in #lawfirms. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Critical attributes for new lawyers are competency in change mgmt and a temprament to lead change. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Client demands 4 efficiency & refusal 2 pay junior associates puts huge pressure on law schools. 1/2 #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: When clients won't pay 4 junior associates, this drives lateral hiring & reduces the appeal of an expensive education 2/2 #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Clients are now focusing more on their in-house depts. So law schools R teaching skills that help grads thrive in-house. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @rightbrainlaw :) There's a world of difference...    
    
    
    Rodriguez: The 3rd rail Q is whether we R educating students 2 B successful in #lawfirms, businesses, or anywhere else. We need to. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @sinclairKM Collaboration? Or courtesy & consideration?    
    
    
    Pearson: Has Northwestern considered making its 3-year JD/MBA program its entire program? Rodriguez: Is the market ready 4 this? #ArkKM    
    
    
    See Rodriguez's post on the law-biz-tech interface: http://bit.ly/1bZ53JO  #ArkKM    
    
    
    @DustinFRobinson The judges are tough. Are you sure it will be strictly fun??? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Rodriguez: Univ of Iowa Law School = canary in the coal mine. They have reduced class size and dropped tuition by $8K. #ArkKM    
    
    
    How 2 live in a world governed by rankings/league tables? Rodriguez: Hire graduates of law schools that focus on useful #Innovation. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next: The SHARK Tank. 3 entrepreneurs will pitch #innovations to a tough panel of judges. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Morford: Be sure to read @wihender's paper on what attributes a law student needs 2 B successful in a #lawfirm. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Sharks: @Kingsley_Martin, Joe Morford (Tucker Ellis), Doug Horton (Handshake Software). #ArkKM    
    
    
    @_Sarah_Andrews_ Why are none of the "entrepreneurs" women? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Reading recommended by @Kingsley_Martin :The Art of the Start by @GuyKawasaki http://amzn.to/GSJdJD  #ArkKM    
    
    
    Entrepreneurs: Stuart Kay (Baker McKenzie), @AndrewMBaker (Seyfarth), Colleen Nihill (Dechert) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Apologies! I didn't realize that Colleen Nihill is one of the entrepreneurs. Thank goodness at least one woman is participating. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Kay's proposal: CommLease = a one-stop shop 4 legal advice 4 commercial leases relating 2 properties under $1m. #ArkKM    
    
    
    .@TCRegan_at_LR The slow action of peers creates enormous opptys for early adopters. They will laugh all the way to the bank. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt @MEKowalski @clearspire  Clearspire = a terrific exmple. There R also pockets of #innovation in sum trad'l #lawfirms #ArkKM    
    
    
    @AKKerani Unfortunately not. Chicago came to us. I'm attending a conference in NYC.    
    
    
    .@jeffrey_brandt 2 many animals! In a world of turtles, U need 2 B fastr than other turtles. If rabbits invade, the turtles R toast. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @_Sarah_Andrews_ @DynamicAdaptatn A KM "mothering" rabbit-hole? Don't fall in. You've been warned! #ArkKM    
    
    
    .@sinclairKM Black shirt, haircut, accent -- it might work. But I fear that @Kingsley_Martin is too kind to be Simon Cowell. #ArkKM    
    
    
    The Sharks are threatening 2 rip off the idea offered by 2 entrepreneurs from Seyfarth Shaw. Is this how VCs work?  #ArkKM    
    
    
        
    
    
    @TCRegan_at_LR @jeffrey_brandt Very true. Traditional #lawfirms are leaving money on the table by allowing this work to drop away. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @TCRegan_at_LR Enjoy!    
    
    
    @sinclairKM Nothing ventured, nothing gained.    
    
    
    @AndrewMBaker @RyanTilot @DustinFRobinson Thanks, Andrew. There was a gap btwn the printed program & reality. (BTW, they R doing a gr8 job!)    
    
    
    .@KMHobbie @thelihunter Thanks, David. I used those words after delivering some tough love at #ArkKM    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt @_Sarah_Andrews_ @DynamicAdaptatn Not tough love. Just tough-mindedness. #KMers need to learn how to say "no." #ArkKM    
    
    
    Next entrepreneur is Colleen Nihill, Chief Administrative Officer at @dechertllp. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @KMHobbie Until we are trending on Twitter, we haven't even begun 2 reach our potential! #ArkKM    
    
    
    Hey @rmcclead! Would you be willing to do this again? http://www.geeklawblog.com/2012/10/arkkm-asylum.html … We'd all be most appreciative! #ArkKM    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann @KMHobbie @jeffrey_brandt @highqsolutions A single platform would make the most sense. Clients should drive this. #ArkKM    
    
    
    .@rmcclead @KMHobbie Hmmm. I might need to check out an offshore alternative. (Now are you willing 2 reconsider your stance?) #ArkKM    
    
    
    .@markgould13 That's brilliant marketing by @highqsolutions. @ronfriedmann @KMHobbie @jeffrey_brandt    
    
    
    Next Session: How #lawfirm biz & practice strategies are changing in the USA, UK and Canada. Moderator: @ronfriedmann.    
    
    
    Next Session: How #lawfirm biz & practice strategies are changing in the USA, UK and Canada. Moderator: @ronfriedmann. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Speakers: @andrewterrett (Borden Ladner Gervais) and Andy Daws (@RiverviewLawUS) #ArkKM    
    
    
    Daws: If U create a #lawfirm from scratch, you can ask questions like what kind of person is best 4 a 21st C practice? #ArkKM @RiverviewLaw    
    
    
    Q 4 audience: What is driving #lawfirms to #innovation? Most firms represented at #ArkKM say "fear."    
    
    
    Morford: A key factor depressing #innovation in #lawfirms is the aging partnership. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @mattwha @ronfriedmann @KMHobbie @jeffrey_brandt @highqsolutions Would it work if you focused on one industry at a time? #ArkKM    
    
    
    Daws: There is a huge cultural gap btwn traditional #lawfirms & emerging firms such as @RiverviewLaw. 1/2 #ArkKM    
    
    
    Daws: @RiverviewLaw is looking to double its size -- thru this transition it will need to protect its unique culture. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Daws:the DNA of a trad'l #lawfirm is diffrnt than that of an emerging legal srvcs org. In the latter, #innovation is woven into DNA. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Terrett: When #lawfirm #KM started, too many #KMers focused on bldg a KM department rather than a KM culture. Big mistake. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @RiverviewLaw @sinclairKM Thanks! You had a beautiful summer in England, so you can't complain now about the weather! #ArkKM    
    
    
    @RiverviewLaw @sinclairKM Too true. I withdraw my objection. #ArkKM    
    
    
    We've just heard the conference wrap up by @JoshuaFireman. Thanks for following along via Twitter. It's been a great 2 days. #ArkKM    
    
    
    @lizamadden It was a great venue, Liza. In particular, the space lent itself to some great new programming formats. #ArkKM    
    
    
    Overheard: #KM 1.0 (creating document collections & expecting users 2 sort thru them) doesn't work. In #lawfirms U hv 2 deliver content.    
    
    
    Overheard: #KM 1.0 (creating doc collections & expecting users 2 sort thru them) doesn't work. In #lawfirms U hv 2 deliver content. #LegalKM    
    
    
    Overheard from a savvy #lawfirm partner: "The fee pressure is steady, heavy and growing all the time. It is not going away." #LegalKM    
    
    
    Terrett quoting G.B. Shaw: “The single biggest problem in communication is the illusion that it has taken place.” @andrewterrett  #LegalKM    
    
    
    Large Law Firm #KM: Meeting Our Internal Clients' Needs http://bit.ly/1a49dL5  #lawfirm #KMers #LegalIT #LegalKM    
    
    
    @vanderwal Enjoy! Sometimes it's the simple things in life that bring the most happiness.    
    
    
    Large Law Firm KM: How to Manage Legal IT Vendors http://bit.ly/1a41muZ  #lawfirm #LegalIT #LegalKM    
    
    
    @markgould13 While it was unabashedly vendor-centric, it was still instructive to hear their perspective. Next, the #lawfirm perspective…?    
    
    
    @jmccuealb @marciamarcia If it were only that easy, JIm!    
    
    
    It's a brave new world! RT @gebhardtr: Experimental Law Review Note Uses Twitter As Its Research Source http://www.lawsitesblog.com/2013/10/experimental-law-review-note-uses-twitter-research-source.html …    
    
    
    Thanks @roundtrip @sapreston @ArkGroupPubs @ronfriedmann @Business_of_Law @CarolynMWhite @CaseTrek @illanaRaia @LibMuse for the recent RTs.    
    
    
    @elsua Where are you??? (Or more accurately, where is your queue located?)    
    
    
    Thanks @LNFirmManager @BenTheCIO @GerhardPeter @JamesKleinig @Lex_connect @AnswerHub @ldamon @DiligenceEngine @pscampbell for recent RTs.    
    
    
    @elsua What a pain! Doesn't the prospect of playing the slot machines at the gate make you feel better??? ;)    
    
    
    @elsua I understand. I haven't yet spent one red cent in an LV casino.    
    
    
    @catshinners @gordonr @deb_lavoy Looking forward to seeing all of you!    
    
    
    @gordonr @deb_lavoy @catshinners How about Thursday? A group is gathering that evening.    
    
    
    @catshinners @gordonr @deb_lavoy Yes, it's the dinner @katrinapugh is organizing.    
    
    
    @elsua We're missing you and @BillIves, so @catshinners and I have gone back to the restaurant we all went to together last year.    
    
    
    Hey Luis, will your talk be live streamed or taped? I'd love to see it. @elsua    
    
    
    Mele: Technology profoundly empowers individuals. It allows opting out of the workforce. 1/3 of adults in US are self-employed. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @elsua Fabulous. Thanks, Luis. And Good Luck!    
    
    
    Mele: technology gives ppl the ability 2 take immediate & effective action. They operate at a pace that outstrips lrge institutions #KMWorld    
    
    
    Mele: With tech, this audience has amazing power. We can check his facts. We can affect sales of his books on Amazon. #kmworld    
    
    
    Mele: We need 2 combine leadership & distributed power. This means moving responsibility further down the org chart. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Mele: In order 2 create institutions that work, 1st create a culture that ensures accountability & THEN use tech 2 manage yr staff #KMWorld    
    
    
    Mele: Never b4 in US history has so much public space been privately owned: Amazon, eBay, FB, Google, Skype, Twitter.  #KMWorld    
    
    
    Mele: The new "public" institutions (FB, Twitter,Google, etc.) need to adopt a greater sense of public responsibility. #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes on Nicco Mele's Keynote: Building Collaborative Organizations http://bit.ly/16FQaro  @nicco #KMWorld #KMers    
    
    
    My notes on Kamran Khan Keynote: A Big Data Architecture for Search http://bit.ly/17b71EP  #BigData #KMWorld    
    
    
    See the Digital Workplace Trends 2013 Survey http://bit.ly/XcNUDv  by Jane McConnell #KMWorld    
    
    
    Key trends to track: BYOD, BYOPC (bring your own PC) and BYOA (bring your own app). @netjmc #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes on @netjmc's preso: Digital Workplace Trends and Transformation http://bit.ly/17MB589  #KMWorld    
    
    
    Next Session: Encouraging Knowledge-Sharing Behaviors. Speakers from US Secret Service (!) and Kent State University. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Speakers: Marion Georgieff, CKO, US Secret Service & Denise A.D. Bedford, Kent State University - Knowledge Management #KMWorld    
    
    
    Fasten your seatbelt, @jeffrey_brandt. The rest of week should produce a blitz of #KMWorld blog posts and tweets.    
    
    
    @rhappe @nicco Yes -- he gave a thought-provoking talk. A good start to the day!    
    
    
    Bedford: We need to get #KM out of the organization and out onto the streets and into society. #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    Bedford: Knowledge Scientists are concerned w/ the transformation of cities into "Knowledge Cities." #KMWorld #KMers #KM    
    
    
    .@conniecrosby That kind of open organizational culture is a huge boost for recruitment. But do enough organization's realize this? #KMWorld    
    
    
    @rhappe @nicco Actually, your worlds are just syncing up! #KMWorld    
    
    
    Knowledge Moment =a spontaneous moment when knowledge is created, nurtured & shared.These happy all the time OUTSIDE the workplace #KMWorld    
    
    
    Bedford: We need code of ethics re: info. Eg, there shld B penalties 4 stealing someone else's idea, book burning, killing an idea #KMWorld    
    
    
    Recent survey says 41% of employees use unauthorized file sharing services. #kmworld    
    
    
    Next: Expedited Learning for Smarter Orgs. Spkrs: Sandra Montanino, Goodmans LLP & Ted Graham, Director, Knowledge & Learning, PWC #KMWorld    
    
    
    .@conniecrosby Oops! Next time you'll know...    
    
    
    .@conniecrosby I know the feeling. I faithfully blogged one session but will not publish the post. The session didn't deliver the goods.    
    
    
    My Notes on Expediting Learning for Smarter Organizations http://bit.ly/HxIbDk  #KMers #KM #KMWorld    
    
    
    Thanks to @ericzigus we're hearing all about Change Agents. @ITSinsider, enquiring minds want to learn more!    
    
    
    We're in a room filled with Snowden Virgins. They are looking forward to their first @snowded session. (We are too!) #KMWorld    
    
    
    This session will discuss techniques for handling intractable problems in #KM. @snowded #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    1. Start by describing the present as accurately as possble. 2. ID what cn B changed. 3. Try it, then amplify what works. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Systems thinking works 4 simple linear processes. U can reliably ID the drivers. It won't work 4 complex adaptive problems. #KMWorld    
    
    
    See my notes from @snowded's preso at last year's #KMWorld http://bit.ly/OIOMwk  #KMers #KM    
    
    
    The idea that all hypotheses are equally valid is really bad science. @snowded (Has anyone told US journalists this?) #KMWorld    
    
    
    Start by testing each hypothesis 4 coherence. Does it make sense? Is it plausible? If so, conduct an experiment 2 test it @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Fail-safe experiments work 4 simple problems. W/ complex problems, U need 2 test coherent hypotheses by safe-to-fail experiments #KMWorld    
    
    
    All of the safe-to-fail experiments should be strictly time-limited. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    At least one safe-to-fail experiment should be oblique. See Obliquity http://amzn.to/1eXCWGS  @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    At least one safe-to-fail experiment should be naive = proposed/designed by someone who is from another field. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    There shld B contradictions among experiments: if one succeeds, another must fail. This allows U 2 eliminate hypotheses. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Interactive Exercise: Create a safe-to-fail experiment that would prove the value of #KM 2 senior managers. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    The more dissent you have, the more information participants cover & absorb. It's more effective than trying 4 consensus @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    The major problem is ppl start w/ experiments that are too big. Start w/ small projects. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Ritual dissent is a more effective way of doing strategic planning than a traditional brainstorming session. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    If U R creating a #KM strategy, don't limit it 2 #KMers. B sure biz ppl R involved.The strategy is 4 them not the KM team. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Next: Following the Curve: A Change Mgmt Strategy 4 the Digital Workplace. Spkrs: Monica Wiant, U.S. Bank & @bobpeery @MoxieSoft #KMWorld    
    
    
    “@stangarfield: In our world of innovation acceleration, you are only as good as your trusted network! #kmworld” -- NB: @ClaudiaBatten    
    
    
    Monica Wiant: "Change moves at the pace of people and at the pace of your organization." @monicawiant #KMWorld #changemanagement    
    
    
    US Bank's "US Book" is using @IBM Connections. They are phasing out #SharePoint. @monicawiant #KMWorld    
    
    
    “@ITSinsider: @VMaryAbraham @ericzigus Glad to hear, Mary!  Start by following @chagww.” /Done!    
    
    
    My Notes on Following the Curve: A Change Management Strategy for the Digital Workplace http://bit.ly/16GSzBW . #KMWorld    
    
    
    @vanderwal @gordonr @deb_lavoy @catshinners @jbordeaux Tonight is the SIKM dinner. Unfortunately, last I heard, they were over capacity.    
    
    
    Griffiths: on 8/1, the formula for GDP changed 2 make R&D a profit center. This is GREAT news 4 #KM and #KMers. @KMskunkworks #KMWorld    
    
    
    Griffiths: The most valuable knowledge affects your competitiveness. Ppl want this, but don't want 2 share it. @KMskunkworks #KMWorlds    
    
    
    Gary Bollinger: Indiana CPA Society's #KM project = how 2 leverage the knowledge of 8k members 4 the benefit of ALL members. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Griffiths: Ppl tend 2 gravitate 2wards problem solving. If you provide a forum 2 discuss problems, ppl will swarm. @KMskunkworks #KMWorld    
    
    
    @KMskunkworks That would be terrific, David. Safe travels!    
    
    
    "We need to manage the entire knowledge environment, not just the bits that are easily codified." @snowded #KMWorld #KM #KMers    
    
    
    In the Iraq, troops had no use for doctrine. They valued most blog posts from the frontline. Narrative is hugely powerful. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Exaptation: developing a capability for a specific function & then using that capability 4 a different function. @snowded #KMWorld    
    
    
    Q for @snowded: Is Exaptation another way of saying "off-label use"? #KM #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes on Jeffrey Phillips' preso: Innovation Techniques http://bit.ly/1aabvJO  @ovoinnovation #innovation #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    Thanks @jeffrey_brandt for the Pinhawk shoutout. Today is shaping up to be another whirlwind tour through #KM and related topics. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Next: @lrainie, Director, Pew Research Center's Internet Project speaking on Networked Worlds & Networked Enterprises #KMWorld    
    
    
    Pew Research Center does primary research. They are a "FACT" tank, not a think tank. @lrainie #KMWorld    
    
    
    Joseph N. Pew: "Tell the truth, and trust the people." @lrainie #KMWorld    
    
    
    "Tweckle = To abuse a speaker to Twitter followers in the audience while he/she is speaking." @lrainie #KMWorld    
    
    
    The Internet in American Life Project is what @lrainie runs at the Pew Research Center. #KMWorld    
    
    
    We lose out as a species when we reduce the likelihood of serendipitous encounters. @lrainie #KMWorld (NB: @ClaudiaBatten)    
    
    
    Information overload makes it harder to see the opportunities that lead to serendipitous encounters. @lrainie #KMWorld (NB: @ClaudiaBatten)    
    
    
    Phenomenal session on networked individuals & work by @lrainie. We could have used at least a full day w/ Lee & his data! #KMWorld    
    
    
    Here are my notes on @lrainie's superb preso: Networked Worlds & Networked Enterprises http://bit.ly/HAA7ll  #KMWorld (NB: @ClaudiaBatten)    
    
    
    Listening to @JeanneHolm speak about communities of practice and the US Government's Open Data Policy. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Listening to Jeff Slapper (MWH) and Richard McDermott speak about The Art & Science of Clever Thinking. #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes on @JeanneHolm's preso Communities for #Innovation http://bit.ly/1cZeWU9 . It's great 2 see the power of open data. #KM #KMWorld    
    
    
    @vanderwal @gordonr @deb_lavoy @catshinners Absolutely! I don't leave until the evening.    
    
    
    “@KMWorldMagazine: Congratulations @NASA on being named the winner of the KM Reality Award. #kmworld” / Congratulations @hedhj16 !!!    
    
    
    @dpontefract Absolutely. Looking forward to it!    
    
    
    @mdieterle You're most welcome, Michael. I hope you find the notes helpful.    
    
    
    My notes from @snowded's thought-provoking keynote speech: Big Data vs Human Data http://bit.ly/1aIrF00  #KM #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    O'Dell:Why do we need 2 bring Social Media inside our orgs? "It's easier 2 ride a horse in the direction it is going." #SM #socbiz #KMWorld    
    
    
    O'Dell: The holy grail 4 #KM = 2 help ppl participate AND 2 measure the impact of what our orgs do. #Bigdata helps predict impact. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @lbcook The activitation code is KMworld2013. (Case sensitive)    
    
    
    O'Dell: #Bigdata = a BIG oppty 4 #KM. We can help make sense of the "digital dust" & breadcrumbs our daily activities create. #KMWorld    
    
    
    O'Dell: APQC has a Knowledge Analytics Advanced Working Group. See info on their process: http://bit.ly/SWoSUD  #KMWorld #Kmers    
    
    
    @lbcook You're welcome!    
    
    
    O'Dell: One of the best books ever written on social media is Groundswell http://amzn.to/1acdayB  #SM #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    @DanielWRasmus One challenge is the timing of the measurement. Sometimes the value manifests much later. It's still valuable. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @elsua @gordonr We miss you!!    
    
    
    O'Dell: "Culture is key. But you change it through behaviors, not posters! #KMWorld #KM #KMers    
    
    
    O'Dell: "Knowledge is sticky. (B/c people hoard their energy & time.) Without a process, it will not flow." #KMWorld #KMers #KM    
    
    
    “@DanielWRasmus: @VMaryAbraham Absolutely-KM lives in The Serendipity Economy.  More here: http://danielwrasmus.com/welcome-to-the-serendipity-economy/ …” (@ClaudiaBatten !!)    
    
    
    @DanielWRasmus "Serendipity Economy": Great concept!    
    
    
    Jeff Veis: People are data rich, but information poor. They are making more "gut" decisions than ever before. @HPAutonomy #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    Vies quoting @Gartner_inc : 10% of workers will engage search via natural language expression (e.g, Hello Siri!) AT WORK.  #KMWorld    
    
    
    Great @IBM video shown by O'Dell: "Stop talking, start doing" to bring social media inside the org http://bit.ly/HMY2h7  #KMWorld #E20    
    
    
    You will love this example, @ClaudiaBatten http://bit.ly/HMY2h7 . Purposeful networking is the ONLY way!    
    
    
    My notes on Carla O'Dell Keynote: Transforming the Way We Collaborate http://bit.ly/1c5pjoB  #KMWorld #KMers #KM @APQC    
    
    
    My notes from @dpontefract's great preso. @TELUS has a great #collab story! http://bit.ly/19KUGpz  #e20 #socbiz #KMWorld    
    
    
    @lrainie @barrywellman Thanks for a FANTASTIC preso. We could have used a full day to discuss your data!    
    
    
    Byrne: Since #SharePoint is a platform, w/ enuf time, money and ibuprofen, you can get it to do what you need. @TonyByrne #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    Byrne: If you need a vendor comparison, see the Real Story Subway Map http://bit.ly/Xj8UWe  @TonyByrne #KMers #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes from @TonyByrne's Enterprise Collaboration Technology Market Overview http://bit.ly/1avXt26  #KMWorld    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy Perhaps now is the time to think about a virtual get together? @vanderwal @gordonr @catshinners @stangarfield    
    
    
    @conniecrosby I wish I knew this 15 minutes ago!!!    
    
    
    @conniecrosby Understood ;)  It was wishful thinking on my part.    
    
    
    Boampong: How 2 measure #innovation or innovative culture? Process metrics + outcomes metrics + staff perception of innovation #KMWorld    
    
    
    Boampong: #Innovation Process Metrics = number of ideas generated, number of ideas funded. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy @vanderwal @gordonr @catshinners @stangarfield That would be a great start! Of course, the biggest challenge is scheduling... ;)    
    
    
    Boampong: Once U collect #innovation indicators, analyze trends, ID positive actions, refine indicators, define new indicators. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Theodori: They bought #SharePoint as a #collab tool, but is it better 4 biz processes? (Is it a solution in search of a problem?) #KMWorld    
    
    
    Theodori: Where does #collaboration stop and work begin? (From an #e20 perspective, shouldn't they overlap?) #KMWorld    
    
    
    @conniecrosby  Collaboration track    
    
    
    JHAPL's #SharePoint personas: individual contributor, early adopter, team player, timid learner, pragmatic manager. #KMWorld    
    
    
    Common #SharePoint needs/frustrations: Permissions, infrequent use, getting others 2 use it, understanding the info architecture. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @conniecrosby And I was actually headed your way and changed my mind at the last minute!    
    
    
    Higgins: the most important part of their enterprise search = expertise search. It pulls data from many sources (DMS, portal, etc.) #KMWorld    
    
    
    Higgin: Measurement drives program focus & key initiatives (culture, tool, #innovation) #KMWorld    
    
    
    Stemke: It's not too long until we see this headline -- "Wisdom of crowds replacing company experts. Company IQ takes a hit!" #KMWorld    
    
    
    @jackvinson Very true. The people/processes are key here.    
    
    
    Stemke: Passive #KM = building content repositories. Active KM = effective knowledge transfer. #KMWorld    
    
    
    My notes on Jeff Stemke's preso Building Smarter Networks http://bit.ly/1aJKTSN  #KMWorld    
    
    
    Next @DanielWRasmus speaking on 10 Things #KMers Can Learn from Angry Birds. #KMWorld    
    
    
    See 10 Lessons from Angry Birds That Can Make You a Better CIO  http://bit.ly/frajFJ  @DanielWRasmus #KMWorld #legalit    
    
    
    Rasmus says he isn't a futurist-- he's an anti-futurist. Some jobs of the future: asteroid miner, time-shifting coach, etc. #KMWorld    
    
    
    See info on The Serendipity Economy http://bit.ly/IinoRk  by @DanielWRasmus #KMWorld (NB: @ClaudiaBatten !!!)    
    
    
    Rasmus: Good practice is good. Best practice means we've stopped trying. @DanielWRasmus #KMWorld #KMers    
    
    
    @LeanLawStrategy @DanielWRasmus That will keep you on your toes!    
    
    
    @ericzigus @catshinners @stangarfield @MaryMaida @gordonr @rosscavan It was great to see you at #KMWorld #FF    
    
    
    @ericzigus I wish it were smoother. This train was supposed to get to NYC at 12:10. We're stopped in Maryland rescuing a dead Acela.    
    
    
    @ericzigus What happened to your train?    
    
    
    @KatyMGeorge @lvanderkam @FastCompany The Serendipity Folder is an interesting way to address the cost of random interruptions. Thanks!    
    
    
    My Notes from @DanielWRasmus's closing keynote at #KMWorld: 10 Things #KMers Can Learn From Angry Birds http://bit.ly/18maYBu     
    
    
    @KMWorld  We need more convo abt why humans behave the way they do, & less abt why technology behaves the way it does. #KMWorld    
    
    
    @melissaomara Melissa, thanks for the retweet and for your comment on my blog. I'm glad you found the summary useful.    
    
    
    @DanielWRasmus It was my pleasure! Thanks for providing an enjoyable end to a great conference.    
    
    
    .@jeffrey_brandt Glad you enjoyed it, Jeff. Thanks for the shout-out in this morning's Pinhawk.    
    
    
    @lizamadden Thanks a million, Liza! Hope you are enjoying your new position.    
    
    
    NYC Tweeps: I'm looking 4 an indoor space 4 a brief photo shoot. Clean/simple lines & decor. City views a plus. Needs 2 B free/cheap. Ideas?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Listening to the SIKM Leaders call. Murray Jennex is speaking on Where 2 look 4 #KM Success. #kmers    
    
    
    @stangarfield Stan, does Murray have a twitter handle?
 #kmers    
    
    
    Murray Jennex is a professor, San Diego State University; Editor in chief, Int'l Journal of Knowledge Management. #KM #kmers    
    
    
    Jennex's background is in the nuclear industry. In that industry U R allowed 2 make a mistake only once. You must learn. #KM is impt. #kmers    
    
    
    This preso is part of the Int'l J of #KM's effort 2 define the KM discipline. #kmers    
    
    
    #KM's Critical Success Factors: strategy; motivation/commitment of users; integrated tech infrastructure; supportive org culture. #kmers    
    
    
    More success factors: common enterprise wide knowledge structure; senior mgmt support; learning org; clear goal/purpose 4 K sharing. #kmers    
    
    
    Success Factors: metrics 2 assess impact of sharing/use & that right K is captured; gd search, retrieval & visualization in KM system #kmers    
    
    
    Success Factors: work processes that incorporate knowledge capture & use; security/protection of knowledge. #kmers    
    
    
    KM Success is multidimensional; defined by capturing the right knowledge; getting the right K 2 the right user 2 improve performance. #kmers    
    
    
    Measure #KM success by impact on biz processes, impact on strategy, leadership & knowledge content. #kmers    
    
    
    @stangarfield Thanks, Stan! #kmers    
    
    
    Today's SIKM speaker is @murphjendss (Murray Jennex) #kmers    
    
    
    MT @jbordeaux Listening 2 SIKM Call, #KM #KMers - wondering how results would differ if we surveyed business leaders rather than KM folk.    
    
    
    #KM Impact on biz processes:improved efficiency & effectiveness; reduced cost; better ROI, decisionmaking, resource allocation. #kmers    
    
    
    Impact on #KM Strategy: revised org's KM goals,incentives 4 using/sharing K; impact on KPIs; more resources 4 KM. #kmers    
    
    
    Impact on Leadership/Mgmt Support: verbal/political support; increased awareness of, use of, reliance on, and financial support 4 #KM #kmers    
    
    
    Impact on Knowledge Content: more & better content; greater awareness of existing & needed content; gr8er demand/searching 4 content #kmers    
    
    
    Jennex's initial study created a personal productivity model 2 show where knowledge use improved individual productivity. #KM #PKM #kmers    
    
    
    How could #KM practitioners use this study? 1. Use the success factors 2 create a knowledge dashboard 4 mgmt. #kmers    
    
    
    2. Tie the measures to KPIs. #kmers    
    
    
    3. Use the measures/metrics 2 tell a better story abt #KM's value 2 mgmt & users. Better story = anecdote + numerical evidence. #kmers    
    
    
    Balancing knowledge sharing w/ security is a BIG challenge- especially if IT wants zero risk & therefore wants 2 lock everything down #kmers    
    
    
    As editor of a #KM journal he sees young academics looking 4 new areas, without acknowledging their area is an extension of KM. #kmers    
    
    
    The key is that new #KM work should walk the talk: reuse the best of the work that has already been done. @murphjendss #kmers    
    
    
    Knowledge doesn't flow thru the org chart, it flows thru the underlying network that ppl rely on 2 get things done. @murphjendss #KM #socbiz    
    
    
    #socbiz is not merely abt new tools or channels. It's also abt new behaviors that enable better knowledge sharing. @jbordeaux #KM #kmers    
    
    
    @stangarfield Thanks very much, Stan!    
    
    
    “@KMHobbie: Always love planning stuff with @VMaryAbraham @ronfriedmann and @ozbenamram | Great team!    
    
    
    @PamelaRyckman @ClaudiaBatten @alelariu "Dancing with Anxiety." What a great concept! It's up there with #DeliberateDiscomfort    
    
    
    @LangeStudio It was such a pleasure to work with you yesterday! I left the session so impressed by your creativity and good humor.Thank you!    
    
    
    Female & Male brains are wired differently. @alelariu and @ClaudiaBatten here's more fodder 4 preso http://bit.ly/18mSfWX . H/t @milouness    
    
    
    BUT "if U take away the pressure of societal expectations, gender differences in cognitive skills R reduced or disappear" @alelariu    
    
    
    2013 Most Admired Knowledge Enterprises Awards http://www.knowledgebusiness.com/knowledgebusiness/Templates/ReadKnowledgeLibrary.aspx?siteId=1&menuItemId=33&contentHeaderId=7704 … #km #kmers    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt It's embarrassing! Big Accountjng is there, as is Big Consulting. But no #BigLaw. In fact, no #lawfirm of any size! #LegalKM    
    
    
    In Miami this week to do a deep dive into #km with #LexMundi. Looking forward to meeting folks from these #lawfirms. #kmers    
    
    
    I'll be presenting some related sessions on #innovation for #lawfirms. Hope to spark lots of convo & learning. #kmers    
    
    
    Mike Roster, co-chair of ACC's Value Challenge Steering Cttee is talking abt the inherent tensions of  the #lawfirm biz model #LexMundi #KM    
    
    
    Bill Turner,CKO of Womble Carlyle:Changing the pricing model changes the biz model. (#lawfirms need 2 be prepared.) #LexMundi #LegalKM #KM    
    
    
    Mike Roster, co-chair of ACC's Value Challenge Steering Cttee is talking abt the inherent tensions of the #lawfirm biz model #LexMundi #KM    
    
    
    Turner:many #lawfirms operate less like a business & more like a small town. Managing partner = mayor. Initiatives require votes. #LexMundi    
    
    
    Next: I'm speaking on "Finding and Keeping the #Innovation Edge." We'll be looking at how 2 help lawyers & #lawfirms innovate. #LexMundi    
    
    
    @TurnerTweeting Great to meet you today, Bill. I look forward to more convo with you abt making #lawfirms more effective.    
    
    
    @ClaudiaBatten You're too kind! Can we work together??? ;) #lovemyteam    
    
    
    Listening 2 Lucy Dillon (Berwin Leighton Paisner) talk about the changing role of professional support lawyers. #lawfirm #legalKM #LexMundi    
    
    
    Dillon:PSL is a terrible title. In her #lawfirm, they R called "Knowledge Development Lawyers." They R responsible 4 R&D. #LexMundi #legalKM    
    
    
    Dillon: It's hard 2 implement process improvement unless the partner in charge acknowledges there is a need 2 increase efficiency. #LexMundi    
    
    
    Impact of #KM on Old & New Business Models http://bit.ly/1eZNB6a  H/t @TurnerTweeting and Mike Roster. #LexMundi #LegalKM    
    
    
    People-based #KM: the Role of the Professional Support Lawyer http://bit.ly/18bCgQJ  H/t Lucy Dillon #LexMundi #LegalKM    
    
    
    Components of Effective Legal Project Management http://bit.ly/1hAswm7   H/t Lucy Dillon #LexMundi #LegalKM    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy Congratulations, Deb!    
    
    
    Meredith Aiello: #KM is more than just the technology. To quote Anonymous: "A fool w/ a tool is still a fool." #LexMundi #KMers    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy Excellent. Adventures are good for us! #BoldIsBetter    
    
    
    “@ValaAfshar: Big data is set to change small businesses http://s.hbr.org/1aDmBnL ” || Are #lawfirms ready? #LegalIT    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann Actually, I'm listening now to @ozolincomments talking abt #lawfirm opportunities in #BigData & why #KM shld care. #LexMundi    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann Very true! The mid-term monitoring & course correction can save time & money. Can't wait for after action review.    
    
    
    A 2012 HBR study says fewer than 44% of employees say they know where 2 find the info they need 4 their work @ozolincomments #LexMundi    
    
    
    @ronfriedmann @ozolincomments HOWEVER, the @ACCinhouse Value Challenge expert here is making a gr8 case 4 the client interest in #DoLessLaw    
    
    
    Hearing abt a challenge 2 #lawfirm librarians: They can't just gather data. They now hv 2 analyze it & hv an opinion on it. @ozolincomments    
    
    
    @andrewtrickett Thanks very much, Andrew!    
    
    
    So looking forward to @alelariu's talk today at @TEDxBrooklyn. Break a leg, Ale!    
    
    
    Santa's Brand Book: http://bit.ly/1cqxEW2 . A hilarious sendup. Enjoy! @alelariu @ClaudiaBatten    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy Imagine being trapped in the air w/ someone who won't stop talking on the phone??? Amtrak's Quiet Car is looking mighty fine!    
    
    
    @tibbr @webtechman Thanks! Can you resend the link? The original link didn't work.    
    
    
    @josecarloskm @stephendale @QEDGroup @bloomfire Thanks so much. Great infographic!    
    
    
    “@FastCompany: How the most productive people grow their network while still getting it all done: http://f-st.co/gDuy4Cx ” @broadli    
    
    
    @tibbr @webtechman Not a problem. Just let me know when it's ready to go.    
    
    
    Looking forward to hearing @NancyMDixon speaking on #KM: where has it been & where is it going?  #kmers    
    
    
    Here are the slides for @NancyMDixon's preso http://www.slideshare.net/SIKM/km-3-eras-nancy-dixon-slides … #kmers    
    
    
    The 3 Eras of #KM by @NancyMDixon http://bit.ly/1dK4ccA  #kmers    
    
    
    Before the 1990s, we assumed that training was the key, no need 4 special #KM focus. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Peter Drucker caused orgs 2 focus on the value of knowledge. This led 2 focus on #KM. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Initial #KM focus = connecting ppl 2 content (doc collections, databases, etc.)  @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Initial gains of #KM = standardized practices, reduced duplicated effort. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    BUT, not many orgs achieved these benefits. Result? Prevailing view that #KM doesn't work as billed. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    This led 2 a shift in #KM's focus from explicit knowledge 2 tacit knowledge. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    New focus of #KM = leveraging experience (tacit knowledge). Connecting ppl 2 ppl. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Another shift was 2 move from spreading mgmt know-how 2 leveraging experience of frontline workers. @NancyMDixo  #kmers    
    
    
    Leveraging experiential knowledge led to 23-28% gains in productivity & reduced silos. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    BUT we had only been moving knowledge laterally (at the frontlines), not vertically. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    And, we were dealing only w/ existing knowledge. Insufficient attn on creating knowledge. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    AND, we tended 2 focus on tactical knowledge (how-tos), rather than strategic knowledge. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    New ways of thinnking abt knowledge: leaders convene convos, but shldnt try 2 control their content/outcomes. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Why shld mgmt step back? B/c there is no single person/grp that has all the answers 2 the hard problems orgs face. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    To solve the really hard problems, orgs need to convene diverse groups and convos. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Another reason mgmt steps back: frontline workers hv special insights into probls facing their org. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Ron Heifetz: the power of leaders does not lie in inventing solutions, but in using their authority 2 convene convos. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    Collective sensemaking = a convo in which participants intentionally use their varied perspectives 2 make sense of an issue.  #kmers    
    
    
    Enhanced search capability has helped provide quick resources for the 1st 2 levels of #KM. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    How has the role of #kmers changed? In 1st era of #KM, focus on collecting, vetting, providing knowledge. @NancyMDixon    
    
    
    In 2nd era of #KM: focus on tacit knowledge - how 2 share it, how 2 connect ppl 2 ppl. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    In 3rd era of #KM: convene diverse grps 4 convo, find ways 2 develop/create knowledge, collective sensemaking. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    As we moved from focus on documents 2 experience, it became harder to quantify value #KM. (It's easy 2 count documents in a db.)  #kmers    
    
    
    One of the challenges of the newer types of #KM is how 2 make the creation of knowledge transparent. @catshinners #owork #kmers    
    
    
    Al Simard: Start w/ understanding the biz you're in. What R the biz processes? How does the #KM effort support these? #kmers    
    
    
    Linda Hummel: Where shld an org starting a new #KM program begin? #kmers    
    
    
    Just filling a db with info is meaningless. #KM needs 2 manage the flow of knowledge from the db 2 address the biz needs. #kmers    
    
    
    Manufacturng/regulated biz may need 2 start w/ 1st era of #KM. A creative org, shld start 2/ 2nd era. #kmers    
    
    
    Al Simard: no matter where U start yr #KM effort, u need 2 cover all 3 eras so U hv a strong foundation 4 biz growth. #kmers    
    
    
    How 2 balance #owork w/ enough time 4 reflection/sensemaking? @NancyWhite #KM #kmers    
    
    
    2nd Era of #KM is helpful 4 #owork. 3rd Era is helpful 4 reflection/integration. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    We need to oscillate between our independent virtual work AND coming 2gether 2 reflect. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    How do we put into our asynchronous online discussions the kind of behaviors we want 2 see in f2f discussions? @KatrinaPugh #kmers    
    
    
    Our virtual online convos often are just a series of declarations NOT a true convo. @NancyMDixon #kmers    
    
    
    A TRUE convo is when we build upon each other's contributions. @NancyMDixon #kmers #KM    
    
    
    @NancyWhite Unfortunately, popular media do not model the best behaviors for healthy discourse. #kmers    
    
    
    .@NancyWhite Perhaps we just need to remind ourselves periodically that courtesy is an impt part of convo. #KM #kmers    
    
    
    @rotkapchen Thanks, Paula! #kmers    
    
    
    @jbordeaux Can you you tell me more?    
    
    
    @mneff You're absolutely right. The challenge is in moving from those pockets of energy to the wider organization. #KM #KMers    
    
    
    @jbordeaux It's not crashing. You're always more than welcome!    
    
    
    @jbordeaux Outcome metrics are key. But can be hard if you haven't already established a baseline and isolated the variables.    
    
    
    @josecarloskm Thanks for this. I'm looking forward to reading it. However, I'm a little under the gun right now. What's your timeframe?    
    
    
    12 Business Books to Read in 2014 by @AdamMGrant http://linkd.in/1baAiuT  | Read one each month! @broadli    
    
    
    When Technologists are Challenged by Technology http://bit.ly/1cVDgtR   -- WiFi challenges reduced today's conference tweet stream #ILTA13    
    
    
    @robsaccone My pleasure. Thanks, Rob!    
    
    
    @planty Thanks, Jason. We'll try to do better tomorrow.    
    
    
    @johngillies You are too kind, John! Thanks so much for participating in the session.    
    
    
    Alternative Billing: What's Working and What's Not http://bit.ly/12krKRS  @KMHobbie's notes on #IDPG #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hallelujah! The WiFi is back.  Kudos to #ILTAs Clay Gibney and team. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Co-chair Skip Lohmeyer is introducing Rohit Talwar (Interviewed by Monica Bay). Topic: Law 2020 Emerging Biz & Tech opptys #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Rohit Talwar is the founder of fast future research. He is leading the #ILTA future tech project. He has #law firm clients. #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Rohit Talwar is a good sport! He is doing a great job of dealing with a small tech hiccough.  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Talwar on aging populations: How do you motivate an 190-year old network manager?  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Talwar: what's the extended human life span going to do to marriage? (You get shorter sentences for double murder!)  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    See "23 and me" -- it's website that can compare yr genetic profile w/ others. It will show how yr genetics affect yr daily choices.   #KEY2    
    
    
    Talwar: Airports are getting vertical farms. See O'hare. #key2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Keynote: Rohit Talwar – Law 2020: Emerging Business and Technology Opportunities http://bit.ly/181cwjC  #KEY2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Listening to Tracey Smith as she leads #KMers and technologists in the art of storytelling. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @johngillies Science of storytelling: Broca's brain translates meaning. It stimulates every other part of brain affected. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Smith: Storytelling induces a sense of safety. That's why they show movies on an airplane. #KMPG2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    #Storytelling to Transform Your #KM Projects, Strategy and Culture http://bit.ly/14YTU8U  #KPMG2 #ILTA13 #KMers    
    
    
    Ginevra Saylor is singing the praises of "stealth #KM." Finding ways 2 incorporate KM into other functions. #KMPG3 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal 2 keys to #BigData - analytics & dark data (what's piled up in a room & you hv no idea what it is) - Galina #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal Galina Datskovsky - #BigData 4 most firms means keep everything 4ever. Need policies 4  mining & disposition. #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT @InsideLegal It's maddening that we R still discuss'g how 2 gt attys 2 put info in CRM. #BigData can save CRM-Blain Banick #SPEC9 #ILTA13    
    
    
    KM in Support of Firm Operations http://bit.ly/170VDGO  #KMPG3 #ILTA13    
    
    
    MT “@tgnbibr: Quick poll of audience ranks 75% of firms R getting by, 24% failing & only 1% have visionary leadership. #SPEC16 #ILTA13”    
    
    
    MT “@tgnbibr: If you start defining your strategic goals within budgetary constraints, you’re already stuck in the box. #SPEC16 #ILTA13”    
    
    
    Bryan Cave focuses budget convos on (1) what has 2 B done & (2) what can we do that would make a real difference to the firm? #ORG7 #ilta13    
    
    
    Grok the Grid (Susskind's): matrix = External <--> Internal; Technology <--> Knowledge/Action #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman: The strategic opptys are client-facing. However, you have 2 master the internal projects since they R foundational. #org7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow What evidence did the panelists cite?    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow Stories like this raise huge barriers to entry for younger women, Who wants to live this way? #Misc2 #ILTA13    
    
    
    “@ShirleyCrow: #MISC2 #ILTA13 Networking: find out who your really excellent peers are and watch and follow them.” // Start w/ #ILTA    
    
    
    The path 2 strategic thinking, 2 differentiating your firm is NOT through the Sheep Pasture. (Sheep are blind followers.) #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman: Just b/c someone else did it does not necessarily make it useful 4 you & your firm. You need to think strategically. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @johnalber cautions against a "consumerist approach" to IT = "Now that I have a budget, what shall I buy??" #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: what decisions in the biz process most affect profitability? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: what info is necessary for optimal decision making? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Ask: What information presentation & location is optimal for effective decision making? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow Thanks a million, Shirley and @TimGolden. I so appreciate your participation in the session & your kind words. #SPEC16 #ILTA13    
    
    
    How 2 make a direct connection to the profits of the firm? Focus on client-facing projects. @JohnAlber #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Citing @ronfriedmann's Do Less Law #ILTA talk, @michaelmillsny suggests that we do less IT. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Testing a new idea: Can you tie it to a measure currently in use by the firm? Are there metrics that matter? #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Hoffman is explaining Bryan Cave's proprietary "octagon" = 8 metrics by which they measure EVERYTHING -- ppl, projects, etc. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @tgnbibr You are extravagantly kind, Ted! Thank you.    
    
    
    @VQab Thanks so much for attending and tweeting the session, Ann! #SPEC16 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Bryan Cave is cost-conscious & careful, bt their overwhelming preference is 2 focus on moving the needle on the revenue side. #ORG7 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Technologists who just happen to be attorneys -- that's how @AndrewMBaker describes most of his team. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Don't waste time creating documentation no one will read. Focus yr energy on creating real value 4 clients. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Why scrum? Speed allows U 2 stay on the cutting edge; projects R more complex & hard 2 plan 4.  @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    The @seyfarthshawLLP legal #innovation group is a "small development shop inside a #lawfirm". @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    For speedy wireframes, @seyfarthshawLLP  uses @balsamiqNext to help bring a concept 2 life. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    "User stories" = basis 4 a develop't project. They define who, what & why (biz value). Also a "definition of `doneness.'" #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    With over 1400 user stories, @seyfarthshawLLP always focuses on prioritizing & possibly combining projects. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @KMHobbie Curious. What are they saying about task codes & profitability analysis? Or is the problem that they are not saying anything?    
    
    
    @tgnbibr Does this means they do the first calculation on the basis of time and then adjust?    
    
    
    Soriano: Scrum is about fostering a sustainable pace 2 produce a good quality of work. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    They have a 15-minute daily status meeting on the projects - held standing up in front of their scrum board. Good communication btwn teams.    
    
    
    Moving from the old waterfall method 2 agile scrum is totally worth it, but isn't w/o challenges. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano: The developers love the new transparency that scrum provides. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Scrum has enabled even better communication between the developers & the legal innovations team. @AndrewMBaker #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @KMHobbie Interesting. Is a new methodology emerging? #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano:The @seyfarthshawLLP intranet looks NOTHING like #SharePoint b/c they have a brilliant in-house designer. #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Soriano: They have integrated Google calendar & Outlook with their SeyfarthLink extranets. @seyfarthshawLLP #INFO11 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow  Thanks for the clarification, Shirley. It was a provocative claim. #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ShirleyCrow I agree. It's important for junior women that senior women frame a more sustainable and sane path to success. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Serious cool #ILTA13 session. We're attending Using Virtual-World Technology in the Real World #SPEC14. We have presenters IRL & via avatar.    
    
    
    Presenters: Col. Scott Reid (CKO, USJAG), Dr. Paulette Robinson (Nat'l Defense University), Randy Hinriche (CEO, 2b3d)  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    This preso is being given simultaneously to #ILTA13 and the Serious Play Conference http://bit.ly/i6BljQ  #SPEC14    
    
    
    We R taking a virtual tour of the second life facility. It has configurable spaces & can incorporate biz apps & cloud tools. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    A room can be configured to create a permanent "war room" w/ all the legal resources/files U need 4 the matter. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    You cn reconfigure conference space w/ a couple clicks of mouse. No need 2 call hotel staff 4 extra chairs! @TJJohnsonILTA #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Virtual world conferences R more engaging. U feel present & experience what your avatar experiences. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Contrast this great sense of engagement w/ the continuous partial attention typical of webinars where everyone multitasks. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life has serious healthcare uses. See Snow World, which helps children w/ burns. http://slate.me/yjW9Tz  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life for business purposes is an emerging technology NOT a bleeding edge technology. (Would #LegalIT agree?) #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    2nd life has challenges w/ security & identity. However, these issues also exist IRL. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    We're about to see a rehearsal for a litigator preparing for a trial. It happens in a 2nd life courtroom. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: U have 2 make a personal investment 2 become "fluent" in any new technology. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    How did they create the 2nd life courtroom? It took their graphics designer 2 hrs after receiving a picture of a court. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    We're watching Scott Reid maneuver around the virtual courtroom 2 learn where 2 stand, how 2 move in IRL. Gr8 prep 4 court. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    A litigator can practice the blocking, flow & choreography necessary 4 a good courtroom preso. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    As in sports, you can visualize every step of the experience, so when U face it IRL, U know how 2 respond fluidly. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: we typically react 2 others in IRL based appearance, personality, etc. How will we react 2 each other's avatars? #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Since avatars can provide a little distance from volatile emotions. Wld 2nd Life B useful 4 resolving family law matters? #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    One audience member suggested that the US & Iranian governments should be negotiating via Second Life. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @StephKimbro Thanks for the feedback. Would love 2 hear more about your experience. #ILTA13    
    
    
    Second Life has been used to help veterans with post traumatic stress http://1.usa.gov/132Bhz6  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Microsoft will soon B providing the means for users 2 move easily between IRL & the virtual world from their office apps. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Now meeting Dr. Don Workman on the PTSD Island. It is an immersive 3D enviro 2 provide PTSD resources. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Correction: PTSD Island is 4 active-duty personnel & their families, not veterans. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Watching T2 Virtual PTSD Experience http://t2health.org/vwproj  #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    This virtual PTSD experience makes key resources available to military personnel who might not otherwise seek help IRL. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Military personnel can visit the PTSD Experience using an anonymous avatar, so they protect confidentiality. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @rightbrainlaw @StephKimbro Agreed. As the technology improves, the opportunities expand. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Now that you mention it, there is a striking resemblance! ;)    
    
    
    @GameOnLaw @StephKimbro Fair point. I hope the technology improves sufficiently 2 lower barriers 2 entry. Perhaps widespread gaming will too    
    
    
    The PTSD Experience includes #gamification elements to provide feedback 2 the user. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @ldamon It was great to see you across the room during the @seyfarthshawLLP preso for the #ILTA13 Most Innovative #lawfirm award. Congrats!    
    
    
    One thrill for sci-fi fans: the presenters have been moving around their virtual world by teleporting. Cool! #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    From inception to beta of PTSD Island was abt 6 months. That's impressive speed! #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    Reid: DARPA brought us the internet and is bringing us these great virtual world applications. It's the future. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    The avatars ended the 2nd Life preso Gangnam Style. Lots of fun & lots of learning in this session. Thanks, Col.Scott Reid. #SPEC14 #ILTA13    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Glad we were able to wave at each other. Sorry we didn't have a chance to chat.    
    
    
    @jeffrey_brandt Unfortunately not. I'm seated in 19A and about to depart.    
    
    
    @rmcclead @KMHobbie @johngillies @bren924 @tangledom @highqsolutions It was my pleasure, Ryan. It was great 2 see all of you.    
    
    
    @KatyMGeorge So glad to connect here. Welcome to the Twittersphere!    
    
    
    Keynote: Chris DeSantis – The Crucible of Experience as a Catalyst for Leading #ILTA13 http://bit.ly/14TAJYd  (Contains excellent advice)    
    
    
    Thank YOU, Jeff!! MT @jeffrey_brandt: RT They forgot @VMaryAbraham & @HackettInHouse: 25 women 2 follow on Twitter. http://www.fastcompany.com/3016225/dialed/25-of-the-smartest-women-on-twitter …    
    
    
    Chris DeSantis – The Crucible of Experience as a Catalyst for Leading #ILTA13 http://bit.ly/14TAJYd  (Contains excellent advice) #mgmt    
    
    
    Back at @Columbia University's Information & Knowledge Strategy Masters program. Glad to help teach new #KMers. #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    First session is on Strategy taught by Guy St. Clair (@smr_knowledge) and Kate Pugh (@katrinapugh), academic director of program #IKNS    
    
    
    1st Qs: Where do we compete? How do we win? How do we sustain our competitive advantage? #IKNS    
    
    
    Start by clarifying the client's vision, most fundamental goals. Then consider Michael Porter's 5 forces.  #IKNS    
    
    
    Here's a link to Michael Porter's Five Forces Analysis http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Porter_five_forces_analysis … #IKNS    
    
    
    @siftonpark (from @Microsoft) says us that we shldn't hv 2 leave our work 2 be social. We shld B able 2 B social in our work apps #e20 #IKNS    
    
    
    Listening to Susan Baktis (@Accenture) speaking on topic: "Technology isn't the answer, but it can help lead the way." #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: Sharing happens around a topic, around content, around people. You need to facilitate all of these. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They track extensive "transaction #metrics" on activity in their #e20 platform. It's harder to measure the value of content #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They try 2 help direct ppl 2 other other useful content by showing "more like" and Amazon-like suggestions. #IKNS    
    
    
    @pygkno @Columbia Hi there! Hope you're enjoying the residency.    
    
    
    Baktis: They are looking 4 new ways 2 help ppl find content w/o having to email a request 2 everyone. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: @Accenture is using a proprietary algorithm 2 power their content recommendation engine #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: The more data you have, the better the results from the recommendation engine. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They have simplified the "#SharePoint form. Instead, they created a little app 4 contributing content. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They also enabled contribution by email. They have a batch job that processes email attachments & adds them 2 #SharePoint #IKNS    
    
    
    Will do. Are the #IKns tweets appearing together w/ the tweets under #IKNS?    
    
    
    @mrs_wynn Just checked -- both tags are consolidated. You can use either #IKnS or    
    
    
    Baktis: SME (subject-matter experts) are expected 2 contribute content in their areas. It's part of their performance evaluation. #IKNS    
    
    
    Q from class: How 2 manage info overload via social activity streams? What if you miss something impt? A: FILTERS! #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They R exploring #gamification 2 help improve participation & 2 provide feedback 2 users. #IKNS    
    
    
    If you are interested, here is a quick overview of #gamification I wrote earlier this year: http://bit.ly/WPUii8  #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: Just as technology is not the complete answer, neither is #gamification. Use it help ppl learn or become more engaged. #IKNS    
    
    
    Here is more info on @Accenture's use of #gamification 2 improve knowledge sharing http://bit.ly/XSvXqJ  #KMers #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: @Accenture is using tools from @Badgeville 2 add #gamification 2 their #SharePoint platform. #IKNS    
    
    
    Baktis: They use @Wordpress to enable blogging in their #SharePoint environment. #IKNS    
    
    
    Next speaker: Tom Stewart (@BoozCompany) on Taking Knowledge to Market." #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If you are speaking 2 biz folks, it's impt that U use the language of money. #KMers #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: a good #KM system helps a knowledge worker answer the Q: what do I need 2 do 2day & how do I do it? #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: We can sell knowledge as a product. That's what @Accenture and @BoozCompany do. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Over time, the price of commodities declines, while the value of knowledge assets grows. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: The internet increases competition. In an online world, a reasonable substitute is just a click away. (Big strategic issue.) #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart cites stats that show that only 48% of executives believe that their strategies (that they wrote!) will succeed. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart's stats also show that 2/3 of executives believe they have too many conflicting priorities. This impedes strategic direction. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Don't settle for strategy on the margins. Demand strategy that matters. Key focus = how do we create value for our clients? #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: recommends 'Putting Leadership Back into Strategy" by Cynthia Montgomery http://bit.ly/17oEB5K  #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: What do we sell that is unique & valuable? Ask yr clients: why do you buy from us & not the other guy? #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Knowledge assets take inputs & transform them into something more valuable. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Differentiation lies in your knowledge assets: human capital, structural capital, relationship capital. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Customers don't buy human, structural or relationship capital. They buy what you do 4 them. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Create a competitive advantage based on what U know (knowledge assets) & what U do well (execution). #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Once U know how 2 differentiate your firm, U then need a clear way 2 play the game 2 win. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: looking at @Apple's Form 10-K. Their #strategy = to create the best #UX thru 6 specific capabilities.  #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: R&D is incredibly concentrated. 1000 companies account for 48% of all R&D spending. #Innovation #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: tech leader #strategy; fast follower strategy; needs seeker strategy (responding 2 customer needs early). 1/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: Each of these strategies requires different types of knowledge assets & knowledge #strategy. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a tech leader, who is my best friend? Scientists @ a great university. I put my lab next 2 them. #strategy #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a market reader/fast follower, who is most impt? My CFO, it's all about operations & guaranteed return. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: If I'm a Needs Seeker, who's most impt? My CMO = the person who understands clients the best. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: As #KMers, it's impt 2 think 1st abt the type of #strategy yr firm is pursuing. Then ID the key knowledge assets 2 manage. #IKNS    
    
    
    @ValdisKrebs Yes -- those are wrapped up in your Human Capital.    
    
    
    “@jordan_law21: "If something cannot go on forever, it will stop." Stein's Law. |But it might linger too long on life support    
    
    
    Stewart: #KM needs 2 b like Janus. One face looks 2 the market 2 understand clients better; the other face understands internal needs. #IKNS    
    
    
    Stewart: "Ideas are capital. Everything else is just money." #Innovation #strategy #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    “@OPENForum: The right way to ask for a coffee meeting: http://bit.ly/19ObvPi ” | @ClaudiaBatten -- this is an improvement.    
    
    
    “@ValdisKrebs: @VMaryAbraham ...and how they work together, learn, share, and grow knowledge is all about social capital! || BIngo!
#IKNS”    
    
    
    Next speaker is Bob Libbey, @Pfizer's Head of Digital & Social Communications #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey's topic: The Digital Communications Battle for User Attention  = A fight that's sure to grow. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: Communications is an arm of #KM. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: we started by "telling & selling." Now it's about engagement. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: we used to just put content out & hope 4 the best. Now we use targeted #metrics 2 plan & track our work. #IKNS    
    
    
    LIbbey: The competition in the content realm is tough. It's very hard 2 get ppl's attention. How 2 induce repeat traffic 2 yr site? #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: quoting EU survey that shows 1/3 of respondents say that their smartphone is their main source of digital content. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: In digital communications, don't confuse the means with the end. (Don't focus on an #FB or #Twitter strategy.) #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: How employees spend their time online? According to one study, 60-80% is "cyberloafing." You hv 2 compete for this attention. #IKNS    
    
    
    Libbey: Self-syndication was key 4 @ESPN and works 4 @Pfizer as well. Create gr8 content & then push it out thru a variety of channels #IKNS    
    
    
    @zeapen How can this be a good thing? Wasn't that study revolutionary?    
    
    
    @miunger @sklososky Thanks for your kind words, Mark. I had good material to work with!    
    
    
    @ClaudiaBatten @nilofer @OPENForum That makes sense when U have beautiful mountains all around you. The scenery isn't quite the same in NYC    
    
    
    @ClaudiaBatten @nilofer @OPENForum Ha! How you're talking!!!    
    
    
    #ILTA13 - The tides are turning - HighQ http://highq.com/ilta13-the-tides-are-turning/ …    
    
    
    Harris: significant companies are hugely data driven -- Disney, P&G, Netflix, Progressive Insurance Company, etc. #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: Companies that build a good analytics capability can use that to stay one (or more) steps ahead of the competition. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: 60% of respondents to a recent survey say their organization lacks the skills needed 2 leverage #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris quotes @tdav who says that "a lot of #BigData is low analytics." Some major insights from data may B missed in the media hype. #IKNS    
    
    
    MT @jamesdavidsaul "Embedding analytics into core biz processes creates sustainable competitive advantage." - Jeanne Harris, Accenture #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris: One challenge is that a significant number of decision makers in orgs are essentially innumerate. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    Harris; Lack of trust [in data] remains the #1 barrier to the widespread adoption and impact of analytics. #BigData #IKNS    
    
    
    @VQab Thanks so much 4 including my materials in yr overview. Honored 2 B in such good company @jordan_law21 @HackettInHouse @ronfriedmann    
    
    
    Sad but true! RT @mloxton: @VMaryAbraham heck, most firms lack even rudimentary data skills even for #littledata, never mind #bigdata    
    
    
    Does the compensation model of your org reward a "we" focus or "me" focus? This will affect your #KM program. @KatrinaPugh #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    Pagani: Ppl see themselves as the center of their network OR as participants in a lot of networks. This colors their action & yr #KM #IKNS    
    
    
    Pagani: There R many paths 2 a good #KM outcome. Start by understanding the person U R helping. Put them at the center. #IKNS    
    
    
    @orgnet @ValdisKrebs Thanks 4 the RT & the link 2 yr article. Stay tuned -- the next session is Practices of the 21st C. Learning Org #IKNS    
    
    
    @orgnet It's entirely my pleasure. Thanks for participating via Twitter. @ValdisKrebs #IKNS    
    
    
    Next Session: @KatrinaPugh is speaking on Practices of a 21st Century Learning Organization. #KMers #IKNS    
    
    
    It helps when ppl in the org can think about issues in other "frames" besides their own. @KatrinaPugh #IKNS    
    
    
    A vast number of arguments arise from ppl looking at different (& incomplete) data. Ladder of Inference analysis can help avoid this. #IKNS    
    
    
    Argyris: If you've had a convo go south recently, review it 2 identify what was going on in your head during the convo. 1/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Argyris: How did your focus (distraction/subtext) affect the convo? 2/2 #IKNS    
    
    
    Jeanne Harris: How High Performers Compete – and Win – with Analytics http://bit.ly/15znsU4  @Columbia #IKNS #KMers #KM #BigData    
    
    
    Recovering from ILTA 2013 http://www.geeklawblog.com/2013/09/recovering-from-ilta-2013.html … /by @rmcclead #ILTA13 #lawfirm #legalIT    
    
    
    MT @ronfriedmann: Can We See Scale & Experience Benefits in Law Practice? http://bit.ly/15wy8ns  //Ron raises sobering questions 4 #lawfirms    
    
    
    How will Amazon MatchBook upend the publishing industry? http://amzn.to/17nLaTS  It certainly strengthens brand loyalty 2 Amazon.    
    
    
    @newroccindy @legalerswelcome  I'd be happy to help, Cindy. Just let me know where and when. Thanks!    
    
    
    @legalerswelcome Glad this is starting up again, Natalie.    
    
    
    @deb_lavoy My pleasure, Deb. Hope all is well with you.    
    
    
    @KMHobbie @ronfriedmann Subcontracting works in other industries. Why not in legal too? Better 50 local experts than 1 over-stretched firm.    
    
    
    @LegalTypist  Thanks so much, Andea!    
    
    
    @LawTechLegalIT Thanks very much. I'll send DM with details.    
    
    
    Attending the Legal IT Forum at beautiful Hanbury Manor in England. #LIFT13    
    
    
    RT'd w/ correct hashtag: Attending the Legal IT Forum in beautiful Hanbury Manor in England. #LITF13    
    
    
    Keynote is by Mark Stevenson, a futurologist talking about the Future and What To Do About it.  http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mark_Stevenson … #LITF13    
    
    
    A huge added benefit this morning = Mark Stevenson is a bona fide comedian as well as a gr8 guide 2 the future. Challenging info + laughs    
    
    
    Stevenson: Talking about a "carbon-neutral oil refinery." Mind boggling. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: the Thingiverse has tons of downloadable prototypes available 4 immediate 3D printing. What will this do 2 manufacturing? #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Nanoscribe is a technology 2 watch. With nanoscribe, you can 3D print a 3D printer. Bye Bye manufacturing!  #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Why aren't people adopting the newer/better ideas? They R surrounded by "idea-proof fences." #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: How to handle the shift from the digital revolution to the future? Start w/ optimistic, ambitious goals. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Definition of happiness? Find something bigger than you are and devote your life to it. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Keep smashing yourself into new ideas. Stay curious. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: make sure your org is spending to engineer serendipity. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: You are what you do, not what you intend to do. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Making mistakes is ok. Not trying is irresponsible. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: The first mistake is a learning opportunity. A repeated mistake is incompetence. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Think like an engineer, not a politician. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Play the long game. (Inevitably, the early rounds will be failures.) #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson quotes the writer of The Sopranos: The road 2 success is littered w/ corpses. Most are suicides. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Cynicism is the ultimate enemy of the future. So police your own cynicism. #LITF13    
    
    
    Stevenson: Be defined not by what you own, but by what you create. #LITF13    
    
    
    “@JoannaMG22: @LegalITForum #LITF13 following @VMaryAbraham for great live tweeting #legalit” // Thanks, Joanna.    
    
    
    Stevenson: Every technology is dual use = it can be used for good or evil. We need 2 B part of steering it in a positive direction. #LITF13    
    
    
    Next: Derek Southall, Janet Day & Neil Cameron speaking about the delivery gap btwn what we hv & what our clients need. #LITF13    
    
    
    @BenWightwick Just until tomorrow, unfortunately. I've got another speaking gig next week in NYC.    
    
    
    Southall: Most IT products R for the general market.They need to be customized heavily 2 work in the legal sector. This is the gap.  #LITF13    
    
    
    