When all else fails, it's #pinterest time! http://pinterest.com/pnhart/pins/     
    
    
    @AlliWorthington torn between top left and right.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/133898048/  Amazing read!    
    
    
    @sweettoothfairy your chocolate peanut butter cc made my night! Thanks for sharing your amazingness.    
    
    
    Trying this!  DIY Beauty: Make Your Own Lip Balm http://pulse.me/s/1jeIc     
    
    
    How is it that my gaydar can be so intuitive and my crazydar so totally obtuse?    
    
    
    I just downloaded one of 100+ free HTML email templates from http://campaignmonitor.com/templates/     
    
    
    Thank heaven my stupid-dar is fully functioning    
    
    
    Sweet!  Build Your Own Grid-It Tech Organizer in a Vintage Book [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1kqU2     
    
    
    Style Syllabus: Cheap Tricks For An Uncommonly Cool Common Room http://pulse.me/s/1kjMI     
    
    
    @chipwade i am a total newbie and learn as you go gal with my dremel, I'm wondering about polishing and texturizing some leather-ideas?    
    
    
    i am a total newbie and learn as you go gal with my dremel, I'm wondering about polishing and texturizing some leather-ideas? #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @dremel thx--I have the 75th ann. LE from costco--which should i pick up next?    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy my biggest problem using the tool is it gets really hot while i'm working. Am i in need of a larger tool?    
    
    
    brilliant RT @momsworkbench: Just went on the website and noticed the Pumpkin Carving kit - now that's a way to a DIY mom's heart #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @barbarakirk #dremeldiy I do it all the time--works great with metals too, and cutting leather--Love my dremel!    
    
    
    #dremeldiy I want to set up a flex shaft workstation for my jewelry/costume making. If I can only get one, which tool would be best?    
    
    
    @dremel leather cosplay helmet #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @barbarakirk #dremeldiy I like instructables.com and searching youtube and there's a bunch on dremel.com    
    
    
    r u kidding--diy is how i relax--i luv it!RT @repurposedlife:so right! RT @asliceofwood: @ChipWade there is no time for relaxing #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy craft & diy equally    
    
    
    #dremeldiy my dremel makes me feel like I know what I'm doing, even if I'm faking it! lol    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy electrical-but I'm working on it. . .    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy q3 had to think--i would take advantage of an expert and get a personal tutorial on all my projects. . lol    
    
    
    @ChipWade #dremeldiy fixing and repurposing for sure!    
    
    
    Totally doable!! The Fold-Away Treadmill Workspace [Featured Workspace] http://pulse.me/s/1lKWc     
    
    
    5 Ways to Turn Happiness Into An Advantage http://m.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-happiness-advantage/201108/5-ways-turn-happiness-advantage?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews,http://pulse.me …    
    
    
    Sneak in These Simple Exercises at the Office to Stay Healthy [Health] http://pulse.me/s/1lk5s     
    
    
    PhotoLive for Chrome Downloads Your Facebook Photos for Easy Migration [Chrome Extensions] http://pulse.me/s/1l7tf     
    
    
    Want!! Olympus PEN E-PM1 Mini gets a $500 price tag, September release date http://www.engadget.com/2011/08/25/olympus-pen-e-pm1-mini-gets-a-500-price-tag-september-release/ … via @engadget    
    
    
    WANT!!  Wacom’s Inkling Captures What You Draw On Paper Digitally (Amazing Video) http://pulse.me/s/1pZDO     
    
    
    Star Wars Crafts: Bonnie Burton http://pulse.me/s/1pn42     
    
    
    Tutorial: Tree Pillow with heart-shaped leaves http://pulse.me/s/1pIwa     
    
    
    Gratitude Card made with Purple Cows CraftGeek tools  ;): http://re.pn/aczwn    
    
    
    One of my favorites! http://pinterest.com/pin/150755937/  Gratitude Card made with Purple Cows CraftGeek tools  ;)    
    
    
    Path.to Helps You Create a Professional Profile and Get Noticed [Webapps] http://pulse.me/s/1qyLv     
    
    
    Hoot Turns Facebook into a Study Hall and Project Collaboration App [Webapps] http://pulse.me/s/1qmvE     
    
    
    This is brill!!  Add Used Tea Bags to the Bottom of Planters to Feed Plants [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/1qinX     
    
    
    I’ve created my profile at about.me! Check me out: http://about.me/pnhart  and sign up at http://about.me .    
    
    
    Handmade Vellum Wedding Card http://pulse.me/s/1rkHs     
    
    
    Great idea--Bug-Away Paper Cup Covers http://pulse.me/s/1rwcj     
    
    
    Craft Product Review: Craft Geek “Roll It” Texture Tool by Purple Cows http://pulse.me/s/1spFe     
    
    
    Vote for me to be the face of @aboutdotme on a Times Square billboard: http://about.me/pnhart     
    
    
    HOW TO: Follow New York Fashion Week Online http://pulse.me/s/1wSXv     
    
    
    A Piece of Lisa: About My Camera http://lisaedoff.blogspot.com/2011/08/about-my-camera.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Tatting! http://needlework.craftgossip.com/recent-tatting-tutorials/2011/09/05/?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews,http://pulse.me …    
    
    
    Recipe: Snickerdoodle Pumpkin Ice Cream Sandwiches http://pulse.me/s/1xozc     
    
    
    Getting ready for a segment on KUTV 2news fresh living segment today--sharing the purplecows & scrapbookusaexpo    
    
    
    Left brain/Right Brain http://pinterest.com/pin/186332950/  I love these ads!    
    
    
    left brain/right brain passion: http://re.pn/cCTXW    
    
    
    The "Introduction to Arduino" Comic Makes It Easy to Get Started with Electronics Hacking [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1DUK1     
    
    
    Avoid hot spots when burning the candle at both ends!    
    
    
    Fabby! http://www.makeandtakes.com/school-lunches-ideas-and-a-free-printable …    
    
    
    @PopArtMinis how in the world do you do it, girl? Keeping up with a day job and brilliantly creating your own stuff? It's killing me!    
    
    
    My @Klout score is 36. I improved it by 4 points over the past  30 days! http://klout.com/user/pnhart/score-analysis?n=tw&v=daily_welcome …    
    
    
    Cigar Box Fiddles by Xylocopa Design http://pulse.me/s/1MC85     
    
    
    Fall Decorating Inspirations {Weddings} http://pulse.me/s/1MaHY     
    
    
    Love this!  Tutorial: Pretty pintucked skirt http://pulse.me/s/1LUvo     
    
    
    Fab post! RT %40CraftTestDummy Cutting Fabric with Sizzix Framelits Dies %7C Craft Test Dummies http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2FqZ5o2a    
    
    
    @sarahndipitous At the end of the day sometimes the underside is more beautiful    
    
    
    Me time is now over--let the day begin-dammit    
    
    
    Looking for a new camera--something between point&shoot basic and dslr.  Suggestions?    
    
    
    sewing 101: electronics sleeve http://pulse.me/s/1MSJK     
    
    
    diy project: leather envelope phone case http://pulse.me/s/1MQjQ     
    
    
    Star Wars AT-AT Walker Pancakes http://pulse.me/s/1N55v     
    
    
    Parent/teacher conf w/B*rod -so far so good.    
    
    
    Seriously? I know you can breastfeed anywhere--but jr hi parent teacher conferences? Science teacher is sweating    
    
    
    Poor guy--all the teachers in the gym-parents waiting in line. Very funny reactions all around    
    
    
    @starmile83 I watched zuckerberg introduce it today--looks interesting!    
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy thinking about it sorta wears me out ;)    
    
    
    @starmile83 you can. That's one of the great features is how you can customize it and add info and photos to fill in    
    
    
    @starmile83 @jimmersallstars my bro is there!!    
    
    
    @WendySparrow sweet pea fo sho    
    
    
    Social Network Faceoff: Facebook vs. Twitter vs. Google+ [Lifehacker Faceoff] http://pulse.me/s/1OgLD     
    
    
    Make Your Own RFID Shielded Wallet To Foil ID Thieves [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1NWfc     
    
    
    Freebie | Harmony in Autumn Printable http://pulse.me/s/1Rspj     
    
    
    You Want Dishcloths? I Got Your Dishcloths! http://pulse.me/s/1RcKs     
    
    
    Stunning! Inspiration: Hearty Craft http://pulse.me/s/1QWfv     
    
    
    OMG!-- New Sizzix and Vintaj DecoEmboss Folders and DecoEtch Dies http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fsNCagVhpDA&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    My name is Paula, and I'm a Mean Mother http://nblo.gs/nDdUq     
    
    
    My name is Paula, and I'm a Mean Mother http://nblo.gs/nDdZm     
    
    
    How-To: Make a Spider Loom for Lace http://pulse.me/s/1RX1p     
    
    
    Open Hardware Silver Pendant http://pulse.me/s/1Sc31     
    
    
    Inspiration: Vintage scissors as decor http://pulse.me/s/1SjYV     
    
    
    It's true, I'm a mean mom! http://hartofthemountain.blogspot.com/2011/09/my-name-is-paula-and-im-mean-mother.html …    
    
    
    Recreating Iconic Scenes with Legos http://pulse.me/s/1TkgE     
    
    
    DIY Capacitive Touch Brush Stylus http://pulse.me/s/1TGaF     
    
    
    Step Up Your Fall Swagger: Half-Off 60+ Jeffrey Campbell Stunners! http://pulse.me/s/1OiWS     
    
    
    diy project: vintage-style book dustcovers http://pulse.me/s/1TSs2     
    
    
    How-To: Fall Handbag with Fabric Flowers http://pulse.me/s/1U2EO     
    
    
    Salsa! And Free Canning Labels http://pulse.me/s/1UzKj     
    
    
    Flip Over a Muffin Tin to Make Delicious Ready-to-Fill Cookie Bowls [Food Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/1W0uG     
    
    
    Bunker App Is a Super Simple Project Tracker and Invoice Generator for Freelancers [Web Apps] http://pulse.me/s/1Vfun     
    
    
    Gigantic, Creeptastic Lego Victorian http://pulse.me/s/1VcHF     
    
    
    .: In the beginning... http://thesewingedwords.blogspot.com/2011/09/in-beginning.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    It's Friday, it's Friday ...(now doing a little dance!)    
    
    
    #ldsconf tuned in late-Where's Pres Monson?    
    
    
    @michael_crook thanks    
    
    
    @SisterDiane I can relate    
    
    
    'Arrested Development' Returning To TV http://pulse.me/s/1Ynsy     
    
    
    Halloween Party Ideas http://pulse.me/s/1YgII     
    
    
    Flaming Foliage Candleholders http://pulse.me/s/1YLNr     
    
    
    Heading to the Martha Stewart Show (again!) for Craft Week http://pulse.me/s/1YDKM     
    
    
    Tote from Trash Bag http://pulse.me/s/1ZkrC     
    
    
    Math Monday: Flexible Stick Structures http://pulse.me/s/1ZfMq     
    
    
    Color in the Kitchen: Kitchen Bars that Pop! http://pulse.me/s/1ZkoC     
    
    
    Tips & Tricks | Using Patterned Paper http://pulse.me/s/1ZR8v     
    
    
    Sew in Love {Wooden Spools + Weddings} http://pulse.me/s/1ZvnF     
    
    
    Super Simple Cards with Terri O http://lnkd.in/9G2rDH     
    
    
    living in: far from heaven http://pulse.me/s/20kXH     
    
    
    Pantone Christmas Ball Ornaments http://pulse.me/s/20djs     
    
    
    InBook iPhone Charging Docks http://pulse.me/s/1Zi4W     
    
    
    Zero to Maker: CNC Class Comes Full Circle http://pulse.me/s/20Ja3     
    
    
    Want this!! Volkswagen Buggy Up Concept http://pulse.me/s/20bqI     
    
    
    Another Beautiful Alexander McQueen Show Walks in Paris http://pulse.me/s/20Fsl     
    
    
    DIY Wedding Emergency Kit http://pulse.me/s/23etn     
    
    
    Antiquaria Rubber Stamp Wedding Invitations http://pulse.me/s/236jh     
    
    
    DIY Paper Flower Centerpieces http://pulse.me/s/23aBT     
    
    
    A pendant with a secret http://pulse.me/s/25MRN     
    
    
    Ditching DRM could reduce piracy, prices, inconvenience http://pulse.me/s/265Y0     
    
    
    Look at This Incredible $2,300, 30,000 Brick Lego Imperial Hangar [Lego] http://pulse.me/s/25Rif     
    
    
    Autumnal http://pulse.me/s/25qev     
    
    
    trook http://pulse.me/s/26s8a     
    
    
    How-To: Glow in The Dark Corset T-Shirt http://pulse.me/s/268q0     
    
    
    iPhone 4 Passive Amplifier Case http://pulse.me/s/27B9l     
    
    
    Project: Dye Your Own Yarn, Naturally http://pulse.me/s/26LmI     
    
    
    How-To: Felt Vintage-Style Christmas Baubles http://pulse.me/s/26Dnl     
    
    
    Apple-Cranberry Pocket Pies | Williams-Sonoma http://pulse.me/s/27EGk     
    
    
    Inspiration: Clock gears and cogs mandala http://pulse.me/s/278Ns     
    
    
    New Apple Software Adds Features to Older Phones http://pulse.me/s/299iD     
    
    
    Stock Up on Peanut Butter Now Before Prices Get Ridiculous [Saving Money] http://pulse.me/s/274DS     
    
    
    PhotoFast iFlashDrive now available to pre-order in US and UK http://pulse.me/s/2a7Xl     
    
    
    Autumn Bird's Nest Fascinator http://pulse.me/s/28Mt4     
    
    
    @kosairnurse first dye it with gold dye with @ritdye then get some gold floral spray (like spray paint, but flexible) and spray it    
    
    
    @kosairnurse you could also try the glitter spray after dying it. What kind of fabric is the dress?    
    
    
    @kosairnurse I LOVE the dr who idea!!!    
    
    
    Getting ready for a day on the show floor at Sourhern women's show in Orlando- @CraftyChica is in booth behind us-gonna be a blast!    
    
    
    Start Something New with Sharpie http://pulse.me/s/2c722     
    
    
    Candle Chandelier Tutorial http://pulse.me/s/2c5mD     
    
    
    Tutorial: Sturdy, semi-see-through templates for quilting, sewing and applique http://pulse.me/s/2buYW     
    
    
    100 Years of Fashion in Under Two Minutes http://pulse.me/s/2bCpE     
    
    
    How-To: Weave a Hula Hoop Rug http://pulse.me/s/2e4Nr     
    
    
    Free pattern and tute: Matryoshka ornament http://pulse.me/s/2iwNR     
    
    
    Tip: Get Better Artwork Photos http://pulse.me/s/2hVqP     
    
    
    A close look at pateh http://pulse.me/s/2mJnu     
    
    
    How Science Can Teach You to Easily Spot a Liar [Video] http://pulse.me/s/2n4LF     
    
    
    How to Fix Internet Embarrassments and Improve Your Online Reputation [How To] http://pulse.me/s/2mhrd     
    
    
    The Do’s And Don’ts Of Infographic Design http://pulse.me/s/2dzlj     
    
    
    Glitzy Lucite Bangle http://pulse.me/s/2nsIf     
    
    
    Brill: How-To: Make a Sewn Leaf Garland http://pulse.me/s/2mNUA     
    
    
    Tip: Printing on Ribbon http://pulse.me/s/2pj6b     
    
    
    Eye candy alert: Dimensional flowers http://pulse.me/s/2p26s     
    
    
    Store Appliances in Old Pillowcases to Avoid Dust Buildup [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2pnQg     
    
    
    How-To: Make a Robot Halloween Costume http://pulse.me/s/2pa2O     
    
    
    Stunning Lace Spider Webs http://pulse.me/s/2oXjs     
    
    
    Steampunk Controller is all Brass and Burl http://pulse.me/s/2p1zS     
    
    
    Score! One red-ish puffy vest for Marty McFly. #Halloween    
    
    
    @SUEDEsays lmk if the google image search works-good luck!    
    
    
    @thehumming_bird luv ur guts!!!    
    
    
    @thehumming_bird and seriously--you aren't following me?  Wat up wid dat?    
    
    
    Interesting perspective. http://lnkd.in/qg82dc     
    
    
    What a great idea--Hoop Storage Bags http://pulse.me/s/2rtdm     
    
    
    This New Trojan Disables Your Mac's Auto-Updates [Malware] http://pulse.me/s/2rlKX     
    
    
    TieSight Instructs You in the Art of Constructing Cravats [Mac Apps] http://pulse.me/s/2rck2     
    
    
        
    
    
    Relieve Headaches with Hot Peppers [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2qTc2     
    
    
    Can watching Twitter trends help predict the future? http://pulse.me/s/2qTW2     
    
    
    Designing for Autism: Lighting | ArchDaily http://www.archdaily.com/?p=177293     
    
    
    Maybe in the studio .... Effektiv cabinet concrete hack http://pulse.me/s/2qAPM     
    
    
    Amazing! Will try today! How-To: Autumn Leaf Bouquet http://pulse.me/s/2qmfy     
    
    
    Proper Business Attire Working Group http://pulse.me/s/2pAyY     
    
    
    Lytro's new light field camera lets you focus after you take a picture http://pulse.me/s/2ss0A     
    
    
    Remove Tough, Greasy Stains from Clothing with Coca Cola [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2s9Oq     
    
    
    How-to: cross-stitched cell phone case http://pulse.me/s/2ssAF     
    
    
    How-To: Longboard Deck From Popsicle Sticks http://pulse.me/s/2slGN     
    
    
    Apple Manager Breaks Rule, Makes 10-Year-Old Girl's Dreams Come True http://pulse.me/s/2rLWz     
    
    
    Day 19: Work on a Hobby You Love #30DaysofGOOD http://pulse.me/s/2qaDS     
    
    
    Meet the New Digital Public Library of America http://pulse.me/s/2tfsc     
    
    
    John Fluevog Needs Crafters! http://pulse.me/s/2tJ5u     
    
    
    Brilliant!  http://content.photojojo.com/diy/make-your-own-scanner-camera/ … via @photojojo    
    
    
    Etched Victorian Pumpkins http://pulse.me/s/2ucNn     
    
    
    Lil’ People Birthday Chart http://pulse.me/s/2tyxF     
    
    
    Under the Influence: Steampunk and Neo-Victorian Fashion http://pulse.me/s/2txLy     
    
    
    Just installed @waze on my #iPhone - it's a free navigation app with fun gaming & social elements! http://bit.ly/WazeHomePage     
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy it's a gift and a curse.    
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy I am so glad I'm not the only one! If there were only another 10 hours in a day!    
    
    
    Just munched a @waze '' road goodie worth 3 points!    
    
    
    How Recruiters Use Social Networks to Screen Candidates [INFOGRAPHIC] http://pulse.me/s/2vWZu     
    
    
    Great commentary on the term makers http://pulse.me/s/2vGaI     
    
    
    Making a Virserum look expensive http://pulse.me/s/2vDBb     
    
    
    How-To: Homemade Candy Corn http://pulse.me/s/2w2gd     
    
    
    Freebie: Owl Lover Calendar 2012 http://pulse.me/s/2wk57     
    
    
    Weapon of Ice Destruction: A Snowball Launching Crossbow [Tools] http://pulse.me/s/2wxta     
    
    
    The Single Cord Workspace [Featured Workspace] http://pulse.me/s/2wx7h     
    
    
    Protect Your Car from Halloween Tricksters with a Fresh Coat of Wax [Security] http://pulse.me/s/2xbQV     
    
    
    All Star Animators Recreate the Entire Ocean Online http://pulse.me/s/2xaZe     
    
    
    Freebie: Organic Vector Elements in EPS (80 Vector Files) http://pulse.me/s/2xXoJ     
    
    
    Felt Leaf Garland Tutorial http://pulse.me/s/2xhZS  flour? Who knew?    
    
    
    ideacious: support creators http://pulse.me/s/2wNUI  just what I was looking for!    
    
    
    Things People Make http://pulse.me/s/2xW3q     
    
    
    Circus Costumes from the 50s http://pulse.me/s/2x9w0  I wanna quit my day job & make these full time!    
    
    
    Made by Hand: Now in Paperback http://feedproxy.google.com/~r/makezineonline/~3/Q7rQJheqh6o/made-by-hand-now-in-paperbak.html …    
    
    
    How To Declutter Your Home http://pulse.me/s/2yoEy     
    
    
    How to make a Totoro cookie cutter / food shaper | Anna The Red http://pulse.me/s/2zr5F     
    
    
    Getting to know you…5,4,3,2,1 things http://pulse.me/s/2yUar     
    
    
    I need to grow thicker skin!    
    
    
    Soften Itchy Wool Clothing with Hair Conditioner [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2AcRP     
    
    
    iPad CF and SD Card Readers Make Transferring Photos to iOS a Snap [Stuff We Like] http://pulse.me/s/2A4uP     
    
    
    diy project: wool camera wrap http://pulse.me/s/2AmMD  this is fabulous!!    
    
    
    Cat Eye Eyeliner How-To http://pulse.me/s/2AeVC     
    
    
    How-To: U-Shaped Handle Purse http://pulse.me/s/2zB6Y     
    
    
    AT-AT Dog Is Awesome http://pulse.me/s/2AaYv     
    
    
    Pac-Man Cookie Cutters http://pulse.me/s/2AOGG     
    
    
    Craft Product Review: Purple Cows Melt Tool http://pulse.me/s/2APrA     
    
    
    Project: Witches Broom Treat Bag http://pulse.me/s/2BthQ     
    
    
    The BurdaStyle Designer's Guide: An Entrepreneurial Path http://pulse.me/s/2BkrB     
    
    
    Codecademy Raises $2.5 Million To Teach You How To Code http://pulse.me/s/2BFJu     
    
    
    How to Add Movie-Quality Special Effects Makeup to Your Halloween Costume [Video] http://pulse.me/s/2Bhdj     
    
    
    before & after: funky desk makeover http://pulse.me/s/2ATZW     
    
    
    Hanging Ornament Pattern Fabrics http://pulse.me/s/2BuPI     
    
    
    Make a Fog Machine for Your Party for $5 [Video] http://pulse.me/s/2DAZu     
    
    
    Understanding why a crazy block works http://pulse.me/s/2F3LK     
    
    
    Tutorial: Fabric labels from pantry supplies http://pulse.me/s/2EFqG     
    
    
    @kosairnurse fabulous!!!    
    
    
    Invent a collection http://pulse.me/s/2FTz5     
    
    
    Brain Workout Part I http://pulse.me/s/2GcU2     
    
    
    Quickly Break in a New Pair of Shoes with Rubbing Alcohol [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2GkCy     
    
    
    How to Be Your Own Therapist and Solve the More Manageable Problems in Your Life [Video] http://pulse.me/s/2FWfa     
    
    
    Third Person Effect: an excerpt from You Are Not So Smart http://pulse.me/s/2Gm9y     
    
    
    Tweephone is a rotary phone Twitter client, even your grandma could love http://pulse.me/s/2JNse     
    
    
    2011 design*sponge scholarship! http://pulse.me/s/2IYVQ     
    
    
    @thehumming_bird I'm up for it. Especially w/snow in the forecast! Xoxoxo    
    
    
    Freebie: Organic Vector Elements in EPS (80 Vector Files) http://pulse.me/s/2xXoJ     
    
    
    Improving The Customer Experience: Meet The Problem Users http://pulse.me/s/2J6Op     
    
    
    diy project: salvaged barnwood headboard http://www.designsponge.com/2011/11/diy-project-salvaged-barnwood-headboard.html …    
    
    
    helen friel http://pulse.me/s/2LgbW     
    
    
    Woodland Home http://pulse.me/s/2Mr31     
    
    
    Zen and the Art of Making http://pulse.me/s/2LXW8     
    
    
    Freebie | Printable Tags http://pulse.me/s/2NsZW     
    
    
    Repurposed Shutter Magazine Rack http://pulse.me/s/2LMos     
    
    
    Make Your Own Whipped Cream Using Coconut Milk for a Longer Lasting Topping [Food Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/2Os2U     
    
    
    Free pattern: Scrappy house ornament http://pulse.me/s/2S8zH     
    
    
    My bro-in-laws new show  -- Knights of Mayhem http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YaoOML9fSgE&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    The Rise Of Pinterest And The Shift From Search To Discovery http://pulse.me/s/2Uc8R     
    
    
    Customize Your Crayola http://pulse.me/s/2SUEN     
    
    
    Printable Bias Tape Maker http://pulse.me/s/2S7Y2     
    
    
    Festive Thanksgiving Printable http://pulse.me/s/2VBwc     
    
    
    Faux Mercury Glass Tutorial http://pulse.me/s/2UQXB     
    
    
    Shutter Side Table http://pulse.me/s/2UPDl     
    
    
    Doing this today! RT @CraftTestDummy Make Your Own Washi Tape with the Xyron | Craft Test Dummies http://bit.ly/vHlfKN     
    
    
    Texas Instruments and Brookstone debut iPhone Pocket Projector case http://pulse.me/s/2Wtsf     
    
    
    caran d’ache neon pens http://pulse.me/s/2WMpE     
    
    
    Lovely lace jewelry holder http://pulse.me/s/2XxV4     
    
    
    Printable Snowman Candy Bar Wrappers http://pulse.me/s/2WKDS     
    
    
    Beer Bottle Chandelier http://pulse.me/s/2WskQ     
    
    
    The droid nobody was looking for: an R2-D2 MP4 player http://pulse.me/s/2Zsow     
    
    
    Writing WordPress Guides For The Advanced Beginner http://pulse.me/s/2ZxKW     
    
    
    How to Make (and Sustain) a Good First Impression Every Time [Social Gps] http://pulse.me/s/2Y6va     
    
    
    Printable Iron Man Shoelace Covers http://pulse.me/s/2YAGf     
    
    
    See the new Making Spot http://pulse.me/s/2ZMid     
    
    
    @CraftyChica fab!!    
    
    
    @pulsepad check @pinterest check. Now I can tackle the day!    
    
    
    Can 3D Printers Make Libraries Useful Again? [Libraries] http://pulse.me/s/31gEl     
    
    
    Jedi Mind Tricks: 17 Lesser Known Ways to Persuade People (169 points) http://pulse.me/s/30C22     
    
    
    Lifestyle Portraits of Stormtrooper Toys http://pulse.me/s/2VDeY     
    
    
    Graceful Kelly Bag Pattern From U*Handbag http://pulse.me/s/30EG5     
    
    
    Freebie | Printable Fall Subway Art http://pulse.me/s/31HNY     
    
    
    Freebie | Printable Holiday Organizer http://pulse.me/s/31CPg     
    
    
    Getting these for gifts! (&me) RT %40CraftTestDummy Smash Book by K %26 Company %7C Craft Test Dummies http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2FrZDMVh    
    
    
    @sarahndipitous Lucky--I just got-son (13) "mom, this is not gratuitous violence, it's just a lot of blood. Jeez." very loud with a growl.    
    
    
    Darn--time to get the day in gear and strap on my purple persona--catch me at @purplecowscre8 for my 8-5+ yammerings    
    
    
    ChocoKebabs Are the Only Reason I Need To Move To Italy [Foodmodo] http://pulse.me/s/332Sv     
    
    
    This is a great, quick read.  Medieval marketing http://pulse.me/s/32xz9     
    
    
    Yea!!! The Stanza Ereader is Back, Now with iOS 5 Compatibility [Updates] http://pulse.me/s/32Dnf     
    
    
    Wow! before & after: chair redo with screen-printed fabric http://pulse.me/s/32Vo5     
    
    
    Free embroidery pattern: Christmas reindeer http://pulse.me/s/33DsO  #craft    
    
    
    Book Page Bird Ornament http://pulse.me/s/388hW     
    
    
    Snowglobe Cookies http://pulse.me/s/38dok     
    
    
    Magnetic Spice Jars http://pulse.me/s/37ufD     
    
    
    Adorable!!! Tutorial: Fabric gift boxes http://pulse.me/s/37GUS     
    
    
    Amazing Star Wars Cookies From Holiday Cookie Cutters http://pulse.me/s/368mF     
    
    
    The 6 pillars of Steve Jobs' design philosophy http://pulse.me/s/35PsY     
    
    
    Repurpose a Suit Coat into a Laptop Bag [Repurpose] http://pulse.me/s/37Mxg     
    
    
    Flower power bottles http://pulse.me/s/357Ti     
    
    
    How-To: Mini Silk Screens http://pulse.me/s/345JM     
    
    
    DIY Star Wars Snowflakes | Matters of Grey http://mattersofgrey.com/diy-star-wars-snowflakes/ … via @mattersofgrey    
    
    
    Button Bracelet -really cute idea http://re.pn/AAy73     
    
    
    Use a Vinyl Decal to Screen Print Your Own Designs for Super Cheap [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/38Tsd     
    
    
    Google announces 'opt-out' feature for wireless network owners, aims to allay privacy concerns http://pulse.me/s/3aFS5     
    
    
    German museum recreates 130-year-old EV, looks like a steampunk Segway http://pulse.me/s/3a74B     
    
    
    sneak peek: annie coggan & caleb crawford http://pulse.me/s/3a8Si     
    
    
    Guest Post: Christmas Candle Chandelier http://pulse.me/s/3aNsg     
    
    
    Felt-applique hoops for holiday decorating http://pulse.me/s/3aKta     
    
    
    Me too! RT @Bobbi_Jean: Right about now #craftsocial    
    
    
    Every year I have good intentions to start early, but alas. . . .  #craftsocial    
    
    
    We started a homemade Christmas tradition a couple of years ago w/the fam--all gifts exchanges had to be made #craftsocial    
    
    
    agreed! @mmpmuskie: @SisterDiane There are definately some that dont get handmade gifts....dont appreciate them #craftsocial    
    
    
    balancing expectations is my biggest downfall for the next few weeks
 #craftsocial    
    
    
    @penguintrax My 13yo son makes jewelry for his sisters out of legos (with help from dad)  #craftsocial    
    
    
    @NeverPlainJanie reality is I would love to give only handmade-but with only 24 hrs in a day. . .  #craftsocial    
    
    
    @sandbar17 it's still "handmade" #craftsocial    
    
    
    Me2RT @CrochetLibFront @LionBrandYarn @Bobbi_Jean Doing handmade for the holidays helps me not get ovrwhlmd w/the consumerism #craftsocial    
    
    
    @niftyfoodie love the inspiration and "education" i get using pinterest. New techniques abound! #craftsocial    
    
    
    @bcre8uv I love this too, but realized when i gave my kids "craft kits" it was usually stuff i wanted. . didn't go over well. #craftsocial    
    
    
    Type2Phone Turns Your Mac into a Bluetooth Keyboard for Your Smartphone [Mac Downloads] http://pulse.me/s/3bKMJ     
    
    
    http://lifehacker.com/5859758/learn-from-elites-consolidate-your-most-important-work-hours-into-distinct-periods … #productivity    
    
    
    Getting Started With bbPress http://pulse.me/s/3cKKu     
    
    
    Ordering this book today! wildwood http://pulse.me/s/3aSmj     
    
    
    Pattern: Becoming Jane Sweater http://pulse.me/s/3bUn8     
    
    
    Project: Rustic Woodland Candleholders http://blog.craftzine.com/archive/2011/11/project_rustic_woodland_candle.html … via @craft    
    
    
    Self-Assembling Objects – at Home http://blog.makezine.com/archive/2011/11/self-assembling-objects-at-home.html … via @make    
    
    
    Inspiration: Veronica Fuentes · Needlework News | http://CraftGossip.com  http://needlework.craftgossip.com/inspiration-veronica-fuentes/2011/11/16/ …    
    
    
    Bag your floss · Needlework News | http://CraftGossip.com  http://needlework.craftgossip.com/bag-your-floss/2011/11/15/ …    
    
    
    Huge disagreement--please help me out by taking one side or the other. http://purplecows.net/blog/art-or-craft-you-decide/ … #frustration    
    
    
    "fighting mad!!"    
    
    
    @dawndsokol love those days!    
    
    
    I have been on Twitter for 2 Years, 8 Months, 4 Weeks, 20 Hours. http://www.howlonghavei.com  #howlonghaveibeenontwitter    
    
    
    @kosairnurse Since it's an ugly argument between me and a company sales rep, I don't want to say until we get some feedback.    
    
    
    @kosairnurse your answer is great--I need everybody's gut reaction!! Thx for posting!    
    
    
    Scrollbar of Contents Adds Clickable Headers Next to the Scrollbar for Navigating Long Articles [Chrome Extensions] http://pulse.me/s/3eQrx     
    
    
    Fix slippery heels-- #lifehacker http://lifehacker.com/5860050/fix-slippery-heels-with-a-diy-cloth-insert …    
    
    
    Meta Lego Storage « Kellbot! http://www.kellbot.com/2010/06/meta-lego-storage/ …    
    
    
    Can ‘Serendipity’ Be a Business Model? Consider Twitter | Epicenter | http://Wired.com  http://pulse.me/s/3eU4p     
    
    
    peter pan collars by polli http://pulse.me/s/3dd2W     
    
    
    Laser-Cut Enclosure Features Sweet Bends http://blog.makezine.com/archive/2011/11/laser-cut-enclosure-features-sweet-bends.html … via @make    
    
    
    Generative Construction Toy http://pulse.me/s/3cKcI     
    
    
    Foam Board Cabinet Tutorial · Indie Crafts | http://CraftGossip.com  http://indiecrafts.craftgossip.com/2011/11/17/foam-board-cabinet-tutorial/ …    
    
    
    Just in time! http://pinterest.com/pin/550764741/  Laminated leaf table settings!    
    
    
    perfect activity with kids http://pinterest.com/pin/550790561/  free printable Nativity set    
    
    
    Make it tonight Sew Sweet Sewing Kit  http://www.purplecows.net/makeprojects/sew-sweet-sewing-kit/ …    
    
    
    Now I'm pinning my heart http://pinterest.com/pin/550907182/  Mixed media melange with encaustics    
    
    
    One "Fasten"ating Book  http://www.purplecows.net/makeprojects/one-fastenating-book/ … another great gift idea!    
    
    
    Harvest Gift Bag and Card  http://www.purplecows.net/makeprojects/harvest-gift-bag-and-card/ … pink and brown are so pretty together.    
    
    
    Awesome giveaway from @wherewomencreat  and @tccevent http://www.wherewomencreate.com/2011/11/fabulous-friday-with-westminster-lifestyle-fabrics-and-ellison/#comment-29618 …    
    
    
    Inspiration: Elsa Mora http://pulse.me/s/3kELf     
    
    
    400 Free Online Courses from Top Universities (67 points) http://pulse.me/s/iqTN     
    
    
    150 Free Textbooks: A Meta Collection | Open Culture http://pulse.me/s/3lNSs     
    
    
    4 Tips for Optimizing Your Resume with Social Media http://pulse.me/s/3kStk     
    
    
    Looking For a Job or Internship In Fashion? Check Out Our Careers Page! http://pulse.me/s/3km6z     
    
    
    Store Frozen Corn and Peas in Plastic Water Bottles [Kitchen Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/3kc2T     
    
    
    Freeze Cooked Pasta to Have Quick Meals on Hand [Kitchen Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/3iJCd     
    
    
    DIY Glitter Tattoos http://pulse.me/s/3lDkF     
    
    
    "You Are the Window Through Which You See the World" [Quotables] http://pulse.me/s/3mA6A     
    
    
    dry erase paint - 30 sq ft - http://whiteyboard.com  http://www.whiteyboard.com/order-now-whiteboard/paint.html … via @whiteyboard    
    
    
    I LOVE this -- My Embroidered Headband. http://bit.ly/uPL0wU     
    
    
    Acorn Cake Bites http://pulse.me/s/3n3Wy     
    
    
    Build the Lego Ornament That Can Do the Kessel Run in 12 Parsecs [Lego] http://pulse.me/s/3pnNl     
    
    
    Fluidity Of Content And Design: Learning From Where The Wild Things Are http://pulse.me/s/3f4Gj     
    
    
    knot basket http://pulse.me/s/3qNqo     
    
    
    biz ladies: 5 customer service tips for your web-based business http://pulse.me/s/3qbZO     
    
    
    Golden Baroque Ung Drill http://pulse.me/s/3qGlk     
    
    
    HolgaDirect - Buy Holga Cameras, Accessories and Digital Holga Lenses Online at the Best Price - Holga iPhone Len... http://pulse.me/s/3berf     
    
    
    In Preparation for Thanksgiving: Dining Etiquette 101 http://www.apartmenttherapy.com/la/in-preparation-for-thanksgiving-dining-etiquette-101-161600 … via @apttherapy    
    
    
    kind over matter: A Collection of Free Thanksgiving Printables! http://bit.ly/aVEzGa     
    
    
    Craft Tutorial: Home Made SMASH book using the Cinch http://pulse.me/s/3qQgX     
    
    
    Sheer joy http://pulse.me/s/3svWp     
    
    
    Love this!! Hope theres a black fri sale on felt! Stitch a candy village http://pulse.me/s/3szt9  via @craftgossip.    
    
    
    Tutorial: Thimble or change pouch with squeeze opening http://pulse.me/s/3rIC4  # craft    
    
    
    A must do for the new year!! http://www.imperfecthomemaking.com/2011/10/31-days-to-organized-home-day-one.html …    
    
    
    Soft, soft sweeties http://pulse.me/s/3vTLC     
    
    
    Anna Maria’s studio scraps http://pulse.me/s/3vbyj     
    
    
    Tutorial: Fabric tag pocket Advent calendar http://pulse.me/s/3v8o3     
    
    
    Easy Gingerbread House How-tos http://pulse.me/s/3z7K8     
    
    
    Some Homemade Food Gift Guides http://pulse.me/s/3z29Q     
    
    
    The Eyes of Imagination Calendar http://pulse.me/s/3zaKC     
    
    
    How-To: Holiday Soap Wrappers http://pulse.me/s/3A42F     
    
    
    How-To: Felted Wool Wrist Warmers http://pulse.me/s/3zUVH     
    
    
    Surprise Gift Ideas: Digital-to-Door Subscription Services http://pulse.me/s/3zY0a     
    
    
    Freebie | Last Minute Christmas Cards http://pulse.me/s/3AVjR     
    
    
    TED Goes Mobile with New iPhone App [IPhone Apps] http://pulse.me/s/3Cehc     
    
    
    Chewing Gum Makes You Smarter—But Then You Get Dumb Again [Science] http://pulse.me/s/3BOwK     
    
    
    Glif Updates Increase Its Utility http://pulse.me/s/3BxSX     
    
    
    How to Identify and Learn from Your Mistakes [Mistakes] http://pulse.me/s/3BGUf     
    
    
    Stradivarius violin recreated from CAT scan, 'sounds amazingly similar' http://pulse.me/s/3CDQS     
    
    
    How-To: Simple Altoids Smalls LED Flashlight http://pulse.me/s/3BxQT     
    
    
    Kit-A-Day Giveaway: Drawdio Fun Packs http://pulse.me/s/3BlBl     
    
    
    Tutorial | 2012 Planner | Gift Idea http://pulse.me/s/3CKfg     
    
    
    Build a Smartphone Projector for Around a Dollar [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/3Dci1     
    
    
    Taxidermy Deer LEGO Kit http://pulse.me/s/3DPkE     
    
    
    Random Tutorial Generator http://pulse.me/s/3D4TU     
    
    
    The Get More Out of Google Infographic Summarizes Online Research Tricks for Students [Infographics] http://pulse.me/s/3EzBs     
    
    
    Can Lego be considered art? http://pulse.me/s/3FfiV     
    
    
    Tonara Aims To Change Your Relationship With Sheet Music http://pulse.me/s/3Fdxc     
    
    
    DIY Smart Autofocus Assist Lamp http://pulse.me/s/3FpB1     
    
    
    A Simple Clay Nativity http://pulse.me/s/3FWGS     
    
    
    Your elf needs shoes · Needlework News | http://CraftGossip.com  http://needlework.craftgossip.com/your-elf-needs-shoes/2011/12/01/ …    
    
    
    Beautiful!!! The song and the girl -- Glorious Song of Old (Silent Night) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    @kosairnurse yes. She's amazing!!    
    
    
    Glorious Song of Old (Silent Night) http://nblo.gs/qWqZM     
    
    
    My new Christmas favorite by my little sis.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    @snaps2scrap I'm glad you liked it. Pass the link on if you can ;)    
    
    
    @bekathwia love this!!    
    
    
    @mtn_dew diet code red in a fridge pack is the BEST!! Now I can face the holidays.    
    
    
    Glorious Song of Old by Katherine Nelson -- my new favorite Christmas Song! http://re.pn/K6eWD     
    
    
    @knelson_music This is gorgeous! Thanks for the download! #christmasmusic    
    
    
    Beautiful Christmas song with free download. If you like it, please pass it on! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    IKEA Lack : Audiophile Rack http://pulse.me/s/3IKur     
    
    
    Spotlight for roll-up displays http://pulse.me/s/3IaN2     
    
    
    How-To: DIY Spray Paint http://pulse.me/s/3H03X     
    
    
    Chic + Pretty DIY Clutches for Your Bridesmaids http://pulse.me/s/3Jbi8     
    
    
    Event: Occupy Your Sewing Room http://pulse.me/s/3J5kt     
    
    
    How to Print on Burlap http://pulse.me/s/3IDMp     
    
    
    Reduce Stress by Dividing Your Day into Three Operational Modes [Mind Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/3KgH1     
    
    
    DIY iPad Cash Register http://pulse.me/s/3L6oV     
    
    
    LetterMpress http://pulse.me/s/3L1XN     
    
    
    DIY Lace Pottery http://pulse.me/s/3L1pb     
    
    
    Freebies | Printable Holiday Scrapbooking Elements http://pulse.me/s/3Lfxm     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Today's #Festivusgiveaway: AR Drone, Star Walk, Inspire Pro & NFL Flick Quarterback - In The App http://bit.ly/sVdZT9     
    
    
    Best new Christmas Song! - Katherine Nelson - Glorious Song of Old (Silent Night) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=share … via @youtube #xmasmusic    
    
    
    Conveniently Hang Nearly Anything with Legos and Sugru [Video] http://pulse.me/s/3M5eK     
    
    
    The Best Antivirus App for Mac [Mac App Directory] http://pulse.me/s/3LtgE     
    
    
    How Music Affects the Brain and How You Can Use It to Your Advantage [Music] http://pulse.me/s/3LnBb     
    
    
    22 stylish tech gifts http://pulse.me/s/3MTmC     
    
    
    2011 gift guide: $25 and under http://pulse.me/s/3Lx2M  #xmasgifts    
    
    
    CraftSanity Issue 5 Available Now http://pulse.me/s/3Mhwi     
    
    
    Brilliant!!  Clip Pin http://pulse.me/s/3LoqF     
    
    
    How To: Make a Clementine Candle Apartment Therapy Videos http://pulse.me/s/3LFzD     
    
    
    From @appadvice: Festivus is upon us with the @AppAdvice app #festivusgiveaway http://bit.ly/tAi5O3     
    
    
    Add Telephoto Powers to Your Lens for Cheap [Photography] http://pulse.me/s/3NCbP     
    
    
    I Could Have Really Used This Children's Book About Calculus In High School [Books] http://pulse.me/s/3NPWp     
    
    
    Corter Leather Guitar Picks http://pulse.me/s/3NLA2     
    
    
    biz ladies: creating fans from scratch http://pulse.me/s/3Nkin     
    
    
    Love this! XL Modern Macrame http://pulse.me/s/3NXhj     
    
    
    Paracord Camera Strap http://pulse.me/s/3OGu2     
    
    
    Designated Theater Tweet Seats Allow Audience To Chronicle Shows In Real Time http://pulse.me/s/3NLtY     
    
    
    DIY Pearl Collar Necklace http://pulse.me/s/3OcPU     
    
    
    The Internet's Best 404 Error Pages [Humor] http://pulse.me/s/3P7fD     
    
    
    Art + Design in Miami: The Art of Craft http://pulse.me/s/3OdiW     
    
    
    Make Better Decisions by Thinking of Yourself in the Third Person [Mind Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/3Q85m     
    
    
    Activity Book For Young Scientists Encourages Coloring Inside the Cellular Walls [Books] http://pulse.me/s/3Q23X     
    
    
    Skirt the Fashion Hoi Polloi With Poshmark Mobile Auction App [Apps] http://pulse.me/s/3PmHp     
    
    
    Mixing Up Illustration: Combining Analog And Digital Techniques http://pulse.me/s/3Pq79     
    
    
    “X Is For X-Ray” An Inside Look At The Everyday http://pulse.me/s/3PG7A     
    
    
    Getting Crafty on Google+ http://pulse.me/s/3Ppsc     
    
    
    Twig Christmas Tree Art http://pulse.me/s/3QKWQ     
    
    
    Pretty hair pins http://pulse.me/s/3QR4g     
    
    
    Book Binding Loom http://pulse.me/s/3Rk0B     
    
    
    Paper Doll Kit http://pulse.me/s/3QWOb     
    
    
    Gingerbread Geodesic Dome Kit http://pulse.me/s/3SwIJ     
    
    
    Love this!! RT @uncrate: Here's To The Crazy Ones Letterpress Poster http://uncrate.com/stuff/heres-to-the-crazy-ones-letterpress-poster/ …    
    
    
    Fabulous!! RT @dornobdesign: Hyper-Flexible Wood Notepads Bend the Rules of Materials http://goo.gl/fb/hGqza  #more #newmaterials #material    
    
    
    listening to Silent Night/It Came Upon A Midnight Cle... by Katherine Nelson #nowplaying http://tinysong.com/QQck  via @grooveshark    
    
    
    @snaps2scrap Thanks!    
    
    
    Split Lack http://www.ikeahackers.net/2011/12/split-lack.html … great idea!    
    
    
    Jaw-droppingly Gorgeous Bathrooms http://www.home-designing.com/2011/10/jaw-droppingly-gorgeous-bathrooms-that-combine-vintage-with-modern …    
    
    
    Hoping we get more than a few to show up for our performance at tonight's choir side.    
    
    
    My new Christmas Favorite! A free download! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Great take on harnessing #fb RT @mashable: Here's how to make your Facebook fans super fans - http://on.mash.to/vm47wD     
    
    
    Tutorial: Fabric and burlap photo ornaments http://sewing.craftgossip.com/tutorial-fabric-and-burlap-photo-ornaments/2011/12/12/ …    
    
    
    Love this idea RT @Makemagazine: #Make iPhone Bottle Opener Case http://bit.ly/vRH11t     
    
    
    Just what I've been pulling my hair out over! Thx!!RT @smashingmag: Useful: Magento Project Guidelines for Designers - http://bit.ly/txjF8u     
    
    
    @lucykatecrafts sorry to hear that--happy new year to you...    
    
    
    Attn: developers-I need an online, fill in the blank marketing strategy builder. Anyone?    
    
    
    The Bride really Sparkled! http://nblo.gs/ruX2B     
    
    
    And I have the perfect socks for this! http://re.pn/oF0qP     
    
    
    Great gift idea--crochet necklace http://re.pn/oFagY     
    
    
    Another fun diy cuff http://re.pn/oFbzh     
    
    
    I think I have a cubbie fetish--I love small separate spaces to organize my myriads of collections!  http://re.pn/oFjhE     
    
    
    Oh my . . . holy freaking night. . .this is my dream armoire! http://re.pn/oFxYr     
    
    
    The Mayfair Steamer Secretary Trunk.  {sigh} http://re.pn/oFO0D     
    
    
    Yes, please. http://re.pn/oFUQV     
    
    
    Wooten Secretary Desk http://re.pn/oGKd0     
    
    
    Beautiful http://re.pn/oHemv     
    
    
    Turn Your Old Netbook or Laptop Into a Touchscreen PC http://lifehacker.com/5867803/     
    
    
    7 Things Highly Productive People Do (110 points) http://pulse.me/s/400fp     
    
    
    Freebie | Dangly Gift Tags http://scrapbooking.craftgossip.com/freebie-dangly-gift-tags/2011/12/14/ …    
    
    
    Fabulous shelf. . . http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976054486/ …    
    
    
    I'm in love! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976054497/ …    
    
    
    I hear barking coming from the bath tub followed by Dr. Who quotes--just 13 yo B*rod washing up....    
    
    
    Snowman Ornaments from Corrugated Cardboard http://homeandgarden.craftgossip.com/snowman-ornaments-from-corrugated-cardboard/ …    
    
    
    For the birds http://jewelrymaking.craftgossip.com/for-the-birds/2011/12/16/ …    
    
    
    Oli Phillips, Darth Vader by Bellino Alain http://indiecrafts.craftgossip.com/2011/12/15/oli-phillips-darth-vader-by-bellino-alain/ …    
    
    
    I love this--Ikea X-Mas Tree http://www.ikeahackers.net/2011/12/ikea-x-mas-tree.html …    
    
    
    Love this Christmas song! 
listening to Katherine Nelson #nowplaying http://tny.gs/vEmfYu  via @grooveshark    
    
    
    Love the happy graphic! RT @businessinsider: Markets Make Overnight Turnaround -- Stocks Now Rallying http://read.bi/uZZmSA     
    
    
    Wanna try this w/burlap & fabric--stffened RT @craft: Woven Paper Ball Garland: #xmascraft    
    
    
    The Cheese Thief: How to Weave a Paper Ball Ornament: http://www.thecheesethief.com/2011/11/how-to-weave-paper-ball-ornament.html …    
    
    
    Live google doodles! RT @engadget: Google launches revamped doodle website, store, self-celebration ensues http://engt.co/thpaOL     
    
    
    Make it last minute: iPhone Cozy http://quilting.craftgossip.com/make-it-last-minute-iphone-cozy/2011/12/18/ … #diygifts    
    
    
    Repair Rusty Dishwasher Racks with Sugru http://lifehacker.com/5869157/  #diy    
    
    
    #diy mic pop filter=brill!! http://lifehacker.com/5869094/make-a-diy-microphone-pop-filter …    
    
    
    Felt Cookie Garland http://homeandgarden.craftgossip.com/felt-cookie-garland/ …    
    
    
    # lightbulb RT @copyblogger: A 5-Minute Guide to More Persuasive Copywriting - http://copy.bz/sMy2aU     
    
    
    Maker Table - Project - Simplified Building http://www.simplifiedbuilding.com/projects/maker-table/ …    
    
    
    CraftGeek Stamp It by Purple Cows http://www.crafttestdummies.com/commentary/craft-product-review-craftgeek-stamp-it-by-purple-cows/ … #craft    
    
    
    French Metal Box & French Sheet Music Ornaments http://graphicsfairy.blogspot.com/2011/12/brag-monday-french-metal-box-french.html …    
    
    
    Great inspiration for book pages http://www.thenester.com/2011/09/20-ways-to-decorate-with-book-pages-and-other-things-about-the-book-party.html/comment-page-2#comment-174328 …    
    
    
    Project Downloads: Holiday Paper Crafting http://stamping.craftgossip.com/project-downloads-holiday-paper-crafting/2011/12/20/ …    
    
    
    Put Windows Defender on a USB Drive for Offline System Saving http://lifehacker.com/5870008/     
    
    
    "Happiness Is the Best Revenge" http://m.lifehacker.com/5869890/happiness-is-the-best-revenge … #gettingthrutheholidays    
    
    
    Love this! Most Popular Repurposing Tricks of 2011 http://m.lifehacker.com/5869281/most-popular-repurposing-tricks-of-2011 … #lifehacker    
    
    
    R29 Reserve: Score 2 Pairs Of Super-Chic Frames And Lenses For Just $88! http://reserve.refinery29.com/offer/210/lookmatic …    
    
    
    Dual-Lid Design Turns Jar on Its Head, Opens at Both Ends | Designs & Ideas on Dornob http://dornob.com/dual-lid-design-turns-jar-on-its-head-opens-at-both-ends/ … via @dornobdesign    
    
    
    Fabulous work space http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976070334/ …    
    
    
    I think I'm in love http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976070335/ …    
    
    
    coat/tie/scarf rack made from tree branches. http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976070348/ …    
    
    
    rustic elegance http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976070358/ …    
    
    
    Watch my new favorite #christmas song! Merry Christmas-pass it on http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4W_J69cQbao&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    @kosairnurse thanks. Merry Christmas to you!!    
    
    
    Merry Christmas Greeting http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976071173/ …    
    
    
    You can download the PDF from the artists site.  http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976072872/ …    
    
    
    This is  **STILL **  one of my favorite prom dresses so far! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074467/ …    
    
    
    Leaky Faucet http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074470/ …    
    
    
    Factory Windows as Shower Enclosures http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074471/ …    
    
    
    Large work table - two hollow core doors ($25 ea.), 4 Walmart book cases ($16 ea.)  Very smart!
 http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074472/ …    
    
    
    Love this!!!  http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074478/ …    
    
    
    Burlap flowers. Fun idea! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976074481/ …    
    
    
    Pierre Choque, Commémoration de la mort d’Anne, reine de France, duchesse de Bretagne, Pa http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976075699/ …    
    
    
    Printing and framing for my office! RT @copyblogger: 9 Rules of a [Content] Creator's Life - http://copy.bz/tM581w     
    
    
    Dalek Dress For Halloween « Randommization http://indiecrafts.craftgossip.com/2011/12/28/dalek-dress-for-halloween-randommization/ …    
    
    
    Printable seed packet PDF http://indiecrafts.craftgossip.com/2011/12/27/printable-seed-packet-pdf/ …    
    
    
    Trying to organize my twitter acct for the new year. Any great tips?    
    
    
    @auntieamyr #dumbquestion how?    
    
    
    Expedit cutting table on wheels http://www.ikeahackers.net/2011/12/expedit-cutting-table-on-wheels.html …    
    
    
    Hello! RT @MakeUseOf: YouTube Thumbnail Generator: Generate Thumbnail From Youtube Video http://muo.fm/sJu6Da     
    
    
    Great tutorials on sewing details, not to mention fabby patterns!  http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976087914/ …    
    
    
    Taking all the help i can get...RT @Remodelista: How to stay organized in the new year http://bit.ly/uBuRcC     
    
    
    Agreed!! RT @designsponge: the dress, the flowers, the berries..having a weak in the knees moment ... http://bit.ly/sKs082     
    
    
    Yummy!! New from Kreinik http://needlework.craftgossip.com/new-from-kreinik/2012/01/02/ …    
    
    
    Crafts | Handmade Gift Ideas | DIY Projects - http://Craftbits.com  http://www.craftbits.com/  #crafts    
    
    
    $12 Monitor Stand http://www.ikeahackers.net/2012/01/12-monitor-stand.html …    
    
    
    Book Review: Sweat Shop Paris: Lessons from a Sewing Cafe · Recycled Crafts | http://CraftGossip.com  http://recycledcrafts.craftgossip.com/book-review-sweat-shop-paris-lessons-from-a-sewing-cafe/2012/01/03/ …    
    
    
    Love this  RT @craft: Project: Cutting Clipboard Organizer: http://dld.bz/aBRcq  #2k12todo    
    
    
    Love this wall!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976093160/ …    
    
    
    AMEN! "@kentdavid: This appeared overnight on the gate to the North Fork @ Sundance pic.twitter.com/sqtHQWSC"    
    
    
    I love this card!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976098308/ …    
    
    
    Caterpillar babies http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976098311/ …    
    
    
    Ballerina with a popcap face http://purplecows.net/blog/craftgeek-fun-for-celestes-birthday-blog-hop/ … via @purplecowscre8 #craft #card    
    
    
    Snow White Goes Goth... Swarovski Crystal Cross Necklace http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976100067/ …    
    
    
    OMG. Caramel-wrapped marshmallows. Dip these in Valrhona and they'd be perfect! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976100070/ …    
    
    
    Love this!! Make Your Own Custom Buttons http://dollarstorecrafts.com/2012/01/make-your-own-custom-buttons/ … #diy    
    
    
    Tutorial: DIY fabric cover for an e-reader http://sewing.craftgossip.com/tutorial-diy-fabric-cover-for-an-e-reader/2012/01/08/ … #diy #craft    
    
    
    Inspiration: Hearty Craft http://needlework.craftgossip.com/inspiration-hearty-craft-3/2012/01/09/ … #craft    
    
    
    Soo cute! Tutorial: Gorgeous layered petal dress http://sewing.craftgossip.com/tutorial-gorgeous-layered-petal-dress/2012/01/09/ … #sewing    
    
    
    To do!! RT @craft: Travel Jewelry Clutch: By Emilee Gettle  http://dld.bz/aDJAg     
    
    
    resurrected leather -- these were boots!  http://www.facebook.com/album.php?fbid=194786797284031&id=192313710864673&aid=43300 …    
    
    
    Let's get this party started!!
Giddy up!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110680/ …    
    
    
    Casting 4 Crazy Crafters 4 a major TV series http://craftgossip.com/blog/casting-for-crazy-crafters-for-a-major-tv-series/2012/01/10/ … #craft    
    
    
    Tutorial | Birthday Card http://scrapbooking.craftgossip.com/tutorial-birthday-card/2012/01/10/ … via @craftgossip #craft    
    
    
    Tutorial | Birthday Card http://scrapbooking.craftgossip.com/tutorial-birthday-card/2012/01/10/ …    
    
    
    LOVE this! RT @make: An entire Darth Vader mask lovingly pieced together using architectural salvage! http://t.co/  #craft    
    
    
    Love the barn doors and the desk aspect!! Perfect inspirational set up! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110908/ …    
    
    
    Barn doors to enhance and hide the media center--brill!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110912/ …    
    
    
    Button & String Mini Journal http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110915/ …    
    
    
    hang it up http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110916/ …    
    
    
    drawers-  love this http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110917/ …    
    
    
    industrial pipe table. @scotthart this one's for you!!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110921/ …    
    
    
    mason jars + hose clamps = great idea! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976110923/ …    
    
    
    Wow. That's felt! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976113876/ …    
    
    
    Definitely on the #todo RT @craft: Project: Reverse Canvas Wall Pockets: By Cathe Holden ... http://dld.bz/aEnFZ     
    
    
    Beautiful branding--RT @FastCoDesign: Rebranding The British Pub For Stylish Snobs http://bit.ly/ntayFx     
    
    
    Damn-it's time to start the rest of the day. Those demanding salt mines... #offtoworkigo    
    
    
    Who's going to CHA? #chashow    
    
    
    lace inspired vintage. http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976127731/ …    
    
    
    Pretty patterns – Victory Patterns http://indiecrafts.craftgossip.com/2012/01/16/pretty-patterns-victory-patterns/ … #sew #craft    
    
    
    Wow!! Inspiration: Thom Atkins http://needlework.craftgossip.com/inspiration-thom-atkins/2012/01/18/ …    
    
    
    Fabulous!! RT @2digs: Industrial Black Plumber Bookshelves http://bit.ly/zkXl0W     
    
    
    Gone Too Soon!  Sarah Burke, au revoir! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976140945/ …    
    
    
    Love #5 the dangling participle! RT @copyblogger: 5 Grammatical Errors that Make You Look Dumb - http://copy.bz/5mJMM1     
    
    
    Colors info graphic!   http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976147440/ …    
    
    
    Industrial shelves and books with stairs--Oh My-this makes me giddy! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976147474/ …    
    
    
    A must have for the house on the hill!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976147479/ …    
    
    
    Fabric beads workshop.  http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976147532/ …    
    
    
    Lego style groom's cake http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976151016/ …    
    
    
    colors. http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976151018/ …    
    
    
    Fabby!! RT @refinery29: $55 snow boots. $35 rain boots. Enough said. http://r29.co/zasusK     
    
    
    Tutorial: Bound buttonholes http://sewing.craftgossip.com/tutorial-bound-buttonholes-2/2012/01/22/ …    
    
    
    Tutorial http://sewing.craftgossip.com/tutorial-cleaning-an-older-sewing-machine/2012/01/22/ …    
    
    
    Love this 1! RT @FastCoDesign: Passion Is Great, But There's 4 Keys To Having A Vision http://bit.ly/xIMV2M  (More lessons from Steve Jobs)    
    
    
    NOT Expensive Glass Whiteboard http://pulse.me/s/5h3j9  #hacks #ikea    
    
    
    I love a great recycled #craft http://craftside.typepad.com/craftside/2012/01/how-to-make-a-key-and-knife-frame-holder-inspired-by-the-book-steampunk-chic.html … http://bit.ly/zlobc3  via @addthis    
    
    
    Boarding at SLX-- It's official--big stitch jeans are soooo passé!    
    
    
    @creativegoddess right? Just trying to get out the door for #CHAShow leaves a path of disaster worthy of FEMA    
    
    
    Awkward attracts attention -- welcome to my world  http://lifehacker.com/5881054/order-is-never-observed-it-is-disorder-that-attracts-attention-because-it-is-awkward-and-intrusive …    
    
    
    Must read! RT @copyblogger: 9 Social Media Hacks You Need to Embrace Now - http://copy.bz/yhvI4n     
    
    
    orange you glad this pen exists? http://pulse.me/s/5mpBa  must find for Vday!    
    
    
    Carola Remer by Greg Kadel http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976215811/ …    
    
    
    Carola Remer by Greg Kadel http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976215817/ …    
    
    
    dreamy http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976215819/ …    
    
    
    Felt soft sculpture in motion http://needlework.craftgossip.com/felt-soft-sculpture-in-motion/2012/02/06/ …    
    
    
    Best news! Will be humming theme-song "take a look, its in a book..."RT @mashable: @levarburton: @readingrainbow http://on.mash.to/AouhjD     
    
    
    Amazing! RT @craft: Gorgeous Video on The Process of Yuzen in The Creation of a Kimono. http://bit.ly/yoyvcP     
    
    
        
    
    
    I've got the perfect case!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976240753/ …    
    
    
    mint green window cabinet http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976240791/ …    
    
    
    St. Paul, France - nearly stopped my heart. http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976240797/ …    
    
    
    "I wanna dance with somebody" AMAZING voice. #RipWhitneyHouston    
    
    
    7 Essential Tips for WordPress Beginners | Copyblogger http://pulse.me/s/5WacE     
    
    
    Fantastic solution!!! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976258885/ …    
    
    
    The One Drink Swap That Instantly Slims http://pulse.me/s/60KvH     
    
    
    Clik for iPhone and Android: Magically Control Any Web Browser from Your Phone [Apps] http://pulse.me/s/63nO3     
    
    
    "The Three Inventors" Papercut Animation (1980) http://pulse.me/s/63IMT     
    
    
    Businessweek Predicts “Culture Clash” Between Open Source and VCs http://pulse.me/s/63O8u     
    
    
    The “Unhyped” New Areas in Internet and Mobile http://pulse.me/s/69bc6     
    
    
    Lemon...Aid? From Weight-Loss to Pain Relief, This Citrus Has You Covered http://pulse.me/s/61e12     
    
    
    Make a Super Thin, Portable, and Cheap Boombox for Your Smartphone or Music Player [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/6cOFv     
    
    
    Great boot DIY tut!! http://abeautifulmess.typepad.com/my_weblog/2012/01/floral-boots-diy.html?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews&utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews …    
    
    
    @SalvageWest Welcome to twitter!    
    
    
    10 Reasons Why You Need to Try BodyRock.Tv http://pulse.me/s/6f0F7     
    
    
    Snow Drawings http://pulse.me/s/6kTMy     
    
    
    Great tut for making this hamper! ikat bag: Hamper http://pulse.me/s/6nPc2     
    
    
    Brit Hammer – Mosaic Artist…http://Emptyeasel.com  http://pulse.me/s/6pan4     
    
    
    Ucreate: The Petal Top by Made It On Monday http://www.u-createcrafts.com/2012/02/petal-top-by-made-it-on-monday.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    These are fabulous! http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976361193/ …    
    
    
    Love these! RT @designtaxi: Ladies and gentlemen, the official Moleskine x LEGO stop-motion video http://ow.ly/9nIGy     
    
    
    Learning to Code: The Roadmap I Wish I Had Been Given (25 points) http://pulse.me/s/6DY1T     
    
    
    Enhance Your Photos in an Instant with These Awesome Photoshop Actions [Video] http://pulse.me/s/6HPAb     
    
    
    Earn Extra Money on The Side, Even When You Have No Free Time [Money] http://pulse.me/s/6GGVs     
    
    
    Amazing eye candy!! Clockwork love paper - Tjep. - Think, amaze. http://pulse.me/s/6J3Nx     
    
    
    9 Essential Skills Kids Should Learn, by Leo Babauta (53 points) http://pulse.me/s/6PQJH     
    
    
    Elegant. Useful. Tiny. http://needlework.craftgossip.com/elegant-useful-tiny/2012/03/12/ …    
    
    
    Khan Academy for iPad Puts World-Class Educational Lectures in Your Hand [Ipad Downloads] http://pulse.me/s/6TMko     
    
    
    believe http://pulse.me/s/6U7mi     
    
    
    Use a Drop of Water to Turn Your iPhone Camera into a Microscope [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/6VxlQ     
    
    
    Get on the wait list for @pinerly for the best way to manage your Pinterest account! #pinerly http://www.pinerly.com/i/g6qhk/next     
    
    
    Inspiration: And Sew It Goes http://pulse.me/s/6ZWyE     
    
    
    Free Chore Chart Download http://sewcraftcreate.com/2012/03/free-chore-chart-download/ …    
    
    
    25 free fun fonts http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976451002/ …    
    
    
    Explore Einstein's Brain Through His Notes and Letters [Past Perfect] http://pulse.me/s/7dSvJ     
    
    
    I need suggestions for permanently coloring leather shoes/boots.  ideas? Anyone? #craft @sarahndipitous @CraftTestDummy    
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy tried alcohol inks with so so results. @clearsnap smooch spritz works fab but a little too glittery    
    
    
    Tutorial | Using PNG Files in Word http://pulse.me/s/7pnl9     
    
    
    Make a Flashy HTML5 Website Without Coding or Plug-Ins http://pulse.me/s/7qc71     
    
    
    Adjustable fruitbowl lamp http://pulse.me/s/7q2e1     
    
    
    Mighty mini men http://pulse.me/s/7qtuc     
    
    
    I have always wanted to take one of Susan's classes--now I can!!!! http://www.craftsy.com/class/The-Couture-Dress/53;jsessionid=E3149496C25E9DE9483E4DA26DCFEEA0.beastie …    
    
    
    @Gardenofdaisies I use her book like the bible for gowns. Can't wait!!!    
    
    
    Ready, Set, Go!  Wedding Gown in a Weekend! http://nblo.gs/vPoFb     
    
    
    Wedding Gown in a Weekend--scary! http://nblo.gs/vPCWE     
    
    
    WGW--Call it a Night http://nblo.gs/vQd55     
    
    
    Day 2--Wedding Gown in a Weekend http://nblo.gs/vRtrf     
    
    
    Final Day: Wedding Gown in a Weekend http://nblo.gs/vSl52     
    
    
    Skirt almost there: Wedding Gown in a Weekend http://nblo.gs/vSWru     
    
    
    The Final Countdown! The blood, sweat, tears, Diet Coke, Downtown Abbeymarathon, and pita chips have ... http://nblo.gs/vSZ2r     
    
    
    Success!! Wedding Gown in a Weekend http://nblo.gs/vTCaf     
    
    
    Dishwasher safe labeling for jars--I love this!  http://lifehacker.com/5898268/use-chalkboard-paint-to-make-reusable-dishwasher-safe-labels-for-your-storage-jars …    
    
    
    I am trying this soft serve ice cream this week! I wonder if I could make it in the mini freezer at work?  http://lifehacker.com/5900231/make-easy-delicious-soft-serve-ice-cream-with-ingredients-you-already-have …    
    
    
    #Creativity http://pulse.me/s/8gwHC     
    
    
    Ruffle Back Chair Redo http://homeandgarden.craftgossip.com/ruffle-back-chair-redo/ …    
    
    
    24 Professional Free Fonts for Graphic and Web designers – Download now http://designyoutrust.com/2012/04/24/24-professional-free-fonts-for-graphic-and-web-designers-download-now-2/ … via @designyoutrust    
    
    
    You are Beautiful Free Download http://nblo.gs/xaTVy     
    
    
    Download the new single, Beautiful here:  http://katherinenelson.com/  http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976661659/ …    
    
    
    Project Prom: the final chapter http://nblo.gs/xfuYk     
    
    
    Project Prom Dress 2012 ch. 2 http://nblo.gs/xfKnd     
    
    
    Project Prom Dress: T - 14 http://nblo.gs/xg5jX     
    
    
    Project Prom Dress -- Complete! http://nblo.gs/xhKe1     
    
    
    Road Trip 2012 begins http://nblo.gs/xoIp3     
    
    
    The road trip has begun and already he wants to know if we're getting close #roadtrip #aspie (16 hours to go)    
    
    
    Extended stretches with no cell service and I start hearing dueling banjos. #roadtrip #aspie    
    
    
    "we have got to stop somewhere soon!  I am SOOOOO hot I'm going to rip all my clothes off" #roadtrip #aspie (15 hours to go)    
    
    
    @thehumming_bird @DonOsmond just for you: "we really need to get some toenail clippers. I be got some problems going on" #roadtrip #aspie    
    
    
    We ALL needed a break!!! pic.twitter.com/JZzQBMG5    
    
    
    Wedding Bells in Kansas City http://nblo.gs/xuzsF     
    
    
    Love this graphic!! Learn the Simple Tricks to the Art of Persuasion [Infographics] http://pulse.me/s/9lNmO     
    
    
    Mind Wandering Can Boost Your Creativity-But Only After More Intense Brainstorming [Creativity] http://pulse.me/s/9yZIU     
    
    
    Beautiful Lu!  This wedding was a family affair--@Xan Hart did the make-up for this shot from the re http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976757297/ …    
    
    
    Super Intricate Hand-Cut Paper Designs http://pulse.me/s/9B8jm     
    
    
    "Impossible Is Not a Fact. It's an Opinion." [Quotables] http://pulse.me/s/9XJA8     
    
    
    DIY Hermes Paper Purse http://pulse.me/s/9ZUQK     
    
    
    Support JC Penney's first gay Father's Day ad.  on @upworthy @jcpenney http://www.upworthy.com/call-to-action-show-your-support-for-the-very-first-gay-fathers-day-ad?g=4&c=mrp1 …    
    
    
    Crafting Community http://pulse.me/s/a5Gza     
    
    
    The "uniform" wardrobe --love http://it--timoni.org  http://pulse.me/s/a55st     
    
    
    Free Darth Vader Paper Craft http://pulse.me/s/a5bER     
    
    
    Tattoo by *BrotherOstavia http://pulse.me/s/a6kqg     
    
    
    On the road again. #roadtrip #aspie so many many many words -- in so few minutes...gonna be a long night    
    
    
    "I need to go, I can hold it for a little while. I can go about a half hour--nope--do we have a pee bottle?" #roadtrip #aspie    
    
    
    @kosairnurse we made it. Phew!!  Thanks!!    
    
    
    @kosairnurse on our way to Disneyland -- woot woot!!    
    
    
    My baby sisters husband telling his dad they're expecting #fathersday (I hope it's a girl!!) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KKmainbmaoA&feature=youtube_gdata_player …    
    
    
    Are You Interested? [Communication] http://pulse.me/s/arp1d     
    
    
    "Change Is Not a Bolt of Lightning That Arrives With a Zap, But a Bridge Built Brick by Brick Every Day" [Quotables] http://pulse.me/s/arfxS     
    
    
    Just hoping to take a little color out of this lining! #weddinggowninaweekend2 http://instagr.am/p/MMCT7ohPRa/     
    
    
    Vote for Brand Connect on Mission: Small Business℠: http://bit.ly/L1iKGB     
    
    
    Great idea!! RT @designtaxi: A radio show that uses frequency sounds to repel mosquitoes http://ow.ly/bPpXk     
    
    
    #justheardfromtheotherroom "Can we please have some grilled cheese? 2 tiefighters & 2 mil. falcons? Please" #aspie    
    
    
    Make that 3 millennial falcons and 1 tie fighter. Order up! #aspie #heardfromtheotherroom    
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy you mean some don't??    
    
    
    Recipe: Grilled Corn on the Cob with Cilantro Lime Butter and Feta http://pulse.me/s/aEhWf     
    
    
    Love the new single!!! Katherine Nelson | Born | CD Baby http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152976941021/ …    
    
    
    @kosairnurse we're safe for now, but Scott (vol. fire chief) has his unit on high alert. It'll be a scary summer here in the Rockies    
    
    
    @kosairnurse thanks for thinking of us--so far for us it's just been smokey.    
    
    
    The Snarky Voice in Your Head Is Killing Your Productivity; Here’s How to Stop It [Snark] http://pulse.me/s/aI4dz     
    
    
    Pretty as it is, waking up to smokey skies is never good. #utwildfires http://instagr.am/p/Mas--phPcU/     
    
    
    Target + Neiman Marcus Holiday Collection – Browne, Jacobs, Rodarte… http://pulse.me/s/b7RCI     
    
    
    A Simple Strategy for Neutralizing Stress [Stress] http://pulse.me/s/b6ZZs     
    
    
    Life isn't about waiting for the storm to pass... it's learning to dance in the rain.- Anonymous http://pulse.me/s/bap0c     
    
    
    Love the view on my way to work!!  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/NBUx-khPRE/     
    
    
    These are made from discarded boots!  Love the colors!  Fancy Boot Cuff Classic #12612-50-01 - CUFFS http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152977053382/ …    
    
    
    I live in freaking heaven!! http://instagr.am/p/NSWf2vhPT0/     
    
    
    That just happened!! http://instagr.am/p/NSWkgZhPT3/     
    
    
    I am in love with #encausticart and beeswax! #purplecows #craftgeek #hsn http://instagr.am/p/NWCiBFBPV1/     
    
    
    Great products from old boots http://instagr.am/p/NUgHjQQI3I/  #recycled #cowboyboots #salvagewest    
    
    
    It's a baby voss! #aspengrove   @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/NXQj_zBPfm/     
    
    
    Finally got my cd. A-MAZ-ING!!!! #katherinenelson #bornbrave #sisters http://instagr.am/p/NZ3apOBPZY/     
    
    
    My kind of cat!  Snuggled up with random bolts of fabric snoozing away. #chimera #cutekitty #sewingroom http://instagr.am/p/Ne8cyEhPS7/     
    
    
    #frontiernight #aspengrove #sisters   @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/NfAIBAhPVq/     
    
    
    Just a doodle... http://instagr.am/p/Nj1tpABPf7/     
    
    
    How Autism is Changing the World for Everybody [Psychology] http://pulse.me/s/bCjCK     
    
    
    6:15 am on the mountain #lovemyhome #aspengrove http://instagr.am/p/NlX0ioBPS0/     
    
    
    Great idea #ikea #sewingroom Melltorp to Sewing Desk http://pulse.me/s/bIdxx     
    
    
    My cute nieces #aspengrove #familyrocks  @ Aspen Grove Family Camp http://instagr.am/p/NxGmJ7hPZb/     
    
    
    How an American Can Stream the BBC's Official Olympics Coverage and Overcome #NBCFail [Video] http://pulse.me/s/bKa2A     
    
    
    Silk Satin Embroidered Zolotova Dress by Wai Ching http://pinterest.com/pin/190277152977174749/ …    
    
    
    I am curating the things I like on the web using Pearltrees. Join and team-up with me! http://pearltrees.com/pnhart     
    
    
    #katherinenelson #bornbrave love this girl and this music  http://instagr.am/p/N4uexghPWY/     
    
    
        
    
    
    A fallen star #movienight #stardust  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/N5GlwkBPYz/     
    
    
    Just welding a little something--that's my girl  @cecillyhart #industrialcreativity #salvagewest http://instagr.am/p/N7K6qChPb2/     
    
    
    another day in paradise #homesweethome #goldenhandcuffs  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/N9rlLnBPbX/     
    
    
    Dusk. #nofilter #mountainlife   @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/OApJOOhPR7/     
    
    
    DIY Macro Lens for your phone – iArt Chronicles http://pulse.me/s/bZsAc     
    
    
    DIY Mason Jar Speakers [DIY Creations] http://pulse.me/s/c0gd6     
    
    
    Yeah!!! ‘Arrested Development’ Set Pictures Hit the Web http://pulse.me/s/c2MmG  via @mashable    
    
    
    Are We All Crafters? http://pulse.me/s/c0Naf     
    
    
    10 places to learn geeky stuff online for free http://pulse.me/s/c5jvy     
    
    
    Getting ready to cheer on the racers #tou12 @zozohart #giddyup  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/OMjDamBPUz/     
    
    
    The Lego Story: 80 Years of Playing Well http://pulse.me/s/cfZXp     
    
    
    The Disciplined Pursuit of Less [Success] http://pulse.me/s/cfwrY     
    
    
    Seriously--who left the chickens on the side of the rd?? #chickenrun #toughbird  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/OZ6_MyhPS4/     
    
    
    That's some serious arm candy! #aspengrove2012 #bffs   @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/Oagl4DhPf5/     
    
    
    And she's a little one! #mooseontheloose #mountainlife #ilovemymt  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/Oc-PZ7BPdY/     
    
    
    #fall #sunflowers  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/OhtBgchPYF/     
    
    
    Happy Friday--love this--The History of the Color Wheel http://pulse.me/s/cqnMu     
    
    
        
    
    
    #GOP2012
Giddy Up!! It's time for a businessman!    
    
    
    #GOP2012 "when people don't do their job, we should let them go!"    
    
    
    Tutorial: 3-thread flatlock seam to join fabric without the bulk http://pulse.me/s/cNo6j     
    
    
    AMAZING!! #mandypatinkin #whatavoice #chops #byu  @ DeJong Concert Hall http://instagr.am/p/PBIzaGBPZt/     
    
    
    Holy Hail, Batman! The size of marbles.   @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/PDlf2EhPd7/     
    
    
    @salvagewest #sundaypaper @el_thum #amazingprdude http://instagr.am/p/PGA2xRhPQM/     
    
    
    Bind Pages Together with a Paper Clip and a Rubber Band [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/cZSlC     
    
    
    Get Started Coding The Raspberry Pi with Cambridge University Tutorials [Programming] http://pulse.me/s/cZXqe     
    
    
    How to Avoid the Natural Reactions that Prevent Good Decision Making [Psychology] http://pulse.me/s/ddFQr     
    
    
    The Attention Deficit Designer, by Jon Winebrenner http://pulse.me/s/decNy     
    
    
    I expect the leaf lookers to be out in force this weekend #drivingrealslow #sto  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/PlZ93nhPVv/     
    
    
    Counting down the last few minutes till the 6 hr mark. #migrainesucks #wastedwe  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/PnfPauhPZz/     
    
    
    Will be here Friday & Saturday with chalk in hand with Cecilly and @zozohart --our as yet untitled entry wil http://instagr.am/p/Ps06sVBPT0/     
    
    
    Laying some foundation #chalktheblock #hartofthemountain #artforautism   @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P2JHHNhPY6/     
    
    
    #hartofthemountain #artforautism #chalktheblock   @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P2P37-hPd0/     
    
    
    @zozohart chalking away on Godzilla and a burning city #chalktheblock #artforauti  @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P2ZMpUBPUg/     
    
    
    It's after 3pm already??  My legs hurt! #chalktheblock #artforautism #hartofthemo  @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P2iaa9BPb1/     
    
    
    Serious progress #hartofthemountain #chalktheblock #artforautism   @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P2wRIjhPXQ/     
    
    
    #hartofthemountain #chalktheblock #artforautism   We'll finish tomorrow?!  @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P3EPubhPY0/     
    
    
    Finally finished!!
#hartofthemountain #artforautism #chalktheblock #tributetobrod  @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagr.am/p/P5BGLlBPaU/     
    
    
    22 years ago today:  Lexandra Christine Hart #happybirthday #theprettyone #bubb  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/QBUc9lBPcG/     
    
    
    Even though they were never buddies, she keeps looking for him. #missinghoratio  @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/QYpDWjhPbz/     
    
    
    Recycled Fashion Accessories http://www.cw30.com/s/OOKgdGivbUKM9wSJDcUlIA.cspx#.UG9XDwKApio.twitter …    
    
    
    A little #SalvageWest promo with my new friend, Rob. http://www.cw30.com/content/news/dailydish/story/Recycl … http://instagr.am/p/QaqDh0hPUt/     
    
    
    AMEN!@Bonnie4UT: Young people dealing with SSA are particularly vulnerable and need our love and acceptance. #LDSConf Thank you, Elder Oaks.    
    
    
    Artist http://pulse.me/s/e9GWp     
    
    
    Craft Product Review: Fuse Creativity System by Fiskars http://pulse.me/s/eaFDJ     
    
    
    Driving into the sunset #westwardho #nofilter #caliherewecome #ochomeshow #salvagewest   @ Kanosh, Utah http://instagr.am/p/Q8gwi0hPf5/     
    
    
    You've come a long way, baby! #cholula #daddysasoftie #oldmanglasses http://instagr.am/p/Q8hIINBPQO/     
    
    
    If you're in So Cal come see us at the home show/women's show at the OC fairgrounds @ OC Fair & Event Center http://instagr.am/p/RA2k_TBPX2/     
    
    
    Don't you hate it when the snow scrapper is not where you thought you put it last spring? #fi @ the cottage http://instagr.am/p/RKmDQ7BPV6/     
    
    
    Today:
jenn_jnelson -"Did you color your hair?"
Me- "No"
jenn_jnelson - "You shouldn't! Your silver highli http://instagr.am/p/RbjLyGBPQP/     
    
    
    Happy Halloween? #doomguy #trickortreat http://instagr.am/p/RdVdc-hPQn/     
    
    
    Doodle gone wild....
#doodleart #meetingdoodles #ishouldgetsomebetterpaper  @ cozy cottage in the woods http://instagr.am/p/R9ATE0hPcT/     
    
    
    iPhone pix at DI.  thanks icolorama #freeapplove #cecillyhart http://instagr.am/p/R_iHJihPTS/     
    
    
    Oh what a beautiful morning! #nofilter #lovewhereilive #thanksgivingeve @ Alpine Loop, Provo Canyon http://instagr.am/p/SUNVduhPVB/     
    
    
    Well, it is a bird feeder . . . . #blackfridayfeast #turkeyontheporch #2ndthankgivingrocks @ the cottage http://instagr.am/p/SY8UVOhPdG/     
    
    
    Apple & Cherry wood smoked turkey, masa cornbread stuffing with Anaheim chilies, @ cozy cottage in the woods http://instagr.am/p/SZVRl8hPXD/     
    
    
    Most Popular How-To Guides of 2012 http://pulse.me/s/fXuU8     
    
    
    DIY Paper Speakers Turn Scrap Into Sound http://pulse.me/s/fVcV1     
    
    
    Ribbon & Bead Christmas Tree http://pulse.me/s/fZSLa     
    
    
    Trying different pens #doodleart #doodlealladay #pentelslicci025 #foraystylemarkfine http://instagr.am/p/S23xpTBPSm/     
    
    
    Love Of Spicy Food Is Built Into Your Personality http://pulse.me/s/g1XgC     
    
    
    How To Floss And Marry Your Way To Immortality [Infographic] http://pulse.me/s/g2LaV     
    
    
    3D Paper Diamonds http://pulse.me/s/g31vq     
    
    
    God Help Us #benstein http://drudgegae.iavian.net/r?hop=http%3A%2F%2Fspectator.org%2Farchives%2F2012%2F12%2F17%2Fgod-help-us …    
    
    
    Why yes, I think I will sweeten my tea with this gummy worm! #mmmmmgood #sweetg @ Marriott Cleveland Airport http://instagr.am/p/TZTOJ2BPZc/     
    
    
    Tic Sweden: Popped buttons ditch needle and thread for a quick new fix http://pulse.me/s/golPP     
    
    
    Star Wars Fans Building a Full Scale Replica of the Millennium Falcon http://pulse.me/s/glvTd     
    
    
    Lady Ada AKA Limor Fried Named Entrepreneur Of The Year http://techcrunch.com/2012/12/18/lady-ada-aka-limor-fried-named-entrepreneur-of-the-year/ … via @TechCrunch    
    
    
    DIY LEGO Ornaments: http://blog.makezine.com/craft/diy-lego-ornaments/?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews … via @make    
    
    
    Snowed in Christmas Eve. (Sort of) #muppetchristmascarol #diyamplifier #surehopesantabringsatv http://instagr.am/p/TodmsXhPTo/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Christmas Eve. Raclette and Minecraft. #aspieholiday #ilovemyfamily @ cozy cottage in the woods http://instagr.am/p/TpF6afBPQM/     
    
    
    Transform Plain White Sugar into Powdered Sugar at Home http://pulse.me/s/gE7dw     
    
    
    Startups: Tim O’Reilly’s Key to Creating the Next Big Thing http://pulse.me/s/gpKBF     
    
    
    At work! In the real world there's no vacation until the work  @ Purple Cows Craft Lab & Glamination Station http://instagr.am/p/TvzEA4BPZ3/     
    
    
    My uncle Dave and his son Caden last week at my sisters Christmas Party. So grateful I got one last bear hug http://instagr.am/p/T7B3s3hPXK/     
    
    
    Lego Mindstorms EV3 arrives tailored for mobile, infrared and more hackability http://pulse.me/s/h0Sgy     
    
    
    Victorville?
#ithoughtweleftthesnowbehind #charoadtrip2013 @ Cajon Summit Elevation 4190 http://instagr.am/p/UUMBHjBPT0/     
    
    
    Netflix to debut new 'Arrested Development' episodes in May http://pulse.me/s/h6xgY     
    
    
    Needless to say, Brody is thrilled! #missioncall http://instagr.am/p/UkoNijBPYj/     
    
    
    iPad Hack Statement Of Responsibility http://pulse.me/s/hDZXq     
    
    
    Just whipped this up in the hotel room last night! #salvagewest #giddyup @ Dallas World Trade Center (WTC) http://instagr.am/p/U6RsXPBPby/     
    
    
    This is two of the three signs posted in the women's restroom #dontdrinkandgestate @ dallas, TX http://instagr.am/p/U-D0jBhPcd/     
    
    
    Just posted a photo @ Twisted Root Burger Company http://instagr.am/p/U-GwEchPQw/     
    
    
    What--SLC airport runways are closed?  Cec says--Tell the pi @ Dallas/Fort Worth International Airport (DFW) http://instagr.am/p/VAbtHvBPf2/     
    
    
    My all time favorites made by the pretty one xanhart   Thanks Becky Nyman for this family favorite!!… http://instagr.am/p/VK3spKBPfh/     
    
    
    A search for vacuum attachments has turned into a hall/game closet redux. #analoggames #hartfamrocks… http://instagr.am/p/VhJ8opBPeA/     
    
    
    What is she walking? http://drawquest.com/s/d6xg  via @DrawQuest    
    
    
    Choose carefully - the wrong face could lead to an epic #meltdown #marchoftheminifigs #legos @ cozy… http://instagr.am/p/WDeoFThPY-/     
    
    
    Getting everything ready for Friday's birthday boy #myfirstbuild #brodysgoingtobe15 #gamerstyle #imageek… http://instagr.am/p/WQEHpIBPY9/     
    
    
    Over some Great Lake--Michigan, I think. @ friendly skies with delta http://instagr.am/p/WdJRb-BPTI/     
    
    
    Saturday jobs. Scott loves his natural cleaners--me-bring on the pine sol! #notcleantillitsmellsclean @… http://instagr.am/p/WpOtfGBPWE/     
    
    
    She lurks, ready to pounce, from a nest of cast off scrapbook paper curls #xanskitty… http://instagr.am/p/XGH8Q-BPRi/     
    
    
    @DonOsmond have you heard the one about the carpool road trip?    
    
    
    Creative Repurposing with Cardboard: Victorian Birdcage Card http://flip.it/lNJOc     
    
    
    My siblings ROCK!! #nfs el_thum @jessiosmond nelsonnumber7 mnelsonxy joe5nelson morindabeane ferfhatch http://instagram.com/p/X-1L6GhPQa/     
    
    
    The coffee table #homework #recycledflora #tonicstudiostools #paperflowersonfridaynight #craftaholic @… http://instagram.com/p/YBvZ65BPSN/     
    
    
    #staticandrhesound #uncledavesguitar #myfamilyrocks @ Provo Beach Resort http://instagram.com/p/YEgKvxhPeC/     
    
    
    Nelson grandkids #1 and # 30  Cec & Tru #nfs @jessiosmond donosmond #noinstacec http://instagram.com/p/YlFhmhBPfh/     
    
    
    The countdown on ON! http://instagram.com/p/Y_NzlOhPQw/     
    
    
    Filling up 77 envelopes to last 18 months with love and encouragement. Thanks to all those who came!… http://instagram.com/p/Zg7fwWBPZO/     
    
    
    #staticandthesound. #Summernights love!! @ The Shops at Riverwoods http://instagram.com/p/Zwgv-OBPfX/     
    
    
    I love you, baby girl.  Tomorrow your selfless adventure begins. 
 
 "Be still, wild and young,
long… http://instagram.com/p/aJ7OVBhPco/     
    
    
    Sister Hart. That's one if two suitcases. 18 months of gear. Love this girl! #zoeinflorida… http://instagram.com/p/aMf53QBPUC/     
    
    
    On the set at Scrapbook Soup with Julie @balzerdesigns #scrapbooksoup purplecowscre8 http://instagram.com/p/aPJimqBPXK/     
    
    
    Love this crazy crew! http://instagram.com/p/aY4XybBPcN/     
    
    
    Thank you #KhaledHosseini for another fabulous read. It leaves an echo on your heart! #lovethisauthor http://instagram.com/p/arXa__hPTy/     
    
    
    This IS his frontier costume. #shortbrimhat #alamartymcfly http://instagram.com/p/auIhYbBPTI/     
    
    
    #oops #gladitsnotmycar #parkingfail #duh http://instagram.com/p/a1r9wbBPZt/     
    
    
        
    
    
    2 workshops, 2 make & takes, 1 presentation, and the ever popular Cowstume. #chavegasorbust http://instagram.com/p/b_3ldWhPfI/     
    
    
    A hammer, heat and an anvil can solve a lot of frustration!! #truhstpaula #didit http://instagram.com/p/cajzgDhPWG/     
    
    
    Gearing up for high school. Thanks to @lxhart for the stop at h&m #backtoschoolshoppingwithxan… http://instagram.com/p/csetlNhPSN/     
    
    
    salvagewest's photo http://instagram.com/p/cuIyWMQI6d/     
    
    
    See kids, we still slow dance, sort of. #noinstantyoungfilter #westilllikeeachother… http://instagram.com/p/cxw5l7hPbf/     
    
    
    #encaustic Klimt inspired on black canvas #lovewarmwax http://instagram.com/p/c0ZUp9hPdI/     
    
    
    Day 3
#slcomiccon #migraine #murdochandface #waitingfirstanlee @ Salt Lake Comic Con http://instagram.com/p/d9-ojUhPfD/     
    
    
    Waiting in line for Stan Lee. #motherofthecenturyawardismine #slcomiccon http://instagram.com/p/d-GCRahPdu/     
    
    
    Got it!!
#slcomiccon @ Salt Lake Comic Con http://instagram.com/p/d-NwgBhPfD/     
    
    
    Wow http://instagram.com/p/enpSeHBPf9/     
    
    
    Happy Birthday @lxhart 143 http://instagram.com/p/etMhxQBPWT/     
    
    
    Um, seriously?!?! @ SR 92 http://instagram.com/p/etSCEDBPdo/     
    
    
    Just came home to this.  #tooearlyforsnow @ cozy cottage in the woods http://instagram.com/p/etSXW7BPd7/     
    
    
    7:15 am #latergram @ cozy cottage in the woods http://instagram.com/p/evis_BBPQg/     
    
    
    The perfect day to play with warm wax! #encaustic #mixedmedia #purplecows @ hart of the mountain studio http://instagram.com/p/fD_jezBPUf/     
    
    
    Truth. Slowly but surely crafting will be redefined by gifted makers like these. 
http://lnkd.in/bjMCWZ3     
    
    
    Sister's got chops!!! Amazing rendition of "At Last" for the tv show Bones wedding by cyndilauper… http://instagram.com/p/fyjPsrBPU_/     
    
    
    @cyndilauper way to bring it! Best "at Last" ever!!! #BonesWedding    
    
    
    #winterwonderland #itsabouttime #hopewemakeitdown http://instagram.com/p/gyEAFLBPRf/     
    
    
    Date night with French Chantilly! I love the details--and no--not Xan's!! #weddinggowninaweek… http://instagram.com/p/hCuDwdhPdx/     
    
    
    Christmas Eve Jam #nfs #ilovemyfamily @ honey's home http://instagram.com/p/iVE0D4hPYk/     
    
    
    Love my baby girl!! Best Christmas gift EVER!!
#lovemymissionary #floridaorlandomission @ cozy cottage… http://instagram.com/p/iXk7xRhPbZ/     
    
    
    When all else fails, it's #pinterest time! http://pinterest.com/pnhart/pins/     
    
    
    @AlliWorthington torn between top left and right.    
    
    
    http://pinterest.com/pin/133898048/  Amazing read!    
    
    
    @sweettoothfairy your chocolate peanut butter cc made my night! Thanks for sharing your amazingness.    
    
    
    Trying this!  DIY Beauty: Make Your Own Lip Balm http://pulse.me/s/1jeIc     
    
    
    How is it that my gaydar can be so intuitive and my crazydar so totally obtuse?    
    
    
    I just downloaded one of 100+ free HTML email templates from http://campaignmonitor.com/templates/     
    
    
    Thank heaven my stupid-dar is fully functioning    
    
    
    Sweet!  Build Your Own Grid-It Tech Organizer in a Vintage Book [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1kqU2     
    
    
    Style Syllabus: Cheap Tricks For An Uncommonly Cool Common Room http://pulse.me/s/1kjMI     
    
    
    @chipwade i am a total newbie and learn as you go gal with my dremel, I'm wondering about polishing and texturizing some leather-ideas?    
    
    
    i am a total newbie and learn as you go gal with my dremel, I'm wondering about polishing and texturizing some leather-ideas? #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @dremel thx--I have the 75th ann. LE from costco--which should i pick up next?    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy my biggest problem using the tool is it gets really hot while i'm working. Am i in need of a larger tool?    
    
    
    brilliant RT @momsworkbench: Just went on the website and noticed the Pumpkin Carving kit - now that's a way to a DIY mom's heart #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @barbarakirk #dremeldiy I do it all the time--works great with metals too, and cutting leather--Love my dremel!    
    
    
    #dremeldiy I want to set up a flex shaft workstation for my jewelry/costume making. If I can only get one, which tool would be best?    
    
    
    @dremel leather cosplay helmet #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @barbarakirk #dremeldiy I like instructables.com and searching youtube and there's a bunch on dremel.com    
    
    
    r u kidding--diy is how i relax--i luv it!RT @repurposedlife:so right! RT @asliceofwood: @ChipWade there is no time for relaxing #dremeldiy    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy craft & diy equally    
    
    
    #dremeldiy my dremel makes me feel like I know what I'm doing, even if I'm faking it! lol    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy electrical-but I'm working on it. . .    
    
    
    @dremel #dremeldiy q3 had to think--i would take advantage of an expert and get a personal tutorial on all my projects. . lol    
    
    
    @ChipWade #dremeldiy fixing and repurposing for sure!    
    
    
    Totally doable!! The Fold-Away Treadmill Workspace [Featured Workspace] http://pulse.me/s/1lKWc     
    
    
    5 Ways to Turn Happiness Into An Advantage http://m.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-happiness-advantage/201108/5-ways-turn-happiness-advantage?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews,http://pulse.me …    
    
    
    Sneak in These Simple Exercises at the Office to Stay Healthy [Health] http://pulse.me/s/1lk5s     
    
    
    PhotoLive for Chrome Downloads Your Facebook Photos for Easy Migration [Chrome Extensions] http://pulse.me/s/1l7tf     
    
    
    Want!! Olympus PEN E-PM1 Mini gets a $500 price tag, September release date http://www.engadget.com/2011/08/25/olympus-pen-e-pm1-mini-gets-a-500-price-tag-september-release/ … via @engadget    
    
    
    WANT!!  Wacom’s Inkling Captures What You Draw On Paper Digitally (Amazing Video) http://pulse.me/s/1pZDO     
    
    
    Star Wars Crafts: Bonnie Burton http://pulse.me/s/1pn42     
    
    
    Tutorial: Tree Pillow with heart-shaped leaves http://pulse.me/s/1pIwa     
    
    
    Gratitude Card made with Purple Cows CraftGeek tools  ;): http://re.pn/aczwn    
    
    
    One of my favorites! http://pinterest.com/pin/150755937/  Gratitude Card made with Purple Cows CraftGeek tools  ;)    
    
    
    Path.to Helps You Create a Professional Profile and Get Noticed [Webapps] http://pulse.me/s/1qyLv     
    
    
    Hoot Turns Facebook into a Study Hall and Project Collaboration App [Webapps] http://pulse.me/s/1qmvE     
    
    
    This is brill!!  Add Used Tea Bags to the Bottom of Planters to Feed Plants [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/1qinX     
    
    
    I’ve created my profile at about.me! Check me out: http://about.me/pnhart  and sign up at http://about.me .    
    
    
    Handmade Vellum Wedding Card http://pulse.me/s/1rkHs     
    
    
    Great idea--Bug-Away Paper Cup Covers http://pulse.me/s/1rwcj     
    
    
    Craft Product Review: Craft Geek “Roll It” Texture Tool by Purple Cows http://pulse.me/s/1spFe     
    
    
    Vote for me to be the face of @aboutdotme on a Times Square billboard: http://about.me/pnhart     
    
    
    HOW TO: Follow New York Fashion Week Online http://pulse.me/s/1wSXv     
    
    
    A Piece of Lisa: About My Camera http://lisaedoff.blogspot.com/2011/08/about-my-camera.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    Tatting! http://needlework.craftgossip.com/recent-tatting-tutorials/2011/09/05/?utm_medium=referral&utm_source=pulsenews,http://pulse.me …    
    
    
    Recipe: Snickerdoodle Pumpkin Ice Cream Sandwiches http://pulse.me/s/1xozc     
    
    
    Getting ready for a segment on KUTV 2news fresh living segment today--sharing the purplecows & scrapbookusaexpo    
    
    
    Left brain/Right Brain http://pinterest.com/pin/186332950/  I love these ads!    
    
    
    left brain/right brain passion: http://re.pn/cCTXW    
    
    
    The "Introduction to Arduino" Comic Makes It Easy to Get Started with Electronics Hacking [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1DUK1     
    
    
    Avoid hot spots when burning the candle at both ends!    
    
    
    Fabby! http://www.makeandtakes.com/school-lunches-ideas-and-a-free-printable …    
    
    
    @PopArtMinis how in the world do you do it, girl? Keeping up with a day job and brilliantly creating your own stuff? It's killing me!    
    
    
    My @Klout score is 36. I improved it by 4 points over the past  30 days! http://klout.com/user/pnhart/score-analysis?n=tw&v=daily_welcome …    
    
    
    Cigar Box Fiddles by Xylocopa Design http://pulse.me/s/1MC85     
    
    
    Fall Decorating Inspirations {Weddings} http://pulse.me/s/1MaHY     
    
    
    Love this!  Tutorial: Pretty pintucked skirt http://pulse.me/s/1LUvo     
    
    
    Fab post! RT %40CraftTestDummy Cutting Fabric with Sizzix Framelits Dies %7C Craft Test Dummies http%3A%2F%2Fbit.ly%2FqZ5o2a    
    
    
    @sarahndipitous At the end of the day sometimes the underside is more beautiful    
    
    
    Me time is now over--let the day begin-dammit    
    
    
    Looking for a new camera--something between point&shoot basic and dslr.  Suggestions?    
    
    
    sewing 101: electronics sleeve http://pulse.me/s/1MSJK     
    
    
    diy project: leather envelope phone case http://pulse.me/s/1MQjQ     
    
    
    Star Wars AT-AT Walker Pancakes http://pulse.me/s/1N55v     
    
    
    Parent/teacher conf w/B*rod -so far so good.    
    
    
    Seriously? I know you can breastfeed anywhere--but jr hi parent teacher conferences? Science teacher is sweating    
    
    
    Poor guy--all the teachers in the gym-parents waiting in line. Very funny reactions all around    
    
    
    @starmile83 I watched zuckerberg introduce it today--looks interesting!    
    
    
    @CraftTestDummy thinking about it sorta wears me out ;)    
    
    
    @starmile83 you can. That's one of the great features is how you can customize it and add info and photos to fill in    
    
    
    @starmile83 @jimmersallstars my bro is there!!    
    
    
    @WendySparrow sweet pea fo sho    
    
    
    Social Network Faceoff: Facebook vs. Twitter vs. Google+ [Lifehacker Faceoff] http://pulse.me/s/1OgLD     
    
    
    Make Your Own RFID Shielded Wallet To Foil ID Thieves [DIY] http://pulse.me/s/1NWfc     
    
    
    Freebie | Harmony in Autumn Printable http://pulse.me/s/1Rspj     
    
    
    You Want Dishcloths? I Got Your Dishcloths! http://pulse.me/s/1RcKs     
    
    
    Stunning! Inspiration: Hearty Craft http://pulse.me/s/1QWfv     
    
    
    OMG!-- New Sizzix and Vintaj DecoEmboss Folders and DecoEtch Dies http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fsNCagVhpDA&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    My name is Paula, and I'm a Mean Mother http://nblo.gs/nDdUq     
    
    
    My name is Paula, and I'm a Mean Mother http://nblo.gs/nDdZm     
    
    
    How-To: Make a Spider Loom for Lace http://pulse.me/s/1RX1p     
    
    
    Open Hardware Silver Pendant http://pulse.me/s/1Sc31     
    
    
    Inspiration: Vintage scissors as decor http://pulse.me/s/1SjYV     
    
    
    It's true, I'm a mean mom! http://hartofthemountain.blogspot.com/2011/09/my-name-is-paula-and-im-mean-mother.html …    
    
    
    Recreating Iconic Scenes with Legos http://pulse.me/s/1TkgE     
    
    
    DIY Capacitive Touch Brush Stylus http://pulse.me/s/1TGaF     
    
    
    Step Up Your Fall Swagger: Half-Off 60+ Jeffrey Campbell Stunners! http://pulse.me/s/1OiWS     
    
    
    diy project: vintage-style book dustcovers http://pulse.me/s/1TSs2     
    
    
    How-To: Fall Handbag with Fabric Flowers http://pulse.me/s/1U2EO     
    
    
    Salsa! And Free Canning Labels http://pulse.me/s/1UzKj     
    
    
    Flip Over a Muffin Tin to Make Delicious Ready-to-Fill Cookie Bowls [Food Hacks] http://pulse.me/s/1W0uG     
    
    
    Bunker App Is a Super Simple Project Tracker and Invoice Generator for Freelancers [Web Apps] http://pulse.me/s/1Vfun     
    
    
    Gigantic, Creeptastic Lego Victorian http://pulse.me/s/1VcHF     
    
    
    .: In the beginning... http://thesewingedwords.blogspot.com/2011/09/in-beginning.html?spref=tw …    
    
    
    It's Friday, it's Friday ...(now doing a little dance!)    
    
    
    #ldsconf tuned in late-Where's Pres Monson?    
    
    
    @michael_crook thanks    
    
    
    @SisterDiane I can relate    
    
    
    'Arrested Development' Returning To TV http://pulse.me/s/1Ynsy     
    
    
    Halloween Party Ideas http://pulse.me/s/1YgII     
    
    
    Flaming Foliage Candleholders http://pulse.me/s/1YLNr     
    
    
    Heading to the Martha Stewart Show (again!) for Craft Week http://pulse.me/s/1YDKM     
    
    
    Tote from Trash Bag http://pulse.me/s/1ZkrC     
    
    
    Math Monday: Flexible Stick Structures http://pulse.me/s/1ZfMq     
    
    
    Color in the Kitchen: Kitchen Bars that Pop! http://pulse.me/s/1ZkoC     
    
    
    Tips & Tricks | Using Patterned Paper http://pulse.me/s/1ZR8v     
    
    
    Sew in Love {Wooden Spools + Weddings} http://pulse.me/s/1ZvnF     
    
    
    Super Simple Cards with Terri O http://lnkd.in/9G2rDH     
    
    
    living in: far from heaven http://pulse.me/s/20kXH     
    
    
    Pantone Christmas Ball Ornaments http://pulse.me/s/20djs     
    
    
    InBook iPhone Charging Docks http://pulse.me/s/1Zi4W     
    
    
    Zero to Maker: CNC Class Comes Full Circle http://pulse.me/s/20Ja3     
    
    
    Want this!! Volkswagen Buggy Up Concept http://pulse.me/s/20bqI     
    
    
    Another Beautiful Alexander McQueen Show Walks in Paris http://pulse.me/s/20Fsl     
    
    
    DIY Wedding Emergency Kit http://pulse.me/s/23etn     
    
    
    Antiquaria Rubber Stamp Wedding Invitations http://pulse.me/s/236jh     
    
    
    DIY Paper Flower Centerpieces http://pulse.me/s/23aBT     
    
    
    A pendant with a secret http://pulse.me/s/25MRN     
    
    
    Ditching DRM could reduce piracy, prices, inconvenience http://pulse.me/s/265Y0     
    
    
    Look at This Incredible $2,300, 30,000 Brick Lego Imperial Hangar [Lego] http://pulse.me/s/25Rif     
    
    
    Autumnal http://pulse.me/s/25qev     
    
    
    trook http://pulse.me/s/26s8a     
    
    
    How-To: Glow in The Dark Corset T-Shirt http://pulse.me/s/268q0     
    
    
    iPhone 4 Passive Amplifier Case http://pulse.me/s/27B9l     
    
    
    Project: Dye Your Own Yarn, Naturally http://pulse.me/s/26LmI     
    
    
    How-To: Felt Vintage-Style Christmas Baubles http://pulse.me/s/26Dnl     
    
    
    Apple-Cranberry Pocket Pies | Williams-Sonoma http://pulse.me/s/27EGk     
    
    
    Inspiration: Clock gears and cogs mandala http://pulse.me/s/278Ns     
    
    
    New Apple Software Adds Features to Older Phones http://pulse.me/s/299iD     
    
    
    Stock Up on Peanut Butter Now Before Prices Get Ridiculous [Saving Money] http://pulse.me/s/274DS     
    
    
    PhotoFast iFlashDrive now available to pre-order in US and UK http://pulse.me/s/2a7Xl     
    
    
    Autumn Bird's Nest Fascinator http://pulse.me/s/28Mt4     
    
    
    @kosairnurse first dye it with gold dye with @ritdye then get some gold floral spray (like spray paint, but flexible) and spray it    
    
    
    @kosairnurse you could also try the glitter spray after dying it. What kind of fabric is the dress?    
    
    
    @kosairnurse I LOVE the dr who idea!!!    
    
    
    Getting ready for a day on the show floor at Sourhern women's show in Orlando- @CraftyChica is in booth behind us-gonna be a blast!    
    
    
    Start Something New with Sharpie http://pulse.me/s/2c722     
    
    
    Candle Chandelier Tutorial http://pulse.me/s/2c5mD     
    
    
    Tutorial: Sturdy, semi-see-through templates for quilting, sewing and applique http://pulse.me/s/2buYW     
    
    
    100 Years of Fashion in Under Two Minutes http://pulse.me/s/2bCpE     
    
    
    How-To: Weave a Hula Hoop Rug http://pulse.me/s/2e4Nr     
    
    
    Free pattern and tute: Matryoshka ornament http://pulse.me/s/2iwNR     
    
    
    Tip: Get Better Artwork Photos http://pulse.me/s/2hVqP     
    
    
    A close look at pateh http://pulse.me/s/2mJnu     
    
    
    How Science Can Teach You to Easily Spot a Liar [Video] http://pulse.me/s/2n4LF     
    
    
    How to Fix Internet Embarrassments and Improve Your Online Reputation [How To] http://pulse.me/s/2mhrd     
    
    
    The Do’s And Don’ts Of Infographic Design http://pulse.me/s/2dzlj     
    
    
    Glitzy Lucite Bangle http://pulse.me/s/2nsIf     
    
    
    Brill: How-To: Make a Sewn Leaf Garland http://pulse.me/s/2mNUA     
    
    
    Tip: Printing on Ribbon http://pulse.me/s/2pj6b     
    
    
    Eye candy alert: Dimensional flowers http://pulse.me/s/2p26s     
    
    
    Store Appliances in Old Pillowcases to Avoid Dust Buildup [Clever Uses] http://pulse.me/s/2pnQg     
    
    
    How-To: Make a Robot Halloween Costume http://pulse.me/s/2pa2O     
    
    
    Stunning Lace Spider Webs http://pulse.me/s/2oXjs     
    
    
    Steampunk Controller is all Brass and Burl http://pulse.me/s/2p1zS     
    
    
    Score! One red-ish puffy vest for Marty McFly. #Halloween    
    
    
    @SUEDEsays lmk if the google image search works-good luck!    
    
    
    @thehumming_bird luv ur guts!!!    
    
    
    @thehumming_bird and seriously--you aren't following me?  Wat up wid dat?    
    
    
    Interesting perspective. http://lnkd.in/qg82dc     
    
    
    What a great idea--Hoop Storage Bags http://pulse.me/s/2rtdm     
    
    
    