197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rbn6Y     
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/rbn6Z     
    
    
    What prizes do you offer for your business plan competitions? http://ow.ly/rbn66     
    
    
    Scaling a Platform for Device-Agnostic Web Interfaces: Michael Mullany, CEO of Sencha http://ow.ly/rbn73     
    
    
    1M/1M: An Incubator for Startups That Accelerators Dont Want http://ow.ly/rdGXI     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rdGXK     
    
    
    What if an idea doesnt work or a product doesnt sell? http://ow.ly/rdGXM     
    
    
    Pandora Competing with iTunes Radio http://ow.ly/rdGXN     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Maya Ray, BPO venture servicing doctors' offices http://ow.ly/rdGXO     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits?: Gartner forecasts the SaaS market to grow 19.5% over th... http://bit.ly/1cvayMg     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits?: Gartner forecasts the SaaS market ... http://bit.ly/IoLFcf  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rdGXQ     
    
    
    December 5 – Next 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited... http://bit.ly/1eA8qER  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What is an example of a great startup executive summary? http://ow.ly/rdGXa     
    
    
    In Silicon Valley, Partying Like It’s 1999 Once More http://nyti.ms/1jGPwfS     
    
    
    My answer to Are deals like SnapChat, Instagram and Tumblr confusing young entrepreneurs, and distracting them from … http://qr.ae/GAKKR     
    
    
    @HarvardBiz: Corporate Innovation: Must Read from Harvard Business Review http://ow.ly/rdGXS     
    
    
    My answer to Will SnapChat implode? http://qr.ae/GAsMa     
    
    
    Much Ado About Bitcoin http://nyti.ms/1eyEN6M     
    
    
    Is it ethical for an accelerator to charge money from Startups for mentoring? http://ow.ly/rdGXT     
    
    
    Helping SaaS Companies Grow Through Revenue Sharing: Avangate CEO Carl Theobald http://ow.ly/rdGXV     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rdGXY     
    
    
    What do you think are good ideas for improving your neighbourhood as a social entrepreneur? http://ow.ly/rdGXi     
    
    
    Outsourcing: LN Balaji, President of ITC Infotech http://ow.ly/rdGY5     
    
    
    The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid http://ow.ly/rdGY8     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 2): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/IkUwLv     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/1bpFTDn  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $40 Million: iCIMS CEO Colin Day http://ow.ly/rdGYa     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rdGYb     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : Can 1M/1M Help Me Raise Money? http://ow.ly/rdGYc     
    
    
    How do you get people to respect you and want to work with you, in Silicon Valley? http://ow.ly/rdGYe     
    
    
    Are there any examples of strtups successfully scaling a free-lance based model (e.g. consulting, programming etc)? http://ow.ly/rdGYf     
    
    
    What are the best books on the subject of women entrepreneurs? http://ow.ly/rfQJV     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rfQJ9     
    
    
    Salesforce Says Grow First, Profit Later: Gartner’s recent forecasts for worldwide enterprise software peg the... http://bit.ly/1ihKjzT     
    
    
    Salesforce Says Grow First, Profit Later: Gartner’s recent forecasts for worldwide enterp... http://bit.ly/1ihKjzX  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    When is the right time to join @1Mby1M? http://ow.ly/rfQJX     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits? http://ow.ly/rfQJZ     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @OrangeScape OK Let me say it, generic PaaS is not disruptive http://ow.ly/rfQJd     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rfQK0     
    
    
    One Million By One Million - In Photos: 100 Best Websites For Entrepreneurs  http://onforb.es/HKUexc  via @forbes    
    
    
    @GalyaBelyaeva @SepidehN Thank you!    
    
    
    What's preventing India's youth from Entrepreneurship? http://ow.ly/rfQK2     
    
    
    Now on Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rfQMG     
    
    
    Seed Capital Series: Inventus Capital Partners: 1M/1M ambassador Irina Patterson talks with Parag Dhol of Inve... http://bit.ly/1czZL3x     
    
    
    Seed Capital Series: Inventus Capital Partners: 1M/1M ambassador Irina Patterson talks wi... http://bit.ly/1aYAiSF  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How Automation is Helping Investors With Trading Strategies http://ow.ly/rfQNY     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/InxMdC  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Framed Ivory Films http://ow.ly/rfQK4     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rfQK6     
    
    
    My answer to Do economists think we're in a bubble right now (Nov 2013)? http://qr.ae/GCP4M     
    
    
    What is the best way to bootstrap a company while working a full-time job? http://ow.ly/rfQK8     
    
    
    Seed Capital Using Crowdfunding: Korstiaan Zandvliet, CEO of Symbid, Amsterdam http://ow.ly/rfQK9     
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/rfQKa     
    
    
    Which incubators and accelerators don't take equity in the startups they invest in? http://ow.ly/rfQKd     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $12M+, Getting Ready to Raise Money: MindTouch CEO Aaron Fulkerson http://ow.ly/rfQKe     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rfQKg     
    
    
    How will @1Mby1M scale without losing quality? http://ow.ly/rfQKh     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck: DudaMobile CEO Itai Sadan http://ow.ly/rfQKi     
    
    
    How do you model an innovation lab within a large corporation? http://ow.ly/rfQKj     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rhGTe     
    
    
    A must read  informative Article for Entrepreneurs on Building the Right Product.Read here http://ow.ly/rhGTf     
    
    
    HP Continues Shifting Toward Enterprise: Gartner’s PC Shipment report for the third quarter this year did not ... http://bit.ly/1eFv7HY     
    
    
    Innovation’s Next Decade: While the world economy continues to look shaky, the technology industry has never l... http://bit.ly/1ikxrZF     
    
    
    HP Continues Shifting Toward Enterprise: Gartner’s PC Shipment report for the third quart... http://bit.ly/1eFv7Yi  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Innovation’s Next Decade: While the world economy continues to look shaky, the technology... http://bit.ly/1eFv6Ul  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    My company is funded by Angels. How can @1Mby1M help me? http://ow.ly/rhGTg     
    
    
    Salesforce Says Grow First, Profit Later http://ow.ly/rhGYc     
    
    
    What prizes do you offer for your business plan competitions? http://ow.ly/rhGTh     
    
    
    How do you rate or compare accelerators and incubators in India? http://ow.ly/rhGTj     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rhGTm     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 4): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/IqQtNA     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/1buZdz6  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    If I join @1Mby1M, when am I introduced to Angels and VCs? http://ow.ly/rhGTn     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Oishi, a high-end online gift retailer http://ow.ly/rhGTo     
    
    
    Getting Your Game to Players: Keela Robison, VP of GameHouse Distributions http://ow.ly/rhGTq     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rhGTt     
    
    
    @Sramana's Kindle book: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rhGTu     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Mobile and Social: Interview with Alex Bratton, CEO of Lextech http://ow.ly/rhGTv     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rhGTx     
    
    
    @adamscrabble thank you adam :-)    
    
    
    Forbes names 1mby1m in the top 100 websites for entrepreneurs: http://www.forbes.com/pictures/emjl45gkke/one-million-by-one-million/ …    
    
    
    Are there companies that start and run accelerators for corporations? http://ow.ly/rhGTy     
    
    
    Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit http://ow.ly/rhGTz     
    
    
    Seed Capital In India: How To Navigate http://ow.ly/rhGTA     
    
    
    What are the best startup online courses? http://ow.ly/rhGTB     
    
    
    Building a SMS API Company from London: Nexmo CEO Tony Jamous http://ow.ly/rhGTC     
    
    
    Best way new tech start-up CEO to approach & develop mentors? http://ow.ly/rhGTD     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rjs95     
    
    
    Which startups were rejected several times by VCs before getting funded? http://ow.ly/rjs96     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 5): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1jU0a2V     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/1jU0a30  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Love & Startups discussed in @Sramana's new book, Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rjs8I     
    
    
    From New Zealand To Silicon Valley: Victoria Ransoms Wildfire Journey http://ow.ly/rjs98     
    
    
    How One Man Successfully Entered the SAP HANA Platform Eco-System http://ow.ly/rjs9a     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Are Dividends Dead? http://ow.ly/rjs9b     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rjs9c     
    
    
    What are some great 'Bootstrapping with a Paycheck' case studies? http://ow.ly/rjs9d     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Steve Shine, CEO of Actian http://ow.ly/rjs8S     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rjs9f     
    
    
    Building a Conversion Optimization Co from London: Graham Cooke, CEO of Qubit http://ow.ly/rjs9h     
    
    
    What are the best methods of bootstrapping a startup? http://ow.ly/rjs8V     
    
    
    Are deals like SnapChat, Instagram and Tumblr confusing & distracting young entrepreneurs? http://ow.ly/rjs9j     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rjs9k     
    
    
    Collection of @Sramana's essays for Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rjs9l     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Big Data in 2013? http://ow.ly/rjs9m     
    
    
    Does @1Mby1M take equity in the companies it works with? http://ow.ly/rjs9n     
    
    
    Built to Enjoy: Aptify CEO Amith Nagarajan http://ow.ly/rjs9o     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: MIT India http://ow.ly/rjs94     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 1): Girish Rowjee is the CEOof Greytip ... http://bit.ly/IwahiQ     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 1): Girish Rowjee ... http://bit.ly/1bzSVhC  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 6): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/IxlwHL     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/IxlwHN  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 2): Sramana: Did you form a business ou... http://bit.ly/1iry6sn     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 2): Sramana: Did y... http://bit.ly/1iry6bN  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Darjeeling tea http://ow.ly/rlG1T     
    
    
    Splunk’s Stock Rising Despite Growing Losses: According to recent reports, worldwide big data hardware and sof... http://bit.ly/1cMw4ft     
    
    
    Splunk’s Stock Rising Despite Growing Losses: According to recent reports, worldwide big ... http://bit.ly/1cMw6ny  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Women, entrepreneurship may be the answer - check out new book Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rlG1Z     
    
    
    HP Continues Shifting Toward Enterprise http://ow.ly/rlG20     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Online Education / EduTech in 2013? http://ow.ly/rlG21     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rlG22     
    
    
    Thursday, Dec. 5 – 197th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited to the 197th ... http://bit.ly/1ePpbfi     
    
    
    Thursday, Dec. 5 – 197th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are ... http://bit.ly/1isv3Ak  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Which women entrepreneurs have small children and are serious tech entrepreneurs? http://ow.ly/rlG24     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : How Does 1M/1M Help Entrepreneurs Connect With Silicon Valley? http://ow.ly/rlG26     
    
    
    @1mby1m member @nirogam's Startup Success & Niche eCommerce Within Healthcare http://ow.ly/rlG28     
    
    
    Managing Risk: MetricStream Chairman Gunjan Sinha http://ow.ly/rlG2b     
    
    
    My answer to Which Indian IT services companies are also developing products? http://qr.ae/GPNdM     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rlG2c     
    
    
    Glad to see Indian startups like Little Eye Labs & Frrole starting to show up on radar of Silicon Valley companies like Facebook & Twitter.    
    
    
    My answer to Are more women getting into technology? http://qr.ae/GPtPk     
    
    
    My answer to What is the likelihood of a good idea being stolen? http://qr.ae/GPtWX     
    
    
    My answer to Which Indian startups have got acquihired? http://qr.ae/GPtey     
    
    
    Which Indian IT services companies are also developing products? http://ow.ly/rlG2d     
    
    
    My answer to What are the advantages of accelerator programs for startups? http://qr.ae/GPtj8     
    
    
    My answer to What are the core characteristics of a startup accelerator? http://qr.ae/GPtdP     
    
    
    My answer to What have been the top trends in online advertising in 2013? http://qr.ae/GPnTK     
    
    
    My answer to What are the top trends in Online/Mobile gaming in 2013? http://qr.ae/GPnIP     
    
    
    My answer to What have been the top trends in social media in 2013? http://qr.ae/GPnrR     
    
    
    My answer to What have been the top trends in Cloud Computing in 2013? http://qr.ae/GPnsf     
    
    
    My answer to What have been the top trends in e-commerce in 2013? http://qr.ae/GPnCV     
    
    
    Is there a real trend towards 'built to enjoy' businesses? http://ow.ly/rlG4Q     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 7): John Meyer... http://bit.ly/1eQOo9a     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/1eQOo9f  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Venture Capital in India: Age of Reckoning http://ow.ly/rlG2e     
    
    
    Bootstrapping To $1 Million, Then Growing to $40 Million: iContact CEO Ryan Allis: Chapel Hill, North Carolina http://ow.ly/rlG2f     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rlG2g     
    
    
    @Sramana's book for Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid http://ow.ly/rlG2i     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: Black Friday Trends http://ow.ly/rlG2j     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Outsourcing in 2013? http://ow.ly/rlG2l     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 3): Sramana: Did you complete your proj... http://bit.ly/1iuKR5w     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 3): Sramana: Did y... http://bit.ly/1iuKRT1  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/roanO     
    
    
    How Not To Sell Equity Too Cheap, Too Soon @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/roanP     
    
    
    HP Continues Shifting Toward Enterprise http://ow.ly/roanQ     
    
    
    Uber Faces Scalability Hurdles: The advancements in mobile and internet technology have h... http://bit.ly/1k63IiM  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What have been the top trends in online advertising in 2013? http://ow.ly/roanR     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/roanU     
    
    
    What are the top trends in Online/Mobile gaming in 2013? http://ow.ly/roanW     
    
    
    @1Mby1M The Million Dollar Club: Quantifying The 1M/1M Value Equation http://ow.ly/roasW     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Members in Bengal! @souryamohanty @atulstays @aurusnet @nilmonibasak @shopofficein @doubts http://ow.ly/roanX     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Andy Nibley, CEO of Yieldex http://ow.ly/roanY     
    
    
    My answer to What has being a mentor taught you? http://qr.ae/G4I3S     
    
    
    Innovation’s Next Decade http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/11/29/innovations-next-decade/ …    
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/roao0     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Healthcare IT in 2013? http://ow.ly/roao1     
    
    
    Helping Publishers Monetize Premium Ad Inventory: isocket CEO John Ramey http://ow.ly/roao2     
    
    
    Festival of Light, Chartres http://www.fotopedia.com/reporter/stories/x9rQ4V25RCX … via @ReporterHQ    
    
    
    Feminine Feminism Explored In @Sramana's new Entrepreneur Journeys book http://ow.ly/roao5     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Urja brings designers and artisans together http://ow.ly/roao7     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions (Part 1): Shaul Kupe... http://bit.ly/1eUlR2K     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions... http://bit.ly/1eUlPIe  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What have been the top trends in social media in 2013? http://ow.ly/roao8     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/roao9     
    
    
    Learn from the experiences of successful entrepreneurs. Follow @Sramana, @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/roaob     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Mobile computing in 2013? http://ow.ly/roaoc     
    
    
    An SEO-Driven Bootstrapping Success: Benchmark Email CEO Curt Keller http://ow.ly/roaoe     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 4): Sramana: You essentially operated y... http://bit.ly/1iybzdx     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 4): Sramana: You e... http://bit.ly/1eUVVUt  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    100 Best Websites For Entrepreneurs http://ow.ly/rqFRj     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rqFVb     
    
    
    Baidu and Alibaba: The Chinese Dragons Counting on Mobile for Growth: According to recent data released by the... http://bit.ly/1cVCLvL     
    
    
    Baidu and Alibaba: The Chinese Dragons Counting on Mobile for Growth: According to recent... http://bit.ly/1bfSxDi  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video: Does Your PowerPoint Have Power? http://ow.ly/rqFRl     
    
    
    Uber Faces Scalability Hurdles http://ow.ly/rqFS0     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Gangotri to produce fresh drinking water http://ow.ly/rqFS3     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rqFS5     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Cloud Computing in 2013? http://ow.ly/rqFS8     
    
    
    Collection of @Sramana's writings on Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): http://ow.ly/rqFSb     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions (Part 2): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1cXpTWa     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions... http://bit.ly/1cXpUcs  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rqFSj     
    
    
    What have been the top tech trends in 2013? http://ow.ly/rqFSn     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO, Arise Virtual Solutions http://ow.ly/rqFSq     
    
    
    Is @1Mby1M a funding broker? http://ow.ly/rqFSs     
    
    
    Building a Virtual World from Berlin: Smeet CEO Sebastian Funke http://ow.ly/rqFSu     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rqFSw     
    
    
    @1Mby1M The Million Dollar Club: Freshdesk http://ow.ly/rqFSA     
    
    
    What's preventing India's youth from Entrepreneurship? http://ow.ly/rqFSD     
    
    
    Is it better to outsource ecommerce marketing or do it in-house? http://ow.ly/rqFSF     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 5): Sramana: In the early days of your ... http://bit.ly/IQ3qS8     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 5): Sramana: In th... http://bit.ly/1cZqeaQ  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What do you do when you don't trust your co-founder? http://ow.ly/rt3jC     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rt3jD     
    
    
    Online Real Estate Sector Update: According to recent S&P/Case-Shiller Home Price Indices, housing prices in t... http://bit.ly/1d006fX     
    
    
    Online Real Estate Sector Update: According to recent S&P/Case-Shiller Home Price Indices... http://bit.ly/1d006g3  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    When is the right time to join @1Mby1M? http://ow.ly/rt3jE     
    
    
    Baidu and Alibaba: The Chinese Dragons Counting on Mobile for Growth http://ow.ly/rt3jF     
    
    
    New Book – Seed India: How To Navigate The Seed Capital Gap In India: While tremendous interest in entrepreneu... http://bit.ly/1d0zQlv     
    
    
    New Book – Seed India: How To Navigate The Seed Capital Gap In India: While tremendous in... http://bit.ly/1d0zQlz  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rt3jG     
    
    
    197th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 197th FREE online... http://bit.ly/IRmbo1     
    
    
    197th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Toda... http://bit.ly/IRmcZm  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    197th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting NOW, Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 197th ... http://bit.ly/1iCW0RV  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How do you manage your start-up if you don't have a co-founder? http://ow.ly/rt3jH     
    
    
    Now on Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rt3jK     
    
    
    The Past and Future of Recruiting Tech http://ow.ly/rt3jM     
    
    
    A Tablet App from Invention Labs Helps Kids with Speech Disabilities | Xconomy http://www.xconomy.com/san-francisco/2013/12/05/tablet-app-invention-labs-helps-kids-speech-disabilities/ … via @xconomy    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Bioscope media for those in rural India http://ow.ly/rt3jO     
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 5 – Seed India Book Launch: During today’s roundtable, we launched the book Seed In... http://bit.ly/1bkpq1u     
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 5 – Seed India Book Launch: During today’s roundtable, we laun... http://bit.ly/1d1U0eV  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rt3jP     
    
    
    My answer to Why there are few Seed investors in India? http://qr.ae/GMnai     
    
    
    Are there startups that may address our unemployment issues? http://ow.ly/rt3jR     
    
    
    My answer to What is the avialibility of seed capital in India? And how difficult is it to raise? http://qr.ae/GMnZb     
    
    
    Seed Capital: Kae Capital Managing Director Sasha Mirchandani http://ow.ly/rt3jS     
    
    
    How will @1Mby1M scale without losing quality? http://ow.ly/rt3jU     
    
    
    What startups are there in the mental health field? http://ow.ly/rt3jV     
    
    
    How to Sharpen Focus and Own a Market: Imprivata CEO Omar Hussain http://ow.ly/rt3jW     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rt3jY     
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/rt3jZ     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an Online Education Company to $12M: Pluralsight CEO Aaron Skonnard http://ow.ly/rt3k0     
    
    
    Are there any web startups addressing mental illnesses? http://ow.ly/rt3k1     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 6): Sramana: Selling to small businesse... http://bit.ly/IUajlp     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 6): Sramana: Selli... http://bit.ly/1d3Phtf  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rvm5O     
    
    
    My company is funded by Angels. How can @1Mby1M help me? http://ow.ly/rvm5Q     
    
    
    Online Real Estate Sector Update http://ow.ly/rvm5R     
    
    
    Is there such a thing as an Incubator Think Tank? http://ow.ly/rvm5V     
    
    
    New book! Seed India: How To Navigate The Seed Capital Gap In India http://ow.ly/rvm5X     
    
    
    December 12 – 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited to the 198th FREE online... http://bit.ly/1d57Qxp     
    
    
    December 12 – 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited to ... http://bit.ly/1bmSntU  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rvm5Y     
    
    
    My answer to What websites are a good source credible leads to finding entrepreneurs who need funding, people with i… http://qr.ae/GMDcs     
    
    
    @Sramana's Kindle book: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rvm5Z     
    
    
    Concur: A Good Model, But Still No Profits: The latest report by Global Business Travel A... http://bit.ly/IVSxOt  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: AdiShakti solar technology http://ow.ly/rvm61     
    
    
    How Do You Develop Seed Eco-systems Around The World?: In the last five years, there has been a distinct globa... http://bit.ly/1f3IvWy     
    
    
    How Do You Develop Seed Eco-systems Around The World?: In the last five years, there has ... http://bit.ly/1f3IwK4  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How Do You Develop Seed Eco-systems Around The World? http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/06/how-do-you-develop-seed-eco-systems-around-the-world/ …    
    
    
    My answer to Most geographies in the world have little or no seed capital eco-systems. What are some practical ways … http://qr.ae/GMQyb     
    
    
    @isanzc end March/early April.    
    
    
    From Mannarakoil To CEO Of Global Scholar: Kal Ramans Journey http://ow.ly/rvm62     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rvm63     
    
    
    Seed Capital In India: How To Navigate http://ow.ly/rvm66     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Mobile & Social: Intrview with Kelly Passey, EVP of Bus. & Prduct Developmnt @ Access Develpment http://ow.ly/rvm68     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rvm69     
    
    
    Future of Indian entrepreneurship discussed in new book Seed India http://ow.ly/rvm6a     
    
    
    Future of Entrepreneurship in India http://ow.ly/rvm6c     
    
    
    If I join @1Mby1M, when am I introduced to Angels and VCs? http://ow.ly/rvm6d     
    
    
    Is there such a thing as an Entrepreneur Support Group? http://ow.ly/rvm6e     
    
    
    Revolutionizing the Limousine Service: http://Limos.com  CEO T.J. Clark http://ow.ly/rvm6f     
    
    
    What movies teach you how to build and run a successful company? http://ow.ly/rvm6g     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 7): Sramana: When did you bring a produ... http://bit.ly/1bpbPWW     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee (Part 7): Sramana: When ... http://bit.ly/1bpbSlw  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rxu81     
    
    
    Seed India book discusses how to navigate seed capital http://ow.ly/rxu82     
    
    
    Love & Startups discussed in @Sramana's new book, Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rxu7q     
    
    
    Building a Cross-Border e-Commerce Success Selling to Russia: Bay.Ru CEO Aaron Block http://ow.ly/rxu83     
    
    
    Vision 2020: Education Will Change Beyond Recognition http://ow.ly/rxu85     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Are Dividends Dead? http://ow.ly/rxu87     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rxu88     
    
    
    New Seed India book discusses why there are so few seed investors in India http://ow.ly/rxu89     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions... http://bit.ly/1jy41W2  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Now, with mSapience - Optimize your day while on the go! Download it here http://ow.ly/rxu8a     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 1): Mike B... http://bit.ly/1jy5pYV  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Prem Uppaluru, Co-Founder, CEO and President of Transera http://ow.ly/rxu8b     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rxu8c     
    
    
    Using Facebook For Lead Generation: Underground Elephant CEO Jason Kulpa http://ow.ly/rxu8e     
    
    
    What is the best way to negotiate the valuation for the seed fund?? http://ow.ly/rxu8f     
    
    
    How much time should entrepreneurs spend reading books or online materials? http://ow.ly/rxu8g     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rxu8h     
    
    
    Collection of @Sramana's essays for Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rxu8i     
    
    
    What prizes do you offer for your business plan competitions?? http://ow.ly/rxu8j     
    
    
    Does @1Mby1M take equity in the companies it works with? http://ow.ly/rxu8k     
    
    
    Bootstrapping A 130 Million VAR In The Midwest: Ahead CEO Dan Adamany http://ow.ly/rxu8l     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Lucid education http://ow.ly/rxu80     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 1): Sangeeta (San) Baner... http://bit.ly/1dbXU50     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 1):... http://bit.ly/1dbXU56  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/ryyOc     
    
    
    Venture Capital in India discussed in @sramanas new Seed India book http://ow.ly/ryyOd     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video: Whose Silicon Valley Party Is The Coolest? http://ow.ly/ryyOe     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $7M with DIY Business Apps: Andrew Gazdecki, CEO of Bizness Apps http://ow.ly/ryyOf     
    
    
    Smartest entrepreneurial advice you have ever received? http://ow.ly/ryyOg     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How Zoho Overcame the Capital Gap http://ow.ly/ryyOh     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/ryyOi     
    
    
    @sramanas Seed India book discusses bootstrapping with a paycheck http://ow.ly/ryyOj     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Cloud Computing: Mike Toplisek, EVP, Product and Marketing, EarthLink http://ow.ly/ryyOk     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/ryyOm     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 2): Sramana Mitra: In terms of ... http://bit.ly/1iNrSmV     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 2): Sraman... http://bit.ly/1faz1J2  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Building a Fat Startup: From Israel to Silicon Valley, Qwilt CEO Alon Maors Journey http://ow.ly/ryyOn     
    
    
    What are the best startup online courses? http://ow.ly/ryyOo     
    
    
    Healthcare IT: Making Good Progress http://ow.ly/ryyOp     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/ryyOq     
    
    
    Reducing Infant Entrepreneur Mortality discussed in The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) book http://ow.ly/ryyOr     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions (Part 6): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1kr5Cux     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions... http://bit.ly/1kr5CuD  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Renaissance, rejuvenating heritage buildings via a hospitality enterprise http://ow.ly/ryyOt     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: 10 Inventions to Watch For: CNN features a fun and thought-provo... http://bit.ly/1bv6E7C  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Have a question on business strategy? Like 1Mby1M here and Ask Sramana a question : http://ow.ly/ryyOu     
    
    
    Building a Robust Business with Eugene (Oregon) Angel Investors: Jake Weatherly, CEO of SheerId http://ow.ly/ryyOv     
    
    
    How do I look for startup advisors in the Bay Area? http://ow.ly/ryyOb     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 2): Sramana Mitra: You l... http://bit.ly/1kryvGX     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 2):... http://bit.ly/1kryxP1  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Doctor At Hand http://ow.ly/rzzcW     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rzzcX     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Techieworks, Gurgaon, India: Techieworks provides remote technical support se... http://bit.ly/1krShCi     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions (Part 7): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1jD1Bpb     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Techieworks, Gurgaon, India: Techieworks provides remote... http://bit.ly/1krShSF  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Interview with Shaul Kuper, CEO of Destiny Solutions... http://bit.ly/1jD1BFD  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Women, entrepreneurship may be the answer - check out new book Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rzzcY     
    
    
    Concur: A Good Model, But Still No Profits http://ow.ly/rzzd0     
    
    
    Moving to Silicon Valley discussed in new Seed India book http://ow.ly/rzzd2     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rzzd3     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 3): Sraman... http://bit.ly/1jE3guM  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Which LA tech startups are doing more than $10m in revenue?? http://ow.ly/rzzd6     
    
    
    @1Mby1M The Million Dollar Club: Conclusion http://ow.ly/rzzd7     
    
    
    How to Fund Indian Start-Ups - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/12/how-to-fund-indian-start-ups/ …    
    
    
    Thursday, Dec. 12 – 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited to the 198th FREE ... http://bit.ly/1dhZPFl     
    
    
    Thursday, Dec. 12 – 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invit... http://bit.ly/1dhZPFp  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    1M/1M: An Incubator for Startups That Accelerators Dont Want http://ow.ly/rzzd8     
    
    
    Child Entrepreneur David Koretz, Now CEO Of Mykonos Software http://ow.ly/rzzdb     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rzzdd     
    
    
    198th 1M/1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs December 12 8:00am PST …http://strategyroundtable-dec1213.eventbrite.com/?aff=estw     
    
    
    Last day of free download promo on Seed India book: http://www.amazon.com/Seed-India-Navigate-Entrepreneur-Journeys-ebook/dp/B00GS9QRUE/ …    
    
    
    What are the top blogs / online media sites catering to entrepreneurs in France? http://ow.ly/rzzde     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with services discussed in @sramanas Seed India book http://ow.ly/rzzdf     
    
    
    The Myth About Seed Funding @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rzzdh     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review on How To Fund Indian Startups: http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/12/how-to-fund-indian-start-ups/ …    
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @OrangeScape Supply-side Long tail will explode the SaaS Market further! http://ow.ly/rzzcv     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to 8 Million from Brittany  Digitaleo CEO Jocelyn Denis http://ow.ly/rzzdi     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rzzdj     
    
    
    Is Your Region Full Of Savvy Entrepreneurs? @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rzzdl     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: Black Friday Trends http://ow.ly/rzzdo     
    
    
    Why haven't we figured out any feasible alternative to capitalism yet? http://ow.ly/rzzdp     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 3): Sramana Mitra: When ... http://bit.ly/J9LrGm     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 3):... http://bit.ly/J9LrGo  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rC4x2     
    
    
    Still No Sign of Revenue at Snapchat: A recent report published by researcher Ovum, Social Messaging 2014 Tren... http://bit.ly/1jHK7Ip     
    
    
    Still No Sign of Revenue at Snapchat: A recent report published by researcher Ovum, Socia... http://bit.ly/1jHK7Iv  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How many 1-on-1 private sessions with Sramana in a year as a @1Mby1M Premium member? http://ow.ly/rC4x6     
    
    
    MercadoLibre Continues to Deliver Strong Growth http://ow.ly/rC4x9     
    
    
    What are some good examples of entrepreneurial scrappiness? http://ow.ly/rC4xc     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How To Fund Indian Start-Ups: Harvard Business Review has published Sramana Mitra’s p... http://bit.ly/1kvK0gx     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How To Fund Indian Start-Ups: Harvard Business Review has publis... http://bit.ly/1kvK0gC  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rC4xe     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 4): Sramana Mitra: Let’s say on... http://bit.ly/J1Te8q     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 4): Sraman... http://bit.ly/1jIMj2o  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    New book! Seed India: How To Navigate The Seed Capital Gap In India http://ow.ly/rC4xh     
    
    
    5 Mompreneurs say you CAN do it all in new book, Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rC4xl     
    
    
    Success Story of an Indian College Drop Out http://ow.ly/rC4xn     
    
    
    @nandinizg Thank you, Nandini.    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Sandy Steier, CEO of 1010data http://ow.ly/rC4xs     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rC4xv     
    
    
    Future of Indian entrepreneurship discussed in new book Seed India http://ow.ly/rC4xz     
    
    
    CEO Transition, Founder Liquidity, and More: Bill Daniel, CEO AllWebLeads http://ow.ly/rC4xD     
    
    
    @1Mby1M The Million Dollar Club: Sapience Analytics http://ow.ly/rC4xF     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Elixar animation http://ow.ly/rC4xI     
    
    
    Would a Series A investor rather see $1M in revenue or 1M users? http://ow.ly/rC4xL     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rC4xN     
    
    
    Sramana Mitra's 197th 1M1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs December 5 20131205 1600 1: http://youtu.be/dz_9A9pi0JU?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video: Are You Too Old For Silicon Valley? http://ow.ly/rC4xQ     
    
    
    Is it possible to have a decent crowdfunding platform in India like Kickstarter? http://ow.ly/rC4xT     
    
    
    How To Build A Profitable Gaming Company: Kenny Rosenblatt, CEO of Arkadium http://ow.ly/rC4xV     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 4): Sramana Mitra: You h... http://bit.ly/J4wjti     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 4):... http://bit.ly/J4wjJy  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Stop Making These Startup Mistakes http://ow.ly/rEtOL     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rEtON     
    
    
    Online Travel Sites Growing as Usual: According to the U.S. Commerce Department, international travel to the c... http://bit.ly/1jMDNPR     
    
    
    Online Travel Sites Growing as Usual: According to the U.S. Commerce Department, internat... http://bit.ly/1jMDPHk  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Collection of @Sramana's writings on Kindle: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): http://ow.ly/rEtOP     
    
    
    Still No Sign of Revenue at Snapchat http://ow.ly/rEtOQ     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: NCTV, non-cricket sports television http://ow.ly/rEtOR     
    
    
    197th Roundtable Recording On December 5, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to the recording here:
___ http://bit.ly/1dpL2bz     
    
    
    197th Roundtable Recording On December 5, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to ... http://bit.ly/1bDxV8f  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thursday, December 12 – 198th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs... http://bit.ly/1bDzVNG  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rEtOT     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 5): Sramana Mitra: What is the ... http://bit.ly/1iWMNnB     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads (Part 5): Sraman... http://bit.ly/1fk04lk  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Seed India book discusses how to navigate seed capital http://ow.ly/rEtOW     
    
    
    My answer to What is your take on Snapchat? http://qr.ae/GgCxM     
    
    
    My answer to What newsletters should I subscribe in New Year? http://qr.ae/GgCqy     
    
    
    Strong Entrepreneurs vs. Weak Entrepreneurs @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rEtOZ     
    
    
    Should the US Government create incentives for corporationss to bring off-shore cash back into the US? http://ow.ly/rEtP1     
    
    
    Launching and Scaling a Security Startup During an Out-of-Favor Time: HyTrust President Eric Chiu http://ow.ly/rEtP3     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rEtP5     
    
    
    New Seed India book discusses why there are so few seed investors in India http://ow.ly/rEtP7     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with David DeWolf, CEO of 3Pillar Global http://ow.ly/rEtPa     
    
    
    @Harvardbiz Incubators need to stop pretending that funding = success http://ow.ly/rEtPb     
    
    
    Acquiring Deadpool Technology to Leapfrog a Services Company into Products: Canara CEO Steve Cotton http://ow.ly/rEtPd     
    
    
    198th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 12 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rEtPe     
    
    
    How To Access Silicon Valleys Tribal Knowledge @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rEtPi     
    
    
    Is too much liquidity in the angel capital market good or bad? http://ow.ly/rEtPk     
    
    
    Are there any incubators that accept a founder who has hired an out-sourced development team? http://ow.ly/rEtPm     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 5): Sramana Mitra: What ... http://bit.ly/1iZ5N50     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 5):... http://bit.ly/1iZ5KGn  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Privacy Debate May Hurt Palantir: According to a report by research firm MarketsandMarkets, the global big dat... http://bit.ly/JhzaQ9     
    
    
    Privacy Debate May Hurt Palantir: According to a report by research firm MarketsandMarket... http://bit.ly/JhzazH  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rHxUb     
    
    
    198th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 198th FREE online... http://bit.ly/1j03gHF     
    
    
    198th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Toda... http://bit.ly/1j03gY5  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    198th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting NOW, Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 198th ... http://bit.ly/1jSD7bF  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Venture Capital in India discussed in @sramanas new Seed India book http://ow.ly/rHxWv     
    
    
    The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) book: Can crowdfunding can solve the startup capital gap? http://ow.ly/rHxWA     
    
    
    @CharisseHiggins Sure. I haven't seen anything. Pls email us through support@1mby1m.com.    
    
    
    @HighRoadsCEO @HighRoadsHR My pleasure.    
    
    
    [Book review] Seed India: Bootstrap your products with paycheck and services http://yourstory.com/2013/12/book-review-seed-india/ … via @YourStorydotin    
    
    
    A Framework For The Next Rev Of Capitalism http://ow.ly/rHxWE     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Harvard Medical School, India http://ow.ly/rHxWM     
    
    
    My answer to How much truth is there to the belief that VC's do not work with investment bankers for capital raises? http://qr.ae/GOPjC     
    
    
    Great discussion on HBR: How to Fund Indian Start-Ups - @HarvardBiz http://blogs.hbr.org/2013/12/how-to-fund-indian-start-ups/ …    
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 12 – Spotlight on Kae Capital, India: During today’s roundtable, we saw a couple of... http://bit.ly/JjC0Ei     
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 12 – Spotlight on Kae Capital, India: During today’s roundtabl... http://bit.ly/1dunXoo  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rHxWR     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: Ten Lessons We Have Learned: These days, everyone seems to be a startup mentor. Whether th... http://bit.ly/JjUPqX     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: Ten Lessons We Have Learned: These days, everyone seems to be a start... http://bit.ly/JjUODj  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    @sramanas Seed India book discusses bootstrapping with a paycheck http://ow.ly/rHxWU     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/12/mentoring-startups-ten-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    Seed Capital: Independent Investor, Mukund Mohan http://ow.ly/rHxWZ     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video: Whose Silicon Valley Party Is The Coolest? http://ow.ly/rHxX3     
    
    
    How do you evaluate an incubator? http://ow.ly/rHxX6     
    
    
    A Successful Husband-Wife Team: Moonfruit Cofounders Wendy Tan White and Joe White http://ow.ly/rHxXb     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rHxXe     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: 10 Lessons We Have Learned at 1Mby1M http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/12/mentoring-startups-ten-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    Why confidentiality is overrated http://ow.ly/rHxXg     
    
    
    Trends And Opportunities In Cloud Computing: Jim Burleigh, CEO Of Cloud9 http://ow.ly/rHxXm     
    
    
    What are avoidable mistakes that first-time entrepreneurs make repeatedly? http://ow.ly/rHxXp     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 6): Sramana Mitra: In 20... http://bit.ly/Jln8VS     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 6):... http://bit.ly/1dvNnSl  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rJ1Ks     
    
    
    Athenahealth Counting on Product Launches: According to a recent report, US EMR Market Outlook to 2017, the el... http://bit.ly/1jWi7AY     
    
    
    Athenahealth Counting on Product Launches: According to a recent report, US EMR Market Ou... http://bit.ly/1jWi7Rg  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/rJ1Kt     
    
    
    Privacy Debate May Hurt Palantir http://ow.ly/rJ1Ku     
    
    
    What are the biggest obstacles for developing an incubator? http://ow.ly/rJ1Kw     
    
    
    Startups, is confidentiality overrated? http://ow.ly/rJ1Kx     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rJ1Kz     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups at 1Mby1M: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/12/mentoring-startups-ten-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    December 19 – 199th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited to the 199th FREE ... http://bit.ly/JfI93T     
    
    
    December 19 – 199th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invit... http://bit.ly/JfI9kb  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How To Become An Agent Of Change In Your Region @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rJ1KA     
    
    
    "Sramana - thank you for drawing attention to this. We are not talking enough about the acute…" — Sharad Sharma http://disq.us/8gm0wo     
    
    
    "I can vouch for this as the truth! Thank you Sramana for writing this out in plain speak." — Arjun http://disq.us/8gm0y3     
    
    
    "This is so true. I can imagine someone with an idea of "snapchat","twitter","instagram" going to…" — kanwar http://disq.us/8gm0y7     
    
    
    "Thanks for this very practical advise. I cofounded Melio Systems two years back with "Bootstrap…" — Venkatramani B http://disq.us/8gm0yg     
    
    
    "You have summed it up beautifully. I myself  have gone through this experience. Good advise at…" — Pankaj Chauhan http://disq.us/8gm0yo     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Doctor For Sure http://ow.ly/rJ1KC     
    
    
    Bootstrapping E-Commerce to 16 Million: Valerie Holstein, CEO of http://Cableorganizer.com  http://ow.ly/rJ1KD     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rJ1KG     
    
    
    I am self-funded. I am not looking for investors. What could @1Mby1M possibly offer me? http://ow.ly/rJ1KH     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Mobile & Social: Intrview w/ Nick LeCuyer,VP of Strategy & Distribution at Westrn Union Digital http://ow.ly/rJ1KI     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rJ1KJ     
    
    
    Do Coworking spaces have aspirations of turning themselves into full-fledged incubators? http://ow.ly/rJ1KM     
    
    
    Seed India: Bootstrap your products with paycheck and services http://ow.ly/rJ1KN     
    
    
    @Harvardbiz How to Fund Indian Start-Ups http://ow.ly/rJ1KO     
    
    
    Which incubators and accelerators do NOT take equity in the startups they invest in? http://ow.ly/rJ1KQ     
    
    
    Building the Worlds First Mobile Rewards Network: Brian Wong, 20-Year-Old Founder of Kiip http://ow.ly/rJ1KR     
    
    
    I didn't get into an incubator, should I mention that to other accelerators? http://ow.ly/rJ1KS     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 7): Sramana Mitra: How d... http://bit.ly/1dzbWhm     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 7):... http://bit.ly/1dzbYFT  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rLcMm     
    
    
    I'm a co-founder in two startups teams, should I choose one or wait? http://ow.ly/rLcMo     
    
    
    What is good mentoring? http://ow.ly/rLcMq     
    
    
    How To Build A Strong IP Portfolio: rPost CEO Zafar Khan http://ow.ly/rLcMr     
    
    
    Venture Capital Aid Should Not Be Sole Focus Of Start-ups http://ow.ly/rLcMs     
    
    
    Zohos Sridhar Vembu discusses bootstrapping in new book The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rLcMt     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rLcMv     
    
    
    Is an incubator necessary to a first-time entrepreneur's success?? http://ow.ly/rLcMy     
    
    
    Drawing Yourself Into the Scene http://nyti.ms/Jj6nL0     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Constantin Delivanis, CEO of BDNA http://ow.ly/rLcMz     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rLcMB     
    
    
    Cool and Creative Serial Entrepreneurship: 99Designs and DeveloperAuction Co-Founder Matt Mickiewicz http://ow.ly/rLcMC     
    
    
    Who is India's first successful technology "product" entrepreneur? http://ow.ly/rLcME     
    
    
    Which was the first disruptive Internet startup? http://ow.ly/rLcMF     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rLcMG     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Chasing Investors = Distraction from chasing customers http://ow.ly/rLcMH     
    
    
    How are startups in India plugging the seed capital gap?? http://ow.ly/rLcMI     
    
    
    If YCombinator or TechStars reject us, can we then apply at @1Mby1M? http://ow.ly/rLcMJ     
    
    
    Scaling With VARs And OEMs: Nexenta CEO Evan Powell http://ow.ly/rLcMK     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Care healthcare http://ow.ly/rLcMj     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 8): Sramana Mitra: Who r... http://bit.ly/1dCtEk2     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 8):... http://bit.ly/1dCtF7x  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rMWx9     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with services discussed in @sramanas Seed India book http://ow.ly/rMWxa     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Doctor On Wire http://ow.ly/rMWxb     
    
    
    How to evaluate an incubator http://ow.ly/rMWxd     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $6M from Durgapur, West Bengal: Pinnacle CAD CEO Bimal Patwari http://ow.ly/rMWxg     
    
    
    Why there are few Seed investors in India? http://ow.ly/rMWCZ     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 9): Sramana Mitra: Let’s... http://bit.ly/1kO4Nw5     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 9):... http://bit.ly/1kO4NMp  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Green Village http://ow.ly/rN93I     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rN93J     
    
    
    Sramana Mitra's 198th 1M1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs December 12 20131212 1600 1 1: http://youtu.be/w1YhZS8E-ls?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    @1Mby1M The Million Dollar Club: Orangescape http://ow.ly/rN93M     
    
    
    Athenahealth Counting on Product Launches http://ow.ly/rN93N     
    
    
    Are there any startup mentors that work for a startup outside their country on small budgets? http://ow.ly/rN93P     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rN93R     
    
    
    198th Roundtable Recording On December 12, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to the recording here:
___ http://bit.ly/1fyhY3K     
    
    
    198th Roundtable Recording On December 12, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to... http://bit.ly/1fyhY3O  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    The1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: VOZIQ, Washington, D.C.: VOZIQ is a social media analytic... http://bit.ly/1dGqsUw  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thursday, December 19 – 199th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs... http://bit.ly/1fyrio9  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What to read if opening a new start up in Latin America? http://ow.ly/rN93T     
    
    
    How is 1M/1M democratizing management consulting? http://ow.ly/rN93U     
    
    
    My answer to Can we believe in hackatons and their incubator concepts? http://qr.ae/G9Qm2     
    
    
    Adobe Counting on Digital Marketing Growth: In a survey of 253 marketers for U.S.-based companies earning more... http://bit.ly/1kPnuiU     
    
    
        
    
    
    Innovative ways to incubate small biz ideas http://ow.ly/rN93Y     
    
    
    My answer to What lessons have you learned mentoring startups? http://qr.ae/G9ffy     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with $120k Credit Card Debt to $7m Revenue: Scott Skinger, CEO of TrainSignal http://ow.ly/rN940     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rN942     
    
    
    Can you be a successful entrepreneur without having a brand name associated with your name? http://ow.ly/rN943     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/12/mentoring-startups-ten-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    Should I go to Stanford GSB if I want to be an entrepreneur? http://ow.ly/rN944     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How to Fund Indian Start-Ups http://ow.ly/rN945     
    
    
    Indias Flagship Global Product Story: Druva CEO Jaspreet Singh http://ow.ly/rN947     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rN949     
    
    
    5 Mompreneurs say you CAN do it all in new book, Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rN94b     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: 10 Inventions to Watch For http://ow.ly/rN94e     
    
    
    Your one piece of advice to someone starting a web-based company? http://ow.ly/rN94f     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 10): Sramana Mitra: I li... http://bit.ly/1bWsGRb     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA (Part 10)... http://bit.ly/1dIL927  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @OrangeScape 5 Reasons why customers are leaving Lotus http://ow.ly/rPqXb     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rPqXW     
    
    
    Zulily’s Successful IPO: According to the Euromonitor, the North American retail market was worth $3.1 trillio... http://bit.ly/JvA23d     
    
    
    Zulily’s Successful IPO: According to the Euromonitor, the North American retail market w... http://bit.ly/JvA23j  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    If Sramana doesnt have experience & connections in my industry how could she help me? http://ow.ly/rPqXX     
    
    
    Adobe Counting on Digital Marketing Growth http://ow.ly/rPqY1     
    
    
    How can top Indian colleges like IITs develop an entrepreneurial culture like at Stanford? http://ow.ly/rPqY4     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rPqY9     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned: Further to my earlier post, Mentoring Startups... http://bit.ly/1kcYpkC     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned: Further to my earlier pos... http://bit.ly/JwAb6o  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    If you want to be a successful entrepreneur, best to go to an accelerator or get an MBA? http://ow.ly/rPqYc     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/17/running-a-global-virtual-incubator-10-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    January 9 – 200th Roundtable For Mentoring Startups: Everyone seems to be a startup mentor these days. As Sram... http://bit.ly/1kdmtDS     
    
    
    January 9 – 200th Roundtable For Mentoring Startups: Everyone seems to be a startup mento... http://bit.ly/1kdmtUe  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Series A Crunch: Revenue vs. Equity @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rPqYf     
    
    
    BonitaSoft CEO Miguel Valdés-Faura on building a global software company from France http://ow.ly/rPqYi     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Brian Bulkowski and Srini Srinivasan, Co-founders of Aerospike http://ow.ly/rPqYm     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rPqYp     
    
    
    Ready to quit your 9-to-5 job to run a startup but feeling burnt out?? http://ow.ly/rPqYt     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to Exit in Israel: Eli Sasson, Founder of Minicom http://ow.ly/rPqYx     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : The Other 99% http://ow.ly/rPqYA     
    
    
    Vision India 2020: a series of startup ideas http://ow.ly/rPqYE     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/17/running-a-global-virtual-incubator-10-lessons-we-have-learned/ …    
    
    
    When is the time to start your own venture if you have an idea but are still in school? http://ow.ly/rPqYK     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rPqYM     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://ow.ly/rPqYP     
    
    
    What is the solution to the youth unemployment problem? http://ow.ly/rPqYV     
    
    
    Long Journey to a $435M Exit: Bytemobile Cofounders Chris Koopmans and Nicholas Stavrakos http://ow.ly/rPqZ0     
    
    
    Scaling an SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 1): Nick Mehta is the CEO of Ga... http://bit.ly/1fDJbCh     
    
    
    Scaling an SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 1): Nick M... http://bit.ly/1jgZ86f  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Is Entrepreneurship Just About the Exit? http://ow.ly/rRVu5     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rRVu6     
    
    
    OpenTable Prepares to Battle Apple: Recently, the restaurant technology market made news when none other than ... http://bit.ly/1kUBAja     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Omninox, Gainesville, Florida: Omninox develops interactive, mobile study gui... http://bit.ly/1kUBAzq     
    
    
    OpenTable Prepares to Battle Apple: Recently, the restaurant technology market made news ... http://bit.ly/1kgOOcw  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Omninox, Gainesville, Florida: Omninox develops interact... http://bit.ly/1kgOPNt  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    10 avoidable mistakes first-time entrepreneurs make repeatedly http://ow.ly/rRVu7     
    
    
    Zulilys Successful IPO http://ow.ly/rRVu9     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Thakur, quality packaged foods http://ow.ly/rRVua     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rRVub     
    
    
    How do you rate or compare accelerators and incubators in India? How do you pick the good ones? http://ow.ly/rRVuc     
    
    
    Thursday, Dec. 19 – 199th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are... http://bit.ly/JCjPcu  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Kindle edition: The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid http://ow.ly/rRVud     
    
    
    Which Berlin tech startups are doing more than $10m in revenue?? http://ow.ly/rRVue     
    
    
    Niche E-Commerce to $5M: Dan Dillon, CEO of http://CleanItSupply.com  http://ow.ly/rRVuf     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rRVug     
    
    
    Are business schools setting up entrepreneurs to fail? http://ow.ly/rRVuh     
    
    
    Outsourcing: Million-Dollar Freelancer: A1 Future CEO Srish Agrawal, Kolkata, India http://ow.ly/rRVui     
    
    
    @Harvardbiz Why do incubators pretend that Funding = Success? http://ow.ly/rRVuk     
    
    
    A Serial Entrepreneurs Journey: Zscaler CEO Jay Chaudhry http://ow.ly/rRVum     
    
    
    199th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 19 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rRVuo     
    
    
    @1Mby1M tells entrepreneurs what they NEED to hear, not WANT to hear: http://ow.ly/rRVup     
    
    
    Want to be an entrepreneur, but have no background in business? http://ow.ly/rRVur     
    
    
    Did you face a major failure and how did you rebound from it?? http://ow.ly/rRVuv     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 2): Sramana: I think it is great... http://bit.ly/1kXgzEg     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 2): Sramana... http://bit.ly/1kkH09I  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Is the current market full of bad ideas?? http://ow.ly/rUh4j     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rUh4l     
    
    
    Sramanas contacts in LinkedIn don't relate to my business? Is @1Mby1M not the right program for me? http://ow.ly/rUh4n     
    
    
    OpenTable Prepares to Battle Apple http://ow.ly/rUh4p     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rUh4r     
    
    
    Electronic Arts Preparing for Next-Gen Console Market: Gaming aficionados have been waiting for this holiday s... http://bit.ly/1dRUtB3     
    
    
    199th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 199th FREE online... http://bit.ly/1dRUtRl     
    
    
    Electronic Arts Preparing for Next-Gen Console Market: Gaming aficionados have been waiti... http://bit.ly/1dRUvZw  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting In 30 Minutes: Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Toda... http://bit.ly/1c40qfx  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    199th Roundtable For Entrepreneurs Starting NOW, Live Tweeting By @1Mby1M: Today’s 199th ... http://bit.ly/1kmaXWM  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    How can we implement a Startup Initiative within our college? http://ow.ly/rUh4t     
    
    
    Pre-Incubation For Sustained Deal Flow @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rUh4w     
    
    
    Startup Success With Crowd Sourced Software Testing and 99Tests http://ow.ly/rUh4z     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Maya Ray, BPO venture servicing doctors' offices http://ow.ly/rUh4C     
    
    
    @khan_io contact irina@1mby1m.com to learn how we work.    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rUh4E     
    
    
    Who are the most successful entrepreneurs with Iranian roots? http://ow.ly/rUh4H     
    
    
    Seed Capital: IndiaCo Investor Rahul Patwardhan http://ow.ly/rUh4L     
    
    
    Democracy + Capitalism on Harvard Business Review: http://ow.ly/rUh4N     
    
    
    Where can you find many authors/enterpreneurs/CEOs sharing their experiences in one place? http://ow.ly/rUh4P     
    
    
    A Successful Corporate Innovation Effort in HealthcareIT: Bruce Johnson, CEO of GHX http://ow.ly/rUh4R     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rUh4U     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://ow.ly/rUh4Y     
    
    
    How Not To Finance Your Company: TalkPoint CEO Nick Balletta http://ow.ly/rUh4Z     
    
    
    How do bootstrapped companies hire talent? http://ow.ly/rUh52     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 3): Sramana: What came after you... http://bit.ly/1joj4UU     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 3): Sramana... http://bit.ly/1fKuKwa  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rWt5b     
    
    
    For-profit Education Sector Still Under Scrutiny: The for-profit education sector was in the news recently whe... http://bit.ly/1kp6yT1     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Fossa LLC, Chicago, Illinois: Fossa LLC is dedicated to delivering the most c... http://bit.ly/1l0FJlu     
    
    
    For-profit Education Sector Still Under Scrutiny: The for-profit education sector was in ... http://bit.ly/1kp6yT8  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: Fossa LLC, Chicago, Illinois: Fossa LLC is dedicated to ... http://bit.ly/1l0FKWM  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Moving to Silicon Valley discussed in new Seed India book http://ow.ly/rWt5d     
    
    
    Electronic Arts Preparing for Next-Gen Console Market http://ow.ly/rWt5e     
    
    
    Square IPO in 2014? http://ow.ly/rWt5g     
    
    
    I'm in finance but want to run my own tech startup. What steps should I take? http://ow.ly/rWt5h     
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 19 – Final One For 2013: During today’s roundtable, we had representation from Texa... http://bit.ly/1dWoQGk     
    
    
    Roundtable Recap: December 19 – Final One For 2013: During today’s roundtable, we had rep... http://bit.ly/1dWoPlS  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs On January 9th: Entrepreneurs are invi... http://bit.ly/1kpX9ut  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rWt5k     
    
    
    Case-study based learning and mentoring is working very well for @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rWt5l     
    
    
    Caught between choosing motherhood and your ambitions? Read Feminine Feminism. http://femgineer.com/2013/12/caught-between-choosing-motherhood-and-your-ambitions-read-feminine-feminism/ …    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Framed Ivory Films http://ow.ly/rWt5m     
    
    
        
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rWt5p     
    
    
    The other 99% (entrepreneurs) http://ow.ly/rWt5q     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Mobile and Social: Interview with Khris Loux, CEO of Echo http://ow.ly/rWt5r     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rWt5s     
    
    
        
    
    
    The Problems with Incubators, and How to Solve Them http://ow.ly/rWt5w     
    
    
    Key differences between @1Mby1M and YCombinator/startup accelerators? http://ow.ly/rWt5x     
    
    
    How has mentoring made a difference in your professional life? http://ow.ly/rWt5y     
    
    
    Equity Financing from Customers: Modernizing Medicine CEO Daniel Cane, Boca Raton, Florida http://ow.ly/rWt5z     
    
    
    Using a convertible note for a securities based crowdfunding campaign? http://ow.ly/rWt5B     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 4): Sramana: Which firm did you ... http://bit.ly/1cjCdDn     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 4): Sramana... http://bit.ly/1cjCdDu  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rYxme     
    
    
    Can you start a company while holding on to your job?? http://ow.ly/rYxmf     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Deal Radar 2013: Finish Line PDS, Hudson, New Hampshire: Finish Line PDS is a product development se... http://bit.ly/1jszpI7     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Deal Radar 2013: Finish Line PDS, Hudson, New Hampshire: Finish Line PDS is a p... http://bit.ly/1fOa7iF  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    @1Mby1M's bootstrapped, lean, capital-efficient startup methodology vs. financing media hype http://ow.ly/rYxmg     
    
    
    Startup, Survival, Scaling: Kareo CEO Dan Rodrigues http://ow.ly/rYxmh     
    
    
    Caught between choosing motherhood and your ambitions? http://ow.ly/rYxmj     
    
    
    How is 1M/1M democratizing entrepreneurship education? http://ow.ly/rYxmk     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rYxml     
    
    
    The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid? http://ow.ly/rYxmn     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @IndusNetTech "Understanding CMMI levels (in plain english!)" http://ow.ly/rYxlQ     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Josh Rogers, SVP of Data Integration Business at Syncsort http://ow.ly/rYxmo     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rYxmr     
    
    
    Moving a Technology Company from Israel to America: Perfecto Mobile CEO Eran Yaniv http://ow.ly/rYxms     
    
    
    Is Pinterest overvalued? http://ow.ly/rYxmt     
    
    
    What are the most interesting enterprise software startups right now? http://ow.ly/rYxmu     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rYxmv     
    
    
    Running A Global Virtual Incubator: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://ow.ly/rYxmw     
    
    
    ?What are some interesting startups developing on SAP HANA?? http://ow.ly/rYxmx     
    
    
    Love & Startups discussed in @Sramana's new book, Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/rYxm4     
    
    
    Playing with Love to $10M: SeekingArrangement Founder Brandon Wade http://ow.ly/rYxmy     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Oishi, a high-end online gift retailer http://ow.ly/rYxmd     
    
    
        
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 5): Sramana... http://bit.ly/1fQAxAi  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rZo8E     
    
    
    What would be the min amt of capital required to start an incubator and best way to raise it? http://ow.ly/rZo8G     
    
    
    @Harvardbiz How to Fund Indian Start-Ups http://ow.ly/rZo8H     
    
    
    Built to Enjoy in Utah: Jana Francis, Founder, http://Steals.com  http://ow.ly/rZo8I     
    
    
    Is it a good idea to be an entrepreneur when you have only a computer, a degree and $0.00? http://ow.ly/rZo8J     
    
    
    Lesson #4: There are no silver bullets, building a business is a marathon, not a sprint http://ow.ly/rZo8K     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rZo8L     
    
    
    What Startups in Chennai have crossed $5M in annual revenue? http://ow.ly/rZo8M     
    
    
    Does working long hours make an employee seem valuable to their employer? ? Find More here http://ow.ly/rZo8O     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Cloud Computing: Steve Singh, CEO of Concur http://ow.ly/rZo8P     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rZo8R     
    
    
    Moving a Tech Co from Israel to America: Perfecto Mobile CEO Eran Yaniv http://ow.ly/rZo8T     
    
    
    Which Boston tech startups are doing more than $10m in revenue? http://ow.ly/rZo8U     
    
    
    Five Mompreneurs Say You Can Do It All! http://ow.ly/rZo8V     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rZo8X     
    
    
    Vikrant Mathur: Why Joining 1M/1M Was The Best $1,000 I Ever Spent @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/rZo8Y     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: MIT India http://ow.ly/rZo8Z     
    
    
    @Harvardbiz Why do incubators fail? http://ow.ly/rZo90     
    
    
    Successfully Navigating a Slow-Growth Healthcare IT Industry for 10 Yrs: Stan Nowak, CEO of Silverlink http://ow.ly/rZo91     
    
    
    Where can I find a business mentor in the UK who can help turn my ideas into reality?? http://ow.ly/rZo8C     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 6): Sramana: Thought leadership ... http://bit.ly/196tYEQ     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 6): Sramana... http://bit.ly/1996sdE  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Darjeeling tea http://ow.ly/s0gZQ     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/s0gZT     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: enMarkit, Singapore: enMarkit is a social engagement and business intelligenc... http://bit.ly/196XPgm     
    
    
    The 1M/1M Incubation Radar 2013: enMarkit, Singapore: enMarkit is a social engagement and... http://bit.ly/196XN8d  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    1M/1M Incubator-in-a-Box for corporate incubation, intrapreneurship, and internal innovation http://ow.ly/s0gZU     
    
    
    For-profit Education Sector Still Under Scrutiny http://ow.ly/s0gZW     
    
    
    How much to get a pitch deck developed? http://ow.ly/s0gZX     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/s0gZY     
    
    
    How do you get by if you're a one-man startup and don't want a 9-5 job?? http://ow.ly/s0gZZ     
    
    
    My answer to What are some introductory level articles to understand Big Data? http://qr.ae/GVCXl     
    
    
    Accenture Continues to Grow Through Acquisitions: According to market researcher, Source Information Survey, t... http://bit.ly/1cNpdRp     
    
    
    Accenture Continues to Grow Through Acquisitions: According to market researcher, Source ... http://bit.ly/1crxC21  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Lesson #5: Strategy and execution are what really drive success for entrepreneurs http://ow.ly/s0h00     
    
    
    Before you Pitch an Investor, Pitch Here http://ow.ly/s0h01     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA http://ow.ly/s0h03     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/s0h04     
    
    
    ?What are the top blogs/online media sites catering to entrepreneurs in Germany?? http://ow.ly/s0h06     
    
    
    Is there need for educating young entrepreneurs? http://ow.ly/s0h07     
    
    
    CableOrganizers Valerie Holstein on building her venture in The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) book http://ow.ly/s0h08     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @Yathes.com, an exclusive gift registry portal for all occasions located in Chennai http://ow.ly/s0gZv     
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $12M+, Getting Ready to Raise Money: MindTouch CEO Aaron Fulkerson http://ow.ly/s0h09     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/s0h0a     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : How Does 1M/1M Democratize Management Consulting? http://ow.ly/s0h0b     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: 10 Inventions to Watch For http://ow.ly/s0h0d     
    
    
    Why is India's e-commerce industry growing so slowly? http://ow.ly/s0h0e     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 7): Sramana: There are larger co... http://bit.ly/19atKg1     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta (Part 7): Sramana... http://bit.ly/19cvCIf  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Xoom Focuses on International Expansion: According to the World Bank, India is the largest market for inward r... http://bit.ly/1ldSLMy     
    
    
    Xoom Focuses on International Expansion: According to the World Bank, India is the larges... http://bit.ly/1kDOrsA  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 1): Paras Chopra is the fou... http://bit.ly/1kEVrpe     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 1): Pa... http://bit.ly/1leQzEw  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Can Hulu Replicate The Success of Netflix?: Over the last year, online streaming player, Hulu, has toyed with ... http://bit.ly/1cxMPyM     
    
    
    Can Hulu Replicate The Success of Netflix?: Over the last year, online streaming player, ... http://bit.ly/1cReF3U  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    French culture: Bleak chic | The Economist http://econ.st/Jy3tSP     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 2): Sramana: When did you g... http://bit.ly/1cT0pHU     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 2): Sr... http://bit.ly/1cT0pHX  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
     Looking for startup accelerator that is looking for great idea that is still in development? http://ow.ly/s3WVI     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/s3WVL     
    
    
    Disney Counting on International Growth: According to a PwC report on global entertainment, the consumer deman... http://bit.ly/1jL0mXw     
    
    
    Disney Counting on International Growth: According to a PwC report on global entertainmen... http://bit.ly/1jL0mXy  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Small Cash Cows Can Lead To Big Successes http://ow.ly/s3WVO     
    
    
    Can Hulu Replicate The Success of Netflix? http://ow.ly/s3WVS     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/s3WVW     
    
    
    Can we create the NEXT BIG thing from India?? http://ow.ly/s3WW0     
    
    
    The Wolf of Wall Street Movie Review (2013) | Roger Ebert http://www.rogerebert.com/reviews/the-wolf-of-wall-street-2013 …    
    
    
    Lesson #6: Entrepreneurs are obsessed with financing http://ow.ly/s3WW3     
    
    
    Stimulating Startups http://ow.ly/s3WW6     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Urja brings designers and artisans together http://ow.ly/s3WW9     
    
    
    The Future of Education: 10 Trends To Watch: It is that time of the year when we tend to pause and reflect. Wh... http://bit.ly/19k2vja     
    
    
    The Future of Education: 10 Trends To Watch: It is that time of the year when we tend to ... http://bit.ly/19l0ars  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    The Future of Education: 10 Trends To Watch http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/26/the-future-of-education-10-trends-to-watch/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    @wizardofid Urja is a concept from my vision india book    
    
    
        
    
    
    Best practices for marketing a YouTube channel?? http://ow.ly/s3WWf     
    
    
    Seed Capital: Independent Investor Rehan yar Khan http://ow.ly/s3WWi     
    
    
    How Not To Waste Your Money On Useless Things @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/s3WWl     
    
    
    What is it like to work in Silicon Valley and not be from Harvard, MIT or Stanford? http://ow.ly/s3WWn     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee http://ow.ly/s3WWp     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/s3WWq     
    
    
    Sramana Mitra's 199th 1M1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs December 19 20131219 1600 13: http://youtu.be/qlzpk_MjpB8?a  via @YouTube    
    
    
    1M/1M Incubator-in-a-Box for corporate incubation in platform ecosystems http://ow.ly/s3WWr     
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck: DudaMobile CEO Itai Sadan http://ow.ly/s3WWs     
    
    
    What are some significant tech startups in Russia? http://ow.ly/s3WWt     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 3): Sramana: Obviously you ... http://bit.ly/1cDNgrn     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 3): Sr... http://bit.ly/1cVo9ep  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    @sramanas Seed India book discusses bootstrapping with a paycheck http://ow.ly/s5rL9     
    
    
    Disney Counting on International Growth http://ow.ly/s5rLa     
    
    
    Why does it seem like every major social issue is caused by greed or monetary gain? http://ow.ly/s5rLc     
    
    
    199th Roundtable Recording On December 19, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to the recording here:
___ http://bit.ly/1jPrZib     
    
    
    199th Roundtable Recording On December 19, 2013: In case you missed it, you can listen to... http://bit.ly/1jPrZie  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Can startup accelerators/incubators be an alternative to MBA degrees? http://ow.ly/s5rLe     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/s5rLf     
    
    
    Comment by Dan Stewart on an answer to What are the top entrepreneurship networks both in USA and globally? http://qr.ae/Gq1yi     
    
    
    Lesson #7: Positioning is poorly understood by most entrepreneurs. @1Mby1M can help! http://ow.ly/s5rLg     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Gangotri to produce fresh drinking water http://ow.ly/s5rLh     
    
    
    Getting Your Game to Players: Keela Robison, VP of GameHouse Distributions http://ow.ly/s5rLi     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/s5rLj     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Fortune at the Middle of the Pyramid: http://ow.ly/s5rLk     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Mobile and Social: Interview with Oliver Bussmann, CIO of SAP http://ow.ly/s5rLn     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Jan 09 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/s5rLp     
    
    
    ?What is Narendra Modi's plan to tackle the massive water crisis coming to India?? http://ow.ly/s5rLq     
    
    
    Should You Move To Silicon Valley? Administradores Brazil: http://ow.ly/s5rLr     
    
    
    How One Entrepreneur Can Create a Big Shift for Your Incubator @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/s5rLs     
    
    
    What incubation efforts are under way at large tech companies with platform ecosystems? http://ow.ly/s5rLu     
    
    
    Building a SMS API Company from London: Nexmo CEO Tony Jamous http://ow.ly/s5rLv     
    
    
    Most promising Finance startups? http://ow.ly/s5rLw     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 3): Sramana: Did you build ... http://bit.ly/1cXRZPr     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 3): Sr... http://bit.ly/1cXRZPA  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on January 9 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/s6OMK     
    
    
    Examples of transformative leaders? http://ow.ly/s6OMM     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : Testimonials http://ow.ly/s6OMO     
    
    
    Niche E-Commerce in Textbooks: ClassBook CEO Tony Pfister http://ow.ly/s6OMQ     
    
    
    Lesson #8: Except for places like Silicon Valley, NYC, Boston, seed capital eco-systems are very week. http://ow.ly/s6OMT     
    
    
    *200th* @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Startups Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s6OMU     
    
    
    How do you foster a culture of innovation in a large company?? http://ow.ly/s6OMV     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @OrangeScape Amidst the developer noise, PaaS signals for growth http://ow.ly/s6OMs     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Seth Redmore, VP of Product Management at Lexalytics http://ow.ly/s6OMX     
    
    
    Join us for our milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s6OMY     
    
    
    Internet Advertising Pioneer: Kevin OConnor, Founder of DoubleClick and FindTheBest http://ow.ly/s6OMZ     
    
    
    How do you model an innovation lab within a large corporation?? http://ow.ly/s6ON1     
    
    
    Which companies are offering, like Google, a 20% free time to their staff?? http://ow.ly/s6ON3     
    
    
    Milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/s6ON4     
    
    
    How Not To Waste Your Money On Useless Things @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/s6ON5     
    
    
    ?Which tech companies are running Intrapreneurship programs?? http://ow.ly/s6ON6     
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/s6ON8     
    
    
    Optimizing Websites With Machine Learning: BloomReach CEO Raj De Datta http://ow.ly/s6ON9     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Bioscope media for those in rural India http://ow.ly/s6OMJ     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 4): Sramana: What timeframe... http://bit.ly/1jW1I1R     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 4): Sr... http://bit.ly/1jW1Ka0  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/s7FTE     
    
    
    ?Solopreneurs: What strategies do you use to grow your businesses?? http://ow.ly/s7FTF     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How to Fund Indian Start-Ups http://ow.ly/s7FTG     
    
    
    Connecting The Censored Internet: AnchorFree CEO David Gorodyansky, Mountain View, CA http://ow.ly/s7FTH     
    
    
    The biggest differences between the Internet in 2010 and the Internet in 2013?? http://ow.ly/s7FTJ     
    
    
    Lesson #9: Some entrepreneurs give up, even good ones. Entrepreneurship is not for everyone. http://ow.ly/s7FTK     
    
    
    Come pitch your business at our big 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable! Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s7FTL     
    
    
    Why did RedBus.in founders make only about 15% of the entire deal?? http://ow.ly/s7FTM     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Cloud Computing: David Guthrie, CTO of PGi http://ow.ly/s7FTN     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on January 9 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/s7FTO     
    
    
    Having Fun At The Cusp Of Technology And Entertainment: Phunware CEO Alan Knitowski http://ow.ly/s7FTP     
    
    
    Most innovative and lesser known startups?? http://ow.ly/s7FTQ     
    
    
    Love and Startups http://ow.ly/s7FTR     
    
    
    Join us for our milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s7FTS     
    
    
    I am going to try my luck with YCombinator or TechStars and if I am rejected there, can I then apply at @1Mby1M? http://ow.ly/s7FTT     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: AdiShakti solar technology http://ow.ly/s7FTU     
    
    
    How Do You Connect Deeply To Silicon Valley? @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/s7FTV     
    
    
    Built to Enjoy: Aptify CEO Amith Nagarajan http://ow.ly/s7FTX     
    
    
    What Big Data startups have crossed $5M in revenue?? http://ow.ly/s7FTD     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 6): Sramana: It sounds like... http://bit.ly/1d2ndF7     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 6): Sr... http://bit.ly/1h86GGA  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Lucid education http://ow.ly/s8zzY     
    
    
    Check out our big 200th @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/s8zA0     
    
    
    Oracle Focuses on Digital Marketing: According to a Gartner report, by the year 2016, a majority of the enterp... http://bit.ly/1d2MTl1     
    
    
    Oracle Focuses on Digital Marketing: According to a Gartner report, by the year 2016, a m... http://bit.ly/1d2MU8D  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Distributed Capitalism on Harvard Business Review: http://ow.ly/s8zA2     
    
    
        
    
    
    Is it possible to plan your way to become a millionaire?? http://ow.ly/s8zA7     
    
    
    *200th* @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Startups Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s8zA8     
    
    
    200th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs On Jan. 9th: Entrepreneurs are invited to join us for our m... http://bit.ly/19BNlJj     
    
    
    200th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs On Jan. 9th: Entrepreneurs are invited... http://bit.ly/19BNlJt  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Best social media marketing course for beginners?? http://ow.ly/s8zA9     
    
    
    Lesson #10: Intellectual honesty matters. Equal opportunity doesnt mean equal outcome. http://ow.ly/s8zAa     
    
    
        
    
    
    Authors as Entrepreneurs: Bella Andre, Hugh Howey, Jasinda Wilder http://ow.ly/s8zAd     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on January 9 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/s8zAf     
    
    
    Which incubators and accelerators don't take equity in the startups they invest in?? http://ow.ly/s8zAg     
    
    
    How can I get a great advisory board if I don´t live in the US/Sillicon Valley? http://ow.ly/s8zAi     
    
    
    The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs) book discusses how big companies can support startups http://ow.ly/s8zAj     
    
    
    200th 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs On Jan. 9th http://www.sramanamitra.com/2013/12/30/200th-1m1m-mentoring-roundtable-for-entrepreneurs-on-jan-9th/ …    
    
    
    Indias Earliest Product Entrepreneur: FACT CEO Arvind Agarwalla http://ow.ly/s8zAk     
    
    
    Join us for our milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/s8zAl     
    
    
    Incubator Lesson #1: Reach and Scalability http://ow.ly/s8zAm     
    
    
    Catching Up On Readings: 10 Inventions to Watch For http://ow.ly/s8zAn     
    
    
    ?How are startups in India plugging the seed capital gap?? http://ow.ly/s8zAo     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 7): Sramana: What are your ... http://bit.ly/1d5r30n     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra (Part 7): Sr... http://bit.ly/1cT0Max  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    *200th* @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Startups Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/sakht     
    
    
        
    
    
    Oracle Focuses on Digital Marketing http://ow.ly/sakhv     
    
    
    Are there any incubators in India run by smart people like Paul Graham?? http://ow.ly/sakhw     
    
    
    Come pitch your business at our big 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable! Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/sakhx     
    
    
    Best way for a new tech start-up CEO to approach & develop mentors in the funding & start-up community? http://ow.ly/sakhy     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: Customers = Validation, Revenue, Cash, Valuation, Fundability http://ow.ly/sakhz     
    
    
    Should you move to Silicon Valley? http://ow.ly/sakhA     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Dr. Saed Syad, Chief Data Scientist at AdTheorent http://ow.ly/sakhC     
    
    
    Check out our big 200th @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/sakhE     
    
    
        
    
    
    Building a VC-Funded Tech Co. from Upstate NY: Sinclair Schuller, CEO of Apprenda http://ow.ly/sakhH     
    
    
    How To Leverage 1M/1M Programming Through Local Meetups @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/sakhI     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Renaissance, rejuvenating heritage buildings via a hospitality enterprise http://ow.ly/sakhJ     
    
    
    What companies have started through bootstrapping? http://ow.ly/sakhL     
    
    
    200th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on January 9 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/sakhM     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : How Does 1M/1M Democratize Management Consulting? http://ow.ly/sakhN     
    
    
    Which NYC tech startups are doing more than $10 million in revenue? http://ow.ly/sakhO     
    
    
    Solving Problems in Healthcare IT for 2 Decades: American Well CEO Ido Schoenberg http://ow.ly/sakhQ     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 1): Varun Shoor is the... http://bit.ly/1cWQBBY     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 1... http://bit.ly/1cWQDcU  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 2): Sramana: When did ... http://bit.ly/1d0fqgd     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 2... http://bit.ly/1dbUpKv  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What have been the top trends in e-commerce in 2013? http://ow.ly/scpRE     
    
    
    Milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/scpRF     
    
    
    @Sramana's Entrepreneur Journeys book: Feminine Feminism http://ow.ly/scpRG     
    
    
    Oracle Focuses on Digital Marketing http://ow.ly/scpRH     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @IndusNetTech "Why web designers must go mobile first?" http://ow.ly/scpR5     
    
    
    Check out our big 200th @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/scpRJ     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in Cloud Computing in 2013? http://ow.ly/scpRK     
    
    
    @Sramana discusses the Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid in new book: http://ow.ly/scpRL     
    
    
    Talented Women: Please Do Not Quit. http://ow.ly/scpRM     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Doctor At Hand http://ow.ly/scpRO     
    
    
    *200th* @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Startups Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/scpRP     
    
    
        
    
    
    Seed Capital From Angel Investors: Jason Stoffer, Principal at Maveron http://ow.ly/scpRS     
    
    
    How To Navigate the Seed Capital Gap in India http://ow.ly/scpRT     
    
    
    What are the top trends in Online/Mobile gaming in 2013? http://ow.ly/scpRU     
    
    
    Solo Founder, Bootstrapping to $7 Million in India: Wingify CEO Paras Chopra http://ow.ly/scpRV     
    
    
    Come pitch your business at our big 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable! Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/scpRW     
    
    
    Mentoring Startups: 10 Lessons We Have Learned http://ow.ly/scpRX     
    
    
    Scaling a SaaS Company in a Competitive Space: Gainsight CEO Nick Mehta http://ow.ly/scpS1     
    
    
    What have been the top trends in online advertising in 2013? http://ow.ly/scpS2     
    
    
        
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 3... http://bit.ly/1dfq5yF  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Join us for our milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/senT7     
    
    
        
    
    
    Abundant Venture Capital Powers Glassdoor: According to recent reports by the Bureau of L... http://bit.ly/1dfRv7t  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Venture Capital in India discussed in @sramanas new Seed India book http://ow.ly/senT8     
    
    
    Oracle Focuses on Digital Marketing http://ow.ly/senTa     
    
    
    What are the top entrepreneurship networks (organizations/clubs)? http://ow.ly/senTc     
    
    
    What are the core characteristics of a startup accelerator? http://ow.ly/senTg     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 1): This is a wonderful s... http://bit.ly/19PGVTN     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 1): ... http://bit.ly/19St56r  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Come pitch your business at our big 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable! Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/senTh     
    
    
    Why haven't too many IT services entrepreneurs become angel investors in India? http://ow.ly/senTj     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Elixar animation http://ow.ly/senTm     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Jim Donohue, Chief Product Officer, Cengage Learning... http://bit.ly/1kh19Qj  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapping with a Paycheck in India: Sangeeta Banerjee, CEO of ApartmentADDA http://ow.ly/senTp     
    
    
        
    
    
    Lesson #5: Strategy and execution are what really drive success for entrepreneurs http://ow.ly/senTu     
    
    
        
    
    
    Milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/senTw     
    
    
    What are the advantages of accelerator programs for startups? http://ow.ly/senTx     
    
    
    Internships at One Million by One Million (1Mby1M). http://bit.ly/16RHos1  via @Letsintern    
    
    
    2014 1M/1M Internships: Geo-Specific Social Media Marketing: Students, as you are gearing up to apply for 2014... http://bit.ly/1lagzUt     
    
    
    2014 1M/1M Internships: Geo-Specific Social Media Marketing: Students, as you are gearing... http://bit.ly/19RzlIj  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    A Tablet App from Invention Labs Helps Kids with Speech Disabilities http://ow.ly/senTy     
    
    
    Lesson #7: Positioning is poorly understood by most entrepreneurs. @1Mby1M can help! http://ow.ly/senTz     
    
    
    Which Indian startups have got acquihired? http://ow.ly/senTB     
    
    
    Bootstrapping a SaaS Company in India: Greytip CEO Girish Rowjee http://ow.ly/senTC     
    
    
    What is the likelihood of a good idea being stolen? http://ow.ly/senTF     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 4): Sramana: Let’s dri... http://bit.ly/19SfZCV     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 4... http://bit.ly/19SfZCZ  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    *200th* @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable For Startups Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/sgdb2     
    
    
    Are more women getting into technology? http://ow.ly/sgdb3     
    
    
    The Myth About Seed Funding @1Mby1M http://ow.ly/sgdb6     
    
    
    Capital-Efficient Customer Acquisition, Company Building: ReTargeter CEO Arjun Dev Arora http://ow.ly/sgdb8     
    
    
    Harvard Business Review: How To Fund Indian Startups http://ow.ly/sgdb9     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video: Does Your PowerPoint Have Power? http://ow.ly/sgdbb     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 2): Sramana: Okay. Let’s ... http://bit.ly/1e5ka0H     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 2): ... http://bit.ly/1leYpko  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Check out our big 200th @1Mby1M Mentoring Roundtable! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/sgdbc     
    
    
    Which Indian IT services companies are also developing products? http://ow.ly/sgdbd     
    
    
    RT@1M1M Premium Company @Yathes.com, an exclusive gift registry portal for all occasions located in Chennai http://ow.ly/sgdar     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Jim Donohue, Chief Product Officer, Cengage Learning (Part 2): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1i5hmDG     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Jim Donohue, Chief Product Officer, Cengage Learning... http://bit.ly/1i5hoeM  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Big Data: Interview with Mike Byers, CEO of HighRoads http://ow.ly/sgdbe     
    
    
    Come pitch your business at our big 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable! Jan. 9 8 AM PST http://ow.ly/sgdbg     
    
    
        
    
    
    What has being a mentor taught you? http://ow.ly/sgdbj     
    
    
    Why are there few Seed investors in India? http://ow.ly/sgdbk     
    
    
    Milestone 200th @1Mby1M Roundtable For Entrepreneurs! Jan. 9 11 AM EST http://ow.ly/sgdbm     
    
    
    Feminine Feminism book, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/sgdbn     
    
    
    What is the avialibility of seed capital in India & how difficult is it to raise? http://ow.ly/sgdbo     
    
    
    Incubator Lesson #2: Inclusive vs. Exclusive http://ow.ly/sgdbp     
    
    
    Gaps in Analytics: Jon Kondo, CEO of Host Analytics http://ow.ly/sgdbq     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: NCTV, non-cricket sports television http://ow.ly/sgdb1     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 5): Sramana: Did you d... http://bit.ly/1i6D22l     
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 5... http://bit.ly/1i6D3TX  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 3): Sramana: Were you bri... http://bit.ly/1lnpORs     
    
    
    Bootstrapping an App to $10 Million in Revenue: Christophe Bach, CEO of TextMe (Part 3): ... http://bit.ly/1i7wQXV  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Jim Donohue, Chief Product Officer, Cengage Learning (Part 3): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/1dnB2y4     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Online Education: Jim Donohue, Chief Product Officer, Cengage Learning... http://bit.ly/1loGjN9  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    My answer to What are Sramana Mitra's views on the future of startups in Kolkata? http://qr.ae/hX0FH     
    
    
        
    
    
    Bootstrapped Journey of a Child Entrepreneur in India: Varun Shoor, CEO of Kayako (Part 6... http://bit.ly/1ltBfab  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Harvard Medical School, India http://ow.ly/sime4     
    
    
        
    
    
    MongoDB Aims For $10 Billion Valuation: The worldwide database market is estimated to be worth $30 billion and... http://bit.ly/1eeAYCs     
    
    
    MongoDB Aims For $10 Billion Valuation: The worldwide database market is estimated to be ... http://bit.ly/1eeAZ9A  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Why confidentiality is overrated http://ow.ly/sime7     
    
    
    Abundant Venture Capital Powers Glassdoor http://ow.ly/sime9     
    
    
    Subscribe to 1M1MRoundtables channel on YouTube http://ow.ly/simeb     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rbn6Y     
    
    
    New Book - Feminine Feminism, "Talented Women, Please Do NOT Quit" http://ow.ly/rbn6Z     
    
    
    What prizes do you offer for your business plan competitions? http://ow.ly/rbn66     
    
    
    Scaling a Platform for Device-Agnostic Web Interfaces: Michael Mullany, CEO of Sencha http://ow.ly/rbn73     
    
    
    1M/1M: An Incubator for Startups That Accelerators Dont Want http://ow.ly/rdGXI     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 10 AM CST : http://ow.ly/rdGXK     
    
    
    What if an idea doesnt work or a product doesnt sell? http://ow.ly/rdGXM     
    
    
    Pandora Competing with iTunes Radio http://ow.ly/rdGXN     
    
    
    Vision India 2020 idea: Maya Ray, BPO venture servicing doctors' offices http://ow.ly/rdGXO     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits?: Gartner forecasts the SaaS market to grow 19.5% over th... http://bit.ly/1cvayMg     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits?: Gartner forecasts the SaaS market ... http://bit.ly/IoLFcf  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 9:30 PM IST : http://ow.ly/rdGXQ     
    
    
    December 5 – Next 1M/1M Mentoring Roundtable For Entrepreneurs: Entrepreneurs are invited... http://bit.ly/1eA8qER  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    What is an example of a great startup executive summary? http://ow.ly/rdGXa     
    
    
    In Silicon Valley, Partying Like It’s 1999 Once More http://nyti.ms/1jGPwfS     
    
    
    My answer to Are deals like SnapChat, Instagram and Tumblr confusing young entrepreneurs, and distracting them from … http://qr.ae/GAKKR     
    
    
    @HarvardBiz: Corporate Innovation: Must Read from Harvard Business Review http://ow.ly/rdGXS     
    
    
    My answer to Will SnapChat implode? http://qr.ae/GAsMa     
    
    
    Much Ado About Bitcoin http://nyti.ms/1eyEN6M     
    
    
    Is it ethical for an accelerator to charge money from Startups for mentoring? http://ow.ly/rdGXT     
    
    
    Helping SaaS Companies Grow Through Revenue Sharing: Avangate CEO Carl Theobald http://ow.ly/rdGXV     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE on Dec 05 11 AM EST : http://ow.ly/rdGXY     
    
    
    What do you think are good ideas for improving your neighbourhood as a social entrepreneur? http://ow.ly/rdGXi     
    
    
    Outsourcing: LN Balaji, President of ITC Infotech http://ow.ly/rdGY5     
    
    
    The Other 99% (Entrepreneurs): Fortune In The Middle Of The Pyramid http://ow.ly/rdGY8     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions (Part 2): Sramana Mi... http://bit.ly/IkUwLv     
    
    
    Thought Leaders in Outsourcing: Interview with John Meyer, CEO of Arise Virtual Solutions... http://bit.ly/1bpFTDn  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    Bootstrapping to $40 Million: iCIMS CEO Colin Day http://ow.ly/rdGYa     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rdGYb     
    
    
    @1Mby1M Video : Can 1M/1M Help Me Raise Money? http://ow.ly/rdGYc     
    
    
    How do you get people to respect you and want to work with you, in Silicon Valley? http://ow.ly/rdGYe     
    
    
    Are there any examples of strtups successfully scaling a free-lance based model (e.g. consulting, programming etc)? http://ow.ly/rdGYf     
    
    
    What are the best books on the subject of women entrepreneurs? http://ow.ly/rfQJV     
    
    
    197th @1Mby1M Roundtable FREE onDec 05 8 AM PST : http://ow.ly/rfQJ9     
    
    
    Salesforce Says Grow First, Profit Later: Gartner’s recent forecasts for worldwide enterprise software peg the... http://bit.ly/1ihKjzT     
    
    
    Salesforce Says Grow First, Profit Later: Gartner’s recent forecasts for worldwide enterp... http://bit.ly/1ihKjzX  via @sramana @1mby1m    
    
    
    When is the right time to join @1Mby1M? http://ow.ly/rfQJX     
    
    
    Workday: High Revenue Growth, but What About Profits? http://ow.ly/rfQJZ     
    
    
    