@dwakabayashi Tx for follow, be sure to check out Susan Rich Talks 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com , lots of marcom/writing chat.    
    
    
    @BrandNg Tx for follow!    
    
    
    @NoGlutenFoods Amazing, isn't it! Tx for follow, pls listen to Rich&GlutenFree Tuesdays, 8 am PT, 11 am ET http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks…Week of May 7, 2012  http://bit.ly/IPSGOq  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @LesleyORice tx for the follow, plz tune into Living the Writing Life, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @timkober  thanks for the follow! Tune into Susan Rich Talks weekdays 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com  or #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Please tell your job-seeking buddies: Free Tele-Seminar on May 9, 1 pm PT, 4 pm ET: How to write a kick-butt resume cov…http://bit.ly/J3kf5L     
    
    
    Monday: Living the Writing Life – Design and marketing tips for self-publishing your book. 8 am PT, 11 am ET, http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    Tuesday: Rich & Gluten-Free – Learn about Celiac Disease! 8 am PT, 11 am ET, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Self-publishing tips for book authors, from today's show: Living the Writing Life. http://tindeck.com/listen/iwzl  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Don't forget the free cover letter writing tele-call! http://bit.ly/J3kf5L     
    
    
    Tuesday: Rich & Gluten-Free – Learn about Celiac Disease! 8 am PT, 11 am ET, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Write a kick-butt cover letter in this free tele-call: 1 pm PT, 4 pm ET. Details and download here:...: http://lnkd.in/QegXyu     
    
    
    CONTEST!! Enter and Win! I Love Udi's! - http://goo.gl/PXmqi     
    
    
    Celiac Disease - Dr. Lisa Shaver tells how to cope with this frustrating health condition. http://tindeck.com/listen/ytmo     
    
    
    How do coaches get noticed?  http://bit.ly/IYgs8b     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TStX8X  Thanks, it'll go live in a bit. I love how you don't HAVE to toast the bread, but I do anyway. Love toasted bagels,...    
    
    
    Learn how to write a kick-butt cover letter, TODAY: 1 pm PT, 4 pm ET. Call-in number & download info here.  http://bit.ly/J3kf5L     
    
    
    Free call: Write a kick-butt cover letter, TODAY: 1 pm PT, 4 pm ET. Call-in number & download info here.  http://bit.ly/J3kf5L     
    
    
    Stick with Udi's - they know the score. And now you can get your very own Udi's love: http://bit.ly/JswM2S     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/JQ-STi  Sharing my own journey w/ “pre-melanoma.” Cancer is scary, no matter what it is. You’ll be fine, you caught it...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/s_X8pi  Stop me if I'm wrong (been known to happen) but the question to me has more to do with clients: Do they know what...    
    
    
    NEXT DATE for free telecall: Learn to write your own kick-butt cover letter 4 pm PT, 7 pm ET on Tuesday, May 22. http://lnkd.in/qMiiHg     
    
    
    NEXT DATE for free telecall: Learn to write your own kick-butt cover letter 4 pm PT, 7 pm ET on Tuesday, May 22.  http://bit.ly/KtnF35     
    
    
    If you need a speaker for a live event - could be a lunch and learn or corporate meeting, a business summit, ask me: I teach several how-to…    
    
    
    Learn to write your cover letter, free call: http://bit.ly/IzczJH     
    
    
    @ClassySharelle @richwriting I've got you on FB, please follow me there, too.    
    
    
    @abkaiser Tx for the follow! Be sure to check out Living Writing Life & Writing Craft (M/Th) 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The promotion is still going strong, please share your Udi's love story and maybe win an awesome 3-pak of treats. http…http://lnkd.in/3Jk92e     
    
    
    The promotion is still going strong, please share your Udi's love story and maybe win an awesome 3-pak of treats. http://bit.ly/JswM2S     
    
    
    What's your daily work rhythm? Best time of day to get 'er done? #soloproradio    
    
    
    Worry re food supply? Look at Sinclair's book The Jungle. It was worse then, for animals, people. Not perfect now, but better.    
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks…internet radio's best daily talk show. Guest list for week of May 14  http://bit.ly/IJmkUI     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/H_V7cK  Hi Julie, if you haven't already, please post this on the blog at Rich&Gluten Free - under the I Love Udi's promo....    
    
    
    Blood Pressure: When doc doesn't know best - http://goo.gl/kzbIE     
    
    
    Don't take BP meds...just because. Here's my story on why not. http://lnkd.in/8U_u88     
    
    
    RichWriteBites! 5.13.2012 http://aweber.com/t/BuSGk     
    
    
    Join @CaterinaRando June 16 & 17 for http://soughtafterspeaker.com  summit & learn to get past your fear & double your income by speaking!    
    
    
    Are your speaking engagements not bringing more $$? Learn how influence and style can help. http://ow.ly/aRuvl  Save the date: June 16-17    
    
    
    Don't miss this free call! http://lnkd.in/qMiiHg     
    
    
    Free tele-seminar: How to write a kick-butt cover letter  http://bit.ly/KtnF35     
    
    
    Special sale! How to write a kick-butt resume cover letter http://lnkd.in/kJRaPF     
    
    
    On Sale Now: How to write a kick-butt resume cover letter (book): http://lnkd.in/j8YvGw     
    
    
    @GreenEventCo Tx for the follow; plz tune into Susan Rich Talks weekdays 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    Share your Udi's love story and win a prize! Don't talk about it on LinkedIn, FBook, Comment on it in blog. http://lnkd.in/3Jk92e     
    
    
    @disorder2order Tx for follow. Join me June 6 for new show, Business Bits on http://w4wn.com , 8 am PT, 11 am ET. Featuring coaches.    
    
    
    @AMAnet Tx for follow. Plz check out Susan Rich Talks days, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @rbacal  Tx for follow. Please tune in to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Free MP3 download: Susan Rich Talks - WritingCraft-Humor&Blogging -- http://tindeck.com/listen/bvjj  #tindeck    
    
    
    @mohamedosam Tx for the follow, pls tune into Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @edeckers Tx for follow!    
    
    
    Great week coming up on Susan Rich Talks! Tune in 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com  http://lnkd.in/c_sQSq     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks week of May 21  http://bit.ly/KlPEBg  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/if-egd  I agree - otherwise what's the point of the webinar? I'd say pick a problem, offer a solution, and make sure it...    
    
    
    Winning Student Essays on Bullying: http://nyti.ms/Jys0FZ     
    
    
    Hey job seeker! Worried about your age? Don't be. http://bit.ly/K11otA : http://lnkd.in/xu43Kc     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RAsWyp  Homework matters. Even if you take a long walk, let your mind roll over problems -- it's amazing how that kind of...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/3RWnq5  I belonged to BNI for two years, and that was enough for me. I think BNI is a great place to launch your career,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/vAmdfK  Prices should reflect the value of your work. It can be good, it can be great. But the idea is to be paid what you...    
    
    
    RichWriteBites! 5.20.2012 http://aweber.com/t/DtlpW     
    
    
    Flash Fiction Contest #6: Write, Win, Wow!  http://bit.ly/JeuKDM     
    
    
    Writers, the game is on. Enter, win, hear your name and words on the radio. http://lnkd.in/jXyzZv     
    
    
    @GlobalPeopleLou Tx for the follow. Pls listen to Susan Rich Talks 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @CaterinaRando is having another Sought After Speaker Summit June 16-17 http://ow.ly/aRuvl , catapult credibility, expand your influence.    
    
    
    @Recruit2HQ   Thanks for the follow. Plz check out Susan Rich Talks weekdays,  am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    Writing your memoir: Advice from 2 religious perspectives. http://bit.ly/Lf8HPJ  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Got some "Lookit-Me" news you want to share? Send me a blurb and I'll post it in my newsletter, RichWriteBites, no cha…http://lnkd.in/MmmExz     
    
    
    Tuesday: Rich & Gluten-Free – Anthony Kane, MD discusses: ADHD, Oppositional Defiant Disorder, child behavior, teen behavior and parenting.…    
    
    
    Some great how-to advice on memoir writing, from two authors.
http://www.richwriting.com/2012/05/writing-your-memoir-advice/ … #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    TOMORROW! Free tele-seminar: How to write a kick-butt cover letter. Details and download here:  http://bit.ly/KtnF35     
    
    
    Tuesday: Rich & Gluten-Free – Anthony Kane, MD discusses: ADHD, Oppositional Defiant Disorder, child behavior, teen behavior and parenting.…    
    
    
    @DrBermant Tx for follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @WeddingNetworX Tx for follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @sueblaylock Tx for follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @WelnessChannel Tx for follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    After the job interview, saying Thank YOU is so important! http://lnkd.in/TdPYJq     
    
    
    @Chris_DeWolfe Thanks for the follow. Pls check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Are you an earthworm, or a bird? http://lnkd.in/YU8FZD     
    
    
    Are you an earthworm or a bird? http://bit.ly/KpWt6D     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/DcNi8a  Grammar yes, spelling no. We speak colloquially, using idiomatic expressions, that's grammar/word choice. Spelling...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AaitSd  All very good advice.     Consider: Shift your mindset: Stop being a freelance writer - to me freelance is someone...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/bbTd7p  Consider: Shift your mindset: Stop being a freelance writer - to me freelance is someone who lunges job to job, is...    
    
    
    Thursday: The Writing Craft – Publication Coach Daphne Gray Grant on power writing strategies. 8 am PT, 11 am ET, http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @DitzelAndCo Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @CaterinaRando is having another Sought After Speaker Summit June 16-17 http://ow.ly/aRuvl , catapult credibility, expand influence    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/6g4Bxg  Forgive the cliche, but I love all things writing -- writers, ideas, their stories, their struggles. That's my...    
    
    
    @EPhost Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CZWmUN  Precisely - and even if you didn't give a knock-out interview the thank you note might raise your standing. After...    
    
    
    Join @CaterinaRando June 16 & 17 for http://soughtafterspeaker.com  summit & learn to get past your fear & double your income by speaking!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/CdZPX3  Maybe I should take a poll - how many folks do/don't write thank you notes and why or why not...!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/WrFvZf  I posted my suggestions, what do you like to say?    
    
    
    @Fitness_Girl1 Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Flash Fiction Contest Ends June 4! http://lnkd.in/jXyzZv     
    
    
    8 am PT, 11 am ET, Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com/radio-personalities/susan-rich/ … @w4wnradio #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Listen Live: New App For Radio Stations http://w4wn.com/new-app-for-radio-stations/ … #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    10 Fun Ways to Use Pinterest for Business - http://bit.ly/KOE9nP  via @Shareaholic    
    
    
    @DrBarrySears @richwriting Tx for retweet, hope you are doing well.    
    
    
    Coaches: What is the difference between BEING and DOING? http://lnkd.in/gtYMqu     
    
    
    Ah, the nuances of language! Coaches: What is the difference between BEING and DOING?  http://bit.ly/N93pVS  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @LeaMcLeod Thanks for the follow! Enjoyed our chat today and look forward to more!    
    
    
    That donut you ate can lead to infertility and other problems that do NOT cause a bellyache.  http://tindeck.com/listen/soio  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @DrMichaelWald Gluten&your hormones: That donut you ate can lead to infertility.  http://tindeck.com/listen/soio  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Join @CaterinaRando June 16 & 17 for http://lnkd.in/iAjb8P  summit & learn to get past your fear & double your income by speaking!    
    
    
    Ladies: you deserve to attend this FREE online women’s event... Climb The Mountain, Plant Your Flag and Prosper!  http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    I think this sounds amazing!! http://lnkd.in/enaRtn     
    
    
    do you have money? listen live danny kofke,, http://w4wn.com  8 am PT NOW    
    
    
    is your life meaningful or a consolation prize? Danny Kofke, http://w4wn.com , now. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    systematic approach to eliminating debt, similar to a diet. Danny Kofke, http://w4wn.com , NOW. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Comedian Dan Nainan live on Susan Rich Talks Writing Craft, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on Thu June 14. http://lnkd.in/HSZkqn     
    
    
    Is Business Meaningless?  http://bit.ly/LgnGH9     
    
    
    Business is business: A word without meaning. http://lnkd.in/C9QWXq     
    
    
    @ContentFac Tx for the follow. Excited to have you on Susan Rich Talks Writing Craft 8 am PT, 11 am ET May 31!    
    
    
    @NealSchaffer Tx for the follow! Been eyeballing you long time now. Pls listen to Susan Rich Talks, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    I Love Udi's, Contest #2 - http://goo.gl/lc29m     
    
    
    Help us to empower women by supporting this free event... http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    Ladies... ever climbed a mountain? You’ve got to see this:  http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    Join @CaterinaRando June 16 & 17 for http://soughtafterspeaker.com  summit & learn to get past your fear & double your income by speaking!    
    
    
    @GlenGilmore Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    And the winner is: William Marden. Read blog comments for more. Thx all for your words. Listen live Mon, 8 am PT, 11 a…http://lnkd.in/jXyzZv     
    
    
    Winner is: William Marden.  Thx all for your words. Listen live Mon, 11 am ET http://w4wn.com  http://bit.ly/JeuKDM     
    
    
    Business is a Bad Word  http://bit.ly/MaVO9P     
    
    
    Is Business Meaningless?  http://bit.ly/LgnGH9     
    
    
    Business is a Bad Word http://lnkd.in/MTrH-P     
    
    
    Coaches: What is the difference between BEING and DOING?  http://bit.ly/N93pVS     
    
    
    6 Super-Simple Steps to Networking Success  http://bit.ly/Nb39bi     
    
    
    6 Super-Simple Steps to Networking Success http://lnkd.in/iKezyE     
    
    
    Bagel Energy-booster breakfast - http://goo.gl/vhKvG     
    
    
    I Love Udi's, Contest #2 - http://goo.gl/uJePm     
    
    
    Are your speaking engagements not bringing more $$? Learn how influence and style can help. http://ow.ly/aRuvl  Save the date: June 16-17    
    
    
    You’re invited to attend the online Women’s Event Of The Year - for FREE!  http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    @GlobalPeopleLou @richwriting Thanks for the mention!    
    
    
    Don't forget: Susan Rich Talks weekdays  am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com : Coach Caterina Rando on Wed!!    
    
    
    @KarileeD Hey! Thanks for the connect and for being on Susan Rich Talks Writing Craft. Plz stay in touch.    
    
    
    Hi all, get ready for Rich&Gluten Free -- 8 am PT, 11 am ET Tuesday! The Cosmic Dance of Sugar and Salt, with guest Bonnie Kane, health/wel…    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/NxjBXE  Interesting insights, thank you for sharing Peter! I'm fascinated by words that get over-used in general, and what...    
    
    
    cosmic dance of sugar and salt on now http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    chinese med and how it helps organs: sour bitter sweet pungent salt, now on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    eat less sugar, you'll want less salt; eat less salt and want less sugar. Amazing. Bonnie Kane, http://w4wn.com , NOW    
    
    
    food & comfort; healthy food, is it comfort food? Why jello instead of green smoothie when we feel sick? http://w4wn.com , until 9 am PT    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AaC858  Nice, thank you. To enter the contest next time, please post in the comments section for the blog on Susan Rich...    
    
    
    Flash Fiction Contest #7! Ready, set, write, win. http://lnkd.in/2PnkRD     
    
    
    Flash Fiction Contest # 7: The buzzards were circling, why oh why? http://bit.ly/MdoR92     
    
    
    http://tindeck.com/listen/gfkg  - ADHD and nutrition: your kids are what they eat and you can help them heal!    
    
    
    http://tindeck.com/listen/fbyh  The cosmic war between salt and sugar...can you win the battle?    
    
    
    @anitafiander Thanks for the follow. Plz check out Susan Rich Talks Business Bits, 8 am PT, 11 am ET internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Discover how to accelerate success in career, relationships and situational self-esteem for a more prosperous life http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    My final thoughts on the language of business: How to write better business content  http://bit.ly/MfzrMW     
    
    
    @ebookprof Thanks for the follow. Please check out Living the Writing Life, Mondays, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @getasalesjob Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    You’re invited to attend the online Women’s Event Of The Year - for FREE!  http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    Get ready for Living the Writing Life, Jessica Morrell is going to talk your writing bible.  8 am PT, 11 am ET http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @kokasexton Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @DonCooper Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Stay tuned for Rich&GlutenFree, the brain-body connection for gluten, and relieving stress. 8 am PT, 11 am ET on w4wn .com    
    
    
    @HealthInHarmony tx for follow, let's have a great show.    
    
    
    @HealthInHarmony @richwriting You were terrif, thank you for coming on. Learned much. Enjoy the day.    
    
    
    http://orthomed.org  - Rosale Moscoe on Rich&GlutenFree today. Her book: Frazzled Hurried Woman!    
    
    
    @HealthInHarmony Yes! When I get the link will share w/ your publicist unless you send me your email: susanrichtalks@yahoo.com.    
    
    
    Wanted: your burger recipe! I Love Udi's, Contest #2 - http://goo.gl/uJePm     
    
    
    Wanted! Your best burger recipe. I LOVE UDI'S Contest #2 - http://goo.gl/uJePm     
    
    
    Advice for the new business or lifestyle coach http://lnkd.in/CK9eJh     
    
    
    Don’t demonize HR! http://lnkd.in/SrcRxW     
    
    
    A hand and an eye: Portion control from Zone author Barry Sears, MD http://lnkd.in/itNFTY     
    
    
    A hand and an eye: Portion control from Zone author Barry Sears, MD - http://goo.gl/FWbsN     
    
    
    @CThanks for the follow. Please check out Rich&GlutenFree, Tuesdays, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com 
eliacScoop    
    
    
    @WeejeeMedia Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Mark your calendars for the funniest interview of the year!! 
Susan Rich Talks Writing Craft with comedian Dan Nainan:…http://lnkd.in/HSZkqn     
    
    
    @AliveAndReal Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/PCNV4m  Ya gotta use your words, yes! Thanks Barbara. And if you run out of your own, ask me, I know how to go make some...    
    
    
    You’re invited to attend the online Women’s Event Of The Year - for FREE!  http://bit.ly/L9mlEk     
    
    
    @Notsalmon Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @drsarahdavidbiz Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    TODAY!!!!
Susan Rich Talks Writing Craft with comedian Dan Nainan:
http://lnkd.in/HSZkqn 
Thursday, June 14: 8 am PT, 11 am ET on All Women’…    
    
    
    @lovliving Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/FUyNwP  Jacqueline, yes - I think the art has fallen out of favor. It's good that a gentle reminder helps we "older" folks...    
    
    
    @ThisIsFunner Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/-nKJrJ  What a refreshing realization: Manners are not dead! It seems like we're so time-pressed and rushed that we forget...    
    
    
    @corrinnearmour  Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @robnights Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @DailyDimmick Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Kirstys_ Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Samsamum Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    I am NOT sorry, but I do apologize http://lnkd.in/8E6NMK     
    
    
    @momentum30 Thanks for the follow. Please check out Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on internet radio http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/KVpvsU  Stay tuned -- I've got a series coming on how to write one. It's a cornerstone of my belief - if you can say why...    
    
    
    @HertfordOxford Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @FosterPrinciple Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @ClientRush Would like to interview you on my internet radio show, Susan Rich Talks.    
    
    
    One more week - I've been out of town and it's not summer in Portland - yet!! Share your favorite burger recipe!! http://goo.gl/uJePm     
    
    
    One more week, it's not summer in Portland - yet!! Share your favorite burger recipe!! http://lnkd.in/9q4zz2     
    
    
    Share your favorite hamburger recipe and you might win a prize: A 3-pak of Udi's gluten-free goodies. http://lnkd.in/9q4zz2     
    
    
    Wow! New home page on http:http://susanrichtalks.com .    
    
    
    Prilosec: The scary fact doctors don't tell you - http://goo.gl/ZYiAQ     
    
    
    @blazelazarony Thanks for the follow and great chat today. We forgot to talk radio show. Let's do that soon.    
    
    
    Writers: Should you write for free?  http://bit.ly/L6yay5     
    
    
    Taizhou farmer stops traffic taking his 5,000 ducks for a walk to the local pond http://bit.ly/MAHk39  via @MailOnline    
    
    
    3 Quick Tips to Update Your Resume - Dress for Success Oregon http://www.dressforsuccessoregon.org/1/post/2012/06/june-21st-2012.html …    
    
    
    @pamelakingcable Tx for the follow, let me know when it's time to talk Televenge.    
    
    
    YouTube Makeup Star Lauren Luke’s Moving Domestic Violence PSA (Video) - Carbonated.TV http://www.carbonated.tv/wow/youtube-makeup-star-lauren-lukes-moving-domestic-violence-psa-video …    
    
    
    @Dawn_Abraham Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @LisaSasevich Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com . Ping me if you'd like to guest.    
    
    
    @fabienne Thanks for follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com  Ping me if you want on show.    
    
    
    @healthlady Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @igabashvili Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @haforhope Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @derekfred Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SusanBrdfrdArt Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    New offer for sought after speakers! http://www.richwriting.com/copywriting-services/speaker-sheet-pitch-letter-combo/ …    
    
    
    Tuna on Udi's Bagels, hold the mayo - http://goo.gl/Mo97D     
    
    
    @kayasinger Hi, thanks for the follow!    
    
    
    @LeeBrochstein Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @TheVAPassport Thanks for the follow. Plz listen to Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @EnterpriseEff Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Decadent Dessert: Divine Brownies, my summertime cheat, er, treat!- http://goo.gl/6HX1h     
    
    
    @CathyPresland Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @windycityparrot Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The Day I Became My Own “Ideal Client” by Jocelyn Mozak, guest blogger http://shar.es/tiezu  via @sharethis    
    
    
    @Wendy_Kerr Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Guest post by Bonnie Kane, CHHC -- if you struggle with those dang cravings, her advice will help.  - http://goo.gl/p0d2J     
    
    
    Are cravings making you crazy? http://lnkd.in/eA4UCu     
    
    
    @everybodywalk Plz connect with Walk About magazine -- http://walkaboutmag.com . Free print/online pub, 10+ years dedicated to walkers.    
    
    
    @everywomanovr29 Absolutely, looking forward to it Trudy. My long-awaited, ever-patient guest!!    
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks - BusinessBits-Elizabeth Purvis, Attract Top Paying Clients - Tindeck MP3 Download http://po.st/3zASrA  via @po_st    
    
    
    @VeryShortStory Thank you to Sean Hill for a great show today: http://tindeck.com/listen/aqwq   Adverb: subderisorious: mocking gently    
    
    
    @simasays Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Getting ready for tomorrow's guest on http://w4wn.com , Erik Deckers talks social media strats for writers. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @mitchtobol Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    LIVE now, http://w4wn.com , talking about branding writers - first claim the title of writer, it is first brand. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  call out your niche as part of your brand, mystery writer,/health writer - blog on this, let audi know    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  get over the idea that it is bragging to talk about what you do. Ok to state fact about yourself.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  If you make a mistake on Soc Med, the next best thing will push it away. Learn by mistakes.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  blog is live as long as you say it is. Dele and gone. book around 4ever. Mistakes: perspective    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  own up to your mistakes, be ethical and honest, don't be a jerk visible for all to see    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  if you wrote it, remain in conversation. If someone asks a question, answer it.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Erik Deckers talking about effective writing and blogging. If it's your blog, you can remove it.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Freel writers as speakers, yes. Write ebook, give a talk, build rep, get more clients. Takes time.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks best way to get clients is to tell them what you do and then convince them that hiring you is the most efficient way.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Write good content every day. Don't wait for inspiration. 2-3x/week. Tx to Eric Deckers today    
    
    
    Missed today's show? Follow #susanrichtalks on twitter    
    
    
    How To Change Careers: Expert Tips and Inspiration  - http://www.gethappinesspowerloveandsuccess.com/how-to-change-careers-expert-tips-and-inspiration/ …    
    
    
    @SeanMChandler Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks coming up Jess Lourey, author of the amazing, funny, and amazingly funny DECEMBER DREAD.  8 am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Check it out: small-town mayhem with Jess Lourey on Susan Rich Talks http://tindeck.com/listen/fpoj     
    
    
    Kristrun Grondal, Alzheimer's Assn, on Susan Rich Talks, today at 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Did you know Alz is a neurological disease, NOT normal aging?    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Who gets Alz? It's not just bad genetic luck. Check out the show.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Diet fix for Alz? Eat healthy. Get up and move.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Yes, there IS life after an Alzheimer's diagnosis. Listen and find out more.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Caregiver crisis - how does the caregiver role affect you?    
    
    
    Call Alz Assn, 1800 272 3900 for info  #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    End of life decisions, make them sooner if you have been diag'd w/ Alz #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Rich&GlutenFree, The Alzheimers Show: http://tindeck.com/listen/poyb  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @StephanieEmmons Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @IrishSmiley Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SneezeAdverts Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks. Weekdays, 8 am PT/11 am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    You are what you eat and if you are feeling anxious it could be what you had for breakfast! http://lnkd.in/7t_QNu     
    
    
    @BodyofYouth Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @CristinaCorski Thanks for the follow! Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 8am PT/11am ET on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @MaloneEditorial  Thanks for the follow! Susan Rich Talks on Internet radio, 11am ET/8amPT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Doing great, loving the weekend. I'll be in san fran Jan. @classysherelle    
    
    
    @SachinKamdar Thanks for the follow! Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11 am ET, 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @OrlandoBonwick Thanks for the follow! Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET, 8 am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Why is 50 Shades so popular? No, not the obvious answer.  Susan Rich Talks today, 11 am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @AGSalesworks Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks organic food: reality, hype, benefits. All questions answered today 8am PT/11am ET  http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Pesticides. Do you know what you're eating? It isn't just food. Listen now on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Bonnie Kane -- the non-food triggers chronic disease. And we are plagued with disease. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW what's laden with pesticides?  apples, potatoes,celery peaches, pears, grapes. Shop wisely. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: stores will listen if you ask them to stock organics. Even in cans. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Eat locally, eat in season, beware exploitation. Some people will take advantage and overcharge. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: You are worthy. You deserve health. You deserve food that won't sicken you. Health = best value http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Great show today on Susan Rich Talks. Bonnie Kane on why go organic...and how to afford it.
Check out the show link: http://tindeck.com/listen/jefr     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks: Suzanne Bigelow last Friday: guided meditations on the air, how to relax and focus. Check it out: http://tindeck.com/listen/jhpc     
    
    
    Coming up: You don't need fear-based sales tactics. Learn why. Susan Rich Talks, 11am ET/8am PT, http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : selling without bad karma. No lying, no scaring. You can do it. And it works.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks  NOW on http://w4wn.com : love based marketing and the full-bodied yes. Clients say, "I can do this."    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com . Anastasia Netri: decisions made from emotion; reach for the emotion. And be visual!    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com  with Anastasia Netri. Really find out what your clients want, not what you think they want.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : Been in your client's shoes? tell them. You get what they're going through. No judging. It's safe.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks with Anastasia Netri: Make it about your client, not about you. So important. NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    5 Keys for a Quantum Leap in Business, free from http://Ananetri.com , video training, what worked for her. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @nfmaonlineorg Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 8 am PT/11am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @HouseOfShakti Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 8 am PT/11am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @5280Bookstore Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Thursday, Susan Rich Talks: Get your point across. Get people to agree. Phil Bernstein tells how. 11am ET/8am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    If you want to make your business thrive, I can help. I have access to free tickets for Caterina Rando's upcoming event in San Francisco. A…    
    
    
    Coming up on SRT: Can you sell sand in the desert? Ad pro Phil Bernstein can!  Today at 11am ET/8amPT #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Phil Bernstein: "If you need 20 seconds for the disclaimer, is it the right offer for you to give?"    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Be mindful of your audience, where are they right now? What are they thinking? What should happen? http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Know your target audience. Is it the right group of people? #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Get to the point immediately, deliver your message and leave. Phil Bernstein on Susan Rich Talks, NOW. http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Facts don't matter as much as the emotion attached. Keep in mind during ads. NOW on Susan Rich Talks,http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Phil Bernstein: the story is important. Stories are what change our minds and get us on board. http://w4wn.com  NOW#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    "You are paying by the word. Make every single one of them count." NOW on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Bernstein's Brainstorming by phone
In an hour, Phil will review your marketing, you get a report and ideas. email http://pdxfinest.net     
    
    
    Phil Bernstein's brainstorming services pdxfinest@comcast.net    
    
    
    @DavidChitester  Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Mitralaw Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @KD_Rush  Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8 am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Bleak, sad, riveting. Sheila McClear on her searing memoir of her life in New York's peep shows http://tindeck.com/listen/bbwt  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Placebo effect: It's all in your mind. And it's real.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: In pain? Depressed or anxious? Maybe a placebo would work. Don't laugh, it's real. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com . I'm craving chocolate and baked potatoes. Not together. What does it mean? Beside tasty calories.    
    
    
    @Daezarkian Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11 am ET/8amPT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @inthewriteplace Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11 am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Are you ready to learn how to tell your story to sell your services? Free teleclass on 9/6 http://tinyurl.com/AdvStratSep     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks - Rich&GlutenFree-Do placebos work? - Tindeck MP3 Download http://po.st/jGawoE  via @po_st    
    
    
    Do placebos work? What do your cravings mean?  http://tindeck.com/listen/tfou  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks with Aaron Lapedis, Garage Sale Millionaire – Labor Day's coming: what’s your next big yard sale find?
http://tindeck.com/listen/eiyh     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Mike Russell pivotalwriting,com helps your personality shine through in your writing.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : Amber Jones on finding your niche, controlling the workload. Find a tagline that resonates.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : The joys of freelancing and managing your business. Yes, there are many!    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Mike Russell/Amber Jones- what is storytelling in business realm? Don't people just want facts?    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : Do the clients hire me for my words? For my voice? What do I offer that's unique?    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: Sometimes you have to say no to a new project, especially if you can't stretch any further. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com  Is the client even ready for you? Sometimes you have to fire the client. Yes, really.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : What do you do when you take on a project that you don't actually know how to do?    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks guests today Mike Russell http://www.pivotalwriting.com 
Amber James http://www.ajamesediting.com     
    
    
    @CornOnTheJob Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    @SuzyManning Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @TheRedheadRiter Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Are you ready to learn how to tell your story to sell your services? Free teleclass on 9/6 http://tinyurl.com/AdvStratSep     
    
    
    Coming up on Susan Rich Talks: Marya Hornbacher on the craft of writing and new book, WAITING. Today, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Marya Hornbacher on writing: write from a place of DIScomfort, like writing in a diff genre.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com  Marya Hornbacher: don't begin with end in mind, allow change as you write, let your characters evolve    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Organic how-to with Bonnie Kane. LISTEN http://tindeck.com/listen/jefr     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks, w4wn. Alzheimer's. It isn't normal aging. Listen: http://tindeck.com/listen/poyb     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Alan Morgan talks about rural health care. Elderly are penalized for living rural    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  the impact of ObamaCare on rural comm. Access is there but still not the same as urban    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  A higher rate of diabetes; rural is a food desert, not always have access to good nutrition.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Docs don't go rural b/c bills to pay so end up in urban even if want to be rural.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Rural healthcare - the goal is an easy seamless system that works nationwide. Too complex now.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  We need nationwide ok for docs to treat rurals in any state, that would build access.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Rural hosp DO deliver quality care. Getting there might be hard but good svc when you do.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Healthcare innovation is NOT in DC, it is in the rural areas, where locals work it.    
    
    
    World may be forced to go vegetarian by 2050, scientists say | The Lookout - Yahoo! News http://news.yahoo.com/blogs/lookout/vegetarian-2050-190426669.html … via @YahooNews    
    
    
    @PatrickStrother Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Today on Susan Rich Talks, Jerry Fletcher, Networking Ninja. 11am ET/8am PT only on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks with Sheri McConnell, launching a membership biz model for women-owned businesses. http://tindeck.com/listen/stja     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW w4wn: how-to on relational networking. You connect with people. You take time. You form a relationship. It works better.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com  Jerry Fletcher on importance of t-you notes. One guy increased sales $1200k with a simple ty note    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Jerry Fletcher, Networking Ninja http://go.envolve.com/  Check it out!    
    
    
    #susanrichtalksNOW: Ask people not just for their money, but for their time. People want to be involved. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: social media is tricky, time suck. Make sure people understand your mission. Let others sell to you.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalksNOW http://w4wn.com : Have a new business? Tell *everyone.* And they'll tell others. Be funny; people remember.    
    
    
    @SalesGravy Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Book today's guest or check out his upcoming events, Jerry Fletcher http://www.networkingninja.com     
    
    
    Are you ready to learn how to tell your story to sell your services? Free teleclass on 9/6 http://tinyurl.com/AdvStratSep     
    
    
    Coming up on Susan Rich Talks, http://w4wn.com : Sandra Lamb on words, words, words. 11am ET/8am PT    
    
    
    Want to do more in less time? Rosie Aiello on Susan Rich Talks, http://tindeck.com/listen/muvb     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : Sandra Lamb on email rules, respond in kind. For special occasions, write thanks by hand    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : if it's personal or confidential, or for negotiations, use face-to-face or phone.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : Sandra Lamb: Don't just "send" until you're sure to whom you're sending it.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : How to apologize in writing. No shame in apologizing; it shows strength of character    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW writing a red-hot love letter http://w4wn.com  Focus on lover and his/her wonderfulness    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks: Acknowledge the offense, make retribution. It's hard but worth it. Sandra Lamb on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks: Alan Morgan, Nat'l Rural Health Association, on the challenges of rural medicine. There's hope. http://tindeck.com/listen/wmaf     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Pass on gluten and ease your anxiety, with Trudy Scott http://tindeck.com/listen/muhu     
    
    
    @EmilieTD Thanks for the follow! Susan Rich Talks, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @destresstherapy Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays at 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Are you ready to learn how to tell your story to sell your services? Free teleclass on 9/6 http://tinyurl.com/AdvStratSep     
    
    
    Coming up: Joni Aldrich on taking care of others while not losing yourself, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  when diag'd w/ cancer, shocking, feel like a 2 yr old. yet lot of decisions must be made asap    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Joni Aldrich talks caregiving and cancer or chronic illness.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Even after 2 years grief continues. Focus is on winning, so never think might lose. Counseling.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Grief means you don't care as much, can become ill or have car accident or a bad fall.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Guard your heart. Brain illness patient can really hurt you, so care but don't take it in.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  have you lost center of universe? Joni Aldrich on cancer, coping, caregiving.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Death: Our shell becomes broken but we still have beauty and purpose.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Decisions must be patient-centered, not based on young or old.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  what are the liabilities for you as caregiver, who is not a medical pro.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Or what if they ask you to end their life for them?    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Full brain radiation - think long and hard on it.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com   Caregiving at end of life: Adapt and realize there is still a person in there.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Caregiving can create PTSD. You are still who you were before you became a caregiver.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  a malnourished cell will not absorb chemo as well as well nourished. Do best to eat.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  But at end of life, don't force them eat, if on hospice.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Caregiving is an unhuman human situation. We do our best, but we will make mistakes.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Caregiving is learn as you go, know to ask for help. No formal training outside of CPR.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Aftermath, the love and humor help you heal the pain.    
    
    
    Reduce rudeness in the world. Listen to #susanrichtalks with Sharelle D. Lowery, Wednesday, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Are you ready to learn how to tell your story to sell your services? Free teleclass on 9/6 http://tinyurl.com/AdvStratSep     
    
    
    I'm the host of Susan Rich Talks - live weekdays on w4wn. com. Always looking for guests, so pitch me. But I am also a word-craft and marke…    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks with Erik Deckers on marketing strategies for writers. http://tindeck.com/listen/uxrc     
    
    
    @JNCoachingU Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays 11am/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @ChaseGiving Blooming With Autism https://apps.facebook.com/chasecommunitygiving/ … #InOnTheGiving    
    
    
    @JonahLupton Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT, on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Looking healthy doesn't always mean healthy. Invisible Illness Week, Tuesday. #susanrichtalks 11amET/8amPT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://w4wn.com , NOW Wayne Connell talking about invisible illness. Yes, they're real AND they hurt.    
    
    
    http://w4wn.com  NOW an invisible illness impacts family, friends and is hard to manage, like PTSD, MS, neurological #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Our culture says you are not sick unless you look sick.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Disability vs disabled. Disability can mean you function ok. Disabled means you can't.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Instead of how are you feeling, ask how are they doing? Subtle difference.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  It's not contagious, be supportive, don't abandon friends.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  ASK what the illness is, it's ok to ask.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  ambiguous loss. Their dreams of who want to be and who they were has changed. Affects marriage.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  you have to take changed dreams and work on building new ones. Do together as family.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  What happens when person is not the same one you married, due to illness. Better or worse?    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  Big fear: You rely on your well partner, what if they meet someone healthy?    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  you manage it day by day. Don't look at it as rest of your life, or 30 years. Person has VALUE!    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  you can't fix chronically ill spouse, but you need room to dream and thrive yourself.    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com  PTSD as the ultimate invisible illness, honor this on 9.11    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks for the twitter feed of Susan Rich Talks, daily on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Manifest your dreams. Tomorrow on #susanrichtalks, Blaze Lazarony shows us how. Wednesday, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks with Christie Korth. What's in YOUR chicken? http://tindeck.com/listen/lyvm     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Have you heard the whispers?    
    
    
    Cancer was an opportunity to change, to reshape. Blaze Lazarony, #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "The life I was living had to die." #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Find the threads you forgot in childhood. Do things that feed your soul. Blaze Lazarony, #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How are we BEing? Who are we BEing? Writing 20m a day changes inner being. Blaze Lazarony, #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com  Blaze Lazarony, Listen to your body, your body *knows*.    
    
    
    Blaze Lazarony, helping you find your inner radiance. #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Look out through the lens of compassion. It changes everything. #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How you live your life shows up in your work life. Once you know your skills, can find a way to shine. Delegate irrelevant. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Blaze Lazarony: who are you being? We all have a purpose.  Watch what we're doing, what's that say? http://www.blazeabrilliantpath.com     
    
    
    @4thWeb Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @advice_4Sales Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Lisa Merriam on branding strategies, short form copywriting. Thursday, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, Lisa Merriam -- Name should be memorable, not descriptive. Pick name that makes you uncomfortable. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Naming not creative, more like digging in the dirt. What makes you really different? #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Lisa Merriam: http://wordpart.com  very useful. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, always test your name, write down, get instant reactions. Word associations. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "It's not about aesthetics, it's about the marketplace." Lisa Merriam on brand names, Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com : business name is forever tagline is changeable. branding expert Lisa Merriam    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: what if your client has no interest in taglines? what if client freaks out? http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Where's your value? In knowledge of product, knowledge of market, knowledge of words. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    SEO: is a chosen name findable? Will it get lost in the forest? You don't want generic. Lisa Merriam, #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Lisa Merriam: Keep it short, keep it simple, keep it basic, keep it memorable. Who looks for "complementary" in a search? #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Make your copy skimmable. Break into subsets. People online are in control of what they consume. #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "Write the toilet paper first, then boil it down and boil it down." Lisa Merriam. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "Merriam's Guide to Naming" book. or website http://merriamassociates.com/ 
for more Lisa Merriam #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @BaronLBC Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @AMAnet Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks to Wayne Connell of the Invisible Disease Association. Amazing interview. http://tindeck.com/listen/rkks     
    
    
    @GHAFN Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @jeffspires Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @GlobalKnowledge Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SmartyCassie Congrats, would love to see. Pls send file susanrichtalks @ yah.. etc    
    
    
    @GKonMicrosoft Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @GKJohnMarkIvey Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @MikiStrong Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @MarketingStrat8 Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @jewelrocks Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SmartyCassie You're quite welcome! Stay in touch, we have great things planned for 2013.    
    
    
    @SoulInspiredBiz Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SuperstarCriest Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Jerry Fletcher, the Networking Ninja! How to expand your network without annoying others. http://tindeck.com/listen/jcmm     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : when you're wired to see opportunities, you aren't a one-shot pony. You can always do it again.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, w4wn: Jim Feldman, sometimes Shift Happens. How to embrace change, embrace failure.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Unemployed? Jim Feldman suggests realize your talent, then join direct sales co in that field.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com , with Jim Feldman. "Knowledge is free... People will pay for wisdom."    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks on http://w4wn.com : When opportunity smacks you across the forehead, accept it!    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Failure happens. Don't be afraid. When you blow it and don't die of it you go on. Jim Feldman.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, with Jim Feldman. Get really good at one or two things. Build your marketing out of it. Or be a creative problem solver    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com . Jim Feldman's book, "Shift Happens." No job? No money? Reinvent yourself.    
    
    
    Divide a problem into components. Look at each piece. Ask the right questions to get the right answers. #susanrichtalks Jim Feldman    
    
    
    Thinking *inside* the box. Outside the box you can't see all aspects of the problem. Jim Feldman, #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Find the pain, find the cure, charge for the cure. #susanrichtalks with Jim Feldman.    
    
    
    Jim Feldman at http://shifthappens.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @mlmcompaniesnow Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW: after tech glitch, we;ve Glad Doggett, talking copywriters. How to hire, how to fire. listen in, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks on http://w4wn.com : Glad Doggett on hiring a copywriter, know the project goal, be clear on what you do    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Hiring a copywriter? Please, identify your target market and narrow it down. Glad Doggett.    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com : Are you the copywriter? Value yourself. You are worth what you charge.    
    
    
    Get to know the client. What's in her head? Exercises to try. Glad Doggett on the initial interview for copywriting. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    You have a unique writing voice, and that's the one that's needed. Don't copy someone else's. Glad Doggett, #susanrichtalks NOW, w4wn    
    
    
    Pricing models, packages for writing. #susanrichtalks NOW with Glad Doggett, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Budget adequately for copyediting work. The writer is worth it. Do the research; how will the writer help your goals. #susanrichtalks w4wn.    
    
    
    The copywriter's an important part of your new business team, not someone you pick at random off the Internet. Glad Doggett, #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    To hire a copywriter: be sure to ask for portfolios, find out their strengths and weaknesses. Glad Doggett on #susanrichtalks, w4wn.    
    
    
    What to do when it all goes south. The writer hates you, you hate the writer. Breaking up doesn't have to be awful. #susanrichtalks, w4wn.    
    
    
    Oh, please, give the gift of solid feedback. Don't just say, "It doesn't have pop." http://w4wn.com , #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    And please, please...adhere to deadlines! Both of you! Glad Doggett, on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @KarileeD LOL exactly! Thanks for listening.    
    
    
    @EvanBenner Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 8am PT/11am ET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @RevAnne1 Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @BraveGirl31 Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The American way of death: costly, scary. TODAY on #susanrichtalks: Kathy Brandt on hospice, palliative care. 11am ET, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Deborah Reed's amazing publishing saga, and words of hope-Literary fiction isn't dead. 11am ET/8am PT w4wn    
    
    
    A business lesson from my dog! http://lnkd.in/5TNeRE     
    
    
    It's not that you have no words, you probably have too many ideas. http://lnkd.in/K4UXzj     
    
    
    Effective communication, what does it take to drive action when no one is listening? http://lnkd.in/J2vAcn     
    
    
    @doubletied Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @BarbaraBakken Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @jogebauer Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @S2Solutions Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8 am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @rockerlifecoach Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Fashion4Closets Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @DreamwithJulie Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SharingSpreePTL Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @FemBizCoach Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @DebReedAuthor Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up next - 8 am PT, 11 am ET on http://w4wn.com : Rich and Gluten Free Travels in Italy - http://w4wn.com :    
    
    
    Scared of holidays? Afraid of looking like an idiot at parties? Listen to #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Violence isn't the answer: etiquette when people treat you badly. Expert Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Do what you want to do. If you don't want to go...then don't! Please! Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Don't be a spaghetti-back. Don't let people walk all over you at your party. Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Guest etiquette: Oh, please, RSVP. Early. If you have to change, let the host know. How hard is that? #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Rules for presents. You know you want to learn this. You hate picking gifts. Learn what to do. #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Easy: give a holiday card to everyone. Or a journal. Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Food for guests with food allergies or diets. Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "Do not be late, do not be late, do not be late." It's just kindness, folks. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    More from Sharelle D. Lowery, etiquette goddess: http://classyblackgirl.com     
    
    
    "As we are loving on other people, don't forget to love on yourself." Sharelle D. Lowery on #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    I saw Hurricane Sandy - my bird's eye view of the world before the storm hit. http://lnkd.in/rD__NM     
    
    
    How few words do you need to get your point across? Samantha Arigapudi on #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Listening to the words beneath the words. Samantha Arigapudi on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The psychology of shortened attention spans. Why aren't we fighting it? #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Eliminate the ambiguous, use images, don't confuse. Samantha Arigapudi on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Use an outline, start by overwriting, then consolidate. Risk it: cut it down, see if it works. #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Got a weird idea? Present it anyway! You never know. Samantha Arigapudi #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How to handle Internet ads. What if you aren't seeing results? Samantha Arigapudi on #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Repurpose your work, vlogs, transform written word to visual. Video is far more attractive. #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Find Samantha Arigapudi at Marketing Maven Public Relations, http://marketingmavenpr.com     
    
    
    Free MP3 download: Susan Rich Talks - Samantha Arigapudi, Minimalist CopyWriting -- http://tindeck.com/listen/nsnn  #tindeck    
    
    
    Booking Blitz: Susan Rich Talks - broadcasts live every day. 8 am PT/11 am ET with a new time slated for 2013: 9 am ET/NOON ET.
Talk show f…    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/pUnhxk  Thank you for reading Tracy - I just heard from my friend who lost her home. It's filled with mildew now but she...    
    
    
    Coming up on Susan Rich Talks: Bullying-- Therapist Kristi Fowler on how to deal, how to heal. 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com/     
    
    
    Coping with bullying: Learn more from family therapist Kristi Fowler at http://kristifowler.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Joe Israel did jail time and died in a mental hospital. Because he was born a woman. #susanrichtalks/Bambi Lobdell  http://tindeck.com/listen/ylrb     
    
    
    Author Sue Knot talking about writing Twilite parody NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Marketing Mess:Is your product for sale? Make sure people can buy what you sell.NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Paranormal lit: Why is it so big?  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    how long should your book be? NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    do you need an editor?  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    what mistakes do you make between write, edit, publish?  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
        
    
    
    Plan your book launch and marketing 3 mos early, minimum.  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Facebook not as effective for book mktg, personal website is better.  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Can you piss your followers off so they stop liking you?  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Get Sue Knot, author: Twilite parody 'anywhere' all her books by search.  NOW on Susan Rich Talks http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Wow, show mascot Basket the Wonder Cat is in the dog house. Listen 9 am PT/Noon ET TODAY to find out what happened. And then stay tuned to …    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/t4xATG  #in    
    
    
    How did the Twilite parody come to be? Find out from author Sue Knott http://lnkd.in/3kHh-y     
    
    
    Laura Fenamore's diet revolution: Love the body you're born with. #susanrichtalks http://tindeck.com/listen/tezx     
    
    
    @MacadamOS Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @SweetMandarins Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @HellBoyKern Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Back_Stories Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @7k8madni Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Listen to "Susan Rich" hosted by Power Women Magazine on 12/5/2012 5:00 PM #BlogTalkRadio http://www.blogtalkradio.com/powerwomenmag/2012/12/05/susan-rich …    
    
    
    Coming up TODAY on #susanrichtalks: Elizabeth Hanley:how not to let problems get in your way. 11am ET/8am PT http://w4wn.com/     
    
    
        
    
    
    Change yourself to cope w/ people who won't change - how you react to them 
Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    There are 4 tips to manage your life. First is DEFINE, see as it is, not worse than it is. Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Negative thinking is what upsets you, not the problem itself. Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    A problem cannot be solved w/ same thinking that created it. Einstein. Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #2 Own problem. After you define. Gives you control of problem. Accountability. Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    you can always do something, even it comes down to changing your thinking. Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    EM Hanley talking No Problem, Focus on Solutions Susan Rich Talks, NOW on http://w4wn.com . #3: Truth tip, how can I learn from it?    
    
    
    #3 look at beliefs, your perceptions and see where truth is. #SusanRichTalks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #4 tip is the balance tip, will it matter 1 yr from now? #SusanRichTalks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    EM Hanley took the brilliance of self-help gurus and streamlined into one easy tip book. #SusanRichTalks, NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Collecting Likes for my brand new Facebook page: http://lnkd.in/NyEKAu . Stay abreast of what's happening on my LIVE internet radio show, pi…    
    
    
    Tomorrow on Susan Rich Talks: Sheila Wagner on the illnesses to which entrepreneurs are prone, and how to deal so you c…http://www.w4wn.com/     
    
    
    @FreeEbooks_4U Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @David_Tjikana Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Handling illness when the business depends on you. Sheila Wagner TODAY #susanrichtalks , 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Hello all, stay tuned for Susan Rich Talks LIVE with today's guest Sheila Wagner, we'll be talking about chronic illnesses solo pros face, …    
    
    
    Sheila Wagner on the solopro health bell curve: why do so many not get better? #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The nutrition connection: focus on it and fix so much. Sheila Wagner #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The art of medicine and nutrition - to find the connection to nutrition. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Solopreneurs have tenacious health issues: so much work, must be done now. Our minds flit from idea to idea. We don't settle #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Sheila Wagner on blood sugar mastery, use eating schedules or metabolism goes haywire. #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Sheila Wagner: Sequencing matters. It might be why you aren't better. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Your medical history should include even the crazy stuff. And if test results are normal? Maybe you still aren't normal. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    A balanced meal will make you feel better, and it may not be what you think *should* be right. Keep your brain sugar up! Sheila Wagner    
    
    
    Entrepreneurs need more brain food. Sometimes that includes carbs. Really! Watch your hunger, energy#susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Watch your cravings - they mean something. What that is needs to be figured out.    
    
    
    Reach out to Sheila at http://sheilawagner.com/     
    
    
    @AppleRouge Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Tomorrow's guest on Susan Rich Talks is Laura Hansen, the life mechanic. Find out why your life is a wreck, and what you can do about it! C…    
    
    
    Life mechanic Laura Hansen on Susan Rich Talks, tomorrow: Find out why your life is a wreck! 9 am PT/Noon ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    Today on Susan Rich Talks: Is your life a wreck? Laura Hansen, Life Mechanic, has answers. 11am ET/8am PT on www.w4wn.c…http://www.w4wn.com/     
    
    
    Laura Hansen on #susanrichtalks: controlling how thoughts work. So much time mired in our minds. Why we can't let go. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Ice cream hits the ground? Pick it up and keep eating. But when we fall, we think we belong on the ground. Laura Hansen, #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    We create transformational moments while doing daily tasks. Laura Hansen's exercises NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Eat the whole apple: the parts of your life you do control, and the parts you don't. #susanrichtalks NOW, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Survival: sometimes it meant hiding in a corner, eating. Don't hate yourself; it was the best you could do. Laura Hansen on #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Similarities between homelessness and growing a business. Fear, doubt that we can rise above what we were. #susanrichtalks NOW w4wn    
    
    
    Every day we wake up and have to believe in the reality of our business. Laura Hansen #susanrichtalks on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The slow erosion of women's rights, keeping us out because we'd rather work together. Laura Hansen, Life Mechanic http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The business world's slow shift to collaboration. Laura Hansen on #susanrichtalks NOW http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    "To be successful, we can't destroy our competitor...we have to look on them as part of our community." Laura Hansen NOW on #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Creating connection, creating new town squares, creating a world. Laura Hansen on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Resources on http://laura-hansen.com , free audio, classes, meditations, discounts on book, DVDs, on sale through holidays. Check it out    
    
    
    Wow, what an AMAZING interview with author Laura Hansen - http://www.laura-hansen.com . Please check out the replay today 9 am…http://lnkd.in/eThSXq     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TaZZjG  Sounds like a great call. We talked about collaboration today, and how powerful it is in this solo pro new economy...    
    
    
    Taking nominations for favorite book of the year. We talk books on #susanrichtalks, Monday 12/3 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    A fun little holiday story... http://lnkd.in/BeUxGd     
    
    
    Oh, what’d you do to my dog? http://www.richwriting.com/2012/11/oh-whatd-you-do-to-my-dog/ …    
    
    
    Warren Whitlock talking social media strategies NOW on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    There are 3 stages to effective SM strategy. Get past 1 and 2 fast and start sharing. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    We know this: don't talk about breakfast. We know this too, Don't push your product endlessly. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Interact, creatively.  #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  with SM pro Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    "send me a personal message and I'll send you something very good free."  #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    River of data, you dip in when you need something.  #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock.    
    
    
    you need to be ready to take an order, BUT not perceived as selling. Be natural! #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    Find a way to 'bond' on social media. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    FB for pro relships; Twitter helps one at a time. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    Media is only 1% Y'all should be asking questions. On Tw, FB, LI. Be social 99%.  #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  WarrenWhitlock    
    
    
    hashtag is for an event #susanrichtalks. Are we not an event? LOL
Warren Whitlock NOW on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    It's not generating a big audience, it's the quality product. Solve problem. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    You don't generate followers, you help people. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    Build a network, not a mass following. #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock. You don't have to be LadyGaga to win.    
    
    
    You can search for & answer Q on Twitter, answer those you want to know better #susanrichtalks NOW on http://w4wn.com  Warren Whitlock    
    
    
    Warren Whitlock www.profitablesolutionmedia and ASK HIM A QUESTION.
 #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @WarrenWhitlock Thank you so much! It was a wonderful show; I'm surrounded by notes. Annemarie Schuetz    
    
    
    @Veritas_Office Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Rick_Sadle Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Laura_M_Hansen Thanks for the follow! Laura, your show was incredible. The chat room wants you back to talk spirituality. Susan Rich    
    
    
    @chadrobley Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Laura, stay in touch and we'll do this again!    
    
    
    Content Marketing Is The New Search Engine Optimization by @adherecreative http://po.st/zaIEGV  via @B2Community    
    
    
    @David_Tjikana @AdhereCreative    
    
    
    @RichWriting @David_Tjikana @AdhereCreative All good advice, do you have a blog w/ more deets?    
    
    
    @AdhereCreative @RichWriting @David_Tjikana We had a guest on #susanrichtalks today addressing ROI of SMedia. Good stuff. Your blog fit.    
    
    
    Coming up today on #susanrichtalks: Of course you want books. But which ones? We'll tell you what to buy. 11amET/8amPT  http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @UpSearchSEO Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, 11amET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @GardenOfTheSoul Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @ResumeInsights Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    I miss my grandma! Who else is missing a loved one this season?  http://www.richwriting.com/2012/12/4711-not-007/ …    
    
    
    Mary Pitman,missing money expert on #susanrichtalks Are you entitled to some cash? Find out today! 11am ET/8am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How does money go missing? Find your money! Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    $32.M missing, they didn't know about it. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The state will hold your $ forever, but keep interest it earns. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    If home forecloses but sells more than you owe, the extra $ is YOURS. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    A finder's fee is legit but most of time YOU can't find $$ yourself. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    The little book of missing money, find money that is YOURS, by Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://unclaimed.org , http://missingmoney.com  free. Never pay for online search Mary Pitman, NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    $41.7 billion in US alone, people are missing money. What if all claimed? Mary Pitman, money finder on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Use combos of 'estate of' for deceased's $$. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    If have Life Ins policy, update benef info. Make sure the $ goes to you or who you want. Mary Pitman on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Digital assets are worth tracking: Ebay, domain names, make sure all know your deets. Mary Pitman, on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    She was first person to tell Suze Orman about missing money. Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    You don't need financial know-how to do it. Even the indigent can have $ 
Mary Pitman, NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Even unclaimed child support can be found! Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    List your assets, safe dep box, what bank, which branch, box # and key location. Mary Pitman, NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Unclaimed goods get auctioned, the $ is still kept but you may lose trinkets. Mary Pitman NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    If bank fails, money is insured by FDIC at first. $ goes to state. After 10 yrs, back to FDIC and you lose your rights. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    While finders are legit, many red flags. Be very careful or look first. Mary Pitman, money finder on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://www.thelittlebookofmissingmoney.com  
Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    $6.2 M unclaimed gift cards in MO Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://scritsmart.com  find missing gift card money, you didn't nec lose it! Mary Pitman, money finder on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    non-profits have missing money too! Mary Pitman, money finder NOW on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @Allie4csjv    
    
    
    @Allie4csjv Thank you for the retweet!    
    
    
    @SpinnitRecords Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @exploreB2B Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Susan Rich will read a 15 sec PSA for smaller non-profits on her radio show and then record it so it can be used to build awareness. All Fr…    
    
    
    Your Non-Profit: Get Noticed Now http://lnkd.in/kG8_3A     
    
    
    Your Non-Profit: Get Noticed Now http://www.richwriting.com/2012/12/your-non-profit-get-noticed-now/ …    
    
    
    @TonyMichael Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @ShantezPR @Enchantedpr @AWMediaGroup @insightsKW    
    
    
    @ShantezPR @Enchantedpr @AWMediaGroup @insightsKW  This will be a great show, we can't wait to learn more! #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks, PSA for Severson Sisters: http://youtu.be/ZjskjMVCsSo  via @youtube    
    
    
    Need to get your non-profit noticed? http://www.richwriting.com/2012/12/your-non-profit-get-noticed-now/ …
FREE.    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://screensforteens.org , dedicated to making sure your kids' hearts survive school. Check them out! #susanrichtalkspsa http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Do the inner work before you get back into the dating world. Rosalind Sedacca Now on #susanrichtalks on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Be open and receptive to trying something new. Rosalind Sedacca Now on #susanrichtalks on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Date safely! and don't forget to take your time. Rosalind Sedacca Now on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Watch for the relationship ruts. Make different choices! Rosalind Sedacca Now on #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Looking for your prince? That's fairytale thinking. Guess what? No one can fix us. Rosalind Sedacca #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    It's not your partner's job to make you happy. It's impossible. Rosalind Sedacca on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Watch out for jealousy, controlling behavior, isolation, intimidation. It's not just the younger guys. #susanrichtalks on w4wn    
    
    
    STDs for middle-aged and older adults, a big problem. Talk!  Ask! Rosalind Sedacca Now on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Come from a place of joy. Rosalind Sedacca now on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    If you have to change who you are to be with your partner, something's wrong. Rosalind Sedacca on #susanrichtalks http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://womendatingafter40.com  free ebook from Rosalind Sedacca. She has exercises, guides, will help you do the work.    
    
    
    Adam Hommey | Websites that Sell https://www.spreaker.com/user/soloproradio/adam_hommey_websites_that_sell …    
    
    
    Friday on Susan Rich Talks: Gina Guddat on exercise, connection to anxiety and depression in women. 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Dating after 40, 50, 60? Yes! http://lnkd.in/zH2FPW     
    
    
    Talking about depression in holidays & more. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    5% of weight up or down in one month can be sign of depression. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    Cognitive therapy helps w/ depression in conjunction w/ meds. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    Try to find the thought that made the feeling that made the behavior. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    A myth that holidays are joyful. Not reality for most. We feel pressure, makes it worse. #SusanRichTalks Gina Guddat http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Less stress is best, fewer gifts, ignore what 'others' do. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    Prolonged anxiety leads to depression. Journal, look for what you can fix, change. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    We worry about what we can't control. Keep a worry journal for 15 min day. Give it to higher power to solve. #SusanRichTalks Gina Guddat    
    
    
    There is evolutionary reason for anxiety/depression. Gina Guddat on #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    Retro Kitchen #SusanRichTalks, http://w4wn.com  NOW    
    
    
    EAT dark chocolate, more serotonin than Wellbutrin. #susanrichtalks RetroKitchen    
    
    
    A little bit about our show: http://lnkd.in/F4uf8W     
    
    
    @agaentinc Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @JimCorbettPDX Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    @MobileGivingApp Thanks for the follow! Please listen to Susan Rich Talks, weekdays, 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks, Blooming with Autism: http://youtu.be/6nXDeZZqgsU  via @youtube    
    
    
    Up next on Susan Rich Talks, 8 am PT/11 am ET: Keisha Walker talks about entrepreneurial success and giving back. http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Jennifer Omner on the ISBN and working with your book designer. 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Green cleaning expert Leslie Reichert on keeping things spic-and-span. 11am ET/8am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Virtual Christmas party! Hey all you solo-pros, let's have some holiday fun. Listen live here: http://lnkd.in/az_CuE 
Friday Dec 21 at 11am …    
    
    
    How NOT to clean your oven...how to clean mold...
http://lnkd.in/AkSyvA     
    
    
    A Giving Goal: Internet Radio Show features 5 non-profits per week for 2013 http://bit.ly/U0g29v  #Nonprofit    
    
    
    Portland OR--Jan 8, 2013: Mark your calendars for a super-caffeinated event. Join Susan Rich and Barbara Saunders and …http://lnkd.in/SYK-ND     
    
    
    2 great reasons to tune into Susan Rich Talks!  Guest List for week of Jan 2, 2013: http://youtu.be/juagyh08n4I  via @youtube    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great show with Veronika Noize, top 3 tips for business success in 2013! http://lnkd.in/zUBJVG     
    
    
    An amazing non-profit: http://lnkd.in/hcPqXP     
    
    
    FREE BOOK to first 5 who comment on the Susan Rich Talks page: Stop Looking for a http://Husband.www.facebook.com/susanrichta …http://lnkd.in/PgM5Dp     
    
    
    FREE BOOK to first 5 people who comment on the Susan Rich Talks page: Stop Looking for a Husband. http://facebook.com/susanrichtalks     
    
    
    Sometimes No. 2 is best when you're in business... it's just a hop skip and a vrrrrr from No. 1! http://lnkd.in/5ACwx5     
    
    
    Special offer: Your Lovable Website. Turns yours from lackluster to lovable. http://www.yourlovablewebsite.com  http://lnkd.in/nA2Xh7     
    
    
    Susan Rich, word-craft & marketing coach + host of internet radio's daily talk show Susan Rich Talks is available for interviews on: You Fa…    
    
    
    Idea test:
How to think like a writer: Susan Rich, creator of the Write it Rich! series shares her tips, tricks and no-fail strategies for …    
    
    
    Wonderful interview today with actress/author Tina Sloan on her book, CHANGING SHOES.  Listen to the show: 
http://tindeck.com/listen/lxkv     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/richwriting 
Agility Training for Busy Solo Pros, enroll now in our Master Mind  Group strategies. Two coaches, twice the power.    
    
    
    http://tindeck.com/listen/ctad 
Master Mind Group: Agility Training for Busy Solo Pros. Two coaches, twice the power. Say yes on FB: susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks on James Malcolm Rymer, author of Varney the Vampire. Yes, he's dead, but we were guestless. 12pmET on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Katrina Sawa, Love ourselves successful! Yes, it comes down to love, even in business. #susanrichtalks 9am PT on http://w4wn.com/     
    
    
    Come support Susan's nervous co-host, Annemarie, on Friday at Deb Bailey's Power Women Radio on BlogTalk. 12pm ET/11am CT/9am PT.    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Suzanne Casamento from the Fantasy Dating Game on the game of dating. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Shameless self promo We are funny. That'd be Susan Rich and Annemarie Schuetz on our daily show, NOON ET on w4wn .com.  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YTjeuV0HX2o …    
    
    
    What's the difference between  rich and poor? A handful of habits. Thomas Corley today  #susanrichtalks, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Do you want to think like a writer? Save the  date, June 21-22 (Th-Fri) in Portland, OR. 
 http://www.richwriting.com/event-how-to-think-like-a-writer/ …    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/t4xATG  #in    
    
    
        
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/DPjgDv  Excellent information, thank you for sharing. I've been focusing hard on my YouTube videos...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/P4MWrv  Glad you enjoyed. We interview writers on a regular basis on the show. If it's not overload or a violation of this...    
    
    
        
    
    
    25 to 5: This week's topic: What to do when "it's" not working, plus your questions & concerns. FREE conference...: http://lnkd.in/ieFzgq     
    
    
    25 to 5: This week's topic: What to do when "it's" not working, plus your questions & concerns. FREE conference...: http://lnkd.in/YXDSST     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/RdAEdW  Good article, good advice. Helpful for anyone who has to develop a slideshow. Thanks. My challenge is I teach...    
    
    
    Fix your Biz: What to do when IT is not working anymore. Free call:
Friday, 4:25 pm to 5 pm PT
Call: 424.203.8400
Access Code: 312065#    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/phcNbT 
I'm a featured speaker at this event. Portland OR. Early Bird registration is now. Who wants to join me?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/g6CwVg  Stop trading dollars for hours. Create a package that includes ALL your writing services so you present everything...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/UXxy7Z  If your budget permits: Attend conferences in the industry you want to cover, not where writers hang out. Then when...    
    
    
    What death teaches us about business success...humor. http://lnkd.in/JuJdEe     
    
    
    Of cats and chipmunks: What death teaches us about business success http://www.richwriting.com/2012/11/what-death-teaches-us/ …    
    
    
    If you prefer to eat vegan...Jon Robertson, Vegan Cookbooks & Publishing
http://tindeck.com/listen/fweo     
    
    
    Feng Shui master Linda Lenore gives tips on using this ancient wisdom in our homes and business. http://lnkd.in/6bPJmz     
    
    
    Hey copywriters! Do you write sexy copy?: http://lnkd.in/VfUdqZ     
    
    
    Will sexy copy bring you business? Let's talk about it on Friday's free call, 25 to 5! http://lnkd.in/nME3cM     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/ht5Hsg 
Linda Lenore rocked the show today. Be sure to follow her or catch one of her seminars.    
    
    
    Agilty Training for Solo Pros https://www.spreaker.com/user/soloproradio/agilty_training_for_solo_pros …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Written on a bathroom wall: http://youtu.be/g2qgDCjL9hY  via @youtube    
    
    
    Kelly Preston talks 'sunshine moments' with special needs pets.: http://youtu.be/yIR17kY4QrQ  via @youtube    
    
    
    Great call with Kathie Nelson today - we discussed monetizing your business, customer buying trends, where to find mor…http://lnkd.in/6NsTXP     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/HQNCUv  Valuable advice, thank you. It's the underpinnings of being a good business owner, too.    
    
    
    Why calling yourself a freelance writer hurts your business http://www.richwriting.com/2013/02/why-calling-yourself-a-freelance-writer-hurts-your-business/ …    
    
    
    Download a free chapter of You Famous Speaker. Put in the magic words YOUSPEAK to save $7 when you buy. http://lnkd.in/KntC3p     
    
    
    My book was nominated!: http://lnkd.in/FDBPiJ     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9ASgDi  Ha, thank you, from one hired gun to another.    
    
    
    Spring cleaning? Get help! #susanrichtalks with Jan Dougherty on The Lost Art of Housecleaning, Monday 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/q4D5mc  
Voting is open now, please hop over and vote for my book. Thanks!    
    
    
    Admit it: we're afraid to be beautiful. Kenetia Lee tells  how to get over it. #susanrichtalks today, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #susanrichtalks Maggie Currie tells us how to build our confidence and survive life's upheavals. http://tindeck.com/listen/alsb     
    
    
    Today Laura Hansen on spirituality and her new book: A Good  Relationship. #susanrichtalks 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com/     
    
    
    Beauty is such a loaded concept, but it's there for all, just takes belief. Kenetia Lee, beauty  activist http://tindeck.com/listen/nqnk     
    
    
    Feng shui has a  place in business as well as in homes. Give it a try! Linda  Lenore explains, #susanrichtalks. http://tindeck.com/listen/xeop     
    
    
    You should read Finnegan's Wake,at least the first page. Bill Cliett tells us why, 12pm ET/ 9am PT. #susanrichtalks, http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Please vote for my book! You can vote once every 24 hours until March 26.
Thank you! http://lnkd.in/q4D5mc     
    
    
    Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Lyn-Dee Eldridge shows the powerless how to find their power  12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Today #susanrichtalks: Bill Cliett on Finnegan's Wake. Wonders await in this puzzle of a book. 12pmET/9amPT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Thus the unfacts, did we possess them, are too imprecisely few to warrant our certitude... (quote)
We are talking James Joyce, Finnegans Wa…    
    
    
    Coming up #susanrichtalks: Shell Tain tells us how to untangle our money beliefs. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    FREE Download!
How to get cash, cache & connections.
http://susanrichtalks.com     
    
    
    Today on Susan Rich Talks: Dawn Eskins, Carolina Cupcakery on GF baking and the joys of the baking world. 12pm ET/9am PT on w4wn    
    
    
    Bill Cole Cliett on Finnegan's Wake: a frighteningly addictive stew of words, wrapped in a story. #susanrichtalks
http://tindeck.com/listen/kjat     
    
    
    45-minute talk on how to write for the internet. Can be live, telecall,webinar. Ideal for sales/marketing teams, …http://susanrichspeaks.com     
    
    
    Write for the internet, free talk. Contact me for deets. http://susanrichspeaks.com     
    
    
    Need a speaker, telecall, webinar, live event? Susan Rich talks business strategies, marketing, copy writing. http://susanrichspeaks.com     
    
    
    From 2011:  Chef  Joel Schaefer on safe restaurant dining. Is your takeout  gluten-free? #susanrichtalks
http://tindeck.com/listen/bbwi     
    
    
    Check out my professional profile and connect with me on LinkedIn. http://lnkd.in/t4xATG  #in    
    
    
    Dead Writer Day on #susanrichtalks. Samuel Richardson!  Also the EVENT, the Yarnslingers, the cats. noonET/9amPT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Today  #susanrichtalks: Kathy Henderson-Sturtz on negative energy: getting it, getting rid of it. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Breaking through to stunning success. Coming up on #susanrichtalks: MaryAnn d'Ambrosio. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/tht_wX  Awesome show, it's great to be a guest on it.    
    
    
    At midlife? Are you thinking about a new direction? Susan Tolles on Susan Rich Talks, today, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/vn8bEV 
Susan Tolles was our featured guest on today's show. Contact me if you'd like to be a guest.    
    
    
    Turn your words into revenue. Sept. 28-29, Portland, OR
 http://lnkd.in/KVjxMq  Early bird reg gets private dinner with me.    
    
    
    Writers: How to attract paying clients http://www.richwriting.com/2013/04/how-to-attract-paying-clients/ …    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/9q6MvM  Thank you Joss. Some folks said the term freelance writer ties in well with ad agencies and some online search...    
    
    
    The only business strategy workshop with a how-to writing focus. Sat/Sun Sept. 28-29 in Portland, Oregon. http://lnkd.in/KVjxMq     
    
    
    Calling all non-profits, anywhere in the US! http://lnkd.in/kG8_3A     
    
    
    How about some Friday Fun-Shine? http://lnkd.in/BeUxGd     
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Buy stuff, resell on Amazon: Debra Conrad and Beth Sawickie tell us how. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Some business systems that will help you manage clients! Thanks to Ronnie Noize.
http://lnkd.in/gDqwxi     
    
    
    How to sell on Amazon FBA, lots of great ideas. http://lnkd.in/GR7XHb     
    
    
    Sponsors & referral partners needed. Message me if you'd like to learn more.
http://lnkd.in/uCtnyi     
    
    
    Too much to do? Can't get started doing it? Rosie Aiello can fix that. #susanrichtalks today 12pm ET/ 9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Writing about your business is like writing fiction. Sept. 28-29 in Portland, Oregon. http://lnkd.in/uXauax     
    
    
    Pitch And Be Heard - Suzanne Duret http://lnkd.in/esAawN     
    
    
    Coming up on Susan Rich Talks: Dr. Pamela Jeanne explains intuitive healing. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    What's behind our belly fat?
http://lnkd.in/CF226y 
Rest of show:
http://lnkd.in/qq2Hv8     
    
    
    Figure out what you want and Go Get It, with Ciara Anderson #susanrichtalks, today, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Women: How to break the glass ceiling. Susan Rich, Annemarie Schuetz and Tammy Washington discuss.http://lnkd.in/Rkjueb     
    
    
    A snippet from today's show, with the amazing Debbie Saviano, on how to use LinkedIn as a pull marketing tool....: http://lnkd.in/vgq6Su     
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/t4xATG  #in    
    
    
    I was so inspired by having Debbie Saviano on my show today, I just updated my  profile. What are some of your LinkedIn secrets?    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/AG7uPu  Yes of course it does -- it has made me a better, more thoughtful writer. Even though my focus is business writing...    
    
    
    Rediscovering your sense of who, on today's Susan Rich Talks. 
http://lnkd.in/Rr6DPX     
    
    
    If you can't say it in 500 words, you can't sell it in 13,000. Here's what today's sales letter DOES NOT need.  http://www.richwriting.com/2013/04/wanted-27-page-sales-letter/ …    
    
    
    What is your idea of perfect breasts?  http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bPiny0byMUs …: http://lnkd.in/Krst-z     
    
    
    Brand expert Tammy Tribble/Mimetic Design was a guest on Susan Rich Talks today (noon ET on w4wn .com) http://lnkd.in/HZf8se     
    
    
    Million-dollar marketing copy? Yes! Write it! Say it! Sell it!
http://lnkd.in/thh5J9     
    
    
    Writers: I'm curious if there's interest in a writing workshop that builds your game for clients....: http://lnkd.in/bHrUXh     
    
    
        
    
    
    Website design strategies: http://lnkd.in/gEKWx6     
    
    
    New ebook download: Tips for Reluctant Writers, how to write to sell. Sign up http://susanrichtalks.com , scroll down 1/2 way to the form    
    
    
    When a beloved pet is dying. Heather Merrill from the New England Pet Hospice on how to cope. #susanrichtalks 12pm ET http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Got a dog? A cat? Love them to pieces? Today's show was about animal hospice, & your end of life options.
http://lnkd.in/CZVCTx     
    
    
    Coming up today on #susanrichtalks: Are you looking for happiness?Kathy Brandon guests today, 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up today on #susanrichtalks: the awesome Shell Tain is back, talking money traps and hidden assets. 9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    The truth behind your budget. http://lnkd.in/xvt9YZ     
    
    
    Free MP3 download: Susan Rich Talks - Shell Tain, Money! Your Hidden Assets -- http://tindeck.com/listen/rlst  #tindeck    
    
    
    NOW on #susanrichtalks: Bonnie Kane on the challenges of staying healthy when disaster strikes. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    What if it happened to you?
http://lnkd.in/uh55gm     
    
    
    Today's Million Dollar Marketing Movement. Join us Fridays, Noon ET on http://w4wn. com. 
http://lnkd.in/VN4MXz     
    
    
    How to turn your target market into your buying market.
http://lnkd.in/YyQ5De     
    
    
    Write it! Say it! Sell it! | Turn your words into revenue | Writing Work...: http://youtu.be/mEnNzV28-Co  via @youtube    
    
    
    Your sales page: Shorter, please http://www.richwriting.com/2013/05/your-sales-page-shorter-please/ …    
    
    
    Part 2 on how to write a good online sales letter. This is Part 1: http://lnkd.in/RTKhTt  http://lnkd.in/Xs8p6Q     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/kYwiVa  that's the idea -- focus on your busy reader, respect her time and you're more likely to get noticed.    
    
    
    Susan Rich, word-craft & marketing coach + host of internet radio's daily talk show Susan Rich Talks is available to give live talks, webin…    
    
    
        
    
    
    The Law of Attraction drives Fear, Uncertainty and Doubt!
Agree or disagree?  Comment in the YouTube comment section.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=boE1KqT_cu4 …    
    
    
    No money? No time? No excuses! Andre Turan on how to get fit no matter what. #susanrichtalks today 12pmET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Become a Metabolic Millionaire - listen to today's show for great health and wellness advice from Andre Turan. http://lnkd.in/2GNrxs     
    
    
    New ebook download: Tips for Reluctant Writers: How to write to sell. Sign up http://susanrichtalks.com/ , scroll down 1/2 way to the form.    
    
    
    Starting a new business doesn't mean the death of your marriage. Don Purdum on #susanrichtalks, today 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Let the Million Dollar Marketing Movement grow your business http://www.richwriting.com/2013/05/million-dollar-marketing-movement/ …    
    
    
    "Just a writer?" Not anymore... http://lnkd.in/ghiv4Q     
    
    
    mosaicHUB - Business Advice, Education, Jobs, and more http://www.mosaichub.com/     
    
    
    I just joined mosaicHUB where you can find the people, information, and tools to grow your business. http://www.mosaichub.com  via @mosaichub    
    
    
    How to have a good relationship AND a great business. Don Purdum explains.
http://lnkd.in/X4N5fp     
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Patty Farmer on how to follow up, convert your connections into cash. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Parents, you're only human. Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Anne Kjellgren on authentic parenting. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Do you know the difference between your Target Market and your Buying Market? http://www.richwriting.com/2013/05/do-you-know-the-difference-between-your-target-market-and-your-buying-market/ …    
    
    
    Your Target Market is NOT Making You Any Money!
Here's why.
http://lnkd.in/FVdujA     
    
    
    Anne Weismantel Kjellgren: Here's your permission to parent authentically!
http://lnkd.in/sy_8Gu 
Be sure to listen to the whole show, terr…    
    
    
    TOMORROW!! Join me every Friday, Noon ET on http://w4wn.com  for the Million Dollar Marketing Movement. Call w questions: 561.422.4365    
    
    
    Coming up, Noon ET -- we are talking headlines on the Million Dollar Marketing Movement. Join us, http://w4wn.com/     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/5Tzivq  Thank you Barbara! I'll be running a series of blog posts on this topic and if anyone wants to join the discussion...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/YJNpeK  I'm a journalist by training, published a few ebooks, and have more than 1 million words in print. I'm not a...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/an_Ahw  Noon ET every Friday -- no show next week, I'm traveling. If you missed today's show on how to write headlines,...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/daDPek  Hi Sophie-  Thanks for taking a look. Here's why I don't like the term freelance:...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/R7x3KS  Thank you! When it's live, please send me the link. And I like this one of yours -...    
    
    
    For women only: How many times have you been told to charge what you're worth? http://lnkd.in/hfPHxa     
    
    
    Women only! How many of you can write, say, or sell your true value? If you don't know how, I do. Learn how.
http://susanrichteaches.com     
    
    
    How vampires help find your buying market http://www.richwriting.com/2013/05/how-vampires-help-find-your-buying-market/ …    
    
    
    Coming up today on #susanrichtalks: Steve Fulmer on coaching: style stigma, more. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Coming up today on #susanrichtalks: Charmaine Hammond,GPS our best life. Plus a new Toby book!12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u2z5mmadOxo … Daily Hat Attack, AlexSandra Vintage Emporium & Susan Rich Talks.    
    
    
    Yes  we can teach our daughters math! http://tindeck.com/listen/alwm 
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Get your BLOG on, blog for attention. http://tindeck.com/listen/adnn 
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Coming up on #susanrichtalks: Faye Kufahl on having a family member with schizophrenia. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Daily hat attack and living with mental illness, today's guest was Faye Kufahl -- http://tindeck.com/listen/xbof  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    What's the best part about paranoid  schizophrenia? Heartwarming answer http://lnkd.in/H5a9Xh  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    The Turban and Queen Nefertiti: Daily Hat Attack on Susan Rich Talks. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=RmxR77Ga8ZY …    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Rosalind Sedacca, sparing children pain in divorce, caring for divorced elders. 9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    MamaRed Knight on #susanrichtalks: bacon, repurposing, not writing, networking, bacon. Today, noon ET/9am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How to write fiction eloquently, Jessica Morrell, #susanrichtalks http://tindeck.com/listen/hciq     
    
    
        
    
    
    Patty Farmer shares 6-figure Follow-up for Networking
http://tindeck.com/listen/pujc 
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    #susanrichtalks today: PTSD in adults, children. How can we help when friends suffer? 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    #SusanRichTalks - How to heal from severe trauma, dealing with PTSD -- http://tindeck.com/listen/vaoh     
    
    
    What kind of hat should you wear to church? #susanrichtalks
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_eZRa6xD0DY …    
    
    
    How to rebuild your business after disaster, today on #susanrichtalks with Bonnie Kane, 12pmET/9am PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    How to re-start your business when natural disaster strikes. Bonnie Kane on life post-Sandy http://w4wn.com  NOW. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    If disaster strikes, are you prepared? http://w4wn.com  NOW #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    When disaster strikes, tell your clients ASAP what is going on. Keep customer base, be HONEST. http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    How to re-start your business after natural disaster hits w/ Hurricane Sandy survivor Bonnie Kane. http://tindeck.com/listen/dlab  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    And now, for your lighthearted viewing pleasure.... http://lnkd.in/YgKegF     
    
    
    vintage hats and styrofoam duckies
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I1gCYNA40iQ … #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Why Constructive Wallowing Works, Tina Gilbertson on #susanrichtalks http://tindeck.com/listen/kaeq     
    
    
    Medium Dr. Rom Weber on Spiritualism, seeking the dead, the skeptical world. Today on #susanrichtalks, 12pmET/9amPT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    This FRIDAY!!  Million Dollar Marketing Movement, Noon ET on http://w4wn.com   Call w/ your question: 561.422.4365
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Today: Mindsets and the Million Dollar Marketing Movement on #susanrichtalks, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Can you talk to the dead? Interview with a Psychic Medium, Dr. Rom Weber,  http://tindeck.com/listen/cdhp  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Change your mindset, change your income, http://tindeck.com/listen/tsex  Million Dollar Marketing Movement, noon ET every Friday. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/t4xATG  #in    
    
    
    You: Famous Author! Book Development from Start to Finish. Tell your story, build your business. http://www.richwriting.com/2013/06/you-famous-author/ …    
    
    
    Business or life off track? Charmaine Hammond gets you back on the rails. Susan Rich Talks today, 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Susan Rich Talks - Do it once, Use it many. MamaRed Knight - http://po.st/fVMQSz  via @po_st #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    GPS Your Best Life,  great publishing advice. Charmaine Hammond -- http://tindeck.com/listen/wxtv  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    GPS Your Best Life! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jUbJsqmx82c&list=UUsKVTcZJgT1uYXhf4B-_YHw …
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    New ebook download: Tips for Reluctant Writers -- how to write to sell. Sign up http://susanrichtalks.com/blog 
#susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Create content once, use it many times. MamaRed Knight explains.
http://tindeck.com/listen/fvam 
Also: #susanrichtalks about toddies & colds. Fun.    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Dr. Missy Johnson, mapping a path to your dreams. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    YOU ARE Powerful Beyond Measure, words to live by from Dr. Missy Johnson http://tindeck.com/listen/gufm  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    One daily affirmation a day. Say it, believe it and it will happen. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QHItF6vvc_I … #susanrichtalks    
    
    
        
    
    
    895 connections on LinkedIn. I'd love to get to 900 and on to 1,000 by October. Who hasn't connected with me yet? http://www.linkedin.com/in/susanrich     
    
    
    You: Internet Radio Superstar. Join me on #susanrichtalks Noon ET daily. Send pitch: susanrichtalks@yahoo.com    
    
    
    Getting ready to do it: Wed off all summer long so I can write my big book. Will she do it? Follow me #susanrichtalks and find out.    
    
    
    Love this! Perfect analogy for why I am in business for myself. 
http://lnkd.in/3_mT8y     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Marketing is information. Sales is choice. http://www.richwriting.com/2013/07/marketing-is-information-sales-is-choice/ …    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Beauty queen Hermanie Pierre on the value our society places on looks. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    One piece of a conversion strategy is driving interest: I want what you have -- over awareness (I see you, blah blah) http://www.richwriting.com/2013/07/marketing-the-difference-between-awareness-and-interest/ …    
    
    
    Stop Bullies! The solution for parents, their kids and unhappy workers! Jen Hancock explains. http://tindeck.com/listen/jfiq  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Beauty & the Civil Engineer, Hermanie Pierre at 26 shares wisdom about beauty and hard work. http://tindeck.com/listen/jtlz  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    http://www.showcasingwomen.com/magic-of-business-collaborations/ … talking about this now #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Angela Giles and Suzanne Duret talking partnerships on http://w4wn.com  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Tune in TODAY. How to build a business that you love and how to write an email blast that WORKS. 9 am PT/Noon ET http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Collaborate & Blaze in Business, Suzanne Duret, Angela Giles -- http://tindeck.com/listen/humz  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Build a business you LOVE, How to Write Email Blast, Barbara Saunders & Susan Rich explain.  http://tindeck.com/listen/yzhq  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Build a business you LOVE, How to Write Email Blast, Barbara Saunders & Susan Rich explain.  http://lnkd.in/Vb2yHg  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Ramona Jan on life, Lyme, and lysurus. Wait, not the last one. 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    In 15m on #susanrichtalks: Manga artist M. Alice LeGrow, her new book, and the best career ever. 7pm ET/4pm PT on http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    New city, new life, time to re-launch your solo pro biz. How to move on and get unstuck. Noon ET http://w4wn.com , #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Reboot your biz after a move, special networking & kid advice. Kristi Fowler shares. http://tindeck.com/listen/tamt  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Sales advice for the solo pro, Let's Make a Deal, Christine Clifford -- http://tindeck.com/listen/ewzq  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Coming up today #susanrichtalks: Jennifer Estep: writing, assassins and the YA world. Also barbecue. 12pm ET/9am PT http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Urban Fantasy Phenom Jennifer Estep shares writing advice, future fic plans on #susanrichtalks http://tindeck.com/listen/aiit     
    
    
    How to write email, autoresponder blast, #susanrichtalks http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F0XQNzMkBgQ&feature=c4-overview&list=UUsKVTcZJgT1uYXhf4B-_YHw …    
    
    
    No more wondering what's for dinner. Sarah Kallio, Stacey Krastins tell how. #susanrichtalks 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement, telecall/radio show. BizCom advice. ALL Fri, Noon ET http://w4wn.com  561.422.4365 #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Today Noon ET, Expert Kathy Gruver talks GMOs: good, bad, how to improve your food supply/source: http://w4wn.com , #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    3 Must-Have's for copy that converts -- http://tindeck.com/listen/yrcl  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    GMOs and how to deal, Dr. Kathy Gruver shares. http://tindeck.com/listen/aexh  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement, telecall/radio show. BizCom advice. ALL Fri, Noon ET http://w4wn.com  561.422.4365 #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Is there a picky eater in your house? Stephanie Lucianovic can help. Today #susanrichtalks 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    6 marketing trends, how to write email blast headlines. Weekly Million Dollar Marketing Movement! http://tindeck.com/listen/ypsm  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Suffering Succotash! Helping Picky Eaters, Child or Adult.  http://tindeck.com/listen/gjee  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement: Friday Noon ET http://w4wn.com  Differentiate or DIE. Call in: 561.422.4365    
    
    
    Tomorrow on Susan Rich Talks, Zander Sprague talks about dealing with sibling grief, Noon ET on http://w4wn.com .    
    
    
    Today on Susan Rich Talks, Zander Sprague talks about dealing with sibling death and the grief process, Noon ET on http://w4wn.com/ .    
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement: Friday Noon ET http://w4wn.com   Differentiate or DIE. Call in: 561.422.4365    
    
    
    Been the lead editor on a great book, enjoying the words of: Candy Messer, @ASB_VA, @dianacmorgan @DebbieSaviano, Linda Sturdivant, Pam R…    
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement: Friday Noon ET http://w4wn.com   Today's topic: Differentiate or DIE. Call in: 561.422.4365    
    
    
    Differentiate or Die, stand out with your story, font, theme song & business archetypes http://tindeck.com/listen/umqy  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Today on #susanrichtalks: Veronica Drake on intuition, business, and what entrepreneurs overlook. 12 pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
    Get unstuck from your money story, create you-niqueness for you, your clients. Veronica Drake -- http://tindeck.com/listen/lghc  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Million Dollar Marketing Movement: Friday Noon ET http://w4wn.com   Call 561.422. 4365    
    
    
    Are you an innie or an outie? 9 am PT, join us http://w4wn.com/  Let's get inside the marketing mind of an introvert. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Introverts make better business owners, find out why from marketing expert Ronnie Noize http://tindeck.com/listen/cctr  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    We're so hard on ourselves. It's not necessary. Natalie Forest today #susanrichtalks, 12pm ET/9am PT http://w4wn.com     
    
    
    Monthly Business & Marketing Meeting! Join us for marketing dollars and sense.  http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/monthly-bizcom-meetup/ …    
    
    
    How to write your best sales letter, ever! http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/workshop-best-sales-letter/ …    
    
    
    Learn to write your best sales letter, ever. Build a word bucket, never struggle with 'just the right words' again! http://bit.ly/14TjBkn     
    
    
    Who wants to join me in Sacramento? This will be an amazing event! http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/life-changing-conference/ …    
    
    
    Check out "Million Dollar Marketing Movement, Lunch & Learn with a Twist" …http://milliondollarmarketingmovement-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Hope you can join us next week. Please RSVP yes or maybe on EventBrite so we know how many to expect. http://lnkd.in/kGjiav     
    
    
    I'll be in Sacramento giving a life-changing talk about using life-changing words. VIP tix to 1st 4 who ping me.  http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/life-changing-conference/ …    
    
    
    How to write your best sales letter, ever! http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/workshop-best-sales-letter/ …    
    
    
    If you're in Portland, Ore. vicinity: Monthly Business & Marketing Meeting http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/monthly-bizcom-meetup/ …    
    
    
    Small Business DIY Marketing Conference: Write it Say it Sell it: How to Find the...: …http://smallbusinessdiymarketingco2013.sched.org/event/17c55702022b819523ae573af6a3b050#.Uhv-72C2Lg4.twitter … #diymarketing    
    
    
    Today, #susanrichtalks: Tara Smith, corporate executive turned organic farmer. 12pm ET/9am PT on http://www.w4wn.com     
    
    
        
    
    
    96-Year Old Man Pens Love Song to His Late Wife & Studio Surprises by Recording Professionally  http://laughingsquid.com/96-year-old-man-pens-love-song-to-his-late-wife-studio-surprises-him-by-recording-it-professionally/ … via @LaughingSquid    
    
    
    Learn the best Facebook Fan Page Strategies from SM expert and biz strategy coach Michele Scism -- http://tindeck.com/listen/gzsa  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Massive networking event 9.7.13 PDX http://www.reciproty.com/events/2013_09_07/Default.aspx … I am also a featured speaker. Learn how to become a standout in your business.    
    
    
    6 steps to a marketing plan that works, from expert Ronnie Noize.  http://tindeck.com/listen/ggxk  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Use your life numbers for business success, learn how to build signature systems, Marcia Bench shares http://tindeck.com/listen/myqs  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
        
    
    
    I was a featured guest on this show. Get some do-it-how, do-it-now writing strategies.    
    
    
    DIY Small Business Marketing Conference: Local Experts, Global Success http://www.richwriting.com/2013/09/diy-small-business-marketing-conference/ …    
    
    
    @wordette So excited to have you on. Loved your book and Walt just made my day.    
    
    
    @wordette PS, I like Vera scarves and vintage hats and coats...    
    
    
    Grow BIGS with us at next lunch & learn in Portland, Ore. https://growbigs.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw     
    
    
    Ta-Da! Interview with the awesome, magical, knee-sock wearing Kari Luna, author of my fave YA book of the year. http://tindeck.com/listen/rzkv     
    
    
    Fabulous, informative talk-fest with queen of social media, Debbie Saviano. Thank you for an amazing show. http://tindeck.com/listen/bkta     
    
    
    Using astrology in business, Aubrie DeClerck -- http://tindeck.com/listen/mdld  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Monthly Business & Marketing Meeting! Grow BIGS with us at next lunch & learn in Portland, Ore. https://growbigs.eventbrite.com/?ref=estw     
    
    
    Build your Word Bucket, write your best sales letter, eblast & more. $47 for 3-week telecall.https://bestsalesletter.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Get the most out of using KLOUT and Pinterest. @DebbieSaviano explains in this lively podcast for #susanrichtalks http://tindeck.com/listen/bkta     
    
    
    http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pTfCT4Cf24Q&feature=c4-overview&list=UUsKVTcZJgT1uYXhf4B-_YHw … @BuildListNow your WORD BUCKET and write to sell... make pots and pots of money. Live happily ever after.    
    
    
    Can fear sell better dog food? You bet. http://www.richwriting.com/2013/10/can-you-really-sell-your-stuff/ …    
    
    
    Let's talk about Lead Generation - what do you do, how does it work, what can you do differently? Let's talk about i…http://lnkd.in/b7BBBeF     
    
    
    Can stalking help you reach your buying market? It sure can, but better learn how to do it the right way. http://lnkd.in/bmyH-Fj     
    
    
    Sales is not always about making money. http://www.richwriting.com/2013/10/sales-is-not-about-making-money/ …    
    
    
    Fill your Word Bucket, Spill out sales http://aweber.com/t/PDeCT     
    
    
    New ebook download: Tips for Reluctant Writers -- how to write to sell. Sign up http://susanrichtalks.com/blog     
    
    
    Check out "TeleCall:Build Your Word Bucket, Spill Out Sales! 10-11am PT Nov. 11, 18, 25" http://bestsalesletter-estw.eventbrite.com  via @eventbrite    
    
    
    How to write a sales letter that works http://www.richwriting.com/2013/10/how-to-write-a-sales-letter-that-works/ …  Also: writing workshop. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Hey authors! It's time to promote your book. A bit of advice I gave during one of my author training sessions. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=w6Glrl9P_hY …    
    
    
    It's time to launch your YouTube channel and start making videos that promote your book and expertise.   http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ti3xU9K6s_k&feature=c4-overview&list=UUsKVTcZJgT1uYXhf4B-_YHw …    
    
    
    Build your word bucket, spill out sales: Write to connect, write to sell. https://bestsalesletter.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    You can't escape the FUD line, no matter how much NWD you throw at it. 
http://www.richwriting.com/2013/08/6-words-that-drive-your-marketing-message/ …    
    
    
    Animal lovers: Advice on what to do when the hard moment comes: http://tindeck.com/listen/jyhp  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Do your clients know what you do? That's the subject of today's VIF -- Very Important Fact. http://lnkd.in/b56_vc2  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    @BuildListNow your Word Bucket, stop struggling with writer's block!  https://bestsalesletter.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    FREE PREVIEW CALL. Discover how your Word Bucket helps create a communication strategy. Tue Nov 5, 1 pm PT, 30 min http://bit.ly/17AiBrA     
    
    
    FREE CALL. Discover how to write to sell.  Tue Nov 5, 1 pm PT, 30 min http://bit.ly/17AiBrA  #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Build Your Word Bucket: Write to Sell! Sales letters, email blasts, website copy! stop struggling w/ writer's block.
https://bestsalesletter.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
        
    
    
    FREE CALL. TODAY 1 pm PT, 30 min http://bit.ly/17AiBrA   How your Word Bucket helps you write better, with more influence so you get results    
    
    
    http://bit.ly/17AiBrB  -- Video: how to write to sell, how to create content that connects you with your potential client. #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    The Secret to Writing GOOD Online Content http://www.richwriting.com/2013/11/write-good-online-conten/ …    
    
    
    How to build your Word Bucket so words come easier, clients come faster, cash register ka-chings louder.  https://bestsalesletter.eventbrite.com/     
    
    
    Video: How to write a cover letter http://www.howtowriteresumecoverletters.com/2013/11/video-how-to-write-a-cover-letter/ …    
    
    
    How to get your emails read, capture eyeballs and action. http://www.richwriting.com/2013/11/how-to-get-your-emails-read/ … #susanrichtalks    
    
    
    Talk to me: How do you track your marketing ROI? And how does this fit in with your lead generation strategy? http://www.richwriting.com/2013/12/how-to-measure-marketing/ …    
    
    
    NEW! Weekly writing workshop forces you to blog about your book or business. All genres. Portland, OR for now. http://bonsmagicjourney.com/write-your-book/ …    
    
    
    One way to use a storyboard to keep your plot and fiction writing organized. #bonsmagicjourney http://www.youtube.com/edit?o=U&video_id=6_ioMdBGano …    
    
    
    