OMG! somehow i had always known, though we never talked about it. good for you! i wish you well! :)    
    
    
    U there God?It's Cindy.I know that I canbe impatient indignant dictatorial&downright crappy.But I'm sweet&cute too so pls don't resign on me    
    
    
    aryt aryt aryt! on with the current cramming, and on to the next thing to cram, but let me just pause for a widdle mischief in between ❤    
    
    
    i am now at the One Billion Rising campaign / parade on Tomas Morato. join us! :)    
    
    
    @cabring - regalo mo sa akin on your birthday, please? http://www.startrek.com/article/star-trek-tunic-tanks-unveiled …    
    
    
    with hubby @cabring at the One Billion Rising campaign at Tomas Morato on Valentine's day :) http://twitpic.com/c4lvpg     
    
    
    sunkissed - from sunrise to sawa at Tomas Morato for the One Billion Rising Philippines campaign :) http://twitpic.com/c4lwjs     
    
    
    @theallamson for good?!    
    
    
    @owlinthemoon kuya bodjie!!! miss na kita! :)    
    
    
    5 double chocolate chip cookies and counting #sinsoftheday    
    
    
    lemery batangas: met a wonderful girl w/ much to share on migration&effects on the family. honored she trusts me to write abt it! #migration    
    
    
    "Who you are determines how you experience violation." >>> Horn, 2007 #women #feminism    
    
    
    funny, just checked out 2 people with fake stuff in their linkedin accounts - don't mean to flatter you, just wanted to be entertained :)    
    
    
    bad work ethics and psycho tendencies make for self-lauding write-ups to be very entertaining reads, don't you think? :)    
    
    
    2wks of no sleep &all these now done! class trip to gather data; fact sheet for fieldwork report compilation; forum emceeing;midterm exam :)    
    
    
    still lots of cramming to go for the rest of feb & march (&the 1st week of april), but here's to my first night of good sleep in a stretch ❤    
    
    
    have a month to review and re-read everything covered in my subjects from june 2006 to march 2008 for my comprehensive exams!!! :)    
    
    
    cribbed from Mae Paner/Juana Change: "Ang gustong abutin, dapat atupagin!"    
    
    
    @imaturla ninenerbyos ako sa kailangang basahin pero game game game! :)    
    
    
    gloomy day outdoors, warm and fuzzy with comfort food indoors :)    
    
    
    some schools have suspended classes! i hope UP Diliman does too!    
    
    
    yayayay Dog Whisperer is on!    
    
    
    stayed home today - my students from the literacy and numeracy program in the community i visit cancelled classes! that's empowerment! :)    
    
    
    at Balay Kalinaw, UP Diliman for the forum "Saving Tubbataha: Securing our Lives, Defending our Patrimony"    
    
    
    I feel I can apply to be a popcorn girl at the Oscars once I've begun my PhD :)    
    
    
    I'm getting my Anthropology PhD application tomorrow, so next year looks golden for my Oscars popcorn girl career huh :)    
    
    
    I don't think it's too much to ask for an internet provider to be able to handle opening Facebook and Twitter in less than 10minutes #Sun    
    
    
    finished checking papers and exams 3 weeks ago but only submitting now HAAAY!    
    
    
    @choenriquez kilig! :) hopefully in a couple of years, i shouldn't go missing for 4 years again like i did with the MA :)    
    
    
    "Is attendance graded?" Me:"You are graded for class participation, meaning you must do much more than just breathe &cast shadows in class."    
    
    
    "But Miss, I gave a very long and good answer in the exam." Me:"Your answer was indeed very good, but it didn't answer the question. Zero."    
    
    
    I will be guesting on DZUP with my Literacy&Numeracy Class for Grassroots Women this Friday 12-1PM. Tune in! :) #CWR #Gabriela #WomenAndDevt    
    
    
    quitting viewing photos i'm mildly interested in on Facebook or Twitter because it's taking too much of my life before loading #panis #Sun    
    
    
    You're so panis. #SunBroadband    
    
    
    Friend:"Your research is in the social sciences, right? Meaning you can bullshit your way through it - what are you so stressed about?" #grr    
    
    
    Dear Ethically Challenged Person Suddenly Showing Up in My Professional Network Feed and Vigorously Friending My Friends: Buhay ka pa pala!    
    
    
    Friend, at the sight of my Daniel Craig wallpaper:"Ewww!" Me:"What? I love him!" Friend:"Okay, okay, have you, like, seen his face?" #kaloka    
    
    
    STAND UP straight!  :) #UP #elections    
    
    
    always thought the magnifying glass app was the most useless thing til i rushed tothe library to cram& i realized i left my glasses at home!    
    
    
    dynamite from UP maskom: comfort food for cramming - konting anghang sa panahon ng kabaliwan! :) pic.twitter.com/gXnc2HgBap    
    
    
    This is new. I guess this means half of Datu's Tribe will perform at next year's fair? #UPD #USCelections    
    
    
    I LOVE HER!!! :) >>> @imaturla “@AP: Toni Morrison talks to Google about creativity:http://apne.ws/Y1mbBm   -CC” @cindycatz    
    
    
    cribbed from People Over Politics: “Wise men speak because they have something to say; fools because they have to say something.” >>> Plato    
    
    
    feeling DJ! :) - at DZUP 1602 Radio Station pic.twitter.com/ifwcz9nSQT    
    
    
    “To live in perpetual want of little things is a state, not indeed of torture, but of constant vexation.” >>> Samuel Johnson    
    
    
    "We accept the love we think we deserve." >>> The Perks of Being a Wallflower    
    
    
    Just watched the movie; I think I will love the book! Here's a review from a rape crisis counselor, spoilers though: http://www.pajiba.com/book_reviews/the-perks-of-being-a-wallflower-by-stephen-chbosky.php …    
    
    
    this reviewer is a prime example of who i will never become as a teacher, a worker with women, and an anthropologist http://www.patheos.com/blogs/churchofthemasses/2012/11/few-perks-for-the-audience-in-wallflower/ …    
    
    
    now playing James Bond music - i've finally succumbed and accepted that, in my heart, i am a Bond Girl! ❤ #bawalbasagtrip haha    
    
    
    wowowow to James Bond's Pussy Galore and, of course, Austin Powers' Allota Fagina :)    
    
    
    scary start to the week with an unproductive Monday morning &a weekend lost to exhaustion; must produce at least one of my gazillion papers!    
    
    
    Bond's martini: "3 measures of Gordon's; 1 of vodka; half a measure of Kina Lillet. Shake it over ice, and add a thin slice of lemon peel."    
    
    
    got the nap i know i deserve! it concluded an unproductive day, but the night to come is wicked & wild, filled w/ words flying fr my fingers    
    
    
    maybe i'll even have a frappuccino, or two, while magically conjuring my papers to life ❤ yeah baby!    
    
    
    lit class consultation at starbucks 1880 eastwood  :)    
    
    
    brewed coffee and early morning cramming at a nearby Starbucks while waiting for my son to finish his exams at Lourdes :)    
    
    
    RIP Hugo Chavez    
    
    
    i would just like to share the scare, so we don't get carried away just in case we are considering :) http://www.grated.com/when-plastic-surgery-goes-wrong/ …    
    
    
    today, march 6, i learned to love myself a little more ❤    
    
    
    tomorrow will be only for you    
    
    
    what a waste of a day #migraine    
    
    
    and #Sun just wasted a several minutes of my life trying to tweet that. labo.    
    
    
    thursday wore me out with love! sweet danger/opportunity and a badass grade in my exam! :)    
    
    
    @imaturla ang feeling ng manliligaw na sa suntok sa bwan ay nagkamit ng matamis na OO, parang ako at ang uno sa prof na di mabibilog ang ulo    
    
    
    sometimes there are lemons you just really need to roll around with for a bit before making lemonade ❤    
    
    
    and to you too! >>> @imaturla @cindycatz, belated happy women's day! 😄pic.twitter.com/6mnkgtj26F    
    
    
    i'm a Catholic girl but OMG to yet another you're-entitled-to-your-human-rights-if-and-only-if Catholic pronouncement http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/03/07/bishops-oppose-violence-against-women-act-because-of-lgbt-provisions_n_2833675.html …    
    
    
    @putingtikbalang happy women's day! :)    
    
    
    first time to have had a migraine that "echoed" in the following days. i still feel woozy.    
    
    
    a week of grand cramming ahead! :)    
    
    
    since it's easier for me to study and write away from the perpetual "mommy" calls of my kids, i have since acquired favorite starbucks nooks    
    
    
    those lovable soft chairs/couches are deathtraps - i've fallen asleep studying in those. but i ❤ ❤ ❤ those discussion tables! #starbucks    
    
    
    mapped out my schedule for 6 weeks from february to april, and by far i have not kept to the first two weeks! i'll be a good girl this week❤    
    
    
    @ramonbautista baka di niya makuhang magtapat na gusto ka niyang halikan, dun na lang dinaan #vicarious    
    
    
    OMG okay back to work :)    
    
    
    i already loved him in Tomb Raider ❤ #DanielCraig    
    
    
    i'm still in the thick of stuff and the beach is calling to me....    
    
    
    perhaps i can treat myself to travelling alone to the beach this summer - graduation gift & a promise i made to myself 3 years ago ❤ lovely!    
    
    
    hail to the queen! :) http://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-2290824/Queen-fights-gay-rights-Monarch-makes-historic-pledge-discrimination-hints-Kate-DOES-girl-means-equal-rights-throne.html …    
    
    
    JASS article with our CWR photo! :) http://www.justassociates.org/en/article/jass-southeast-asia-rises?fb_action_ids=10200305398854322&fb_action_types=og.likes&fb_source=other_multiline&action_object_map=%7B%2210200305398854322%22%3A369192379861337%7D&action_type_map=%7B%2210200305398854322%22%3A%22og.likes%22%7D&action_ref_map=%5B%5D …    
    
    
    wondrous! http://zengarage.com.au/2013/03/marina-abramovic-and-ulay/ …    
    
    
    staunch anti-consumerist with a few favorites in frenzied attempts at academic orderly chaos at coffee shops (beans must be fairly traded) ❤    
    
    
    back in the fold after my three-year boycott and hoping you're as true as you now say you are. having said that, i love you! #starbucks    
    
    
    embrace your contradictions! ❤    
    
    
    my daily debate with myself: "the difference between doing your best & fussing" :) thank you for this wonderful list! http://aerogrammestudio.com/2013/03/07/pixars-22-rules-of-storytelling/ …    
    
    
    happy birthday @SwiminiTiti !!!    
    
    
    in the course of discussing injustices, i remember brushes with people of this sort & laugh at how irrelevant they have been for so long! :)    
    
    
    for the unjust, unethical, unkind to be remembered as a supreme example of what not to be - this is their legacy! :)    
    
    
    frenzied efforts achieving academic orderly chaos at coffee shops (beans must be fairly traded) are slowly gaining concrete form!❤ #cramming    
    
    
    i decided i would not tweet until done with all my academic work. that resolve lasted for about 30 minutes #WhatThe :) #HopelesslyAddicted    
    
    
    #nowplaying Hotdog! #OPM    
    
    
    ♩ ♬ sa kaiisip sa yo, tagiyawat dumadami ♪ ♫ #Hotdog    
    
    
    this morning is full of hope, love, cramming, and thoughts of the beach :)    
    
    
    Jesuit Pope!    
    
    
    just wish he had a better stand on gays. what would Jesus do, right? :) #JesuitPope    
    
    
    here's "some chocolate" from the Broomstick Goddess :) mmmmmmmm
https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=497269456974937&set=a.412272652141285.80864.412242562144294&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    ... and my current wallpaper! the effect is always the same: i stop, gasp, smile, and become bright-eyed :) #eyecandy pic.twitter.com/MJtQckFnGO    
    
    
    another day of errands around UP, research in libraries and writing in coffee shops - another daydream of the beach ❤    
    
    
    these college kids have totally occupied the discussion tables! they leave for classes only when others arrive! grrr! #StarbucksKatips    
    
    
    lugging 10 library books around campus seemed easier in college #crammers    
    
    
    been stuck in traffkc for more than an hour, and i am just 10 minutes away from home. what the hell is up?!    
    
    
    heartbreaking http://www.philippinecollegian.org/upm-freshman-commits-suicide/ …    
    
    
    @imaturla makaraos lang sa kalokang weeks na puno ng requirements, game tayo ha! :)    
    
    
    it's so hard to study when overwhelmed with sadness #STFAP #RIPKristel #UPM    
    
    
    infuriating how some belittle the plight of students like Kristel. some guy even wrote, "wala lang pang tuition, nagsuicide na?" #RIPKristel    
    
    
    konting critical thinking & perspective check naman! sayang lang university education sa mga tulad ninyo #RIPKristel http://www.interaksyon.com/article/57210/up-manila-officials-mourn-coeds-death-but-ask-public-to-await-investigation-results …    
    
    
    Alam ko namang kasunod na ang pagkilos; ang hirap lang talaga ng lungkot at galit sa pagtawid ng weekend #RIPKristel #UPM #STFAP    
    
    
    happy birthday @choenriquez! hope you had a great one!!! :) and yes, i can already smell your new car!    
    
    
    Luksang Pamantasan para sa batang tinalikuran ng sistema #RIPKristel #STFAP https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=525625484156608&set=a.112535818798912.17293.100001274833088&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    Sem-end fieldwork presentation today on literacy education as a tool of empowerment for grassroots women: I dedicate this to you, #Kristel    
    
    
    UPM Chancy's subtext for lengthy carefully-worded explanation: Wala kaming kasalanan. #UPPressCon #RIPKristel #STFAP    
    
    
    #ScrapSTFAP    
    
    
    "Media ka ba?" "I'm a student". "Media muna pwedeng magtanong." Supalpal ang bata. Wow, turned another student away! #UPPressCon #RIPKristel    
    
    
    when the facilitator turned the UP stude away fr asking Qs, no reaction from the top UP officials present! ok lang kayo?! #UPPressCon #STFAP    
    
    
    I should leave right about now for my presentation, but I am glued to the TV and furious! #UPPressCon #STFAP RIPKristel    
    
    
    no worries, was just happy to see you there > @imaturla Oblation in mourning. #Justice4Kristel #ScrapSTFAP @cindycatz pic.twitter.com/poku6gkaKP    
    
    
    @junglejayps what hope is there for what we are fighting for right now if, in the face of a real-time injustice, officials do nothing?!    
    
    
    Tara, hug na lang tayo. #ScrapSTFAP #JusticeForKristel    
    
    
    Tara, hug na lang tayo, and everything will be okay. #ScrapSTFAP #JusticeForKristel    
    
    
    Ika nga ni Nacho Libre, "Hug hug, kiss kiss, hug hug, big kiss, little hug, kiss kiss, little kiss." #JusticeForKristel #ScrapSTFAP    
    
    
    UPIS Contingent :) - Luksang Pamantasan Day 3 @venzie @cabring pic.twitter.com/7Xsv6TKtJN    
    
    
    our little warrior is graduating from grade school TODAY! congratulations Jade @dlo_oIb! we love you! ♥ ♥ ♥ pic.twitter.com/U7rJYw87BX    
    
    
    @choenriquez cramming :) will hopefully be done in a few days! wish me luck! :)    
    
    
    now addicted to #LoveOnATwoWayStreet by #BozScaggs thanks to cramming and Starbucks ❤    
    
    
    after 2wks of sleeping an hour 2x a day, writing over 200 pages for major papers & 25 pages for 18hour comprehensive exams, twitter na ulit!    
    
    
    and now to marathon Dr. Who, Game of Thrones, and Spartacus :)    
    
    
    Mascot pala ng UP ang Oblation, according to Google! :) pic.twitter.com/JQLh4W5tpD    
    
    
    furious at how evil people abound in comfort/blatant abuse of power, then good people participating in a cause suffered/died #bostonbombings    
    
    
    it's official - i made it! #graduating #MA #UPD    
    
    
    @iamsinning thanks!!! it's about time, had only one sem to go when i went missing for 5 years haha! :) so here i am finally. go ka na din!    
    
    
    @iamsinning thanks! glad go ka na! got a call in October "pinagalitan" lang naman ako ng Women&Devt profs - dahil sa sermon, natapos ako! :)    
    
    
    papers (all 200+pp) done; comprehensive exams (all 2days worth stuck in the CSWCD library) done; & grades of my class finally done! FREEDOM!    
    
    
    OMG Jaime Lannister! (huli sa balita)    
    
    
    @mister_sen let's see each other next week for your birthday and my grad! :)    
    
    
    @SwiminiTiti ooooh Gromit! :)    
    
    
    @mister_sen haha weekends pang lovelife only?!    
    
    
    glad this summer day is over - 37 degrees! lagnat!    
    
    
    how i love having nothing better to do! #postcramming #couchcommando    
    
    
    "Batman is cool and all, but Bill Murray is cooler." :) http://screencrush.com/bill-murray-batman/ …    
    
    
    omelette du fromage!    
    
    
    short nap before hitting the road! :)    
    
    
    @mister_sen happy birthday bukas and happy 4/20 :) see you soon!    
    
    
    @imaturla IMA uy congrats ha! :) just getting little obligations that piled up in the aftermath of my grand cramming :) after grad okay? :)    
    
    
    happy birthday @mister_sen! ❤    
    
    
    at UP Los Banos :) pic.twitter.com/JbEAGqLs56    
    
    
    "a knitted boyfriend" & "no Binay debate" - made me laugh so early in the morning! enjoy! http://www.buzzfeed.com/alannaokun/why-having-a-knitted-boyfriend-is-better-than-an-actual-boyf … AND http://sowhatsnews.wordpress.com/2013/04/20/court-grants-nancy-binays-tpo-petition-against-debates/ …    
    
    
    @carlabaful satire - pero pwede, right?! :)    
    
    
    creative workspaces! as for me, with papers & kids strewn about the house, Starbucks will just have to do for now :) http://www.buzzfeed.com/summeranne/40-inspiring-workspaces-of-the-famously-creative …    
    
    
    i just read the most awesomely presented set of spoilers which has restored my admiration for Daenerys Targaryan!Now to watch #GameOfThrones    
    
    
    some inspiration for you and me - for droughts as well as floods of work that drown your own projects :) http://www.buzzfeed.com/whimseybox/11-pinspired-quotes-to-jumpstart-your-creativity-a3nx …    
    
    
    #nowplaying Baby I Love Your Way #BobMarley ❤    
    
    
    Team Targaryen! ❤ #GameOfThrones    
    
    
    better yet, Team Daenerys - baby dragons, Unsullied army and all! :) #GameOfThrones    
    
    
    just what i need to see right when i am trying to starve myself into shape! grrrrr! http://www.buzzfeed.com/arielknutson/delicious-snacks-in-a-mug …    
    
    
    @lickahstowe mine is strewn with coke and lapid's chicharon as well, and lots of rice and patis! :) i need horse blinders!    
    
    
    i get to practice yet again one of my rules: indulge your heartbreak with a deadline - go on & cry, drink, scream, then promptly move on. :)    
    
    
    the more i am refused reasonable consideration given circumstances,the more staunchly i am convinced to grant others this same consideration    
    
    
    @noemiruth thanks noems! i'm alright, and i bounce back quickly :) i'm graduating on sunday, i'll be free after that! cerveza negra na! :)    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester oohhhh yesssss! this has to happen! be my beach date?! #TanningMatesForever    
    
    
    @noemiruth @david and @d4thwinchester DM :)    
    
    
    @noemiruth @d4thwinchester pano ba, blue? ok naman sayo ang threesome tanning? :) boracay?    
    
    
    @jadedEyes yes, thanks auntie cheer! :) haaay DM :)    
    
    
    @sweetestdrugMJ i love him! #TonyStark #Ironman    
    
    
    @imaturla @noemiruth heehee game! sa beach din kung trip mong sumama, kelangan pa naman planuhin yon so marami pang oras! :) DM    
    
    
    @imaturla conference? speaking engagement abroad? international beauty? :)    
    
    
    @imaturla OMG where?! what degree?! congrats! ikaw ang idol! :)    
    
    
    @imaturla @noemiruth noems si ima pala ang magpapa-inom! #congrats    
    
    
    @imaturla CONGRATS! :)    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester @noemiruth @imaturla i'm fresh off of acads&a bit worn out,so i'd like more comfort&convenience, not yet adventure. boracay?    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester @noemiruth @imaturla WOW! congrats yet again to another performance! we should watch blue! :)    
    
    
    #boracay pic.twitter.com/PrDzmfvnSr    
    
    
    @noemiruth @d4thwinchester @imaturla soooo excited! :) can't wait!    
    
    
    @imaturla bwahahaha i wish! that's from my tanning days with @d4thwinchester :)    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester @noemiruth @imaturla bwahahaha oo nga pala! so july?!    
    
    
    it's the crack of noon! new day, new ideas, new hopes, new things to come ❤    
    
    
    ooooh chocolate mud cake! https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10200150280294851&set=a.4901140681464.1073741826.1086353597&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    after three weeks of chronic sleep debt and adrenaline-induced writing, i finally have time to relax, but it stresses me out!    
    
    
    i even woke up with a start from a rare nap because i felt like there was something urgent that i was supposed to be doing! must relax!    
    
    
    this got me accounting! OMG! > @chiniehdiaz Today's random quote.I don't know who said it,but it always cracks me up. pic.twitter.com/pykxG14ZHd    
    
    
    @lonelyplanet ❤!!!    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester i was just checking out the same dates - that's perfect! :)    
    
    
    MA Women and Development :) next year, it's the trek towards the PhD! pic.twitter.com/2Kq5KAXPKK    
    
    
    @curiouscouch missin you chingbee! ❤ pic.twitter.com/yxgy5iESie    
    
    
    @choenriquez thanks cho! :) ang saya saya after weeks of cramming! :)    
    
    
    my feet have tan lines from a few minutes of walking in the sun - and sadly i'm not at the beach #stupidslippers    
    
    
    if you love the WEEKEND and the end of the workday, thank the labor movement! #happylaborday http://www.rlmarts.com/products/note-cards/labor/nc186.html … pic.twitter.com/ZgNxOdkp0t    
    
    
    "I'd merely take a nap!" >>> Cindycatz in a (portable blue) box    
    
    
    "I merely nap!" >>> Cindycatz, in a portable blue box at UP Diliman or any nearby Starbucks. Timelord optional. Bond and Stark preferred.    
    
    
    dawn breakfast in keeping with diet: one tenth cup rice, and a second helping of oooh-la-Lapid's.… http://instagram.com/p/Y3P8FNJRlU/     
    
    
    happy star wars day! :) #maythefourthbewithyou    
    
    
    a postcard pinned to my professor's door :) http://instagram.com/p/Y3jodKpRvx/     
    
    
    my daughter's awesome baneling cake http://instagram.com/p/Y3lx6qpRi5/     
    
    
    @csugee all hail to you, the supreme #galagirl ❤    
    
    
    upon seeing this photo, my mother-in-law asked my kids, "Bakit naman ganyan suot ng da [her son] niyo?" http://instagram.com/p/Y7EvCzpRpx/     
    
    
    @d4thwinchester @noemiruth yes! :)    
    
    
    RIP Ray Harryhausen, stop-motion animation & visual effects pioneer who has inspired so many. much of what we enjoy today is because of him.    
    
    
    @noemiruth @d4thwinchester so this should be late afternoon or really early morning right? for blue's sked? :)    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester DM :)    
    
    
    have been working on my academic (read: nerdy) blog, excited! :) but progress is sooo slow because I am heavily IT-challenged. grrrrr.    
    
    
    @noemiruth @d4thwinchester i'm good with late afternoon :)    
    
    
    @imaturla heehee pag ready na haha :) and you, when are you leaving? ang beerdate natin!    
    
    
    @imaturla when is soon???!!!    
    
    
    since the hubby did this little protest of my #madsmikkelsen facebook cover photo, i'll just tweet it. haaaaay. :) pic.twitter.com/GPe9EgIJXr    
    
    
    @mister_sen bwahaha you know it! i miss you! ❤    
    
    
    let's see how long it takes to remove this indelible ink #manicure #elections2013    
    
    
    was not happy to see the PCOS screen read "Congratulations!" what i wanted to see was "you voted the following...." #elections2013    
    
    
    ang bilis naming bumoto - @teddycasino! :)    
    
    
    laman ng balota ay dadalawa - @teddycasino at @gabrielaphils! :)    
    
    
    canvassing suspended until tom 10AM? ANG LABO!!!    
    
    
    finger-pointing commences with the discrepancies in figures #elections2013    
    
    
    results are dismal with Teddy Casino at number 22 :(    
    
    
    the FPJ vote is so strong #elections2013    
    
    
    "Debates appeal to a snall sector," and "Nancy Binay's refusal to participate was actly a good strategy." ANC discussion #elections2013    
    
    
    so, political debates - not appealing. politicians doing gangnam style - appealing. haaay. #elections2013    
    
    
    @mister_sen wave wave, flying kiss kiss. haaay.    
    
    
    bantayan ang smartmatic    
    
    
    ANC discussion earlier on social media and nrgative effects on Enrile. all i can say is that i was a 12 year old fan of Alfie Anido.    
    
    
    "She is not very impressive in explaining her stand or what she stands for." Randy David on Nancy Binay, ANC discussion #elections2013    
    
    
    proxy runs and namesakes - discussion on correlations by Randy David right now on ANC midterm elections discussion    
    
    
    #breaktime sa #election2013 my mother-in-law is busy spying the pogi brigade reporters of @gmanews    
    
    
    well, we have the miriam defensor-santiago/nancy binay senate sabong sessions to look forward to :)    
    
    
    kindly reread & analyze my tweet ha? haay. "@Connielicious88 @cindycatz pinag-aaway nyo na agad-agad? buti kung patulan ni nancy si miriam."    
    
    
    as of now, those who will be making decisions that will affect us & our children are binay angara estrada poe aquino villar #ayosbatayojan    
    
    
    a senate win for them will be a stepping stone for running for president & VP in the 2016 elections. scary.    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee Randy David discussed these proxy runs earlier. whatever the purpose, long term it's all about keeping /getting more power!    
    
    
    @mister_sen yeah ang lakas! student council officer siya sa UP nung time ng parents ko, late 60s. i saw in my mom's yearbook. omg.    
    
    
    OMG gas prices going up tom?! talaga lang.    
    
    
    well, it's half past beer! :)    
    
    
    @theallamson hahaha i would gladly give you a live demo just to see you again. ano na? beer na! or margaritas :)    
    
    
    sa dadalawang binoto ko, galak sa lagay ng @GabrielaWomenPL, bwiset na malayo pa bilang ni @teddycasino. at sobrang galit sa smartmatic!    
    
    
    @carlabaful OMG!!! bongga! #KrisWillBeatNancyIn2016PresidentialElections    
    
    
    @theallamson when will you be in town? :)    
    
    
    with my senator :) http://instagram.com/p/ZVsHzNJRnU/     
    
    
    @lickahstowe he is! what a tragedy :(    
    
    
    back then, i used to do the hubby's corn rows :) http://instagram.com/p/ZVvVo4pRsI/     
    
    
    thank you chingbee and adam! wheeee! http://instagram.com/p/ZaSpMRpRtP/     
    
    
    just began reading The Nation of Rebels (or Rebel Sell) - the introduction's got me all revved up! :)    
    
    
    "Having a teenage daughter is like having a chicken in the swamp, and there are gators all around." #DuckDynasty #HistoryChannel    
    
    
    so ladies, are we all okay with being referred to as chicken meat? #DuckDynasty #HistoryChannel    
    
    
    so excited about the @NatGeo feature tonight at 10PM on the 80s! my teenage years! :)    
    
    
    now watching "the 80s" on @NatGeo! amazing! :)    
    
    
    happy birthday @sherylldb! just realized i havn't seen you for so long!& when i could,it'd been so hard to get a hold of you! enjoy!see you!    
    
    
    @ramonbautista happy birthday! hope you had a great one, sir! :)    
    
    
    "Say it like you're coming back." #DoctorWho    
    
    
    When you make a movie for a social activism purpose,you have to make a movie they will like regardless of whether they agree #the80s @NatGeo    
    
    
    vid of NASA space shuttle that exploded with "teacher in space" stl heartbreaking, as it had been when i was in highschool #the80s @NatGeo    
    
    
    rushed to check why my mom was screaming in time to see #6 in white make a winning basket in 2.2 seconds left with a 1 point lead OMG! #NBA    
    
    
    inspiring how a seemingly sure loss became a win! :)    
    
    
    @noemiruth the two of them married #truestory hahaha :)    
    
    
    lawsuit for Nutella fans' homage http://prdaily.com/Main/Articles/14534.aspx …    
    
    
    companies and their lawyers should take a good hard look at whether a move is copyright infringement or clearly loving homage #nutella    
    
    
    ex-chief Monsod says Comelec should not get intel funds  http://www.interaksyon.com/article/62407/comelec-should-not-get-intel-funds-says-ex-chief-monsod-as-brillantes-assails-lagmans-motive …    
    
    
    Lagman returns intel money Comelec should not even have in the first place, & gets blasted for it by the commissioner http://www.abs-cbnnews.com/nation/05/23/13/brillantes-lagman-had-return-funds …    
    
    
    Oh such handsome sons of Paula Deen :)    
    
    
    the first step: a pension for housework! :) #WomenAndTheNewLaborLaw http://rabble.ca/columnists/2013/05/venezuelas-new-labour-law-best-mothers-day-gift …    
    
    
    Chloe grumpily watches over her little brother and sister http://instagram.com/p/ZqAx6mpRuu/     
    
    
    sisters :) http://instagram.com/p/ZqOn1QpRhi/     
    
    
    flood of 80s memories because of "The 80s: The Decade That Made Us" :)    
    
    
    hubby & little girl - torchlight; little boy - minecraft; university girl - streaming starcraft tourney. i'm the only one unplugged at home!    
    
    
    of course, in tweeting, i got plugged for a minute. and now to let go yet again of my gadgets - appropriated by the kids. back to the book!    
    
    
    been up since 7AM, and have been reading in absolute peace! they're all still asleep! ❤    
    
    
    too lazy to get coffee    
    
    
    began working on my talk two weeks ago in an effort not to cram. seems my brain will cooperate only when i'm down to the last few hours    
    
    
    in my effort to work on my talks & ppts, i have followed 20 more tumblr blogs, stumbled upon a few ideas for writing, looked at pix of cats    
    
    
    after successfully avoiding work while earnestly trying to work since 7AM, I guess it's time for coffee ❤    
    
    
    of course, the important ideas will come later, when my crazy kids are all bustling and howling around me and i'm caught up being "mommy" ❤    
    
    
    last night was nuts - watched the starcraft tourney as my kids cheered & explained to me what looked like cockroaches charging at each other    
    
    
    years & years ago, the hubby tried to recruit me to starcraft - I do play Diablo after all, & developed a mean sorceress before Diablo III    
    
    
    all i ever understood were "We require more minerals" and "Zephraim Cochrane, is that you?" everything else, Greek    
    
    
    @mister_sen hi david! checking it out now, looks good! :) your tip came just in time since, well, i haven't done anything yet. haha ❤    
    
    
    just watched Revenge Of The Nerds #80sKid    
    
    
    first time to visit Manila Central University :) thank you MCU #MCUenglishworkshop    
    
    
    cramming anew for another workshop :)    
    
    
    celebrating my first anniversary breakup with ciggies - my first year of smoke-free life since 1986 ❤    
    
    
    thanks to the 3 kids who never gave up on me stopping & the hubby who joined me in smoke-free bliss 6mos ago ❤ sarap pala maging healthy!    
    
    
    thanks @iamsinning! :) thesis turned into comps on subjects taken 5-7 years ago & additional fieldwork & papers - but yes, still smoke free!    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee thank you! :)    
    
    
    Just as mentioned in Men In Black, the world is always almost about to end. Shudder! http://news.cnet.com/8301-17938_105-57587097-1/watch-the-enormous-qe2-binary-asteroid-pass-by-earth/ …    
    
    
    fat bastard in the house! :) i mean fatboy slim #RightHereRightNow    
    
    
    i used to admire him so, but now i love him! thank you for this @SirPatStew! fr a longtime fan & worker for women :) http://www.upworthy.com/a-brave-fan-asks-patrick-stewart-a-question-he-doesnt-usually-get-and-is-given-a-beautiful-answer?c=gt1 …    
    
    
    working on my next talk #teachertraining    
    
    
    such sweet peace - a quiet, cloudy morning and i'm the only one up! :)    
    
    
    finally done cramming for tomorrow's talk! and now to bed... but wait, let me just paint my nails :)    
    
    
    My latest upload : Guidelines and practical approaches for test c… on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/guidelines-and-practical-approaches-for-test-construction-cindy-cruzcabrera …    
    
    
    Practical approaches for cultivating english proficiency may 29 talk by @cindycatz on @slideshare #education #english http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/practical-approaches-for-cultivating-english-proficiency-may-29-talk …    
    
    
    hoping it wouldn't happen, yet still shocked despite. #redwedding    
    
    
    will this never end?! #powerpointcramming    
    
    
    and I'm back in the college classroom today! :)    
    
    
    @fingon116 good morning rin!    
    
    
    Introduction to principles of written communication2 cindy cruz-cabrera ppt by @cindycatz on @slideshare #ESA #Thames http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/introduction-to-principles-of-written-communication-2-cindy-cruzcabrerappt …    
    
    
    My latest upload : Introduction to contemporary world literature … #ESA #Thames on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/introduction-to-contemporary-world-literature-cindy-cruzcabrerappt …    
    
    
    This is about how this man looks at women, and what he finds funny ... and it is a judgment on him as well. http://www.rappler.com/thought-leaders/30586-the-rape-of-jessica-soho …    
    
    
    wow! for your art, @csugee and @dlo_oIb ❤ 27 Stunning Works Of Art You Won’t Believe Aren’t Photographs http://www.buzzfeed.com/hnigatu/works-of-art-you-wont-believe-arent-photographs … via @buzzfeed    
    
    
    Margarita #mentionatruefriend bwahaha #gayagaya @lickahstowe Jack Daniels #mentionatruefriend    
    
    
    Use celebrity status to promote awareness of the issue of violence against women... contribute to ending violence. http://entertainment.inquirer.net/96745/message-from-monique-wilson-to-vice-ganda#ixzz2VRl5mZEg …    
    
    
    @csugee was 4 when she & her dad started playing #starcraft. now 18, our journ major's attending barcraft w/ #starcraftph on sun #timeflies    
    
    
    me? i'm a dinosaur. i love the old #diablo and my ass-kicking sorceress, whose skills trees had to be painstakingly built back in the day ❤    
    
    
    so the kids are now up :)    
    
    
    happy about the free month offered for slideshare pro! but, as it turns out, it's for a subscription, not a trial. awwww.    
    
    
    kids off to school next week - then will come time for more writing! now if only i could stay away from photos of cats, coffee, pinterest...    
    
    
    "mommy..." "mommy?" "mom." "mom!" >>> all within the minute they woke up - my day as an adult has officially started. :)    
    
    
    isaw!!!    
    
    
    It's not about finding solutions. It's just about managing expectations. #HANNIBAL    
    
    
    I'm not sand, I'm bedrock. When you doubt yourself, you don't have to doubt me. #HANNIBAL    
    
    
    just woke up and it's long after lunch - haven't done this in a while, not since i left graveyard work. it SUCKS.    
    
    
    my Doctor Who choice: Ben Whishaw :) pic.twitter.com/I7NOTzDBEf    
    
    
    @bbcdoctorwho i vote Ben Whishaw for Doctor Who ❤ #TheNewDoctor #DoctorWho pic.twitter.com/lFvT20E39S    
    
    
    @WhovianNet i vote Ben Whishaw for Doctor Who ❤ #TheNewDoctor #DoctorWho pic.twitter.com/lFvT20E39S    
    
    
    is it true maturity or mere laziness when the millenial daughter is off to barcraft and the gen-x parents prefer to crash the couch at home?    
    
    
    happy family time together: @cabring, inigo & jade multiplayer torchlight; @csugee streaming-tweeting-WOWwing; deviceless me reading a book    
    
    
    thursday: drive-thru frap day ❤    
    
    
    i just ❤ Tyler Durden    
    
    
    rainy night at home - perfect for a couch potato all-nighter! :)    
    
    
    watching NatGeo, but not in peace - surrounded by my little why-wolves "mom! mom? mom. mom... mom! momomom!!!"    
    
    
    ASTI Organizational & Project Gender Analysis on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/asti-organizational-and-project-gender-analysis-jeng-tetangco-queen-olivar-and-cindy-cruzcabrera …. Read full paper here: http://cindycruzcabrera.wordpress.com/papers/     
    
    
    @csugee how's barcraft? :)    
    
    
    @csugee is it over? we're not streaming right now :(    
    
    
    View the ASTI Organizational & Project Gender Analysis on @slideshare #breastfeeding #gender #technology #MDG #women http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/asti-organizational-and-project-gender-analysis-jeng-tetangco-queen-olivar-and-cindy-cruzcabrera …    
    
    
    wide awake sooooo early!    
    
    
    alright, must slowly get movin! :) hello monday! hello students! hello writing! & this week's challenges, prepare to have your asses kicked!    
    
    
    sooooo pretty! #angelinajolie http://www.espressogossip.com/articles/view/123/page:3 …    
    
    
    alright, this time i'm really off to a start na! :) happy monday!    
    
    
    Bien Lumbera:PDI ought to have spoken up for the artist instead of panicking & disowning the artist. @artistangbayan http://www.interaksyon.com/article/63694/concerned-artists-of-ph-lambast-inquirer-for-failing-to-stand-up-for-pugad-baboy …    
    
    
    so my 9am class was cancelled - super bad traffic and a sea of humanity on the streets! :)    
    
    
    rain + bad traffic + difficult commute = cancelled class + forced cab ride + that evil starbucks drive through!    
    
    
    My latest upload: The Sentence as Speech Act on @slideshare #ESA #Thames #SpeechAct #WrittenCommunication #English http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/the-sentence-as-speech-act …    
    
    
    @jayseemerollin so you're a DJ? where do i tune in? :)    
    
    
    @cabring to me: "I am heeeeeelium to your balloooonish heart." heehee hahaha    
    
    
    @lickahstowe exciting!!! sked please!    
    
    
    @lickahstowe sweet!    
    
    
    @cabring:unintelligible sweet nothings. me:WHAT? i can't hear you, there's a plane. now he & @csugee won't stop wth the fantasy island thing    
    
    
    OMG happy birthday @carlabaful! growl growl si daddy bear nung sinabi ko sa kanya, di niya nabati baby bear niya haha :)    
    
    
    This smacks of a true teacher as a manager! http://lnkd.in/sUzmCn     
    
    
    "A true teacher defends his students against his own personal influences." >>> Amos Bronson Alcott    
    
    
    "The true teacher ...inspires self-trust. He guides their eyes from himself to the spirit that quickens him. He will have no disciples." ABA    
    
    
    okay, got sucked in again into mindless pursuits. why is it such a guilty pleasure looking at candid random celebrity photos?! argh    
    
    
    i enjoyed the #GameOfThrones episode. please, we can't have a #RedWedding every time!    
    
    
    dahil may kalayaan akong i-tweet at i-coverpic si keanu reeves kahit nagproprotesta ang aking irog ❤ pic.twitter.com/VMPJLtQlVG    
    
    
    me to hubby > choose: you can go on hating my detailed explanations OR you can demand detailed explanations of me. you can't have both!!!    
    
    
    i am just getting more and more forgetful. even my lists of things and locations need finding. thank God for pocket and evernote!    
    
    
    @noemiruth finally found 1 of the lists i needed, but only after flustering everybody - the kids were all "OMG keep away from mom" mode haha    
    
    
    sure, couples share accounts on facebook and twitter. i wonder, how does it work on linkedin?    
    
    
    i hope the little pains go away soon. i hate the drowsiness brought on by the meds and the where-am-i feeling i get upon waking    
    
    
    My latest upload: Violence and Sanction in Philippine Tribal Societies #anthropology #feminism #women @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/cindy-cruzcabrera-violence-and-sanction-in-the-malefemale-dynamic-of-ilongot-tausug-and-teduray-societies …    
    
    
    restlessly waiting for kids to get home. sky here simply overcast but have just seen news of the pouring rain and scary clouds - OMG!    
    
    
    family is complete, everyone home now ❤ hope everyone out there's alright, getting home in one piece, in this weather    
    
    
    exactly 20 years ago when @cabring and i were shiny new UP grads and the youngest UP faculty members! ❤ pic.twitter.com/QLGvkOLLM5    
    
    
    took a late trip to the nearby store with my little boy, who told me not to worry about the darkness - because he had a sonic screwdriver! ❤    
    
    
    "Life is like riding a bicycle. To keep your balance, you must keep moving." >>> Albert Einstein    
    
    
    feeling my 40s more and more as i can no longer endure overnight marathoning without consequences #Firefly    
    
    
    happy birthday to my little love INIGO, my little doctor with a handy dandy sonic screwdriver! ❤    
    
    
    yey Friday! :) wheee!    
    
    
    our HS freshie is thrilled with her "new" school life, our 2nd grader excited abt his rainy birthday. our college girl is still out there :(    
    
    
    creepy posts on my facebook timeline! most of my contacts have good netiquette, don't feel inclined to limit everything because of just one    
    
    
    so when posts to my timeline are blatantly crass, i delete and block. but what to do with creepy?    
    
    
    @mister_sen hahaha yep, laid back praning :) and the college girl is home now    
    
    
    well, after all the mental retaliations, the high ground still prevailed. sucks.    
    
    
    happy birthday to our little luv, Inigo! ❤ with his sisters @dlo_oIb and @csugee, his spittin image! :) pic.twitter.com/DfhyETtpUh    
    
    
    we kept guessing who's gna die, who's gna die next. such cackles with each guess, there seemed to be a cauldron in our midst #InaKapatidAnak    
    
    
    @noemiruth my scalding remarks gave way to high ground, blame it on yrs of training (wow, a shade of "50 shades") w/ parents & nuns. bwiset.    
    
    
    kids and hubby in stitches yet again over #MontyPython #TheHolyGrail    
    
    
    @noemiruth no worries! in the immortal words of Chaucer, "I will eviscerate you in fiction!" >>> The Knight's Tale ❤ heeheehee    
    
    
    @carlabaful (upon reading your tweet) me: giggles! @cabring : snort! ever the daddy bear :)    
    
    
    hi @luiskatigbak! my book is still waiting for your autograph #HappyEndings :)    
    
    
    happy birthday @curiouscouch! ❤ we love you! :)    
    
    
    20+ years ago - back when i was college kid crashing the araneta backstage at a #HallnOates concert ❤ pic.twitter.com/E1mJGXfpxT    
    
    
    soooo timey-wimey! super LIKE! >>> @noemiruth @cindycatz a thought just occurred to me. "Eviscerate! Eviscerate! Eviscerate!" #Daleks style.    
    
    
    happy father's day! ❤    
    
    
    happy birthday @NiccoDemonyo! :)    
    
    
    happy father's day DAD! here w mom - both UP kids in the 60s, the med resident & his girlfriend-nursing student we❤u! pic.twitter.com/yKN1L3DcfF    
    
    
    thanks for that super sweet vid link @IAmAnnBurgos! #HallnOates :)    
    
    
    I'd take the hard truth anytime. Always have. #readingresponse #GRRMartin    
    
    
    My latest upload: Women and the All UP Unions: Mainstreaming the Women's Agenda on @slideshare http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/jelina-tetangco-and-cindy-cruz-cabrera-women-and-the-all-up-unions …    
    
    
    thank you tito adam @SwiminiTiti @swiminititi! i'm craaaaaazy about it! - inigo #happybirthday… http://instagram.com/p/apzhLTpRud/     
    
    
    rainy days and Mondays #ChildhoodSongs    
    
    
    one of the best feelings in the world: when all the children are safe at home at last - then i can finally tune out the world (for a bit)    
    
    
    and now for comfort food to match the rainy day ❤    
    
    
    still waiting for my Assumption girl - she should be home from the hills soon :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez it's pouring here now! :(    
    
    
    @choenriquez are all three boys still out there? we're still waiting for jade    
    
    
    @choenriquez the good news is the rain just let up. if it stays that way, the river should soon pass :) have a safe drive!    
    
    
    @choenriquez good news is it's remained just a drizzle. traffic both ways though - jade is 1 hour late na from antipolo, so you can imagine!    
    
    
    @curiouscouch and @SwiminiTiti are you both still out? on the road?    
    
    
    it's raining hard again. my daughter's schoolbus is still stuck in traffic, about 200m from home, but there's no way for us to get to her :(    
    
    
    everyone is home sweet home now :) rain back again to a drizzle here    
    
    
    @csugee I, mother of Chloe, hereby suspend all of her classes tomorrow henceforth at UP Diliman until further notice #WalangPasokBukas    
    
    
    @jadedEyes auntie cheer! are you still on the road? jade arrived a few minutes ago!    
    
    
    @jadedEyes ah oh ok! heehee duling na ko sa pagaabang na makauwi na ang mga anak! haaay! :)    
    
    
    it's raining grumkins and snarks! #TeamTyrionLannister    
    
    
    @choenriquez where are you na?    
    
    
    turuan na ba? #BahaMasSaPilipinas    
    
    
    @curiouscouch @SwiminiTiti we're all home. good na rin he's not on the road, hirap daw!    
    
    
    @choenriquez OMG!!! hope you're okay :(    
    
    
    storm to intensify wothin the next 24 hours - kids must stay home then!    
    
    
    "Magic's just science that we don't understand yet." >>> Arthur C. Clarke | i am ready and waiting for some magic! hit me! :)    
    
    
    on certain days, Facebook posts of avid TMI-ers can be quite entertaining :)    
    
    
    my raging mood needs calming. maybe chocolate will do it.    
    
    
    a swig of coke brought a rush of happiness - i am too easy to please!    
    
    
    #TheSpaceBetween the bullets in our firefight is where i'll be hiding, waiting for you    
    
    
    to scare off pervs http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/06/17/china-hair-stockings_n_3455250.html …    
    
    
    big spiders in the bathroom? i got it! flying ipis? no problem (inclusive of shrieks). but little mice stuck to flypaper? stab me.    
    
    
    what a challenge to teach students so restless in class because of the impending basketball finals overtime    
    
    
    basketball viewing time at the office of student affairs haha :)    
    
    
    boys: "Ms, can we have free cut? Please?! Miami won!" celebration? #what #labo    
    
    
    someone at school said i lost so much weight! YAY! (no, not my student AND no, i didn't pay him to say it)    
    
    
    having the most heavenly spoiling feet thing at PoshNails thanks to @curiouscouch! :)    
    
    
    nearly dozed off while being rubbed down with oils and scrubs - was almost convinced i became Daenerys Targaryen ❤    
    
    
    JKRowling prefers to let themes "grow organically", rather than sitting down and consciously attempting to impart such ideas to her readers.    
    
    
    "The key for [Rowling] was the choice between what is right and what is easy." Thanks to Wiki for this morning's random insightful reading!    
    
    
    no more wedding ring for Nigella http://www.eonline.com/news/431934/nigella-lawson-steps-out-without-her-wedding-ring-after-choking-incident?cmpid=tweol-manual …    
    
    
    Charles Saatchi termed his gestures of putting hand on Nigella's throat an attempt "to emphasize my point". http://www.guardian.co.uk/lifeandstyle/2013/jun/17/charles-saatchi-nigella-lawson-playful-tiff …    
    
    
    wrong move trying to read a book now at the office of student affairs #NBAfinals    
    
    
    so "outright violence" is not acceptable, but "discreet violence" is alright? #VAWC    
    
    
    talk of who's buying pizza here #NBAfinals #bets    
    
    
    thrilled and thankful for a grant invite to apply, but so sorry it came only a few days before the deadline. thus, the next round it is! :)    
    
    
    friday ending with opportunities academic, professional & mischievous ❤ awesome if i get to spend this evening with mads mikkelsen #hannibal    
    
    
    had a good business meeting earlier - thank you dear god and the universe! :) happy friday!    
    
    
    #hannibal    
    
    
    OMG help meeeeeeee!aaaaaah! pic.twitter.com/tXANmjH6rQ    
    
    
    @SwiminiTiti and @curiouscouch happy palawan! :)    
    
    
    it's been a long time since i've been called "cher" (suddenly remembering xavier students!)    
    
    
    earlier today, the "psycho" theme playing in my head haha :) thank you for taking care of me auntie… http://instagram.com/p/a3GbPUJRmr/     
    
    
    @jadedEyes thanks to my facorite dentist for the post-checkup frappuccino and cheddar and sour cream pringles! :)    
    
    
    always wonderful to go to our favorite dentist @jadedEyes - there's always a treat after the treatment! ❤    
    
    
    happy textbook meeting capped off with a lovely mug of tsokolate-ah :) http://instagram.com/p/a3PxBJJRiO/     
    
    
    the vow of the Night's Watch is a choice of an honorable life of service, not an excuse for the solitary existence of a bigot #pretensions    
    
    
    Fear cuts deeper than swords. #Syrio #Arya    
    
    
    The man who fears losing has already lost. #Syrio #Arya    
    
    
    time to leap! >>> "Sometimes only leaping can clear the fog and then the other side appears." https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10151662184497988&set=a.302899137987.148033.60086777987&type=1&theater … pic.twitter.com/ZgxI05efvW    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester hello tanning mate! i got your messages, DM in a bit! :)    
    
    
    on women's studies and men's studies https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=580632538644275&set=a.367249613315903.85664.354522044588660&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    "The things that we love destroy us every time, lad. Remember that." >>> Lord Steward Mormont to #JonSnow #GoT    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra i do hope that's not my paper! hahaha :)    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra just teasing! :) ganyan din ako heehee    
    
    
    "You stiff-necked fool, too proud to listen. Can you eat pride, Stark? Will honor shield your children?" #RobertBarratheon to #NedStark #GoT    
    
    
    "The forest is the abbatoir [sic] of the gods." #Varys #GoT    
    
    
    "We are only human, and the gods have fashioned us for love. That is our great glory, and our great tragedy." #MaesterAemon to #JonSnow #GoT    
    
    
    I solemnly swear that I am up to no good. #MaraudersMap    
    
    
    Watch 3rd-graders learn in 2 days what most of us can't learn in a lifetime. @frontlinepbs (via @Upworthy)  http://www.upworthy.com/watch-a-teacher-make-her-3rd-grade-kids-hate-each-other-for-the-best-reason-imaginable-2?g=3 …    
    
    
    “We are proud to present ‘My Father’s Lover‘, the first church-themed series in Philippine television." @SoWhatsNews http://sowhatsnews.wordpress.com/2013/06/26/upon-cbcps-request-mtrcb-suspends-my-husbands-lover-gma7-to-replace-it-with-my-fathers-lover/ …    
    
    
    yes, i'm a catholic girl. doesn't mean i should be braindead, right? :)    
    
    
    IN CLASS TODAY:
student ogling my book: GoT!
me: Can't wait to read the others!
student: ___ kills ___ in the 3rd book!
me: GET OUT! :)    
    
    
    "The hard truths are the ones to hold tight." #LordCommanderMormont to #JonSnow #GoT    
    
    
    "The man who trusts in spells is dueling with a glass sword." #MaesterLuwin >>> would it were dragonglass, i could use some spells right now    
    
    
    enjoyed! especially TCHOTCHKE :) >>> 9 Yiddish loanwords to make you a maven http://dictionary.reference.com/?sshow=yiddish-words&slide=1 … via @dictionarycom    
    
    
    "Laws have a teaching effect. Laws that discriminate validate other kinds of discrimination." >>> Hillary Clinton, on LGBT rights    
    
    
    "My love is the same as yours. Not different, not special, but just equal to you." @shakirasison http://www.rappler.com/move-ph/ispeak/32280-same-sex-marriage-equal-heterosexual … @rapplerdotcom    
    
    
    starting to realize i'm too optimistic for my own good, but i'm sure this feeling will pass soon    
    
    
    @teachervic maestro! :)    
    
    
    If I look back I am lost. #Daenerys #KeepMovingForward #DontLookBack    
    
    
    2006: UP contingent sa Makati rally a lifetime ago with the current Dept of Women & Devt Studies Chair & CSWCD Dean pic.twitter.com/Wn5Mkaarnv    
    
    
    "a head full of fears has no space for dreams" https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=522073247848116&set=p.522073247848116&type=1&theater …    
    
    
    timelords! #LeftBehindByDrWho >>> 100 year-old watch found in tomb sealed for 400 years? http://www.dailymail.co.uk/sciencetech/article-1096959/Mystery-century-old-Swiss-watch-discovered-ancient-tomb-sealed-400-years.html#socialLinks …    
    
    
    "My first rule of war, Cat - never give the enemy his wish." >>> Ser Brynden Blackfish #AClashOfKings    
    
    
    According to #Varys, power resides where I believe it to reside. Hmmm, let me decide. #AClashOfKings    
    
    
    @teachervic remembering when (what, 20 years ago?) you required the assumption girls to all call you "maestro"! :)    
    
    
    @teachervic good, thanks! how've you been?    
    
    
    when sadness strikes: cry, starve a little, and - ooooh, i lost my little potbelly! AWESOME! :)    
    
    
    AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHH! >>> @noemiruth Game of Thrones LEGO Minifigs on Sale NOW! http://bit.ly/17noarp     
    
    
    more archaeological mysteries that i only attribute to timelords :) http://www.collective-evolution.com/2013/01/17/6-baffling-discoveries-that-science-cant-explain/?fb_action_ids=10151712867482069&fb_action_types=og.likes&fb_source=other_multiline&action_object_map=%7B%2210151712867482069%22%3A327485034026766%7D&action_type_map=%7B%2210151712867482069%22%3A%22og.likes%22%7D&action_ref_map=%5B%5D#_ …    
    
    
    @noemiruth we collect minifigs! must have these! :)    
    
    
    baffling >>> "She stole another’s identity, and took her secret to the grave. Who was she?" http://seattletimes.com/html/localnews/2021243552_janedoexml.html …    
    
    
    @noemiruth above all, must get Tyrion Lannister to go with all my tinier minifigs - my garden gnome etc!!! ❤    
    
    
    "I've spent $40,000 on shoes and I have no place to live?" >>> remembering Carrie Bradshaw and her shoes @SATCQuotes    
    
    
    @carlabaful banas din ako at the end. lech. :)    
    
    
    @chitomirandajr oh no pagaling ka chito! after ng onting pahinga, adrenaline ang gasolina mo later sa sure na matinding tugtugan! rakenrol!❤    
    
    
    There are ghosts everywhere. We carry them with us wherever we go. #SerJorahMormont to #Daenerys #AClashOfKings    
    
    
    @fingon116 reading the second, but i have the 5 ebooks, how many are there ba? you done reading them? :) oh do you also have the DUNE ebook?    
    
    
    When you tear out a man's tongue, you are not proving him a liar, you're only telling the world that you fear what he might say. #Tyrion    
    
    
    10 years after reedley: mini-reunion with junnie + minnie's birthday! :) http://instagram.com/p/bJWlFuJRke/     
    
    
    you have no power over me #labyrinth    
    
    
    my all time favorite: A Buddhist monk approaches a hot dog stand and says, "Make me one with everything." http://www.buzzfeed.com/daves4/jokes-only-nerds-will-understand …    
    
    
    my favorite from this list: What happens when you cross a joke with a rhetorical question? :) http://www.buzzfeed.com/daves4/jokes-only-nerds-will-understand …    
    
    
    hewwo! (nose muffled due to allergies) i come in peace!    
    
    
    @SwiminiTiti i emailed you na! :)    
    
    
    dreams haunted by the lannisters, by the houses - reading really gets them into your head the weird way! #ASOIF    
    
    
    hello rainy friday! feeling much better today, plus it's the end of the week! :)    
    
    
    i would like to invite you to connect with me on linkedin :) http://ph.linkedin.com/in/cindycruzcabrera …    
    
    
    "Computer mouse inventor dies at 88" >>> thank you for your legacy! http://www.interaksyon.com/infotech/computer-mouse-inventor-dies-at-88 …    
    
    
    recovery day yesterday at home spent marathoning #GameOfThrones S1 while sorting/folding clothes & cooking :) now S2 while doing the laundry    
    
    
    i know, i should be reading/reviewing the novels i'm teaching, catching up on my papers to check, creating my ppts. alright, GoT awaits! bye    
    
    
    best decision: be a slightly sick, slobbery couch potato until kids get home - only then should i begin my day as an adult. agreed? agreed!    
    
    
    @SwiminiTiti thank you! when are you coming over? wala daw kayo sa sunday? :(    
    
    
    @fingon116 recovering, bad allergies into bad cold, no voice & general zombieness :( couldn't teach all week so my students are super happy!    
    
    
    @choenriquez haha :) just lock your door, boss! tapos may sign that says, "tweet me if you need me" :)    
    
    
    "What would you do if you weren’t afraid?" >>> Sheryl Sandberg, COO Facebook    
    
    
    Check out my @aboutdotme page - http://about.me/cindycruzcabrera … :)    
    
    
    excited again! hope to get all my writing done soon - at least the writing i've been putting off, the writing that's been piling up! :)    
    
    
    @fingon116 must read DUNE! :) and marathon it as well!    
    
    
    after the cramming/rushing/writing to graduate, after MA grad, i relaxed too much, lost my groove. hence my new title: the occasional writer    
    
    
    i am the occasional writer ❤    
    
    
    my son came home with rashes all over fr higad. immediately bathed him, put caladryl all over him. he asked, excited: di ako papasok? #tuso    
    
    
    my 2nd daughter arrived, saw his rashes, hugged him right away. awww, sweet! then she told me, "i'll catch the itchies & be absent tom too!"    
    
    
    @strangechiq thanks jed!:) though it's more like my feeble attempt at feeling good about not writing enough - or not writing heehee :)    
    
    
    @strangechiq left school for five years din, last year ko na dapat nung classmates tayo kay sir bing. game game game na to you! :)    
    
    
    @strangechiq was actly summoned by the Chair, given a mild scolding for my 5yr AWOL,& advised to do comps instead. shempre, sagot ko "OPO!"    
    
    
    really enjoying redesigning the blogs, learning new techie tricks (which must be old since i'm no techie). i think i'm just avoiding writing    
    
    
    student, on behalf of the class: MA'AM! Chismis po, asawa nyo daw yung--
me: yeah, yeah
student: isa sa Parokya ni Edgar?! #facepalm #kaloka    
    
    
    @noemiruth @KnowledgeBishop except if it's @IamStevenT's ❤ "i'm the one who jaded you!" *air guitars*    
    
    
    "cancer: may topak / saltik" >>> hahaha hindi ha... heehee....    
    
    
    work | play | home >>> lovely friday!    
    
    
    head a little clearer, the buzz a few notches lower. Korean movie "I Saw The Devil" also helped jolt me back into my senses. But ugh ugh ugh    
    
    
    word of the day: nakaamba :)    
    
    
    @artistangbayan happy 30th anniversary! :)    
    
    
    just came home from the 30th anniversary celebration of CAP at Kalayaan College. shook Sir Bien's hand! #starstruck @iamsinning @ayalumbera    
    
    
    To be a ninja, you have to avoid the 3 diseases: never doubt, never fear, and never overthink. >>> Ninja Shadow Warriors on History Channel    
    
    
    @choenriquez thanks cho! :)    
    
    
    @jadedEyes thanks auntie cheer! :)    
    
    
    happy with yesterday and today's writing :)    
    
    
    today on Java-Diggin' Cat: "Everyday Feminisms: What Is Reproductive Work?" by @cindycatz http://tmblr.co/ZKCaMypeO9ky     
    
    
    today on Crackin' the Cat O'Nine: "Wife, Mom, and Occasional Writer" by @cindycatz http://cindycatz.wordpress.com/2013/07/15/wife-mom-and-occasional-writer/#more-47 …    
    
    
    Read the full paper on the Gender Analysis of ASTI & their tabletop human breast milk pasteurizer by @cindycatz http://cindycruzcabrera.wordpress.com/2013/07/16/organizational-gender-analysis-and-project-case-study-abstract-and-blog-post-list/ …    
    
    
    sleepy, so why no sleep?! grrrrr    
    
    
    marathonned 3 seasons of Game of Thrones for 3 days while folding and organizing clothes - i got a lot done just sitting on the couch! :)    
    
    
    then when American Dad's Francine said she needed to find clothes to fold, my kids looked at me and cracked up!    
    
    
    Secret Asians #AmericanDad    
    
    
    I'm incendiary too! #AlmostFamous    
    
    
    @noemiruth hahaha it's crazy how my kids love it :)    
    
    
    Lava te las manos. Lava te las manos... LAVA TE LAS MANOS!  #AmericanDad    
    
    
    midterm exams of my classes today - this will be a day of both fulfilling and entertaining reads - and then it's the weekend! :)    
    
    
    students playing guitars and singing at the Office of Student Affairs #Harana    
    
    
    Papers, Pursuits and Purrsuasions by @cindycatz: writings & ramblings on the academe, profession, community, advocacy http://cindycruzcabrera.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    always part of the Terms of Reference #starbucks #presentstions #talks #coffee http://instagram.com/p/b-jWk4JRml/     
    
    
    Jade and Inigo chillin in UPLB :) http://instagram.com/p/b-j_MtpRnT/     
    
    
    tips and tootsies get the royal treatment :) - with my mom and sister chingbee @curiouscouch http://instagram.com/p/b-kaIJpRnq/     
    
    
    When you eliminate the impossible, whatever remains, however improbable, must be the truth. #Spock #StarTrek #marathoning    
    
    
    it's not thursday, but here's a throwback from 2008 - at eastwood with my fave UP profs @cabring and @ramonbautista ❤ pic.twitter.com/zhQU19pQ2m    
    
    
    my little inigo off to Lourdes right now :) enjoy your monday, my little love! http://instagram.com/p/cCw6RGpRgc/     
    
    
    our little birthday girl and high school frehie (still sleepy and reeling from the cam flash), who… http://instagram.com/p/cC1xPPpRpj/     
    
    
    4 UPD students arrested, now detained #SONA2013 - these students must remain surfaced, they should remain in our sights    
    
    
    "We need to have a national conversation about this." >>> Yes, every sector should have a voice. #SONA2013 #ANC #CuratoFrancoAnalysis    
    
    
    yeah i'm your boss, don't you forget it! and wow to your opening disclaimer too :) #SONA2013    
    
    
    layunin sa edukasyon, K-12, itaas ang kalidad? o initiative para sa labor export na naaayon sa "world class" employability? #SONA2013    
    
    
    smells like lots of love in the time of public-private partnership! #SONA2013    
    
    
    yeah, that's what it felt like all these were leading up to lauding #PPP #SONA2013    
    
    
    who will guard the guards themselves, mr president? #SONA2013 #violence #arms #police    
    
    
    we know that not all  incidents of election-related violence are reported or recorded, mr president #SONA2013    
    
    
    OO MAY MALASAKIT AKO! KAYA NGA NAGHAHASIK E #vigilance #SONA2013    
    
    
    PNoy' thought bubble: anjan naman ang US para sa "credible defense" , wag sana masyadong kumpromiso ang kapalit! asa pa #SONA2013    
    
    
    i want my share of those flowers ha #MWSS #SONA2013 #GOCC    
    
    
    sino pa ba ang dapat managot? how about Joseph Estrada and Gloria? #SONA2013    
    
    
    smoker's cough yan, ser. on that point i must agree with you, mr president: smoking is such a joy. #SONA2013    
    
    
    friendster portion #testimonials #SONA2013    
    
    
    PNoy, at the end of SONA: "Ayus! Yosi break na!"    
    
    
    @anyaanyaanya haha me :)    
    
    
    sumakit ulo ko sa #SONA2013 sa kaka kunot ng noo    
    
    
    it felt like the SONA was crafted for foreign investors. >>> Dr Curato #UP #ANC #SONA2013    
    
    
    "Who was he talking to? It didn't feel like he was talking to me, & yet he kept on saying, 'SONA nyo ito.'" >>> Dr Curato #UP #ANC #SONA2013    
    
    
    absence of sustainable political reforms >>> Dr Curato #UP #ANC #SONA2013    
    
    
    @libert_ong @mister_sen protest-related at #thePeoplesSONA no updates yet but #NULP lawyers rushed to assist them within hr of their arrest    
    
    
    i truly get a lot more #cramming done at coffee shops #coffee #starbucks #postgrad #exams #javadiggincat http://instagram.com/p/cGFb1GpRqq/     
    
    
    my long overdue chronicle of over 20 years of teaching & learning, beginning with select postgrad papers. come see :) http://cindycruzcabrera.wordpress.com/     
    
    
    "I am not a gentleman towards women because of who they are. I am a gentleman towards women because of who I am." http://elitedaily.com/dating/response/?fb_action_ids=10151485296181502&fb_action_types=og.likes&fb_source=other_multiline&action_object_map=%7B%2210151485296181502%22%3A154999874674785%7D&action_type_map=%7B%2210151485296181502%22%3A%22og.likes%22%7D&action_ref_map=%5B%5D …    
    
    
    and the article it was a response to ("I have lost count since then on how many girls’ lives I have ruined.") http://elitedaily.com/dating/gentlemen/do-anything-nice-for-girl/ …    
    
    
    too busy to snuggle with me http://instagram.com/p/cHC3AYpRq8/     
    
    
    a dawn date at distillery & coffee bean eastwood three years ago - sloshed and sobered :) http://instagram.com/p/cHEGrvJRsd/     
    
    
    comment to hubby this morning: "Wow, so many people want to see James LeBron." and now i'm never gonna hear the end of it.    
    
    
    "Who exactly has permission to put limits on your dreams?" >>> found on http://linkedin.com  http://www.linkedin.com/today/post/article/20130723045836-52594-skills-shmills-tell-me-what-problem-you-solve?trk=tod-home-art-medium_0 … pic.twitter.com/ZzICIEhemR    
    
    
    hubby: the equivalent of my organizing the music in your device is your unending folding of clothes. he didn't mention that it's his clothes    
    
    
    DZUP radio interview with @cindycatz & LITNUM students March 1 2013 #SoundCloud #SikhayKilos #DZUP #literacy #women https://soundcloud.com/cindy-cruz-cabrera/dzup-cindy-cruz-cabrera-and?utm_source=soundcloud&utm_campaign=share&utm_medium=twitter …    
    
    
    on Google Glass Porn and the very entertaining video :) http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/07/24/google-glass-porn_n_3644321.html?utm_hp_ref=fb&src=sp&comm_ref=false#sb=281760,b=facebook …    
    
    
    things that make everyday easier: @evernote and @Pocket ❤ ❤ ❤    
    
    
    there are really just some days when the universe won't allow you to accomplish anything - a cosmic command to just chill :) happy friday!    
    
    
    the four-toned succubus :) #AmericanDad    
    
    
    congratulations to the beautiful bride @noelle_angelica!!! ❤    
    
    
    surrounded by sleepyheads ❤    
    
    
    my sister's cat! minggoy on my computer desk ❤ pic.twitter.com/2cHAnmA4Ud    
    
    
    my sister's cat! minggoy on my computer desk ❤    
    
    
    @yumikosenir thanks! :) no, this old cat has had my sister for over 10yrs now, she adopted him fr a shelter while studying in Pittsburgh :)    
    
    
    orange mocha frappuccino! #Zoolander    
    
    
    hope announcements on suspension of classes, if any, are made soon - children are already beginning to leave their homes for school    
    
    
    @choenriquez may pasok daw :( but we've decided to keep the little boy home    
    
    
    thanks for the treatment and treat @jadedEyes!!! :) happy teeth, heart, spirit and tummy!    
    
    
    seven years ago(!) in 2006: at Mayrics with former student / VJ Karel @iamkarelmarquez :) http://instagram.com/p/cYYnrZpRsP/     
    
    
    happy birthday @gabnomods! :)    
    
    
    My Latest Upload: "Inquiry Stages and the Thesis Statement" by @cindycatz on @slideshare #claims #research #writing http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/inquiry-stages-and-the-thesis-statement-cindy-cruzcabrera …    
    
    
    TOTAL WOW! >>> @brainpicker The Seven Lady Godivas – Dr. Seuss's little-known "adult" book of nudes http://j.mp/13tXlgq     
    
    
    why do i have to have recent interactions with people before they show in my facebook feed? isn't it enough that i allow them to be there?    
    
    
    on radical children's literature http://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2011/09/21/tales-of-little-rebels/ …    
    
    
    I'm missin you | I never knew how much you meant to me | I need you | and when you go go go go | I know it never ends #SugarRay #MorningSong    
    
    
    by the ancient rite of moon and water are you bound together #JohnCarterOfMars #JohnCarterFromMars    
    
    
    #Poltergeist la lala la la la lala la la lala la la laaaaaaaaaa    
    
    
    little boy stoked 2nd graders are allowed to buy fr the cafeteria; high school freshie off on a field trip; college girl off to jog arnd UP    
    
    
    #DrWho pickup line cribbed from tumblr today: "Is that a Sonic Screwdriver in your pocket, or are you just happy to see me?"    
    
    
    a hopeful stroke of evolution to justify my addiction >>> Coca-Cola debuts bottles made of ice that "self-destructs" http://www.mnn.com/food/beverages/stories/coca-cola-debuts-bottles-made-of-ice …    
    
    
    i get the best ideas and inspiration when i have no time for them due to cramming for stuff i was supposed to do while waiting for them. ha.    
    
    
    occupying a comfy spot at #Starbucks for today's consultation :) #college #students #grades    
    
    
    listening to Vide Cor Meum and remembering #Hannibal    
    
    
    nice to see you both @seyrahlee and @YdaAlexandra :)    
    
    
    @noemiruth remembering you as i sit at a cafe across from where you used to live - you, Jack Daniels and Johnny Walker :)    
    
    
    missin you @sherylldb @mister_sen @yumikosenir @aimee_bernice @theallamson as i sit at a cafe so close to where we used to get sloshed :)    
    
    
    @imaturla @mannypagz @mokivillegas wondering if we'll get to tell drunken stories as we used to while @d4thwinchester and i take photos :)    
    
    
    all these thoughts as i sit waiting for my college students for their consultation haha :) reminiscing about margarita nights #goodtimes    
    
    
    @noemiruth let's schedule a meeting with them soon! :) #JackDaniels #JohnnyWalker oh, remember angelique & the mcdonalds dude? priceless! :)    
    
    
    oh and @nissaenerva babysitting my stuffed toys, showing me her boots :)    
    
    
    @putingtikbalang's yummy dishes, painted blue nails and all the knitted toys congregated around her :)    
    
    
    @noemiruth yay! cmon!    
    
    
    http://www.last.fm/music/Aerosmith/_/Jaded …    
    
    
    http://www.last.fm/music/Patrice%20Rushen/_/Forget%20Me%20Nots …    
    
    
    for Team Bora-OT @yumikosenir @sherylldb @mister_sen @d4thwinchester #NowPlaying http://www.last.fm/music/Incubus/_/Wish%20You%20Were%20Here …    
    
    
    @noemiruth second office?! gweilos?    
    
    
    @NinnWinn missin you, Nin! & each term, whenever i announce that consultation will be held at #Starbucks, i remember you :) #grades #papers    
    
    
    @jadedEyes where are you, auntie? what's up? :) it's raining really hard here, be safe on the road!    
    
    
    @yumikosenir @sherylldb @mister_sen @aimee_bernice @theallamson let's get sloshed! soon!    
    
    
    @noemiruth awww mine too! meet up again soon huh? you look great! :)    
    
    
    @mokivillegas i'd love another round of drunken _ _ _ _ _ _ _ lessons you used to give ❤❤❤ amazing! @sherylldb @theallamson @yumikosenir    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester @mokivillegas @imaturla @mannypagz yes, beach please, soon! :)    
    
    
    @sherylldb @yumikosenir @mister_sen @aimee_bernice @theallamson  i wish i could say i am! in my dreams for now :) #boracay    
    
    
    ang saya lang! ❤❤❤ @Roiserrano11 Malabo na daw ang UP sa UAAP finals ng basketball. Ganyan talaga sila, matatalino. Exempted lagi sa finals.    
    
    
    @jadedEyes okidoki you and daddy take care! :)    
    
    
    let's just all leave chito miranda alone :(    
    
    
    @jameleekarentan omg! from Reedley pa? OMG! 10 years ago and i daresay we both still look the same! :) #ageless    
    
    
    #boycott chito miranda's video #NoToScandalVideos    
    
    
    @imaturla @d4thwinchester @mokivillegas @mannypagz uy game game game!    
    
    
    @NinnWinn NO WAY! do i know him? DM! :)    
    
    
    @aimee_bernice @sherylldb i can't wait! :)    
    
    
    @sherylldb @yumikosenir @mister_sen @aimee_bernice @theallamson fishy pa rin ha? fishy is good for me :)    
    
    
    happy friday afternoon meeting with @noemiruth at her second office - and no, it's not gweilo's! haha! :) pic.twitter.com/h70KfkXpxR    
    
    
    "I'm not young enough to know everything." >>> Oscar Wilde    
    
    
    "Six Tips to Turn Your Passion into Profit"  http://www.entrepreneur.com/article/222971     
    
    
    @jameleekarentan well, i always say, okey lang na tumatanda basta hindi looking!!! and we both don't look it haha :) miss you!    
    
    
    @NinnWinn OMG! well, he's a lucky guy! when are you coming home to visit? we should have coffee or something alcoholic while sharing stories    
    
    
    "The church must be taken to the streets." >>> Our Jesuit Pope    
    
    
    Pope tells youth "to shake up the comfort, self-satisfaction and clericalism of a Church closed in upon itself." http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world-europe-23493038 …    
    
    
    @iamsinning university teaching na ulit? yay for you! at humanda ang antuking studyante :)    
    
    
    fun early morning read: of stoned spiders and unfinished webs -"totally, dude!" http://mentalfloss.com/article/51967/what-does-marijuana-do-spiders …    
    
    
    room 202: my new favorite classroom and work nook :) #college #teaching pic.twitter.com/ksB3rQHry1    
    
    
    @MargxWanders awww kasenti! you should come over to visit! :) i just love it, i had them book the classroom for all my classes forever! :)    
    
    
    International Day Of The Female Orgasm Brings Pleasure To Brazilian Women "Día Internacional del Orgasmo Femenino" http://www.ibtimes.com/international-day-female-orgasm-brings-pleasure-brazilian-women-742490 …    
    
    
    drizzly friday at home with thoughts of drive thru coffee ❤    
    
    
    let's trade music tastes on @lastfm http://www.last.fm/user/cindycatz     
    
    
    "Sunny day" is a state of mind, heart & soul! It's the spirit of your life's rock n roll! (photo fr rlmartstudiocom) pic.twitter.com/eIxi1C41Se    
    
    
    fun day of drunken music talk at a friend's birthday / house blessing thing :)    
    
    
    some people are consistently on the intrigue-production side. why? no life? life sucks? misdirected anger? power lust? attention-starved?    
    
    
    happy birthday @nicoares1983 ! :)    
    
    
    i can now add "writer" to my professions :) now if i could only get around to doing it for fun...    
    
    
    make space in life for even more wondrous and amazing things to come :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez heehee! more on technical-academic tho, but i'm working on hopefully producing literary stuff :) you write literary stuff diba?    
    
    
    so the question oft asked earlier in the house, "Asan na ang labuyo?" didn't quite mean what i thought it did :)    
    
    
    all the lechon, chicken rolls, garlicky cheesy shrimps, and sashimi i had the other day now tell on the weighing scale :( must stop eating!    
    
    
    @choenriquez pabasa!!! :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez me too, all snippets! kids all in big schools na, hopefully i get to finish some! :) will check it out, thanks! respect! :)    
    
    
    no classes at Assumption Antipolo and Lourdes tomorrow plus no monday classes at UP - the house will be full & crazy!    
    
    
    classes in QC suspended - all levels! (huli sa balita)    
    
    
    it's a rare stormy school-day morning when i am not generally worried about children braving the rains and floods #Labuyo #ClassSuspensions    
    
    
    the beginning of the day - just nuts    
    
    
    last meeting with my classes today! will really miss them, and should still see them for my last 2 days of consultation :)    
    
    
    it's crunch time so they're sure to show up! #college #students #consultation #cramming    
    
    
    consultation hour slots and presentation sessions booked quickly during a "bidding" in class :) so amusing #college #students #teaching    
    
    
    no classes next week due to holidays #QCDay #NinoyAquino #MWClasses    
    
    
    when your trusty boots suddenly hurt your feet, your feet have changed?! #MyPoorFeet    
    
    
    @noemiruth hmmmm tempting! cervezas or coffee? :)    
    
    
    the colleague who always has questions, comments & an uncanny interest in you & everything you do & doesn't realize you're just being polite    
    
    
    happy feast day! Assumpta Est Maria :)    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra and @seyrahlee http://www.slideshare.net/CindyCruzCabrera/eng007-portfolio-and-presentation-project-checklists …    
    
    
    tsinelas tan lines #UPDiliman    
    
    
    was at my old college - the College of Education - and saw Pedagogia ads. Pedagogia - the yearbook we put up almost 25 years ago! buhay pa!    
    
    
    @chiniehdiaz just read - hugs hugs hugs to you, amazing woman! gave up smoking too after 25yrs & was shocked at how it wasn't all that bad!    
    
    
    quotables: "There's never a dead end when it comes to love. So many roads, there might even be a tunnel underneath." #college #consultation    
    
    
    quotables: "It's like looking through a diamond when talking about love. There are just so many different angles." #college #consultation    
    
    
    #consultation today from 9am to 6pm - and so many mentions of love amidst thesis statements and research plans #college #students #teaching    
    
    
    quotables: me - "Where are your groupmates?" boy in love with groupmate - "In my heart, Ma'am." #college #students #consultation #teaching    
    
    
    quotables: "Ms., lahat ng naging girlfriend ko, may saltik." #college #students #consultation #teaching    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra @seyrahlee where are you and hans?    
    
    
    i once got asked "Why do you even like to read?" - only his cute face saved him from death by book bash to the head http://www.buzzfeed.com/harpercollins/17-problems-only-book-lovers-will-understand-9npd …    
    
    
    no classes tomorrow at Assumption Antipolo!    
    
    
    was marathoning, and huli sa balita - my kids have no classes! wheee! i'm the only one who needs to leave the house tomorrow - boooo!    
    
    
    red rainfall alert - everyone at home is sleeping / relaxed. while here i am agitated about not getting to work argh! :(    
    
    
    oh, the rainfall alert has just been lowered to orange c/o @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    keep warm, be safe and stay off the road! :)    
    
    
    my son: "Coffee?" (since he couldn't smell it)
me: "Ummm, frozen coke."
my son: "Can I have some?"
#ClassSuspension #RainyDay #ColdMorning    
    
    
    i converted my wordfile to pdf for free :) http://www.pdftoword.com/  via @nitropdf    
    
    
    happy to work from home on a rainy day :)    
    
    
    for you #TheGameOfLove #NowScrobbling    
    
    
    when it's over, is it really over? http://www.last.fm/music/Sugar%20Ray/_/When%20It's%20Over … #NowScrobbling    
    
    
    classes still suspended at Assumption Antipolo and Lourdes School of Manda. UP Diliman na lang and we'll all be home tomorrow! :)    
    
    
    @iampameetupaz yay yay yay thanks pamee! :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez yay thanks! naku, be safe if you have to go to work tom :( haaay sarap lang talaga maging studyante!    
    
    
    please tell me why you don't come around no more #TheGameOfLove http://www.last.fm/music/Santana/_/The%20Game%20Of%20Love%20(Featuring%20%20Michelle%20Branch) …    
    
    
    It can't rain all the time. >>> Eric Draven    
    
    
    we'll miss you @curiouscouch! see you in December! :)    
    
    
    our university girl is stressed out that she can't help out with packing/distribution of goods unless she swims to get there #StandUP #UPD    
    
    
    Tomorrow's classes at Assumption Antipolo & Lourdes School of Mandaluyong suspended! No announcement yet from QC & UP #waterproof #immortal    
    
    
    classes resume in UP and Ateneo tomorrow #QC #waterproof #immortal    
    
    
    Noynoy - why are you MIA during calamities but personally physically present within minutes of Serendra action?!    
    
    
    QC: I'd take "no more sembreak" any day over risking having children brave the rains, winds and floods going to school #waterproof #immortal    
    
    
    @mister_sen i don't think they think at all :S    
    
    
    @mister_sen yup, then when tragedy arises, they're suddenly all sad, grim, warm, caring and makatao, ang pakshet lang talaga.    
    
    
    early day tomorrow for work, and also have to find out at 4AM if QC or UP is calling off classes :) nighty night for now!    
    
    
    #UPISKaKung way of life ang cramming, workaround, at risk of sanction for violation of rules #WagPatalo #WagPasindak #WagPahuli    
    
    
    #UPISKaKung memorize mo ang #UPNamingMahal :)    
    
    
    @carlabaful tayo ang tama! i declare it! :)    
    
    
    awake at 4AM to await announcements? UP congrats, #WalangPasok thanks Chancey! next time, night before sana! ADMU college sorry, #MayPasok    
    
    
    good morning @MMDA! how's ortigas avenue extension and shaw blvd?    
    
    
    hubby: (on our college daughter) "No classes, but let her go out there and help." (then, on me, the adult) "Can't you just work from home?"    
    
    
    i haven't cluelessly stepped into a freakin muddy puddle since grade school. grrrrr.    
    
    
    now supremely enjoying my warm and comforting genetically modified cereal milk drink    
    
    
    @MMDA @PasigInfo alright, thank you!    
    
    
    happy birthday @jadedEyes! :)    
    
    
    for you of the August temper >>> Daryl Hall & John Oates – August Day http://www.last.fm/music/+noredirect/Daryl+Hall+&+John+Oates/_/August+Day … via @lastfm    
    
    
    @mister_sen no school today for you right?! :)    
    
    
    @curiouscouch is finally home! give our love to Albany NY :)    
    
    
    those near the Katips area, you can bring goods to #StandUP at Vinzons Hall, my college girl is there @csugee    
    
    
    those near antipolo, please bring to Assumption Antipolo Multipurpose Hall :)    
    
    
    watching Queen's Wembley concert in the living room with drunken musicians @datustribe    
    
    
    one red horse and i'm sleepy - really out of practice! :)    
    
    
    August 26 >>> 2 days to Luneta, see you all there! #PorkBarrel #OinkOink    
    
    
    Today's Weepy Goodbye Resolve: "If you ever loved me, say it like you're going to come back." #RiverSong #Goodbye #SeeYouAround #SeeYouLater    
    
    
    see you all tomorrow! sign here >>> Abolition of the Pork Barrel System/the Presidential Pork Barrel Fund http://www.change.org/petitions/president-benigno-simeon-cojuangco-aquino-iii-abolition-of-the-pork-barrel-system-and-the-presidential-pork-barrel-fund?share_id=KSfRuCRqOL&utm_campaign=twitter_link_action_box&utm_medium=twitter&utm_source=share_petition … via @change    
    
    
    UP Contingent assembly at Quezon Hall tomorrow 7AM #MillionPeopleMarch #AbolishPork    
    
    
    i trust in my wings :)    
    
    
    happy birthday @iamsinning!!! :)    
    
    
    kept on hearing "J-Dog" in the running commentary of the #Starcraft finals, so distracted: Jemaine? Flight of the Conchords? JaeDong pala :)    
    
    
    in convoy on the way to Liwasang Bonifacio #MillionPeopleMarch @csugee    
    
    
    UP Contingent breaks into groups, leaves for Liwasang Bonifacio #MillionPeopleMarch    
    
    
    got a mild scolding from my dad before leaving for the #MillionPeopleMarch - his spidersense acted up. some things never change #CollegeDays    
    
    
    according to @inquirerdotnet Assumption Antipolo sighted :) yay AA!!! #MillionPeopleMarch    
    
    
    UP Ikot and Pantranco jeeps sighted in Liwasang Bonifacio and Luneta #MillionPeopleMarch #UP    
    
    
    Now marching to Liwasang Bonifacio #MillionPeopleMarch    
    
    
    got pretty knocked out from the day-long march & commute yest - not as waterproof and energizer bunny as i used to be #MillionPeopleMarch    
    
    
    nice one to start the day with! >>> "It always rains hardest on the people who deserve the sun." (cribbed from @iamkarelmarquez)    
    
    
    enjoying a few more minutes of quiet before the chaos of children-off-to-school-in-the-morning starts :) good morning!    
    
    
    ugh me and my unruly rally hair photos    
    
    
    we're wondering this morning what the MileyCyrus buzz was all about & we watched the vid. regrets. it's 1 of those things you'd like to undo    
    
    
    Miley Cyrus vid and PDAF discussions, what a happy combination! grrrr!    
    
    
    wow, let the circus begin! :) #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    so how many ways will the 10 million be split? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    is the president entitled to the 10 million reward? or will it go back into his pork? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    pinatapos muna ang #MillionPeopleMarch right? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    the timestamp is a nice touch, don't you think? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    does Napoles get the 10 million? she did lead to her own capture - and it's honest money for a change bwahaha #twisted #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    no photos? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    i wonder, did the Palace consultant linked to Napoles who got fired get the 10million? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee wow, then it's a two-way preemptive split. 500,000 each - not bad, right? :)    
    
    
    @iampameetupaz haha sabi nga, scripted daw! that or what, nagdoorbell lang sya bigla sa palace right? :)    
    
    
    what happened at 9:37PM, yung pagring ng doorbell? or pagbukas ng pinto? or pagtanggap sa kanya ni Noynoy in his pajamas? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    so many die in police custody while being transported coz the suspect tries to take the gun. will this happen to Napoles? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    i want to see her face. is it still the same? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    lots of deals will be made tonight by guilty politicians to buy their innocence, right? lots more money to be made here #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    @iampameetupaz yeah magkasama silang nanood ng TV sa #MillionPeopleMarch, relax relax lang at may time pa naman #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    was just about to pop a load of laundry (kids' uniforms) tnx to breaking news i'm stuck! yeah baby you had me at "9:37PM" #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee ay kulang ng 3 zeroes my bad! 5M :)    
    
    
    roxas: upon seeing her, the president checked on her medical situation to make sure she's alright. >>> wow! meanwhile rallyists get harmed    
    
    
    roxas:wala syang hiningi kundi ang kanyang seguridad. >>> what magthank you ba ko sa kanya? and please, hiningi nya yung cut nya sa 10M haha    
    
    
    @mister_sen ganun na nga! got two words too: #OinkOink    
    
    
    malakas ang kalakaran itong mga oras na ito: guilty politicians are ready to spend, the bird is prepared to sing #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    i thought my tweeted question earlier funny, if she still looks the same - roxas asked the same question at crame haha #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    not handcuffed, not imcarcerated >>> so, balik sa room ng star? sa backstage? tapos na ang shooting? move to next script? #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee i feel you - scripted! staged! :)    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee Noynoy-Napoles relationship: "Ako bahala sayo, ikaw bahala sa kin" >>> #FriendsWithBenefits much! #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    so pano, kitakits na lang bukas sa St. Luke's? #NapolesSurrenders #HighBlood    
    
    
    lost two hours, doing laundry at 1AM #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    gusto kong matulog pero di ko magawa #NapolesSurrenders    
    
    
    alright, my Napoles-induced adrenaline rush has already subsided - sleepy now :)    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra and @seyrahlee i am reserving 5-6pm for you    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra @seyrahlee please inform hans okay    
    
    
    @YdaAlexandra @seyrahlee dark mocha frap venti :)    
    
    
    waiting for the universe to send me some falling stars - and a wayward comet :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez haha it doesn't matter where i wait for the stars / comet, might as well do it while marathoning on the couch :)    
    
    
    "A bard's truth is different than yours or mine." #Ygritte #ASongOfIceAndFire    
    
    
    "A woman's life is nine parts mess to one part magic." #Cersei #ASongOfIceAndFire    
    
    
    "Love is poison. A sweet poison, yes, but it will kill you all the same." #Cersei #ASongOfIceAndFire    
    
    
        
    
    
    inspiration: Hedy Lamarr, 1930s sultry actress & talented mathematician who invented frequency-hopping, the basis for bluetooth & WIFI tech❤    
    
    
    "Scores indicate that you are a moderate progressive; this is the political profile one might associate with a university professor." Hmmm.    
    
    
    "Your attitudes towards economics appear socialist." #SocialAttitudeTest    
    
    
    "Combined with your social attitudes this creates the picture of someone who would generally be described as left-wing." #SocialAttitudeTest    
    
    
    #SocialAttitudeTest Take it here: http://slackhalla.org/~demise/test/socialattitude.php … :)    
    
    
    "To round out the picture you appear to be, political preference aside, a centrist with several strong opinions." Haaay. #SocialAttitudeTest    
    
    
    good for insomniacs? :) http://b.dietandbeauty.co/foods-that-help-you-fall-asleep-/oatmeal-with-almonds/ …    
    
    
    missed this: "It appears that you're skeptical towards religion, have a pragmatic attitude towards humanity in general." #SocialAttitudeTest    
    
    
    it's september! we should begin hearing Christmas songs on TV and at the malls :)    
    
    
    @patriciaroxlee OMG congratulations! :) beautiful baby! :)    
    
    
    looks like i've outgrown my progressives, oh no.    
    
    
    happy, excited, and restless! :)    
    
    
    also a hankering, hmph.    
    
    
    happy birthday Abelardo Hall! #UPD #piano #music #UPCollegeOfMusic #recitals http://lifestyle.inquirer.net/123239/up-abelardo-hall-marks-50th-anniversary … @inquirerdotnet    
    
    
    "You have no responsibility for what happened to you as a child. You have complete responsibility over what you do about it now." - Hitler?!    
    
    
    @yumikosenir i had recitals there too! :) miss you yooomeee! :)    
    
    
    WOW! >>> "No snowflake in an avalanche ever feels responsible." http://thoughtcatalog.com/2013/25-unintentionally-profound-statements-that-will-change-your-life-today/#7KFLRHykeG8yLXKi.01 …    
    
    
    This is for me >>> The best time to plant a tree is twenty years ago. The second best time is today. http://thoughtcatalog.com/2013/25-unintentionally-profound-statements-that-will-change-your-life-today/#7KFLRHykeG8yLXKi.01 …    
    
    
    ... and this is for you :) >>> Concerning relationships: “It lasts as long as it lasts.” http://thoughtcatalog.com/2013/25-unintentionally-profound-statements-that-will-change-your-life-today/#7KFLRHykeG8yLXKi.01 …    
    
    
    grades are done! those who rose to the challenge: good luck in the journey! those who slacked off: see you again soon! #college #students    
    
    
    @yumikosenir what's your sked? i'll let you know when i'm going to UP :)    
    
    
    sobrang sarap talaga forever ng freshly-baked hopia! soft and steamy and sweetish :)    
    
    
    a long day of analyzing and categorizing data (whew!) should end with an old mushy pinoy romantic movie :)    
    
    
    "scholastic, smart and sarcastic" - "Defined Lines", parody of "Blurred Lines" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tC1XtnLRLPM#t=200 …    
    
    
    thanks for this, @mister_sen! :) http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tC1XtnLRLPM#t=200 …    
    
    
    @anyaanyaanya i'm glad you agree :) about to watch "One More Chance" for the first time - shriek shriek shriek! SHRIEEEEEEEEKl!! :)    
    
    
    one Jedi bathrobe please http://fashion.likes.com/15-of-our-favorite-star-wars-fashions?page=7 …    
    
    
    a whole day of data again - learning a whole lot and getting a kick out of it, but really need to replace my progressives!    
    
    
    the more seamless and entertaining the read, the more coffee and ciggies had gone into it i surmise :) #SustainabilityReporting    
    
    
    waited for Mr. Taho in front of the building for nearly half an hour - the nangka in the arnibal made the wait worthwhile! #taho    
    
    
    @jadedEyes i just read this! see you on saturday! :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez missed you & your boys last night at lola's! left early too, jade, inigo & cabring not feeling well. but had lots of sushi! :)    
    
    
    heard on commute radio and benta! >>> "Pag binato ka ng bato, batuhin mo ng bulaklak para masaya. Isama mo ang paso para may impact."    
    
    
    with everyone asleep,my little boy & i snuck out for an rainy early morning breakfast date at McDo a few streets away pic.twitter.com/xHBLLByakg    
    
    
    @datustribe at conspiracy tomorrow and luneta on friday for #AbolishPork :)    
    
    
    "Instead of spreading yourself thin, set aside large chunks of time to focus on one task at a time." >>> must do! :) https://medium.com/content-creators-curators/348a9f60e176 …    
    
    
    had two photos taken today: shet lang talaga pot belly ko! :)    
    
    
    @jadedEyes haaaay two weeks ago lang okay na ko. ang sarap kasi kumain! :)    
    
    
    OMG Keanu! https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?v=10152198523458448&set=vb.212721722089562&type=2&theater …    
    
    
    @choenriquez hahahahahahahaha i wish! :)    
    
    
    UP kong mahal at Ateneo kong lambing! AGAIN!!! good luck UP and ADMU! #UAAPCDC #915on915    
    
    
    @jadedEyes pls send the chocolate chip cookies over to the house! :) we are home watching the #UAAPCDC2013 #UPPepSquad is up next! #915on915    
    
    
        
    
    
    party theme daw kasi UP, kaya shempre shot shot muna bago salang! hahaha GO #UPPepSquad! #915on915 #UAAPCDC2013    
    
    
    my bets UP, DLSU, NU :) #915on915 #UPPepSquad #UPFight #UAAPCDC2013    
    
    
    OMG second place UP!!! pang-first place pa din! :)    
    
    
    whatevs :) #UAAPCDC2013    
    
    
    @d4thwinchester happy birthday to my bestest tanning bud! :) miss you blue!    
    
    
    spending the day at Assumption Antipolo - nakaka-senti! :)    
    
    
    the tip i read the other day, "For one day a week, eat anything you want" has me wondering, that's today, right? so now it's everyday. argh.    
    
    
    it doesn't help that i'm at the Assumption Antipolo caf, & everything is still made by the old manangs & is as delicious as when i was a kid    
    
    
    daughter back to school today after 2 weeks of vertigo & migraine - so happy about her feat & her sweet friends who help her move around! :)    
    
    
    @carlabaful Jade, she has daily migraines & vertigo managed with meds.was with her today at school kasi mejo hirap pa but she's much better!    
    
    
    @carlabaful kwentuhan kita minsan :)    
    
    
    lots to write and edit - so lost!    
    
    
    starstruck with the great Pen Medina - before last night's screening of "The Guerilla is a Poet" http://instagram.com/p/ekWbLQpRqM/     
    
    
    wish cabring and i could stay home with the kids today on a rainy monday morning!    
    
    
    excited about the teaching, the writing, and - hopefully soon - the studying as well! :)    
    
    
    @mister_sen you look so much like the young Joma Sison in "The Guerilla is a Poet" - so distracting! :)    
    
    
    @mister_sen here :) http://ph.news.yahoo.com/blogs/the-inbox/guerilla-poet-144320733.html …    
    
    
    @mister_sen "The Guerilla is a Poet" lead actor Karl Medina, the eldest son of Pen Medina. (the dad is gorgeous!) :)    
    
    
    finally done! i love the scheduled writing days, but have not been able to do my own writing for my stuff. should schedule days for that too    
    
    
    can't stop thinking of Dexter @SHO_Dexter    
    
    
    marathoning Sex and the City again! :) now to nap a bit    
    
    
    the Italian government assembly and their response to being told "Gay people are inappropriate" :) http://www.upworthy.com/a-bunch-of-government-officials-were-told-that-gay-people-were-inappropriate-so-what-they-did-is?c=ufb1 …    
    
    
    18 year-old girl and incoming Harvard freshman invents supercapacitor that can charge phones in 30 seconds! http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bCCuNYzRou8 …    
    
    
    beware smooth-talking businessmen bearing fairly-traded hand-crafted beverages :)    
    
    
    was treated to something called "Guilt-Free Indulgence" at Starbucks - it sure tasted sinful :)    
    
    
    i fell off my chair! slid right out from under me. office people were too polite to laugh, and i was all bwahahahahaha :)    
    
    
    long day writing!    
    
    
    @putingtikbalang thanks jonette! have you met with vin na? :)    
    
    
    almost done with my first sustainability report, also making progress with my 1st textbook alignment consultancy work - happy happy happy :)    
    
    
    time to get sloshed :)    
    
    
    now if i could only attend to my blogs! haha :)    
    
    
    still awake writing - and i wish it had been for my blogs :(    
    
    
    short interview with Karl Medina / The Guerilla is a Poet http://n5e.interaksyon.com/Videos.aspx?g=6EB7B1510658493&c=4 …    
    
    
    the best news - i'm writing more! #SustainabilityReports    
    
    
    it's difficult when people you feel aren't worth it are important enough for your loved ones for you to have to make it work. tapos BALAHURA    
    
    
    so that's my word for the day (and my sentiments ever since i've had to put up with scummy behavior): BALAHURA :)    
    
    
    brought my son to school. what a grand fuss made by security over my sleeveless shirt! moms in strappies not allowed at Lourdes Manda! :)    
    
    
    would love to watch this movie :) http://bitchmagazine.org/post/review-don-jon-directed-joseph-gordon-levitt-feminist-porn-addiction …    
    
    
    violated rights http://www.realfarmacy.com/video-woman-stripped-completely-naked-by-3-male-police-officers/#yzWbr5PtOqiZcO5G.01 …    
    
    
    spent 2 hours in traffic midmorning to lunch - for a 30-40min commute! OMG tonight is going to be tough!    
    
    
    just found out of my inclusion in the 2011 book Tales From The 7000 Isles:Filipino Folk Stories as part of the early storytelling community!    
    
    
    in the chapter "Today's Filipino Storytelling Community" :) NOTE: i helped to organize in 1999 but i began volunteer storytelling in 1994!    
    
    
    what a pleasant discovery! thanks to authors diane delas casas & @thecoffeegoddes - glad we met at one of my mid90s storytelling workshops    
    
    
    happy saturday :)    
    
    
    a fun feel-good list for a happy and inspired saturday :) http://www.mindbodygreen.com/0-10247/30-things-to-do-before-you-die.html …    
    
    
    i've seen pretty big rats before, but OMG at the sight of ratzilla! http://ph.news.yahoo.com/giant-rat-china-5kg-ratzilla-caught-one-metre-long-shaoyang-hunan-province-095149130.html …    
    
    
    tip from my Cosmo US addiction decade (1994-2003): jangle your keys when walking past places with rats - they'll move away coz they hate it!    
    
    
    OMG i've almost forgotten about my Cosmopolitan US addiction decade! should dig up those mags :)    
    
    
    student: Maam bakit mo ko binagsak?
me: over ka sa allowed absences, wala kang coursework, di ka dumating ng finals.
student: ganun? #kaloka    
    
    
    cramming for a sustainability report deadline - why i always find myself in fixes like this is a mystery to me! #cramming #CrammersNeverDie    
    
    
    @jadedEyes hahaha 2 hours late! good job Globe!    
    
    
    done writing! one hour power nap, then a mad dash to get ready and off to the college classroom argh :)    
    
    
    it's not fair that i didn't get @RealHughJackman for a PE teacher! i would have had ZERO absences! ❤ http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yj46BWpxFcA …    
    
    
    finally caught up on some sleep, little boy off to school, will just tame the chaos on the couch that is the laundry, then be off myself :)    
    
    
    the bed beckons, whispering, "come back!"    
    
    
    okay, i'm dressing up my kids for halloween - even the 19 year-old :) http://www.buzzfeed.com/saraboboltz/32-parents-who-nailed-it-on-halloween-af7c …    
    
    
    the bed won.    
    
    
    working on a new sustainability report, with another one (hopefully three!) lined up - happy! :)    
    
    
    ang sarap talaga ng burger machine longga double burger! lalo pa't libre - thank you @SwiminiTiti! :)    
    
    
    belated happy new birthday (October 6th) to Refreshing Lake of the Heart :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    had a conference with my daughter Jade's class adviser & the academic coordinator about her return to school. i love assumption antipolo! :)    
    
    
    at the end of every long hopeless walk to get a ride home is a coffee shop :) pic.twitter.com/V4C7igYUD7    
    
    
    @jadedEyes yup, but no use :(    
    
    
    did nothing today but laze about with kids and hubby oooh la la what a joy! :)    
    
    
    what a day! #unforgettable #UPCMC    
    
    
        
    
    
    Editing a textbook - OMG nakakaloka! there really should be pedagpgical, language proficiency, & style screening for authors & manuscripts    
    
    
    130 major edits/heavy revisions through 22pp: alarming for something intended to be an educational manuscript for basic education #kapikon    
    
    
    Can't wait to get home to family fun and folly #WorkingMomBlues    
    
    
    @csugee our travel destinations! :) http://www.boredpanda.com/amazing-places/     
    
    
    ♪♫ how my poor heart aches with every step you take ♪♫    
    
    
    last sun: kelangan mamalengke, pls drive for me.
cabring: @#$#$%#%^%
today: mamamalengke lang ako, ako na bahala
cabring: wait for me #anuba    
    
    
    hello PhD in Media Studies! hello to my new college, UP College of Mass Communication! >>> tulala at work! :)    
    
    
    went to grad school for advising wheee! first visit as a PhD Student :) #UPCMC    
    
    
    me to sari-sari store woman: may bawas na ba itong pechay dahil lanta na?

woman: wala ano! ganyan kasi talaga ang gulay, nalalanta.

OMG.    
    
    
    i just want to sleep!    
    
    
        
    
    
    excited about courses to take next sem!    
    
    
    I love exam periods! Students are quiet and focused, and I get uninterrupted reading time. Well, almost. :)    
    
    
    Grading papers. Haaay.    
    
    
    Ang sarap ng "Freshly Fry Crizpy Chicken" sa kanto, P13 isa. Yum!    
    
    
    I just got a LinkedIn invite from Sir Jose Abueva. I think I'm going to faint.    
    
    
    Yay yay for my free longganisa and hot choco meal :)    
    
    
    Discussions on facts, opinions, preferences and conventions are always fun :) Fact? Haha    
    
    
    Halloween requests for freecuts - granted! Well, short class meetings haha #HappyHalloween    
    
    
    Just lazing about in bed, savoring the absence of any urgency & how the kids check in on me but don't really need me. Wonderful, lazy day!    
    
    
    @jadedEyes hi auntie! just at home naman :) inigo has two wobbly teeth! can we drop by your house tom?    
    
    
    Dawn run: wake, palengke, mercury drug, xray. LSS all the way for #Bowling #EthnicFaces :)    
    
    
    At 5AM as soon as we arrived - Friend: Glad you could make it to dad's wake. Me: Of course. Friend: Shot? Me: Sure, whatcha got? #Breakfast    
    
    
    my daughter Chloe's blockmate fr UP Eng'g has been missing,no current info available yet.let's help get the word out https://twitter.com/USCupdiliman/status/393737318898475008 …    
    
    
    It's the 5th of November! Remember, remember....    
    
    
    Ganyan din ang gusto kong dalawang modes ko: as they say, "lukring OR brilliant" - pwede rin both at the same time! #SenatorMiriam    
    
    
    As always, killer wit #SenatorMiriam    
    
    
    Gusto ko ring maging "tama lang sa buhay"! #pakshet    
    
    
    Walang xray film sa UP Infirmary para sa mga due magpphysical exam, kailangan gumastos pa xray bago enrolment. Tapos eto si #Napoles #banas    
    
    
    Favorite moment caption: "Mukhang wala masyadong pinagsisisihan." #SenatorGracePoe #Napoles    
    
    
    Favorite heckle: "Ignorance can be treated but stupid is forever." #SenatorMiriam #Napoles    
    
    
    #WalangPasok Assumption Antipolo and the whole of Rizal! wheeee! hope UP and LSM suspend classes as well! :)    
    
    
    Just now: Mandaluyong classes suspended! Woot LSM :)    
    
    
    Ano na, UP? #Waterproof #SuspendClassesNow    
    
    
    While there are class today in UP, my Urban Anthropology Professor decided to meet next week. YAY! :)    
    
    
    Classes in UP Diliman from 11:30 onwards suspended JUST NOW!!!    
    
    
    Scary how it was already dark at 5!    
    
    
    OMG UP Town Center, you're already falling apart? #PPP #Ayala    
    
    
    I just can't get enough of Zagu't Gulaman #yum    
    
    
    my dad brought home two white cats, both a cross between persian and siamese. my kids are going crazy! :)    
    
    
    Call for Donations - drop off at Vinzons Hall, UP Diliman pic.twitter.com/Wc1A9JTmrt    
    
    
    Foraging for survival in the face of devastation is quite different fr scandalous  plunder beyond the dreams of avarice (Napoles, Erap etc).    
    
    
    Let's have the compassion to make the distinction and the sense of justice to go after these hoodlums. But for now, let's help first!    
    
    
    “It is most unlikely. But - here comes the big 'but' - not impossible." <<< and more Roald Dahl quotes :) http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/09/13/roald-dahl-quotes_n_3909289.html …    
    
    
    donate Family Packs and drop off at UPD, UPM, UPLB, UPB, & UPV. Please share! #UPTulongKabataan #YolandaPH #ReliefPH pic.twitter.com/6Hmctts6g8    
    
    
    Seeing my son off to his field trip - am part of the frenzy of parents warching parked buses at LSM pre-departure :)    
    
    
    Endless waving and flying kisses #LSM #FieldTrip #Grade2    
    
    
    "Machete don't tweet." #MacheteKills #NowWatching #FamilyMovieTime    
    
    
    While taking notes in a PhD class, scribbling madly to keep up with the professor, I realized I put hashtags beside important terms #WTF    
    
    
    @mister_sen the hardest part was i couldn't laugh out loud! :)    
    
    
    @iampameetupaz awwww i miss you too! :)    
    
    
    SC declares PDAF unconstitutional! Woohoo! #AbolishPork    
    
    
    @aimee_bernice saw your tweet while teaching class - am happy to add 'hilarious' to my descriptions 'foolish' & 'crazy'! Blasted twitter! :)    
    
    
    SLEEPY sleepy sleepy    
    
    
    I want to love you madly #Cake    
    
    
    hershel    
    
    
    Last meeting  of one of my 3hr PhD  classes - lots of food, wine and NO WATER!!! #wasak    
    
    
    @wagpoplease game DJ!!! :)    
    
    
    RIP Nelson Mandela    
    
    
    what made my morning wonderful: Benedict Cumberbatch's "Promise" :) http://gawker.com/benedict-cumberbatch-recites-r-kelly-lyrics-like-a-sex-1477117915 …    
    
    
    @csugee where am i meeting you later after class? AS lobby/steps?    
    
    
    @csugee DM    
    
    
    @jadedEyes they look yummy naman! :)    
    
    
    "You’ve questioned the whole notion of morality and think it’s more important to be kind than to be right." http://www.buzzfeed.com/juliapugachevsky/everyday-struggles-of-being-a-right-brained-person?bffb …    
    
    
    i am such a sucker for these stories! :) http://www.viralnova.com/found-freezing/     
    
    
    “Curiosity is gluttony. To see is to devour.”   ― Victor Hugo, Les Misérables    
    
    
    and now, food stacks. OMG. http://www.buzzfeed.com/emofly/most-epic-food-stacks-of-2013?utm_campaign=socialflow&utm_source=twitter&utm_medium=buzzfeed …    
    
    
    Pampasaya :) "10 Words for HAPPINESS", a slideshow from http://dictionary.com  http://dictionary.reference.com/?sshow=happiness-words&__utma=1.1055185084.1377141814.1386306663.1386739792.96&__utmb=1.1.10.1386739792&__utmc=1&__utmx=-&__utmz=1.1386126868.91.7.utmcsr=ask|utmccn=(organic)|utmcmd=organic|utmctr=take%20one%20up&__utmv=-&__utmk=136797104 …    
    
    
    "heaven's on fire" on the road on the radio :)    
    
    
    Pope Francis: my first Catholic inspiration in years and years and years http://www.buzzfeed.com/ellievhall/the-19-best-pope-francis-moments-of-2013 …    
    
    
    goodbye Papadom RIP :(    
    
    
    @csugee and @dlo_oIb 8 things to never say :) http://www.marcandangel.com/2013/12/15/8-things-happy-successful-people-never-say/ …    
    
    
    missing the UP Lantern Parade haaaaay    
    
    
    home now after spending so much time on the road with road-raging allergy-ridden hubby    
    
    
    rush rush rush    
    
    
    a day of temporary goodbyes with family & work, the last of 2013 deadlines, & the midnight departure to Baguio with my Anthropology class!    
    
    
    the winning NatGeo photo: "A polar bear peers up from beneath the melting sea ice...."  http://proof.nationalgeographic.com/2013/12/19/the-2013-national-geographic-photography-contest-winners/?utm_source=Facebook&utm_medium=Social&utm_content=link_fb20131219pr-ngpcwinn&utm_campaign=Content …    
    
    
    Attended simbang gabi mass at St Louis Univesity in Baguio, priest was giving a Holy Rant against the corrupt    
    
    
        
    
    
    Prof Guazon surprised our class with an AM radio station interview in Baguio. Tune in! Hahaha :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez required eh, no choice argh. actually just wanted to stay home, but this urban anthropology tour is indeed interesting!    
    
    
    @choenriquez oh but the mass wasnt rrquired,, ganda nga nung mass. And besides my room is spooky    
    
    
    @choenriquez but I envy you - you're home!    
    
    
    Nocturnal urban anthropology of Baguio - read: bar hopping with professor's annotations / anthropological insights :)    
    
    
    Watching an amazing Baguio band sa tugtugan dito - AGI Igorot Band -  galing!!!    
    
    
    Benguet bound    
    
    
    "hot men of yore" heehee http://www.cosmopolitan.com/sex-love/hot-guys/hot-men-of-yore#slide-1 …    
    
    
    sick hubby meant cancelled Antipolo family lunch reunion (his side) & Muzon family dinner reunion (mine) & a lot of cooking suddenly for me    
    
    
    a day of cooking, herding kids & their cats, finding entertainment to replace all the running around the hills the kids were supposed to do    
    
    
    that makes me one tired mommy so early into Christmas eve!    
    
    
    body still hurting from walking around in Baguio and Benguet. the only time we took a ride was from Baguio to Benguet, that's it!    
    
    
    so Baguio is in Benguet. i'm such a schmuck.    
    
    
    merry christmas!!! :)    
    
    
    @choenriquez hi cho! sorry just read, didn't stop cooking! :( sad to miss it, but we'll be there on new year's eve!    
    
    
    2013 chronic sleep deprivation now catching up: anytime I sit, rest my back, or lie on something soft, I doze off, no matter where I am OMG!    
    
    
    Chronic sleep debt    
    
    
    yesterday: laundry day with a quick trip for new eyeglasses. today: still the laundry (ugh) & hopefully a quick stop at Starbucks    
    
    
    