Longmont is looking good these days! Our ranch would be great for seniors. It's a short drive to the CU campus, too. http://fb.me/HteX9w9Q     
    
    
    The best job prospects for the coming quarter in metro Denver, according to Manpower, are durable goods... http://fb.me/25mSpiWXe     
    
    
    Take another look at Longmont! 

Fall is almost here. Make that move you have been thinking about. http://fb.me/PfqvRAVg     
    
    
    7 tips for working with contractors:

1. Get a recommendation and check their references. 
2. Verify the... http://fb.me/1TgjPCUJm     
    
    
    Boulder Creek Builders is calling the community the Overlook at Steel Ranch.... http://fb.me/265CPhVxS     
    
    
    3 bd townhouse in #Longmont | $144,900 || #colorado #boulder #realestate #invest #retire #property #realtor http://twitter.com/retireNlongmont/status/244313806338154496/photo/1pic.twitter.com/6cG7s4T6     
    
    
    Analysts climbed out on a limb a few years ago to predict a sudden spike in new home construction. While home... http://fb.me/11Q6dEu5s     
    
    
    Rising real estate prices mean the water is lowering. Well, the number of mortgages underwater is, well, drying... http://fb.me/1YNmtFoyE     
    
    
    "We're here because the talent base in this area is unique to the world" 
- Micron Technology Vice President Glen... http://fb.me/1Mqj7NhYk     
    
    
    Boulder County again leads the metro area in high-end home sales, notching 18. Inventory sunk to 10 months of... http://fb.me/1QIzkgR5S     
    
    
    3 Colorado universities in U.S. News top 100 http://www.bizjournals.com/denver/news/2012/09/13/3-colorado-universities-in-us-news.html?ana=twt … via @denbizjournal    
    
    
    New determination to fire up the economy is reflected in this move and a promise to keep rates low. http://fb.me/FpDEupuY     
    
    
    Consumer Reports gets a thumbs up for this article on sidestepping pitfalls of renovation. The best advice comes... http://fb.me/11CcPZNz4     
    
    
    Check with the city to make sure a contractor is licensed. And, ask for proof of insurance.... http://fb.me/Fg2jdSxw     
    
    
    Good advice for the buyer in this CNNMoney article. In Colorado, buyers are more likely to encounter a seller... http://fb.me/1XwD4J1oJ     
    
    
    What was your most pleasant experience in handling a sale for a client? http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/What_was_your_most_pleasant_experience_in_handling-433539 …    
    
    
    If you forgo hiring a staging professional, the most important thing you can do is clean and de-clutter. The... http://fb.me/2iis86ZpY     
    
    
    Talk about tough ... small business owners have a tougher row to hoe to get a mortgage.... http://fb.me/Jvg3tDih     
    
    
    Back to the feature: Back splashes. The number of materials that can be used has grown.... http://fb.me/1Eacvt3na     
    
    
    Easily done ...... http://fb.me/1FkTQBbdw     
    
    
    On the creativity metric, Boulder leads other larger metros - hands down. One of was once asked by a local... http://fb.me/1cAb2Xn3Q     
    
    
    The cottonwoods might not need more moisture, but tree water is a good thing to do on warm days through winter. http://fb.me/1pjdIJQ8b     
    
    
    Keep an eye on your score. http://finance.yahoo.com/news/7-weird-ways-hurt-credit-143552552.html … http://fb.me/FM0YOrbm     
    
    
    It's time to get this economy moving. Even though profits in the financial industry have climbed back strongly to... http://fb.me/FsBo7S6V     
    
    
    The Associated Press is carrying a story today on a report from the National Association of Realtors. That report... http://fb.me/x6syvZER     
    
    
    US home sales jump to highest since May 2010 || http://news.yahoo.com/us-home-sales-jump-highest-since-may-2010-140225603--finance.html … #realestate #colorado #property #in #invest #boulder #longmont    
    
    
    What a terrific concept - mass producing school gardens. Raymond's second grade class in San Bernardino had a... http://fb.me/1Ddv1jfl9     
    
    
    http://www.businessweek.com/articles/2012-07-10/new-credit-score-system-finds-many-borrowers-less-risky … http://fb.me/y9hDnaNs     
    
    
    http://homes.yahoo.com/news/seven-ways--to-cut-mortgage-costs.html …    
    
    
    The inventory of homes for sale was down from 3.02 million from the previous year in August coming in at 2.47... http://fb.me/tMUiAv0f     
    
    
    #Boulder, Broomfield have fewer jobless than rest of state || http://www.bcbr.com/article/20120921/NEWS/120929988 … #Longmont #Colorado #in    
    
    
    Increased overall wealth could give many people and businesses the confidence to step up spending and boost U.S.... http://fb.me/1WPKXn3YI     
    
    
    http://www.bankrate.com/finance/mortgages/5-tips-for-first-time-home-buyers-1.aspx … http://fb.me/1ite0Wom9     
    
    
    The decrease in the unemployment rate was caused by a larger decline in the number of people actively... http://fb.me/ywMAXvs7     
    
    
    If you don't have a wine cellar cut out of a hill like the one I visited this summer, here are some ideas. - Suz... http://fb.me/1zBjTi6mA     
    
    
    De-Cluttering: Renting a storage space and storing a lot of items can be a great investment in getting the... http://fb.me/1SwzQ3qdz     
    
    
    However, if you are selling soon, stick to neutral colors. And, did you know that exterior paint helps to repel... http://fb.me/1J44BWBVD     
    
    
    Use wide shots with a lot of light. And, take some outside shots, too. http://fb.me/2oG2MiWrl     
    
    
    Work on those scores. It pays.... http://fb.me/ImaVEUni     
    
    
    3 bd townhouse in #Longmont | $144,900 || #colorado #boulder #realestate #invest #retire #property #realtor http://twitter.com/retireNlongmont/status/244313806338154496/photo/1pic.twitter.com/6cG7s4T6     
    
    
    When employment returns to previous levels, the county will be really rocking. There is some concern, however,... http://fb.me/1E6CUBS1b     
    
    
    Rising optimism is a good thing to see because people spend more creating jobs, and creating more expansion. We... http://fb.me/1CBxQL8IU     
    
    
    For most of us, classic colors will keep your kitchen from looking dated - not that stainless looks bad.... http://fb.me/uto1oeD0     
    
    
    Seems to be agreement among the experts that the recent upswing in prices may be confined to this year. Given the... http://fb.me/1GjU3AAqg     
    
    
    http://www.bcbr.com/article/20120928/EDITION0804/120929913 … http://fb.me/12Ptgc5bF     
    
    
    Will have to stop through Hygiene on my next trip to Lyons.... http://fb.me/1T4tIXTw8     
    
    
    Sound's fun! Will have to give it a try.... http://fb.me/2suKp3Qq0     
    
    
    Hey Colorado! Ever wonder if there is a great information resource that you could just plug some information into... http://fb.me/20gO0jGDA     
    
    
    A little bit of work can make a huge difference.... http://fb.me/1DF7mLNm7     
    
    
    Bring us an offer on this great ranch-style townhouse. The seller has increased the allowance to $3,000. Call Suz... http://fb.me/29HA41eRz     
    
    
    The real estate market looks like a winner!... http://fb.me/1VqRyqsjV     
    
    
    Buyers - bring an offer! Seller has increased the floor allowance to $3,000 on Longmont, CO townhouse.... http://fb.me/1k7j1gex7     
    
    
    15-year rate where have you been all my life?... http://fb.me/yi7RwMoX     
    
    
    Ideas for Christmas. Guys, you should favorite/bookmark this page! http://www.surlatable.com  http://fb.me/2bHNIqkh5     
    
    
    Outstanding! http://www.bcbr.com/article/20121008/NEWS/121009931 … http://fb.me/26iRwTuo8     
    
    
    Time to blow out sprinkler systems and put away the garden hoses, Colorado... http://fb.me/1GfvtB0Ck     
    
    
    Go Longmont!... http://fb.me/22TM3FQiu     
    
    
    Restorations are beautiful. Some flippers have not quite caught on to what consumers are looking for in a... http://fb.me/1NmYtL7aw     
    
    
    "Does anyone else think that Trulia has the right to ask us to provide email addresses to them?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/Does_anyone_else_think_that_Trulia_has_the_right_t-442408 … #realestate    
    
    
    PRICE REDUCED to $142,900! Check out this secluded townhouse on Longmont's north side. http://fb.me/24QlKK5Ie     
    
    
    PRICE REDUCED to $142,900! Check out this secluded townhouse on Longmont's north side. Call Suz: 720.810.0683 http://fb.me/1lCyV8eFO     
    
    
    Wow! How about a home in Longmont, CO? Longmont sits on a ridge overlooking the St. Vrain and with an inspiring... http://fb.me/2gcbc6liC     
    
    
    Regardless of whether the HOA governs a building, such as a condo or townhome structure, or a neighborhood of... http://fb.me/1zrKwY7Y9     
    
    
    Louisville, of course, is more than mildly disappointed by this news. It seems grand plans like these are falling... http://fb.me/1EGx3hq4v     
    
    
    Interesting picture emerging. If low end and high end are selling well, how far can the middle be behind?... http://fb.me/10mQqw3s1     
    
    
    The team is pondering some remodeling projects. Of course, we'll let you know how things went. I do like the... http://fb.me/1NW2nGZai     
    
    
    What Amy doesn't say is you just have to bite the bullet and hand over documents that you might have pushed into... http://fb.me/1XV5MqVV9     
    
    
    In the late 1970s, (wow that sounds so long ago) Douglas County was asked to imagine planting what would be a... http://fb.me/1m3ismKNT     
    
    
    Remember the rule of three for decluttering - more than three items on shelves and tables is too much clutter.... http://fb.me/1lYkex6Ir     
    
    
    Small drinks for plants help keep the mold at bay.... http://fb.me/xDnsBIWS     
    
    
    Purchasing a home for the first time should be a consideration years in the making. You've treated your creditors... http://fb.me/LK8nHGqb     
    
    
    Less than a third of the card offers carried an annual fee, a fee feared to result from passage of the Credit... http://fb.me/224IEGlG7     
    
    
    http://twitter.com/retireNlongmont/status/258419772692234240/photo/1/large … http://fb.me/1NjgC8ZXi     
    
    
    Some parts of the market have come down in price to take advantage of the huge surge in buying this year as... http://fb.me/1KqHn5QJe     
    
    
    Find some mortgage numbers you like before setting out to look for that dream home.... http://fb.me/1ld4fCQgH     
    
    
    B R I N G   A N   O F F E R ! http://fb.me/2dwQc0vpX     
    
    
    It's so easy for your possessions to become clutter. And this it is this thing that all agents will tell you:... http://fb.me/JGHyvcZi     
    
    
    Check out Longmont, Colorado! http://fb.me/1WRlkxoai     
    
    
    Fun times! 
http://www.cottonwoodfarms.com/  http://fb.me/P1u9s6B9     
    
    
    Shop for the best insurance rate. http://homes.yahoo.com/news/tips-for-new-homeowners-to-save.html … http://fb.me/1Kcvo14Mh     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    If you believe in ghosts and Dan Akroyd refuses your calls ... who are you going to call?
http://on.wsj.com/VzHCZL  http://fb.me/2a4MMwe58     
    
    
    What is different about this year when compared to the previous five years? 

First, with sales receding there is... http://fb.me/LcqwlYct     
    
    
    Are you better off than you were in 2000, Denver area homeowners? Case-Shiller says yes, by an average of 33.48... http://fb.me/1PxbRZ0i5     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Raise your hand if you were there in northern California during the mid-90s. There was an acute shortage from... http://fb.me/1mZUEioAw     
    
    
    This Longmont, Colorodo seller wants to sell. Bring an offer! http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxWMPl2p     
    
    
    As expected, sale prices and the number of sales for the real estate resale market rose in the third quarter, the... http://fb.me/1R6Zu4fd2     
    
    
    “Get ready to bare your soul” 
- Joseph Damiani

http://wapo.st/PoQvW8  http://fb.me/PxFB4FfR     
    
    
    #Denver picked as a site for Brookings/JPMorgan 2013 Global Cities Initiative http://www.bizjournals.com/denver/news/2012/11/02/denver-picked-as-a-site-for.html?ana=twt … via @denbizjournal #Colorado    
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    The next Colorado snow storm is a week off. So there are plenty of days to get some exterior painting done. 

My... http://fb.me/1KtzIRyhe     
    
    
    You're tired of paying rent. The bite hurst even more as rents climb higher. What are you going to do? But you're... http://fb.me/1XrZAJANU     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    The trend began early. Boulder County has sold a disproportionate number of luxury homes when compared with the... http://fb.me/1H4lsb2e5     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Such a lovely home and it would look so much better decorated with Christmas lights along with chimney stockings... http://fb.me/1RFZL5Kp9     
    
    
    Rest of year expected to come in strong, too!... http://fb.me/M0jkGfJD     
    
    
    Move into a beautiful home for the holidays. There's still time. http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxWzdyuV     
    
    
    Are you ready? Get a plan is the best advice that can be offered. Here's how several did it.... http://fb.me/2f4sNv6V6     
    
    
    Homeowners are doing a lot of remodeling these days. They want to design the space they live in to fit their... http://fb.me/27r6uujRT     
    
    
    On the high end of the current spectrum are Swedish Gustavian painted pieces, the curves of the 18th-century... http://fb.me/ZvwlffK2     
    
    
    Real estate optimism is popping up all over.
http://www.mortgagenewsdaily.com/11072012_fannie_mae_housing_survey.asp … http://fb.me/1qnzxb0m0     
    
    
    If it's another mild winter, you might be tempted to replace that deck you've recently noticed has some rotting... http://fb.me/T4nrT0ph     
    
    
    Will real estate market trend continue in 2013? http://fb.me/23FwAPmbm     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    You can manage for many years after retirement. Do some online shopping and you can find many items that enhance... http://fb.me/1IciEGDYO     
    
    
    720 is the magic number. Your credit score is huge. But this article lays out some more tips that could save you... http://fb.me/2wAObAftO     
    
    
    Insurance is for major financial losses that will cause a disruption to your life and livelihood if you did not... http://fb.me/2ekc72qDF     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Here is a DIY that looks fun. We have already changed out our hardware, which means it's probably time to get... http://fb.me/2pIQuziO3     
    
    
    Northern Colorado vacancies are at the low levels we saw back in the late '90s.

John Rebchook, the former Rocky... http://fb.me/SjZ45glY     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Uh-oh. You ever have open a page you wish you had not opened. More than 500 pages of kitchens at this site. I'll... http://fb.me/2v1JYmpIZ     
    
    
    Our house starts looking festive right about now because we have already made center pieces and wreaths. Our... http://fb.me/1Ym8oRGUu     
    
    
    Interior designers suggest clearing out small items from the rooms you'll be using for entertaining. This is where... http://fb.me/zXtYxkyo     
    
    
    Oh yeah, things are looking up for this design.... http://fb.me/zKOPm8Rw     
    
    
    The decline among those 25 to 44 years of age is more than twice the overall decline. Creating more jobs would... http://fb.me/2e9eVAZpK     
    
    
    Rates are down again. But, the amount is so insignificant (six hundredths of a point), it likely would get an... http://fb.me/1mhU3ldEB     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Going mod. http://www.interiordesign.net/newproducts/Kitchen_Bath/index.php … http://fb.me/2eLEKprKa     
    
    
    Oh yeah, pillows add so much to a room. Get creative with arranging your pillows.... http://fb.me/MFJSz0tz     
    
    
    The 30-year fixed-rate mortgage is expected to stay low and average 3.5 percent in 2013.... http://fb.me/NdtKdc2d     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    Friend Kurt Whitt shared this interesting design. He asks if it's smart design or not? Anyone? http://fb.me/2eFr8mHkB     
    
    
    Rates keep sliding. http://www.millionairecorner.com/article/real-estate-market-trends-new-low-mortgage-rates … http://fb.me/23PT3SQqb     
    
    
    Cute Frederick downtown is getting an upgrade. How cool is that?... http://fb.me/DwsKvXN5     
    
    
    Trend is toward continuing improvement. 
http://www.bcbr.com/article/20121123/EDITION0801/121129966 … http://fb.me/1KMUgF7T6     
    
    
    Save energy by keeping that fridge in good shape.
http://homeguides.sfgate.com/repair-fridge-door-seal-27024.html … http://fb.me/1vATRFgUo     
    
    
    Five money saving tips for new home buyers | http://yhoo.it/Vw56ig  #Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property #Boulder #Realtor    
    
    
    http://homeguides.sfgate.com/care-blooming-trellis-38529.html?wa_user1=tombstone … http://fb.me/2uOPTnlQW     
    
    
    Hats off to Cherry Hills Village, Colo., which landed in the No. 1 spot on the MarketWatch list of the 10 Best... http://fb.me/1Kh2uMCCx     
    
    
    This is what sellers have been waiting for: rising prices. Boulder County, if you're thinking about selling your... http://fb.me/UyQrEO6b     
    
    
    This is one of those occasions where we like the good sense thinking of the author. Granite is not for everyone.... http://fb.me/1ao0V7l8J     
    
    
    http://www.marketwatch.com/story/condo-loan-denied-blame-the-building-2012-12-07 … http://fb.me/BAJm1bI8     
    
    
    A tall evergreen sure warms up the house.... http://fb.me/2eY6odwqc     
    
    
    There is something to cheer about in the latest home builder release.... http://fb.me/1edJ1br74     
    
    
    “The buyer pent-up demand continues,” said analyst Gary Bauer, an independent Littleton-based broker and... http://fb.me/105HY55Bn     
    
    
    Consumers are pretty sharp. They figured out in no time that Zillow was just ball-parking its zestimates. How can... http://fb.me/1YNj5Ea1P     
    
    
    After you personally inspect your home you want to have your home inspected by a professional, someone who is... http://fb.me/146aanNR2     
    
    
    "Buyers have said that they think buying a home is a safer haven than buying stocks"
Joan Cox of Metro Brokers,... http://fb.me/WqCn0a46     
    
    
    We love great homes! Love to see all the great upgrades. Fancy faucets, expansive spa-like bathrooms and walk-in... http://fb.me/1bYJ4A62z     
    
    
    The cure for this economy can be summed in one word: JOBS. Lenders could help that situation if they would... http://fb.me/2E5oFp0R4     
    
    
    For sellers, nothing puts a smile on their faces like seeing equity return. That means sellers who postponed... http://fb.me/1O15Nd8Md     
    
    
    Almost a 10 percent growth spurt - again in 2013! Scant inventory remains the story. It's a good time to check... http://fb.me/1PcIlshbC     
    
    
    Richmond is the area's most aggressive builder, having pulled almost one thousand permits in 2012 with one month... http://fb.me/t72NzaBO     
    
    
    It was a very good year!
http://insiderealestatenews.com/2012/12/case-shiller-denver-gains-6-9/ … http://fb.me/1R0uBCrvZ     
    
    
    Shopping for a home? Shop for a neighborhood first and then look for the home you think fits your needs and wants.... http://fb.me/XJdTXZxn     
    
    
    Downward pressure of prices has eased up already.... http://fb.me/2k8JJFh2D     
    
    
    The unclutter incident is not exactly a page turner. But, making it work will help when you go to sell.... http://fb.me/1LL2MemPX     
    
    
    http://homes.yahoo.com/news/cut-home-costs-in-2013-202043327.html … http://fb.me/AEt0vqHS     
    
    
    The area markets remain strong even through the historically slower holiday months. Denver mirrors the Boulder... http://fb.me/26YEzzEqX     
    
    
    Moving on up!... http://fb.me/2n8OVVjBL     
    
    
    "We like the make your home greener suggestion."
http://homes.yahoo.com/news/cut-home-costs-in-2013-202043327.html … http://fb.me/wdwj5Jit     
    
    
    Erie, like other small towns along the Interstate, has undergone a transformation. The streets didn't have... http://fb.me/2adDYUeIZ     
    
    
    Getting on track can work wonders for your financial picture. Just getting on top of things does indeed relieve... http://fb.me/1spbyLnKA     
    
    
    Phenomenal!
http://insiderealestatenews.com/2013/01/home-sales-soar-in-2012/#more-21306 … http://fb.me/2ozUEFFrH     
    
    
    Classic ... http://fb.me/FTXfUnwE     
    
    
    And Northern Colorado was more active, too.... http://fb.me/tHdcnBDR     
    
    
    This is just staggering (and about 30 days old). If you're planning to refinance, you want to read this closely.... http://fb.me/2evB2zIZU     
    
    
    If they build it, when they come?http://www.dailycamera.com/erie-news/ci_22357555/worlds-first-street-league-certified-skate-park-opens …    
    
    
    Like the rest of the Front Range, Longmont real estate has been selling quickly. Total sales hit 1,082, up 21... http://fb.me/UmyJVxl4     
    
    
    With rates at historic lows, we can probably expect to see more than a trickle in the flow of people who finish... http://fb.me/2IdcqbCAz     
    
    
    We were just watching "This Old House" on cable. Raymond, who heads our marketing, says he would like to have... http://fb.me/BIqkKAKo     
    
    
    The hits just keep coming!
http://www.bcbr.com/article/20130115/NEWS/130119977 … http://fb.me/2I8InOwe8     
    
    
    Where is that echo boom that pundits talk about? Could we be seeing the first signs? I don't know, but the... http://fb.me/2wrBXxiwf     
    
    
    It has been a long time since sales were good in December - for us anyway.... http://fb.me/2c8nV1VQj     
    
    
    Love the puddle trays! http://fb.me/CjoHjfc9     
    
    
    Did you ever imagine we would see the day when home prices headed up and the number of sales were lower because... http://fb.me/2fZsmR5IQ     
    
    
    Home buying season is coming (but you can buy anytime, of course). It's time to get the ducks in a row.... http://fb.me/2p6YsxSge     
    
    
    Definitely, things are looking up! http://fb.me/14laqnEhj     
    
    
    Here are the dates for the ArtWalk!
http://www.artwalklongmont.org/index.html  http://fb.me/1FlUr84tA     
    
    
    The all important home inspection ...... http://fb.me/2txQi7RqD     
    
    
    Million dollar (plus) homes continued to sprout in Boulder in December. The number reached nine for the month of... http://fb.me/2aXKUNtKy     
    
    
    Go native! You'll see a lot flower beds with Colorado natives. These plans are survivors that come back after... http://fb.me/1P8wNhMGn     
    
    
    If you live in Boulder County, you are already tethered to aerospace. Aerospace companies are here in abundance.... http://fb.me/2rgNTvOha     
    
    
    Let the searching begin! House hunters, you might have to start early again.... http://fb.me/2yLG2M5jV     
    
    
    Lending has greatly curtailed remodels, though some contractors tell us things might have been different for them... http://fb.me/1Xyq5zYsv     
    
    
    Oh, maybe we should stop reading stories about our state in the national media. We smiled when we read the Top 10... http://fb.me/2i4eSYZkM     
    
    
    Tailored to a client with exceptional means...... http://fb.me/1jUAhqAAd     
    
    
    You don't have to live with that squeak from the floor. http://tlc.howstuffworks.com/home/how-to-repair-floors.htm … http://fb.me/2afA0LaIs     
    
    
    What a great way to start off the year.... http://fb.me/1bxBuFXQY     
    
    
    New construction   has done little so far to improve inventory quantitatively in the Denver metro area.... http://fb.me/1Tui2pCrs     
    
    
    Need to crunch some numbers?http://www.bankrate.com/calculators/mortgages/loan-calculator.aspx … http://fb.me/xM0qhinZ     
    
    
    Job opportunity: Commercial Real Estate Broker at Marcus & Millichap - Greater Denver Area #jobs http://lnkd.in/hRrzQY     
    
    
    Wow! http://www.bcbr.com/article/20130208/NEWS/130209955 … http://fb.me/XaQSN2Ch     
    
    
    If you watched 60 Minutes on Sunday, then you will find the FTC report rather timid. Indeed, 1 in 20 reports have... http://fb.me/1VK6kdJBy     
    
    
    Lending might catch up with the economy one of these days. For now, builders are riding the surge in new jobs.... http://fb.me/CwpBuHo9     
    
    
    Thank you newcomers. - Raymond Alvarez and BoulderSuz, the Bolder Real Estate Team.    
    
    
    Mouthwatering kitchens: http://www.houzz.com  http://fb.me/7CqdMiYRc     
    
    
    One word: Wow!
http://insiderealestatenews.com/2013/02/signature-sales-sizzle/#more-22026 … http://fb.me/2iskh8pe1     
    
    
    In every metric, Boulder County's economy is improving. This might be one more: The Boulder City Council members... http://fb.me/24Zadgusk     
    
    
    A must read: 
http://www.marketwatch.com/story/10-things-credit-bureaus-wont-say-2013-02-15?Link=obinsite … http://fb.me/2OtKJdu19     
    
    
    Hey Joe, whaddayakno! Love Italian! Steaks are great, too. http://www.bcbr.com/article/20130219/NEWS/130219913 … http://fb.me/12PYkHhLo     
    
    
    Keep an eye on these offers. http://fb.me/1yLlwwHI9     
    
    
    That's pretty darned happy. http://fb.me/1USRsdpdK     
    
    
    Some good points about hiring a contractor in this article. Unless you're dealing with a fly-by-night operator... http://fb.me/2uKV57VwG     
    
    
    Aren't those lists great? The ones that tell you the best cities to retire in. Apparently, more than a few people... http://fb.me/FO8iSYq6     
    
    
    Existing-home sales in the West fell 5.7 percent to a pace of 1.15 million in January and were 5.7 percent below... http://fb.me/2QVxLGdkF     
    
    
    I'm a sucker for Soapstone. One of the current kitchen styles just wows me. - Suz... http://fb.me/1LSz341Ug     
    
    
    Longmont needs a few of these. Do we have... http://fb.me/2ulhm8xC8     
    
    
    In cae any one wonders why we cite the Case-Schiller reports on Denver, the reports typically exclude Boulder and... http://fb.me/2pGlAVqoc     
    
    
    Frustrating is today's word for finding rentals. Inside Real Estate is reporting that the vacancy rate for... http://fb.me/1lC5LvSk1     
    
    
    NAR, the National Association of Realtors, says pending home sales rose 4.5 percent in January. The monthly... http://fb.me/Md2kx5aw     
    
    
    Great floors for great homes. http://tlc.howstuffworks.com/home/flooring-tips-tricks.htm … http://fb.me/2nq1bq48r     
    
    
    Art that tastes good. . . http://www.artwalklongmont.org/index.html  http://fb.me/NXueALyJ     
    
    
    Someone inexperienced and young was snared by this kind of scam. A parent posted a question on Trulia asking what... http://fb.me/1DZfkVGgT     
    
    
    http://www.dailycamera.com/lifestyles/ci_22725054/time-start-seeds-and-plant-greens-boulder-county … http://fb.me/2yEIFxi4F     
    
    
    Down by the Bay, old is new again. We agree, this look that says destruction is attractive in its way. Why not?... http://fb.me/2NNpFLdB4     
    
    
    Here's that bike map the city of Longmont offers.... http://fb.me/u3XCIR2v     
    
    
    Florida is the sunshine state again for a few.... http://fb.me/LLMZU4vR     
    
    
    Watch out! Lenders may try to get your business by quoting you bottom-of-the market rates that they know they... http://fb.me/1CcQajJHC     
    
    
    More upward price pressure expected amid falling number of listings.... http://fb.me/2nziMcT3w     
    
    
    http://live.wsj.com/video/scammers-new-target-your-cell-phone-2013-03-08-201151457/E6CA886C-4996-4A99-8AEE-276EC234 …... http://fb.me/zb9ibODo     
    
    
    The downside of student loans ...... http://fb.me/2BDw0RpYo     
    
    
    What's the buzz on candlestick making?... http://fb.me/2BNj4hW2S     
    
    
    “The HPI showed strong growth during the typically slow winter season,” Mark Fleming, chief economist for... http://fb.me/2ngW4QnsZ     
    
    
    Hello newcomers! Hope your year is starting strong!    
    
    
    Inside Real Estate News reports an improving picture for foreclosures in Denver. 

The dreaded "shadow inventory"... http://fb.me/1zQR8067B     
    
    
    http://www.popularmechanics.com/home/improvement/lawn-garden/1273551?click=pop_more … http://fb.me/2wjKQM1T0     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/news/6-worst-home-fixes-money-070151422.html … http://fb.me/158gxUZTl     
    
    
    http://www.bankrate.com/finance/real-estate/7-questions-buying-home-1.aspx … http://fb.me/L0hE7yom     
    
    
    Finally, some good news on this front. http://www.cnbc.com/id/100548913  http://fb.me/2LO00Uimz     
    
    
    Thinking of selling your gorgeous home in Boulder County? Call us for a free market analysis. Suz at 720.810.0683    
    
    
    Oh misery knows no bounds like the misery that accompanies a bad relationship. 

Your neighbors can be a powerful... http://fb.me/E5KgmLxV     
    
    
    Check out this Facebook page. See the art before the launch of the business: 
http://lnkd.in/Vvzdg8     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/2E0RzLmFQ     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/CgOEePyM     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/2RlBwJJUa     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/11MVpubQS     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/uOCepHeX     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/2wSyziNUG     
    
    
    Time to spruce up.
http://www.timescall.com/news/ci_22805386/firestone-host-april-27-cleanup-day … http://fb.me/DzsvzWRZ     
    
    
    http://www.downtownlongmont.com/arts-and-entertainment/downtown-events/clean-and-green … http://fb.me/2IW0x8IoS     
    
    
    Feeling happy, you must be in Colorado.
http://www.marketwatch.com/story/the-10-happiest-states-in-the-us-2013-03-16# … http://fb.me/2yKFZDjCL     
    
    
    Location isn't everything in real estate. No. Price is extremely important. Colorado's Front Range has the best... http://fb.me/1SxY0PH8K     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/calculator/real-estate/hom01/ … http://fb.me/yK2HbYNv     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/calculator/real-estate/hom08/ … http://fb.me/2cBY8uu4c     
    
    
    Oh, those unsightly lines. Have those wrinkles got you worried? 

... the ones on the sidewalk. ;-)

The city of... http://fb.me/1GIM5nmaJ     
    
    
    http://www.bankrate.com/finance/mortgages/mortgage-analysis.aspx?ec_id=cmctre_02_comm_RE_image_headline … http://fb.me/2f95ZFVWY     
    
    
    Stock market has been moving higher. That translates to higher mortgage rates. But rates are still historically... http://fb.me/EdOpb7r2     
    
    
    How does this strategy sound? Price a home right where it is likely to attract a number of agents and buyers... http://fb.me/248UjQVNA     
    
    
    Good news on rates! http://lnkd.in/JhcZu2     
    
    
    This will be a familiar story to anyone who is shopping for a home. It should be no secret to everyone else that... http://fb.me/Mw0mDexM     
    
    
    Housing starts near 5-year high in February ...
It was bound to happen. That was a 5-year stretch that we're glad... http://fb.me/10RNlahYt     
    
    
    Get your money's worth from your appliances.... http://fb.me/1Xd5cBNkd     
    
    
    For many, having a lively downtown is essential to their decision to locate in a particular city. Longmont has it.... http://fb.me/EvGzqjOz     
    
    
    You've heard Realtors tell of homes flying off the market. We are guilty as charged. The sign goes in the yard and... http://fb.me/KDubDIXM     
    
    
    Show the seller you are serious. Throw on some snow shoes and go house shopping this weekend.    
    
    
    Close to some small shops, restaurants, and elementary and middle schools. The middle school has a running track.... http://fb.me/21jlgVZHY     
    
    
    The mantra would be too long if we had to say all of these considerations three times. You get it. Buying a home... http://fb.me/23BASRqAF     
    
    
    http://online.wsj.com/article/SB10001424127887324539404578342733155607320.html?mod=WSJ_article_RecentColumns_Getti …... http://fb.me/2d398dPet     
    
    
    The good news: There are things you can do to get your credit profile in shape. One of the great benefits of... http://fb.me/20HdmGegW     
    
    
    If you have been overwatering your yard, the news isn't good. The roots don't go as deep as they should when a... http://fb.me/2cuDnRAeu     
    
    
    Paying down credit card balances is a good idea, anyway.... http://fb.me/20B6A3Lpw     
    
    
    It's this gorgeous here every day - almost. http://fb.me/1FTh6FrcV     
    
    
    Shadow inventory? Are the banks still holding onto inventory?... http://fb.me/2MEfQI5LD     
    
    
    2007 was the peak for the real estate market. As the local economy continues to improve, who knows? http://fb.me/11N0SZD9c     
    
    
    This bodes well for another good year in real estate. Sellers are able to sell quickly, if they price their homes... http://fb.me/2whGYyCnw     
    
    
    http://www.denverpost.com/breakingnews/ci_22873232/denver-home-prices-rose-9-2-percent-year … http://fb.me/1SEA0YNbu     
    
    
    Sellers love buyers who are serious and are realistic. http://lnkd.in/Yb7k-K     
    
    
    Cautious pundits ... With inventory short its no wonder some are calling #Colorado one of top markets. http://lnkd.in/2eQgMY     
    
    
    Sellers, you betcha you and your Realtor can make a difference. Generally, if you followed suggestions from your... http://fb.me/2gszIi8oE     
    
    
    Snow is stacking up in the high country, but more is needed. Thank goodness there is something called April on the way!    
    
    
    If you are having your basement finished, you should know what an egress window is. An egress window provides an... http://fb.me/1CVuLmzwq     
    
    
    Get your track shoes on. The spring buying season is about to bolt from the starting line. Freddie Mac expect... http://fb.me/1BQjYeZNs     
    
    
    How would a Realtor help with house flipping? House flippers are busy enough ordering jobs materials and managing... http://fb.me/22nTbTBTB     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/calculator/real-estate/hom01/ … http://fb.me/IQjdJqPD     
    
    
    Zillow provides what are called zestimates, an approximation that is drawn on certain algorithms that are quite a... http://fb.me/F722U7Fg     
    
    
    Spring gardening is here! We missed some leaf raking in fall, so that's where we started. We had four bags of... http://fb.me/2mke9oluE     
    
    
    Longmont, Boulder, Erie, Lafayette, Louisville, Superior, Lyons, Hygiene, Gun Barrel, Niwot - you're special!... http://fb.me/2DUwuAIux     
    
    
    When demand reaches a frenzy, you have time-pressed buyers who will even buy sight unseen - at least, that's what... http://fb.me/EWgJM2rc     
    
    
    Could you pay off a mortgage even faster? Some can.... http://fb.me/OwTO7cCy     
    
    
    Interesting read in the Wall Street Journal today: Why It's Still Hard to Get a Mortgage

If you follow these... http://fb.me/2T1YTMwgx     
    
    
    If you need a de-commissioned water treatment plant, We know where to find one. A Longmont Times-Call article... http://fb.me/2xV3GOUog     
    
    
    Give me plenty of white. I love white kitchen cabinets. http://fb.me/EASwomC2     
    
    
    Buying in a market with an inventory shortage is for the brave? The strong hearted? Not if you approach it armed... http://fb.me/1DNK5kipT     
    
    
    Just answered: "If we would like to build a new house in Boulder ... http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/If_we_would_like_to_build_a_new_house_in_Boulder_-503104 … #realestate #Colorado    
    
    
    Considering a "dirt start" home - that is a new home you have built from the ground up. We have worked with and... http://fb.me/1YPpGBvdL     
    
    
    If you ever had a desire to live close to a university campus with all of the entertainment offerings and adult... http://fb.me/1msUFXRfY     
    
    
    If you ever had a desire to live close to a university campus with all of the entertainment offerings and adult... http://fb.me/1e4Inp1ut     
    
    
    Shows like a model home! Gorgeous Niwot home with hardwood and tile floors, granite countertops - and more... http://fb.me/Jk2WSbKP     
    
    
    Just answered the question - "Do you know of any good property managment?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Rental_Basics/Since_my_home_is_not_selling_I_am_considering_ren-216891 … #Colorado #realestate #property    
    
    
    Bulking up - gotta love it! http://fb.me/2dOf1m41r     
    
    
    Was there extra energy in the air this morning? You weren't imagining it. 

Inside Real Estate says March was... http://fb.me/2eKW2DBQd     
    
    
    304 Homestead Parkway, #Longmont CO - Trulia http://pinterest.com/pin/278519558177704040/ … via @pinterest #Colorado #realestate #property #invest    
    
    
    1708 Twilight Court, #Longmont CO - Trulia http://pinterest.com/pin/278519558177704076/ … via @pinterest #Colorado #realestate #property #invest #retire    
    
    
    Looking for a banner year, the pundits say. http://lnkd.in/kmDhDp     
    
    
    http://www.timescall.com/lifestyles/entertainment/ci_22939306/longmonts-firehouse-art-center-sally-stockhold-exhibi …... http://fb.me/vuDNphh4     
    
    
    With rents going up along with a scarcity of inventory, you would think that this would be the perfect time to be... http://fb.me/1Fkkm0Fdk     
    
    
    Want to learn more about me? Check out http://about.me/susanalvarez  #Colorado #realestate #property #invest #homes #Longmont    
    
    
    Check out my about.me page! http://pinterest.com/pin/278519558177708934/ … via @pinterest #Colorado #realestate #property #invest #retire #Longmont    
    
    
    Clear sign of spring: The farmers markets in Boulder and Longmont open Saturday. Bring your re-cyclable bags for... http://fb.me/2iA3tHqmu     
    
    
    Appealing peelers from the San Francisco Chronicle:
http://sfgate.houzz.com/ideabooks/8987015/w/sid=0 … http://fb.me/1jKY3Nnqm     
    
    
    Get your ducks in a row:... http://fb.me/1ZD5dLHAT     
    
    
    http://www.thestreet.com/story/11883918/1/personal-loans-poor-credit--new-online-service.html?cm_ven_int=obinsite … http://fb.me/24TNP5J1b     
    
    
    If you're considering buying something new, you will like this link:... http://fb.me/15rMjEm56     
    
    
    Take another look at Boulder County! Beautiful home ... Close to shopping, walking paths, golf course, marina and... http://fb.me/F9Q4s4gJ     
    
    
    Has the market gone crazy? Reports have been cropping up in Florida about buyers buying over the Internet - sight... http://fb.me/2FEYEdukZ     
    
    
    http://home.howstuffworks.com/home-improvement/construction/projects/home-construction-pictures.htm#page=0 … http://fb.me/1EnpME622     
    
    
    OPINION:

Today we read "Is the Housing Recovery 'Artificial'? Does it Matter?", a headline in DSNews today. We... http://fb.me/2l5kYgJal     
    
    
    The myth of freeloading run amok may have lots of appeal, it's just not true. http://lnkd.in/9xGfDm     
    
    
    "Considering return on investment, where should money be spent on remodeling?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Selling/Considering_return_on_investment_where_should_mon-504137 … #realestate #property #invest    
    
    
    It seems we're all scratching our heads over this inventory shortage. And, I'm not buying entirely the analysis... http://fb.me/1DhtmnvDM     
    
    
    Here in Colorado, we are facing a serious water shortage. Drip systems use less water. Dual flush toilets are... http://fb.me/1WDv2Rajp     
    
    
    I love No. 3! http://lnkd.in/3pgf4k     
    
    
    Where the bold meet adventure: Boulder. http://fb.me/21Tb37Wke     
    
    
    Zillow's zestimates: houses on same side of street in Longmont. 4 bedroom 3 bath is zestimated at $278,000. Any... http://fb.me/2d8BTQDDA     
    
    
    We like the "less is more" advice from USA Today. Do we really need more space? Or do we need more self-control?... http://fb.me/J4WPUmB4     
    
    
    Ahh, Florence! On some days, you might think you're in Tuscany while enjoying panoramic views of the countryside... http://fb.me/23UkrzXoC     
    
    
    Smart people can be mistaken. Looking at the present state of affairs in real estate, you would be tempted to ask... http://fb.me/1lXnsc8qH     
    
    
    http://www.houselogic.com/home-advice/plants-trees/how-grow-your-best-tomatoes-ever/ … http://fb.me/EOP1BjMW     
    
    
    Reclaimed wood is attractive.... http://fb.me/1EdIc328O     
    
    
    Markets are "sizzling" but not quite normal. http://lnkd.in/vFGKMZ     
    
    
    Jim Neighbors - aka Gomer Pyle - from an early TV series had a favorite line: "surprise, surprise, surprise ..."... http://fb.me/1wMb6cAZM     
    
    
    Christmas was good to you this year. You unwrapped an iPhone and you've been downloading apps every since. 

We... http://fb.me/23wJ1NU0O     
    
    
    Save up for a down payment. How you manage your credit has a bit impact on securing a mortgage. We have tightened... http://fb.me/1RmGI0HSY     
    
    
    Builders are buying lots in Longmont. Let us know if you would like to see some models and sites where you can... http://fb.me/1EhFL46Ld     
    
    
    My husband ran a food stand when he was kid. He turned a profit by splitting up big bags of sunflower seeds and... http://fb.me/2DZ5j9OK4     
    
    
    Monitoring the market on a day to day price seems a headache, but it is worth doing.... http://fb.me/2mRme6tUR     
    
    
    The nascent recovery is gaining some traction. The greater story is one of growing confidence. However,  the... http://fb.me/2iJC5yhgf     
    
    
    When you ask your Realtor about the crime statistics in a neighborhood or city, the Realtor might refer to you the... http://fb.me/vFJiZjIR     
    
    
    Prices are up in Northern Colorado, says the Northern Colorado Business Report. Greeley prices have jumped 18... http://fb.me/1woOo1gbG     
    
    
    Have you seen the rents lately? Owning a home is less expensive than renting. 

Smart buyers get their ducks in a... http://fb.me/1FkEQhHXj     
    
    
    Trulia says it has been on Trulia one day. Better run, that doesn't mean recent anymore.... http://fb.me/12Z5mBOmt     
    
    
    Spend some quality time with your plants. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SaazaZwrSE4 … http://fb.me/HQeAFGCV     
    
    
    We've been reading over the years that a recovery in real estate will be uneven. That rings true.

Oregon has... http://fb.me/20Z2rb3vG     
    
    
    Colorado traditionally attracts investment from Canada. Now Canada finds it has come big competition. It was... http://fb.me/2FpE67UP2     
    
    
    Already had our vote! http://fb.me/2AHBlacqh     
    
    
    Wonder if the Bolder Bolder has ever run from Boulder to Longmont ... http://fb.me/2W9cVSa26     
    
    
    8 reasons you want to hire a Realtor

One of our favorite TV programs has the two stars remind the public that the... http://fb.me/CiPR6jck     
    
    
    Longmont has several attractive neighboring communities, some with St. Vrain Valley District schools. The... http://fb.me/1KfiEE3aU     
    
    
    What's to like about Erie? Freeway access. You can be flying down I-25 or E-470 in minutes from the door - if you... http://fb.me/1ZsQLGaoL     
    
    
    What's to like about Firestone? Quick freeway access. Spring is well under way. Are you thinking about a new home?
Call Suz: 720.810.1534    
    
    
    We were just thinking about the foreclosure story we talked about this week. There are states that are seeing a... http://fb.me/23Kx2gIHD     
    
    
    You knew there was a reason you love house plants.... http://fb.me/2jYLSfxbo     
    
    
    Home living gets sweeter with a back yard hive.... http://fb.me/1OyRIjHLU     
    
    
    If your project has left over materials, you should store those - just in case.... http://fb.me/2bhxp68jw     
    
    
    If a lively historic downtown is going to be your next move, check out Louisville. Main Street, Louisville has... http://fb.me/sDUvVP73     
    
    
    Are people really jumping on these 75 and 96 month loans?

Marketwatch says 19 percent of the loans signed in the... http://fb.me/2lV0p5jv0     
    
    
    http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/04/14/lower-down-payment-loans-more-common/2075095/ … http://fb.me/7zJi9fMBB     
    
    
    Guilty as charged. As summer approaches and the prospect of watering restrictions looms, rinsing off dishes falls... http://fb.me/21Am8zwcz     
    
    
    Nice brisk hikes are a few steps outside your door in a lot of places. A favorite: Head over on Baseline west.... http://fb.me/22DCOv0h2     
    
    
    VA loans are great ones for new buyers. http://fb.me/13TN7gD9H     
    
    
    A contributing writer offers their take on the current real estate market in a web article that appeared March... http://fb.me/1s9AGHg9w     
    
    
    Suz has projects like this all over the south side of the house.... http://fb.me/1cGw7seJs     
    
    
    Zero down? Yes, it's not just for vets, zero-down payment mortgages are available through the USDA Rural... http://fb.me/1G1HNF1l2     
    
    
    The trend: New jobs are translating to more construction. http://fb.me/JLSq1oL1     
    
    
    Talk to at least three lenders.

Rates on a 30-year fixed conforming loan can vary at least as much as a quarter... http://fb.me/1n9deFxSF     
    
    
    3 great reasons for those planning to purchase a home to look at their credit scores: 

Whatever your motivation... http://fb.me/2kJhFzqAL     
    
    
    What would you caption this photo? 
You have to see Boulder County.... http://fb.me/1TrUg14qY     
    
    
    See my answer: "What are buyers saying they want to see in 2013? And are you finding it in #Longmont ?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/What_are_buyers_saying_they_want_to_see_in_And_a-503771 …
#realestate    
    
    
    Sellers can aim too high. That might not be the right strategy. 

#realestate #Colorado http://lnkd.in/WsprCu     
    
    
    The road back ... Here is at tip for possibly avoiding bankruptcy.... http://fb.me/2Mg1V6Lba     
    
    
    Multifamily construction is on a pace this year unseen since 2008. Single family building is a different story,... http://fb.me/tzIP4ZpA     
    
    
    Love salmon! Going to try this recipe right away. http://fb.me/Nx1SNHS3     
    
    
    OPINION: Considerations for shopping in the U.S. coastal states:

1) Where are do the journalists live that report... http://fb.me/GR6pShx7     
    
    
    The year 2013 is off to a strong start in Longmont, Colorado, Realtors tell the Times-Call.

Prices that moved 12... http://fb.me/GHsA56ce     
    
    
    Just answered the question - "criminal activity at tyndall green and area 9" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Crime_and_Safety/criminal_activity_at_tyndall_green_and_area_-507479 … #realestate #property #Colorado #invest    
    
    
    Note to sellers:
We do appreciate this is a sensitive subject. But, you may want to give some thought to lowering... http://fb.me/2lXd7tuYz     
    
    
    Karl E. Case, a Wellesley College professor, said Tuesday that the recovery appears healthy. Noting the national... http://fb.me/xQ3MqH19     
    
    
    The snow on the ground says otherwise, but it's definitely spring in real estate!... http://fb.me/21K2C8M3h     
    
    
    The streets might be slick. But the snow doesn't stick. 

Don't sweat the weather here in Boulder County. 

You... http://fb.me/GEwtJtxj     
    
    
    Very cool. http://fb.me/2ItC1P6AL     
    
    
    From the desk of Amy Hoak at Marketwatch:

If you haven't already inspected your home before more Colorado is hit... http://fb.me/2g4rjm0zm     
    
    
    The day after the storm, it's head outside time in Boulder County. http://fb.me/2yK1WPMMT     
    
    
    Boulder County awakens to glorious clear skies. http://fb.me/20zWMzEKK     
    
    
    The picture for housing is quickly changing as Colorado sheds its status as top foreclosure state. Foreclosures... http://fb.me/2b8XJ8n9A     
    
    
    Will you be selling? Or buying? Longmont properties range from modestly priced homes in the 200s to much more.... http://fb.me/2J8h62eq3     
    
    
    Here in Colorado, falling rates could be like throwing gasoline on a fire.

#realestate #property http://lnkd.in/hQy3tt     
    
    
    Check out some of these debit cards:... http://fb.me/2K8w9QNYH     
    
    
    Colorado ranked fifth in the number of homes powered by solar at 43,000 homes. - Northern Colorado Business Report    
    
    
    They key point we observe in this article is investors are fixing up the distressed properties they purchase, and... http://fb.me/2kEsF9aiI     
    
    
    Near record-low mortgage rates and pent-up demand for rental units will keep residential construction a pillar of... http://fb.me/2pedIjvfw     
    
    
    Buyers! There's a break in the weather this weekend. Today's featured house is in Louisville. Shows like a model,... http://fb.me/2blFY3U7E     
    
    
    Love kitchens, especially gourmet kitchens. http://fb.me/2sHZybTiI     
    
    
    We already knew that Denver is on top of the real estate markets in the nation. Here's a conundrum: Sellers need... http://fb.me/HgStGha8     
    
    
    Do you have greater priorities?... http://fb.me/Q2ILhth3     
    
    
    Boulder County - where the sky has no limit #realestate #Colorado #property http://www.trulia.com/profile/BoulderSuZ/qanda/q/ …    
    
    
    http://blog.credit.com/2013/03/the-11-most-commonly-asked-credit-questions/?utm_source=CBS&utm_medium=content&utm_ …... http://fb.me/1HYOcYlUx     
    
    
    Things you need to know about HOAs.

Many communities have web sites and these can be consulted for information.... http://fb.me/CPfj0dUp     
    
    
    Great designs!... http://fb.me/2zfj4a4wp     
    
    
    The porch you always wanted?... http://fb.me/1IKew5RwP     
    
    
    U.S. News and World Report:
You may have heard that rental properties can be a great way to generate passive... http://fb.me/1tH25o2jt     
    
    
    The Bolder Real Estate Team: There are four types of mortgage loans. Available in the market are fixed rate... http://fb.me/2N2kbdqOk     
    
    
    The Bolder Real Estate Team: 
Find out what loan is appropriate for your needs.

Fixed rate loan: Payment... http://fb.me/25sN8kSRq     
    
    
    From the desk of the Bolder Real Estate Team:

Negative amortization happens when a loan payment schedule has... http://fb.me/27L1khCzq     
    
    
    Biggest home price rise since the bubble is latest sign of housing recovery http://lnkd.in/5vt3jZ     
    
    
    Another sure-fire way to tell things are heating up in real estate: the return of spec homes.

Diana Olick of CNBC... http://fb.me/x7j54NVp     
    
    
    Anyone have a home for sale? http://lnkd.in/aZfvAR 
#realestate #colorado #boulder #property    
    
    
    Quail Crossing in Longmont sent out its newsletter today. A garage sale is planned on May 18. Starts at 8 a.m.

-... http://fb.me/M33kvw0Y     
    
    
    It's a 'sellers' market', but ... 
http://www.trulia.com/blog/bouldersuz/ … By Susan Alvarez

#realestate #property #Colorado #Boulder #invest    
    
    
    German Building Uses Algae for Heating and Cooling http://lnkd.in/asvaBn     
    
    
    According to an April 4 analysis written by Trulia’s chief economist and published by Forbes, the supply of... http://fb.me/KHUrb2fT     
    
    
    The number of luxury homes solder were off in March. The Boulder County Business Report quoting Coldwell Banker,... http://fb.me/2p7DhoBjj     
    
    
    A little extra, very little ...
http://homes.yahoo.com/news/a-bathroom-refresher-for--265-174909908.html … http://fb.me/2oQ0yxlmS     
    
    
    Consult a Realtor. http://fb.me/26kYvLkAl     
    
    
    Hiring the right Realtor:

Hire a Realtor and mortgage broker you can tell communicates well. It’s the biggest... http://fb.me/2PAVUdC8a     
    
    
    Keep in mind that more than 30 percent of resale housing is acquired by investors who make these units available... http://fb.me/23ySrmvr8     
    
    
    http://www.homegoods.com/blog/2013/02/16/7-ways-to-arrange-bed-pillows/?cmpid=H_BN2102 … http://fb.me/261wtVY0W     
    
    
    Nothing like having a few cold ones close by. We always had a tub or a cooler. But now you can get stylish and... http://fb.me/15ODOwWcO     
    
    
    http://www.housingwire.com/news/2013/04/29/hud-homes-add-inventory-starved-market … http://fb.me/2izfGkCz3     
    
    
    Shows gorgeous! Wouldn't you like to see what the owners have done? Me, too! Let's go take a private tour. Call... http://fb.me/13iltRULy     
    
    
    http://www.realtor.com/blogs/2013/04/26/6-quick-and-cheap-ways-to-give-your-home-a-spring-makeover/ … http://fb.me/2suriXIan     
    
    
    This in not a rare occurrence. The seller spends weeks getting their home ready, they select a Realtor and then... http://fb.me/7QrAozpvt     
    
    
    Active listing: Let's go see it! Call Suz: 720.810.0683... http://fb.me/svB1Pbba     
    
    
    The next generation is living in mom and dad's basement. They have few job prospects. You know the story. Bleak... http://fb.me/MarlIarO     
    
    
    http://www.bcbr.com/article/20130426/EDITION/130429921 … http://fb.me/22f9TI0iC     
    
    
    This may seem monotonous at this point, but prices keep surging. Prices jumped the most they have since May 2006,... http://fb.me/1FZNxrs5q     
    
    
    Is now the best time to buy? Could be. We like this better: "When you're ready to buy is the best time to buy."... http://fb.me/24Goy9UXh     
    
    
    Fixed-mortgage rates hovered near record lows this past week, amid weaker than expected first-quarter economic... http://fb.me/LqAsSuQl     
    
    
    http://www.housingwire.com/fastnews/2013/04/30/fannie-mae-continues-shrink-its-mortgage-portfolio … http://fb.me/2luJgM3bN     
    
    
    NPR reports that news was better than expected in the jobs numbers - 165,000! Get used to it!    
    
    
    Have you spoken to a Realtor lately? http://fb.me/1RMkhKDsX     
    
    
    Average rate on 15-year fixed mortgage fell to a new low and the 30-year fixed loan declined further. The number... http://fb.me/1zht0ueim     
    
    
    If you are working on building your credit, limiting the number of inquiries can be helpful. (Checking your own... http://fb.me/IvVdc0eW     
    
    
    If you're thinking about selling, this is a great time to meet with a Realtor. The Realtor will provide a market... http://fb.me/1TSE3gCBI     
    
    
    #Longmont #Louisville #Colorado CALL Suz for a free market analysis on your #home. http://www.trulia.com/profile/BoulderSuZ/ … #realestate #property #retire    
    
    
    We changed our name.

Suz is the name we have been promoting. BoulderSuz is all over Google searches. Raymond is... http://fb.me/20JECJNfJ     
    
    
    They're back!

http://www.cnbc.com/id/100716455  http://fb.me/1RZ8rVWyj     
    
    
    Finally, a ground shift that could lead the way to widespread recovery in real estate. http://lnkd.in/NhxSxE     
    
    
    Just answered - "Is the weather a factor in sales? Or is that myth?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/Is_the_weather_a_factor_in_sales_Or_is_that_myth_-264616 … #realestate #Realtor #property    
    
    
    From Trulia (edited for length): 
How do you botch the marketing of your home right out of the gate?
1) Ignoring... http://fb.me/vTBjPdb1     
    
    
    Where does the time go? It's May already.

A lot of you have already headed off for the hardware store. And, a... http://fb.me/199z3f8xv     
    
    
    Congrats to Denver for the lavish of praise in the national press. Forbes points to the emerging downtown as one... http://fb.me/26Gk2dbXv     
    
    
    There is one top 10 list we're happy Colorado has put in the rearview mirror: Its status as a foreclosure state.... http://fb.me/28kKEXLo9     
    
    
    How much lifetime retirement income can your savings generate? A 65-year-old can reasonably expect to generate an... http://fb.me/2w8LJLW3z     
    
    
    http://bit.ly/15TOATW  http://fb.me/26f4oDmDv     
    
    
    Builder lotteries have returned!

We noticed a few weeks ago the Los Angeles Times carried an article that... http://fb.me/2nUro3inX     
    
    
    Just answered: "Is it standard practice for agents to have different commission rates ...?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/Is_it_standard_practice_for_agents_to_have_differe-509476 … #realestate #Colorado    
    
    
    "Risks of doing business with an investor..." http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/Risks_of_doing_business_with_an_investor_-518931 …
#propery #Colorado #Boulder #Longmont #Realtor #realestate #retire    
    
    
    "When should you start the house hunting process if you want to move in by June?" http://t.co/RTeL1JZQq7

#realestate #property #Colorado    
    
    
    Pet odor can drive off prospective buyers as fast as anything else. If an "accident" is not discovered in time,... http://fb.me/28csvS5m8     
    
    
    Looks like a style for everyone.... http://fb.me/2sSFXGo4P     
    
    
    After all the rain and snow of the past several weeks, Colorado might be behind on its chores - like us. We'll be... http://fb.me/LAq3xudW     
    
    
    "Use your knowledge, and your heart, to stand up for those who can't stand, speak for those who can't speak, be a... http://fb.me/GOjEnA0r     
    
    
    You can put your rising equity to work for you. 

Renovation, more schooling? 

Refinance and tap the equity in... http://fb.me/2gu2dJWez     
    
    
    If you waited until tomorrow to mow, you will be attacking this chore with a machete. Mowing once a weeks is... http://fb.me/2bMPNBA7D     
    
    
    Just answered: "Is it necessary to have a real estate social media presence?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/Is_it_necessary_to_have_a_real_estate_social_media-455507 … #realestate #property #Colorado #invest    
    
    
    Just answered: "Where (is) information on building contractors/remodelers?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Remodel_and_Renovate/Where_do_you_turn_to_for_information_regarding_bui-376283 …
#Longmont #Colorado #property #homes    
    
    
    Check out making monofilament line. You could become popular with neighbors and save tons by recycling.... http://fb.me/1ESxG6XHo     
    
    
    Easy fix: If you have a window screen that is worn out, it's an easy fix. You can buy a role of the stuff at... http://fb.me/1c83zPZDE     
    
    
    "What social media outlets ...? What sites do you think drive the most business...?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/What_social_media_outlets_are_you_most_comfortable-522765 …
#realestate #Realtor #property    
    
    
    "How do you sell ownership when it isn't cheaper in the short term?" http://t.co/takqCKiocM

#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont    
    
    
    You get great views when from the top!... http://fb.me/SHYlfIjp     
    
    
    We never get tired of looking out at the Flatirons!
http://bouldersuz.wordpress.com/?p=1010&preview=true … http://fb.me/2G0xbOs6G     
    
    
    Boulder - still the media darling 
Check out my blog:
http://t.co/jJTsP3CDxB

#realestate #realtor #property #invest #retire    
    
    
    Looking good, Boulder! http://fb.me/1G42i7WdK     
    
    
    Erie continues to impress. According to the Daily Camera, the small burg at the E-470 and I-25 crossroads will... http://fb.me/ztAdUqE5     
    
    
    There is a light at the end of the credit card payoff tunnel. See how far it is:... http://fb.me/J24PNpEj     
    
    
    Suz is already busier than a one-armed wallpaper hanger. http://fb.me/JwNME3ZY     
    
    
    Key to obtaining financing is not making major changes like quitting your job, buying a new car. If you're taking... http://fb.me/1Ubueygxz     
    
    
    "The trend is accelerating, helped along by low mortgage rates, rising home prices and a stabilizing employment... http://fb.me/1jjha7YCB     
    
    
    Excerpts from Bloomberg:

It’s too early to say another bubble is emerging. So far, the biggest price gains are... http://fb.me/AvFo6aFO     
    
    
    Remember: Preparation is everything in painting. Knowing how much paint you're going to need will save you an... http://fb.me/TVVLSlVn     
    
    
    Let's you get you started on some projects to get that house looking showroom ready.... http://fb.me/L2o1xBqB     
    
    
    Ever wonder how a $500 TV ends up costing you almost 700 by the time you're finished paying? The interest can eat... http://fb.me/2p9NiaWvr     
    
    
    http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-505145_162-57584806/rate-on-30-year-mortgage-edges-up/ … http://fb.me/2jlhuNfB6     
    
    
    Boulder County had 124 foreclosure filings in the first quarter of 2012 - the state's lowest rate. Completed... http://fb.me/IwNbL7Mc     
    
    
    Overall sales of homes priced above $500,000 are up across the U.S. compared with a year ago. The highest... http://fb.me/Ffm4CMA7     
    
    
    Walk the area and you'll see this is a great location - close to two golf courses, small shops, a grocer and... http://fb.me/2mE7hBSRy     
    
    
    "Since my home is not selling, I am considering renting it... http://www.trulia.com/voices/Rental_Basics/Since_my_home_is_not_selling_I_am_considering_ren-216891 …
#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #invest    
    
    
    http://www.dsnews.com/articles/fannie-mae-economy-will-reaccelerate-in-2nd-half-of-2013-2013-05-20 … http://fb.me/18IOfXlWU     
    
    
    Evidence of an improving real estate market: homes sales have risen 9.7 percent the past 12 months - 24 months in... http://fb.me/1zGDMupPi     
    
    
    Historic homes in Longmont are rare.

http://www.businessinsider.com/american-homes-through-the-decades-2013-5 … http://fb.me/31J2N9FHO     
    
    
    Just answered: "Maple cabinets --- Dark or light cabinets" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/Maple_cabinets_Dark_or_light_cabinets-431859 …
#property #realestate #Colorado #Longmont #retire    
    
    
    That is one huge meal! http://fb.me/2IzlXxtDb     
    
    
    Good to hear. Thanks Lian! http://fb.me/1Pr7mmdnS     
    
    
    Good news just keeps rolling in!

Boulder was No. 2 for luxury home sales in April. According to a report in the... http://fb.me/26R1tjPJl     
    
    
    Just answered: "Moving to Longmont from East Coast" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Rentals/Moving_to_Longmont_from_East_Coast-527998 …
#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #invest #retire    
    
    
    I complimented Mimi’s page at @aboutdotme! Check it out http://about.me/mimideligiannidis … @MimiDeligiannid    
    
    
    I complimented Susan’s page at @aboutdotme! Check it out http://about.me/susantstewart  @stewsue    
    
    
    Just answered: "What areas considered "bad neighborhoods" in Longmont?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Rentals/What_areas_if_any_are_considered_bad_neighborho-464875 …
#realestate #property #homes #Colorado    
    
    
    Just answered: "Im looking for a duplex near downtown longmont ?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Rentals/Im_looking_for_a_duplex_near_downtown_longmont_-451278 …
#realestate #property #homes #Colorado #Longmont    
    
    
    #Boulder County real estate broker with a great line on what is happening in #Longmont, #Louisville ... http://www.trulia.com/profile/BoulderSuZ/ … #Colorado    
    
    
    The Boulder County Business Report notes there will be almost 3,000 apartment units going up this year. The surge... http://fb.me/27mb0iBSn     
    
    
    Just answered: "In terms of staging ... ?" http://t.co/MryF4Sg3ta

#realestate #Realtor #property #Colorado #Longmont #invest    
    
    
    Discover Longmont! Perfect weather to tour homes here in Boulder County. Call Suz: 720.810.0683 http://fb.me/1Gd3YSsRU     
    
    
    The problem for the housing market right now is a lack of supply - not a lack of demand - Wall Street Journal.... http://fb.me/2MfoifE5U     
    
    
    • Start small: Your first purchase may be a duplex or four-flat, something simpler so that you can get the hang... http://fb.me/23jx5c019     
    
    
    Listings are coming. Watch our page for leads, listings and links to great information on home ownership. Have a... http://fb.me/2DAkww6ga     
    
    
    Just answered: "Would it be foolhardy to do a fix and flip NOW?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Market_Conditions/Would_it_be_foolhardy_to_do_a_fix_and_flip_NOW_-266492 …
#realestate #property #Colorado #longmont #invest    
    
    
    Answered: "... the market has not turned crazy. Has it?" http://t.co/ecfvPR52hS

#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #invest    
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/news/3-money-moves-beat-back-124619449.html … http://fb.me/JiR1S4x9     
    
    
    We have a tiny yard because we elected to build a ranch home. There's plenty of space, though, for gardening. You... http://fb.me/GcWbhiSe     
    
    
    Here is the lowdown on inventory. The fact is the market has changed dramatically from two years ago.

The... http://fb.me/2p5N85xpV     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-credit-card-fees-never-120052747.html … http://fb.me/1OPUOGQrh     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/news/5-credit-card-fees-never-120052747.html … http://fb.me/26wUYixWx     
    
    
    Historic homes are a great legacy. http://fb.me/1rFIOV74Q     
    
    
    Very important. 

We know how tough it is. You walk into the sales office in the model home. It is gorgeous. But,... http://fb.me/24IiLTAV6     
    
    
    The recovery is here http://fb.me/22uPUKV3s     
    
    
    A few years ago, this was the provence of the daring. Some agents will tell you that plenty of house flippers kept... http://fb.me/NxG5wCIR     
    
    
    http://finance.yahoo.com/news/why-did-credit-score-drop-113035455.html … http://fb.me/NNMTMOW1     
    
    
    Great neighborhood and close to shopping ... Let's go tour it! Call Suz: 720.810.0683

http://bit.ly/12j1tGi  http://fb.me/28wq5iYMZ     
    
    
    "Does legacy high school and westlake middle serve this home?" http://t.co/ch33tNldpy

#realestate #property #Colorado #schools    
    
    
    Borrowers should keep in mind that some lenders will push hybrid ARMs because they stand to reap a higher return... http://fb.me/24QsY5c4i     
    
    
    Just answered: "do you take dogs?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Property_QandA/do_you_take_dogs_-384196 …
#Colorado #property #realestate #Boulder #Louisiville #Lafayette #Broomfield    
    
    
    Hardwood floors are not just a product, they are a legacy.... http://fb.me/2uGth2BBy     
    
    
    Just one day left before it goes on the market. I have the scoop on a 6-bedroom, 2-story home in the excellent... http://fb.me/1Ouy7nqSG     
    
    
    Home buyers crave ... http://styledstagedsold.blogs.realtor.org/2013/05/27/8-interior-home-features-that-buyers-most-crave/ …
#Colorado #property #realestate #Longmont #Boulder #Realtor #invest #retire #homes    
    
    
    Looking at home buy? Check it out. http://t.co/Oi7kX0vQY7

#realestate #Realtor #Colorado #property #invest #retire #Longmont #Boulder    
    
    
    DIY Home Inspector Checklist: 25 Places to Watch http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001325843/ …    
    
    
    Four unusual ways to pay down your mortgage - Yahoo! Homes http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001325847/ …    
    
    
    Unusual ways to pay down a mortgage 
http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001325847/ … Four unusual ways to pay down your mortgage - Yahoo! Homes

#Colorado #property    
    
    
    Look for it in the future. http://lnkd.in/FhEy_H     
    
    
    I'm posting this for my sister, nephew and friends who recently purchased homes in Los Angeles. Love to visit LA.... http://fb.me/2BSihfXeR     
    
    
    Here is another one for Californians ...... http://fb.me/1ypbONzgu     
    
    
    Everyone makes up their own rules, don't they. This photo is missing the cash jackpot that sits on the middle of... http://fb.me/JBt0t6LN     
    
    
    Shopping for a home in the high 300s in Longmont? How about Quail Crossing? Great neighborhood! Close to schools,... http://fb.me/19ZssZcJD     
    
    
    I love it! The phone never stops ringing. Longmont real estate is on fire! Same for the rest of Boulder County. If... http://fb.me/Tz4iNCda     
    
    
    Water, precious water. For a while there last winter, we wondered what summer was going to be like. Yay! http://fb.me/B28Lbn5Z     
    
    
    This all-white kitchen has my heart. Wouldn't this be divine in a beach house? I hear the waves. I s http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001328750/ …    
    
    
    Vail, Colorado at Christmas ... | See More Pictures | #SeeMorePictures http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001328767/ …    
    
    
    Suz is accepting listings. Call Suz at 720.810.0683 for a market analysis of your home.... http://fb.me/TRbpwF6l     
    
    
    It’s official: Housing has recovered | http://on.mktw.net/12QSyH3  |@MarketWatch
#colorado #property #realestate #invest #investor #longmont    
    
    
    The sad truth is your first offers are likely to be rejected.

With fewer homes for sale and more buyers coming... http://fb.me/1XFZbV2HF     
    
    
    Rejection doesn't have to be the rule. A Realtor can assist you with a strategy to buy your home. http://lnkd.in/9z-uFz     
    
    
    Crown molding, plantation shutters, solid doors, new trim, solar - now you're talking. 

Need some inexpensive... http://fb.me/QksQJ3RM     
    
    
    side swept http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001329334/ …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Use a credit card for anything except its intended purpose at your own risk. You may not have seen Tom Hanks in... http://fb.me/2cdqM2ich     
    
    
    Keep those scores up. Your credit score is will keep your car insurance payments down.... http://fb.me/1CHa2cIgf     
    
    
    Mudrooms deserve a better name, because they prevent a lot of work. Here are some mudrooms ...... http://fb.me/1WMBHZ2fY     
    
    
    Let the good times roll ... More Good News About Housing - Housing Data - Builder Magazine: http://soa.li/GNror3K     
    
    
        
    
    
    Just answered: "Are buyers allowed to walk through homes that are foreclosed?" http://t.co/3dVvXn0m2O

#Colorado #property #invest #retire    
    
    
    Just answered: "Nice House. But over 300...?" http://t.co/EEVJIzkqr6

#Colorado #invest #property #home #realestate #retire #AdamsCounty    
    
    
    Looking to sell real estate in Boulder County?
http://t.co/ZLD9xZrbSV

#Colorado #Longmont #Boulder #realestate #home #invest #property    
    
    
    Just answered: "seller wants no appraisal done but my bank requires an appraisal?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/seller_wants_no_appraisal_done_but_my_bank_require-121414 …
#home #property #Colorado    
    
    
    Just answered: "New construction cost per square foot" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/New_construction_cost_per_sqaure_foot-423398 …
#Colorado #realestate #Realtor #property #home #invest    
    
    
    White cabinets and a subway tile backsplash. Bonney Lake, WA - Richmond Homes http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001334473/ …    
    
    
    Dream kitchen ~ Neutrals, stainless steel and a pop of royal blue! Las Vegas, NV - Richmond Homes http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001334474/ …    
    
    
    20 Things Every Guest Room Needs via homesessive http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001334483/ …    
    
    
    Just answered: "Are home sales in #Longmont picking up for everyone?" http://t.co/uZY24pgKjg

#Colorado #realestate #home #property #invest    
    
    
    Just answered: "I see the value of this home is within the 400s. Can I ..." http://t.co/CeKmruOD59

#Colorado #property #home #invest    
    
    
    Real Estate Watch: New tactics for relisting a home

http://t.co/IvlN0bqgk3

#Colorado #property #home #realestate #Longmont #invest    
    
    
    Just back from a drive in the country. It was nice. Ray came with. We toured Firestone and saw some nice neighborhoods.    
    
    
    Delicate Arch in snow. This is a rare sight as snow doesnt usually stay long in this part of the wor http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001335523/ …    
    
    
    The 10 must-do-chores of getting ready to sell
-Suz Alvarez

Your home is stunning.

Friends and co-workers love... http://fb.me/2GbyyG85i     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/33ggAA  It does create some urgency. But we don't need anymore here in Boulder County, Colorado! We have a housing...    
    
    
    When it comes to economic recovery news, both Boulder County and Colorado are doing better in the short-term than... http://fb.me/1JqKFmpLQ     
    
    
    http://smallbusiness.yahoo.com/advisor/u-housing-market-continues-rebound-sees-strong-home-152355009.html … http://fb.me/2Cl6vGFxP     
    
    
    Ticking Time Bomb: Dryer Lint

Those renting older houses should read this. We rented when we came back from... http://fb.me/2ZasToGWd     
    
    
    Gift cards for carpooling:

To register for the drawing, visit http://surveymonkey.com/s/juneshiftreg . To send photos of... http://fb.me/1gGRZeMnV     
    
    
    What will $300,000 buy in Longmont? http://fb.me/MSorqwAg     
    
    
    Ticking Time Bomb: Electrical Wires Not Up to Code

Depending on the age of the home, the electrical system may... http://fb.me/1s9IwPODM     
    
    
    The National Association of Realtors says new contracts to buy homes are at the highest level in three years.

The... http://fb.me/Jf5nS9yO     
    
    
    Welcome Back, #346! WOW!!!! http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001345761/ …    
    
    
    A special place next to the Rocky Mountains http://fb.me/Aoreevdb     
    
    
    21 Impressive Photos of Amiable Nature That Will Left You Without Words http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346645/ …    
    
    
    Stunning photography.Our world is amazing http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346653/ …    
    
    
    Awesome http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346663/ …    
    
    
    Spooky Home http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346672/ …    
    
    
    Mock Orange.  Along with hyacinths and lilacs, mock orange provides one of spring's best fragrances. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346675/ …    
    
    
    Texas Designer Audrey Curl of Ornamentations Design. Chinoiserie pelmet features Scalamandre "Ping" http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346680/ …    
    
    
    Love it. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346689/ …    
    
    
    storm approaching | by Gian Paolo http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346711/ …    
    
    
    Composite describing Longmont, Colorado. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001346759/ …    
    
    
    Like a champagne life http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001347116/ …    
    
    
    Champagne http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001347117/ …    
    
    
    Forget what the marketers at Trulia and Zillow are saying. They would have you believe that Longmont prices have... http://fb.me/1MtoYIsLk     
    
    
    "I bought a property from REO sale, and have been chasing my HOA for over a year to fix damages." http://www.trulia.com/voices/Foreclosure/I_bought_a_property_from_REO_sale_and_have_been_c-523997 …
#Colorado    
    
    
    We're on the leading edge of what is happening in real estate these days. We have an occasional "pocket listing"... http://fb.me/UEm1dagw     
    
    
    "I plan to be in the market to buy a house in a few years" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Home_Buying/I_plan_to_be_in_the_market_to_buy_a_house_in_a_few-370590 …
#Colorado #Longmont #realestate #property #home #Realtor    
    
    
    http://bouldersuz.wordpress.com/2013/06/03/longmont-a-legacy/ … http://fb.me/2KpTLoTw7     
    
    
    Time to replenish the biz card stack. http://fb.me/MFrH5sUC     
    
    
    Slate really has a great look.... http://fb.me/2YbbGV8CU     
    
    
    Beach at the End of the World, New Zealand http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001352901/ …    
    
    
    . http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001352909/ …    
    
    
    http://www.coopext.colostate.edu/boulder/horticulture/nativeplantmaster.shtml … http://fb.me/1ZNBiB7FW     
    
    
    What will climbing mortgage rates do to the market? 

MarketWatch says the home buyer may push demand even... http://fb.me/2AvznjHT9     
    
    
    http://homes.yahoo.com/news/is-the-refi-party-over--230145308.html … http://fb.me/1BjT9wi0u     
    
    
    Caulk that tub and shower.

Dangerous mold and mildew growing behind the tub is a hard one to get under control... http://fb.me/28r9wihnm     
    
    
    Where do you find homes for a cool million? http://fb.me/1pqG8G3CL     
    
    
    "Realtors - What, if anything, can we do about this?" http://www.trulia.com/voices/Agent2Agent/Realtors_What_if_anything_can_we_do_about_this-531888 …
#realestate #Colorado #Longmont
#Realtor #property    
    
    
    What is an excavation cause?
Escalation Clause

When a buyer wants to outbid a competing offer, they can include... http://fb.me/2aB2U1ltw     
    
    
    Your dream home awaits you in BallenIsles! http://www.waterfront-properties.com/pbgballenisles.php … http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362802/ …    
    
    
    Dream home... photograph by Jose Villa http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362804/ …    
    
    
    HGTV Dream Home Guest Room http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362814/ …    
    
    
    Dream Home http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362818/ …    
    
    
    Dream home! http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362826/ …    
    
    
    Use the power of social media to market your home. Call Suz to talk about listing with PML: 720.810. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362881/ …    
    
    
    ✮ Mount Wilson - Near Dunton, Colorado http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362884/ …    
    
    
    Susan is accepting listings for Longmont, Louisville, Boulder, Niwot, Lafayette, Erie, Hygiene, and  http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362886/ …    
    
    
    Susan Alvarez specializes in residential real estate. She has been assisting home buyers for more th http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362887/ …    
    
    
    Check out my about.me page! http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362891/ …    
    
    
    Bror Johansson http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362951/ …    
    
    
    Saharan Sunset http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001362958/ …    
    
    
    Longmont has historic homes and newer luxurious homes. Call Suz: 720.810.0683 http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001363033/ …    
    
    
    That listing we said was coming in recent days ... gone. The 6-bedroom house in Quail Crossing went under... http://fb.me/2arY6QvKy     
    
    
    If you can stand the rarified air ... there is one of these very close to here.... http://fb.me/27e0dlhkh     
    
    
    A look at elegance http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001365052/ …    
    
    
    Green Blue Butterfly http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001365057/ …    
    
    
    The best May ever!

Real estate broker Gary Bauer described the Denver market in one word: "Wow!"

It was the... http://fb.me/1JchPOX60     
    
    
    Take advantage of the rates while they last. Contact a lender today.... http://fb.me/H0NXZwg9     
    
    
        
    
    
    Longmont has historic homes and newer luxurious homes. Call Suz: 720.810.0683 | or 720.810.1534 http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001365550/ …    
    
    
    Photo: Longmont enjoys one of the great legacies of a long-established community - a vibrant downtown with... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxmkv0G2     
    
    
    Longmont is a legacy - Suz Real Estate | PML

#Colorado #realestate #property #homes #Realtor #invest #retire http://twitter.com/BoulderSuZ/status/341672400108277760/photo/1pic.twitter.com/SSJw6isTCD     
    
    
    Buyers, check out this 3 bed, 3 bath in Firestone. Park on one side and open space on another. Walking trails,... http://fb.me/1WJ1kQMcw     
    
    
    Longmont is more than a community. There is legacy here. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001371891/ …    
    
    
    Longmont is more than a community. There is legacy here. http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001371899/ …    
    
    
    A Realtor for 10 years, I am a residential real estate professional who loves classic and contempora http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001372432/ …    
    
    
    Longmont has wonderful historic homes and gorgeous newer homes. Call Suz: 720.810.0683 | or 720.810. http://pinterest.com/pin/278519558178052273/ …    
    
    
    Charming house next to open space in Firestone, CO. 720.810.0683 http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001372721/ …    
    
    
    Check out this 3bed, 3bath in Firestone, CO. 720.810.0683 http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001372726/ …    
    
    
    #red #pink #retro #vintage http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001372747/ …    
    
    
    Photoset: Check out this charming 3 bed, 3 bath in Firestone. Comes with 3 garage spaces. The tandem space... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxmq1oJG     
    
    
    Great neighborhood! Let's go tour it! Suz: 720.810.0683... http://fb.me/2ou8IcW1h     
    
    
    Aerospace sounding good ... http://fb.me/2HEIvixA9     
    
    
    Beautiful Nature http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001375446/ …    
    
    
    Be careful when you decide to make some upgrades before you sell. Speaking from experience, you shouldn't just... http://fb.me/1NbM15iHr     
    
    
    A legacy waiting to be enjoyed - Longmont 

http://www.trulia.com/blog/bouldersuz/2013/06/longmont_where_a_tradition_of_legacy_resides …
#Colorado #property #realestate #homes #parks #Realtor    
    
    
    30 famous places that you MUST see http://pinterest.com/pin/199073246001379152/ …    
    
    
    Ticking Time Bomb: Faulty electrical wiring runs a very serious risk for homeowners. An electrician can usually... http://fb.me/2IbWG5RzL     
    
    
    http://www.safeelectricity.org/information-center/library-of-articles/44-efficiency-springsummer/279-taking-a-vaca …... http://fb.me/1sf3XGcqI     
    
    
    The sweets pot for the Denver market is a single family home priced between $200,000 and just under $300,000,... http://fb.me/2Dl1F6bDu     
    
    
    The sweet spot for the Denver market is a single family home priced between $200,000 and just under $300,000,... http://fb.me/C7OKfFi5     
    
    
    Could this mean we will be seeing more inventory?... http://fb.me/1LISq1pHi     
    
    
    They were the rage once. Not anymore. Getting rid of popcorn ceilings can increase the value of your home.

Home... http://fb.me/1HfHW7s5h     
    
    
    There might be some pocket listings skewing the data?... http://fb.me/2XaWU1BUQ     
    
    
    The Wall Street Journal today noted that there is room for mortgage rates to grow and keep homeownership the more... http://fb.me/zuQcFoez     
    
    
    Ticking Time Bomb: A leaking roof can collapse without warning, particularly during a fierce storm. Every year,... http://fb.me/2AYGqfV3B     
    
    
    POP QUIZ: Agents, what is the most important thing you will do before your sellers' open house?

A) Put out... http://fb.me/2nSpfFhmy     
    
    
    Longmont is a legacy - Suz Real Estate | PML

#Colorado #realestate #property #homes #Realtor #invest #retire http://twitter.com/BoulderSuZ/status/341672400108277760/photo/1pic.twitter.com/SSJw6isTCD     
    
    
    POP QUIZ? What are 3 questions you should ask when selecting a builder?    
    
    
    Can we be reading this right? The Northern Colorado Business Report carries an article today that says sales... http://fb.me/2h2fou4bj     
    
    
    Lovely ideas from San Francisco... http://fb.me/2ceeyJeYT     
    
    
    They could be drinking more rocket fuel over there on Wall Street today as home builder confidence rises again, a... http://fb.me/1bHRREkAS     
    
    
    Ticking time bomb: Your old furnace should be inspected by an HVAC tech every fall. Carbon monoxide detectors... http://fb.me/KwLZ63JK     
    
    
    http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-505145_162-57589416/housing-trend-builders-offer-home-within-a-home/?tag=nl.e713&s_cid= …... http://fb.me/MCsZTFas     
    
    
    A key measure of builder confidence crossed an important threshold on Monday. The National Association of Home... http://fb.me/2HAtqLeEt     
    
    
    More listings headed your way Boulder County, Colorado!

We'll let you know as soon as we have the green light.... http://fb.me/2EFGoZZcx     
    
    
        
    
    
    Check out the outdoor activities in the Boulder County, Colorado area.... http://fb.me/QNy99Myq     
    
    
    Credit Ben Klaus of Boulder Colorado Hiking. Great photo! http://fb.me/33Gtv0GnO     
    
    
    Thinking of adding value to your home? Add some garage space. When one of us worked for a Firestone builder, the... http://fb.me/VKzaIOZs     
    
    
    They're ba-a-ck! Tens of thousands of homeowners who lost their homes in the Great Recession can qualify for new... http://fb.me/QzHhPCmf     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Gorgeous times 4! http://fb.me/XlWpX884    
    
    
    The importance of staging can't be understated. In any market, you need your home staged so buyers can visualize... http://fb.me/BGQPheMh     
    
    
    Longmont is a legacy - Suz Real Estate | PML

#Colorado #realestate #property #homes #Realtor #invest #retire http://twitter.com/BoulderSuZ/status/341672400108277760/photo/1pic.twitter.com/SSJw6isTCD     
    
    
    Here is what the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency says about air duct cleaning:

"Duct cleaning has never been... http://fb.me/HrSlBHin     
    
    
    Ticking time bomb: Cracks that appear on a basement floor or on a wall are NOT necessarily foundation problems. If... http://fb.me/UthcWnPK     
    
    
    There is a cure for the summertime blues... http://fb.me/2uS7sUiB8     
    
    
    We're seeing this phenomenon over here, Desert Sands. Boy are we ever seeing it. http://fb.me/2qcoIDmuf     
    
    
    TIP: Replace the batteries in smoke detectors yearly. And remember, even hard-wired smoke detectors have batteries... http://fb.me/McQ8OZqT     
    
    
    Longmont listings coming to the market! Stay tuned.    
    
    
    TIP: Picking on Loose Knobs
When a wooden knob comes loose from a door or drawer because the screwhole is... http://fb.me/SZaVJejv     
    
    
    Son turns coconut shells into a handy percussion instrument (in case he ever gets a call from a studio to backup... http://fb.me/1eTIM3Rj8     
    
    
    Beautiful home of golf course. Let's go see it! Call Suz: 

720.810.0683... http://fb.me/2lrxH0zhf     
    
    
    Beautiful home on golf course: Let's go see it! Call Suz: 720.810.0683... http://fb.me/E6ddO3UU     
    
    
    Check out this 4 bedroom 1.75 bath Tri-level home. Home has hardwood and tile floors, wood burning stove in the... http://fb.me/2cJa9WhHt     
    
    
    Photo: Check out this tri-level in Longmont, Colorado! RV/boat parking and 30 minutes from Rocky Mountain... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxo87Qmb     
    
    
    Photo: There is a considerable list here. You’ll find parks, wilderness areas and more. Check it out. http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxo88wHo     
    
    
    Here is our new flyer on our terrific Lincoln Street property. This property is on the West side, so the morning... http://fb.me/Fal3ZGu1     
    
    
    Here is a re-worked ad for our golf course home. This home has custom paint for the lovely interior. We also have... http://fb.me/UP5c9ez1     
    
    
    Grabbed this one from my artist before he was ready to let go. But, we are go-go-go these days. Marvelous home... http://fb.me/2WWtz83cd     
    
    
    Photoset: Check this out. Patio looks out over the 12th tee box. Play a few holes and stop in for lunch a... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoA7Pc3     
    
    
    Photo: Established neighborhood with mature trees. This Longmont home has parking for RV/boat. A wood stove... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoA8FBc     
    
    
    Photo: Perfect for a commuting couple - especially if they are headed to Denver or Boulder. Just 33 minutes... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoA8waR     
    
    
        
    
    
    LOUISVILLE -- The second phase will have about 143 homes. It will include a mix of single-family homes, town... http://fb.me/1XOXHXxjc     
    
    
    Photo: usagov: Image description: Prehistoric granaries along the Colorado River above Nankoweap in Marble... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoEwTor     
    
    
    Denver so far has seen year-over-year price gains of 9 percent or more every month through April, according to... http://fb.me/2AzlQwA5t     
    
    
    Photo: SPLIT the distance: Ideal for a commuting couple - especially if one heads to Boulder and the other... http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoH1VLp     
    
    
    TIP: home inspections

Wobbly toilet? That’s a sign of potential leakage, which can lead to water damage. When... http://fb.me/2PNDvTwox     
    
    
    Photo: Established neighborhood has mature trees.  http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoHtpe2     
    
    
    Photo: Get in 12 holes and then stop for lunch at home. http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxoHu9Ea     
    
    
    TIP: Wood glue and putty knife - good tools for minor repairs to, say, veneer coming up at he edges due to... http://fb.me/1COs7HEVw     
    
    
    Question to ask prospective builder:

What is Your Status with the Better Business Bureau?

The Better Business... http://fb.me/2rFRBSCgq     
    
    
    Neighborhood has walking trails and plenty of open space. House is on a corner lot across from a park. http://fb.me/L8W8Zli1     
    
    
        
    
    
    "Home prices are going up 1 percent" - S. Robert August 

Home building activity surged 43 percent in the first... http://fb.me/37Y2uqECJ     
    
    
    Mortgage rates remain low by historical standards, though they spiked in the last week. 

The sudden jump in... http://fb.me/2zHa4XytS     
    
    
    Still some fixing to do ... http://lnkd.in/ehPdgq     
    
    
    Ugh! Now, I don't want to go to a garage sale.... http://fb.me/Dua3Itlr     
    
    
    Going viral looks like this. http://fb.me/2jDsEn6FD     
    
    
    There’s no generalized strategy for making an offer on a home anywhere, ever. http://fb.me/2AZ9dxFVD     
    
    
    Lifting Damaged Floor Tile
When a vinyl floor tile becomes stained or damaged, you can easily remove it with a... http://fb.me/PuQKLXtR     
    
    
    Retire at the 12th tee box! Check out this 4 bed, 3 bath in Longmont. Let's go see it! Suz: 720.810.0683. http://fb.me/2Ftl85d4H     
    
    
    Home prices jumped a whopping 12.6 percent year over year, the biggest increase since February 2006, says... http://fb.me/2xC5nNXIO     
    
    
    "This index reading is even stronger than we expected" - CU's Business Research Division... http://fb.me/1dM10uhDl     
    
    
    The Denver area market sellers are getting almost 100 percent of their listing price.... http://fb.me/NM9O6MHq     
    
    
    Boulder Foothills Retreat: open floor plan and an expansive patio. Award-winning landscape design as well as fine... http://fb.me/IUP0o1G7     
    
    
    Photo: How about this location at the 12th tee? http://tmblr.co/Z8h5uxojQwff     
    
    
    Erie is a feisty one. Check out the story in the Longmont Times-Call on Erie announcing it has had enough of the... http://fb.me/Hbgvy7sn     
    
    
    You've done everything right. You staged your home well, your agent engaged the right strategy and now you have a... http://fb.me/6mQPRybjA     
    
    
        
    
    
    Looking forward to the day when homes come standard completely off the grid. This is an oldie but goodie from the... http://fb.me/1uXkrZZEP     
    
    
    Long weekend is an opportunity for making some repairs.... http://fb.me/2d56duTWj     
    
    
    LESSONS from LA:
RealtorMag reports that the lack of inventory is so acute, agents are cold-calling home owners.... http://fb.me/2QXQYhYFC     
    
    
    Walk the art in Longmont ... http://www.artwalklongmont.org  http://fb.me/29sxCdVtZ     
    
    
    http://blog.sfgate.com/chronrx/2013/07/03/11-ways-to-lower-the-cancer-risk-while-grilling/#13744-1 … http://fb.me/GmSszblI     
    
    
    If you are contemplating a purchase of a central air conditioner, check with the Xcel website to see if you... http://fb.me/2ni9Gwi8P     
    
    
    The 5 myths of recovery

Trulia's Tara-Nicholle Nelson writes there are five myths that tend to interfere with... http://fb.me/FMs4wQcG     
    
    
    Keep an eye on rates, buyers.... http://fb.me/2eId1WUuS     
    
    
    LESSONS from LA: Naturally, the bubble talk is being generated where the prices are moving quickest - Los... http://fb.me/2bWNrWn4U     
    
    
    Spinnning Wheels?

More than a third of home listings that are labeled as “active” on third-party listing sites... http://fb.me/2v0n6NvBY     
    
    
    Always in the spotlight, Colorado is at the top of many lists. http://fb.me/AYtNAnM8     
    
    
    In Longmont, which was hit hard by foreclosures in the housing market and in high vacancy rates in commercial... http://fb.me/396uxek8i     
    
    
    How much more can real estate take? Mortgage rates have been moving so quickly, it must seem to the home buyer... http://fb.me/6oIpUmbcR     
    
    
    If you're using a debit card, you want to look at this.... http://fb.me/FxXOkLBK     
    
    
    Louisville is posting median and average gains of 23 percent and 18 percent. In Boulder County, the sales price... http://fb.me/1Pl7fsFGL     
    
    
    TIP for landlords
You have a tenant leaving, and shock of all shocks they took care of the place, but they also... http://fb.me/2HgoV8q4J     
    
    
    In 1976, a raging flood of water was sent down the Big Thompson Canyon https://www.facebook.com/Ascending.Art  #gallery #art #Colorado    
    
    
    TIP: Perfect paint job

Paint better be perfect, because it hides things like seams, patches and nail heads. The... http://fb.me/2fyrooc5n     
    
    
    NO BUBBLE

The real estate market is "not going to be what it was in 2005 or early 2006" because mortgage lending... http://fb.me/6mxRM4gOl     
    
    
    LESSONS from LA:

Bidding for homes has made Los Angeles the second best real estate market in the nation. Buyers... http://fb.me/1kZhIKwE4     
    
    
    WALL STREET'S Analysis:

Everyone wishes they had the kind of cash that they could have landed a deal like... http://fb.me/2wEbQKsIu     
    
    
    ... homebuyers will continue to face competition, even as more homes are expected to hit the market this summer.... http://fb.me/TFnRe5Pz     
    
    
    Colorado's drop in foreclosure was more than double the national average of 23.4 percent, RealtyTrac reports - or... http://fb.me/1i98k0bf0     
    
    
    To qualify, your monthly housing, car, student loan, and credit card debt can't be higher than 45 percent of your... http://fb.me/1r0mnX021     
    
    
    TIPs for Perfect Paint

Use a tinted primer before painting. Joint compound can suck the moisture out of paint and... http://fb.me/F6ScVd2r     
    
    
    Your eyes and an extra eye or more can help you avoid major expenses. Have issues addressed for the home you are... http://fb.me/F9gsc3gw     
    
    
    The American Dream is home ownership. Ownership percentages vary, but fewer than 60 percent of the population... http://fb.me/1TtQz11H6     
    
    
    A house that had sat on the market for two years got three offers after an option of seller financing was added

-... http://fb.me/NJNEk5LT     
    
    
    Recent data from the Mortgage Bankers Association shows that the number of applications for new mortgages rose 2... http://fb.me/2xYH91HoN     
    
    
    Was Business Insider looking for irony posting this photo with a story on a decline in housing starts? 

Just... http://fb.me/2r6kixeYs     
    
    
    GET this: 

Denver area real estate is marking new milestones. The Denver Business Journal reports that owners... http://fb.me/1mYT11Jpl     
    
    
    Commuting couple can split the difference. Let's go see this charming Firestone home. Call Suz 720.810.0683 http://fb.me/1HGFqVAX8     
    
    
    INSIDE Real Estate:

Northeast Region: Boulder, Larimer, Logan, Morgan, Weld counties:

This region of Colorado... http://fb.me/Z2Ckme3n     
    
    
        
    
    
    Everyone in favor of paying higher interest don't press like.... http://fb.me/22zM84afa     
    
    
    DID you know?

You can save water using the garbage disposal less often. Start a compost pile.

Look for... http://fb.me/B6Xy4taT     
    
    
    Cooler than the underside of a pillow? You betcha!... http://fb.me/2D7oDTX57     
    
    
    SMART: Consumers should look for the 'low-hanging fruit' and fix the small, affordable things in their house... http://fb.me/2fB0ZWpt1     
    
    
    Magnificent day out there. Great looking neighborhoods in Firestone and Longmont are waiting for buyers. If you... http://fb.me/19tY7SzNL     
    
    
    HOUSING showing no sign of slow down

Rising mortgage rates have done nothing to slow down momentum in home... http://fb.me/6otD9JAZS     
    
    
    RE-LISTING: A time of reflection 

Re-listing is a common strategy of agents, who remove a property for a few... http://fb.me/1up1o26qT     
    
    
    Q: How can I get a free copy of my credit report?
A: You can get one free credit report every 12 months from each... http://fb.me/2weQFNol2     
    
    
    DID YOU know?

One-third of vacation buyers in Colorado own two or more investment properties. So, who is buying... http://fb.me/QyuvAH1B     
    
    
    EYE ON REAL ESTATE

Mortgage rates dipped. They seem to be settling in around four and change. Even though rates... http://fb.me/RhShXIz7     
    
    
    RENTS are rising

Average rent rose in all counties of the Denver metro area, The Denver Post reports. Rents grew... http://fb.me/1odIwj9Gm     
    
    
    Looking for kitchen furniture?

http://www.houzz.com/photos/kitchen-islands--carts-and-pantry-furniture … http://fb.me/1I4nJ3PUU     
    
    
    CNNMoney:

Credit cards are the first to react to rising rates. Advice: Be aggressive about managing your credit... http://fb.me/2FWr09LZd     
    
    
    Ever wonder about those predictions in the business publications?

Forbes earns kudos for its forecast for the... http://fb.me/1PkWPBQQ2     
    
    
    Not complaining about the latest rate story. However, a move from 4.37 to 4.31 percent does not call for a... http://fb.me/2iiSWeruK     
    
    
    How high will mortgage rates rise in 2013? 

http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-505145_162-57595330/how-high-will-mortgage-rates-rise-in-2013/?tag=socsh …
#realestate #Colorado #Longmont #property #homes #invest #Realtor    
    
    
    SELLER's TIP:

There is a common belief the big window of opportunity traditionally begins closing in mid-July.... http://fb.me/6msVWTF82     
    
    
    Hey golfers! How about a home at the 12th tee? http://fb.me/Y4nbLNQZ     
    
    
    STAYING power |||

Alternatives to foreclosure:

FROM the NY Times: Variously called “deed for lease” or... http://fb.me/1XSA2eubw     
    
    
    Better late than ... http://homes.yahoo.com/news/should-you-refinance-012720378.html … http://fb.me/V5RxtnvO     
    
    
    LESSONS from L.A.:

Fast rising prices in Southern California are pulling more and more home flippers into the... http://fb.me/Zi9TmT28     
    
    
    PERMITS up in Colorado, nation

Inside Real Estate reports that new home building activity in the Denver... http://fb.me/2BsJ7nt74     
    
    
    CHA-CHING!

The Case-Shiller report on May shows it was even better than earlier reports indicated. In fact, home... http://fb.me/2LRgLUlpl     
    
    
        
    
    
    TIP: Adding value to your home

Here is a question that is asked often by homeowners on the Trulia Q&A. What is... http://fb.me/ZkdrXugl     
    
    
    Higher rates won't scuttle the housing recovery... http://fb.me/HfCWdP3I     
    
    
    These lists are produced from real-life anecdotes. A few years back, we were approaching closing for a woman who... http://fb.me/6qamtXRiU     
    
    
    Have you disengaged from your money?

Jonathan Burton at http://MarketWatch.com  says you do.

He writes:
A recent... http://fb.me/38OY05Ojf     
    
    
    Dreamy styles ...... http://fb.me/2KZaDk2Fn     
    
    
    Weak jobs number points to continuing low rates.

USA Today reported that the 162,000 jobs added in July is not... http://fb.me/HBDJgz1h     
    
    
    SCOUTING a home

It's never too early to start looking for a home. Ninety percent of buyers begin by looking... http://fb.me/6r53Kawrs     
    
    
    TRULIA busting out big numbers

Fast Money says the "page views and uniques (views) are through the roof!" The... http://fb.me/2YZsl3Ue8     
    
    
    "If you were going to re-brand Longmont, what things would you do?" 

http://www.trulia.com/voices/Quality_of_Life/If_you_were_going_to_re_brand_Longmont_what_thing-369889 …
#Longmont #property #Colorado #realestate    
    
    
    Road closure/restriction Sunday on Deerwood, County Rd 1 in 

#Longmont
#Colorado #realestate #property pic.twitter.com/OGVcqaZd3F    
    
    
    CREDIT: management tips for first-time users... http://fb.me/2wdoWaDJz     
    
    
    Good sign for new-build neighborhood?

Toys in the yard, which of course means a family has moved in. A garden... http://fb.me/2Ck6eMObF     
    
    
    Pay more than the minimum owed. Even better: pay off the balance each month.... http://fb.me/1H7VSfilV     
    
    
        
    
    
    "The recent increase in mortgage rates hasn't slowed demand, as long as home affordability remains high. We are,... http://fb.me/EBB1ZcvF     
    
    
    7 Great Credit Unions Anyone Can Join-Kiplinger http://po.st/18K8h7  via @po_st    
    
    
    Homeownership: Where Single Women Prevail 

http://nyti.ms/15hqHF7 
#realestate #property #Colorado #homes    
    
    
    Was your home a good investment? 
http://cnnmon.ie/13iXXLF  via @CNNMoney
#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #Boulder #homes #retire    
    
    
    Water damage can be insidious. Some might think the ice hanging from a gutter is nostalgic, but that ice may be... http://fb.me/2h2C5sNlI     
    
    
        
    
    
    LUXURY home sales

Citing figures from research firm DataQuick Inc., a Bloomberg report shows home sales from Los... http://fb.me/6r5KnOhph     
    
    
    Million Dollar Home Sales Jump in U.S. | http://finance.yahoo.com/news/million-dollar-home-sales-jump-040004041.html … via @YahooFinance
#realestate #property #Realtor #Colorado #Longmont    
    
    
    STOP an ant invasion

You sprayed and they came back. You caulked and they found a way back in. In a fit of... http://fb.me/2bThighq5     
    
    
    It's not too late.
http://homes.yahoo.com/news/refinance-at-four-percent-211702817.html … http://fb.me/2NHXoOBqI     
    
    
    The Boulder County Business Report shows that luxury home sales have grown in an already strong market. There... http://fb.me/2eyrkdn7o     
    
    
    Nothing mellow about yellow ...... http://fb.me/QlomMYTf     
    
    
    This is so true. Be smart about renovating a home. I know too many people who poured tons of money into their... http://fb.me/2Jxp2LchL     
    
    
    What has been the annual % increase or decrease in home prices FOR BOULDER since 2007?" 
http://bit.ly/13WMJLO 
#realestate    
    
    
    Another sign of a NORMAL market?

"Dramatic national year-over-year inventory declines have evaporated,"... http://fb.me/2ks1rvHj9     
    
    
    I Need to Rebuild My Credit, Where do I Start? 

http://blog.credit.com/2013/04/i-need-to-rebuild-my-credit-where-do-i-start/#.UguvC9kL2W8.twitter …
#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #retire    
    
    
    The good news keeps coming

Quoting Trulia, The Denver Post reports today that Denver is one of the top U.S.... http://fb.me/2xwCScd0N     
    
    
    Sellers, look for the SWEET SPOT

The follicly challenged guy on Mad Money - aka Jim Cramer - is doing our job... http://fb.me/2wTxkmukP     
    
    
    Curb appeal is what invites buyers into your home.... http://fb.me/2V3uRxHos     
    
    
    Kauffman Report: The Most Start-up 'Dense' Area in the U.S. | http://Inc.com  http://www.inc.com/eric-markowitz/startup-density-of-the-united-states.html …
#Boulder #Colorado    
    
    
    HAPPENINGS in LA:

In California, the owner of a neighboring property may live in China, probably paid all cash... http://fb.me/1U0ypfMQh     
    
    
        
    
    
    Great improvement. 

http://www.cbsnews.com/8301-505145_162-57598824/builders-broke-ground-on-more-homes-in-july/ … http://fb.me/2hsIc1vuS     
    
    
    Good advice - but be prepared to get in line. A followup story might "guestimate" how likely you are to find a... http://fb.me/2glols4Nv     
    
    
    http://money.cnn.com/2013/08/19/pf/credit-score-killers/index.html?hpt=hp_t2 … http://fb.me/Ijrj4D66     
    
    
    Zillow Home Value Index Rises to Near 7-Year High 

http://www.dsnews.com/s/p7g-sv  #dsnews
#realestate #property #Colorado #Longmont #retire    
    
    
    Your Money: Home equity loans make a comeback 

http://usat.ly/1c1L89g  via @USATODAY
#realestate #property #Longmont #Colorado    
    
    
    Unclaimed lottery ticket worth $1 million is set to expire this Sunday http://www.cnn.com/2013/08/23/us/unclaimed-lottery-ticket/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter …    
    
    
    Home prices across the US defy gravity - Yahoo! Finance 

http://finance.yahoo.com/news/home-prices-across-us-defy-100000765.html …
#property #realestate #Colorado #retirement    
    
    
    51st state initiative: Erie would be half in, half out of new state - Boulder Daily Camera 

http://www.dailycamera.com/erie-news/ci_23933773/51st-state-initiative-erie-half-half-out …
#Colorado #Longmont    
    
    
    Home prices across the US defy gravity - Yahoo! Finance http://finance.yahoo.com/news/home-prices-across-us-defy-100000765.html …
#realestate #property #Realtor #Colorado #retirement    
    
    
    As investors shift, housing is the new stock market 

http://fw.to/e1F1RDJ 
#realestate #property #Longmont #Colorado    
    
    
    Case-Shiller: Denver home prices at record levels 

http://insiderealestatenews.com/2013/08/27/case-shiller-denver-home-prices-at-record-level/ …
#realestate #property #retirement #invest #housing #Colorado    
    
    
    Housing Growth Is Good - Housing Data, Housing Trends - Builder Magazine 

http://fw.to/qrNHESj 
#Longmont #Colorado #realestate #property    
    
    
    Nearly half of all homes are purchased in cash 

http://on.mktw.net/1dSG2hz 
#realestate #property #retirement #housing #Colorado #invest    
    
    
    OPEN House at 739 Glenarbor Circle n #Longmont #Colorado Today from 1 to 3! 

#realestate #property #golf #housing #homes    
    
    
    OPEN house | Steady traffic ... Going to be here at 739 Glenarm Circle til 3. Come on by! 720.810.0683
#realestate #Longmont #Colorado #golf    
    
    
    Is part-time work the new normal? http://www.usatoday.com/story/money/business/2013/09/02/part-time-workers/2754095/ … via @USATODAY    
    
    
    Autodesk Gives Look At The High-Speed #Hyperloop
http://www.buzzfeed.com/autodesk/a-new-look-at-the-high-speed-hyperloop-b3y4 … via @autodesk
#et3 #transportation #Colorado #Longmont    
    
    
    5 bargain bathroom renovations that pay off
http://homes.yahoo.com/news/bathroom-renovations-that-payoff-000246083.html … via @YahooHomes
#realestate #property #Colorado #retirement #invest    
    
    
    Luxury-home sales in metro Denver still strong

http://bit.ly/1fCBpWY 
#property #homes #Colorado #realestate #retirement #golf #investment    
    
    
    Study Finds 8.3 Million Homeowners Near Positive Equity

http://bit.ly/18FpHHc 
#Colorado #realestate #property #homes #Longmont    
    
    
    America’s Next Decade - Forbes

http://onforb.es/1dE30uh 
#realestate #property #Colorado #retirement #investment #Realtor #housing #homes    
    
    
    Future U.S. growth by region ... heat-mapped

http://bit.ly/14ZriKu 
#realestate #property #Colorado #homes #Realtor #Longmont #retirement    
    
    
    5 cities on the housing rebound: where to buy 

http://homes.yahoo.com/photos/five-cities-on-the-housing-rebound-where-to-buy-and-one-place-not-to-slideshow/ … via @YahooHomes
#property #realestate #Realtor #Colorado #retirement    
    
    
    5 Helpful Tips to Ensure Your Attic is Ready for Winter http://www.localhelpfinder.com/5-helpful-tips-to-ensure-your-attic-is-ready-for-winter/ …
#realestate #property #homes #Colorado #retirement    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Rain is coming down in County Road 1 and Ninth Ave. area.  

#longmontflood    
    
    
    Home builders most confident in almost eight years - Economic Report 

http://on.mktw.net/19aqVvN  via @MarketWatch
#realestate #property    
    
    
        
    
    
    Man run over, killed by dump truck while repairing Colorado flood site - The Denver Post 

http://www.denverpost.com/breakingnews/ci_24175522/man-runover-killed-by-dump-truck-while-repairing … via @denverpost
#coflood    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Scientists: Colorado flooding was 'un-precedented'

http://usat.ly/1fnSDMS  via @usatoday
#coflood #Colorado #Longmontflood    
    
    
        
    
    
    7 fun housewarming gifts
http://cahomefinancing.com/around-the-home/7-fun-and-easy-housewarming-gifts-for-a-new-homeowner-2/ …
#realestate #Realtor #Colorado    
    
    
    How HARP Can Put Money in Your Pocket 

http://homes.yahoo.com/news/harp-put-money-pocket-184210020.html?soc_src=mediacontentstory … via @YahooHomes
#property #retire    
    
    
    