Healthy living is a mindset - get in the habit of being kind to yourself and it will be addictive!    
    
    
    TLS Weight Loss Solutions - http://eepurl.com/gJzYj     
    
    
    These are supplements that deserve attention http://lnkd.in/6eTuiY     
    
    
    The Three Products You Aren’t Taking http://lnkd.in/6eTuiY     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/YeqMBM  Awesome tip Kathy! So true!     http://www.coachirenegreiner.blogspot.com     
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/iUSubp  Here is a testimony from one of my TLS clients:   I have lost 155 pounds and I have people ask me all of the time...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/TAEMZv  That's great Tracy! I am getting ready to begin classes at a large fitness facility but have mainly been doing...    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/atwwgU  The reason I have incorporated TLS Weight loss solutions into my coaching practice is because I believe the only...    
    
    
    Check this video out -- Fat Factors http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yF9OViKEBrs&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    Check this video out -- eGift - "The Gift of Choice" http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Z_pDxbmk5Xs&feature=share … via @youtube    
    
    
    OPC-3 on USA TV Channel WETM18: http://youtu.be/agZCU-GjZJ4  via @youtube    
    
    
    coaching people towards a healthy lifestyle- what an awesome day!    
    
    
    Currently reading TLS Shape Up: A Mother’s Story | at: http://blog.marketamerica.com/blog/tls-shape-up-mothers-stor/?utm_source=feedburner    
    
    
        
    
    
    Hoping to land a position at Bloomington Hospital as a health educator    
    
    
    Transitions Lifestyle System now on Twitter | http://bit.ly/cUUn5c    
    
    
    Do you know the more cardio exercise you do the more you boost your brain power?    
    
    
    Isotonix Resveratrol - Single Bottle (30 Servings): http://bit.ly/9g1mwD via @addthis - A great product with red wine extract    
    
    
    Networking - http://eepurl.com/UUVI    
    
    
    Introducing the New Motives for La La Fall/Winter 2012 Runway Collection http://shar.es/vFb5A  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Check out this site: Irene Greiner, weight loss coach -- http://bit.ly/a5OeC5    
    
    
    Awesome Transitions class tonight! Can't wait to see the lifestyle changes they make!    
    
    
    @jo_smo  I like your saying on spending money to gain wealth & spend wealth to regain health. So very true!!!    
    
    
    @rick_malambri    Pressing On! LLC. You gotta keep pressing on and believe nothing is impossible with God!    
    
    
    http://lnkd.in/_9kVzH  I think one of the most important things besides the quality of the products is the compensation plan. The company...    
    
    
    Irene Greiner, weight loss coach http://coachirenegreiner.blogspot.com/?spref=tw  via @blogger    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Market America - Built on Product. Powered by People http://www.marketamerica.com/pressingon/index.cfm?action=shopping.wpGoShopProducts&skuID=13071&refEmail=0A1F112E0B1C2D0501280215021402274B170802&sms_ss=twitter … via @AddThis
Don't let the flu get you this year!    
    
    
    Checking out "Holiday Shopping on the Internet" on Christian Business Networking As: http://ning.it/Pt4S94     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Mochatonix - Health & Nutrition From Market America http://www.marketamerica.com/pressingon/index.cfm?action=shopping.wpGoShopProducts&skuID=7801&refEmail=0A1F112E0B1C2D0501280215021402274B170802&sms_ss=twitter … via @AddThis
This is awesome for when you have an afternoon slump!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Fixx Instant Line Vanish | Motives Cosmetics http://motivescosmetics.marketamerica.com/pressingon/index.cfm?action=shopping.csProductDetail&groupID=51_CS_USA&cat2ID=USA22724&cat3ID=USA32966&skuID=12522&refEmail=#.UIGCTykl8Rw.twitter …    
    
    
    Did another 5k and beat my time again! Ready for the next one!    
    
    
    @goldmedalmel  Wow! To win a gold medal - would be awesome!    
    
    
    What's your plan B? Don't give up on your dreams!    
    
    
    Networking - http://eepurl.com/bg_3f    
    
    
    Vitamin D3 Might Ease Menstrual Cramps http://www.everydayhealth.com/pain-management/0228/vitamin-d3-might-ease-menstrual-cramps.aspx?xid=tw_weightloss_sf …    
    
    
    Earn cashback on Cyber Monday Deals: http://www.shop.com/pressingon  - over 3,000 stores!    
    
    
    The Best of the Little Black Dress: Holiday 2012 Edition http://www.myfashioncents.com/2012/trends/the-best-of-the-little-black-dress-holiday-2012-edition/ …    
    
    
    Pycnogenol® reduces tinnitus symptoms. | http://blog.marketamerica.com/blog/pycnogenol%c2%ae-reduces-tinnitus-symptoms/ … via @MarketAmerica    
    
    
    Stop Living and Start Designing Your Life http://www.huffingtonpost.com/loren-ridinger/life-goals_b_2268911.html …    
    
    
    Do you know it takes at least 3 months to form a habit? This new year I challenge you to form at least 3 healthy habits:
-Eat healthier
-    
    
    
    Reading @jrridinger Why is my Paycheck Lower in 2013? http://tinyurl.com/axeo5ka     
    
    
    @xoShakia These actually work! Isotonix-rapidly absorb & taste great! Check out: http://www.shop.com/pressingon     
    
    
    @Ms_dawnn I love Mochatonix - vitamins & herbal caffeine. Give u way more energy!
http://www.shop.com/pressingon     
    
    
    @AnisTabet23 definitely try Isotonix - rapidly absorb, taste & work great! http://Shop.com/pressingon     
    
    
    @yanmorg Not just any work! I love Isotonix bc they work & taste great!
http://Shop.com/pressingon     
    
    
    Networking - http://eepurl.com/coyLL    
    
    
    Hurray! I have one of the top 10% most viewed @LinkedIn profiles for 2012. http://www.linkedin.com/pub/profile/11/400/224?trk=200tw …    
    
    
    Excited to be a part of this growing company! Tune in to learn how you can be a part! http://lnkd.in/FKznrd     
    
    
    Need more energy? Try a healthy green smoothie w/fruit & vanilla Mochatonix- yum!    
    
    
    Check out this message from theChapel - "Lie to Me" :  via @TheChurchApp    
    
    
    Motives Product Demo - want a red carpet line of cosmetics for your business? http://Www.motivescosmetics.marketamerica.com/pressingon  http://youtu.be/jfy2u-tESvI     
    
    
    nutraMetrix provides customized wellness solutions for licensed health professionals, adding revenue for the providers while integrating sc…    
    
    
    I'm looking for a personal trainer or fitness studio to team up with in the Tampa Bay area. Please contact me if you are interested.    
    
    
    Motives Product Demo - looking for a red carpet line of cosmetics? http://Www.motivescosmetics.marketamerica.com/pressingon  http://youtu.be/jfy2u-tESvI     
    
    
    I love this because when in a hurry, it's all I need! Motives® Blush Bronzer Duo http://shar.es/edzbi  via @sharethis    
    
    
    3 DIY Coconut Oil Beauty Recipes via @lorenridinger http://www.myfashioncents.com/2013/beauty-finds/3-diy-coconut-oil-beauty-recipes/ …    
    
    
    Reading @jrridinger Don’t Miss these Incredible nutraMetrix Webinars!  http://tinyurl.com/bev9nfw     
    
    
    Looking for pharmaceutical sales reps interested in making residual income with pharmaceutical grade supplements    
    
    
    Don't think I'll be running outside today-crazy weather!    
    
    
    @PrayInFaith Awesome word! This is definitely for me!    
    
    
    Trying to decide if I want surgery or not. Would line to here from others http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/m/pubmed/12130414/?i=3&from=/10959927/related …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Great info on OPC3!
http://MeetON.com  http://www.meeton.com/live-meet/product-spotlight-isotonix-opc-3_922/#.Uc8mGXJhgAs.twitter …    
    
    
        
    
    
    I've just updated my @yola site: http://pressingon4health.com  Get one yourself http://www.yola.com     
    
    
    I've just updated my @yola site: http://pressingon4health.com  Get one yourself http://www.yola.com     
    
    
        
    
    
    •Bring your body to an optimal weight •Increase your energy •Sharpen your mental focus •Stabiliz http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758080940/ …    
    
    
    Muscle increases metabolism http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758080972/ …    
    
    
    Black Bean and Couscous Salad http://Allrecipes.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758081007/ …    
    
    
    Got Stress? https://www.facebook.com/lifestyletransformation …    
    
    
    I will be a breakout speaker at this conference on Oct. 25th 
https://lifechangingconference.com/orlando--fl.html …    
    
    
    Talk to the Wall – part 2 http://shar.es/ieRgJ  via @sharethis    
    
    
    Event: Transition To A Healthier You! http://www.calendarwiz.com/calendars/popup.php?op=view&id=67873993&crd=thesocialitesnetwork& …    
    
    
    http://SHOP.COM  - TLS Whey Protein Shakes  These are great when you are traveling! http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758198553/ …    
    
    
    Fred Howard Beach - especially beautiful at sunset! http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758199107/ …    
    
    
    Sunset Beach - another place we can go down the street and watch the sunset! http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758199131/ …    
    
    
    Healthy Pumpkin Zucchini Muffins http://Allrecipes.com  http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758199150/ …    
    
    
    http://myemail.constantcontact.com/The-Socialites-Newsletter-October-2013-.html?soid=1114623256265&aid=rCFpqp-TzOg …    
    
    
    Check out my Find Your Fit Event for 2014, Start Now! http://www.pressingon4health.com  and go to Scheduled Presentations http://lnkd.in/bUXcxyq     
    
    
    I've just updated my professional profile on LinkedIn. Connect with me and view my profile. http://lnkd.in/bDGxKMu  #in    
    
    
    http://www.winsymposium.org/useful-links/   I am a vendor - hope to see you there!    
    
    
    Dont' let stress ruin your holiday! http://SHOP.COM  - TLS(r) ACTS Adrenal, Cortisol, Thyroid & Stress Suppo http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758554174/ …    
    
    
    Market America's Isotonix products offer the fastest and most efficient delivery system of all nutra http://pinterest.com/pin/470907704758554186/ …    
    
    
    Rethink Wellness Health & Wellness Coaching:  Join The https://perksconnect.com/en/Members/Pages/FacebookVendorLanding.aspx?vendorid=31000193 …    
    
    
        
    
    
    Rethink Wellness Health & Wellness Coaching:  Join The https://perksconnect.com/en/Members/Pages/FacebookVendorLanding.aspx?vendorid=31000193 …    
    
    
    https://perksconnect.com/en/Members/Pages/FacebookVendorLanding.aspx?vendorid=31000193 …    
    
    
    Like me on facebook: www.facebook.com/lifestyletransformation    
    
    
    Thx! Glad to be a part of bright apple! Looking forward to getting some networking meetings together    
    
    
    Awesome day running, biking & tanning on the beach!    
    
    
    To transform the body, you must first transform the mind
www.facebook.com/lifestyetransformation    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I'm attending Fallen Officers Memorial 5k Run & Walk -- http://www.eventbrite.com/s/37wH    
    
    
    Come with me to this Meetup for Indianapolis Marketing Group! http://meetu.ps/Wy9d    
    
    
    Yeah! Second 5k I came in first in my age category! Not bad if I say so myself!    
    
    
    @donnkoonce  Great article!    
    
    
    I joined The Indianapolis Coffee Meetup Group on Meetup. You should too! http://meetu.ps/5vy5    
    
    
    "Stressed" is "desserts" spelled backwards! Don't let weight gain make you stressed -support is within reach!    
    
    
    pressingon - Market America :: Built on Product. Powered by People.: http://bit.ly/lmWllc  via @AddThis    
    
    
    So far three grocery store tours for my Transitions class! I hope now they will read labels - so much junk in our food!    
    
    
    Did not get it? Irene    
    
    
    @EaglePointeJake Don't you hate that!    
    
    
    @vasc0correia  Perfect love casts out fear    
    
    
    Coconut oil is great for weight-loss!    
    
    
    pressingon - Market America :: Built on Product. Powered by People.: http://bit.ly/mWURZq  via @AddThis    
    
    
    