@piersmorgan Ask Morgan about his show, "through the wormhole."  What made him produce a science show?  Thank you!    
    
    
    @piersmorgan Ask Morgan Freeman about his great show, "Through The Wormhole" and what drove his interest in science.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Alabama MADD founder Dee Fine says she's rested, ready for everyone to hang up and drive | al.com http://blog.al.com/aharvey/2010/06/alabama_madd_founder_dee_fine.html …    
    
    
    Rates | 942 Old Church Road http://942oldchurchroad.com/rates     
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Pet product company recalls nearly 75,000 bags of dog treats - http://bit.ly/dooR6m #cnn -- why don't news agencies show photo of package?    
    
    
    FDIC insured monies not back by US Gov't-Forbes: http://blogs.forbes.com/danielfisher/2010/09/13/an-old-case-haunts-the-fdics-bank-closers/    
    
    
    Join me on @HuffingtonPost Social News http://huff.to/bZRJIU    
    
    
    @nprnews I don't see how young voters can be better off than their parents when collage grads are having such a difficult time finding jobs!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @digg_enviro: Cpapavizas@winston.com, law brief says The Cleanwater Act will impact ALL Maritime Commerce.  Can shippers afford insurance?    
    
    
    @Oil_Spill_2010; cpapavizas@Winston.com law brief says ALL Maritime Shippers Will Be Impacted by Cleanwater Act - Insurance Costs Soar!    
    
    
        
    
    
    @ariannahuff Wish I had been there, looks like fun.  Pamela Kostmayer Whitney    
    
    
    @washingtonpost If more reporters would cover this type of news, maybe, just maybe the recession would FEEL like it was over.    
    
    
    Legal News To Use - blog for reporters and advocates interested in legal & advocacy DC breaking news, pamelawhitney.wordpress.com. Visit Us    
    
    
    Share Bookmarklet | dev.twitter.com http://dev.twitter.com/pages/share_bookmarklet …    
    
    
    PhillyBurbs.com:  Smile, you're on Bristol camera http://www.phillyburbs.com/news/local/courier_times/courier_times_news_details/article/28/2010/september/21/smile-youre-on-bristol-camera.html … via @phillyBurbs. That's sad. I loved campaigning there! Pam Kostmayer    
    
    
    @washtimes Thanks for following us.  Our legal and advocacy news releases won't disappoint you!  It's News You Can Use.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @vfthompson You've gotta have Murray's Nantucket reds & Rope Walk's lobster rolls.  Ask  Chris Matthews.  He loves Nantucket, too.    
    
    
    LegalNewsToUse, Up-To-Date Press Releases for Supreme Court, Legal and Advocacy Reporters: http://www.pamelawhitney.wordpress.com
Subcribe!    
    
    
    Just finished reading "Three Cups of Tea."  Must be required reading for all middle schoolers so they'll appreciate US education.    
    
    
    @amFIX Start by requiring students to read "Three Cups of Tea" about Afghanistan parents total sacrifice to educate children.    
    
    
    @nytimes Now that's a marriage of two great, service oriented companies, and a home run for consumers.    
    
    
    @thedailybeast What a tragedy.  I see his product used by security in large malls frequently.  He was a great innovator.    
    
    
    @WholeDogJournal  I think your journal is the best! Re: Training, never ever yell at your dog or puppy, unless there's immediate danger.    
    
    
    @NewsHour You guys deserve it!  For indepth news, no one holds a candle to your reporting.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @washingtonpost David Simon received two honors: 1  for The Wire Genius Grant 2. B/c MacArthur Foundation is stellar.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Maritime Legis Goes Way Beyond DEEPWATER HORIZON http://www.winston.com/index.cfmcontentID=24&itemID=10339&itemType=3    
    
    
    In Massachusetts, Brockton High Becomes Success Story - http://nyti.ms/bKGHqo --smaller schools and classrooms higher test scores.    
    
    
    http://www.law.com/jsp/lawtechnologynews/PubArticleLTN.jsp?id=1202472588424  Social Media Causing Labor Disbutes - NLJ    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @GoDaddy  Why are you "not accepting any more calls at this time?"  My other email is down and you are not answering???    
    
    
        
    
    
    Change or Perish - http://nyti.ms/dwE73r FAB-U-LOUS! LOVE, LOVE, LOVE this!  Don't be too busy to read this.  It's worth it.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wind Power Backbone Sought Off Atlantic Coast - http://nyti.ms/dictmF Maritime/Jones Act Expert: cpapavizas@winston.com. How this will work.    
    
    
    Congrats Google & Partner on $5B Support of Wind Farms!  Energy Reporters need Maritime Expert?  Charlie Papavizas cpapavizas@winston.com    
    
    
    @Legal_Times - GREAT JOB! Consider following LegalNewsToUse in DC.  Thanks, Pamela Whitney    
    
    
        
    
    
    Wind Power Backbone Sought Off Atlantic Coast - http://nyti.ms/dictmF Maritime Expert on impact of Jones Act cpcpavizas@winston.com  PRESS    
    
    
        
    
    
    Investors & Wind Charlie Papavizas, Winston maritime expert http://www.lloydslist.com/ll/sector/ship-operations/article348020    
    
    
    Shareholders in former PSFS win court ruling http://articles.philly.com/2011-01-29/business/27089815_1_psfs-appeal-court-ruling … via @ArchiveDigger    
    
    
    Congress' 112th Energy Bill Outlook. Winston & Strawn's  Larry Kiern article  http://www.winston.com/index.cfm?contentid=34&itemid=4130    
    
    
    Until Congress quickly passes legislation to at least match the permitting time for renewables like offshore wind, to …http://lnkd.in/ibryKP    
    
    
    Great article!  And a future look at where news may be headed. http://lnkd.in/ujPnJ2    
    
    
    Must be posturing.  We bail out Wall Street but kick the American taxpayer when their down for the count? http://lnkd.in/tDB4Qw    
    
    
    Today's SCOTUS Mid-Term UPDATE FREE WEBCAST from Wash Legal Center w/ Winston & Strawn's Gene Schaerr, http://bit.ly/hKM5Oi    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Winston & Strawn hosts 2/24 webinar on avoiding and defeating consumer class actions - http://bit.ly/hH10zB    
    
    
    Gene Schaerr at Winston & Strawn Today Reacted to the U.S. Supreme Court's 8-1 Vote on Protesting at Military Fun… http://wp.me/pUdvX-3d    
    
    
    Offshore Wind Farms Miss US Boat http://wp.me/pUdvX-t    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    likes  Winston & Strawn Bolsters Advertising, M... http://pop.to/1amj    
    
    
    Winston & Strawn Bolsters Advertising, Marketing and Regulatory Investigations Practice With Addition of Anthony … http://wp.me/pUdvX-3o    
    
    
        
    
    
    Via @nprnews: High Court Rules For Anti-Gay Protesters At Funerals | http://n.pr/eYGB77   Gene Schaerr Winston & Strawn    
    
    
    Washington reacts to the death of David Broder - http://voices.washingtonpost.com/44/2011/03/washington-reacts-to-the-death.html    
    
    
    Federal Prosecutors Pierce Corporate Attorney-Client Privilege http://wp.me/pUdvX-3q    
    
    
    I just joined Digg! You should follow me at http://digg.com/legalnewstouse    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    