Devising a 3 hour workshop entitled 'Managerial skills for enhancing well-being and creativity'. What to include, in your opinion?    
    
    
    Profoundly touched by the love & support of my family & friends. Amazing the extent to which we connect & inspire each other to our dreams.    
    
    
    Regardez REIKI SHARE THURSDAYS! Sur Meetup - http://meetup.com/u/SJ    
    
    
    Finally surmounted another hurdle of writer's block...the clusters swarming in my mind are finally pouring out onto paper. Moving forward!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    If depressed, you're living in the past. If anxious, you're living in the future. If at peace, you're living in the present. - Lao Tzu    
    
    
    Happiness is the meaning and the purpose of life, the whole aim and end of human existence. ~ Aristotle 384 BC-322 BC    
    
    
    growing younger by the day, thanks to hot yoga!    
    
    
    delighted to return to lively Paris after sinking into the heaviness of Auschwitz Birkenau in remembrance...    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Once a rising star, chef now feeds the hungry - http://bit.ly/bO4VeJ #cnn    
    
    
    Everybody is a genius. But if u judge a fish by its ability to climb a tree it will live its whole life believing that it is stupid~Einstein    
    
    
    Avancement de thèse presentation tomorrow, explaining the organizational benefits of meditative states. Please send me nice flowing energy!    
    
    
    ‎"Have the courage to follow your heart and intuition. They somehow already know what you truly want to become."  ~ Steve Jobs  RIP    
    
    
    wow, thanks for all of your support! warms my heart! presentation went well, afterwards many questions about the plan of methodology. happy!    
    
    
    “Be who you are and say what you feel, because those who mind don't matter, and those who matter don't mind.” 
― Dr. Seuss    
    
    
    Go placidly amid the noise and haste, and remember what peace there may be in silence...http://www.travelingintuit.com/quotes    
    
    
    How to tune in to communicate with spirit? http://www.travelingintuit.com/tuning-into-spirit    
    
    
    Afro jazz music to stir the soul... http://www.cdbaby.com/cd/CesarBolly    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    A ship in the harbor is safe, but that's not what ships are built for. -G.M. Bright http://www.airbnb.com/tell-a-friend?airef=vhhkz12271zz4 …    
    
    
    Cultivating inner stillness and expansive peace brings resilience to transcend with joy what otherwise might make us boil to anger. ~ MEH    
    
    
    The intuitive mind is a sacred gift & the rational mind is a faithful servant.
- Albert Einstein        www.facebook.com/MarieHolm    
    
    
    Offering intuitive healing and mediumship readings at Generation TAO in Paris for the month of June! www.TravelingIntuit.com    
    
    
        
    
    
    Freedom, Inc.: Free Your Employees and Let Them Lead Your Business to Higher Productivity, Profits, and Growth   http://tinyurl.com/28drvjw    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Music to soothe the soul - have a listen to a new AfroJazz tune: http://bit.ly/aBvkVH & write what you think about it!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Don't ask what the world needs. Ask what makes you come alive and go do it. What the world needs are people who have come alive ~ H.Thurman    
    
    
    We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, therefore, is not an act, but a habit. ~ Aristotle    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    There is more to yoga than making an asana of oneself ;). Namaste, yaar!    
    
    
    Worthwhile watching, regarding left vs. right brain functions and integration : http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=dFs9WO2B8uI# …!    
    
    
    'Beauty is not in the face - Beauty is a Light in the Heart.' Kahlil Gibran    
    
    
    Had the distinguished pleasure of meeting & hearing 2 prodigious 95 year-old gentlemen recently, John G. Morris & Stéphane Hessel. Legends!    
    
    
        
    
    
    I count him/her braver who overcomes his desires than him who conquers his enemies; for the hardest victory is over self. -Aristotle    
    
    
        
    
    
    started building a site at www.TravelingIntuit.com and a blog at TravelingIntuit.blogspot.com. Comments and suggestions much appreciated!    
    
    
    Another published article I wrote that was featured, 'Unleashing Untapped Potential' on Positive Mindsets, pages 27-28: http://www.scribd.com/doc/89002190/The-Brahmaputra-Volume-3 …    
    
    
    "Yoga is a way to freedom. By its constant practice, we can free ourselves from fear, anguish and loneliness." Indra Devi    
    
    
    Upon awakening let the words Thank You flow from your lips, for this will remind you to begin your day with gratitude & compassion. Dr. Dyer    
    
    
    Liberating leadership talk by Professor Isaac Getz, animating themes from the book Freedom Inc: http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_embedded&v=sVBddXmynSc# …!    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Voici mon secret. Il est très simple: on ne voit bien qu'avec le cœur. L'essentiel est invisible pour les yeux.   ~ Antoine de Saint Exupéry    
    
    
    Shana Tov, and Eid Mubarak! Un mélange, je sais ;)    
    
    
    Seeking an organization for my research study, applying meditative practices to increase creativity & well-being. Contact me if of interest!    
    
    
    ~ Not all who wander are lost.  –J.R. Tolkein    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Amman, Jordan. People not only help me here, some want to talk with me for as long as I'll stay ;) ha ha. Guess I stand out just a little ;)    
    
    
    Swam, or floated, rather, in the Dead Sea today, and sat alongside the River Jordan, site of Christ's baptism. Brought back through time...!    
    
    
    @isaacgetz 'We should be driven by ethics as principles, not rules to be exploited for what you can or cannot get away with.'
- Jean Brunel    
    
    
    assimilating into arabic life and culture in the Middle East...beginning to really understand the language, both spoken and un-spoken ;)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @isaacgetz I see in the Economist that Amazon has bought Zappos. I hope that doesn't dampen their prized freedom culture.    
    
    
        
    
    
    Go placidly amid the noise and haste, and remember what peace there may be in silence. ~ Ehrmann    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    I give thanks and send blessings as I peer out over Vancouver's lights as morning gains towards sunrise. Finalizing research study & stats.    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Registered for 10 day silent meditation retreat. Will I emerge as linked in to my 'inner-net' as to the internet? ;) pic.twitter.com/Z3KlQwI2vW    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Slideshow of my Autumn 2010 adventures in the Middle East: http://www.TravelingIntuit.blogspot.com    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Nearly a quarter of employees are actively disengaged! Great Gallup info on reversing this troubling trend! @ESCPeuropeLIVE #globalworkplace    
    
    
        
    
    
    Ken Wilber on IT-'isms'. http://integrallife.com/node/12177  Is pantheistic spirituality most fitting for this technological age? pic.twitter.com/SWxpHBkWdP    
    
    
    You yourself, as much as anybody in the entire universe, deserve your love and affection ~ Buddha    
    
    
    An inspiring, strong and spiritual woman. She transforms tears into laughter: http://www.ted.com/talks/maysoon_zayid_i_got_99_problems_palsy_is_just_one.html?utm_medium=on.ted.com-static&awesm=on.ted.com_Maysoon&utm_content=awesm-publisher&utm_campaign&utm_source=facebook.com …    
    
    
    Essential attributes of game-changing organizations: purpose-driven, performance-oriented & principle-led http://hbr.org/2014/01/building-a-game-changing-talent-strategy/ar/1 … @isaacgetz    
    
    
        
    
    
    Be content with what you have; rejoice in the way things are. When you realize there's nothing lacking, the whole world belongs to you. ~Tzu    
    
    
        
    
    
    I encourage you to your deepest strength. You will know it by its effortlessness... I see you and you are beautiful and capable. ~ Meg Irsay    
    
    
    intense security exiting Israel. Understandable, though. Thanks friends for tips & tricks, avoided me staying in Hezbollah territory & more!    
    
    
    Morning meditation sessions offered within companies: http://travelingintuit.blogspot.com/2010/12/for-organizations-in-vancouver-bc-and.html    
    
    
    Presenting my preliminary research findings Thursday, April 28 7pm at http://www.goeio.com Entrepreneur's meeting at ING Direct Vancouver.    
    
    
    "the efforts of Marie E Holm, who tirelessly read and reread the manuscript...are especially worthy of recognition." www.freedomincbook.com    
    
    
    No need for temples. No need for complicated philosophy. Your own mind & heart is the temple, your philosophy is simple kindness ~Dalai Lama    
    
    
    Enjoying exploring fascinating topics within consciousness and intuition! Look forward to collaborating with others! http://tiny.cc/oMn2z    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    @SFurbanWoman Read your new blog post - very uplifting! Gave me shivers when I read about the angel she gave for you :)    
    
    
        
    
    
    offering intuitive readings, via spirit chanelling - see my new my profile (bottom right) at http://serenitylifestyle.com/referrals.html    
    
    
        
    
    
    Pondering why solitary confinement is considered punishment when in prison, yet blissful solitude when in meditation. Your thoughts, please?    
    
    
        
    
    
    What further can we best do to alleviate the famine in Somalia? Which charities are most able to get help to where it is really needed?    
    
    
    Six months and counting as a full-fledged global nomad. Tricky as a vegetarian here in Romania, where it's typically meat served with meat!    
    
    
    