@archaeologyman You have the internet so it can't be all bad ;-) Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Nice!  I mean not the hiding from Christmas but Marrakech sounds nice.  Couldn't hide in London? Or Shropshire?    
    
    
    @4fifty1 @shelter £260 I think.    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Wooo - where did got for Christmas?    
    
    
    @mredwards Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Nice!  Visiting family or just going away for Christmas?    
    
    
    @crimeficreader Merry Christmas Rhian! Hope you've been well?    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Yup - and I had to laugh at the heat tweet as my parents have a wood stove which makes you not able to breathe after 1/2 hour.    
    
    
    @crimeficreader New home?  Still Wales?  We're all well here. Spending Christmas home thankfully.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Haha! It's when they decide that they can't afford the heating bill but yet will be able to chop wood at 90.    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Well I hope it's a nice one for you too! x    
    
    
    Looking forward to chatting with my family tomorrow although I hate when we get passed around with 'So & so is here, remember them?'    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Awww sweet - you have the grandkids tonight? How freaking magical is that?    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Statistically the average time is 5.15 am. Ho ho ho :-)) Merry Christmas Mr Colgan. xx    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Yep. One year I talked to someone who I thought was a nephew for 10 minutes before I realised it was a neighbor!    
    
    
    @LSpurdle This year we have a secret weapon.  FaceTime with bad wifi.  We get annoyed 'Opps, so sorry! Wifi is bad'.    
    
    
    Thanks @Just_Will_I_am for starting the #royalpardon for Alan #Turing! @AlanTuringYear    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Congrats :-)    
    
    
    @SBarryCooper @Just_Will_I_am @AlanTuringYear Absolutely.  And just to be sure - everyone here knows @Dr_Black & @bletchleypark right?    
    
    
    Woot! A delivery from states is in the UK.  I'll have to wait until Friday but at least it's getting closer :)    
    
    
    @ge0_ff Hooray!    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers I still have to wait until Friday and then figure out how to use them but still ;-)    
    
    
    Eek - 30 minutes until SANTA!  Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dress when you get there!    
    
    
    @SaminaKosar @LSpurdle Good luck! May we all survive 'The Call' :-) Merry Christmas! x    
    
    
    Good morning and a Very Merry Christmas! How is everyone today?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Merry Christmas!!! We're up already as C has been asking to open presents since 5. How is A? x    
    
    
    We gave C the cover to her new phone saying it was a promise for a new one in Jan. Her face was a picture when she got the phone. :)))    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Was there enough sparkles on the shoes? ;-) I can not believe you got her Mousetrap. That game is pure evil ;-)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Damn yes have replied. Should I stick with email/ tweets?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Tweets it is then! Stuff from us has been opened but nanny is doing 20 gift Treasure hunt later.    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I got an air popcorn maker and season 1 Columbo!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Mousetrap has been ban from my house. Many memories of hours setting up for it to be over in 2 minutes. I never had patience!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Normally they did it with advent but C didn't have time in morning this year. They do riddles & directions (north south etc).    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Sweet! Love the steam train book!    
    
    
    @GiantDespair You too Phil! Merry Christmas! x    
    
    
    @Bashtafarian Wow!    
    
    
    @Bashtafarian Merry Christmas to you and Becky!    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Is he outside cooling down? ;-)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Merry Christmas!!    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 What the world needs is festive deers and pretty lights. pic.twitter.com/aH0nIvQupv    
    
    
    @iamamro @linda1966 @insidebooks @stujallen @thebooktower Merry Christmas gang! Hope today is festive & fun! xx    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Enjoy the walk - nice weather here but I'm not going anywhere until Friday.    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Now that is freaking adorable! S/he needs antlers.    
    
    
    @4fifty1 You got a pug? (Autocorrect really wants you to have a pig btw.) @truongthomas    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Like I said, I'm not going anywhere today. It'll be worth the wait by the sounds of it!    
    
    
    @4fifty1 @truongthomas Ha! I should have known better. Pig might have been right after all ;-) x    
    
    
    For those who weren't up at 5:30am - MERRY CHRISTMAS! 

For those who were up at 5:30am - you crashing too?    
    
    
    @wood5y And to you! Hope Santa was kind to you?    
    
    
    @mdoness I know I should be happy that she still has the spirit but more grateful she went to daddy at 4am ;-)    
    
    
    @wood5y Dear Lord no. I'm not allowed in the kitchen which is fine by me! I might be asked to help peel carrots... Maybe.    
    
    
    @dusty_jacket What an angel!    
    
    
    @PhilipArdagh @Alex_T_Smith Merry Christmas you two! xx    
    
    
    @AboutLondon What jackasses! And they can't fix until Sat?    
    
    
    @SumoJim Merry Christmas Jim! How is the family? Santa been kind?    
    
    
    ** QUEEN SPEECH KLAXON ** pic.twitter.com/3zhbyiTqxz    
    
    
    @SumoJim Oh yuck - but glad Christmas is at home! I take it you we're suppose to run in a marathon or two today?    
    
    
    Merry Christmas from the Goofy Dixons. (This was a serious photo if you can't tell.) pic.twitter.com/r77wMU9iDm    
    
    
    @SumoJim So when you get bronchitis I'll remind you of it. ;-) I have been blessed with pneumonia this year again - slows me down :)    
    
    
    @SumoJim Went to doctor Monday as thought it was happening again. Stupid lungs. But nothing compared to tough Brody!    
    
    
    @SumoJim It's been hard, let me tell you ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn This was the non serious ... Not much difference. Merry Christmas Yannick! pic.twitter.com/uGUDMi57m9    
    
    
    @SumoJim What a fantastic way to be!    
    
    
    @aboutlondon Did you get my text?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Sweet of them! Can you watch tv? Dr who on tonight!    
    
    
    @vickybarlo @CaroWallis @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll @LSpurdle And you! Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @CaroleSouter Merry Christmas Carole!    
    
    
    @Madlena_P @akhetherington Oh my - that looks delicious! Merry Christmas! Hope you're having a fantastic day!    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone this lovely Christmas evening?    
    
    
    @jacquesharris The key is to not stop eating. Want some crisps? ;-) It's been a lovely Christmas -lovely gifts, delicious food & family time    
    
    
    Just tried to FaceTime mom. She told me to call back in 20 minutes.  I told her she has to wait until Dr Who is over. Daughter of the year.    
    
    
    @jacquesharris Wooo - I ail try that tomorrow as I'm not planning on stopping until jan 3rd ;-)    
    
    
    @GiantDespair We have a few!! We have the hallmark ornament range - brilliant movie.  Gets better with time :-)    
    
    
    @janetedavis We were waiting for most of the family to get over to moms before FaceTime. Up until now, it'll just be parents arguing ;-)    
    
    
    @custard1980 Amen.  But I'm still going :-)    
    
    
    @custard1980 Was Santa good to you?    
    
    
    @custard1980 CHEESE!  You just reminder me!    
    
    
    Shhh #DrWho is on    
    
    
    Since when is it BBC and not BBC Wales for #DrWho?    
    
    
    FaceTime w family in the states was fun. We couldnt see them but they could see us.  C & I just waved like the Queen until we heard a voice.    
    
    
    Was great to chat with them all though! We need  @scicheer to get on Facetime now! xx    
    
    
    Yes it is :-) RT @sciencemuseum: 'A trip to the @sciencemuseum for the staff - is that a treat?' Mrs Hughes, it is indeed! #Downton    
    
    
    @acediscovery Someone scored well with that deal.  Now I want to know who at  @sciencemuseum has pull with #DowtonAbbey!    
    
    
    @w_stanley @acediscovery Merry Christmas guys!    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Tv, pjs and eating non-stop here.  Exactly as we wanted it.  (Sorry for delay!)    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 Having a good Christmas?    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there!  Hope you have a wonderful Merry Christmas! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this lovely Boxing Day?    
    
    
    @helenahalme Very romantic :-)    
    
    
    I've managed a bit of a lie in today - Whoo hoo!    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 I'm awake but still in bed and planning on staying here as long as possible. Good Christmas?    
    
    
    @courtlady Good morning Susan! How was your Christmas? xx    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 We facetimed with the family last night. Always good to talk to them :)    
    
    
    @helenahalme Absolutely - plan on staying here as long as possible too!    
    
    
    C & I are waiting for packages that should arrive tomorrow. C is waiting for her iPhone 5c sim & I'm waiting for Google Glass :-)    
    
    
    @Hardyduncan We watched it but we're huge fans of the show.    
    
    
    @1stHistorical @state_hermitage No idea what you're chatting about but love that you are chatting on twitter and there is even a smile :-)    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers Ha! But dinosaurs are cool!    
    
    
    @1stHistorical  What a gorgeous building! Congratulations @state_hermitage!    
    
    
    @1stHistorical I'm assuming @state_hermitage is a bit like @nationaltrust in the UK? Saving and restoring building?    
    
    
    Cracking up at @drlucyrogers tweets from last night. My favourite: 

Selfie pic.twitter.com/1NtuhriFS6    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Will - you *will* show me in May ;-) Did you get the train ticket for 29th sorted?    
    
    
    @state_hermitage @1stHistorical I have so much to learn from you guys. :-)    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Perfect. I live around 40 minutes from the train station but still plenty of time for you to see Bridgnorth and is to chat.    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers You need to storify these!    
    
    
    @Madlena_P How sweet! I'm looking forward to seeing you too!    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#LolDinosaurs @DrLucyRogers Bedtime Story" http://sfy.co/eXRO     
    
    
    #LolDinosaurs @DrLucyRogers Bedtime Story http://sfy.co/eXRO  #storify #stempressies #loldinosaurs    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Sounds peaceful! x    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Just be careful!    
    
    
    Anyone else having problems copying and pasting with @tweetdeck?    
    
    
    Following now. cc @VirtualAstro RT @amandajp17: Anyone interested in astrophotography give @Galileo149  a follow #SocialMedianewbie    
    
    
    The Biggest Overlooked Trends of 2013 http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2013/12/overlooked-trends-of-2013-101491.html …    
    
    
    Lovely new Punch and Judy Facebook community created by @jamesarnott #puppets https://www.facebook.com/punchandjudypage …    
    
    
    @TootSweetsShrew Certainly I haven't found it in Telford.  I went all American at Asda the other day.  Twas fun. 

Not.  (Merry Christmas!)    
    
    
    @timb30 Merry Christmas Tim!    
    
    
    Happy birthday Caroll Spinney!   He's the Genius puppeteer behind both Oscar the Grouch & Big Bird! pic.twitter.com/eGIHOWKbTV    
    
    
    @bigdaddymerk Yes yes - Caroll takes care of Big Bird when Snuffleupagus is busy.    
    
    
    Can you get away with it? Then it was probably art this year http://fw.to/QUmaONF  / Very interesting read. #art    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Haha! @4fifty1 @dinoboy89    
    
    
    English mustards cousin, Horseradish is my nemesis this holiday.    
    
    
    Same here! RT @guernseylibrary: Finally... Gangsta Granny! Daughter has been looking forward to this for ages! @davidwalliams    
    
    
    @Richard71108933 Have you read the book? @guernseylibrary    
    
    
    @Richard71108933 Can't you turn it off if you dislike it so much? @guernseylibrary    
    
    
    #GangstaGranny at the gorgeous Tower @HRP_palaces    
    
    
    @ITweetMuseums Did you see @CultureThemes Jan 22nd topic?  #MuseumSelfie http://culturethemes.blogspot.co.uk/2013/12/new-theme-museumselfie-january-22nd.html …    
    
    
    @HRP_palaces Haha - I'm sure you are ;-)    
    
    
    @ITweetMuseums We are too :-) #MuseumSelfie @CultureThemes    
    
    
    #DrinkingAboutMuseums UK January 13th #London FREE http://www.eventbrite.com/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173?aff=estw …  PLS RT cc @w_stanley    
    
    
    @mattpross @TCP1980 @johnshevlin @jacquesharris @acediscovery @RussellDornan @kdwignall @bethfoster @inakiarredondo
https://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173 …    
    
    
    @_NatStar Nope - sounds like you had a proper Boxing Day - well done!    
    
    
    Vasari's Last Supper reassembled 47 years after Florence flood http://gu.com/p/3yek4/tw  #art    
    
    
    Strike closes National Museum of Scotland on Boxing Day http://bbc.in/1daqSUY  / I missed this today!    
    
    
    Shrewsbury museum curator steps down after 16 years http://www.shropshirestar.com/news/2013/12/26/shrewsbury-museum-curator-steps-down-after-16-years/ … via @ShropshireStar    
    
    
    Love BBC's use of hashtag for #SherlockLives in the commercials.  #WellPlayed    
    
    
    Utah. Gay marriage. Boy Scouts. Pizza. Say no more http://www.cnn.com/2013/12/25/us/utah-boy-scout-pizza-for-gays/index.html?sr=sharebar_twitter … #equalmarriage    
    
    
    @DavidMentiply @Museum_Marathon : #DrinkingAboutMuseums UK January 13th #London FREE http://www.eventbrite.com/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173?aff=estw …  PLS RT cc @w_stanley    
    
    
    @stellduffy I'm coming to London for the 14th - lmk what time is good for you.    
    
    
    @stellduffy That's perfect. Just want to take afternoon/early evening train back if possible. Also, having a tweetup 13th if you're free.    
    
    
    @n_maniatis No worries, we try to have them once a month so you're bound to get to one of them :)    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this Fabulous Friday?    
    
    
    @truongthomas Living the dream today I see...    
    
    
    C is excitingly expecting her iPhone sim today, and I'm waiting for Goggle Glass to be delivered. Hope Postman doesn't disappoint!    
    
    
    @mikimoo9 Impressed you're up so early! Christmas has been v relaxing. Been spending time with family and eating my way into 2014 :)    
    
    
    @mikimoo9 Was Santa good to you?    
    
    
    @mikimoo9 That is even better!  Who needs presents when you can have a laugh with family?    
    
    
    @LSpurdle I know! So freaking excited but have to remember it might be Saturday. But they're in Midlands :) Good Christmas?    
    
    
    @mikimoo9 Here is hoping today goes quickly for you. Btw next #drinkingaboutmuseums UK is Jan 13th.    
    
    
    #DrinkingAboutMuseums UK January 13th #London FREE http://www.eventbrite.com/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173?aff=estw …  PLS RT cc @w_stanley    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Same - pjs, food and family (the non fighting family). Been redecorating C's room which means house is upside down right now.    
    
    
    @telfordlive  I'm not sure - @bethfoster does but she doesn't live in Shropshire now (but heart will always be here ;-))    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Move one thing, eat. I'm rolling into 2024 ;-) you up for looking at funding soon? Know it's not festive ...    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Morning! Doing another tube run today?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Well done! So my dad always does that - saw on FB that apparently he got a snake for christmas. I don't know either.    
    
    
    @telfordlive will do - I got them to share the experience :)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I know - I'm not sure of mom knows yet or if it was a joke on FB. Planning on calling him later as haven't talked to him yet.    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Whenever is good for you - I have time too. Shall we meet for cake?!    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said Morning!    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said V well and excitingly waiting for postman today. You?    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Let me find out what's going on & I'll let you know. Sunday I've @Madlena_P coming to Bridgnorth. :)    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said Google glass for me and SIM card for C's new phone.    
    
    
    @gopaldass Amen. Good Christmas?    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said It started as I want to see their uses in museums- but will be interesting to see what comes from them.    
    
    
    C has a friend coming over at 10 - suppose I should get out of bed.    
    
    
    @gopaldass Fabulous here - been in Pjs since dec 24! Was Santa kind to you?    
    
    
    @theluxuryeditor It is an it's a great way to meet new people :-)  @w_stanley    
    
    
    For the record:  I have ZERO patience.  #waitsforUPS    
    
    
    @gopaldass Yes - should be here today but it's showing 10.30pm :-/    
    
    
    @gopaldass Haha!  I believe that is called Shotgun ;-)    
    
    
    Redecorating C's room (with new furniture).  I've established her dream room only works in a different house.    
    
    
    Mark your calendars! January 13th #London #Tweetup Open to ALL 

http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173 …  PLS RT & Come along!    
    
    
    @jackschofield Thanks for the RT - when are you going to come to one?  *taps feet waiting*    
    
    
    @acediscovery Jealous? ;-)    
    
    
    @acediscovery Also HINT http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173 …    
    
    
    @jackschofield Believe it or not, I'm teetotal too.  I drive people to drink but don't drink myself ;-)    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 @dinoboy89 How lucky are you!    
    
    
    Visiting a museum?  Take a #MuseumSelfie and share on Jan 22nd with @CultureThemes
http://culturethemes.blogspot.com/2013/12/new-theme-museumselfie-january-22nd.html … 
PLS RT & Get Involved    
    
    
    I've decided I don't like my website so I updated it a bit.  That and I'm avoiding C's room right now.    
    
    
    @skyfire747 We're in the middle of redecorating - going from pink/purple to beige contemporary. It's hell.    
    
    
    @skyfire747 No chance of that until Monday. Even after the huge clear out her 'stuff' is all over place. IKEA tomorrow :-/    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Beautiful!    
    
    
    @nancyarts @mattcaines Right both of you - there is ANOTHER tweet up Jan 13th - you have to come to one! http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173 …    
    
    
    So instead of texting I just got a FaceTime from C who is up in town.  Hoping this wears off soon!    
    
    
    Transform your Passions Into a Career (Skype Blog featuring me - seriously!) http://blogs.skype.com/2013/12/20/transform-your-passions-into-a-career/#.Ur2WtNfw8CE.twitter …    
    
    
    @middlewest Great - time to tweet then ;-)    
    
    
    The Meanings of the Selfie http://nyti.ms/1jMuody  - #museumselfie    
    
    
    Impressive! RT @YahooTech: NORAD Tracks Santa logs 19.58 million web visits http://yhoo.it/19mYjPC     
    
    
    @AboutLondon Thanks Laura! :-) How was John Lewis?    
    
    
    Educating Yorkshire: An open letter to Michael Gove | Big Issue http://www.bigissue.com/mix/news/3385/educating-yorkshire-open-letter-michael-gove … #GoveMustGo    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Haha - you got this free wifi thing done pretty good! I've yet to take advantage of my free cake at John Lewis.    
    
    
    I've been left to watch the dinner while M drops C's friend off. This can only end in disaster as I only just figure out 1 pan is sprouts.    
    
    
    @M_Fkill They seem to be shredded with bacon and cashews. We're having Boxing Day dinner tonight as too stuffed yesterday.    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone tonight?    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers It wasn't good AT ALL but I don't eat vegetables.  How was London?    
    
    
    Arts and heritage in 2013 – in pictures http://gu.com/p/3yf3f/tw     
    
    
    @jbrunotte Thanks Jorn! Hope you had a lovely holiday?    
    
    
    @jbrunotte That's all that matters :)    
    
    
    @e_chaplin *sniff* They weren't delivered today. Can only assume the weather is to blame.  Know they are in Midlands though.    
    
    
    @textworkshop Don't you just HATE when birds get in the way of making parks beautiful?    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Sweet - have you been to Lebanese restaurant in Carnaby Street?    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 Are you in London Jan 13th?  Tweetup at pub x    
    
    
    @MJCounselling @TootSweetsShrew You can check your archives? Go to Settings then down towards the bottom is Request your Archives.    
    
    
    :-) RT @comcomclaire: Nice portrait of the adorable troublemaker @MarDixon ;) http://blogs.skype.com/2013/12/20/transform-your-passions-into-a-career/ …    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Blissful!    
    
    
    @4fifty1 If by any chance you're back in London, drinks on the 13th. xx    
    
    
    @stujallen Very well here Stu - how are you tonight?    
    
    
    @stujallen Brilliant! Did you have to work today?    
    
    
    @stujallen How are the clients?    
    
    
    @stujallen Did you get many books?    
    
    
    @4fifty1 So is your game plan to just travel the world for a bit?    
    
    
    @timb0e Fantastic exhibition, don't you think?  Did you get the pin? @sciencemuseum @CERN    
    
    
    @stujallen Same here.  I've such a huge TBR pile right now.  I did get Columbo Season 1 on DVD though :-)    
    
    
    @stujallen Wasn't that a brilliant ep?  I watched it twice.  Would love Murder, She Wrote dvd next. Bit obsessed ;)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Cool.  So are all the pieces thrown in the air at the moment or just the ones you feel like ignoring? ;-)    
    
    
    @stujallen I keep hearing that but so far I've had NO luck finding them cheap.  Maybe I'm looking in the wrong places. Amazon?    
    
    
    Diary of a Wimpy Kid card game is quite fun!  Well shouting Zooweemama is at least ;-)    
    
    
    @PDarigan At least you get to spend some time with her :-)    
    
    
    Sherlock Holmes Is Now in the Public Domain, Declares US Judge | Open Culture http://www.openculture.com/2013/12/sherlock-holmes-is-now-in-the-public-domain-declares-us-judge.html …    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 No.    
    
    
    @PDarigan Will be MUCH better when my package arrives (hoping tomorrow).  Oh, C's room gets done. But yes, been home in PJs side Dec 23 ;-)    
    
    
    @PDarigan Best. Invention. Ever.  PJs solve so many problems.  ;-)    
    
    
    OH WOW! 
Internet Archive puts classic 70s and 80s games online http://bbc.in/K9MW7R  
HT @dinoboy89    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 Fine, only because I just saw the awesome news from @samatlounge about Digital Book world. x    
    
    
    Thank you :) RT @dinoboy89: Nice piece on you on @Skype 'a blog , @mardixon ! http://blogs.skype.com/2013/12/20/transform-your-passions-into-a-career/ …    
    
    
    Tomorrow we're heading to Ikillya (Ikea) - too soon to start crying now?    
    
    
    @diddles54 @scrufflove  I've tried to have C look at things online but w funky walls, we have to see the stuff.    
    
    
    @travellingcoral I can't stand crowds, shopping and ques…    
    
    
    @mannyc C is getting new bedroom set but we need to see the stuff as this old house doesn't have normal walls. Was it crowded?    
    
    
    @diddles54 @scrufflove She better ;-) Currently her room is all over the house (but we managed a lot of bags to charity). x    
    
    
    @travellingcoral C wants a new bedroom set from there.  :-/    
    
    
    @mannyc Seriously, we're on the top floor of an old house.  Straight walls aren't an option & we have sloping ceilings.    
    
    
    @mannyc I tried to talk them going tonight as they were open until 10 but we were playing Diary of a Wimpy Kid ;-)    
    
    
    @scrufflove @diddles54 So true!  And I muse remember that I DO NOT NEED CANDLES! xx    
    
    
    @travellingcoral Needs - she's a bit tall for the bunk bed she had :-)    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this stupid o'clock Saturday morning?    
    
    
    @stujallen And here- silly coughing woke me up. You off to work?    
    
    
    @stujallen Hope the day goes quickly for you!    
    
    
    @kevtan1066 Planning to be at ikea for 9 for lunch ;)    
    
    
    @ypldn @AboutLondon 4 step sisters (didn't live with us). Yep 2 hours dial up only at night until 2001 when another type of line installed.    
    
    
    @acediscovery Sounds like you had a nice time with family over Christmas - but nothing like going back to your own home ;) Safe travels!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon We should have left an hour ago but Frick & Frack are moving slow. Mug here was the only one up with alarm. AGAIN!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Breathing and I still have a complicated relationship but getting better. ;-) Any update on virgin coming out?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Haha - you've done really well, much better than I would have been! Here's hoping it's a quick fix! x    
    
    
    @travellingcoral I know - and trying to keep control of the budget at the same time- *think happy place* ;-)    
    
    
    @scottkeir Thanks Scott! @zakmensah    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I heard about it but thought it was in Europe (literally only heard name). Now want to learn more (we're on our way to Ikea!)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Just back and we did really good!  Everything will get delivered tomorrow. Ikea is about an hour away from us so it takes long.    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Hooray for cable being fixed!!  Bet it feels like you can breathe again :-)    
    
    
    Anyone? RT @LebelAube:  @MarDixon Do you know studies on Personal photography in museums : learning programs, visitors behaviors ?    
    
    
    Afternoon all! How is everyone today?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Little bugger is getting a king size bed too!    
    
    
    @bigdaddymerk Just thinking of going back after a trip to ikea!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Sorry - C just decided to go swimming with her friend and we couldn't find googles. Her room is same size as office downstairs.    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 Oh no - been out and about and survived Ikea already :-)    
    
    
    @diddles54 LOADS of candles and C managed quite a nice new bedroom set which was even on sale! How are you? x    
    
    
    @zakmensah @LebelAube I remember Sackler centre in @V_and_A did a program where they lent out cameras to family to snap their fav object.    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 Yes it does.  Been planning it for days now!    
    
    
    Grrrr my package is being held up in a warehouse in East Midlands past 30 hours. Can @UPSHelp provide any more info?    
    
    
    @DavidMentiply Lovely beer :-)    
    
    
    @DavidMentiply New Owner?    
    
    
    @IdrisGeorge Here is hoping they are better than :-) @UPSHelp    
    
    
    @AboutLondon It's in a freaking warehouse in East Midlands.  Hoping @UPSHelp can help me get more info as should have been here yesterday.    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I'm so freaking annoyed it's not even funny - but if they have a good excuse then they should say what it is grrr    
    
    
    @AboutLondon It looks like it got through customs warehouse on 26th so hopefully not *fingers crossed*    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 Fees were paid in the states so I better not have fees to pay! @UPSHelp    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 You don't have that when it's a gift. :)    
    
    
    @UPSHelp @UPS Thanks!  I emailed already as read your timeline ;-)    
    
    
    Visiting a museum?  Take a #MuseumSelfie and share on Jan 22nd with @CultureThemes
http://culturethemes.blogspot.com/2013/12/new-theme-museumselfie-january-22nd.html … 
PLS RT & Get Involved    
    
    
    +1 MT @ri_science Tune to #BBC4 at 8pm to start your #xmaslectures journey through  Life Fantastic w/ @AlisonWoollard http://bit.ly/19gBhth     
    
    
    @CaroWallis 22nd is better for me :-) @vickybarlo @NylonsAndAll @kimbiddulph @LSpurdle Merry Christmas MSW Gang!    
    
    
    QUICK! Turn over to BBC4 for @ri_science #xmaslectures
with @AlisonWoollard http://bit.ly/19gBhth     
    
    
    @VEE6 Think they've always been on BBC4 - at least I thought so? @ri_science    
    
    
    @ri_science I'll pretend I didn't see that tweets… but for the record - TOTALLY jealous. x    
    
    
    @VEE6 Maybe you can catch it on iplayer later? @ri_science    
    
    
    @FranPickering Cake? @ypldn @GWinLondon @LondonKiwiEmma @travelling_dave    
    
    
    And she's on Twitter @AlisonWoollard RT @skirrid: Royal Institution Christmas Lecture, @BBC_Four , Alison Woolard is great.    
    
    
    Haha Sir Paul Nurse! @ri_science #xmaslectures    
    
    
    How Y’all, Youse and You Guys Talk: dialect map & make your own. http://nyti.ms/Kck66i  / Spot on for me (hoagie, sneakers, mischief night)    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Youse and Y'all are funny as was highlighted to me in 1983 as NorthEast from 'new girl' in school.  :-)    
    
    
    @amyldale Lucky you!    
    
    
    @DaddyPerry Cute!    
    
    
    @Zerahlynne I always assume mischief night was everywhere until I moved to the UK.  Hoagie is very Eastern PA :-)    
    
    
    Looking forward to showing @Madlena_P Bridgnorth & @puppetarchive tomorrow :-)    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this lovely Sunday?    
    
    
    @Madlena_P 11:11 Wolverhampton train right? Come to main lobby & I'll meet you there. :)    
    
    
    @skyfire747 Wow! Not sure what that means but sounds nice and warm ;-) Going out for a walk later?    
    
    
    @DrRichJohnston Not a morning person either but have lovely visitor coming today so exception made. Santayana good to you?    
    
    
    I seem to be watching Mega Truckers on Dave. It's not half bad...    
    
    
    @beecee What? Never run unless it's towards cake. Simples.    
    
    
    @beecee And? Have you not heard of spandex? ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn Great here! C's furniture being delivered today and should be done redecorating by Tuesday whoo hoo! How is Brugge trip going?    
    
    
    @ypldn What's the post about?    
    
    
    Antiques Roadshow portrait revealed to be by Anthony Van Dyck http://bbc.in/19uQw8d  cc @AshmoleanMuseum    
    
    
    @beecee Clearly you'll never get me to go with running, but especially not during the Christmas season. I'm the devil on the shoulder ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn Sim came but my package hasn't :-( Looking forward to Bourg a lot! Going out today but will read post when home. :)    
    
    
    @beecee You WHAT?! Dear Lord you need help...    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Adventurous!    
    
    
    The 38 Most Haunting Abandoned Places On Earth. For Some Reason, I Can't Look Away... http://distractify.com/culture/arts/the-most-spectacular-abandoned-places-in-the-world/ …    
    
    
    @upshelp I've requested info on why-after spending extra to get package delivered by Friday-it is sitting in a warehouse since 27th.    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Thank you - and you! @Madlena_P    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Sounds like it was a good night!    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Then sounds like it was a long overdue good night :-) All well here -getting ready to show off Bridgnorth to @Madlena_P in a bit.    
    
    
    Sophie de Oliveira Barata: the woman who turns artificial limbs into works of art – in pictures http://gu.com/p/3yd67/tw     
    
    
    @OonaghTweets Hope it gets sorted soon!    
    
    
    Viewers love television's Mrs Brown because she bucks every trend | Elizabeth Day http://gu.com/p/3yf5h/tw  @MrsBrownsBoys    
    
    
    Showing off gorgeous @blistshill to @madlena_P - C showing Anna Oliver the horse :-) (at @blistshill) [pic]: http://4sq.com/1fSFd8b     
    
    
    Old vs new - who will win the popcorn war? pic.twitter.com/VZWiOOQluX    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone tonight?    
    
    
    @acediscovery We love @MrsBrownsBoys in our house - even managed to see show live in Wolverhampton.    
    
    
    @OonaghTweets Very relaxing Christmas although in the middle of redecorating C's room which is a tad stressful.  How is Phd going?    
    
    
    When @Madlena_P came to Bridgnorth & @blistshill :-) https://www.facebook.com/mardixon/media_set?set=a.10152111651311506.1073741957.814781505&type=1 … [Facebook photos]    
    
    
    @DrRichJohnston I love being museum busy - very lucky to do what I do :-) Hoping to be busier w new toy tomorrow :-)    
    
    
    @Gracie_Flower Sounds blissful and fun!  Hope you had similar weather to us today - it's been gorgeous!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon How was ice skating today ?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Haha well done you! You must be exhausted!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Golden Hinde? What's that?  And seeing them again - any particular reason? (Not that you need one!)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Wooo - that is by the Thames in between Design museum and Shard right?  (Like that general area-ish)    
    
    
    @Gracie_Flower Yep - but did you take a #MuseumSelfie today? ;)    
    
    
    @ZapActive It is fantastic! And @enginuitymuseum is still brilliant (and with wifi!) @Madlena_P    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Haha lovely photo.  Glad you had a great weekend! x @DianaPitchers @M_Fkill    
    
    
    @Gracie_Flower Perfect!  Much better than the ones I've been taking too!    
    
    
    Great charity @carolvorders won money for on #CatchPhase - @CLAPACOMMUNITY has done so much for our family when C was born.    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science We want the dogs please… #socute    
    
    
    @ri_science Look at that face!  Sofreakingcute #xmaslectures    
    
    
    @museweb Sent a dm when you have a chance to read it.  Thanks!    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science It's like me in the kitchen!    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science Is too freaking cute tonight! First the dog and now these kittens. Can't take anymore!    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Have DM'd @museweb to ask about @Museomixuk paper. Should I ask @MWFlorence2014?    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science CAKE!  Wait, what? Oh ok, sweets.    
    
    
    @Madlena_P I'll see what @museweb says first then will contact @MWFlorence2014 *fingers crossed*    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Maybe I could submit about @Culturethemes if not. @1stHistorical @museweb @MWFlorence2014    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Not really - talked about it in Lithuania once but not presented a paper.    
    
    
    Ha! RT @coedybrenin: #xmaslectures-what do you call a fish with  no i's-a fsh !    
    
    
    Beyond selfies and twerking … the words that really mattered in 2013 http://gu.com/p/3ye58/tw  MEGGINGS?  Please, just don't.    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Can't submit for MMUK sadly. :-(    
    
    
    Seeing 'FitBit' photos on FB -, ppl shout from the rooftops about privacy but yet tag themselves for running & eating healthy?  #confused    
    
    
    @fleming77 So true but these are people who lock their account and speak of the evils of the govt but yet fitbit is ok?    
    
    
    Big kids queue for adult 'night at the museum': Grown-ups get to sleep over in @NHM_London http://www.independent.co.uk/news/uk/home-news/big-kids-queue-for-adult-night-at-the-museum-grownups-get-to-sleep-over-in-natural-history-museum-9028626.html …    
    
    
    *fingers crossed* UPS delivers my package tomorrow (as it should have been here Friday).    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick Fear?  One reason is fear of lawsuit.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 I was lucky enough to doe the Dino-snore for C's 10th bday. Would LOVE the adult one! @NHM_London    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick I will never, ever understand football hiring/firing here.    
    
    
    @Gracie_Flower As am I! @NHM_London    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Yep - at least give it a good old try… @NHM_London    
    
    
    The Michael Gove random policy generator http://gu.com/p/3ye2m/tw  #GoveMUSTGo    
    
    
    The Michael Gove random policy generator http://gu.com/p/3ye2m/tw  #GoveMUSTGo cc @MichaelRosenYes    
    
    
    Historic Auschwitz barracks returned to Poland after two decades in US http://gu.com/p/3yfh9/tw     
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone today?    
    
    
    @bristolfemuse Sorry Rose - deleted my KIM tweet as it was from wrong account :-) MERRY CHRISTMAS!    
    
    
    @mattcaines @nancyarts Great! We need a good catch up!    
    
    
    @Madlena_P €200 euros is a bit steep for me sadly.  Good luck with your proposal though! If it was free entry for speaker than I'd try :-)    
    
    
    @bristolfemuse Oh no - can it get fixed soon?    
    
    
    @Aratta I had great fun with @mixedreality's @3doodler last month.  :-)    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Would love to be part of @MuseumsShowoff conference - beed to check with C first as it's her bday. :-)    
    
    
    @bristolfemuse I'll cross fingers for you too! We've been redecorating… it's its own little hell this ;-)    
    
    
    @Aratta My 'art' https://www.facebook.com/photo.php?fbid=10152057219511506&set=pb.814781505.-2207520000.1388400246.&type=3&theater … (FB hope you can see)    
    
    
    @Madlena_P I would love to speak at @MuseumsShowoff - Florence is just too expensive at this point.  So sorry!    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers Here either but it's promised to be delivered today.  I say we go all American on them if they don't arrive.    
    
    
    Want to do this… RT @CurateAward: Have you entered @CurateAward yet? Let us know and we'll retweet you! #curating #arts    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers Being Very LOUD.    
    
    
    @jamiezoob Excellent here - in the middle of redecorating which is a royal pain but will smile when it's over.  Sickness bug?    
    
    
    @jamiezoob Not when it's for an 11yo thinking that she's 17.  Compromises are fun to deal with ;-)    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers @mattdawhit And I'm waiting for Google Glass. The door has been knocked 3 times this morning - NOT for me GRRR    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers Well I just went all American on UPS as they claim not to find the address and will try tomorrow.    
    
    
    Right now - UPS is not my friend.    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone tonight?    
    
    
    @LSpurdle So annoyed - promised to be here on Friday, then went back & forth today. Driver claimed it was wrong address. Getting refund.    
    
    
    @implausibleblog After putting C's room together, I'm very warm ;-)    
    
    
    @Cornettofairy Deep ;-) I'm totally PO'd at UPS. However, got C's food put together so happy for that!    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Hooray for brushing off flu! Where's your new pad?    
    
    
    Only just got C's room done but she has new wardrobe, king size bed and bureau. When I said done, I mean furniture is put together.    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler I'll keep fingers crossed for you!    
    
    
    @ypldn Yes!  I owe you money.  Will try to pay tonight or tomorrow (have money but need to find little machine for transfer)    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Me too!  The promised tomorrow between 10-1.  Any plans for NYE?    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler We usually go to the square at midnight which is always fun.  Unless I'm too tired ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn I know! And well thought out to get the transport tickets :-)    
    
    
    @LSpurdle You up for working on app on Thursday?  I mean I'm free whenever.    
    
    
    @travellingcoral Haha - lets not talk BF but the King size was because the double wasn't in stock.  Got it for same price!    
    
    
    Looks like Google Glass will be here tomorrow now.  Hope @smorgo and/or @mixedreality are up for the challenge ;-)    
    
    
    @w_stanley @GdnCulturePros I've asked for them to come to our DrinkingAboutMuseums …  HINT ;-)    
    
    
    @w_stanley It's the best I can do.  @GdnCulturePros    
    
    
    @travellingcoral I'm struggling that I've an 11year old that doesn't want pink and purple!    
    
    
    Fantastic! cc @bletchleypark @sciencemuseum RT @crave: Make your very own WWII Enigma Machine. http://cnet.co/1eR6prr  pic.twitter.com/lOMYfD1Azx    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science Ok, James outfit is brilliant!  It's like the body at @ExploreWellcome    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Brilliant - shall we meet somewhere or with skype/hangout?    
    
    
    @ypldn @inhandguides Yes - thank you so much! Well pay with cake :-)    
    
    
    @smorgo LMK when you're free then :-) @mixedreality    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Sounds perfect.  Where shall we go?    
    
    
    @LSpurdle How about Museum of Iron as there is free wifi and great cake!    
    
    
    @ypldn Absolutely! That and cupcakes ;-) @inhandguides    
    
    
    #xmaslectures @ri_science Naked Role rat! But not @TehNakedMoleRat ;-)    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Will find out the schedule for Thursday and get back to you.  Hopefully will have glass with me!    
    
    
    Thx! MT @kidsinmuseums: Our Social Media Mger @MarDixon ifeatured @Skype blog "Transform your Passions Into a Career" http://bit.ly/1bx4ArH     
    
    
    Would you want to know when you were going to die? #xmaslectures @ri_science    
    
    
    Thank you for another brilliant #xmaslectures @ri_science series! Hate having to wait another year for next one…    
    
    
    @M_Fkill Still not sure why I was chosen but honored :)    
    
    
    Congrats! RT @AnthonyHorowitz: At last! After weeks of restraint, I can tweet that I've been given an OBE. What a great end to the year.    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this rainy New Years Eve?    
    
    
    @gopaldass And Kevin?    
    
    
    For the record, when given the choice of @UPS or @Fedex - go with @UPS. Tuesday waiting for package since Friday with @UPS.    
    
    
    @skyfire747 Same here! What time is it there?    
    
    
    @gopaldass No one ever talks about Kevin anymore ;-) Any good plans for tonight or quiet night at home?    
    
    
    @JaneAudas When it's brought to you in bed? ;-)    
    
    
    @skyfire747 2014 will be here soon then ;-)    
    
    
    @gopaldass We usually go to the square with everyone but if it's raining we're going for quiet night with family. Either way is fun.    
    
    
    @gopaldass Very sharp but you need your social media information on there in contact also.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 @4fifty1 Happy New Years Eve guys!    
    
    
    @JaneAudas So true - I usually assume anyone but me is better.    
    
    
    Seeing a lot of 'End of Year' videos on social media. None seem to be able to handle my year, they get to end of October at best :-/    
    
    
    @gopaldass And I didn't have to nag.  I still want you to hook up with @SumoJim …    
    
    
    @4fifty1 @Chiddle84 Any good plans for the evening?    
    
    
    If you missed this yesterday:
The 40 funniest tweets of 2013  http://fw.to/8ongDBI     
    
    
    @4fifty1 @Chiddle84 Vienna?! When did that happen?  We might go to the town square if it stops raining. If not quiet celebration at home.    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Wish I had friends that pressured me to Vienna for NYE! @Chiddle84    
    
    
    Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday to you! Happy birthday dear @clairey_ross Happy birthday to you!  Hope you have a cake-filled day! xx    
    
    
    10 Best Inventions of the Year 2013 http://shar.es/9WkXg  I want a Motorola password pill but for it to be a food pill 
HT @SM_Learn    
    
    
    @TinctureOfMuse Great fun - and 2014 will be even better :-)    
    
    
    New Year's Honours: Lansbury and Keith lead women-dominated list http://bbc.in/KhCGdk  - WHOO HOO! Murder, She Wrote Angela Lansbury!!    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Me either but would have thought about it … ok, more dream but still. @4fifty1 @FeliceTherese    
    
    
    @janetedavis Such brilliant news for her!  Dame Lansbury has a lovely ring to it.    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 No @FedEx  would have been here yesterday.  @UPS promised Friday & still no package! Had to call 7 times so far.    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 @4fifty1 @Chiddle84 Great company too!    
    
    
    Farewell Sharknadoes, sequesters, and shutdowns. So long to 2013! #WhatAYear via @JibJab http://bit.ly/jibjab2013     
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Ha!! @dinoboy89 @4fifty1    
    
    
    THEY ARE HERE!!!  THEY ARE HERE THEY ARE HERE!    
    
    
    Setting up now but my @googleglass have arrived!! Think that makes me a #googleexplorer WOOT pic.twitter.com/15qqxff79O    
    
    
    @JudeHabib Will do - been waiting since Friday for the package to arrive.  Took FOREVER!  Hope you're well? Free Jan 13?    
    
    
    @ypldn I'm struggling to get on wifi … ;-)    
    
    
    @JudeHabib Drinks at Porterhouse for 6 again if you can make it?    
    
    
    @LSpurdle If I can get the wifi to work… #firststumble    
    
    
    @MuseumsLuton I'm hoping to see how they can be used in museums :-)    
    
    
    @telfordlive Thanks!  Oh @MuseumofLondon is one of the best museums out there.  Hard to find front door though ;-)    
    
    
    @mixedreality @smorgo I have them now!!!  I even managed to get them setup.  Eek! I'm in Shropshire next week if any good?    
    
    
    @CaroWallis Good for me! @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll @vickybarlo    
    
    
    @AboutLondon They are brilliant the real test will be how they are used in museums and art galleries :-) @googleglass    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer So far, I figured out how to take pictures and videos and managed to get on wifi. WOOT!    
    
    
    @mattdawhit Hey - baby steps here - I'm still trying to figure out how to get to Twitter with them ;-)    
    
    
    A bit late but Happy New Years Australia!    
    
    
    Interesting use of QRCode with #googleglass - it's how you get on wifi!    
    
    
    Make your Resolution to be more social! 

January 13 #DrinkingAboutMuseums UK / Open to All http://www.eventbrite.com/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173?aff=estw … via @eventbrite    
    
    
    Oh wow - just figured out how to take pictures without saying Ok Glass (bit slow but getting there) #googleexplorer    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick Absolutely!  You free Jan 13th?  Drinks at Porterhouse ...    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler We don't discriminate against the days ;-)    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Brilliant!  Look forward to meeting you!    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick It's the monthly Tweetup/ Drinks / meet people in London event :-) http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173?aff=estw …    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler No, now I remember!  I knew we met when I put that but still typed it. #idiot ;-) @CulturalPRconf    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Well looking forward to seeing you again in London :-))) Any plans for tonight?    
    
    
    @custard1980 Oh no!! *gasp*  Rice - you need rice!    
    
    
    Yep. RT @jackshoulder: Does 'Get a cat' count as a New Year Resolution?    
    
    
    These are fab! RT @TheDrum: 2013: A year in Google doodles  http://po.st/NSdscm     
    
    
    @alisonbarrow Nice save ;-) Have a very Happy New Year Alison!  x    
    
    
    I would have to say that 2013 was pretty awesome  Thank you to everyone who put up with my tweets and demands to show up at things. :-)    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers And to you Diana!  Have fun in London!    
    
    
    @readwithsandy Happy New Years Sandy!  xx    
    
    
    @mdoness  2014 will hopefully be even funnier :-)    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Staying home - might popped to square at midnight but not if it's raining. Being home w family special enough for me.    
    
    
    @miss_scribbler Special and rare ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn Here's hoping more fun and MORE CAKE for 2014 ;-)    
    
    
    I love these two. 
RT @SirPatStew 
Auld Lang Syne #gogodididonyc @TwoPlaysInRep pic.twitter.com/UhiBk7STEZ    
    
    
    @truongthomas New avatar!  Looking sharp!    
    
    
    @truongthomas @stevyncolgan If you're free on the 13th - another pub tweet up in organised.  HINT    
    
    
    @MSAconnect Happy New Year from @CultureThemes & myself :-) @CuratedObject @SaxonHenry @jolocktov @virginiacw150 @APS_Museum @OVO_Josh_    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan @truongthomas Brilliant! http://www.eventbrite.co.uk/e/january-13-drinkingaboutmuseums-uk-open-to-all-tickets-9947143173 … 

Happy New Years to you both! x    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick Hooray!  Be great to meet you!    
    
    
    @digitalmaverick I'm sure by the 13th there'll be more added to that list ;-) @w_stanley    
    
    
    If I ever went on @MastermindQuiz my specialist topic would be Muppets, Cake or Twitter. No, definitely Muppets.  Might ask for recipes.    
    
    
    @samatlounge Yummy!  Have a very Happy New Years Sam! xx    
    
    
    #Glassexplorer Just figured out how to use my phone as the wifi point.  WOOT!    
    
    
    @thomstanbury I'm slowly getting there :-)    
    
    
    C has figured out how to use @googleglass … pic.twitter.com/uJXcs8Y9sW    
    
    
    @VirginTrains Happy New Years!    
    
    
    @amandajp17 For me, to see how it can interact with museums. Innovatively, they are going to be game changers to tech …    
    
    
    Done MT @M_Fkill: Before you go out partying would love you to vote for my entry in @Atmel Bend your mind competition http://ow.ly/sbdPv     
    
    
    @clairey_ross Happy NYE to and lets kick some more butt in 2014 (I mean, you have the wedding and phd but kicking butt more important) xx    
    
    
    #GlassExplorer WOOT - just figured out how to make a vignette (and what that actually means).    
    
    
    @custard1980 We have Alan Carr on… but I'm not really watching.    
    
    
    Of course! RT @culturevultures: So shall I pour a G&T?    
    
    
    Non-scientific observation:  Twitter peeps don't do resolution but Facebook users do.    
    
    
    @MrCippy Thanks for the brilliant write up Five tips for a @googleglass newbie - just had mine delivered today and learning loads!    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 I'll catch ya ;-)    
    
    
    @ChristopherChew Happy New Year Chris!    
    
    
    @Gracie_Flower I do love FB for family and friends though :-)    
    
    
    Dear #MuseomixUK - what was your highlight of 2013?  Looking forward to @museomixuk 2014? Have a Happy New Year!    
    
    
    To all our @CultureThemes friends around the world, Have a Very Happy New Year!  Here is to a sharing 2014!  #museumselfie Jan 22    
    
    
    @courtlady And you Susan!  How are you celebrating tonight?    
    
    
    Any clever people out there know how to get Apple ID to point to the states when you're in the UK?    
    
    
    @CBeale1 That was a brilliant creation from Team 6.  Happy new Years Catherine! @museomixuk    
    
    
    @markmacleo I do :-) And managed to get them back off C tonight.    
    
    
    Do I have anyone in the states that would be willing to help me with iTunes app?    
    
    
    @erinfaye I'm trying to buy a Apple iTunes card but it keeps asking for an American address.  I want to download a free app available in US.    
    
    
    @erinfaye I have $ I can transfer tonight or if you trust me to let me use your acct for 2 minutes I'll love you forever. Understand if no!    
    
    
    @erinfaye Google Glass app only available in states :-/    
    
    
    @erinfaye You need to have an apple id that is based in US.  Can only create a new account with Credit card based in USA. Work around is    
    
    
    @erinfaye buy a gift card to create the account.  Pain in the butt!    
    
    
    Love this: 

'Tomorrow is the first blank page of a 365 page book.  Write a good one!'

#NYE    
    
    
    Thank you so much @erinfaye for helping me!! You're a star!    
    
    
    @mcachicago Happy New Years!  See you in 2014 :-) (Jan 22 #MuseumSelfie)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Happy New Year Chris!  Here is to an awesome 2014! xx    
    
    
    Happy New Years!!   (A bit late)    
    
    
    @haslemeremuseum @jbrunotte Here's to a Fabulous 2014 :-)    
    
    
    Never ever thought I'd spend my first 1/2 hour of 2014 Facetiming with my mom and we would be talking about wearable technology.  :-)    
    
    
    @Stu_arts :-)    
    
    
    @mickfortune She is now - she was fascinated! This is the same person who can't turn on a computer but loves her iPhone (she wants a pair)    
    
    
    @mizzlizwhizz And to you Liz! Here's to a fabulous 2014!  x @Stu_arts    
    
    
    @mickfortune We ready to take over the world in 2014? ;-)    
    
    
    #googleexplorer Was told to drain the battery - first 85% flew by - last 15% taking forever.    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there!  And a Very Happy New Year!! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this lovely New Years Day?    
    
    
    Wonder if @museomix was inspiration for game: face-off w museum security to take photos of exhibits http://kotaku.com/tourists-face-off-against-museum-guards-in-a-great-look-1492143680 … HT @dinoboy89    
    
    
    @NHM_London Happy New Years from your favorite follower :-)    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 Morning and Happy New Year! Q: do you know anyway to access a US iTunes acct for a free app?    
    
    
    @clairey_ross Interesting is a major understatement- your 2014 is going to kick ass!    
    
    
    @GillyHamer And same to you! Here's to a fabulous & healthy 2014! x    
    
    
    @OisinTheDeer Ha - all well here although I'm the only one awake. You guys are open today?    
    
    
    @OisinTheDeer Haha! Sounds like a fun night ;-)    
    
    
    'Isnt it nice to think that tomorrow is a new day with no mistakes in it yet.' LM Montgomery 

HT FB    
    
    
    @MuseumBee It isn't working :-( It is asking for a credit card with American addy. Just want to dl Google glass software :-/    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 That's my hope but didn't know if you came across this.    
    
    
    @MuseumBee No although both apple and iTunes are claiming it should be. I've a new email also but didn't work.    
    
    
    @MuseumBee Unless I'm doing something really stupid. Happy new Year btw :-))    
    
    
    @HornimanReviews That stupid bug kept me busy for 2 freaking years.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Coffee and bacon please!    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 @samatlounge Does it show what's happens to the ppl when not on alcohol & how they drive others mad? ;-)    
    
    
    Good Question! RT @Booktrust: Happy New Year! What was your favourite book of 2013?    
    
    
    @samatlounge @dinoboy89 I was brought up to believe Bloody Mary was traditional New Year Day breakfast requirement.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Get in! And non-instant coffee too! 2014 is looking up!    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 You're the Walrus? So is @HornimanWalrus #intro ;-) @DrHelenKara    
    
    
    @Redwoods1 Worth it by the sounds of it!    
    
    
    @HornimanMuseum @PaoloViscardi Swearing so in my timeline has started...    
    
    
    Murder, She Wrote!    
    
    
    Haven't been outside in a few days but assume it's very wet as received call from Shropshire Council warning me to move the livestock :-)    
    
    
    @justinewalshe No but it's because we're v close to the river :) Happy New Year!    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 Macy,Lizzie and the rabbits aren't amused when I try to move them. #lonejoke    
    
    
    Why we are friends :-) RT @dinoboy89: The gym is closed today - YES!!!    
    
    
    @culturevultures Brilliant here - you?    
    
    
    @justinewalshe Yep we have a cellar - was it number 4?    
    
    
    @acediscovery Totally worthy of that title too! Happy New Year!    
    
    
    @gopaldass @dinoboy89 I'm allergic to exercise. And me and my fat have a good relationship ;-) BTW do you two know each other? You should!    
    
    
    @gopaldass @dinoboy89 Adhay is all about digital identity and strategy & Eric is digital (publishing, games, museums)    
    
    
    @mikimoo9 Happy New Year- you're working today?!    
    
    
    @gopaldass @dinoboy89 That and I'm currently only wearing one contact - don't ask Abhay :-))    
    
    
    Start the New Year by getting involved  

Take a #MuseumSelfie & share on Jan 22nd w @CultureThemes
http://culturethemes.blogspot.com/2013/12/new-theme-museumselfie-january-22nd.html … 
PLS RT    
    
    
    @crimeficreader Happy New Year Rhian! All settled in?    
    
    
    @acediscovery Yes there are a few of us trying to go March 22 - you interested? And you're coming Jan 13th right?    
    
    
    @crimeficreader Lovely! Here's hoping the army isn't too demanding ;-)    
    
    
    Top tip :-) RT @mikimoo9: If you are visiting a museum today, enjoy! But do bear in mind the staff's aching heads... :-P    
    
    
    @fleming77 Never - just that the fireworks kept them up late ;-)    
    
    
    @acediscovery @PaoloViscardi @HornimanMuseum There is possibly a grant to help with that - they have outdoor gyms in Wolverhampton.    
    
    
    MT @PeerIndex Amongst trolls and 'fluff' - heartwarming content being shared on Twitter in 2013! http://bit.ly/1dQVaKr  /Crossover w other?    
    
    
    Apparently today is the day for 'specialist' 'gurus' & 'experts' to tell others how to live. What & how to share, along w how to be. Nice.    
    
    
    Just do what you are comfortable with & enjoy. Life is too short to try & please everyone. Besides, that is why there's an unfollow button.    
    
    
    @philkirby You might have read them Phil but you certainly didn't listen ;-) HNY!    
    
    
    @viperdudeuk I don't like auto upload as not everything needs to be online. I am old school like that.    
    
    
    @culturevultures We went Saturday and thought it was going to be mental- surprisingly calm!    
    
    
    @viperdudeuk It resides on an external hard drive.    
    
    
    @viperdudeuk Off site cloud isn't guaranteed either. Have had several people lose their data...    
    
    
    I love that we brought 2014 in Facetimeing with my mom in the states talking about wearable technology. pic.twitter.com/43G26FHTJf    
    
    
    @LizUK I'll be over in 20 minutes...    
    
    
    @dusty_jacket No pressure then ;-) NNY!    
    
    
    Trying to create an iTunes account that is based in the states but it keeps asking me for a credit card. Any ideas? pic.twitter.com/r61I4Ysv1t    
    
    
    @Dr_Biscuit I would if I had one…    
    
    
    @M_Fkill Only if they are from the states.  UK debit doesn't work. Should have No CC option but not appearing. :-/ @Dr_Biscuit    
    
    
    @ThomasMarzano I'm still loving them and learning what they can be used for.    
    
    
    @M_Fkill The killer is I only want to download a free app that is only available in the states. @Dr_Biscuit    
    
    
    @ThomasMarzano Yes - and my response is that these same 'tech overruling life' happened with Smartphones. We humans adjust ;-)    
    
    
    @ThomasMarzano Trade offs could be reworded as progression.  Things *will* be different but doesn't always have to be negative. :-)    
    
    
    @ThomasMarzano Agreed (think we're agreeing on both points).  This is why they are development stage.    
    
    
    @M_Fkill @Dr_Biscuit Genius!  I wasn't trying to d/l app first - it works!    
    
    
    @soundcube Just got it to work thanks to @M_Fkill - Thanks!    
    
    
    Whoo hoo! Thanks to @M_Fkill the itune issue is resolved!  :-)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon @ypldn We're trying not to move much here also although have to go see friend in a bit … think she'll mind PJs? ;-)    
    
    
    @lifeafterbooze Perhaps. @dinoboy89 @samatlounge    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Don't think the argument is with just vision - it's just that it's the most onbious with GG. Good luck. @ThomasMarzano    
    
    
    @ypldn Primark ;-) @AboutLondon    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design I don't think it is undervaluing other senses  - it's starting with the most pronounced. Business sense. @ThomasMarzano    
    
    
    @lumamendes Unfortunately that didn't want to work either - finally managed to fake it out with change of timezone, reboot & none cc :-) HNY    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design I'm not disagreeing but asking that you give it time to grow & not expect miracles in 2 weeks. @ThomasMarzano    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer I adore the @googleglass community.  Everyone is incredibly patient & answer questions like it's the first time asked :-)    
    
    
    @M_Fkill I haven't been out full stop but going today :-)    
    
    
    #Googleexplorer Found the easter egg :-))    
    
    
    @insidebooks @linda1966 @stujallen @aljallen @iamamro @thebooktower @RobAroundBooks Happy New Years Gang!  Here's to a fab 2014! xx    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Tonight I'm going to learn how to get the music to work.  Humming to myself just doesn't cut it.    
    
    
    @DeaBirkett Thanks for the lovely tweets today! x    
    
    
    @Louiestowell *crosses fingers*  Happy New Years!    
    
    
    @Louiestowell I'm sure it'll be fantastic!  Still learning to be #googleexplorer - trying to get music to work tonight.    
    
    
    @alisonbarrow Happy New Year Alison!  Thank you for the offer but you've already sent & I've already read & loved :-)    
    
    
    #googleexplorer Can't get the music to play.  Songs listed & music showing but no sound.    
    
    
    @M_Fkill Turned up.  And there is sound through the ear piece but can't hear music. Not even sure it's playing TBH    
    
    
    @mannyc How could it not love Goo Goo Dolls?    
    
    
    *watches as Twitter explodes with #SherlockLives #Sherlock and @BBCOne tweets*    
    
    
    HAHAHAHA For all those saying  the opening was, er crap, did you really think they would want us to believe that? #SherlockLives    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Not at all - it's not for everyone.  Happy new Years! Did you have a good evening?    
    
    
    @gavreads I agree - gorgeous cover!    
    
    
    Ha! RT @BBCOne: #SherlockLives pic.twitter.com/3uchvtLqAW    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer - Restarting Music Manager seems to have worked.  Made me jump a freaking mile when it started.    
    
    
    Well played with the hashtag @BBCOne #SherlockLives    
    
    
    Couldn't resist ;-) RT @FlossieTeacake: “Online blog”? There are other kinds? #pedant #sorry #Sherlock    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Doing a Factory reset - hope it solves the sending issues.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Woot! Factory reset answered a lot of little issues I've been having. Music, sending emails & taking pictures so easy now!    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Pretty much the same here - other than mom calling at midnight scarring the hell out of all of us.  2014 will be good though :-)    
    
    
    @sophontrack Is @Rigsbyhatstand with you?  He's staying at @COMOHotels tonight too!  Lucky Ducks! HNY!    
    
    
    @sophontrack Well I'm sure @Rigsbyhatstand is ok without being invited to the Name that Robe game (although I cld be wrong) ;) @COMOHotels    
    
    
    @sophontrack I was going to try and let that one go but did smile ;-) @Rigsbyhatstand @COMOHotels    
    
    
    @M_Fkill I can't even thread a needle so you're doing brilliantly compared to me!    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this lovely Thursday?    
    
    
    @mobilejpop That is fantastic! Look forward to reading them (might have to send link please) HNY! @QueensMuseum @sofiadejuan @janelkay    
    
    
    @SkagensMuseum Hope it goes smoothy today :-)    
    
    
    Huh. MT @JDLiteracyTrust21% of yp embarrassed to be seen reading, backing up Ruth Rendell's fears reading is becoming "minority activity"    
    
    
    @COMOHotels The robes were so comfy when we were there! Jealous of @Rigsbyhatstand @sophontrack :-) (And the puns!)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Could be worse, could be What Did the Fox say ;-)    
    
    
    @Rigsbyhatstand Why check out now?! My god we waiting until 11:59. @sophontrack    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I'm sending this from Google glass did you get it    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Managed to get emails to send last night.  Working on sending tweets today.  And music now working. Hooray!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon WHOO HOO!! Had to do a factory reset last night but got things working now.    
    
    
    @4fifty1 I did and I'm freaking loving it!  Happy New Year Chris!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I'm loving being a #GoogleExplorer the possibilities are endless :-) @COMOHotels @googleglass    
    
    
    @Louiestowell @4fifty1 Been asked how Glass could help/work in museums. Only way to find out is to get a pair and play with them. :)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Haha no porn and there are filters thankfully! And I've been taking notes of my experience but only got them NYE. @Louiestowell    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Haven't been out of the house with them yet but will do. @Louiestowell    
    
    
    'Tel Nona, Audience Version', Jerusalem: http://youtu.be/2zLpoYKLSLg  #participatory @museomixuk HT @museumpaige    
    
    
    Can anyone suggest a few good RSS new feeds for digital, museum, innovation? (Please/thank you)    
    
    
    @acediscovery Can you send a link please? Or am I being stupid not seeing it on the site?    
    
    
    @mardixon Sending a test tweet    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers @Longhouses1 Woot!    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Woot - now RSS feed is working!    
    
    
    Duxford aircraft museum closed until further notice http://bbc.in/18ZduDP     
    
    
    This is brilliant! 
A Kids' Book Where Every Character Can Be 3-D Printed http://www.wired.com/design/2013/12/characters-come-alive-in-this-3-d-printable-book/ … #3D #kids #boos    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Ha! Just learning how to play a game and winked.  Glass promptly took a picture. :-)    
    
    
    I'm very sad to hear it also @AvoncroftMuseum - and am wondering if there is anything Twitter can do to help Duxford cc @I_W_M    
    
    
    Being a #GoogleExplorer in the UK (What it's like to own Google Glass)  http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2014/01/being-a-googleexplorer-in-the-uk-what-its-like-to-own-google-glass/ …    
    
    
    @johnshevlin Can't tweet from it yet but can reply :-)    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Woot! Managed to send a picture to Facebook now.  That's Twitter and Facebook completed ;-) Have noticed a bit of delay.    
    
    
    @sulibreaks Happy New Year Suli!    
    
    
    Darn you Twitter - Why didn't you tell me Columbo is on?    
    
    
    Wow - 76% traffic via mobile devices. MT @dinoboy89 John Lewis says majority of online sales shopping came via mobile http://wallblog.co.uk/2014/01/02/john-lewis-expects-the-majority-of-online-shopping-to-be-mobile/ …    
    
    
    @mannyc I know!  My fault as didn't set up Google now for it ;-P    
    
    
    @fleming77 Yes, of course as it's mobile devices. Still large impact. @dinoboy89    
    
    
    @johnshevlin Yup - just announced that rx glasses will be available soon :-)    
    
    
    @johnshevlin yes they haven't forgot about you    
    
    
    @johnshevlin PS that last tweet was sent from Glass :-)    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer: Eric Schmidt's Big Predictions for 2014 Read aloud.  So cool! Google missed Social media trend but on Mobile trend.    
    
    
    Good luck! RT @JDLiteracyTrust: On Sky TV News at 5.30 talking about children's reading.    
    
    
    @custard1980 Ha - my brain is small and managing.  I'm not developing anything but using it is pretty cool :-)    
    
    
    @mattdawhit Thanks! They are a bit fun right now but haven't used them in museums yet (the real test)    
    
    
    @DrRichJohnston Don't you have to hit it's nose or something?  Wait, maybe not.  Move along.    
    
    
    Being a #GoogleExplorer in the UK (What it's like to own Google Glass)  http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2014/01/being-a-googleexplorer-in-the-uk-what-its-like-to-own-google-glass/ …    
    
    
    @mattdawhit No stupid questions!  Yes, GPS built in.  In theory, Iron Insight app could be modified to work on them.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer RT @jafurtado: OK, Glass, Find a Killer App, By Rachel Metz /MIT Technology Review http://www.technologyreview.com/news/522586/ok-glass-find-a-killer-app/ …    
    
    
    @mattdawhit Sorry - lost internet on GG.  No, recognition is to anyone (which is good as C was the first one to use them!)    
    
    
    @mattdawhit Of course!    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia I think there is a scope for it.  Right now, we're at baby steps - things are clunky. @AboutLondon @googleglass    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia But look how far smartphones have come in such a short span. @AboutLondon @googleglass    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia Where are you based?    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia Stupid, just read you're in Leeds.  I don't get there much but if you're coming to London, lmk. I'm in Shropshire :-)    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia I'm in Newcastle for June if that helps.  And I'm in London once a month at least (sure @AboutLondon feels it's more!)    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia PS, if you're a geek, you would have loved @museomixuk that I ran in November.    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia Sure am!  Go every year to @MuseumNext :-) I'm running @MuseumCamp there too.    
    
    
    @BOB_MDO Did we?  Would love a pic if possible? Thanks! @MarchesNetwork @Lspurdle @museum_news    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia Absolutely! I'm following now.  Just be warned, I tweet A LOT! (Usually about cake).    
    
    
    @beelocalmedia But of course!  I know @clandestinecake and we follow each other :-)    
    
    
    +1 RT @pewinternet: 45% of internet users age 65 or older now use Facebook, up from 35% who did so in late 2012. http://pewrsr.ch/19xawqC     
    
    
    @mattdawhit I'm sending this tweet vs glass    
    
    
    #Googleexplorer MT @mattdawhit: @MarDixon Also this is really cool see the sent using pic.twitter.com/UYrjlYwzmy    
    
    
    @gopaldass Oh yes - I 'know' @kajsahartig already but don't believe we have ever met yet.  When in Feb? :-)    
    
    
    @gopaldass London is easier for me to get to #selfish @kajsahartig    
    
    
    @courtlady :-) Too sweet x    
    
    
    @kajsahartig Would be lovely to meet promptly in Feb.  @gopaldass lmk some dates when you can.    
    
    
    @clandestinecake *waves*  :-) @beelocalmedia    
    
    
    Fun day working with @LSpurdle on @MuseumCamp funding app.  We're hoping to tour this year!    
    
    
    Speaking of @MuseumCamp -both @MuseumCamp & @museomixuk are mentioned in Museum Journal (related to unconferences). :-)    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Thank you!  I actually forgot that I chatted to them but yay good advert for @MuseumCamp and  @museomixuk :-)    
    
    
    @Madlena_P I think this month.  It's online too but you have to be a member, Happy New Year BTW    
    
    
    @10_penelope Would love to but need to look at different funding for that :-/ @LSpurdle @MuseumCamp @GiraffeDefender    
    
    
    @M_Fkill Sporadic.  I'm fully charing it tonight and leaving it on (I shut it off last night). Then I'm going to charge again and run it tom    
    
    
    .@mia_out I think smartphones already killed that.  I see a lot of potential for Glass.    
    
    
    @mia_out So I presume you don't like photos in public venues also? Shame that glass owners are prejudged.    
    
    
    @skirrid Kermit is staying for a bit :)    
    
    
    @mia_out Well it seems specific to Glass as you don't expect venues to request smartphones to be handed in at the door.    
    
    
    @mia_out No - both outcomes are the same.  People thought it odd to hold a phone up to take a picture 5 years ago.    
    
    
    @mia_out Oh I 'get' your point, I just don't agree.  It's a bit extreme to the reality of Glass use.    
    
    
    @mia_out If ppl want to take a pic, they will regardless of medium.    
    
    
    @mia_out Assuming that everyone with Glass is out to take pictures of you also doesn't hold much weight. Pics are only part of their use.    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Evening Stevyn! How are you tonight?    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Very well here. Didn't notice you as you're back to your old avatar ;-)    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this fabulous Friday?    
    
    
    @LauraAustinNow It's a sign. ;)    
    
    
    Interesting RT  @BenedictEvans: Desktop, laptop and tablet sales since 1995. Pretty clear trend. pic.twitter.com/gHOWchDTwW    
    
    
    Cheerful topic on #bbcbreakfast - post Christmas divorce! :-/    
    
    
    @samatlounge I just watch you, @dinoboy89, @JustineSolomons et al to keep up-to-date :-)    
    
    
    @zakmensah 'Traditional' business = those with network people afraid of change (e.g. 2007 was too much of a change for them)    
    
    
    @AllEqualsOneArt Hello - where are you based? Google is telling me Thailand?    
    
    
    Incredibly humbled by friends dignified reaction to yet another curve ball thrown their way.    
    
    
    @zakmensah Oh god, remember them (or are they still used?). Signing in took FOREVER with all the 'paths' that had to load.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 I once used C's conditioner. I didn't think my hair could get any bigger with body but apparently I was wrong.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Not when you have hair like mine. I spend money on wax trying to tame it. Hairdresser *always* mentions 'how much hair' I have.    
    
    
    One item marked off the fictitious to do list already this morning.  Next up, train tickets for January.    
    
    
    @museummedia Start the New Year off sharing!  

Take a #MuseumSelfie & share on Jan 22nd w @CultureThemes
http://culturethemes.blogspot.com/2013/12/new-theme-museumselfie-january-22nd.html … 
PLS RT    
    
    
    Fantastic! RT @palazzomadamato: @MarDixon @museummedia @CultureThemes on my calendar! :) #MuseumSelfie Jan22nd    
    
    
    #BBCBreakfast Gotta love Dambusters March  - so upbeat!    
    
    
    @museummedia Thank you :-)    
    
    
    #BBCBreakfast - These guys are too funny! 'This is like being with your family - do you remember….?' 'No!'    
    
    
    @museummedia And to you! x    
    
    
    @CaroWallis either - my email mar @mardixon dotty com :-) @vickybarlo @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll    
    
    
    @christine__gau Fantastic - thank you! @museummedia @CultureThemes    
    
    
    @vlbartlett Loved them! Put a smile on my face.    
    
    
    Darn it - I want to order train tickets but my wallet is on the other side of the room.  #warmduvet    
    
    
    Oh cool @peterjamesUK is on #BBCBreakfast now.    
    
    
    @culturevultures Hooray!    
    
    
    #SherlockLives vs Londoners tube knowledge MT @hotelinlondon: Sherlock and the Curse of the Tube Pedants: … http://bit.ly/19OvRqe  #london    
    
    
    @skyfire747 I've been trying!  I'm waiting until C is awake then going to ask her ;-)    
    
    
    @BHaughwout We normally have that problem with US shows but have to admit, lately UK have been kicking butt!  Why are you awake?!    
    
    
    @aboutlondon RT @zakmensah: Google chrome book yes or no? If you can't get basic software on your work pc ....    
    
    
    @JamesJDenny Had to use my legs in the end.  Just can't get the staff these days ;-)    
    
    
    @mizzlizwhizz The guy is a incredibly dangerous.  no clue why he still has power to make such dramatic changes.He seems to answer to no one.    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Are you in Leicester on the 18th?  I'm working on a project in snibton but will have a spare hour waiting for train -coffee?    
    
    
    Museums + Heritage Awards 2014 Culture Pros Pick – have your say http://gu.com/p/3yfzf/tw  via @guardian    
    
    
    Trying to organize trains but have to wait for people to get back to work on 6th.  A+ for my effort though #cake    
    
    
    @Madlena_P No worries!  Just thought I'd throw it out there.    
    
    
    :-) #lovelibraries RT @ShortList: Best library ad ever pic.twitter.com/wsmQKSCywn    
    
    
    +1 RT @amhistorymuseum: Today in 1977: Apple Computer is incorporated. An Apple II from that year: http://ow.ly/scKlR     
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer I'm playing with Bluetooth.  iPhone rang and had notice on Glass when I picked up. Not sure if I could answer from Glass.    
    
    
    Great! RT @TheDrum: 60 years of children's TV classics celebrated in new @RoyalMail Special Stamp collection http://po.st/jNNqut  #puppets    
    
    
    @mardixon #googleexplorer    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Oh thank you. I know there is another one on 28th but not sure if I can make it yet. Where is that one held?    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Me too - have an author in Shropshire for @PopUpFestival but not sure if I'm needed yet.    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design LMK what you find out please.  What wearable tech are you playing with? So good i.e. of Glass for deaf ppl.    
    
    
    :-) Nosy Crow’s market share will continue to grow. MT @NosyCrow:  Predictions for Children's Books in 2014 http://nosycrow.com/2404     
    
    
    @Acuity_Design I've only played once with smart watches so can't say much there.  Think WT is progressive which has to be good.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Can't seem to be able to make a phone. Tells me call can't be made available on this network. (American issue?)    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Why annoying? As Glass is still beta they are very open to suggestions ... pic.twitter.com/nWf8APGdvB    
    
    
    #GoogleExxplorer An hour gone and still waiting for picture to show on Facebook.    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design There is still built in stereo on the touchpad.    
    
    
    @the_bookette Congratulations Aunt Becky! :-)    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Altough as mentioned on my post, it's best to have ear piece in unless you want to be mocked by 11 yo on your music.    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design pic.twitter.com/pYgfQfH435    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design The touchpad is actually on the other side of the left part. That is the inside.    
    
    
    Something I've been putting off of awhile was actually a lot easier than I thought - Hooray! #probablywrong #dontcare    
    
    
    #googleexplorer Although Bluetooth turned off, received this option when making call on iPhone. Cool! pic.twitter.com/0bTUAcGEW3    
    
    
    @4fifty1 And how are you today - and where are you today? x    
    
    
    @skyfire747 I know - another picture did go through though.  Weird.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Sent two pictures to Facebook via Glass. One to Only Me which worked but one to Friends doesn't seem to work. #BitBucket    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Lucky you! Bring sunshine when you come back please. How long will you be in London?    
    
    
    @jbrunotte Thank you Jorn! Happy #FF to you :-) @SumoJim @KarinHindsbo    
    
    
    @4fifty1 How many hats do you own? ;-) #jealous    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Will Wearable Technology Fail? http://intersog.com/blog/Will-Wearable-Technology-Fail …    
    
    
    @skyfire747 Not sure- still have a lot to play and learn :-)    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer 3pm and have drained battery to 0.  Now charging to see how long it takes.    
    
    
    Might be of use?
Snow, Social Media and Museums  http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2013/01/snow-and-social-media-and-museums/ …    
    
    
    @develop3d Pong and Merlin for me.    
    
    
    #snowday Snow, Social Media and Museums  http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2013/01/snow-and-social-media-and-museums/ … 

(RT as forgot tag)    
    
    
    @CaroleSouter @pubstrat @mrdaveturner Absolutely confirm. No matter what the question, cake is always the answer.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Charge complete! 2 hours total from 0-100%.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Google Directions work good. Warning of driving safety appeared immediately.    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Lovely.  Don't forget about Jim Henson when you have time :-)    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan And Number 1 is to come to the pub on the 13th?  You're so good ;-)    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan ;-) x    
    
    
    @alistardean Of course not - that would mean I was out in the real world and that ain't happening until Sunday.    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Since full charge at 5pm, I used Google Direction for 10 minutes then left Glass alone for 2 hours: battery is 78%.    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone tonight?    
    
    
    @Rantdog Running or cold?    
    
    
    @hannah_would Thank you! @RyanKilleen @rsalmonuk @LukeRobertMason @krissyxkd @mattcaines    
    
    
    Another #snowday tomorrow?  Here is a simple post to help:

Snow, Social Media and #Museums http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2013/01/snow-and-social-media-and-museums/ …    
    
    
    @mardixon #GoogleExplorer tweet to reply to    
    
    
    Interesting - when I tweet myself  (researching Glass) it doesn't show in my Interactions.    
    
    
    @mickfortune Where you heading?    
    
    
    @mickfortune Nice!  I'm not jealous one bit. Not at all. *unfollows*    
    
    
    @mickfortune Haha!  Would love to - Portugal has lovely history and museums!    
    
    
    @mickfortune I did a project with Gulbenkian - gorgeous art taller and museum. Have you been to their library?    
    
    
    @mickfortune Haven't been there - my trips were strictly business so museums, orchestra at night and home.  Let me ask.    
    
    
    Any recommendations for  @mickfortune who is planning on visits to Seville and Tangier? #museums    
    
    
    @amandajp17 Same here although I sort of went back 2 days ago (but working in Pjs)    
    
    
    What fun! RT @drlucyrogers: More fun stuff from @themadmuseum today pic.twitter.com/raShzNHLHX    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design Yes, that was the first picture I sent you. They aren't required but are if you want  privacy ;-) @seeingwithsound    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design No no, my fault.  I didn't know it's name and the box was nearby for me to look at (in other words, I was lazy!)    
    
    
    @Acuity_Design But Glass comes with them although I find them to be a bit of a pain (but I've not been out of the house with them yet).    
    
    
    @CaroWallis Done J17. @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll @vickybarlo    
    
    
        
    
    
    @MuseumCamp test tweet tweet tweet    
    
    
    @skirrid #googleforletmetrythis    
    
    
    @mdoness I'm testing Google Glass tweeting :-) #GoogleExplorer @MuseumCamp    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Just demo'd Glass to 3 11yos. Interest questions: Is it a phone? Where are the lens? How to share pictures?    
    
    
    @CaroWallis I wear contacts and glasses occasion (not as often as eye doc would like!). Rx glasses are going to be available soon!    
    
    
    @nealstimler Oh they figured that out straight away. It was more a snachat/FB question about sharing. :-) @DarrenMilligan    
    
    
    @nealstimler C's been playing with them a bit since I got them but they were new to her friends so good to let them 'play'. @DarrenMilligan    
    
    
    @CultureShockArt That wasn't me, I haven't been to @theMADmuseum … YET :-)    
    
    
    @nealstimler 5 days ago and been loving 'playing' with them. Being a #GoogleExplorer in the UK   http://www.mardixon.com/wordpress/2014/01/being-a-googleexplorer-in-the-uk-what-its-like-to-own-google-glass/ … @DarrenMilligan    
    
    
    @CultureShockArt I haven't been out to a museum yet but once the holidays are over my schedule will have a lot of Glass pics #Googleexplorer    
    
    
    Hi @mobilistar - going to #twitintro you to @mixedreality as you both are into Augmented Reality ... and stuff :-)    
    
    
    @nealstimler The real fun begins when the holidays are over and I start using them in museums and with groups. :-) @DarrenMilligan    
    
    
    @nealstimler How have you found them?    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer 10pm and battery low indicator on.  Not bad since last charge was at 5pm. Bluetooth/wifi on but idle.    
    
    
    @nealstimler Fantastic! So I'll handle UK, you handle US and we'll share/compare along the way :-)    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Hooray! @kimbiddulph @CaroWallis @NylonsAndAll    
    
    
    @nealstimler Have you had many people afraid you're videoing and/or taking pictures of them? #GoogleExplorer    
    
    
    Let the over analyzing begin!  RT @Gizmodo: Digital music sales just dropped for the first time since iTunes http://gizmo.do/zl3kYY0     
    
    
    Haha!  Glad I'm not the only one. RT @jackschofield: How to burn 800 calories in just 30 minutes…. pic.twitter.com/oMXAVb5ZWJ    
    
    
    @CaroWallis And Angela ;-) @vickybarlo @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll @Me_MarkTindle @newjustine    
    
    
    @Madlena_P Brilliant new about @IronInsight (and yay @museomixuk and @MuseumCamp!)    
    
    
    @SparkyRobot Wait what? You're not a robot?! Damn it.    
    
    
    @SparkyRobot ;-)    
    
    
    Done MT @Swissss Ok twitter, my lad's Lego video needs 150 votes in the next 30 minutes.  I need some big-hitting RTs http://shell.stackla.com/c/5288ccfd145cba211a000035 …    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone today?    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer #Battery full. Glass on.    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Haha - I'm just trying to track battery life and silly stuff like that.  How are you today?    
    
    
    @GentleChaos I can still see you ;-)    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said Brilliant!  For you that usually means you went for a run or ate lettuce or something?    
    
    
    @skyfire747 I've been tweeting from it!  But running another test right now :-)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Video uploads to Youtube, searches on Google are my main ones today.  Maybe see how 11yo use them.    
    
    
    @Ioan_Said Well thank Goodness for that! ;-)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 this tweet is from the glass    
    
    
    @stujallen Very well - how is 2014 for you so far?    
    
    
    @stujallen excellent for me so far been playing with Google glass    
    
    
        
    
    
    @4fifty1 still trying to figure out how to get punctuation to work    
    
    
    @stujallen #googlestoreyestheyarefun    
    
    
        
    
    
        
    
    
    Just realized my #GoogleExplorer Wifi connection went *really* weak due to 3 11yo with multiple devices all logging in right now.  *sigh*    
    
    
    @SmilyLibrarian @timbuckteeth Thank you-  I've read that before. It's interesting that some have pushed Glass aside before the fun started.    
    
    
    Anyone? RT @playbythebook: @MarDixon do you know of any online only museums which kids can contribute to / be a curator in?    
    
    
    @EdintheClouds Hello! Nice to 'meet' you :-)    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 @samatlounge WTH Totally jealous!! @Guggenheim    
    
    
    @dinoboy89 @samatlounge I mean, whatever. Who cares. 

*bottom lip quiver*    
    
    
    @ypldn *glares* South London?    
    
    
    @EdintheClouds No no, only just now via twitter :-) What is a google trainer? Interested to hear more.    
    
    
    @samatlounge @dinoboy89 Ha - I can get directions there ;-) #stilllearning    
    
    
    @paulescaped V well here - enjoying last few days home before madness starts again. Good holiday?    
    
    
    @Rigsbyhatstand @ypldn Not at all! I don't even know where South London is! ;-)    
    
    
    @paulescaped Sure is - on the 11th!  (Sorry, wifi went down then got distracted!)    
    
    
    @SmilyLibrarian That's the example I provide - no one predicted the way Smartphones /ipads would change things but mocked them :-)    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Just posted a picture to Facebook and a different one to Twitter via Glass.  13.07    
    
    
    Only managed 6 *hangs head in shame* RT @Londonist: Tried our mystery museum quiz? The answers are now available http://bit.ly/1dZnZ7I     
    
    
    Woot! RT @Londonist: @MarDixon That's the best score we've heard so far, though, so well done. It was fiendish.    
    
    
    @Patrick_Ness Walking?  You must be in a city ;-)    
    
    
    this is a new book I got #throughglass pic.twitter.com/27JPfwxcxe    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Took 27 minutes for tweet RT @MarDixon: this is a new book I got #throughglass pic.twitter.com/27JPfwxcxe    
    
    
        
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Plugged charger is due to low battery indicator. 4.5 hours with pretty active use/wifi. Pics, tweet, FB, music used.    
    
    
    One week today! #MuseomixUK January MeetUp at @urbancoffeeco http://www.eventbrite.com/e/museomixuk-january-meetup-tickets-9483484357?aff=estw … via @eventbrite    
    
    
        
    
    
    @SmilyLibrarian 3500 miles and a big ocean helps.    
    
    
    makers corner #throughglass pic.twitter.com/R8Io3oURvF    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer RT @MarDixon: makers corner #throughglass pic.twitter.com/R8Io3oURvF    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer that last tweet took less than a minute to appear. Just noticed Glass automatically put #throughglass on tweet.    
    
    
    @M_Fkill Depends on if one of them was available on +1 ;-)    
    
    
    OMG Diagnosis Murder is on after Columbo!!    
    
    
    Shut your face. RT @davidmaybury: @MarDixon 1994 called. It wants it's television back!    
    
    
    @davidmaybury Roseanne actually :-P    
    
    
    @jamiezoob Amen!  I thought about doing something - even managed to get out of PJs but not now.  :-)    
    
    
    @CaroWallis Well there are TWO eps on Channel 5 :-)    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer 
Looking through my crystal (Glass) ball http://wp.me/pmlRJ-ED  via @aribadler    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer A lot of valid points in that last tweet.  Glass might not be the answer but it’s certainly a game changer.    
    
    
    @RobAroundBooks Apparently, a smart contact lens is already being worked on ;-)    
    
    
    @RobAroundBooks Haha!  But please remember, we control the technology :-) Wearable Tech can have a great benefit for many issues.    
    
    
    +1 RT @jackandraka: . @WendyDrexler @MindShiftKQED @cathycavanaugh part 3 : to create and innovate; to work in diverse cross-cultural teams;    
    
    
    @jackandraka Happy New Year Jack!    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone tonight?    
    
    
    @donundeen Someone w Google Glass was not to have them in the Met galleries. What a terrible decision. Can you find out why please?    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Seem to be able to send picture to Facebook quicker w/o caption (although still missing from timeline).    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer #ThroughGlass WHOO HOO! Uploaded a video directly to Youtube.    
    
    
    @GreyTrilby Sounds like a painful experience.    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan It’s not already? ;-) x    
    
    
        
    
    
    YAY! RT @AboutLondon: Received a certificate from @GiveBloodNHS today as I can’t give blood for a while. #veryproud pic.twitter.com/Sq2hqTFOC0    
    
    
    @AboutLondon That was incredibly sweet of @GiveBloodNHS!  I’m sure you’ll be able to donate again soon. x    
    
    
    @theMADmuseum @drlucyrogers *butts in* Love this tweet. Dr Lucy is why I’m following you now!    
    
    
        
    
    
    Love this! RT @Distractify: Unknown artist pasted the Photoshop toolbar on several posters of H & M in Germany. pic.twitter.com/J4aY8Lfybi    
    
    
    Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dreams when you get there! xx (Silly Internet not working tonight)    
    
    
    Good morning! How is everyone this lovely Sunday?    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer It’s funny how much I’ve been using G+ since getting Glass.  NOW I’m starting to ‘get it’.    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Cold or just depressed about going back to work tomorrow?    
    
    
        
    
    
    Love this! RT @Distractify Unknown artist pasted the Photoshop toolbar on several posters of H & M in Germany. pic.twitter.com/J4aY8Lfybi    
    
    
    @zakmensah I wear contacts but *always* have sunglasses with me.  As there are no lenses, it’s just a band really.    
    
    
    @playbythebook I tweeted one from @BrooklynKids last night (check my account & @Kidsinmuseums)  @EdintheClouds    
    
    
        
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer 

Can you guys tell me what sort of things you’re interested in knowing about Glass?  Want to share relevant stuff.    
    
    
    @playbythebook I’m sure if kids have used it yet but it is certainly a good way to introduce them to curating a collection.    
    
    
    @Louiestowell I’m working on another post so will try and answer these. How was the states?    
    
    
    @Louiestowell Visit court of law?  Not many ‘visit’ ;-)    
    
    
    @Longhouses1 It’s wearable technology that allows you to ‘do’ things hands free.  The ‘what’ it can do is the big question.    
    
    
    @Louiestowell I’m kidding, I’ve a family with colourful background.  Courts are visited for another reason.    
    
    
    The ten most important buildings in England   http://fw.to/aPlhi6c  - 

Woot! @flax_maltings is one of them #Shropshire    
    
    
    @RobAroundBooks Not unfriend-ing :-) I think you concentrated on the negatives and failed to mention any of the positives. Like us meeting.    
    
    
    Ha! Also ‘I’m not going to’ RT @CorrinneBurns: Is anyone playing Cameron Bingo? I got "Work Hard and Get On" and "Pensioners Are Exempt".    
    
    
    @RobAroundBooks That was almost a ‘I have to add this disclaimer’ rather than point out why ppl spend time w tech. ;-)    
    
    
        
    
    
    @DavidMentiply @TanjaPraske You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#GoogleExplorer @MarDixon Tweets Jan 3 & 4 2014" http://sfy.co/tMK5     
    
    
    @4fifty1 You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#GoogleExplorer @MarDixon Tweets Jan 3 & 4 2014" http://sfy.co/tMK5     
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer @MarDixon Tweets Jan 3 & 4 2014 http://sfy.co/tMK5  #storify #googleexplorer #throughglass    
    
    
    @Louiestowell @AboutLondon You've been quoted in my #Storify story "#GoogleExplorer @MarDixon Tweets Jan 3 & 4 2014" http://sfy.co/tMK5     
    
    
        
    
    
    @AboutLondon And I've not even been out of the house with them :-)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Which reminds me - 13/14, Feb 4/5, 19/20 so far ;-) x    
    
    
    @MarDixon Seriously, do you ever sleep? ;-)    
    
    
    Home today? Why not have the kids curate their own collection with Google Cultural Institute http://www.google.com/culturalinstitute/home …  HT @EdintheClouds    
    
    
    *whew* Internet is back.    
    
    
    :-) RT @BBCOne: Obviously, we’ve already got out hat for the wedding. #Sherlock http://twitter.com/BBCOne/status/419800312082608129/photo/1pic.twitter.com/1xnMuCiGBe     
    
    
        
    
    
    Me to C:  Stop growing up.
C (hugs me): Stop getting old and cranky. 

HA!    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Exactly.  Won’t let it slip again. Was travelling a lot last year. @kidsinmuseums    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Is there a vegetarian option? ;-)    
    
    
    Jane Henson - NY Times The Lives They Lived

http://www.nytimes.com/news/the-lives-they-lived/2013/12/21/jane-henson/?_r=0 …    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer Charged battery to full last night and left Glass ‘on’ but idle util 12.27 and battery at 11%.    
    
    
    It’s amazing! RT @AnneMHayes: I need to get to @BM_AG to see this exhibition. Looks brilliant! #Photorealism    
    
    
        
    
    
    @Chiddle84 True - but you have to remember these are beta. iPhone batteries weren’t brilliant at first either ;-)  LOVE THE HAIR!    
    
    
    So today we’re learning about Henri Matisse as a poster needs to be made.    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan I was kidding!  I don’t do vegetables - bring on the rabbit and bacon! ;-)    
    
    
    @viperdudeuk I’ve addressed battery in this post: http://www.mardixon.com/  - it is depending on what you do/how long it last. 4 hr avg.    
    
    
    I just had to give my phone to C to add names to Instagram to me.  #feelsold    
    
    
    #GoogleExplorer What sort of things are you interested in knowing about Glass?  I want to share relevant information.    
    
    
        
    
    
    @viperdudeuk PS I’m answering in a bit more in-depth in the article.    
    
    
    Well this can’t be right… pic.twitter.com/PMxLNtkXfO    
    
    
    @archaeologyman You have the internet so it can't be all bad ;-) Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Nice!  I mean not the hiding from Christmas but Marrakech sounds nice.  Couldn't hide in London? Or Shropshire?    
    
    
    @4fifty1 @shelter £260 I think.    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Wooo - where did got for Christmas?    
    
    
    @mredwards Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Nice!  Visiting family or just going away for Christmas?    
    
    
    @crimeficreader Merry Christmas Rhian! Hope you've been well?    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Yup - and I had to laugh at the heat tweet as my parents have a wood stove which makes you not able to breathe after 1/2 hour.    
    
    
    @crimeficreader New home?  Still Wales?  We're all well here. Spending Christmas home thankfully.    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Haha! It's when they decide that they can't afford the heating bill but yet will be able to chop wood at 90.    
    
    
    @vickybarlo Well I hope it's a nice one for you too! x    
    
    
    Looking forward to chatting with my family tomorrow although I hate when we get passed around with 'So & so is here, remember them?'    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Awww sweet - you have the grandkids tonight? How freaking magical is that?    
    
    
    @stevyncolgan Statistically the average time is 5.15 am. Ho ho ho :-)) Merry Christmas Mr Colgan. xx    
    
    
    @LSpurdle Yep. One year I talked to someone who I thought was a nephew for 10 minutes before I realised it was a neighbor!    
    
    
    @LSpurdle This year we have a secret weapon.  FaceTime with bad wifi.  We get annoyed 'Opps, so sorry! Wifi is bad'.    
    
    
    Thanks @Just_Will_I_am for starting the #royalpardon for Alan #Turing! @AlanTuringYear    
    
    
    @DianaPitchers Congrats :-)    
    
    
    @SBarryCooper @Just_Will_I_am @AlanTuringYear Absolutely.  And just to be sure - everyone here knows @Dr_Black & @bletchleypark right?    
    
    
    Woot! A delivery from states is in the UK.  I'll have to wait until Friday but at least it's getting closer :)    
    
    
    @ge0_ff Hooray!    
    
    
    @drlucyrogers I still have to wait until Friday and then figure out how to use them but still ;-)    
    
    
    Eek - 30 minutes until SANTA!  Night night all! Sleep well with sweet dress when you get there!    
    
    
    @SaminaKosar @LSpurdle Good luck! May we all survive 'The Call' :-) Merry Christmas! x    
    
    
    Good morning and a Very Merry Christmas! How is everyone today?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Merry Christmas!!! We're up already as C has been asking to open presents since 5. How is A? x    
    
    
    We gave C the cover to her new phone saying it was a promise for a new one in Jan. Her face was a picture when she got the phone. :)))    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Was there enough sparkles on the shoes? ;-) I can not believe you got her Mousetrap. That game is pure evil ;-)    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Damn yes have replied. Should I stick with email/ tweets?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Tweets it is then! Stuff from us has been opened but nanny is doing 20 gift Treasure hunt later.    
    
    
    @AboutLondon I got an air popcorn maker and season 1 Columbo!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Mousetrap has been ban from my house. Many memories of hours setting up for it to be over in 2 minutes. I never had patience!    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Normally they did it with advent but C didn't have time in morning this year. They do riddles & directions (north south etc).    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Sweet! Love the steam train book!    
    
    
    @GiantDespair You too Phil! Merry Christmas! x    
    
    
    @Bashtafarian Wow!    
    
    
    @Bashtafarian Merry Christmas to you and Becky!    
    
    
    @Chiddle84 Is he outside cooling down? ;-)    
    
    
    @4fifty1 Merry Christmas!!    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 What the world needs is festive deers and pretty lights. pic.twitter.com/aH0nIvQupv    
    
    
    @iamamro @linda1966 @insidebooks @stujallen @thebooktower Merry Christmas gang! Hope today is festive & fun! xx    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Enjoy the walk - nice weather here but I'm not going anywhere until Friday.    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Now that is freaking adorable! S/he needs antlers.    
    
    
    @4fifty1 You got a pug? (Autocorrect really wants you to have a pig btw.) @truongthomas    
    
    
    @truongthomas @4fifty1 Like I said, I'm not going anywhere today. It'll be worth the wait by the sounds of it!    
    
    
    @4fifty1 @truongthomas Ha! I should have known better. Pig might have been right after all ;-) x    
    
    
    For those who weren't up at 5:30am - MERRY CHRISTMAS! 

For those who were up at 5:30am - you crashing too?    
    
    
    @wood5y And to you! Hope Santa was kind to you?    
    
    
    @mdoness I know I should be happy that she still has the spirit but more grateful she went to daddy at 4am ;-)    
    
    
    @wood5y Dear Lord no. I'm not allowed in the kitchen which is fine by me! I might be asked to help peel carrots... Maybe.    
    
    
    @dusty_jacket What an angel!    
    
    
    @PhilipArdagh @Alex_T_Smith Merry Christmas you two! xx    
    
    
    @AboutLondon What jackasses! And they can't fix until Sat?    
    
    
    @SumoJim Merry Christmas Jim! How is the family? Santa been kind?    
    
    
    ** QUEEN SPEECH KLAXON ** pic.twitter.com/3zhbyiTqxz    
    
    
    @SumoJim Oh yuck - but glad Christmas is at home! I take it you we're suppose to run in a marathon or two today?    
    
    
    Merry Christmas from the Goofy Dixons. (This was a serious photo if you can't tell.) pic.twitter.com/r77wMU9iDm    
    
    
    @SumoJim So when you get bronchitis I'll remind you of it. ;-) I have been blessed with pneumonia this year again - slows me down :)    
    
    
    @SumoJim Went to doctor Monday as thought it was happening again. Stupid lungs. But nothing compared to tough Brody!    
    
    
    @SumoJim It's been hard, let me tell you ;-)    
    
    
    @ypldn This was the non serious ... Not much difference. Merry Christmas Yannick! pic.twitter.com/uGUDMi57m9    
    
    
    @SumoJim What a fantastic way to be!    
    
    
    @aboutlondon Did you get my text?    
    
    
    @AboutLondon Sweet of them! Can you watch tv? Dr who on tonight!    
    
    
    @vickybarlo @CaroWallis @kimbiddulph @NylonsAndAll @LSpurdle And you! Merry Christmas!    
    
    
    @CaroleSouter Merry Christmas Carole!    
    
    
    @Madlena_P @akhetherington Oh my - that looks delicious! Merry Christmas! Hope you're having a fantastic day!    
    
    
    Evening all! How is everyone this lovely Christmas evening?    
    
    
    @jacquesharris The key is to not stop eating. Want some crisps? ;-) It's been a lovely Christmas -lovely gifts, delicious food & family time    
    
    
    Just tried to FaceTime mom. She told me to call back in 20 minutes.  I told her she has to wait until Dr Who is over. Daughter of the year.    
    
    
    @jacquesharris Wooo - I ail try that tomorrow as I'm not planning on stopping until jan 3rd ;-)    
    
    
    @GiantDespair We have a few!! We have the hallmark ornament range - brilliant movie.  Gets better with time :-)    
    
    
    @janetedavis We were waiting for most of the family to get over to moms before FaceTime. Up until now, it'll just be parents arguing ;-)    
    
    
    @custard1980 Amen.  But I'm still going :-)    
    
    
    @custard1980 Was Santa good to you?    
    
    
    @custard1980 CHEESE!  You just reminder me!    
    
    
    Shhh #DrWho is on    
    
    
    